(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
I gave him my full support
to this day,
just like I would to my son.
So, I felt betrayed
when he said he'd leave me...
when I was the most troubled.
Betrayal? Not at all.
That's far from the truth.
Of course not. He wouldn't do that.
No.
Then, can you talk to him...
and tell him to stay by my side?
Both you and Jin Goo said...
you'd pay back my kindness
for the rest of your lives.
I hope those weren't
just empty words.
Of course not.
Jin Goo wouldn't be here today
if it hadn't been for me.
You gave him birth,
but I kept him alive until now.
Can you promise me...
that you'll make him stay
by my side?
You owe me that much.
You must repay me
for my kindness, Ms. Sim.
What did you just say to my mother?
- Jin Goo.
- Mom, you need to leave.
- You may leave.
- Okay.
If you have anything to say,
you can talk to me.
Stop blackmailing my mom.
- "Blackmailing?"
- What do you want?
Your protection.
You need to save me,
just as how I saved you.
Eun Chong will be exposed
if the public finds out...
about the fake daughter project.
I need you...
to take responsibility
for appropriating company funds.
That's how you can save
me and Eun Chong.
Did you call my mom
to tell her that and blackmail her?
I was asking for a favor.
You thought I wouldn't listen,
so you called her instead!
I would've told you directly
if you were like before.
You've changed lately.
You're trying to leave me.
I don't care about the reason.
How can you tell my mom
that you were the one...
who kept me alive?
Have you considered
how she'd feel...
Well, I guess
how other people feel...
isn't important to you.
Mind your language.
What did I do so wrong
to you and your mother?
You didn't have to say that
to my mom.
I would've listened if you asked me.
I'll do as you wish.
But...
you must let me and my mom go.
What did Yeo Jin say?
I'm asking you. What did she say?
Are you ignoring me right now?
We're no longer in a relationship
to make small talk.
Stop talking to me.
I wasn't asking how you were doing.
- What did Yeo Jin say...
- I watched that video...
on Se Young's impressive power trip.
I'm so glad
the wedding was called off.
Otherwise, Jin Goo would've suffered
from her abuse.
I believe...
my mom and I have done
our best for you to this day.
I am grateful
that you saved me from my illness.
But my mom isn't a sinner.
I didn't treat her like a sinner.
I wasn't even making things up.
I just wanted to ask her for help.
It wasn't just you two
who gave your best.
I also gave my best
for you and your mother.
Yes, you were always nice to us.
We were always grateful.
So, have you considered
why I wanted to leave you...
and stand on my own feet?
I knew you were disappointed
after what I did to Ha Na.
But I was also heartbroken
to see you...
trying to cut our ties that easily.
I've known you for 20 years,
but I still don't know who you are.
I'll deal with the audit result
no matter what the conclusion is.
That is the last thing...
I can do for you.
And from now on,
don't tell my mom
to come and go as you like.
Let me leave you
with one last thing.
Apologize to Ha Na's family.
That's the only way
you can stop a worse tragedy.
Please do that.
Take good care of yourself.
Don't you know
how much I've done for you?
What did you
and the chairwoman talk about?
The business is under audit now,
so she told me to handle problems
if they should arise.
Did she tell you to take responsibility
for the problems?
No.
Mom, I told you last time...
that I'd leave her.
But she said
she wanted to keep you by her side.
I already declined.
She and I will each go our way
from now on.
But still, she was our savior.
Cutting her off that coldly...
I have to do that
to keep the distance.
And don't go over there
whenever she asks you to come.
All right.
Don't just say it.
I get it.
Anyway, an audit sounds scary.
You won't have to deal
with anything big, will you?
There's only one thing
I want to change...
if I could go back in time.
I want to notice my feelings
much faster.
And I'd be honest with her...
about the lies I told...
and my feelings.
I want to apologize to her
for the rest of my life,
right by her side.
It was like making a love confession
during an audit.
He heard the conversation
Chairwoman Shin had with us,
so he would've realized
who she really was.
Will he help me?
The disciplinary committee will
sue and report Jin Goo?
Yes, if he returns
the embezzled amount...
and settles the case
with the company,
he'll only be put on probation.
Please do that.
Will you cut ties with Mr. Hwang?
I want to keep him in my life,
but I don't think he wants to stay.
He once said he wanted to leave
and stand on his feet.
I'm glad
I got a good use out of him...
during the most adequate time.
She's using Hwang Jin Goo
as a scapegoat.
How long will he act
like her loyal pet dog?
I didn't expect her
to do this to Mr. Hwang, too.
I thought
she considered him like her own.
She won't have
anyone left in her life...
if she continues
to cut people off from her life.
Mr. Han, are you worried
about Chairwoman Shin right now?
No, I was just wondering
why anyone would live like that.
Right, how's the preparation going
for the founding anniversary?
They're currently making a video
to promote the chairwoman's image.
I'll touch up the video.
Did you get interviews
with her victims?
Yes, I'm almost done.
The password has four letters,
including the alphabet,
so it's harder to get through.
We're only days away
from the founding anniversary.
I'll ask Mr. Hwang.
Did the police investigation
go well?
Yes.
Did she tell you...
to take responsibility
for everything?
She can't just make me do it.
I said I'd do it.
If this is your revenge,
I deserve to be punished, too.
It's a punishment for me.
I'm not doing it for her.
You finally know
what her true nature is.
How did you feel?
I was in shock.
Would you have preferred
to stay in the dark?
No, it was belated,
but I had to know.
I also understand why...
you and Mr. Goo are out
to get revenge...
and that the chairwoman must
apologize and ask for forgiveness.
But I know she cannot be persuaded.
Have you talked to her?
I told her
to apologize to your family.
But I didn't get an answer.
How's the revenge coming along?
There's crucial evidence
on her security server,
but I can't get to it
without the password.
What's the crucial evidence?
The loan contract my dad signed...
with Hyesung Finance...
and files from the time
his business was sold off.
Do you plan to find those
and sue her?
Yes.
I need to know the password,
so do you think there will be a way?
Only the chairwoman knows that.
And I believe
she changes it periodically.
You don't even know any hints?
I'm sorry I couldn't help.
Someone like you
couldn't attack Chairwoman Shin.
She was like a mother to you,
and she saved your life.
- It'd be like betrayal.
- Yes.
That's who I am.
I can't even dream
of betraying anyone.
All right.
I won't bring it up anymore.
This is it.
I already knew,
but my aunt could be really scary.
You're right.
I didn't expect her to throw
Hwang Jin Goo under the bus.
You should be careful, too.
Jin Goo and I aren't the same.
He's a servant, but I'm her niece.
Is the preparation going well
for the founding anniversary?
Yes, we're almost done
with the PR video.
I'll do the final check.
Send it to me when you're done.
Okay.
Was that audit
the end of your revenge?
It was kind of boring.
I didn't suffer much,
and Aunt Yeo Jin
put the blame on Jin Goo.
After all,
did this only hurt Hwang Jin Goo?
Right?
What was that?
Did she just take my photo?
I'm sorry to ask,
but did you take our pictures?
No, I didn't.
May I check?
I didn't take any pictures.
Babe.
You seemed to be having fun
with Ms. Power Trip.
Just let it go.
Give it back.
What will you do
if I find our picture on here?
Tell me
before I'm done counting to three.
One. Two.
Three.
Oh, no.
My gosh. No.
Darn it. My phone.
Darn it.
Sue me if you want to.
I'll counter it.
Darn it.
This is just awful.
- Babe, look at my phone.
- Let's go.
Okay.
This is so annoying.
An English camp?
Yes, and we'll make campfires, too.
That sounds fun.
Why don't you study English hard...
and talk to me in English?
Okay. When are we going to meet?
Can we meet
when I return from the camp?
I miss you, too,
but my work isn't over yet.
How much longer do I have to wait?
It won't take long.
Will there ever come a day...
when we laugh, talk,
and live together in peace?
Eun Chong, let me call you back.
Okay.
Hello? Yes, Reverend Mother.
Right now?
I was so shocked to hear
that Eun Chong was...
Hyesung Group's grandson.
Me, too.
You won't have to worry
about him anymore.
It would've been great
if Du Na was still with us.
I came here to tell my friends
about your business.
That was why I asked them
to meet here.
I'm giving you business,
yet you still don't like me?
No, I don't like you.
How did
Jin Goo's police investigation go?
"Police investigation?"
- Instead of the chairwoman, he...
- What?
He was investigated by the police
instead of the chairwoman?
Why are you snapping?
Of course,
he must sacrifice himself for her.
Oh, my.
Sorry.
That woman is...
By any chance, was it her?
All of a sudden?
Goodness.
Reverend Mother.
Let me bring you a new dish.
That woman...
That's Se Young's mom.
Do you know her?
She seems familiar.
She's Eun Chong's little grandma.
"Little grandma?"
So, she's Du Na's aunt?
Yes.
Ms. Sim is here.
Why is she here?
Let her in.
How may I help you?
I heard you had
Jin Goo investigated by the police.
How can you frame him
for something you did...
and send him to the police?
- Have a seat.
- No.
Jin Goo can do that much for me.
Everything is ready to make sure
he isn't detained,
so don't worry.
It's not a matter
of getting locked up in prison.
You claim to have considered him
as your own and adored him.
But no parent would send
their son to the police...
by framing him for their parent's crime.
Was that why you asked me
to convince Jin Goo to stay?
These things often happen
when you work in the real world.
He knew everything
and volunteered to do it.
I hope there's no misunderstanding.
He's very dear to me, too.
Why do you wish
to keep him in your life?
To take advantage of him whenever
something like this happens?
Have you
treated him like this all along?
- Ms. Sim.
Please calm down and have a seat.
I may not be well-off,
and Jin Goo may owe his life to you,
but this is just wrong.
I was already heartbroken
that he was born weak...
because of us, his parents.
But how can you do this every time
like he's your hostage?
How can you treat him
like a servant?
"Like a servant?"
- That's strong language.
- Yes, I'll use strong language.
I treated you
like you were my savior,
but I was still happy.
I was happy and grateful...
while I worked here as your maid.
I was glad
I could do something for you.
But I will not allow you to treat
Jin Goo like he's insignificant.
It's a misunderstanding.
I wouldn't have kept him in my life
if I thought he was insignificant.
Jin Goo said he'd leave you,
and I told him to do it.
Thank you for everything.
When did you get here?
I didn't see you at the restaurant.
Take care.
Why was she here?
- Did you tell her?
- Tell her what?
Did she come here to get mad
about Jin Goo's investigation?
Yes.
Why would she run here
over something like that?
You're back.
How did the police investigation go?
How did you know?
I am greatly hurt
and disappointed by the chairwoman.
How can she make you do this?
I wanted to help her one last time.
It'll go well, so don't worry.
What do you mean, it'll go well?
Will you be happy
as long as you avoid the prison?
Why are you so naive?
What's with you?
Mom.
I just don't understand.
The one who committed the crime
should be punished.
Why is she framing you?
How can she do that as an elder?
That's how things work in companies.
That's why you want to leave her.
You couldn't
put up with her anymore.
I'm the real sinner.
I put you on her leash
with your life as the collateral.
Mom, you're
taking this too far again.
I'm fine. Nothing will happen.
I'm sorry.
Goodness, who turned my mom
into a crybaby?
You owe me that much.
You must repay me
for my kindness, Ms. Sim.
I need your protection.
You need to save me,
just as how I saved you.
Where's the chairwoman
I once admired and trusted?
Was this who you really were?
Then, just as Mr. Yoon said,
I should change for your sake.
I know everything now.
I can't turn
a blind eye to it forever.
- I'll wear this.
- Yes, ma'am.
Was that the end
of the Goo siblings' revenge?
- Things are quiet, right?
- Yes, ma'am.
(Incoming Call)
It must be him.
Was this the first time...
- he reached out after that day?
- Yes.
The person you have reached...
Yeo Jin, it's not too late
to change your mind.
Please reconcile
with the Goo siblings. I beg you.
You're asking me
to apologize and reconcile?
How ridiculous.
If he had to beg me on the phone,
it meant they couldn't find
crucial evidence.
- Hwang Jin Goo hasn't called yet?
- No.
We couldn't find the password,
and the hacking attempts
were useless.
We still have time until tomorrow.
Let's do this until the end.
- Yes.
- Okay.
After Chairwoman Shin's speech,
they'll play a commemorative video.
- Danny, check the video once again.
- Okay.
Mr. Han and I will
go through the files again.
Yes, Mr. Hwang.
Really?
What are Ji Seok and Ha Na up to?
They're always together.
How would I know if you don't?
But still, I'm not worried.
They aren't troublemakers like us.
Hey, I got involved because of you.
I've only seen loan sharks on TV.
I never expected to see them
with my own eyes.
Let's think of it as a good lesson.
But thanks to Ji Seok and Ha Na,
I got to keep the business...
- and my legs.
- You're right.
Let's call them up
and get together sometime.
That sounds great.
But it's a shame
Eun Chong can't join us.
Mr. Goo, another order
of cheese tteokbokki for table two.
Yes, okay.
It feels heavy to think
I must betray the chairwoman.
But I believe the chairwoman...
must be punished and apologize...
to break this vicious cycle
and turn everything back.
I'll help with your revenge.
Thank you for making
such a tough decision.
Let's just go for it.
You said you needed a password.
- Did you bring your laptop?
- Yes.
The server gets locked
after ten wrong attempts.
We tried 6 times,
so we have 4 more chances.
I know the passwords
she used in the past.
But it's most likely
she has changed it.
But let me try it, just in case.
I hope one of them is correct.
We have two more chances left.
Is there something she always does
when she makes passwords?
She often uses
something meaningful to her...
or makes abbreviations.
Something meaningful?
The most significant thing
in her life now must be Eun Chong.
Right?
Wait, could it be that?
What?
(Hyesung Group's
30th Founding Anniversary)
- Hello.
- Congratulations, ma'am.
- Thank you.
Please excuse us.
- Congratulations.
Thank you.
Let's go inside, Yeo Jin.
We should go inside, too.
Okay.
(Hyesung Group's
30th Founding Anniversary)
You remembered who this woman was?
Yes.
- I heard she was Du Na's aunt.
- Yes.
When I saw her and heard her voice,
my old memories came back.
- Have you seen this woman?
- Yes.
I ran into her by chance
when I was eating out with Ha Na.
It was her.
She visited the children's home
around when Du Na was adopted...
and emigrated to America.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
She mentioned Du Na
and seemed interested in adoption,
so I didn't think
she was someone who knew her.
Then, this woman knew...
Yu Jin was adopted
and emigrated to America?
Yes.
Since our foundation 30 years ago,
every step toward
what Hyesung is today...
has been made possible
thanks to the dedication...
and tireless efforts of all members.
I wish to extend my gratitude
to every member of the group...
for the contributions you made
to our growth.
Hyesung Group is
about to make another leap forward.
Of course, we'll face
many challenges and projects,
but as long as we stand together
as the Hyesung family,
nothing is impossible.
(Hyesung Group's
30th Founding Anniversary)
Next, we'll watch a video
of Hyesung Group's history,
covering the footsteps we have made
as a social enterprise.
Let's take a look.
(Hyesung Group's
30th Founding Anniversary)
(Hyesung Group's 30th Anniversary)
The beginning of Hyesung Group
goes back to the year 1995.
In the heart of busy Seoul in 1995,
Chairwoman Shin Yeo Jin's
big dream began to dawn.
Hyesung Finance, the predecessor
of what is now Hyesung Group,
did not have a promising start.
However, Chairwoman Shin Yeo Jin's
diligence and perseverance...
successfully pushed
Hyesung Finance into success.
(Profile: Shin Yeo Jin,
chairwoman of Hyesung Group)
Chairwoman Shin Yeo Jin's
corporate raiding...
ruined my business instantly,
the one I worked all my life...
to cultivate.
I fell into despair,
but Chairwoman Shin
did not show any remorse.
She still continues with
her corporate raiding endeavors.
- Shin, the corporate raider,
- What's going on?
- must step down on her own accord.
- Who did this?
- She ruined many companies...
- Goodness.
and made the victims shed
tears of blood.
I cannot stand to see her live
a comfortable life anymore.
- Turn it off right now!
- Youngshin Fashion is a company...
- ruined by her raid 13 years ago.
- Turn it off!
- Hyesung Finance...
- Hurry up and turn it off.
wanted to cause
Youngshin Fashion's bankruptcy.
- Turn it off now!
- It increased the interest rate...
and pressured CEO Goo Young Min
to recover the loan he took out.
After the bankruptcy,
Hyesung took over...
Youngshin Fashion
at an unimaginably low price...
and then disposed
of its assets illegally.
- She's the queen of Korea now.
- Right?
She's the most powerful.
It's not just money.
What's going on?
(Hyesung Group's
30th Founding Anniversary)
Hello.
My name is Goo Ji Seok,
Hyesung Group's head director.
Just as this video said,
Chairwoman Shin Yeo Jin
expanded Hyesung's business...
through corporate raiding attempts.
We found out
through a recent external audit...
that her illegal activities
included...
insider trading, tax evasion,
and accounting manipulation.
I have the evidence here.
I'd like to put together
what she did 13 years ago...
to Youngshin Fashion
and other victims of that time...
and the recent events...
to report Chairwoman Shin Yeo Jin
to the authorities.
This is ridiculous.
Drag him out right now.
You should get the criminal first.
(Hyesung Group's
30th Founding Anniversary)
Chairwoman Shin Yeo Jin?
Chairwoman Shin Yeo Jin,
as of this hour,
you are under emergency arrest
for violating the Capital Markets Act.
You have the right
to consult an attorney...
and choose to remain silent.
Let go of me.
How dare you do this
without evidence?
You can't lay a finger on me...
even if you bring
hundreds of those reports.
Bring me the decisive evidence.
Here's the decisive evidence.
(Request of Compulsory Auction
of Real Estate Property)
How did you get this?
Admit to everything,
just as you promised.
Ms. Shin Yeo Jin,
the corporate raider.
(Cinderella Game)
You and Se Young are
the only ones left in my life.
It's the same for us, Yeo Jin.
It's something important
about your daughter.
You need to meet Mr. Yoon soon.
Eun Chong may fall into danger.
I have a bad feeling about this.
We cannot let them meet.
What kind of awful situation
is this?
She wasn't just repaying
kindness with evil.
She knew everything,
yet she kept it from me?
There's a possibility...
Myung Ji was involved
in Yu Jin's hit-and-run accident.
How much compensation do you expect?
A hundred million dollars
sounds reasonable.