(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children and animals were
filmed under production guidelines.)
(Episode 14)
Wait!
Please take another elevator.
It's all right.
- Get in.
- Right. Thank you.
Wait, we met
at the restaurant, right?
Right.
Do you work for Hyesung Tour?
Yes.
Can you recommend
a place to travel to?
Who are you traveling with?
Alone.
Where could a lonely
and melancholic person go?
If you felt lonely and melancholic,
wouldn't it be better
to spend time...
with your family and friends
instead of traveling?
Should you say that
as an employee of a travel agency?
I didn't mean you shouldn't travel.
The meal may be the same,
but something that tastes
just all right alone...
somehow tastes oddly delicious
when you share it...
with your family or friends.
You don't feel so empty anymore.
So, I hope you visit...
a nice place with people you like.
I'm back.
- Here it is.
- Thanks.
- Sure. Here it is.
- Thank you.
- Ms. Goo.
- Yes?
- How do you feel?
- Sorry?
We all went through this trouble
because of Head Director Goo.
Your brother just ruined
his older sister's workplace.
How does it feel? I'm just curious.
"Older sister?"
What did Mr. Goo say?
You wouldn't say anything
even if he said something.
Well, you wouldn't betray
your younger brother...
for a workplace you were at
for just a few days.
I couldn't tell you that,
yes, my younger brother
will destroy Hyesung Tour.
I'm employed by Hyesung Tour,
so I will work for Hyesung Tour.
I hope you don't hold
a prejudiced opinion...
just because Director Goo
and I are siblings.
So, work is strictly work?
Yes, and I'll also assume
the same attitude.
What can I do next?
It had been almost a week
since I started.
I told you to wait.
Yes.
Where are you going?
- You told me to wait.
- I did.
I told you to wait.
I didn't dismiss you.
Right.
(Team Leader Yoon Se Young)
Why do you keep wriggling around?
I'm trying to work,
and you're getting on my nerves.
Fine, harass me all you want.
You still can't break me.
No rain, no flowers.
How dare you exhale?
You're disgusting.
Am I not even allowed to breathe?
You just defiled...
the air I breathe with your breath.
Is this a rebellion?
Come to think of it,
you're just like your brother.
You both love rebellions, don't you?
Are you glaring at me?
What's going on, Ms. Yoon?
Chairwoman Shin,
what brings you here without a call?
You're here, Chairwoman Shin.
- Please come inside.
- Sure.
Wait, was she the chairwoman
of Hyesung Group?
She is.
Why did I say something like that
to the chairwoman?
She may think I don't qualify
as a guide and fire me.
Is she here because of
the hotel's contract cancellation?
- Why did Director Goo do that?
- Tell me about it.
I never imagined...
he could do something so cruel
with such kind looks.
Ms. Goo, is Director Goo Ji Seok
really your younger brother?
- Is he really your brother?
- Yes.
- No way.
Anyway, why did he do that
to his older sister's workplace?
I heard Hwang Jin Goo
managed to find the rooms he needed.
He must have a trustworthy reputation
in the field.
I guess so.
What about Mr. Jung Man Soo?
Settle the case with his attorney.
Chairwoman Shin's side
became suspicious...
that someone was behind him
after he hired an attorney.
- If you try to settle the case...
- They'll grow even more suspicious.
- Are you sure about this?
- It'll be fine.
I saw the chairwoman
meeting someone discreetly...
out of the office.
She must've been
digging your back...
or doing something
about her lost daughter.
Let her find the girl...
if she wants to be the cause
that makes her daughter more miserable.
You think Hanguk Hotel's
new investor is behind this?
They changed
all their subcontractors, too.
Is that so?
I heard the chairman's son
went to America...
before they broke the ground
because of financial difficulty.
And their subcontractors did protest
when they weren't paid.
One of the clauses
on our contract says,
"Duty to notify when there is
a change of subcontractors."
We can use this to raise a problem.
Do we have to consider...
Hyesung Hotel's cancellation
only as a coincidence?
I am suspicious
of Director Goo Ji Seok.
We can make our judgment
after we hear from him.
Ms. Goo, you should meet her.
Chairwoman Shin Yeo Jin
of our group.
Hello, Ms. Chairwoman.
I apologize for not recognizing you.
I'll take note of your words.
Goodness, Ms. Chairwoman.
That was...
You should get back to work.
Yes, ma'am.
What did she say to you?
Where do you think is
a good place...
for a lonely and melancholic person
to travel to, Ms. Yoon?
Everyone has different preferences,
so it'll depend on the person
and their situation.
Mr. Hwang?
A place
where they can take a rest...
while sharing good food with family,
friends, or someone they love.
Who they're with is more important
than a particular location.
A destination for those
who are lonely and melancholic.
That's not a bad theme to work with.
It's not so bad.
Yes, it was her, right?
She presented the mother-daughter therapy
at the interview, right?
I thought she was eliminated
for taking up an illegal gig.
You remembered her.
I was going to tell you
when I reported on the Dubai contract.
We sealed the deal under the premise
Ms. Goo will take charge.
That was why I gave her a job.
How did they know who she was?
Ha Na, if you have any questions...
or need help, let me know anytime.
What? Okay.
Ha Na, we were colleagues
who started together.
Love for your colleagues is
love for your country...
and your workplace.
You both sound so awkward.
Ha Na, you already know, right?
I was the only one
who treated you...
without prejudice.
Sure.
- Goodbye.
The chairwoman's beauty
must be timeproof.
She has such clear skin
even though she's over 60.
She may look great on the outside,
but her inside must be miserable.
She has a sad story
of losing her only daughter...
a long time ago.
She lost her daughter?
Settle the case?
That homeless man now has
an attorney and settlement money?
After Jung Man Soo's
family business went down,
his family had to spread out.
But recently,
they were finally reunited.
He made it too easy to notice
someone was behind him. It's odd.
I already said
you wouldn't settle the case.
He that would eat the fruit
must climb the tree.
Let's keep an eye on him
and see how he responds.
Summon Head Director Goo.
I'm sorry. The chairwoman called,
so I needed to go immediately.
It must be about the contract cancellation
with Hyesung Tour.
She probably wanted to see you
for the same reason.
You should meet her first.
I'll wait.
I want to sell our hotel rooms
at a better price.
Even if Hyesung Tour
gives us lots of business,
it won't mean a lot
if the unit price is too low.
Insisting on holding a partnership
just because of our affiliation...
is more like friendship
than business.
I plan to attract VIP guests
who pay a higher price per room.
I want to connect directly
with international businesses...
and create synergy
for our advancement overseas.
That's all great,
but if you disregard tradition...
and push forward
aggressively all alone...
I thought...
you'd like it done aggressively
because it was your tactic.
There was a line
you shouldn't cross in business.
The relationship must be
founded on basic trust.
Then, you find the proper timing
to implement aggressive strategies.
Hyesung Tour trusted us.
That wasn't how
you should cancel the contract.
I was disappointed in you.
Then, was everything
you have done to this day...
always within the line?
Recant the cancellation.
From now on, you will consult me
before making any decisions.
I make the calls and orders
as the chief officer of the hotel.
- Remember that.
- Yes, ma'am.
The intruder
of your appointment ceremony...
offered a settlement
through his attorney.
How much should I demand?
Are you willing to settle?
- No.
- Then, why...
I can guess how powerful
the hand behind him is...
by offering the amount
for the settlement.
You won't settle anyway,
so you should go big.
What if he accepts it?
Is there someone you believe is...
behind everything?
I don't know.
You can't remember...
because there are so many of them...
and you find them all insignificant.
You don't have to mind it.
I wasn't asking for your opinion.
Yes, ma'am.
The police will handle the case
if she refuses to settle.
Will Mr. Jung be all right?
He'll hang in there.
Do you believe
there is no chance of settling?
I'll make her do it.
And to do that,
we need a strong variable.
Such as?
Chairwoman Shin's daughter...
suddenly showing up,
although it's impossible.
I'll tell Zero to report back
if anything extraordinary happens.
Has President Hwang called?
No, sir.
He probably left after waiting.
He'll be there.
It's now lunch.
Do you want to bet?
It's my win.
Yes, sir.
You were still here.
I said I'd wait.
My talk with the chairwoman
took a while.
I thought you'd leave
by the time it was lunch.
You should go eat.
It's not a big deal to skip a meal.
Let's go inside.
Come in.
I apologize for the shock yesterday.
Thankfully, I heard
you managed to find enough rooms.
Are you really sorry?
I am.
But I don't regret it.
Would the situation have changed
if I gave you a forewarning?
I thought you had basic manners
for the subsidiary...
who partnered with you in business,
but I must've overestimated you.
I didn't have basic manners.
I'm sorry.
I admit that
my process is rather rough.
Let's cut to the chase.
If another place offered
a better price than Hyesung Tour,
would it be a win-win situation for us
to hold fast to Hyesung Tour...
just because it was our subsidiary?
The deal is only sweet
for Hyesung Tour.
What's sweet is honey.
We've had our share
of tough moment with Hyesung Hotel,
although there's no use
in sharing this now.
We're here to do business,
so you should take the better offer.
It's a shame to break a long partnership
with Hyesung Hotel,
but we'll use it
as a chance to change.
The chairwoman asked me
to recant the cancellation.
But if that's what you want,
I won't need to do that.
I'll report back to her.
I want to ask you something.
Were you behind
Hanguk Hotel's decision?
You didn't try to change my mind,
so I thought you were the cool type.
But you have an impatient side.
You'll find out in time.
I don't think I'll need more time.
I felt relieved to know
you seemed to be reasonable.
It's always reasonable
to follow the trend.
And I'm the current trend.
But trends don't stay the same.
We'll see.
Hanguk Hotel and Hyesung Hotel...
What's next?
The Dubai deal?
You love jumping to a conclusion.
What if that conclusion was right?
Do you want to bet?
I'll bet my presidency
of Hyesung Tour.
I'm the head director.
I'll bet Hyesung Tour, too,
if that's what you want.
I'm in.
We're canceling the contract?
Yes, cancel all reservations
with Hyesung Hotel at this time.
- But we're affiliated.
- This is bad.
Don't be alarmed.
We'll find a way around this.
- Come in, Ms. Yoon.
- Yes.
I thought he went
to come to an agreement.
Mr. Hwang isn't the type
who'll call the contract off.
It looked like Mr. Goo was
set on ending this.
Do you know anything, Ha Na?
- Have you heard anything?
- No.
Does he really plan
to destroy Hyesung Tour?
This is bad.
We'll find another hotel.
Great decision.
He wanted to call it off,
and we weren't that desperate.
Did he make you stand out there
just to say that?
He has so many ways
of messing with you.
He must've been behind
Hanguk Hotel, too.
If my guess is correct,
he's trying to destroy the travel agency.
Why would he destroy
the travel agency?
His excuse will be that
he wants to focus on the hotel business.
Who knows what else he's after?
We can't just sit around, then.
Tell the chairwoman right away.
Don't get worked up.
They gave us a blow first,
so we'd hit them once, too.
I always liked something more dramatic
than playing it safe.
I've played too safely until now.
And that security wasn't free.
Everyone knew you worked hard
after taking up the travel agency.
Back then,
I had such a fun time working.
I should warm up slowly.
Is this situation fun for you?
I began to feel motivated
whenever Mr. Goo irritated me.
- Am I a pervert?
- You're impossible.
Should I meet this punk?
I can't barge into his office, so...
Right.
His older sister was
working for Se Young.
Should I take advantage of her?
Take a look at this.
I made this blanket.
"Blanket?"
It's for Jin Goo and Se Young.
I made it with light cotton,
so it'd feel unbelievably warm,
and it'd help them sleep better.
Se Young is rather sensitive, right?
It's because she doesn't get
enough good sleep.
She's not sensitive.
Bang Ul,
you don't have to pull it out.
Cotton can't be too light anyway.
Se Young can't sleep under anything else
except goose down.
She'd feel too stifled.
No one uses
cotton blankets these days.
It needs to carry some weight
to help you sleep better.
No, thanks. You can use it.
I guess I will.
Hey, the chairwoman found them...
a newlywed home,
so I wanted to fill it
with some furniture.
Everything was built in,
so you wouldn't need to.
The just need a bed,
a sofa, and a sound system.
All right.
Write down whatever they need.
What about the wallpaper
and the flooring...
It's an apartment complex,
so they don't need that.
Se Young just wants to hang
a few paintings on the wall.
Don't be like that.
Jin Goo was a talented guy...
with a perfectly good parent.
They'll need dishes
and utensils, though.
How can your tacky taste
be enough for Se Young...
Well, the chairwoman said
she'd get everything for them.
Would you like a cup of tea?
Here.
Here. Have some, Bang Ul.
It tastes bitter.
Clean it well.
If it's not clean,
I won't give you 50 cents.
I am cleaning it.
All done.
I just need to pour some sawdust.
Let me put the treadwheel up first.
Eun Chong, you're really good.
It's not even a big deal.
Hey, what's going on, kids?
Hello? Yes, ma'am.
Did something happen to Eun Chong?
I'm sorry. All right.
Mr. Yoon,
is Ms. Yoon out of the office?
I don't know. Why?
I was wondering
if I could take a leave.
I'll call her.
She won't pick up?
If you're in a hurry, you can go.
I'll tell her.
Thank you.
- What are you cooking?
- What do you mean?
Please walk on by.
I don't care
if you block me off like this,
but don't mess
with Jin Goo's future.
If you want your revenge,
do it personally.
Don't play dirty
and cause a commotion at work.
"Revenge?"
I already said
I had zero feelings about you.
I'm only doing my job.
Do you want me to get my revenge?
Is that a sort of regret?
If not, then never mind.
Keep your emotions under control.
Someone might catch you.
Hey, Hwang Jin Goo was
an interesting man.
I get what you see in him.
(Teacher's Room)
(1. I will walk your dog
for 50 cents an hour.)
It had been a few days
since Eun Chong...
gave this out to his friends.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
I should've paid
more attention to him.
He's a thoughtful kid.
He cares a lot about you, too.
I felt moved
after seeing this flyer.
(1. I will walk your dog
for 50 cents an hour.)
Who gave you 50 cents?
Ji Soo. I cleaned her shoes.
I'm not mad.
You can lift your head up.
You can be honest with me.
I have a great job now,
so I can buy the toys you want.
That wasn't the reason.
Then, why did you do that?
Hello, General Manager.
When does your hotel
finish remodeling?
Why don't you sign with us
when that's done?
(President Hwang Jin Goo)
We're having tourists from Dubai
starting next month,
two hundred teams a year.
I'm certain.
You already heard
about Hyesung Hotel?
Not all subsidiaries
turned out to be on the same side.
That's why
you're getting this chance.
Let's talk in person soon.
Bye.
I'll sign with every hotel
except for Hyesung Hotel.
Hey, Lee Eun Chong! Where are you?
What brings you here?
Look at this.
He's such an embarrassment
to this neighborhood.
I thought I took everything down.
- Where did you find it?
- You knew about this?
Keep it down.
I just found out today.
How can I stay quiet?
It's like making a seven-year-old
go out and beg for money.
Don't you know I dread
looking pathetic the most?
I saw a few women
reading this and laughing at it.
What's going on?
Why are you here?
What? What's this?
Lee Eun Chong!
Where are you? Get over here!
Leave him alone.
I asked him a few times,
but he wouldn't tell me.
That little kid is
already obsessed with money?
My gosh, he's charging
50 cents for everything.
This was why he asked...
how many 50 cents he needed
to make 5 dollars.
What's this about five dollars?
No idea.
Is that how much a new toy costs?
- It wasn't because he wanted a toy.
- Then what?
Why would this 7-year-old need
5 dollars?
- I doubt he meant 50,000 dollars.
- Wait, 50,000 dollars?
How much
did you extort from Seok Ki?
There's more than
the 50,000-dollar bank loan, right?
Why won't he come out?
Kongkong, you understand, right?
I just wanted to help Auntie Ha Na.
Eun Chong.
You must...
answer me honestly.
Were you trying to make...
the five dollars to pay...
Mr. Seok Ki back?
- Auntie...
- Don't cry.
Here. You can have the drumstick.
You can eat it.
Eat it while the offer stands.
You worked hard to make money.
I only made 50 cents.
Eun Chong, I paid everything back.
- Really?
- Yes.
Mr. Seok Ki's mom...
won't come here again.
No, she can't.
Where did you get the money?
Do you remember
Uncle Ji Seok giving me money?
- You saw it, right?
- Yes.
I paid everything back
with that money.
Uncle Ji Seok gave me
a lot of money.
I see.
You should've shared this with us.
A little kid like you
shouldn't worry about making money.
Tell me about it.
But don't you think
50 cents is way too cheap?
You were always hogging the phone,
so I thought you had a girlfriend.
Eun Chong, what did I say?
Adults were supposed
to worry about money.
You don't have to worry about that.
If something like this
happens again,
I will get mad.
- I'll be very scary.
- Okay.
I just need to know
that you care that much about me.
Will you do this again or not?
I won't.
It's a promise.
I promise.
If you felt lonely and melancholic,
wouldn't it be better
to spend time...
with your family and friends
instead of traveling?
The meal may be the same,
but something that tastes
just all right alone...
somehow tastes oddly delicious
when you share it...
with your family or friends.
You don't feel so empty anymore.
Did you make this?
What do you think?
It looked crudely made.
No way. Take a good look.
It still looks like it to me.
I worked so hard to make this,
imagining you drinking tea with it.
It does look rough and simple,
kind of homey.
Isn't that so?
Anyway, what's this teacup?
It's for our baby.
You already made one
for our nonexisting baby?
What do you mean, already?
We can make a baby now.
Let's drink tea later.
Why don't we make the baby first?
My gosh. Stop it.
Let's have tea.
Let's be together for a long time,
enjoying tea with one another.
What are you up to, Yeo Jin?
You still had these?
I figured you threw out
everything he made...
and thought it was unfortunate.
But you left these behind.
It was wonderful to see
the two of you...
sharing tea together in love.
She must still have feelings
for her husband.
I couldn't throw it away
because of the baby teacup.
It must've reminded you of Yu Jin.
I keep seeing her in my dreams,
and it's always the same.
My goodness.
What was the dream about?
(1. I will walk your dog
for 50 cents an hour.)
I'm sorry.
I made your son
do something like this.
But you know what, Du Na?
I was a little happy
because of Eun Chong.
May I feel that way?
Ms. Goo.
I am your direct superior.
How dare you leave early
without my permission?
I'm sorry, Ms. Yoon.
You weren't in the office,
so I called you,
- but you didn't pick...
- You're so unruly.
Why did you go
to your nephew's kindergarten?
Does he not have a mom or dad?
What's going on?
You need to report to me directly...
when you want to leave early
or take the day off.
Yes.
Did something happen to your nephew?
It wasn't a big deal.
It must've been serious
if you had to leave early.
This doesn't concern you, Mr. Hwang.
Well, okay. I'm glad.
Go easy on her, Ms. Yoon.
- Ms. Goo!
- Yes?
I'm suddenly getting chills.
Go to my place and pick up a coat.
It's the violet-colored one
in my closet.
Okay.
The real estate market is dead,
so I'm out of money, too.
You need to stop this.
You can't say that to me.
I can expose everything.
The only daughter of Hyesung Group,
Yoon Yu Jin...
You need to wait.
Yeo Jin said
she kept dreaming of Yu Jin,
and this punk
began to call me more often.
What the heck is going on?
This is so irritating.
Who is it?
Yes, hello.
I work with Ms. Yoon Se Young,
and I'm here to run her errand.
Hello.
She told me to bring her coat.
Which one?
She said she had
a violet-colored coat in the closet.
- Go to the second floor.
- Yes, ma'am.
What are you doing over there?
I'm sorry.
The door was opened,
so I thought this was the room.
Good grief.
Wait here.
Okay.
I haven't seen you before.
What's your name?
My name is Goo Ha Na.
I see. She's a Goo.
She's Goo Ji Seok's older sister?
Did the chairwoman's family
include a little girl?
She has a sad story
of losing her only daughter...
a long time ago.
Is that the room
for the chairwoman's lost daughter?
(Cinderella Game)
Do you know Richard Han?
He's suspecting us
as Hanguk Hotel's investors.
An envelope with money went missing?
What's wrong?
Only you saw me
putting this envelope into my drawer.
Wait, why was this in my bag?
We can't let her get kicked out
by taking false blame as a thief.
Can you think of a way?
You seem like a real heiress
after acting like one for a while.
So, people can get better
at talking nonsense.
Has the real heiress died?
Someone who went missing
seemed to be my Yu Jin?