It's me, Yoon Yu Jin.
- What now? - I'm Yoon Yu Jin.
Yes, you are Yoon Yu Jin.
Gosh, I forgot for a moment.
No, I shouldn't forget that.
I'm sorry for not realizing that.
Why are you suddenly doing this?
Can you handle the consequences?
What do I have to handle?
Are you saying that Aunt Yeo Jin may kick my mom and me out?
It may be something else.
Let's see who'll end up leaving.
- What? - I'm warning you.
That bracelet. Why did you think I threw it out?
I know what you're up to.
I knew you'd try to get him involved in your life by using that bracelet,
calling this old friendship, fate, or whatever nonsense you make up.
I don't care if you're Yoon Yu Jin. You can't do that.
Let me give you a warning, too.
Be careful with your lies.
- What lies? - Your lies to Mr. Hwang.
You talked this nonsense about how I was lying last time.
This again?
- So, no? - What's that lie?
Tell me.
You can't even say it.
You're seeing another man.
Did you think I wouldn't know?
And he works at our company, doesn't he?
All you ever say is nonsense.
Who's this guy at our workplace, then?
Tell me. Who is it?
You said you knew. Who is this at our company?
I'm not going to tell you now.
I'm going to consider whether I'll share it or not...
depending on what you do.
You're slandering me right now with complete nonsense.
That's considered defamation by using false information.
It may be defamation due to factual information.
Did you think I'd flinch if you threw random things at me?
How dare you make up this soap opera...
with zero evidence just by eavesdropping on my call?
Were you trying to use whatever you could to get me?
You're rather talkative. You must be scared.
I'm not scared at all.
Go ahead and try to track me down.
If you find anything, make sure you let me know.
How did she notice?
It didn't seem like she knew it was Ji Seok.
She acted tough because she felt guilty.
I'll make sure I find who the guy is.
Ha Na found out I was seeing someone else.
- What did she say? - She asked me to my face...
and said it must be someone at work.
Does she know this is you?
- No. - Are you sure?
If she thought it was me, she would've asked me first.
It didn't seem like she knew anything.
Then, how did she know?
That must be it.
She overheard me when we were on the phone,
just before you dropped the article on disposal...
and when they worked on the shredded file.
You already gave away that it was someone at work.
If Ha Na knows,
Hwang Jin Goo will also find out very soon.
We better be careful.
Let's go inside.
You must be tired after your first day of business.
It still feels weird when everyone treats me as the owner.
Other than that, it felt hectic, but I had fun.
It's the most important to have fun.
How was the sales?
That's a secret.
You are already such a business owner.
Right. I want to say goodbye to the chairwoman one of these days.
- I had to leave without doing that. - Okay, then.
There's no problem between you and Se Young because of me, right?
It seemed like you two were doing fine.
We are.
To me, that sounds like you don't love me.
Love.
Mr. Hwang, what do you see in Se Young to marry her?
I've known her for a long time since when we were children.
Everything happened naturally and led to our marriage.
But you must love her if you want to marry her.
Is that love?
Why did you meet Ji Seok?
And if you did, you shouldn't have let Jin Goo see you.
I made a good excuse. Did he say something?
He doesn't believe you.
It seems like he's suspicious of Ji Seok and me.
Exactly! Stop seeing that punk.
If you keep doing this, you'll get caught.
- Cut him out of your life. - I'll be careful.
- What about playing both sides? - I'll start that now.
- Hey, are you getting a massage? - Yes.
I was tired, but my fatigue melted away...
with the massaging and tapping.
Yeo Jin, I...
Gosh.
I wasn't so sure...
if I should tell you this.
What is it?
I went to the police station with Se Young this morning, right?
The police said there was a previous report...
on suspicion of child abuse regarding Eun Chong.
What kind of abuse?
The kid was told to pick up empty bottles.
"Empty bottles?"
And he was told to beg for money, too.
"Beg for money?"
Did the police tell you that?
No, that was...
Well...
It was Yu Jin's ex-boyfriend's mom.
Her ex-boyfriend's mom?
How do you know her?
She was lurking in front of our place, so I asked who she was.
She said she was Yu Jin's ex-boyfriend's mother.
She was in front of our house?
How did she know Yu Jin was my daughter?
She must've told her.
She said she wouldn't tell anyone. You don't have to worry.
So? How did he end up begging for money?
Yu Jin took out a housing lease...
of 50,000 dollars under her ex's name.
Eun Chong went out...
and posted flyers to find part-time jobs to pay that back.
Goodness.
You're Yu Jin's son?
A seven-year-old successor?
Gosh, look at that. Isn't that a huge bubble?
Yes, that's huge.
Tap.
I popped the bubble.
It popped.
I'm not very good at this.
Can you show me how to do it?
Mix it like this.
Then, stretch it out.
It stretches out so easily.
Se Young looked back on herself quite a lot after nudging his head.
Eun Chong seems very creative, and he has good focus, too.
I must've taken after my mommy.
I heard my mommy was good at arts and crafts.
I see, Eun Chong. You must've taken after your mommy.
What do you want to be when you grow up?
I'm a human. Do I have to be something else?
What? Goodness.
I'm home.
- Auntie Ha Na! - Hey.
Hey, there. Were you having fun?
I was playing with slime.
- Welcome back, Yu Jin. - Hey.
- Have you had dinner? - I'll whip up something.
- Eun Chong, let me get changed. - Okay.
Eun Chong, have you ever put up flyers to get part-time jobs?
How did you know?
Why did you do that?
I wanted to help Auntie Ha Na,
but I only made 50 cents.
Yes?
Mom, would you like a cup of tea?
No, I'm fine.
How's work?
Mom, I want to include a cruise trip for the mother-daughter tour.
There's a place called Seongbuk Port in Incheon.
I lived there when I was ten.
That place is so famous for the beautiful sunset...
Stop.
I don't want to discuss seasides, ports, or cruise trips.
I don't like how it reminds me of the time when I lost you.
I'm sorry.
I need to get some rest.
Okay.
Eun Chong, let's go. Grandma needs to rest.
You can let him play.
Okay.
Get some rest, then.
How did this little kid end up begging for money?
Why couldn't both Mom and Se Young...
be freed from that memory even after I returned?
Yu Jin, will you take a seat for a moment?
Okay.
Hey, about that photo you lost.
Did you ask why it was in your mom's room?
She didn't know, either.
Really?
It wasn't just your photo.
Who would leave a photo you took with total strangers in her room?
Did she take it there and forget about it?
Wasn't it you, Aunt Myung Ji?
Did she want to see Eun Chong's baby photo?
Why would she want to see Eun Chong's baby photo?
She thinks of him like he's her own grandson.
I also didn't think she should get mad at you...
when he scalded himself that time.
She yelled at her daughter over a stranger's son.
I'm grateful that she adores him so much.
"Grateful?"
Don't you feel slighted?
Maybe a little,
but I'm more grateful.
So, please don't tell me anything negative about her.
Right. Of course, I won't.
- Please excuse me. - Okay.
Goodness. You have no idea she's taking advantage of you.
What a foolish girl. Gosh.
What's wrong? Is it hard to play both sides?
She's kind of weird.
What did she say?
It'll seem odd to anyone...
because she adores Eun Chong more than her daughter.
Eun Chong is just that lucky.
And Mom's just that loving.
But it'd be nice...
if she treated me with more warmth and affection.
Why is she laughing so hard all day?
She also laughed when she talked about that person who got scammed.
You'll lose that laughter right away once I find that man and show him.
He's Chairwoman Shin's grandson?
So, she made your sister into a fake daughter...
- to protect her grandson? - Yes.
How can she do that?
You found out everything now. What's your plan?
When she gets exposed as a fake daughter,
people will naturally find out that the boy is her grandson.
The problem is this.
I don't know how to tell Ha Na...
that boy is her enemy's blood.
It would feel like...
the world was crashing down on her.
And the boy would feel the same way.
Your sister and that boy didn't do anything wrong.
Do you think she'll accept him even after she finds out?
For now, there is a 50-50 chance.
What do you think?
As you just said, that boy isn't at fault.
His only crime is that he's of Chairwoman Shin's blood.
So, if I can take advantage of him to get revenge,
I will.
"Take advantage of him?" How?
I'll let Ha Na adopt him.
If the boy becomes her son,
Chairwoman Shin won't be able to mistreat her.
And she may end up becoming...
the chairwoman of Hyesung Group.
That's true.
It seems like Chairwoman Shin and Se Young's mom are...
interfering with the adoption.
I get Chairwoman Shin because he's her grandson.
But what about Yoon Se Young's mom?
I think she knows that Ha Na is a fake.
You drive.
- Why? - You'll drive from now on.
Take it.
Driving around isn't even a big deal.
You can wait downstairs.
Hello. Yes, I called.
It's about the home visit you're making this weekend.
Can you make it seem like it's spontaneous?
"The home visit?"
During the last visit,
someone made a false report of child abuse,
so we couldn't finish.
This time, I thought I should keep it a secret.
Can I do that?
They're coming back for another home visit?
What do we do? How did that happen so fast?
You need to get to work. I'll find a way.
Call me when you find a way.
Okay. Go, now.
This is bad.
They're doing another home visit this weekend.
How are you going to stop this?
Hey, stop slamming on the brakes.
How many times do you have to reverse to park?
It's a little difficult today.
Hey!
Darn it.
Goodness.
You're doing this on purpose.
Stop picking a fight and get out.
Darn it.
- What are you doing? - It's Mr. Yoon.
How long do I have to live as her hidden daughter?
Why is she driving?
She's Yoon Yu Jin, Chairwoman Shin's daughter.
You saw me?
That's what I want to know.
She's been laughing whenever she saw me since yesterday.
And she began her power trips again.
You're the one who has power. Why would she do that?
Exactly.
I won't let her get away with it.
I'm Yoon Yu Jin. She can't harass me for long.
She'll back down soon enough.
She must've found out that Ha Na was a fake.
How's the adoption process going?
Yes, I talked to the agency this morning.
I asked to make it spontaneous as you suggested, and they agreed.
- Thanks. - Call me when the visit is over.
Okay.
Why don't we all meet at Ji Chang's tteokbokki place,
including Eun Chong?
It'd be nice for the entire family to go and show him some love.
We can do it on the weekend after the home visit.
Yes, okay. That day sounds great.
(Team Leader Yoon Se Young)
Ms. Yoon, you can tell us now.
Something good recently happened to you, right?
No, not much.
But you look so radiant these days,
and you're always smiling.
You can't be dating anyone new, so you must've made money.
That's not it.
I'm doing my best to live a lighthearted and happy life.
While we're on the subject, let me share a fun story.
What? A fake?
What about the real daughter?
Is she dead?
Ha Na, you can join us, too.
It's okay. I have to catch up on work.
You can come, Ms. Goo.
She's sharing a shocking story with us.
What is it?
Yesterday, I mentioned this person who got scammed, remember?
She was the daughter of an affluent family,
- but she found out she was a fake. - "A fake?"
Everything after that was tragic, so I couldn't share the rest.
She'd leave on her own, right?
She shouldn't.
She should hold out until the end.
I'd feel too betrayed to stay in that house.
Forget money or whatever. I'd want to leave right away.
You're right. It'd hurt too deeply.
If you think about it, it's like deceiving...
and making a fool of someone.
It only lasted a moment,
but she lived a good life in comfort with that rich family.
I'd love to live as someone rich even if it ended like this.
Me, too.
The family used her as a fake daughter?
Ms. Goo, how would you feel...
if someone used you as a fake daughter?
I never thought about that.
But I'd hate anyone who deceived me, even if they were rich.
Gosh, bad news. This was about you.
- You can pick it up. - Okay.
Hello? You've reached the Travel Service Department.
Okay.
Ms. Yoon, Director Goo wants to see you.
Your brother, Ji Seok, is the other man you want to find.
Know your fight before you start it.
Did your friends upload the photos on social media accounts?
Her phone broke, so she lost all the photos.
Gosh, what a shame.
If I had known, I would've taken the photos.
She couldn't have met with only one friend,
yet she had zero photos?
Did you find my power trips on Goo Ha Na unpleasant?
She's Yoon Yu Jin, not Goo Ha Na.
I didn't get why you'd do that to Chairwoman Shin's daughter.
Is there something I don't know?
I just don't like her.
You know that I hate her and why.
Because of Hwang Jin Goo?
Her involvement with you is even worse.
What if Chairwoman Shin finds out?
She wouldn't condone you harassing her daughter.
Did you call me so you could tell me to stop harassing Ha Na?
It's a cautionary tale, just in case you get hurt.
Why would I get hurt? Yoon Yu Jin is a fake.
You said she remembered everything.
What did she remember?
I was mistaken.
She knows Ha Na is a fake,
but she's keeping it a secret for a while?
It's Jin Goo.
Hey, I'm at the hotel.
Right now? Okay.
You might find a snitch on Hwang Jin Goo's side. Be careful.
"A party?"
Your friends and my friends can all meet up.
My friends are busy, so I don't know if they're free.
They'll be happy to meet with my friends.
How was the venue for your bridal shower?
- Was it in Gangnam? - Yes.
Call your friends.
- Let's find a date to meet up. - Okay.
Hey, it's me.
If Jin Goo asks,
tell the girls to say...
you all threw me a bridal shower in Gangnam last weekend.
If she had to lie to me to meet someone,
it must be a guy.
Who could it be? Is it someone at work?
Mr. Hwang.
Yes, Ms. Goo.
I have the edits on the mother-daughter tour.
Right. Thank you.
Is something going on?
- Why? - You look rigid,
unlike how you usually are.
So, if...
Yes?
Never mind. Good work.
- I'll take a good look. - Okay.
Ms. Goo made Eun Chong beg for money?
Myung Ji said she heard it.
That woman must've come to our place.
How did she know Ms. Goo lived there?
Ha Na could've told her.
I'm not so sure yet.
Should I just ask her?
You can ask when you're sure of everything.
This may cause a misunderstanding.
Did she really make Eun Chong beg for money?
Her love for him seemed genuine.
I also can't believe it.
I still want to check.
Danny, what kind of cake do you prefer for tteokbokki?
Rice cake? Flour cake?
I like both.
Me, too. We have the same taste in food.
Try it like this. Open up.
How is it?
I knew it'd be delicious.
Mr. Owner, why are you stealing your customer's food?
I'm not sure how my sister snatched you,
but this is your chance. Run!
Hey, Mr. Owner. Just go.
This is my place. Where would I go?
Ji Seok, Ha Na, and Eun Chong are all coming this weekend.
- You heard, right? - I already know.
You know, my brother is really into exaggeration.
It's great to see such realistic siblings.
Hey, is that a compliment or condemnation?
It's a compliment.
Gosh.
It's not so great to see.
My gosh.
You still haven't found a way?
Will you let her adopt him?
I'll find a way.
I can't do anything here,
so I'll have to lure Eun Chong out,
but that's not so easy.
What will you do after you lure him outside?
What do you think? Just stall for time.
Did she really make that young boy beg for money?
Is he taking the dressing off at the hospital on the weekend?
Yes.
After the hospital, we're going to Uncle Ji Chang's tteokbokki place.
"The hospital?"
Is Eun Chong going to the hospital to take the dressing off?
When?
- On the weekend. - I see.
Fate is on my side. That's the perfect day.
You've been so patient, Eun Chong.
Good for you.
Is there something you want to do once your hand is better?
I want to play with sand at the kindergarten...
and go to a kids' cafe.
We can do that.
- Really? - Yes.
You can use this hand to do everything now.
I'm so happy to be done.
- Lee Eun Chong's guardian, please. - Yes?
- Sit here for a second. - Okay.
Hello.
- Here's the bill. - Okay.
- Here. - Thank you.
- Here's your card. - Thanks.
- Thank you. - Sure.
Excuse me. Have you seen the boy who was sitting here?
He just left.
Thank you.
Eun Chong!
Where are you?
Excuse me.
Have you seen a boy in a blue jacket?
No.
Eun Chong!
Mr. Hwang.
Are you at home?
Can you e-mail me the edited version of the mom-daughter tour proposal?
No.
Mr. Hwang...
What's wrong? Is something going on?
Eun Chong...
disappeared.
What?
Today was the home visit?
I didn't hear anything.
This was a spontaneous visit.
So, I didn't even tell the guardian.
I can't let the adoption proceed like this.
She went to the hospital with Eun Chong.
- You should call her. - Okay.
Are you at the hospital?
The agency just came for Eun Chong. When will you come home?
I can't be there now.
You aren't done yet?
I don't think we can do this today. Please ask her to return.
What's wrong? Is something going on?
Eun Chong is gone.
What? "Eun Chong is gone?"
What?
Eun Chong is gone?
What are you talking about?
He was there while I paid the bill at the hospital,
but he suddenly disappeared.
"Suddenly disappeared?"
Have you looked everywhere?
Have you called the police?
- Aunt Yeo Jin. - Yeo Jin.
Eun Chong!
(Cinderella Game)
Someone must've known he'd be at the hospital.
Who could've leaked the information?
Didn't this look completely staged?
I need to put a bodyguard on Eun Chong.
It's been a while.
Are you crazy? How did you know I was here?
I heard Ha Na was Hyesung Group's hidden daughter.
Why don't you adopt Eun Chong?
Why don't we take a break?
I think I know who took Eun Chong.
- Is it someone you know? - Yes.