(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
I was greatly impressed
with your management style...
when I first began to study
business management.
You help sell businesses in trouble
at a good price before they go down,
like you're their savior.
- Is that so?
- I also heard...
you were the evil hand that profits off
of troubled businesses...
at giveaway prices.
I realized it was possible
to manage businesses like this,
both as a savior and the evil hand,
like Jekyll and Hyde.
Since then, I decided
to have you as my role model.
Not all hearsay is true.
At times, the truth could be
covered up by hearsay.
- I don't care.
- I'm like that, too.
I'm glad to know we're like-minded.
You're now one of us,
so feel free to tell me
whatever you need.
I do have a favor to ask.
I believe President Hwang Jin Goo...
reports to you
regarding Hyesung Tour.
Please allow me to take over.
I cannot condone
a mere president of a subsidiary...
ignoring hierarchy...
and reporting to the chairwoman
in a private setting.
This is irrational
in most organizations.
I'll talk to President Hwang.
Allow me to talk to him.
As you wish.
Who are you?
Why did she just slap me?
Who the heck are you?
A tour guide.
Yes, a tour guide
who causes all kinds of trouble...
and resorts to illegal acts.
Were you sent here
by Jaemin Construction? Or Taeyang?
I know. I heard
Daeri Construction's second son...
began to feather his own nest,
so was it him?
What are you talking about?
I said I caught you
acting as a spy...
trying to ruin our business.
- "Spy?"
- That was why you were...
going through other people's trash.
Going through what?
- The bag popped, so I had to...
- Search all you want.
You won't find anything.
I knew something was up
when you followed us here.
She's driving me crazy.
- That's not the case.
- If so,
then how did you know we'd be here
and followed us?
You messed with the wrong person.
I'll find out everything about you
and release a follow-up article,
an industrial spy
disguised as a tour guide!
- Hey.
- And your family will suffer, too,
so just wait.
What's going on?
Why is she here again?
It's nothing.
Did you find the reason?
Not yet.
I haven't been slapped
since my childhood.
- What are you doing?
- What?
What was the problem?
I didn't use
any artificial flavoring,
and I thoroughly checked
the list of allergies, too.
Yes, ma'am.
Why did the guest from Dubai
lodge the complaint?
No idea.
All he had to do was
just tell us what the problem was.
He's making
everyone's life difficult.
What if I end up taking the blame?
Yes, he was a guest
for Hyesung Tour,
so he must be staying
at Hyesung Hotel.
(Haengun Meat,
Product: Beef ribs, halal, frozen)
By any chance,
did he use frozen halal meat?
Probably.
Did he not eat it
because the meat was frozen?
Hey, Ji Eun.
Can you check if there is
a guest from Dubai at your hotel?
What? His name was...
- Hassan.
He's not in his room?
Is he not back yet?
Why are you prying
into a guest at our hotel?
Hey, isn't that him?
Hey, yes.
Hello.
It's an honor to meet you,
Mr. Hassan.
Hello, my name is Goo Ha Na,
a tour guide.
Are you with Hyesung Tour?
No, I was at Restaurant Mirim
because of work,
and I saw them leave
without finishing his meal.
I was wondering
if it was because of frozen meat.
These meal boxes were made
with fresh halal meat.
- If they didn't have dinner...
- They did.
- Is that halal?
- Yes.
Really?
They seem to enjoy it, right?
Even Hyesung Tour didn't know this.
How did you find out?
I have a regular guest of seven years
who is also like them.
The guest never eats
any frozen meat.
By any chance,
could you ask if that dinner
would have a negative impact...
on his business
with Daeri Construction?
No problem.
- "No problem."
- My gosh.
Thank you.
Are you busy in two days?
No, why?
There was a problem
with my scheduling,
so I've been looking for a guide
to assist the lady when she shops.
I'll do it.
But she's a guest
traveling with Hyesung Tour,
so I need to ask
for their understanding.
I'll manage that.
Gosh, thank you.
It all came down to this,
so you should apply for a job
at Hyesung Tour.
They were hiring
tour guides with experience.
Hwang Jin Goo is the president,
so I'm never going to get it.
On top of that...
- Who are you?
- Why did she just slap me?
Who the heck are you?
The more I thought about it,
the more offended I was.
How am I going to retaliate?
Do you know that woman
who's always with Hwang Jin Goo?
Yoon Se Young?
She's the team leader
of Hyesung's Tour Planning Team...
and Hwang Jin Goo's fiancee.
Why? Did you have a go at her, too?
I don't go around picking fights.
What's she like?
A girl hated by everyone.
Right?
She obviously seemed rude.
Does she go on power trips
with her team members?
That wasn't what I meant.
She's the chairwoman's niece
and the only legal heiress,
so everyone is jealous of her,
like Cinderella.
An heiress?
I want to be like her.
She's my role model.
All women should
live like Yoon Se Young.
Move.
- Gosh.
- My fight is too strong.
I'd never meet her again,
so I should've just slapped back.
Come on.
Ha Na, life always comes...
with variables and exceptions.
Hwang Jin Goo
may wake up late in the morning,
and he may get into an accident
the day before your interview.
I kicked a slipper
and hit Hwang Jin Goo's head.
You're really tough.
I said he'd suffer from betrayal...
if he stabbed me in the back
like this.
You're over.
Ha Na, I think this is a sign...
that you should focus on
becoming a housewife.
- Do you want water?
- No.
Why didn't you sew that in the day?
It's bad for your eyes, Mom.
My eyes are still going strong.
These blankets are for you
and Se Young. Isn't it pretty?
We could've just bought one.
Why did you make this hard for you?
It's for my precious son
and daughter-in-law,
so it's hardly trouble.
I wanted to do this myself.
Myung Ji said you'd be
the head director very soon.
Is that so?
The head director was recruited?
It's something I heard
from the board of directors.
He seemed to be recommended
by the investor.
Mom, did you want to see me
become the head director?
It'd be great if you became one.
But you prefer assisting
the chairwoman to getting promoted.
Myung Ji kept patronizing me.
I just wanted to knuckle her
on the head yesterday.
The chairwoman will do what's best.
Aren't you going to wash up?
Why? Did something bad happen
during the wedding photoshoot?
How did you know?
Why? What's going on?
I ran into Goo Ji Seok at the hotel.
What?
Wait, why was he at our hotel?
He's staying there.
There are many other hotels.
Why is he staying there?
Tell him to leave immediately.
He must've made it big.
He looked sharp.
My gosh.
He's an orphan
without any connections.
He couldn't have made it big.
Hey, if he makes it big,
I'll eat my hat.
If you make enough money,
it means you made it.
So, what did he do to make money?
No idea. I don't care.
(2024 Hyesung Hotel
Financial Statement)
(Hyesung Hotel
Management Strategy Analysis)
Not all hearsay is true.
At times, the truth could be
covered up by hearsay.
I don't care.
She doesn't care?
How long do you think
you can afford to do that,
Chairwoman Shin Yeo Jin?
Yu Jin.
My baby.
Come here.
My baby. Yu Jin!
It's that dream again.
Don't cry, my baby.
Don't cry.
- It's Eun Chong's project.
- Oh, no.
I don't know. I found it like this.
(Lee Eun Chong)
Oh, no.
I'm sorry, Eun Chong.
That's bad news for your auntie.
You should make it again.
Tease you!
Hey, you!
Something went in there.
Hey!
The loan?
Right, for the lease.
Yes, the loan I took out
at the bank I work at.
There were 17 more years
to pay it off,
so I thought I should
settle our finances.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
I should've brought it up first.
I was too out of it,
so it didn't come to my mind.
Well, I already know your situation,
so I won't ask you
to pay everything back now.
I plan to find some money
and pay it back in a lump sum.
But please write me an IOU.
Yes, of course, I should.
No, you don't have to do that here.
Let's go somewhere else.
(Park Jae Hwi Law Office)
I hope you weren't hurt
that I got this notarized.
I wasn't.
I'll try to pay back
as soon as I can.
I'm sorry to cause trouble.
All right. Please do that.
Stay strong.
Please press a button.
Confirming check card information.
- Please choose a menu.
- What? Why is my balance so low?
(Balance: 158.65 dollars)
It must've been the rent.
Press the amount.
Well, I already know your situation,
so I won't ask you
to pay everything back now.
- Please take your card.
- I plan to find some money...
and pay it back in a lump sum.
Thank you.
If I could, I'd take out a loan
and pay him back right away.
Hey, Eun Kyung.
So you heard.
I'll find a different job.
If there's a gig I can take up...
A pick-up service?
Stop crying.
You don't deserve to cry.
They weren't in the kindergarten.
Tae Hoon, please think about it.
Maybe you left them somewhere else.
No.
Those were my favorite sneakers.
Be quiet.
You're in for trouble at home.
- Hello.
Eun Chong!
Auntie!
Hey. My gosh.
Are you done with work?
No, I'm taking you
to pick someone up at the airport.
All right!
Hold my hand.
You're taking office?
Were you recruited
as a president or a director?
- Something like that.
- Gosh, where at?
A major corporation?
If you're an executive at that age,
you're guaranteed success.
Nothing is guaranteed in this world.
That's great news.
You can find a job for Ha Na.
- "Find a job?"
- Right.
She took up an illegal gig
and got fired.
I don't know what your company does,
but it'll be a piece of cake
for an executive to find a job.
You should take charge
and give her a job.
It's illegal
to request a job like this.
On top of that, I couldn't do that
if she was fired for an illegal gig.
That's why you need to help her.
- Why should I?
- "Why should I?"
We're family!
Family should help each other
when we're in need.
Didn't you learn that
back in kindergarten?
- Family?
- Yes, family.
Right, that was the word
you hated most.
Little brother,
do you have to do this now?
You need to eat first.
You love raw fish.
Don't get delusional and think
you're doing your part...
as an older brother
just by buying a few pieces of fish.
Like it or not, Ha Na is
the breadwinner for our family.
What have you done
as the eldest son anyway?
You left for America five years ago
as if you were running away.
Did you want to be an older brother
now that you were better off?
No, thanks. You aren't welcome.
- That's enough!
- Ouch.
Yes, I'll do my part as an older brother
and the breadwinner.
So, stop complaining
and try to work with me.
How are you going to play your part?
Do you think
giving us money is the end?
I'm moving to an apartment soon.
You two should move in.
An apartment?
Is it yours? Where is it?
I'll tell Ha Na.
So, pretend like you didn't know.
She'll marry anyway.
Are you trying
to split her up from us?
Look what we're doing!
Why are we leaving Ha Na out?
What will happen to her without us?
She'll be happier.
Don't you think you two are
holding Ha Na back?
- Gosh.
- I'm tired.
My goodness. It looks so pretty.
The entrance is huge.
- It looks amazing.
- It does.
- Thank you.
Please.
- It's huge.
- I'm looking forward to this.
She doesn't share
a drop of blood with us.
How long will you live off her?
Who cares about blood?
Mom and Dad wouldn't have adopted her
if they cared about that.
- That's enough.
- Continue!
Ha Na and the two of us...
never had such a thought.
Isn't that so, Ji Eun?
I don't know what Ha Na is thinking.
How disloyal.
I don't want to force anything.
Live however you want to.
It's up to you
to choose who you live with.
Take your time to finish
before you come out.
And now I'm too depressed to eat.
Why did you come today?
Did you come here to fight?
You shouldn't live like that,
you evil brat.
"Brat?"
Don't be so cheeky! That punk.
Darn it.
- My gosh.
- Breakfast begins at 7 a.m.
- Please enjoy your meal.
- Okay.
Your guide will come
and meet you at 9 a.m.
Then, please have a great rest.
- Thank you.
Uncle Ji Seok.
He looks like Uncle Ji Seok.
Did the three of them meet
without telling Auntie Ha Na?
Let's go, Auntie.
You must be hungry.
Let's go.
Wait.
What's wrong, Auntie?
(Hyesung Tour: Open Recruitment
for Experienced Operators and Guides)
Auntie, are you getting a new job?
I don't know.
(Hyesung Tour: Open Recruitment
for Experienced Operators and Guides)
Come here.
What?
Ji Eun and Ji Chang?
(White Butterfly Tour)
Ji Eun! Ji Chang!
I thought you had to meet someone
for dinner, Ji Chang.
Yes, I did.
Wait, you did, too.
I met someone at the hotel.
Was it the two of you?
Are you crazy? I'm already sick
of eating with him at home.
Jeez, those are my words.
They're doing this again.
- Hop in.
- We'll take the bus.
That's the car for your work.
Yes, Ha Na. You should do your job.
I can do that
after I drop you off. Hop in.
Just go.
There's no need to pay the bus fare.
Hop in now.
Come on.
It's not like
the bus fare costs a lot.
It's not every day
you run into your family outside.
It's so nice
to run into each other, isn't it?
Maybe it's just me.
Ji Chang, did you meet someone
at the hotel, too?
Yes... I mean...
No, I was passing by,
then I had to use the restroom.
What did you eat for dinner?
I had spicy fish soup.
Was it good?
It tasted like spicy fish soup.
- Who did you eat with?
- What?
- My friend.
- Your friend? Who?
Someone you don't know.
Did you have a friend
I didn't know of?
Do you now keep secrets from me?
Can we please go in peace?
You're so talkative.
Did something make you mad, girl?
Why are you glaring at me?
Look forward.
Darn it. Jeez.
Like it or not, Ha Na is
the breadwinner for our family.
What have you done
as the eldest son anyway?
You left for America five years ago
as if you were running away.
Did you want to be an older brother
now that you were better off?
Make sure you feed Eun Chong first.
Don't worry about that,
and drive safely, Ha Na.
I'll be back.
Uncle Ji Chang, Auntie Ji Eun,
you two are bad!
You lied to Auntie Ha Na!
What's he saying?
Hey, we didn't lie.
- I saw everything.
- What?
You two met with Uncle Ji Seok.
Why didn't you tell Auntie Ha Na
that Uncle Ji Seok was here?
She's always waiting for him.
Hey, that's...
Hey, this kid has a knack
for making me feel flustered.
Uncle Ji Seok did come.
But it's a secret
from Auntie Ha Na for a while.
- Why is it a secret?
- Tell me about it.
Keep that going, Eun Chong.
You finally did something I liked.
You're too little
to know everything.
We're doing this for Auntie Ha Na.
How is this for Auntie Ha Na?
Hey, you're pretty sharp.
Why? Because things are hectic
after she lost her job...
She lost her job?
Yes, she got fired.
Your favorite Auntie Ha Na is
now unemployed. Happy now?
- What is she going to do?
- What do you mean, kid?
Just stay quiet.
Do you like it?
- My gosh.
- Oh, my gosh.
Look at this.
- Do you want to try this?
- Yes.
Oh, my gosh. It's so cute.
How about you try these two?
Let's see which one is better.
Oh, my gosh. It looks so pretty.
- It looks so pretty.
- Really?
- My gosh, you look great.
- How is it?
One, two, three.
It's so beautiful.
This one.
This one is so pretty, too.
- This one is so cute.
- My gosh.
Amira's interpreter left?
Then, who is she shopping with?
The interpreter said
she found someone on her own.
They're our guest.
We should've found someone.
Did another travel agency hear this
and get to her first?
They were greatly satisfied
with the halal boxed meals,
and the guide was
someone who got those.
"Halal boxed meals?"
Who was the guide?
Thank you, Ha Na.
I had such a great time, thanks to you.
I will definitely call you
when I'm in Korea next time.
I'm glad to hear that.
If you need anything,
just call me anytime. Okay?
Of course.
Oh, my brooch. It's gone.
I think I lost it.
When did you start not seeing it?
Do you have any idea
where you dropped it?
I must've dropped it
while we were shopping.
It's an important gift
from my mother.
It's super important to me.
Oh, my gosh. Where did it go?
Okay, Amira. I'll go check
the places we visited today.
Just... Don't worry,
and go up to your room.
You might be late
for your prayer time. Okay?
Okay.
You have to find it.
Sure.
- Take these.
- Okay.
Please don't worry about it.
Thank you so much.
Amira.
Hello.
Yes, hello.
My guest lost her hijab brooch.
Could you look in the store
and see if she dropped it?
It's very important.
Yes, I'll be there now. Goodbye.
It's you again.
You knew she was
an important guest to us,
yet you took up this job
as an unqualified guide...
Hey.
I guess you have a habit...
of suspecting people, blaming them,
and talking down to everyone.
It was a personal request
from the interpreter.
I said I had to ask Hyesung Tour
for their understanding,
and she said she'd manage.
What more do you want?
You should've done your job
if you snatched our guest.
What will you do about the brooch?
I'll start looking.
If that brooch causes trouble
for my client's business,
I won't let you live.
She brought the halal box meals
and found out about the frozen meat?
What's with my luck
yesterday and today?
She was the one
who should apologize to me!
What?
Gosh, that's not it.
Excuse me.
Where could it be?
I was worried
about how you couldn't sleep.
Should I get you a prescription?
I don't want to depend on drugs.
Instead, I may consider
picking up drinking.
Be my drinking buddy.
Sure. Please think about
the type of liquor you like.
Something strong.
President Hwang Jin Goo knows
he didn't get the job,
so why did he stay quiet?
He might be more cautious
than I expected.
Should I leak the information
to the board?
They'll find out soon enough.
I didn't expect to see you here.
There are millions of hotels
here in Seoul.
How dare you set foot in here?
Hey, get out of here.
Why do you care
which hotel I stay at, lady?
"Lady?"
You little...
Let go of me.
Mom.
- Let go of me.
- Let go of her.
Darn it.
Hey. You must've become a big shot.
What's with you?
You're at the hotel.
- Let's go.
- You.
Leave the place now.
Good grief.
Have you lost your mind?
What if Jin Goo
or Aunt Yeo Jin saw you?
I lost it...
the moment I saw him.
Why is he lurking around here?
What an eyesore.
He'll find you the same.
Why did you date
someone lowly like him?
That was why we broke up.
I'm dating Jin Goo
and marrying him as you want.
Do you think
Jin Goo is good enough for me?
I had no other choice
because of Yeo Jin.
Why are you here?
I went to see your newlywed home,
then came to have dinner with you.
I have to eat dinner
with Aunt Yeo Jin and Jin Goo.
The three of you?
Will she appoint him
as the head director?
I know it.
I'll stay out of this,
so call me right away
after you hear the news.
I'm sorry. I wanted to make you
the head director before marriage.
It's all right.
The business comes first.
Jin Goo will do
great things in the future,
so he won't fret
over a small matter like this.
We knew you made a wise judgment.
Thank you.
When did those little kids
grow up this much?
You know how much
your support means to me, right?
I'll work even harder, Aunt Yeo Jin.
My dream had always been
to support you by your side,
so I should be thankful.
Do you want to know what he's like?
I heard he was someone
recommended by an investor.
You knew about this?
It wasn't anything official.
What's he like?
All I know about him is
his educational background.
I was worried because
he hadn't shown what he could do.
I'll keep an eye on him,
find a fault, and then fire him.
He should be a decent man...
both for your business and me.
That would hurt my pride
a little less.
What you just said
had a hidden meaning.
Honestly speaking, I'd be lying
if I said I wasn't bothered.
I was a little bothered.
Then, you can be the judge.
I thought you should meet him
before he takes office, so I called him.
It'd be nice to meet him
as soon as possible.
All right, then.
Ms. Chairwoman.
Come on in.
He's President Hwang Jin Goo
of Hyesung Tour.
- My name is Hwang Jin Goo.
- I'm Goo Ji Seok.
She's Team Leader Yoon Se Young
of Hyesung Tour...
and my niece.
Hello, my name is Yoon Se Young.
Hello, I'm Goo Ji Seok.
(Cinderella Game)
You should've handled the money issue
as soon as you broke up.
I can't pay that back right away.
What the heck is wrong with you?
Come here!
Show me what you can do.
That's the only way
I'll approve of you.
Why do I need your approval?
It was
the chairwoman's special order.
Find the contact for the guide
who found the brooch for Hassan's wife.
Who knows what Aunt Yeo Jin
is hiding to surprise us?
You get just one month.
If you don't keep your promise,
I'll set your place on fire.