(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
Aunt Yeo Jin!
Congratulations.
I'm so happy for you.
Thank you, Se Young.
When will Yu Jin come home?
When can we meet her?
We have to keep quiet
about finding her for a while.
Things could become rowdy
once her identity gets exposed.
You'll meet her when she comes home.
You understand, right?
Yes.
I look forward to seeing
this fake daughter or fraud.
I know how hard you helped
by my side until this day.
That was how I could find her.
Don't say that
like we're some strangers.
Yu Jin and I grew up
like we were real sisters.
Things would be the same as then
even if we met now.
Yes.
I have a favor to ask of you.
Yu Jin was traumatized
at the time of her disappearance...
and didn't remember
anything about her childhood.
Please refrain from mentioning
anything about her childhood...
and whatever happened
before her disappearance.
The doctor said
her condition could worsen...
if we tried
to force her memories to return.
Goodness, of course.
We'll let her remember naturally.
I'll do that, Aunt Yeo Jin.
And keep it a secret
from anyone outside.
Yes, we'll do that.
My goodness.
How could we have known...
Yu Jin was so close by?
Take your medicine.
Everything will be over
if she sees...
how you're trembling.
It's such a relief
she doesn't remember her childhood.
She may not remember it now,
but what if she remembers
getting on the boat with me?
She'll never remember.
Mom, where do you get the confidence
to be so composed?
Lower your voice!
You said she died.
You paid all those shamans,
and it ended up like...
What will you do
if you don't trust me?
What can you do alone without me?
If you can do something, do it.
I'm sorry.
You just need to trust me
and follow my lead.
I can still keep you safe...
even if Yu Jin comes here.
Do you mean it?
Of course.
Wait, could she be
the Yu Jin she found?
Did you go out for a walk?
- Please have dinner with us.
- Sure.
I wasn't trying to eavesdrop,
but did you find your birth mother?
Please keep it a secret
from my siblings.
Why? It's great news.
She said she'd come home
and tell them herself.
By any chance,
was she the one you met
a few days ago,
the chairwoman of your workplace?
How did you know?
It's a secret.
All right.
Yeo Jin is her birth mother?
Yeo Jin, what have you done?
Did you turn Ms. Goo into Yu Jin
to keep Eun Chong safe?
The chairwoman and I are besties.
So, I told her to come over.
Hey, the chairwoman
doesn't have that much time.
She wouldn't be at this humble home
just because you were her bestie.
If you really are her bestie,
get me the highest position
at the cafeteria.
Ha Na, I think
Eun Chong needs to see a doctor.
He said the chairwoman would
come over to our place.
She will.
Tell Ji Eun to come on the weekend.
No way. Are you serious?
Wait, why would she come here?
She'll come and tell you.
I got chills.
What's going on? You're scaring me.
Did you do something?
Yes, I did something.
Something huge.
Wait.
Is she our new landlady?
She turned Ms. Goo
into your daughter?
She couldn't tell others
that Eun Chong was her grandson,
so she must've turned Ms. Goo
into Yu Jin.
The two must've had an agreement.
Well, yes. Of course.
It'd be impossible to do
without her permission.
If she becomes Yu Jin,
Eun Chong will be her friend's son
and remain safe.
She made a fake daughter
to protect Eun Chong?
She seemed to have found
the best way out.
Ms. Goo is like Cinderella,
while Eun Chong is
the hidden seven-year-old successor.
Thanks to this act,
she'll get to live with him.
Is there another problem?
Ms. Goo is unaware of the history
between the two families.
What if she finds out Eun Chong is
the blood of her worst enemy?
I didn't expect her
to do something like this...
to protect Eun Chong.
How long can she keep doing
this fake daughter thing?
We'll leave that up to fate.
She must have another plan
in case they get exposed.
Yoon Yu Jin?
Yoon Yu Jin.
That was my real name.
Do you know who Yoon Yu Jin is?
It was the name
Ji Seok asked me about.
Why did he ask me
about my childhood name?
Because it was the name
of the chairwoman's daughter?
(President Hwang Jin Goo)
Look at Yali.
Gosh, she's so cute.
Whoa, a cat.
Look. Isn't Yali cute?
Gosh, it's called Yali?
Where is Yali?
She's at Mr. Hwang's place.
Gosh, can we go see her?
I want to see Ms. Bang Ul, too.
I'll ask him.
Gosh, she's so cute.
Sleep well.
- Mr. Hwang said, "Sleep well."
- What?
Yali looks so happy
as she's sleeping.
It's such a heartwarming night.
Goodnight, Mr. Hwang.
Goodnight.
What are you doing, Eun Chong?
I just texted Mr. Hwang.
I said, "I want to see you."
What? What am I going to do?
No, he read it.
I want to see you.
- My gosh!
- Whoa.
(Yali)
She wants to see Yali?
I'm sorry, Mr. Hwang.
Eun Chong just sent those.
You can't text him and say
you want to see him.
He'll take it the wrong way.
I meant that I wanted to see Yali.
Yali?
Goodness. Lee Eun Chong!
You're so mischievous!
You're such a troublemaker. Hey.
Goodness, Eun Chong.
If Ms. Goo chose this
for the other two's happiness,
should I also show my support
and keep an eye on everything?
No, don't come.
Don't come. Don't.
Go away!
What's wrong? Did you have a dream?
Over there. Yu Jin is there.
Yu Jin...
It was just a dream.
Yu Jin isn't here.
Come here.
It's all right.
No one is here.
I'm scared.
Don't be scared. I'm here with you.
It's all right. Nothing will happen.
I can't believe
I'm Chairwoman Shin's daughter.
Eun Chong.
I met my birth mother.
I still can't believe it.
I can't,
but I love it.
I would've met her even sooner
if I had registered my DNA...
when your mother told me to.
I must be getting blessed...
for living so diligently.
Do you also want to know
what she's like?
She's a big deal.
You'd be really surprised
if you found out.
I'm the daughter
of this company's owner?
It still doesn't feel real.
Gosh, I hope
I don't become a nuisance.
I haven't even started.
Let's not get scared.
When did you know she found Yu Jin?
I found out yesterday.
She only shared this with Ms. Jang
and kept it from you, too?
Have you heard anything about her?
Where does she live?
What does she do?
She wouldn't tell me,
so I didn't want to pry.
We'll find out soon enough,
so let's wait.
How do you honestly feel?
If she comes back,
she may steal our positions.
I wouldn't use the word "steal."
It was hers to begin with.
Don't you have any ambition?
Think of everything
you have done by her side.
Don't you want to be her successor?
I started working here
to repay her kindness.
If her daughter shows up,
I must help her.
Everyone will call you pretentious
if you say that.
You already know people think...
we're in a win-win relationship
because we're both halfsies.
Why do you care
about what others think?
We're just us.
Are you also marrying me...
to repay Aunt Yeo Jin's kindness?
What are you talking about?
Am I the kind of man...
who'll marry someone I don't love
just to repay her kindness?
Who knows?
Your priority is my aunt, not me.
Do you even love me?
I recently began to wonder
if I really were your fiancée.
I'm sorry.
I'll be more attentive from now on.
Do you want to eat dinner today?
It doesn't feel great
to force you to do things.
Se Young.
I made a mistake yesterday.
- Please forget it.
- "Mistake?"
Why would you make such a mistake?
Because Yoon Yu Jin showed up?
You shuddered
after getting that phone call...
because the substitution
would be thrown out...
as soon as the real deal showed up.
Shut up. That won't happen.
(Jin Goo)
You should've chosen me,
not Hwang Jin Goo.
It's still not too late.
You're a better match with me
than Hwang Jin Goo.
What do you want, then?
- For me to break off my engagement?
- Can you?
Then, prove that you're serious.
I need to do the math and see...
if I can switch over to you.
Can you prove it?
If you trust me.
You don't trust me, either.
Mutual trust is
absolutely necessary in a contract.
I guess this one will take a while.
You're about to go down,
so you need to hold tightly...
to whatever lifeline you can find
with all your might.
Trust, my foot.
I was told not to grab
a decaying lifeline.
Anyway,
I'll keep your offer in my mind.
(President Hwang Jin Goo)
Am I the kind of man...
who'll marry someone I don't love
just to repay her kindness?
Your priority is my aunt, not me.
Do you even love me?
"Love?"
Come in.
Mr. Hwang, I revised the details
for the mother-daughter therapy tour.
Good work.
I want to see you.
Mr. Hwang?
Eun Chong must want to see
Yali a lot.
You should bring him over sometime.
Your mother would
find us uncomfortable.
She adores Eun Chong, too.
If you still feel uneasy,
then just send Eun Chong over.
He'd be thrilled.
The first thing he did this morning
was to look at Yali's photos.
It's hard to go back
once you become a cat lover.
One moment.
You've reached Hwang Jin Goo.
The official document from Dubai
was forged?
Are you sure?
All right.
Thank you for your hard work.
The document that proved...
their suspension of three months
was fake?
Yes.
The form was different
from what they usually used.
Also, the Dubaian travel agency is
business as usual in Dubai.
We were stabbed in the back, then.
Why would Hassan lie to us?
That's what we need to find out.
Let's keep
the forged document a secret...
until we find evidence.
Let's find out who's behind Hassan.
You believe it was
Head Director Goo Ji Seok, right?
I don't have hard evidence, though.
What do I have to do
in the middle...
if Ji Seok becomes
the chairwoman's enemy?
You want to keep an eye on her?
She hasn't announced
finding her daughter,
and things at her business
are quiet, too.
She'll probably keep her hidden
for a while.
We must find out who she is
before she goes public...
and come up with countermeasures.
The succession may change
depending on her position...
Sir?
Your daughter
became Chairwoman Shin's daughter.
What if you found out?
Sir?
- Yes?
- Do you feel unwell?
You don't look so well.
I'm fine.
Here's how I expect
everything to unfold.
She'll keep her daughter hidden
and teach her as a successor.
Hwang Jin Goo and Yoon Se Young will
get married in that while.
The two will remain
as her potential successors...
until her daughter
comes to the front.
Would those two do
as Chairwoman Shin wants...
while her daughter gets trained
as the actual successor?
I doubt that.
And that's when we come in.
In order to do that,
we must finish putting Hyesung Tour down,
according to our plan.
I'm afraid this will...
harm you and your sister
in the gravest way.
If...
Chairwoman Shin apologizes
and seeks forgiveness right now,
will you be willing
to stop your revenge?
No, if she was capable of that,
I wouldn't be here today.
Is something going on?
No.
Let me know
if anything troubles you.
Getting your revenge is important,
but nothing is more important
than your family and those you love.
Now that I look back,
the people in my life were
the most precious to me.
I can't do that anymore,
but I hope you live that life.
Yes, sir.
Chairwoman Shin postponed
the video call,
so let me call it off altogether.
Tell her Richard Han is returning
to Korea at the end of this month.
Are you sure?
It was about time
I made my entrance.
- Please try again.
- Gosh.
(Goo Ji Seok)
What?
- You should go through.
- Thank you.
Do you still run coffee errands?
It wasn't an errand.
I lost a ghost leg game.
Here. It's decaf.
- I'm fine.
- I have mine, so drink it.
Those who do the coffee run
get to drink two cups of coffee.
Do you remember?
We always played
the ghost leg game as kids...
because we hated cleaning the house.
I always lost back then,
and I still do now.
Back then, you lost on purpose
not to let our siblings...
or me do it.
Don't let others win anymore.
You knew that?
Gosh, you're such a softie
on the inside.
I said I'd destroy Hyesung Tour.
I'm promoting a business
with an investor I met in America,
and our goal is Hyesung Group.
Chairwoman Shin and I are
technically enemies.
I didn't want her
to be involved with our family.
Would Ji Seok change his mind
if he found out...
the chairwoman was my birth mother?
You asked me if I knew
someone named Yoon Yu Jin...
from my children's home, right?
Do you remember her?
I wanted to share the news
with your siblings myself.
No, I was just curious
because you had asked.
You're about to go down,
so you need to hold tightly...
to whatever lifeline you can find
with all your might.
Trust, my foot.
Do you think I'll back off
just because Yu Jin is here now?
You were still stuck
in your childhood.
Think of everything that
makes you afraid as a toy.
It doesn't matter if the toy
opens its eyes and walks around.
You're the owner of that room
as long as you keep this talisman.
Yes, Yoon Yu Jin.
You're just a toy.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
Here's your coffee.
Oh, no!
A talisman?
- What's wrong?
- Are you okay?
Did you spill the coffee?
- What? Is this a talisman?
- What?
Darn it.
You spilled coffee on your talisman?
Why couldn't you stick that
while it was dry?
I don't know.
It's all Goo Ha Na's fault.
She left the coffee on my desk
to make me spill it on purpose.
It was that brat again?
That unlucky girl is
always getting in your way.
You should stick that talisman
on that brat!
Keep your distance from her
to keep bad luck away.
Could it have bad luck now?
We can always get another talisman,
so just stop minding
that petty girl.
All right. Bye.
Someone who might be my birth mother
suddenly showed up.
Did you meet that woman
who could be your birth mother?
- So, was she?
- Yes.
She must've heard that
the chairwoman found her daughter.
Does this mean Yoon Se Young
and I will become cousins?
Did you run a parentage test?
Yes.
What kind of a face will she make...
when she finds out
that I'm the chairwoman's daughter?
How does it feel when a stranger
suddenly shows up as your mom?
It seemed like...
you weren't too glad
or moved to meet her.
I'm not so sure.
It doesn't feel real yet.
I felt bewildered.
What does she do?
Is she well-off?
Why do you want to know that?
It reminded me
of a third-rate drama.
This is when a rich mom comes in
and changes the whole landscape.
It's so tacky.
Why won't she answer me?
Tell me no.
What am I imagining?
A girl like Goo Ha Na can't be her.
So, she made a fake daughter...
because she didn't want
to leave the company to Se Young?
If so, she would've put on a show
long ago.
Why would she do that now?
Did she find out
that her daughter died?
If she found out,
she would've lost her mind by now...
Wait.
She once collapsed at work...
and was brought home on a gurney.
Yes, since that day,
things began to feel quite eerie.
- Yes.
- That file was around then, too.
She'd quickly hide the files
she was looking at when I walked in.
So, I opened her safe
and found nothing.
She found out
that her daughter died.
How would she know?
Only you and I know that.
Who knows? I did my part
and cleaned up everything.
If she found out
about her daughter's death,
she must've found out
about the hit-and-run accident.
Then, she probably got
suspicious of the driver.
She must be suspicious of you, too.
- Me?
- You and your daughter...
would suffer the most
if her daughter came back.
Is she testing you
and your daughter...
by making that fake daughter?
She's suspicious of me?
No.
She may not trust me,
but she won't be suspicious of me.
A woman in her early thirties
will use this room.
Please make it look
simple and modern.
But Eun Chong will
stay in this room with her.
He should stay with me in my room.
It's more natural for him to stay
with Ms. Goo in the beginning.
You must keep your distance
from Eun Chong.
Then, decorate the room...
for a mom in her thirties
and her seven-year-old son.
Yes, ma'am.
Please pick up what you'll keep
and leave what you'll throw out.
We'll tear it down
starting tomorrow.
Please have it done within a week.
Yes, of course. I'll stay in touch.
Why is she suddenly redecorating
her daughter's room?
I guess
Mr. Hwang hasn't told you yet.
She found her daughter.
Oh, my. Are you serious?
Ms. Chairwoman, you should pick out
the things to throw out...
"Throw out?"
All these belonged to Yu Jin.
How can you tell me
to throw these out?
You found your daughter now,
so you must do it.
You also found your grandson.
I did find Yu Jin.
And Eun Chong.
Is it finally time to let Yu Jin go?
You must make the decision
for Eun Chong's sake.
Yes. I'll only think of Eun Chong.
Your bestie lady is
coming over on the weekend?
Yes, I invited her.
Auntie Ji Eun will also come.
Grandpa, how high can a kite fly?
Well, very high.
Will it reach my mommy?
Of course.
I hope she reads this
and grants my wish.
- Did you decide on a wish?
- Yes.
I want all my family to be happy.
All right.
Let's write down our wishes...
and go fly the kites.
Yeo Jin will be here tomorrow?
Then, Ji Seok will find out
very soon.
(Head Director Goo Ji Seok)
Here. It's decaf.
Do you remember?
We always played
the ghost leg game as kids...
because we hated cleaning the house.
Director Goo,
the accident with Ms. Yoon's car...
will be handled quietly
by the insurance company.
Things must've been hectic...
since the chairwoman's daughter
appeared.
- That's great.
- Yes, sir.
Wait.
Can you find a robot vacuum cleaner?
Is it for you?
It's for my older sister.
It's so much easier
to clean the place now.
We now have a bidet
and a robot vacuum cleaner.
We're pretty well-off, too.
Uncle Ji Seok is awesome!
What about me?
I'm here with you,
so you should be good to me.
- Grandpa.
- Hey.
I'll introduce you
to my best friend later.
I'm sorry.
I have to go out and do something.
Are you giving us privacy
on purpose?
No, I had a previous engagement.
The unemployed are
always the busiest.
Hey.
Hey, Ji Seok. You're here.
I made salad,
so you could have that.
Are you going to work?
No, I'm going to Ha Na's place.
Wait, you haven't heard, right?
The chairwoman is
coming to her place today.
What do you mean?
You mean Chairwoman Shin?
She must be her new landlady...
if she's coming there herself.
I'll use this chance to make sure
she knows who I am.
- "Landlady?"
- Bye, then.
Hello, Ms. Chairwoman.
Hi, Eun Chong.
Thank you for inviting me.
Have a seat, Ms. Chairwoman.
Thank you.
I'll get some tea.
Well, if I may ask,
are you here to ask us
for a rent increase...
or for us to move?
Hey, that's not it.
Then, what is it?
Isn't she the landlady?
Actually, I recently found...
my lost daughter.
- Really?
Congratulations, Ms. Chairwoman.
Oh, my.
Yes, congratulations, ma'am.
- You lost your daughter?
- Yes.
But I found her now,
so I was very thrilled.
Who's your daughter?
So, what does
finding your daughter...
have to do with our family?
- Ha Na!
- My gosh!
Where's your class?
Gosh, I'm sorry.
Are you...
No, right?
Gosh, what am I imagining?
How can you be...
Gosh, that makes no sense.
Yes, you're taking things too far.
We're sorry.
Please don't take it the wrong way.
You didn't get it wrong.
- Sorry?
- What?
Ms. Goo was my lost daughter.
I am Ha Na's birth mother.
You're the chairwoman's daughter?
(Cinderella Game)
I want to live with you
as soon as possible.
This is going to be really fun.
When did everything go wrong?
Is there a reason why she can't be
the chairwoman's daughter?
Please show some respect.
She's my birth mother.
You need to run
the parentage test again.
Please keep it a secret for a while.
Everything went as you hoped,
Yeo Jin.
Please be happy.
Think of everything I went through
to be here right now.
No!