(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
(Episode 87)
Yeo Jin, remember?
When we first met,
we hit it off right away.
We talked all night, not realizing
time passed by so quickly.
You were so endearing
when you talked...
with your sweet voice.
Can you get up...
and call my name just once?
I'm sorry for everything.
What...
are you doing right now, Mr. Han?
Ji Seok.
Was it true...
that you were...
Chairwoman Shin's husband?
Was it?
Let's talk outside.
Ji Seok.
I can't believe it.
Just tell me it wasn't true.
Tell me that it was a lie.
I'm sorry.
How can you be
Chairwoman Shin's husband?
How can the helper of my revenge be
my enemy's husband?
Do you have any idea
how much trust I had in you?
You were like
a father figure to me...
If you're the husband
of the enemy who killed my parents,
that makes you my enemy, too.
You're just like
my parents' murderer!
Why did you help me?
Why did you take things this far...
and deceive me to help
take Chairwoman Shin down? Why?
You and I had the same idea.
Did you want your revenge
on Chairwoman Shin, too?
Did you use me as your tool?
I genuinely wanted to help you
get your revenge,
and it was my calling.
"Genuine? Calling?"
Forget that kind of nonsense!
What else did you lie about?
Were you happy...
living as Eun Chong's grandfather...
when you deceived my siblings
and moved into Ha Na's place?
That was why you told me
to stop trying to get revenge.
You wanted to protect
your grandson. Isn't that so?
You're a worse hypocrite
and crueler than Chairwoman Shin.
I saw you...
when you were begging the chairwoman
by the factory 13 years ago.
Then, fate led me
to reunite with you...
in a faraway country, in America.
I took that...
as my calling to save you.
I also wanted to atone for my wife,
who had been destroying the weak...
through her
corporate raiding schemes.
I wanted to save you.
The only thing
I could do to do that...
was to give you hope that
you can get your revenge on her.
It may sound like an excuse,
but would you have
accepted my help...
if I told you who my wife was?
Would you have agreed to see me?
In that case,
you might have died five years ago.
You should've just left me to die.
Then, I wouldn't have felt...
as miserable as I did.
I thought of you as my own.
When you trusted me and admired me,
I really thought of you as my son.
You thought of me as your son?
Don't make me laugh.
You took advantage of me...
to keep your petty conscience,
hoping to be freed
of that false sense of guilt.
Yes.
That might have been the case.
I truly apologize for deceiving you.
Did I actually get revenge?
How is my revenge significant
in any way?
What am I supposed to do now?
How am I supposed to go on?
Ji Seok.
Will you please forgive me?
- I want us to continue to...
- No.
No.
I'm completely shattered.
I never want to see you again.
Ji Seok.
Hello? I'm at the hospital.
The chairwoman is
in critical condition.
What?
I'll be there right now.
Yeo Jin!
She still does not have a pulse.
Her blood oxygen level fell
under 60 percent.
Get the defibrillator.
Yes, Doctor.
She fell into cardiac arrest.
Yeo Jin, please.
Her pulse is back.
Is she okay?
Yes, thankfully,
her heart began to beat again.
We'll keep an eye on her
and update you on her condition.
Okay.
Thank you.
Yeo Jin...
- You're here.
- Hello.
My goodness. How can this happen?
- Mr. Han.
- Grandpa.
Hey, Eun Chong.
What brings you here, Mr. Han?
I'm sorry for not telling you
until this day.
Not telling me what?
He seems like
the chairwoman's husband.
"The chairwoman's husband?"
Yes, I'm Du Na's dad.
You're Du Na's dad?
Does Ji Seok know?
I wanted to save you.
The only thing
I could do to do that...
was to give you hope that
you can get your revenge on her.
Hey!
Hey, are you okay?
Can you hear me?
Have some.
Thank you.
Were you really
trying to kill yourself?
I can't even die as I wish.
You should've left me to die.
If you hold that much grudge,
you should live instead of dying.
I wasn't trying to take a peek,
but I saw that you had
lots of files on Hyesung Group.
Let me know if you need my help.
I saved your life,
so I should help you live on.
(Ha Na)
- The person you have reached...
- He won't pick up?
No. He must be somewhere
getting a drink.
He'll want to be alone.
Don't be too anxious.
I'm sure.
How can this happen?
Auntie, is Grandpa Beard
my real grandpa?
Yes, you're right.
He's your mommy's dad.
Does this mean
I found both my grandma and grandpa?
Yes.
No way.
- Good for you, Eun Chong.
- Yes.
So, why is Grandma sick?
She's getting a rest
after working too much until now.
She'll get up
after she gets a good sleep.
When?
You should
pray for her quick recovery.
Yes, if you pray hard,
she'll wake up very quickly.
I'll pray every single day.
Honey.
Did I do...
both you and Ji Seok wrong?
Did the things I did
to atone for my sins...
only end up hurting you two?
She had a cardiac arrest?
Is she in bad condition?
What are the chances
of her waking up?
Yes, all right.
Your aunt had a cardiac arrest.
I don't think she'll make it.
Shouldn't you go there
and check on her condition?
What if she suddenly wakes up?
I'll take over her hospital room.
It makes me shudder to think about
how I got kicked out yesterday.
Who does he think he is
to kick me out?
Tell me about it.
Do you have a plan?
I kept the divorce paper
to use in times like these.
I felt so sore all around
trying to rack my brains for once.
This feels much better.
My gosh!
Darn it. I didn't order any food.
What do you want?
Wait, that was a massage chair?
These days, what looks pretty
performs the best, too,
- just like me.
- That's not important right now.
I saw Ha Na and Eun Chong together
while delivering food.
What? Darn it.
I can't let Ha Na do this.
Yes, let's have
a serious talk with her.
Lead the way. We're going home.
Okay.
Hey, you told me to lead the way.
Yes, right.
Did you have fun with Eun Chong?
My gosh.
How can you do this?
You already know
why our parents passed away.
How can you want to see him?
- I'm sorry.
- You're sorry?
That means you'll see him again.
Ha Na, will it be us or Eun Chong?
Make your choice.
Wait, are you choosing Eun Chong?
- No.
- Then, what?
Chairwoman Shin...
fell unconscious.
What are you talking about?
She's unconscious?
- Stop lying.
- I'm not lying.
That was why I took Eun Chong
to the hospital.
Are you serious?
Ji Seok.
Have a seat here.
Jeez.
You didn't pick up your phone.
Were you drinking alone?
I heard about Mr. Han.
I wasn't as shocked as you,
but I was still surprised.
He was Eun Chong's grandfather?
He's also our new landlord.
That was why we didn't have to move.
I was so mad and dumbfounded, too.
How can he hide something like that?
I'll tell him to leave right away.
He'll go back to the chairwoman's place
or something.
Ha Na.
Do you think...
my revenge had any significance?
Of course, it did.
You awoke the chairwoman.
And you paid her back a little
for our parents' unjust death,
though not completely.
"A little?"
I got revenge on my enemy...
with my enemy's help.
What am I doing?
It wasn't your fault.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Sometimes, fate throws things
that are out of our control.
I heard you tried
to take your own life in America,
and Mr. Han saved you at that time.
I say that's more than enough.
I'm sure our parents will
think the same way.
He saved you.
What more could Mom and Dad want?
I don't know...
what to do.
Everything is such a mess.
It all feels like a nightmare.
It's okay.
Hold your head up as you go to work.
And put this on.
What? I really wanted this.
It works perfectly with my skin.
- How do I look?
- You look radiant.
Is it because that's made of caviar?
Do not lose heart
even when you're at work.
I'll hold my head up high
and walk into her hospital room.
Will Uncle Sung Ho let you in?
Yes, that should be enough...
to crush his spirit.
So, they had that kind of story
back in America.
It sounds like fate.
If you put it like that,
I guess it seems so.
I think time will take care of them.
They seem to have
a father-son relationship.
Actually, I'm a bit jealous.
Can you tell me
about your father later?
My dad?
I have a lot to share
from down memory lane.
Then, let's make a bet
on how many memories we can share.
I know I'll win.
Me, too.
Let me share a secret.
"A secret?"
Do I have to be nervous?
It's about the disappearance
of Eun Chong's mom.
Oh, that.
Tell me.
I lived in Seongbuk Port
when I was ten.
- Did you?
- I ran into two girls from Seoul...
at the port on the day before
we met at the hospital.
And were the girls
Se Young and Eun Chong's mom?
Probably.
I saw one girl's face.
A few days ago, I ran into Du Na,
who had lost her memories.
If you're correct,
the one you saw back then
must be Se Young.
Yes.
But that isn't evidence to prove
she's involved in the disappearance.
I do want to check with her, though.
I don't think
she'll give you an answer,
but you should still ask.
- Ms. Yoon, are you okay?
- Are you okay?
Of course.
I just did as my superior told me.
Your superior?
Which one of your superiors?
Do I have to state the obvious?
- Right. Chairwoman Shin.
- Chairwoman Shin.
You've reached Hyesung Hotel,
Travel Service Department.
All right.
Ms. Yoon, you're wanted
at the investigation room again.
Again?
What will you use this time
to get me involved?
You framed Chairwoman Shin
for your embezzlement.
Is that how you take advantage
of her unconsciousness?
Your family is so cold-hearted.
We didn't take advantage of her.
It's the most reasonable way.
"Reasonable?"
Then, let's unravel this
in the most reasonable way, too.
You know
where Seongbuk Port is, right?
That was random.
I lived there when I was young.
I got sent back to the home,
then met Du Na there.
So what? Did you call me here
to share your pathetic history?
But I had met Du Na
at Seongbuk Port...
before we met
at the children's home,
and you.
What are you talking about?
We never met.
I gave you a hand
when you got off the boat.
Don't you remember?
Du Na and you both got on the boat
when her hat flew away.
But why were you the only one
who got off?
Never mind if you don't remember.
Why do you care
if I remember it or not?
What does that have to do
with Yu Jin's disappearance?
Are you making up a story...
where I came up with a plan
to let her disappear?
This isn't funny.
- Is it not?
- No.
And you seeing me or whatever
can't be used as evidence.
What does that have to do with work?
Why did you call me here?
This isn't your playground.
Seeing you there
can't be used as evidence.
But I find you more suspicious
after you snapped.
She helped me get off the boat?
Be careful. It's slippery here.
Are you all right?
That girl was Ha Na?
You can't come in.
- Please leave.
- Who do you think you are?
I stayed by her side until this day.
You can't suddenly come and act like
her husband after all these years.
Think of why she had kept this.
She tried to divorce you.
Look.
(Divorce by Mutual Consent,
Yoon Sung Ho, Shin Yeo Jin)
You left her all alone
while she was in distress...
in her empty house after she lost
her daughter and her husband left.
It's ridiculous to see you
act like her husband now.
You played a part in that.
What did you say?
We would've found Yu Jin
if you didn't get in our way.
Then, I wouldn't have had to be away
from home for all those years.
What do you mean
I played a part in that?
You stayed by her side
until this day.
So, I'll be a husband from now on.
Wait, are you doing this...
to inherit her assets
when she passes away?
Do you think you can take back...
the life you abandoned 20 years ago?
Yeo Jin...
and I lived much longer together
than with you.
Why should I listen to you?
I'm Yu Jin's dad
and Yeo Jin's husband.
Is that so?
Then, let's call someone
at this hospital...
and see which one of us is
her real family.
She spent 20 years
apart from you, her husband,
but we lived every single day
of the last 20 years as a family.
Which one of us is her real family?
Both you and I don't share
a drop of blood with her anyway.
I was always there for her
whenever she needed me.
Where were you when she was...
in the darkest
and most painful place?
Her husband?
What makes me worse than you?
You only have your name on paper
as her husband!
Move aside. I have to see her.
You can't go in.
Sir.
Good. Ms. Jang, you tell him.
Between me and Sung Ho,
who's closer to Yeo Jin?
Sir.
They've located Detective Cho.
Good. Where is he?
I'll go.
The hired hands will
find him and bring him here.
Please stay with the chairwoman.
Myung Ji is acting recklessly.
Yes, it's also suspicious
that the video file...
for the CCTV in front of her place
got deleted.
I asked the house across
to find the footage,
so we'd find out soon enough.
Yes, we should
heighten the security.
Yeo Jin.
I'm here.
Do you think...
I killed Yu Jin or not?
So, why did you find that notebook?
You caused Yu Jin's
hit-and-run accident and killed her!
Everything is in here!
You're over.
Yeo Jin.
It's time for you to join Yu Jin...
before you face anything worse.
- It's me, Myung Ji.
- Where are you?
I'm getting chased right now.
I told you to go to New Zealand.
Why didn't you do that?
Leave the country now.
Find a ship to stow away.
Myung Ji,
can you send me some money?
Lay low.
And send me the list
of Yeo Jin's assets first.
My friend will reach out
and have it delivered to you.
Ha Na said she saw me
at Seongbuk Port.
How did she see you?
She lived there...
until she was sent back
to the children's home.
Nothing would change
even if she saw you.
I don't know.
She doesn't have evidence,
but I know she's suspicious
of you and me, Mom.
There's nothing to be suspicious of.
She wouldn't know
I instigated the hit-and-run accident.
Bye.
You came to work.
I thought you'd take a leave.
Why should I?
The sponsor
who helped you get your revenge...
turned out to be her husband.
That would've broken you.
Your revenge is over,
but it probably doesn't seem like it.
So, you should continue.
This time, take down
both my aunt and uncle.
Do you...
still get nightmares?
What nightmares?
I always held you in my arms...
whenever you had those dreams.
Don't you remember
everything you told me in my arms?
- What did I say?
- Words you kept quiet for 20 years.
That was what you said.
No, it looks like
you're the one having nightmares.
All right.
How much did I tell him?
How much does he remember?
Real estate assets...
and everything in her bank.
(Transfer of Ownership)
(Trustee: Goo Ha Na)
What?
(Trustee: Lee Eun Chong)
(Original Book of Trust,
Trustee: Lee Eun Chong)
She entrusted everything...
to Lee Eun Chong
and the Goo siblings?
When did she do this?
"Entrusted on March 1st, 2025?"
She didn't leave a penny...
to me or Se Young?
I will...
end that woman's life.
The doctor wants to see
Ms. Shin's guardian.
Sure.
Ms. Jang,
can you come to her hospital room?
How can you do this to me?
I served you for 20 years,
yet you didn't leave me a penny.
Well, you leave me no choice.
I must take your grandson,
whom you love so dearly.
So, it's time for you to go.
You'd be better off
by your beloved daughter's side...
than being stuck here
on the hospital bed.
But you know,
we've been through
thick and thin together,
so let me help you take
that one last breath.
You brought this upon yourself.
Farewell.
(Cinderella Game)
They probably found out
it was me by now.
She had a cardiac arrest.
I honestly can't trust you,
Myung Ji.
Her respirator had come off.
How did that come off?
I'll be fine if there's no evidence
that I was in her hospital room.
I saw you at the hospital yesterday.
So what if you saw me?
Mr. Han was arrested
without a warrant.
There was a witness.
I'm getting framed.
Go ahead and try to stop me.
I won't let anyone stand in my way.