Wataru?
I...
I should probably head home...
- Let's go.
- Okay.
We're here.
Huh?
My place.
Come on.
Come on in.
Excuse me.
It's just a temporary place,
but if you're willing to move in,
I'm happy to find a better spot.
You really don't give up, do you?
I prefer the term "persistent."
What's wrong? Come inside.
Aren't you staying for dinner?
I am.
Then get in here.
Welcome home.
Thanks for having me.
Yeah.
"Countdown To Yes"
(Episode 6)
Nice room.
Wait, I took this photo, didn't I?
Yeah.
Just how much do you love my work?
A lot.
Huh?
Looking at them brings it all back.
The sound of the waves that day...
and the smell of the fireworks.
I really love your photos, Wataru.
Let's see who can keep their
sparkler going the longest.
You're on.
(September 26, 2017)
Is this good?
Don't move.
Okay, perfect.
Go, go, go! Yes, yes, yes!
There we go.
Once I develop today's photos,
I'm going to hang them up too.
Can I have your roll of film, Minato?
I'll take it back and develop it.
He lets you use the darkroom?
The manager said it's a perk of the job.
Your manager is a saint...
Right?
Today was so much fun.
Go wash your hands.
- Okay.
- Over here.
Oh, you got a new shampoo.
The one you bought
before was pricey, right?
I like the kind that makes my hair soft.
So soft and smooth.
Stop touching it, you'll get it wet.
Is your face turning red?
It's just my allergies.
Dry skin.
I win!
The longer you gargle, the better.
No, the first one to finish wins!
Oh, bean sprouts.
Wataru, do you still burn them?
I do not burn them, thank you very much.
You used to.
How long ago was that?
Back when we first moved in together.
When we were 18.
(June 1, 2018)
Liar, I know they're bitter.
We're 26 now.
I'm still 25.
You're younger than me.
Show some respect.
- Cheers.
This reminds me of my birthday.
I know what you mean.
(December 21, 2019)
- Cheers. - Cheers.
We have to celebrate
our 10th year together too.
The 10th year...
25 years old?
Hey, will we still be together then?
Shut up, idiot.
Slow down, you're drinking too fast.
Want some water?
Yeah.
Even in our 10th year,
I'll still be by your side.
Ten years.
It went by in a flash.
They say your 30s go by even faster.
Ten years from now... we'll be 35.
By then, we'll have known
each other for 20 years.
We'll have spent over
half our lives together.
But we had that three-year gap.
Huh?
The three years after graduation.
That doesn't really
count as being "together."
It counts.
We didn't even see each other.
When work got busy,
I'd always talk to this guy.
(March 20, 2022)
The one I made?
What, were you lonely?
I really love this thing.
I'd pretend it was you
and tell it everything.
So it wasn't really a gap.
What?
Thanks to him, I was able to
work hard on making good yogurt.
Do you have any of your yogurt left?
It's from the factory where I used to work.
That's a lot of dairy.
This one.
"Yogurt from the Land of
More Cows Than People."
That's a great name.
It's really good.
I want some too.
Good, right?
I hate to admit it, but it's delicious.
Hate to admit it?
It's because of this yogurt
that you were stolen away to the north.
You...
You chose yogurt over photography.
Why does it have to be one or the other?
Because that's just how it is.
Haven't you heard the saying?
"If you chase two rabbits,
you'll catch neither."
Neither?
If you want something,
you have to make a choice.
And at that moment, Minato,
you chose yogurt.
Right?
I wanted to make yogurt my career.
See?
But photography is important too.
I still take photos, and I still love it.
They're both important to me.
Eating this much yogurt
can't be good for you.
Too much of anything is bad.
That goes for everything.
Maybe you should quit yogurt for a while.
Quitting only makes me
crave it more. I've tested it.
You tried?
I'm not talking about yogurt.
I'm talking about you.
- Huh?
I'm not even done with dinner,
and everything tastes like sugar.
There's no added sugar in this.
It's sweet enough for me.
Huh.
Whoa, Minato, you're fast.
Ready?
- 9, 8, 7...
- 6.
5! I win.
What? I lost again?
I'm out of interesting stories to tell.
Then tell me what you've been
up to for the past three years.
What I've been doing?
Just taking photos.
Whether I was working or off the clock.
I want to see.
This was from Shioiri's wedding shoot.
They look so happy.
Oh, the manager...
This is his son.
I call him Big Bro.
"Big Bro..."
Nice to meet you.
The day I took my first client's photo...
it finally felt like photography was
my job. I kept this as a memento.
That's so cool.
Right?
You should just make a
living from photography too.
What if we opened a studio together?
That sounds nice.
A huge studio right by the ocean.
But then you disappeared.
I won't disappear again.
We'll see about that.
Being apart made me realize...
that being with you
is when I'm truly happy.
(September 4, 2015)
Yokoi Minato.
Yeah?
What is it?
You called my name.
The first time you called me by my name...
Wait, did you take this?
I absolutely love your photos.
Ever since you said you liked my work,
I've been so happy.
(September 16, 2015)
Whoa!
Don't get it on me!
Give me a sip.
- Hey, I bought that! Why'd you drink first?
- My mom's gonna kill me.
Want to see?
I love them.
I love your photos, Wataru.
Man, I'm so happy.
When I'm with you,
I can actually feel my heart beating.
(August 6, 2019)
You're so cute.
I want to stay with you like this forever.
That's what I was thinking.
(March 19, 2022)
It's freezing.
It's still so cold.
I couldn't believe
I was actually leaving you.
So...
That's why I said you
were the one who left.
When I decided to come back,
all I wanted was to live with you again.
Me too.
When I'm with you,
I can't help but feel the same way.
I'm so glad.
I wish it could stay like this forever.
- Then...
- We can live together.
Just like back in college.
Easy and fun.
- That's not what I meant...
- Enough.
Stop playing with semantics.
I'm not. I'm serious.
I don't get it.
Why are you so obsessed
with being "boyfriends"?
Why can't we just go back to how it was?
We're best friends.
Isn't that enough?
I love you.
And you love me.
Being a couple wouldn't
be a problem at all.
Nothing would have to change.
It would change.
Like how? Tell me.
Forget it.
Actually, I'm over it.
What?
I don't love you anymore.
I'm done with that.
Being best friends is for the best.
It's the happiest we can be.
What we have right now...
is perfect.
This is enough.
How do you know it couldn't be better?
We haven't even tried.
Okay, I win.
Wataru.
Shower. I'm going to take a shower.
I'm tired.
What is even going on...
What was that?
Minato...
He's acting different.
He doesn't smell like he usually does.
Get it together.
Minato is a friend...
Minato is just a friend.
I don't love him.
There's only one bed.
Dammit, I didn't think this through.
What's up?
That was a fast shower.
I'm always fast.
Oh, the pillow...
I meant to go buy one.
I'll sleep on the floor.
Why?
It's too cramped for two.
I don't even have a spare blanket.
- It's fine, really...
- No, it's not.
I'll sleep on the floor.
You take the bed.
No, no, no, absolutely not.
The host sleeping on
the floor? That's weird.
Are you...
mad at me?
You smell like my house.
- Does that mean I win?
- Not a chance.
What's that?
Toner.
Since when do you use that stuff?
When I was in Hokkaido,
my face got all dry and cracked like yours.
It hurt so much.
Does it sting?
No...
You just startled me.
Once you use this,
your face won't hurt even in winter.
I highly recommend it for your dry skin.
Oh.
So bouncy.
It'll be even better
once I put on the lotion.
Surprised?
It's soaking in...
Wait, really?
Sorry.
It's you... you've soaked into my heart.
What?
What does that even mean?
Back then...
I didn't actually want to leave.
Before I moved out of the apartment,
on that last night,
we slept on the floor together, remember?
Oh, yeah.
I remember that.
It was freezing.
Because you packed all the blankets away.
You could've just done it in the morning.
You didn't stop me, so it's your fault too.
That was the first time I couldn't sleep.
And that's when
I realized I loved you.
I thought I'd eventually
forget once we were apart.
But I didn't.
Me too...
I couldn't sleep that night either.
Because you were leaving.
I hated it.
Can we do what we couldn't do back then?
I told you, I'm over it.
Can I kiss you?
You can...
I wish morning would never come.
(Next Episode)
Wataru...
Minato and I...
Are you two moving in together again?
Why are you deciding things on your own?
I don't want to. It's not a good idea.
Then why did you say I could kiss you?