[Kim Nurim]
[Lee Sun]
[Jang Yeonwoo]
[Yoo Habok]
[Let the Curse of Taekwondo Be Free]
Do you not blog on Cyworld?
Cyworld?
No.
Have you watched "Temptation of Wolves"?
What is that?
You don't have a phone or use the Internet.
Are there no theaters here?
I told you not to look down on Haseong.
But there's no theater here.
[Learn etiquette and taekwondo]
What are you doing?
Huh?
You punk!
Goodness.
Your legs are so weak.
No matter what it is, the basics are key.
Did you do 500 squats every day?
I...
didn't do 500.
Always slacking off.
Do it every day. Check every day.
100 roundhouse kicks a day. Got it?
Yes.
[Let the Curse of Taekwondo Be Free]
324!
350.
500!
Do it properly.
I think you skipped a few.
Just three.
498!
499!
500.
Enjoy your dinner.
Do you call your mom often?
Of course. I call every day.
Enjoy the food, Grandmaster.
Bring some kimchi.
Kimchi?
Come to think of it,
I think it's my first time eating with you.
I don't want him to feel uncomfortable.
Come on. It's great if we can eat together often.
Have a proper sparring session next week.
Sparring with Lee Dohoe
is the best test of your skills.
When he was in middle school, even athletes got nervous
going up against him in national competitions.
[Award Certificate]
If you can beat him,
[First place: Lee Dohoe]
you can basically beat anyone.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Is Ha Hyeonho doing well?
Yes.
I heard he's very obedient at home,
but he's so stubborn like his father.
Just like you,
happy-go-lucky kids are the ones who live well.
As the saying goes, even monkeys fall from trees.
If someone like him fails, he'll never recover.
So charismatic.
Dry off before you come out. Don't get water everywhere.
Watering the plants?
Yeah.
Hey.
My abs are defined after exercising.
What do you think?
Look.
It's better under the light.
What are you doing?
Feel my thigh.
It's harder. Touch it.
-Touch it.
-What are you doing?
Just touch it. It's no big deal.
Gosh.
-Get out. Get out!
-It's so cold!
Hey.
You might've forgotten this because you're dense,
but mind your own business.
While you're here, just do what you need to.
Don't pretend to be nice and do nice things.
Seriously. Is he a pervert?
Why should I touch him?
So annoying.
Yes, Mom.
I had to go outside to pick up the phone.
Dinner?
Of course I've eaten.
I eat regularly every day.
Trouble?
I'm not causing any trouble.
I heard he gets good grades.
I'll go in after the call.
Great weather here. It's not cold.
I get hot easily anyway.
Yes. Yes.
I told you making breakfast is my duty.
It's ready, so stop arguing and just eat it.
I made yours
specially for you.
I told you your parents paid us a lot.
Just accept it. Ask for classes when you want.
If...
you get beat up or wronged,
call your parents right away.
I know what to do.
Just have your breakfast.
Yesterday...
I think... I was too harsh.
I'm sorry if I hurt you.
It's okay.
Wait, even so,
I'm not asking you to be nosy.
And don't cook again.
This is what I should do.
What's wrong with making my own food?
Just make sure you stock up on groceries.
Did you cook for the person
who stayed here before me?
Of course. Who else would do it?
Just take care of your meals today.
I'll be home late.
Why?
Why are you so surprised?
You're always studying. Where else can you go?
I told you I'll move out soon.
Are you looking for a place to stay?
It's not that.
I don't know.
I'll move out once the vacation starts.
You should think about it too.
Who drew this?
[Teaching etiquette and taekwondo]
One, two, three!
Here I come!
Hey!
I need to train.
Aren't you going home?
Just do it. We'll play a bit longer.
Don't worry about us.
We're not done playing.
I can't train with you kids
running around me!
We'll be alone if we go home.
So we've to go home late.
Why do you think we take lessons here?
What do you want to play?
-Dodgeball!
Come in, you bastards.
Dodgeball! Dodgeball!
-Come in.
-Hey.
Come on. Gather around.
If you don't want to be beat up in front of the kids...
-Come in now.
-Who wants some ice cream?
-Me!
Come here.
Hang on.
Now you're taking money from the kids...
Buy yummy ones from the store.
Okay? Can you do it?
-Yes.
-Go on.
-Thank you.
You're asking for it.
What will you be when you grow up?
Hooligans?
So what if that happens?
-It's none of your business.
-None of my business?
How dare you glare at me?
You deserve a beating.
You're dead today.
-Bastard.
-Grandmaster!
Um...
Since they said they won't do it again...
They might take it out on Dohoe.
Damn it, Dohoe!
Behave and come with us.
This is a roundhouse kick in taekwondo!
I'll give you a taste too.
Take my punches too.
Bastard!
Hyeonho, show him.
Damn it.
What's wrong?
Why did you stop?
Have a go at it!
Do it!
It's enough.
Why?
If we go on,
his dad will kill us.
Since we've started, let's go all the way.
Yeah. What is this?
Damn it.
If you tell your dad, you're dead.
Just tell him you fell down.
Got it?
Damn it.
Back then...
there were many things I didn't understand.
Hey.
Let's go.
Hang in there.
I'm coming.
Come on.
How could you collapse?
He fell at the back.
You should have held on.
Is it because we're in puberty?
Are you okay?
What now?
You on attack again?
Yeah, one more round.
-We have to go again.
-Come on.
One more round, Hyeonho.
Let's change the order.
-I'm done.
-One more round.
Damn it.
What's wrong?
-Huh?
-What's wrong with him?
-I don't know.
-Did we say something wrong?
I didn't think a close friend
would suddenly become the one I hate the most.
And a stranger that I thought I couldn't be friends with...
I thought you weren't coming back today.
Actually became someone close.
Life's full of...
things I don't understand.
Hey.
What's wrong?
What happened?
Did someone beat you up?
Hey, hey!
Who did it?
Did those bastards hit you?
Why are you covered in dirt?
Gosh.
Can I make it?
Everything seems to be cursed.
I want to...
get out of this place.
You're smart, and you work so hard.
You can do anything.
Anything you want.
The ice cream must've melted.
[Datull ice cream]
It's winter now.
I'm sure it hasn't melted.
Let's go home. I'll help you apply ointment.
Slowly.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Hey.
If they hit you again, tell the teacher.
You said that was cowardly.
That's the best way.
Do you really not need my help?
I said I don't.
Apply it carefully.
Okay.
It said it'd snow, but there's just rain.
It doesn't snow much here.
Really?
I heard it snowed a lot in Seoul.
Even if it snows, it's super light.
Then...
You've never seen the ground filled with snow?
Nope.
I wish it'd snow a lot.
I want to step on the snow,
have snowball fights,
and make a snowman.
Okay, I'll be right there.
Another errand?
Mm.
Want me to go with you?
Forget it.
Just eat your ice cream.
Hey, hey. Wait. Hang on.
The garlic ice cream is really good.
I promise you've never tasted it before. Try it.
Ah.
Your saliva.
Gosh.
Ah.
Isn't it good?
Mm.
You have a spoon there. Eat with yours.
What's wrong?
Wow. So yummy.
It's so good.
You said it's cold, but you keep eating ice cream.
I'll go with you.
Wait for me.
What are you doing?
Huh?
Taking a walk.
-Is this walking?
-Yeah.
Hey, it's cold. You should run too.
I'm not running because it's cold.
I'm so warm after running that I can't see my breath.
It stinks!
What did you say?
Hey, what is this?
I made this snow. Look.
-Isn't it like real snow?
-Wow.
It's so real!
Here. Look.
I made this too.
-You made it?
-Yeah.
-No way.
-I searched online for this and that
and made this and that all by myself...
[Dohoe Taekwondo]
Are you not going to attack?
Let's stop here.
You're so stubborn.
Hey, Lee Dohoe.
Let's talk.
What is it?
Why did you go easy on me again?
Do you still think that I'm not even worth competing with?
I told you I don't like taekwondo.
But you could spar properly for my sake.
Did you have to make a fool out of me?
Isn't it good that you won?
No.
I wanted to have a fair competition.
I want to know if I'm doing well and making progress.
If I beat you, I could proudly tell my parents
that I'm doing well.
Did you get hit or injured?
What do you mean?
You were in pain when I barely kicked you.
Your steps were way worse than usual.
Let me see.
-Hey.
-Let me see.
What are you doing? Are you crazy?
-Stop it.
-Hey!
-Just listen.
What are you thinking?
Come to your senses.
You think too much.
What do you think I'm thinking?
I'm an athlete.
I don't just spar with you.
It's normal for me to get bruises.
Also, all athletes get disciplined.
-It happens to everyone!
-So?
Did you get hit?
That's not what I meant.
So you got hit.
Hey.
Why would I get hit?
I'm a crybaby.
If I got hit, I'd have made a scene and called my parents.
Don't go easy on me because of your ridiculous
misunderstanding.
I worked really hard to beat you.
I want to be praised for doing well too.
Hey. Seriously, what's wrong with you?
Should I bring you proof? What do you want me to do?
I don't want to care.
I'm already drained from this and that.
I don't want to have to care about if someone's beating you up.
Did I ask you to?
You said you don't want to go pro.
Then just take it easy and leave when you're done.
Don't act tough and take beatings
just because you're an athlete.
No matter how stupid you are, you should know better.
Back then...
things I couldn't understand kept happening to me too.
I was so dense,
but why did I feel like I understood Lee Dohoe whenever he got angry?
I'm sorry.
I just don't understand.
Hitting someone...
It's ridiculous.
That winter... was filled with enigmas.
Are you asleep?
I'm sorry.
I like you.
I really care about you too.
Lee Dohoe!
Come out, you bastard!
Because you hate your dad,
you even gave up your passion of taekwondo.
Come out!
Come out now!
-Grandmaster.
-Who's this?
He keeps going on about Seoul. Take him with you.
What? Want to talk back?
Okay, come here.
Are you so eager to get to Seoul?
Speak up.
Answer me!
Stop it.
I told you not to speak like you're from Seoul.
Are you protesting?
Are you protesting to me to follow your mom?
Not answering again?
But you can't leave. What can you do?
I said you can't leave.
Your mom was always like that.
She never kept her promises.
She never planned to keep her promises!
I told you to stop.
How dare you glare at me, you bastard?
Mom...
became happy after she left us.
I actually prefer this.
Because she won't have to come back to this hole anymore.
You're really asking for it.
Hey, come here.
No, Grandmaster.
You bastard.
-Let's talk after you sober up.
-Come here!
You should've given me some time to get dressed.
Yeah.
It's so cold.
Damn. It.
Say that again.
Curse again.
Are you a pervert?
Give me a cigarette.
Do you have one?
Cigarettes?
Are you kidding me, kid?
Now you want to curse and smoke?
What a joke.
Just now...
You misunderstood.
I really got hurt during a sparring session.
I didn't get hit.
Hey.
Here... Here?
Then what?
Can we do it at home?
Well... no.
Forget it. Go away.
You're such a bummer.
Should we go down there?
Kiss at the underpass?
Who'd kiss at a underpass?
Is that so?
What about the pavilion over there?
It looks nice.
It's kind of... cold here too.
We should've stopped by the house.
I... like it.
I didn't say I don't.
It's warm.
Um... What... What should I do?
I'll... tilt to the right.
-To the right...
-Yeah.