[Falling Into You]
[Adapted from the novel "Blazing Trail" by Twentine]
[Episode 22]
[Jiangzhou: 2017 National Athletics Championships]
They are here, too.
The taller one
is Wei Lai, last year's pole vault champion.
The strongest one is Big Xia's teammate.
I've seen his game before.
You look more nervous than the contestants.
Of course.
That is part of the job of a coach,
unlike you.
"A coach"?
More like the job of a girlfriend.
Relax. This is just the Nationals.
If he makes it to the international games,
will you have a heart attack?
If he can make it,
I'll admit to it.
[2017 National Athletics Championships]
- How are your feet? Are you done warming up?
- All good.
Ladies and Gentlemen, welcome to the game.
Is Cai Li Qiu your target?
You may have a chance.
But I don't think I'll reach his score.
Is he guided by Coach Cai now?
Didn't you know? Cai Li Qiu is Coach Cai's nephew.
At school, Coach Cai talks about him every day...
every day.
- I got tired of hearing his name.
- The athletes will be ranked...
according to the total score of ten individual events.
Hello, everyone, welcome to the twenty-second
National Athletics Championships.
Coming next is the men's decathlon.
The decathlon is a combined event consisting of
ten track and field events,
[2017 National Athletics Championships]
including running, jumping, and throwing.
In the second track, it is Cai Li Qiu, an active athlete on our national team.
He is a two-time decathlon champion in the Nationals Championships
and a two-time runner-up of the National Games.
He is believed to be the favorite of this game.
Standing on the fourth track is Duan Yu Cheng, a new decathlon athlete from South Lake.
He may be new to the game, but in the earlier National University Games,
he had excellent results.
He is also very active and handsome.
Let's wish him good results in this competition.
You got this!
[All Out Effort to Challenge the Best Performance]
It must be a camerawoman.
She keeps focusing on the handsome one.
Your boyfriend has been in the frame for a while.
Handsome and capable, I'd focus on someone like that, too.
The men's 100 meters is about to start.
Let's wait and see.
[2017 National Athletics Championships]
- You can do it!
On your marks.
In the first group of 100 meters are many high-level athletes.
Two outstanding athletes from South Lake, Duan Yu Cheng and Zhang Bo,
as well as the all-around athlete, the two-time Nationals champion, Cai Li Qiu,
are all in this group.
They are in adjacent tracks.
Get set.
The race starts.
Cai Li Qiu on the second track and Duan Yu Cheng on the fourth track
started a fierce competition in the first single event.
They are now neck and neck.
Cai Li Qiu took the lead
in crossing the finish line.
Cai Li Qiu, 10.72 seconds.
[Men's 100 Meters Final]
Competing in the Nationals for the first time, the new all-around athlete, Duan Yu Cheng,
ranks second in this group. He is on fire today.
Now, Duan Yu Cheng's total score has reached 1540,
ranks first.
Cheer him on now.
[Men's Decathlon Finals. No. 3. Duan Yu Cheng, 2205]
Cai Li Qiu's superiority
[Men's 400 Meters Finals]
in stamina and throwing events is shown.
[Men's Decathlon Finals No. 4. Duan Yu Cheng, 2950]
[Duan Yu Cheng]
The audience likes him.
Of course.
With his current performance, he'll most likely make it into the national team.
Do you think so?
Handsome and strong,
that meets the promotional standards.
Besides, this is the decathlon.
How many who specialize in 100 meters can get results better than 10.8 seconds?
I can!
I can.
Go away.
♫ The pulse, I feel it ♫
♫ It's here, believe it ♫
The high jump was Duan Yu Cheng's special event in the college team.
Now, this is his first jump with a crossbar height of 2.20 meters.
[2.20 Meters]
♫ We're front and center ♫
♫ We're part of something bigger than ourselves ♫
♫ Everybody, on your feet ♫
♫ And breathe in the moment ♫
♫ Put your hand to your heart ♫
♫ As we all come together ♫
Approach run,
start of J-Curve,
takeoff,
a very long takeoff distance.
Absolutely confident.
Succeeded in the first jump.
The success of this jump helps pull his score
further away from other competitors.
Way to go, Brat.
You pulled off 2.2 meters.
The 2.2 meters is about the best result
of the national team's high jumpers.
It will take him to the leading position
among the domestic decathlon athletes.
♫ Put your hand to your heart ♫
♫ As we all come together ♫
♫ Everybody, on your feet ♫
Coach.
Good job.
With 4000 points, you rank first now.
What is it?
Can't good results make you happy?
In the 400 meters,
I didn't do well in the last part.
That was, by far, your best result. What more do you want?
My best events are all on the first day,
but I have only about 50 points more than Cai Li Qiu.
What are you trying to say here?
Are you thinking about winning the gold medal?
Shouldn't I?
You brat,
good for you.
I heard you made rapid progress recently.
I'm okay.
Mao Mao Qi is truly amazing though.
He is now competing in international games.
He doesn't even bother to come to the Nationals.
He's such a high achiever.
And you?
How is it?
Who?
You and Duan Yu Cheng, of course.
How did you know about it?
What?
It's so embarrassing.
Why? You two make a good couple.
I thought you'd be together long ago.
Really?
Maybe you two are surrounded by an aura.
Isn't Jiang Tian also younger than you?
Four years younger.
Don't you think the younger ones are nice?
They indeed are.
They are considerate.
They are obedient.
Young and energetic.
By the way,
I saw the national team decathlon coach today.
I suppose he came to see Duan Yu Cheng.
- Really?
- Yes.
Most likely.
Tell him to give his all.
Otherwise, Cai Li Qiu wouldn't have tried so hard.
I guess he is trying to beat Duan Yu Cheng with his results.
Doesn't he want Duan Yu Cheng to join the national team?
Of course not.
Only three people can win medals.
All athletes must fight hard for a position
in the national or international games.
Who'd want such a strong opponent as Duan Yu Cheng?
And I heard that this time,
the sponsor wants to shoot an advertisement
with a less popular event, to promote an unknown grassroots character.
Now both men's and women's decathlon are possible choices.
If you were a sponsor,
with Duan Yu Cheng and Cai Li Qiu before you,
who would you pick?
It's too early to discuss that.
We should focus on the game now.
[Jiangzhou: 2017 National Athletics Championships. Day Two]
Among the events today, javelin is your best event.
Take good advantage of it.
In other events,
you can reserve some physical strength.
Save it to fight for the 1,500 meters.
Give me a signal if you hear me.
It'll be her birthday soon.
Who?
- My girlfriend.
- Oh. What?
When did you get a girlfriend?
How come I didn't know?
Have you reported it to the team?
Has Director Wang approved?
We've dated a while.
I'll introduce her to you when I get the chance.
Bye.
Good luck to me.
[All Out Effort to Challenge the Best Performance]
Ladies and Gentlemen,
2017 National Athletics Championships,
the men's 100 meters final.
You can do it!
[Men's 100 Meters]
Li Ge, you got this.
- You can do it!
What are you doing?
Can you please man up?
Athletes, stand up.
- You can do it!
On your marks,
get set.
The game begins.
Focus on acceleration.
The fifth track.
The athlete accelerated after 40 meters and is ahead of other competitors.
Nice rhythm.
He continues extending his lead.
[Men's 100 Meters Final]
Li Ge from South Lake crossed the line first.
Li Ge just won the first gold medal
of this Nationals for South Lake Province.
The camera is now on his coach Wu Ze,
who was on the national team ten years ago.
His best result was 10.28 seconds.
And today,
he changed his role to a coach
and trained a good disciple for his hometown.
[Men's 100 Meters: Li Ge, No.1]
His disciple is now a champion.
His dream of winning
a gold medal in the Nationals is fulfilled.
The greatest joy and glory of this moment
belongs to Coach Wu Ze.
The first place.
The first place, yes!
Look.
[Striving to Forge Ahead to Create Brilliance]
Coach Luo.
I believe you know why I'm here today.
Can we talk somewhere else?
Sure.
The ninth event of the men's decathlon,
javelin, has ended.
Decathlon Athletes, please have a short break.
In forty minutes,
the last event of
1,500 meters will begin.
Please just cut to the chase.
Director Wang told me that you went to him.
Actually, you could have come to me directly.
Are you trying to reprimand me?
I didn't say anything to Director Wang.
I know that everything you said was reasonable.
Duan Yu Cheng just became a professional athlete.
Having a relationship now will distract him.
I won't try to find excuses for myself.
I do like him.
I also understand
this is hard for you to accept.
So if you have any requests,
you can just be frank with me.
Fine. I want you to...
I'll try to follow your instructions
apart from breaking up with him.
Then what's the point of discussion?
Auntie...
Sister, calm down, please.
We can discuss this nicely.
I'm sure we can find solutions.
In fact, I already noticed it
when you came to my house.
That's not right,
when we had the barbecue.
I knew something was wrong with him.
If so, you knew before I did?
You found it out so early.
Why didn't you stop him then?
What a pity.
Are you blaming me now?
That's not what you think at all.
You promised me that you
would do only what's good for him.
That's right.
Is this what's good for him?
Is it not?
You are older than him.
Isn't your husband eight years older than you?
That's different.
He is a man, and you're a woman.
Men and women should be equal.
The average life span of women is longer than men's.
I'm a bit older than him.
Then maybe when we get old,
we can die...
Are you talking about my son's death already?
No, no.
That's not what I meant.
I mean
that women older than men
and men older than women
are actually the same thing.
I disapprove.
I disapprove of your relationship.
Let's put your ages aside.
Just like you said,
now is the critical moment of Xiao Cheng's career.
A relationship will affect him in a bad way.
I understand your worries,
but I promise that I will not...
What are you doing?
Didn't I tell you not to talk to her alone?
I'm asking you what you're doing.
Did you leave the middle of the game?
Right, the game isn't over yet, is it?
Haven't I told you...
Duan Yu Cheng!
What?
Do you know how important this competition is?
I can't believe you left the game
for such a trivial matter!
This isn't a trivial matter.
Mom, please be quiet.
Break up.
Let's break up now.
Break up?
Why... why do you want to break up with me?
You dare ask me why.
Get back to the game right now!
Why are you yelling at my son?
Mom, can you stop talking now? I am...
If you can't reach 7400 points,
I won't see you ever again!
Will 7300 do?
Enough talking!
- Luo Na, you two...
- I...
It starts now.
He did well at Javelin.
[Javelin. Duan Yu Cheng: 66 m]
It exceeded our expectations.
There is only the 1,500 meters left.
Will he reach 7400 points?
To 7400?
The 1,500 meters is not his specialty.
To get 7400 points,
he must finish the run within four minutes.
His best result so far
was 4.12 minutes.
What does it mean?
You want him to aim for the medals.
We can have dreams.
Interesting.
You two are very much alike.
However,
games aren't like training and not up to us.
Dreams won't help you.
You can do it.
[Men's 1,500 Meters]
In the final 100 meters,
all athletes are giving their best.
Come on! Come on!
Cai Li Qiu took the lead in crossing the line
and won his third Nationals.
He took home the championship.
[No. 2, Duan Yu Cheng, 4:09.06]
Duan Yu Cheng and Zhang Bo arrived right after him.
Please, 7,400 points.
I must reach 7,400 points.
Ladies and Gentlemen,
the screen will show you
the total score ranking
of athletes participating in this year's men's decathlon.
Cai Li Qiu, 7750 points.
[No. 4, Duan Yu Cheng, 7375]
He defended his title again.
Duan Yu Cheng. Duan Yu Cheng.
Duan Yu Cheng, hello.
I heard this was your first time
participating in a national competition.
You got such good results on the first try.
Are you happy with your performance?
It was okay.
You were so close to claiming a medal.
Does that leave you with some regret?
It's all right.
You did exceptionally well in the javelin throw
and won this event's first place.
Did you focus training on this event?
Not really, I was in good condition.
So I managed to throw it a bit further.
Excuse me, the athlete needs to rest.
Okay, okay.
Thank you for your time.
Hopefully, I'll see you soon.
[Lu Yao, reporter]
First time being interviewed?
Well done.
Your answers were flawless.
Only this way you prevent people from finding your faults
and exaggerating them.
Coach, why are you so happy?
You tell me.
I'm not worried you may get cocky.
Your overall performance this time
is unexpectedly good.
Yesterday, you said you want to win as champion.
I thought you were daydreaming.
But judging by your performance these two days,
it's really possible.
Perhaps, you'll be someone extraordinary one day.
But my results aren't that good, are they?
Good attitude is spot on.
Modesty makes people progress.
You did well in each individual event,
but your physical strength clearly dropped the next day.
The most important thing in decathlon games
is to allocate your physical strength.
Take Cai Li Qiu as an example.
He has a mature method of competing in decathlons.
But again,
your performance was already quite good.
- Really?
- Of course.
Very good.
Is 7375 a high score, too? Right?
Of course.
There's no need to reach 7400, right?
Who said you needed to?
Don't get too proud.
You've come this far.
You almost won a medal.
Yet you missed it when you were so close.
Don't you think it's upsetting?
Next time, Coach.
I'll win medals next time.
Thank you, Coach.
Where are you going?
To find my girlfriend.
Oh, right.
You haven't explained to me about your girlfriend. Stop right there!
Hey, Beauty.
What are you doing? Put me down.
Let go of me.
Tell me this first.
Say you were just kidding about breaking up with me.
You were just scaring me, right?
Put me down first.
I won't, unless you answer my question.
A 7375 is also a nice score. Am I right?
Yes.
I was just kidding.
The 7375 is a very nice score.
Put me down.
Hurry.
But...
but you must obey the rules.
Are you aware of your own mistakes?
How many times have I told you?
Nothing is as important as your game.
You left as soon as you threw the javelin.
You didn't even know if it was foul.
Will you fool around again?
I won't.
I was wrong.
I swear I'll change.
Right, did Director Wang find out about our relationship?
How do you know?
That's just how my mom is.
Did she say anything to you?
You should have told me first
and let me talk to her.
She didn't say much.
You'll only make things worse.
But I got a good result, didn't I?
He won't say anything about it.
You might be right.
You were only 25 points short.
There isn't any proof anyway.
You can find a way to get away with it.
What?
Give me a hug.
No.
- Why not?
- So many people are here.
Where are the people? Nobody is here.
No.
Stop.
Duan Yu Cheng,
I can't believe you said those words.
I was telling the truth.
Look how well I performed today.
That is the power of love.
Coach Yang, why don't you take a seat?
Calm down first.
Okay? Take a seat.
Here is the thing.
They all say that the castle
is destroyed from the inside.
Luo Na,
good for you.
I am your mom.
I do everything for your good.
Ha ha (what a joke).
If you did it for my good,
you wouldn't come today.
If you hadn't come,
maybe I could have performed better
and won a bronze medal.
Can you blame me for that?
You should blame her!
I disapprove.
I firmly disapprove.
Having a relationship now
will surely affect his performance.
You were coaching him for a while.
Why don't you understand him at all?
Duan Yu Cheng is the kind of athlete
who needs love to nourish him.
Only then he makes progress.
Mom,
I am really tired from the nationals.
Please give me a break.
If you approve or not,
she is your daughter-in-law.
Duan Yu Cheng, what do you mean?
Did you steal the household register and marry her?
Mom, can you come to your senses?
I can't!
Mom, Mom!
Not everyone is like you and my father
who stole the household register to get married.
You...
Who is it?
Is it your coach?
Why... why are you here?
Come home with me.
Now?
Wh-What kind of theory was that?
Duan Yu Cheng has really got into your head.
Isn't that nice?
Isn't he your favorite athlete?
Maybe you'll like me as well.
I won't talk to you anymore.
I'm going to Wang Qi Lin for an explanation.
Coach Yang, don't be angry.
If you see my point of view,
please talk to Director Wang for me.
You're beyond help!
You're completely beyond help.
Don't look at your mom.
I'll leave her to you, Dad.
Rest assured.
About the relationship,
have you made up your mind?
I really like her.
I must be with her.
That's good then.
You've grown up.
You have your own ideas.
As parents, we won't interrupt you.
Don't worry.
I'll take care your mom.
She won't disturb you.
I have no objection to your relationship with Luo Na.
But since you've decided to be with her,
you need to take on responsibilities.
Be a man.
Don't let her down.
I know.
That's all I have to say.
Take care of yourself.
Call me if you ever need something.
Okay.
I'm going.
Go back.
See you, Dad and Mom.
He is talking to you.
Don't bother me.
- Bye now.
- Drive safely.
Did your mom leave?
Yes.
She was moved by our beautiful love story.
You didn't give in, did you?
What if I did?
You can't.
If you give in, I'll...
I will lock you in this room
and have you eat takeout every day
until you promise me.
Don't worry.
I made a promise.
I will take on my responsibility.
Are you tired?
Do you want to sleep?
Not yet.
It tickles.
♫ I'd rather see the world with these eyes ♫
One more kiss.
Do you promise to behave yourself in future?
♫ This vision of sight ♫
Didn't I promise you already?
♫ And if we can ♫
♫ Cling to this ♫
♫ Before we turn to dust ♫
♫ And if we have a say in this ♫
Why are you still so energetic now?
Did you try your best in the games?
Of course, I did.
You tell me.
I got more points than Coach Yang expected, didn't I?
♫ Before we turn to dust ♫
That hurts.
You didn't win the gold medal.
Why would I need a gold medal?
If you had won the gold medal,
we might have more passion now.
What do you mean?
Do you mean from now on, when I hold you,
I must hang a medal on me to make you happy?
No medal this time.
I owe you one.
Luo Na!
Is Duan Yu Cheng in your room?
No. I... I didn't see him.
Are you sure?
Is anything wrong?
The national team coach is here to see him.
Never mind.
I'll find him elsewhere.
Hang on.
"Sunshine, Waves, You and Me" by Liu Yu Ning
♫ Sunrise captures the silhouette of the island, while shadows dance across the tides ♫
♫ The waves chase after the footprints, breathing them in ♫
♫ I want to follow you; let the sun melt the distance between us ♫
♫ I'm faltering in my steps; I won't be too greedy ♫
♫ The breeze shares with me a secret ♫
♫ You can't hide your scent from me ♫
♫ We are stuck together ♫
♫ After the heavy rain's evaporation ♫
♫ The convenience store blasts with cold air ♫
♫ But we are still sweating bullets ♫
♫ Stop checking your phone all the time ♫
♫ And pretending that you don't care about me ♫
♫ For me, summer is not just about ♫
♫ Carbonated drinks and jerseys ♫
♫ With clear and transparent courage ♫
♫ Don't stop me; I want to tell you everything ♫
♫ As long as you are here, I won't stop ♫
♫ This passion will burn forever ♫
♫ Let's sprint toward the ocean ♫
♫ The blazing waves are glistening ♫
♫ I look forward ♫
♫ To the infinite future ♫
♫ I leave everything behind except to stride with you across the sky ♫
♫ I'll give it my all to leap toward this stage ♫
♫ I look forward to the infinite future ♫
♫ You said there will be success and failure if I come to you ♫
♫ Great things come naturally ♫
♫ I look forward ♫
♫ To the infinite future ♫
♫ I leave everything behind except to stride with you across the sky ♫
♫ I'll give it my all to leap toward this stage ♫
♫ I look forward to the infinite future ♫
♫ You said there will be success and failure if I come to you ♫
♫ Great things come naturally ♫
♫ The blazing waves are glistening ♫