[All depicted events, behaviors, and names
are fictional
and for entertainment purposes only
Viewer discretion is advised]
Hey!
Who the hell are you?!
Oh, wow...
Why are you covering my face with a bag?
Just keep it on.
You have to thank me
for taking care of him this well, though.
Thank my ass.
Ouch!
It's fine if it's just that.
But you had over a thousand people
review-bombing this place
What's the deal with that?
Huh?
So we meet again.
You two know each other?
- Yes.
- No!
[The nerd]
[The villain]
[The rude guy]
[The cool one]
[The (beloved) best friend]
[The cheeky one]
[The love rival]
[Flirt Milk The Series:
Based on a novel by Arpo]
You didn't come back here with Rong?
Seriously,
what do you have against him?
Nothing.
It's a long story.
I don't wanna talk about it.
You just can't stop disliking others, can you?
You guys just don't get it.
Rong, did you ride your motorbike here?
Yes.
Can you take care of Pai?
I need to take Ten home.
Your place is pretty close to his.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
Let's go, Ten.
Get up. It's time to go home.
Come on.
God, you're so damn heavy.
- See you later.
- Take care.
Hey, you.
Hey!
Need some water?
Let's go.
Let me take you home.
Leave me.
I'm not going with you.
I'll manage myself.
Hey, you.
There are no more buses for tonight.
Whatever.
Just leave me alone.
You're waiting for your dad or something?
He's in Suphan Buri,
so he won't be here.
But if you're just gonna sit and wait here,
others may think that you're homeless.
Fuck off.
Do you dislike me or something?
No wonder why
you always bark like a dog.
I hate you so much.
Well, I didn't tell you to like me.
Right.
You might not like me now,
but maybe... you will in the future.
Huh?
Why are you still here?
I just wanna chill out here.
Got a problem?
Hey.
Are you hungry?
No.
Come on.
Let’s grab some food.
What would you like to have, boys?
I'll have a bowl of pork porridge
with everything in it, sis.
What about the person next to you, dear?
Hey.
You.
- What do you wanna have?
- Sausage porridge, no vegetables.
Another bowl of pork porridge
with everything in it.
Pork porridge?
Okay, please wait.
You said sausage porridge?
Are you good?
- Here you go, dear.
- Thank you.
Bowls of porridge and pork.
- Sorry, it's pork porridge.
- Right.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
How wonderful.
- You mean the porridge?
- You.
Aww, you're drunk.
So is he, I guess.
They paid you to study,
not to get drunk, dear.
How fantastic.
You want some?
Hey.
You're ruining the bowl.
This is how I like it, okay?
You're kinda weird.
Here's for my bowl.
Also, I'll split the bill
for pa tong go with you.
Here. Take it.
It's okay.
No, I don’t wanna owe you anything,
so just take it.
The porridge was pretty good.
I've gotta go.
Hey...
Your wallet's here.
Thank you.
Welcome. What would you like to have?
Right...
I'll have this one.
- Fried chicken? That'll be 50 baht.
- Alright.
- Please give me a minute.
- No problem.
QR code payment is also available.
- Right.
- Yes.
Where did it go?
Okay.
Here's the QR code.
Alright.
Did I leave it at that restaurant?
Nine.
What's up?
Do you have
your fraternity brother's contact?
You mean Rong's contact?
Yeah.
I'll send it to you in a second.
It's done.
What happened?
You somehow fall for him?
Fuck no.
Are you crazy?
Hey, easy now. Take it slow.
He's a cool guy, though.
Right. Thanks.
Talk to you later. See you.
- What are you doing, Korn?
- Oh.
Nom Jued.
I'm adjusting the camera settings.
I'm doing a portrait shoot.
- Really?
- Mm.
Would you like to be a model for me?
Are you sure?
Change up your pose.
One more.
There. See?
If you want some shadow cast on your subject,
simply adjust the light and attach a softbox.
It softens the lighting.
Can you notice it?
Mm.
Korn, what's that camera for?
Oh.
That's for promoting
the club's social media pages.
I think it's not a good idea.
I don't want people to take me the wrong way.
Mm, sure.
If it makes you uncomfortable,
it's totally fine.
Oh.
- You haven't picked your assignment, right?
- Mm.
Let's see what you'll get.
Oh?
You're here to borrow a camera, right?
Noey! Hello!
That's right, Korn.
You said you were gonna use
your own camera, no?
I was gonna shoot it like how I always do.
But after some consideration,
I wanna try a different camera.
Freshmen already have
a lot of work on their hands, though.
Would you like to take it slow
so that you can find your own style?
Sure thing, Korn.
That means you knew photography
since you were in high school?
Yeah.
And what's your assignment?
Can I tag along?
I still don't know
what I'll shoot for my assignment.
Mm...
No problem.
What's your photo assignment, though?
It's "Environment."
Wait, yours is similar to mine.
I got "Nature."
Really?
Would you like to go out on a shoot together?
That sounds awesome.
- Let's find a date for it.
- Mm!
- This is gorgeous.
- Yeah.
Beauty.
This one's pretty, isn't it?
- Mm.
- Right?
It's kinda pretty.
It's got great meaning behind it, too.
The message sounds hopeful.
Mm.
Can you take a photo of me
with this painting?
Sure.
Thank you.
How is it?
Mm...
I don't look that great in this photo.
Can you retake it?
- Here.
- How is it?
I don't like it.
Can you make the frame a little bit tighter?
Make it look normal.
Mm.
Just make it look normal.
What about this?
Are you kidding me?
What?
How is this normal?
My head is out of frame.
It's the vibe.
But I want a normal photo.
- I'll try again, I guess.
- Stand closer to the wall.
Mm.
I'll shoot it for you.
Turn your body a little bit this way.
- Like this?
- No, the other way.
- This way?
- Uh-huh.
Uh-huh.
- Is it good?
- That's perfect.
- Would you like to see the photos?
- Mm.
Whoa, this one's gorgeous.
Can I have the photo?
Mm, you can have it.
How can you send it to me, though?
It's fine. You can send it to me.
Then, I'll forward it to her.
Yeah, sure.
By the way...
Why are you here by yourself?
Well, the exhibition
I wanna check out is almost over.
So I have to be here before it's too late.
Then, that's great.
Let's ask her to tag along with us.
Maybe she wants to be alone, Jan.
Sure, I'm coming with you guys.
Awesome.
That's perfect.
Please take photos of me, okay?
Take lots of pictures of me.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
- Let's check out that section.
- Mm.
Yingyam, can you take photos of us?
I want candid shots.
I want them for a reel.
Okay.
What are you doing, Jan?
Taking photos of us.
Can we do it later?
I wanna enjoy the work first.
We haven't had any couple photos, though.
And you said I can do whatever I want today.
But we...
We're not a couple, Jan.
We're still not?
When did I say that I'm yours?
Then why did you hit me up
if you didn't wanna date me?
Hey, stop shooting!
You're doing this again.
Jan, wait!
Phra Aek.
Why are you making that face?
It's too hot.
We've arrived.
I guess I've gotta go now.
Wait.
I have a class for half a day tomorrow.
That's the same for me, actually.
I think I'm gonna work on my photo assignment.
Lately, the Club Room looks kinda quiet,
doesn't it?
Everyone's busy with their midterm project.
Meet me in front of my faculty building
when you're done tomorrow.
Hm?
I'm not doing that.
That's all you'll get.
Phra Aek, wait!
Why do you wanna see me there?
What's up with him?
[Kornthep: Would you like to try a product shoot
on the day after tomorrow?]
[Satrupai: Have you seen my wallet?
I think I left it at the restaurant]
[Phra Rong: This one?]
[Satrupai: Yeah, did you find it?]
[Phra Rong: You dropped it
I was going to give it to you,
but you already left]
[Satrupai: Right, give it to
your fraternity brother]
[Satrupai: I'll get it from him]
[Phra Rong: I'm currently outside]
[Phra Rong: I'll come to your place
and give it to you]
[Satrupai: No, I'll get my wallet myself]
[Phra Rong: It's okay.
I'll go to your place]
[Satrupai: Hey, hold on]
[Phra Rong: That's it.
I have things to do now]
How did he know where I live?
What are you doing here?
I told you not to come.
Why didn't you tell me that
you didn't want your stuff back?
How did you know where I live?
Thanine told me your address.
Nine, you piece of...
Just hand it over already.
Hey.
You're not gonna say thank you?
Quit horsing around.
Hand it over.
I'm not horsing around.
But...
What does a man with good manners do?
I don't know. Give it!
If you don't, then you can't have it.
We're all grown-ups here.
Thank you.
Huh?
It's that simple.
Here.
Gosh.
It's your friend's.
She dropped it at the cafe.
Thank you.
By the way, how's the cafe doing?
It's just like what you saw.
It's gonna stay closed for a while.
But...
I've deleted the comments
and had my friends delete all of the videos.
It's whatever.
By the way, about the photo of your ID card...
I...
The photo of you with a buzz cut...
I didn't know that hairstyle
can make your forehead look so
brilliantly shiny.
What the hell?
What?
You're stunned, aren't you?
What I'm trying to say is that
you looked pretty cute with a buzz cut.
Am I allowed to throw you into jail
for going through my ID card?
I had to look at it, didn't I?
I have to know who it belongs to.
Right.
Oh...
Don't block my contact, okay?
Or else...
I'm gonna come all the way here to see you.
You're blocked.
Why are you here again?
I already told you
not to block my contact.
Or else I'd come all the way here for you.
Go the hell away.
Let me guess.
You're thinking about
moving to a different place
to get away from me.
How nosy.
'Cause I wanna be nosy.
Be honest.
Why did you come here?
I don't know.
If it weren't for you,
I'd have already called the police.
I don't know.
I just wanna be here.
Please.
Can we just do our own thing?
No promise.
Go the hell back the way you came.
- Just get the hell out already.
- Ow!
- Leave!
- Hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
Would you like to have shabu-shabu?
No.
Please.
I said no.
- Please have shabu-shabu with me.
- Hey!
- Please, please, please.
- I already said no.
- Hey!
- Let's have shabu-shabu.
Hey, brother!
- Hello, Mr. Security.
- Good day to you, sir!
Come on now.
Your boyfriend has already come this far.
Just say yes already.
He's not my boyfriend, sir.
Nuh-uh!
Don't be shy.
I've already seen ones like you.
You're so lucky to have
a boyfriend this handsome.
I already told you that he's not mine.
Look at him.
He looks so pitiful.
His eyes are all watery.
He's been waiting for you for hours.
Don't be so mean to your boyfriend, please.
Be gentle and take it slow.
That's how a love life thrives.
That's enough, sir.
It'll be too much if I tell you my story.
It's okay, sir.
I’ll keep waiting for him here.
Fine.
I'll go.
Amazing! That's how you do it!
May you two love each other forever!
Time to get back to work, brothers!
- Have a good day, sir!
- Bye-bye!
Have a safe journey.
Thank you!
Let's go.
Hey, stop!
Where are you going?
I'm not having shabu-shabu with you.
Uncle.
I'll have a bowl of egg noodles
with BBQ red pork and dumplings.
Hey!
"Uncle," you say?
It's "sis." Can you see how pretty I am?
I'll have a plate of BBQ red pork
with gravy and rice, sis.
Of course! Please wait, dear.
You're so sweet, dear.
Huh?
You said you're having shabu-shabu.
You're at this place.
So where else am I gonna go?
Your face is ruining my appetite.
It makes me wanna vomit.
Got morning sickness?
Morning sickness my ass!
You said you were gonna throw up
because of my face.
So I thought you got it.
So funny.
- Here you go!
- Oh!
- Thank you.
- Thank you, sis.
How sweet of you!
You got it for me?
What?
No. It wasn't me.
Oh, and...
I just wanna know you more, Nom Jued.
I saw photos of you online,
so I wanna meet you in person.
You really study at this faculty?
I haven't seen your face before.
I'm a junior student,
and you do look kinda familiar.
Are you that playboy?
You're being too harsh.
I'm not that type of person.
I'm kind-hearted
and sweet.
I see...
I'll be on my way then.
Hold up.
Before you go,
can I ask you something?
Can I have your LINE ID?
Mom told me not to give it to strangers.
What about your Instagram?
I don't use it.
Huh?
Why are you taking so long, Nom?
You're taking...
Fucking...
My friend's been looking for me.
I've gotta go now.
Hold on. Who was that guy?
Hey, guys!
Oh, Pai.
You're late again.
I was having food.
What's with your face, though?
You look upset.
It's nothing.
By the way,
Nom Mhee Cafe is reopening soon.
Really?
Yeah.
I think it's next week.
Mm.
We can go and work there after the exam.
Let's do it together, Pai.
I probably won't return there.
Huh? Why?
If I were there,
I’d probably mess things up again.
Let's go to our class.
The professor will prepare us
for the exam today.
Let's go.
Oh, hey, Nom Jued.
Hey, Nong Noey.
You're working on something?
That's right.
Whoa...
I almost didn’t recognize you
without your glasses.
That's what a lot of people say, too, actually.
You look busy.
Yeah.
I haven't worked on
the club's assignment, either.
Me too.
I still don't know what I wanna shoot
and what to borrow from the club.
Don't worry about it, Nom Jued.
I'll borrow one for you.
Thank you so much, Noey.
By the way, what are you doing here?
Phra Aek told me to meet him here.
Nom Jued.
Be honest.
You and Phra Aek
are not dating, are you?
Are you crazy?
It's not like that.
You're not falling for each other, right?
Not at all.
Where did you hear that from?
Here.
I saw a comment under a post
about your photo,
saying that you're in a relationship.
[He keeps to himself.
I guess his partner's possessive]
I'm not that type of person.
Nom Jued, let's go.
Come with me.
Where are we going, Phra Aek?
You'll find out if you come with me.
What...
What if this is a kidnapping?
God, I'm not gonna do that!
You still owe me.
- Let's go!
- See you later, Noey!
See you, Nom.
I'll tell you more about the shoot, okay?
Mm!
Why are you just standing there?
Follow me.
You're getting a pair of glasses?
Me?
You're the one getting a new pair of glasses.
No!
It's expensive.
I can't afford it either.
I'm also wearing contact lenses.
Come on.
Just get inside already.
Quickly.
Get inside.
Excuse me.
Get him this pair.
Sure.
I'm not getting a new pair, Phra Aek.
Just get it.
This is an obligation.
I don't have the money for it today.
Madam Mommy gave the money to me.
Huh? My mom?
Yes, your Madam Mommy.
So just get one.
This way, you can study your notes better.
- Get this pair for him, please.
- Alright.
Is this pair similar?
Here you go.
Thank you.
Try walking around first.
Right.
Is it giving you double vision
or making you dizzy?
Not at all.
Now, this is a step up.
You look as ugly as sin
without your glasses.
Hey.
Don't be so harsh, Phra Aek.
Is this pair perfect?
Yes, it is.
Let me see.
Yeah, there we go.
What's wrong?
Thank you for the new pair of glasses.
Is there anything you wanna tell me?
Nothing.
What's wrong?
Tell me.
I'm all ears.
Is it a big deal
if I don't wear my glasses?
Well...
It's not.
I'd rather no one else lay their eyes on you
Why?
I just wanna change how I look.
Why am I suddenly the center of attention?
There are even mean comments about me.
I just didn't reply to them.
Why do they have to be so mean?
It's because you're adorable.
Really?
About the comments...
I'll deal with them.
Phra Aek.
You don't have to do that.
Do you know what you have to do?
Give me your phone.
Here.
For anyone who comments on your photo,
just reply to them like this.
Look at you.
You're crying like a lost little pup.
Honestly...
I'm also possessive of you.
I'm sorry for forcing you
to get a new pair of glasses.
It's okay.
It's my mom's order anyway.
I can't say no to that.
Here.
I got this for you.
It's Star Lab facial cream and serum.
Your skin has been looking a bit dull.
How do I use them?
Well...
Apply the serum first,
then the facial cream.
And you're here because
you wanna give me these?
Are you okay?
You're worried about me?
No.
But I...
On that day, you and Jan...
We broke up.
Huh?
It's already over?
Why?
She wasn't who I wanted.
So you're letting it out by taking photos?
Mm.
I finally get to do things myself.
I no longer need your help this time.
What are you shooting, though?
No idea.
I wanna set things up myself,
and make it look abstract and complicated
just like yours.
Just like my work?
There's nothing complicated behind it.
Why?
You can't say it to my face,
so you're expressing
your thoughts through your work?
What are you saying?
Are you out of your mind?
Just tell me if you wanna date me.
Why do you have to
shoot photos of me with others?
Even if I like you,
all I can do is admire you, right?
Someone like you
isn't perfect for me.
I also know that
you're not gonna change yourself.
Isn't that right?
Okay, students.
For this class, I'll be teaching you
about product photography.
The key to this class is lighting.
Nom Jued.
Sorry, I'm late.
The class just started, though.
I'd like two volunteers
to help me set up the light.
Okay, stand up, please.
Okay.
Okay, you...
Whoa.
I wanna use this for an actual shoot.
For what shoot?
For Nom Mhee Cafe, of course.
Can I help you with that?
Are you for real, Korn?
Thank you.
You're the kindest person on Earth.
[Lighting class lectures]
You're the one who gave me the milk, right?
Mm, yes.
Thank you. I finished the entire carton, too.
Nom Jued.
Can I ask you a question?
Mm, go ahead.
Are you...
with someone?
Well...
I'm with Pomphrab and Satrupai.
As for the club members, I'm with Nong Noey.
No, not like that.
Like what?
Like, in a relationship.
I'm not.
Wait, don't tell me that
you've read those mean comments,
bullying me.
Yes.
I've already dealt with all of them.
"Dealt with them"?
Mm.
See?
[Nawat Prachmethee: It's none of your business]
Why?
It sounds too harsh?
That's nice.
Those people deserve those kinds of words.
Nom Jued.
Can I ask you something?
Two of us...
Is there a chance that...
Okay, students.
That's it for today.
This class is over.
Feel free to ask me anything
if you've got questions.
Class dismissed.
Thank you.
Hey, Korn!
I've got business to attend to.
I'll talk to you later.
Mm.
Oh, Phra Aek.
You've got something to do with me?
No.
Hm...
You're coming with me?
Yeah, just in case your fans abduct you.
This is a university, though.
Nobody's gonna do that kind of thing here.
Who knows.
You're so sweet, Phra Aek.
Just get going already.
Go! You're running late.
Hey, man.
Why didn't you bring Phrab over, too?
I did,
but he said he'd game at his own place.
I don't think he's doing that, though.
I think he's secretly studying his notes.
Yet, you're here gaming with us?
I've been preparing for the exam
since last semester.
So the exam's gonna be a walk in the park.
You don't have a class tomorrow?
I do.
It's an early morning one,
but I'm going there late.
Yeah, yeah.
I've got a class at 9 A.M. tomorrow.
- You can head out together with me.
- Right.
- One more game?
- Of course.
- Bring it.
- Let's go.
- Pass it to me.
- See that?
I forgot!
- Yeah!
- How about that?
- Come on! Pass it to me.
- Quickly! Run.
- I'm doing a diagonal pass.
- Quickly.
Shit!
God damn it!
Oh, fuck.
Hello.
Hurry up. The Professor is pissed.
She's giving us a quiz.
Fucking hell!
Right.
Whoa!
With this...
What kind of relationship do you wanna be in?
If you say "friends."
Friends don't do that, though.
It's said that if we get the same number
from the fortune stick
it means we're destined to be together.
I know that you're hitting on him.
I have a crush on Phra Aek.