50 YEARS LATER
How was your flight?
Well,
I miss the old days when you'd have
a meal and take a nap on the flight.
You don't have time for a nap
before landing these days.
Have you tried the sleeping machine
from More than Machines?
Yes, that was good.
It allowed me to have a sound sleep
for the time I set.
It's going to be a huge hit yet again.
It's a large company now.
They made it!
TV.
That's impressive, sir!
Good morning. You're watching
a live broadcast of Newsroom.
Yellow Pants has just returned
from his 50th anniversary
world tour concert.
At the age of 78,
he has toured around 23 cities
in 20 countries across the world.
He'll soon be having
his farewell concert in Incheon.
His fan club, Yemy,
is converging here in Songdo, Incheon,
to witness his final performance.
The international city of Songdo
is already covered in yellow.
Reporter Kang Tae-su will now give you
a view of Songdo from up in the sky.
I'm above Songdo International City.
REPORTER KANG TAE-SU
Looking down from the sky,
Songdo is full of yellow.
It's not a field of forsythia
or a flock of chicks.
Members of Yemy from all around the world
have gathered here in Songdo
to see his goodbye concert.
What a magnificent view.
On the ground, we have
Park Ju-yeong on the line with us.
REPORTER PARK JU-YEONG
I am in front of Songdo Central Park.
As you can see, everyone behind me
is wearing yellow pants
and headed to the same place.
They are all waiting here
to catch a glimpse of Yellow Pants.
Let me interview
one of his fans from overseas.
-Hi.
-Hello.
-Where are you from?
-I'm from Iran.
-Do you speak Korean well?
-Yes.
I learned it because I like Yellow Pants
and Korean dramas.
Is there anything
you want to say to Yellow Pants?
Yellow Pants is loved by people
of all religions and races.
But I'm disappointed that the Middle East
was not included on the tour list.
That didn't stop you from coming here?
Well, I couldn't miss it.
The House of Saud expressed disappointment
even though I stressed that
the locations were selected in rotation.
They asked for a couple of tickets
for the Crown Prince and his wife.
The time has passed
for currying such favors.
But there's a political and economic side
that we can't ignore.
Give them back-row seats.
Certainly.
Why don't you greet your fans
before you leave for your health checkup?
Sounds good.
Magnifier.
Here you are, sir.
See you all next week!
Min-ah!
Where are you going, sir? Follow him!
Okay, ma'am.
Boss.
Let's go.
Excuse me! Hey!
Let me come with you.
You wish!
I can harm humans.
I beg you.
I'll just watch.
I won't pull any tricks on you.
All I want is to worship them, you know.
Let me see them off. Please?
Let's take him.
What can he do anyway?
Hands.
Do you think we're going on a picnic?
That's it. A picnic.
Life is like a picnic, you see.
It's all fun and games until you die.
We are merely specks of dust
floating around on Earth.
Sir, he's not in his right mind!
No! I'm sorry.
I'm just too excited, that's all.
Yellow Pants,
the one who fought with his life.
You were so awesome!
That's the power of love.
One-way love!
I told you I can harm humans.
I'll take that back. Forgive me, sir.
Let's go. Yeah.
Bro.
Fine. Shut up.
I felt the scent of your shampoo
In the swaying flowers
Big Bang.
Have you figured out the Big Bang?
Where it all started?
Probably at YG Entertainment.
It's incredible
that you can make this kind of joke!
Come on. If you could please tell me--
I can't tell you.
That means you do know something.
Just a little bit.
Can't you just give me a hint?
I can't tell you.
Then do you believe in God too?
Oh man!
At least tell me why you came here.
Kind of a tour.
What are those marks on the machines?
Something like travel agency logos.
-They look like Hangul, though.
-We use Hangul too.
But why?
It is the most perfect writing system
we have discovered so far.
That is the only thing
where Earth is ahead of our planet.
Now I'm high on Korean pride!
Do you people have cats
or other pets like dogs?
We do.
We don't keep them. We protect them.
We're the top species,
but we don't own the planet.
Is there any way we can keep in touch?
Email or something?
That's impossible.
What do I do if I miss you?
Please stop.
I'm so sorry, but I love you
It was all lies
Stop it.
I didn't know
Now I realize that I need you
Seriously, stop.
-Do you like karaoke?
-Stop!
Min-ah!
Min-ah.
MORE THAN MACHINES
What is it?
I want you
to take over this company.
What's going on?
And what's up with you?
Stop joking now.
You guys are already a joke.
I get it now. I'm sorry.
I was really tired yesterday,
so I went to the sauna.
All right, I went to an Internet café too.
I'm sorry.
That's what I'm talking about.
You've always been professional
about slacking off.
You calculated the time,
every single day without fail,
slacking off diligently and persistently.
Yet you always finish your work.
Never ever dropped the ball.
In a way, you're a genius, kid.
Okay, you can stop.
I will slack off less from now on.
-No, I'll stop.
-I'm being serious, kid.
If you just build an ownership mindset,
you are sure to make it.
Please look after this company.
Has something happened to you?
I have to live a long life.
Until I'm 105.
No,
I have to stay healthy until I'm 106,
which means I'll have to get away
from this factory and this city.
This city.
This factory. This…
Mr. Ko.
Yes?
Do music.
Sorry?
I don't know much about music,
so I'm not sure if you're good at it,
but you should follow your passion
while you're still young.
If you get old and still can't make it,
More than Machines will rehire you.
Right?
Well, I guess so.
But boss, you are still young too.
How are you going to make a living
until you're 106?
I'm going
into the wilderness.
Come to think of it,
we've never had a team dinner.
Let's go.
Let's have some beer with chicken nuggets.
BAEKJUNG CHICKEN NUGGET
Ko Baek-joong, three people.
Here.
Come in.
Well, it's good to have
a little get-together like this.
What's good about it?
A boss who ditches his company
to live longer.
A coworker who tries to make music
in a machine company.
How can that be good?
It's just good to be out
during office hours.
Look at you shamelessly smirking
after being called a skilled slacker
and running your mouth on top of that.
You're really something else.
An irresponsible boss
and a shameless successor!
What a mess this is--
Enough.
You always take it too far.
But just how far is too far?
I'm sorry.
"A Chicken Nugget Rhapsody"?
Right, it's him!
You're a YouTuber, right?
What? I'm--
You sang "A Chicken Nugget Rhapsody"!
Oh my God, this is crazy!
I mean, I do upload songs on YouTube--
Are you in a band?
I'm just a one-man band.
That's freaking sick!
Can we take a picture with you?
-Yeah, sounds good.
-Let's go!
-You should make a video now.
-Okay.
Hurry up.
By the way, what's the name of your band?
Yellow Pants?
Yellow Pants!
-Let's take a picture!
-Do it now!
Okay. Here we go.
Nice!
I love you!
JUST CHICKEN NUGGET
Aren't those chicken nuggets?
For 50 years, my grandma was a fan
of "A Chicken Nugget Rhapsody."
She told me she saw you
before you became popular as Yellow Pants
when you were singing and dancing
while walking down the street.
She said that she might be
your first-ever fan.
Is that so?
Where is your grandmother now?
She passed away last month.
I always had chicken nuggets with her.
Would you like to join me?
Shall I?
What a beautiful moment this is.
A grandmother who is no more.
A fan of 50 years who passed away.
A girl shares the memories
of her grandmother,
and Yellow Pants
eats chicken nuggets with her.
Media and critics
from all around the world
described this day
with the following sentence.
"A great poet who sang about peace
and love for humanity for half a century."
Can there be any reason left
to prevent him
from receiving the Nobel Prize?
Thank you for watching Newsroom.
That guy never grows old.
I could say the same of you.
You're right.
I've had this face for 60 years.
I think it's time now. Shall we go?
Let's go, then.
A month ago,
I sent this new product
made by More than Machines
to my old friend as a gift.
I saw him on the news today,
and he looks even younger now.
Baek-joong always looked young
for his age.
Look.
That guy really loves to drink.
But his eyes shine brighter than ever.
What's his secret?
Can you believe he is 78?
Hello.
I'm Yoo Tae-man, the principal engineer
and CEO of More than Machines.
How old do I look?
I'm 75. Can you believe that?
I met BLACKPINK at an event
the other day.
They treated me like their nephew.
Can you guess why?
All right.
I won't drag this out.
The secret is in sound sleep.
Let me introduce
More than Sleep.
You can sleep soundly
whenever and however long you want.
First of all,
I'd like to express my appreciation
to the late Chairman Kim Hwan-dong,
who, for a very long time,
had always supported us
in inventing machines for mankind.
And also to my uncle,
who was also a principal engineer,
the late Dr. Yoo In-won.
To this day…
I'm thankful to them.
YOO TAE-MAN, KIM HWAN-DONG, YOO IN-WON
You are here.
Sorry to disturb you at this hour.
No. Don't be.
Why is she still…
I'll explain now.
250 years ago,
shortly after we were trapped on Earth,
weapons of mass destruction
were invented here.
Earth was then classified
as a travel-banned planet,
and, as a result,
all the machines were discarded.
I took back the only remaining machine,
but I needed one more day
to recharge its energy.
But, as you know, taking another day means
there will be no one left on Earth
who remembers Min-ah.
Thanks to your kind heart, my friends
and I were able to meet our families.
But I couldn't turn--
You wouldn't have known
what was to happen.
I am aware that your kind cannot lie.
I'm sorry.
I didn't have much time
to find another way.
If you press this button,
you'll go back in time
to the point you desire.
But you'll lose all of your memories
up to this point.
But what about the billions of people
in this timeline?
Memories will be gone,
but fate won't change.
Only Min-ah's life will be added to it.
I'm sorry
to leave you with such a tough decision.
I should invite the boss here.
You might not see me again,
but we'll be back in three days.
If I find Min-ah as she is now,
we'll take her back with us.
If traveling to Earth has been banned,
does that mean that aliens
are not coming to Earth anymore?
No.
The human race evolves
through a considerate heart.
Weapons and wars will all disappear.
And at the peak of that evolution,
we will all meet again.
Someday.
Yes. Someday.
It's been a while.
I missed you.
Ma'am, could you call Mr. Choi in?
-Guys, pack up quickly.
-Yes, sir.
Let's go home.
Hey, excuse me.
We're here to meet Mr. Choi.
Who?
-Isn't this where Mr. Choi Sun-man lives?
-Oh, Sun-man?
I fucking want to see him too.
Why curse?
We came to film
Into the Wilderness, but we couldn't.
Look at our guy over there.
He broke his leg while following him.
He can't be 105. He's 500 years old.
He's not even human. Hey!
Tell the What in the World! guys
to take over.
At least tell us where he is.
Over there.
There.
Look closely. He'll jump once more.
One, two…
There! That's a person.
It's not some weird natural phenomenon.
It's a flying person.
He even caught a boar and trained it
so that it wouldn't ruin the crops
in the village.
The boar nodded as if it heard him.
Unbelievable, right?
I'll show you
something even more unbelievable.
There.
Where did he go? There.
Over there. He's so damn far away, right?
Now he'll pop up here.
See?
I won't die!
I'm ready.
Welcome, boss.
Boss.
Boss?
Boss!
What is it like…
to live as a chicken nugget?
I'm not sure.
But that's not what really matters.
Which is harder?
To live as a chicken nugget for five days
or a human for 50 years?
How would you have answered the question?
I respect the time you have lived so far.
The time I spent was too short
compared to that.
Of course, what I saw in that short time
was truly invaluable.
I saw how deeply you and my dad loved me.
I also saw another world
that could someday be our future
here on Earth.
Everyone was happy there.
They didn't try to share
their happiness with others.
They just let the happiness flow naturally
to where it needed to go.
There was pain too,
but people weren't afraid of it,
because everyone tried to lessen the pain
by sharing it.
A wonderful place, isn't it?
I'll lose my memories of that place,
but they're not as important
as the time you've lived.
Giving you back the time
you should have spent with your father.
I think that's the right thing to do.
I believe…
that you'll understand my decision.
BAEKJUNG CHICKEN NUGGET
Dad.
Min-ah!
You must be hungry.
I brought chicken nuggets.