[English subtitles are available]
[Time to Fall in Love]
[Episode 18]
Hello?
My queen, are you sober yet?
It's so chaotic outside.
What happened?
Some unscrupulous media
suddenly published photos of
you and Fu Boya.
They even came up with a scandalous title for it.
Now the whole Huayan...
No.
The whole cosmetics industry
is talking about it.
What?
[Fu Boya and He Jinxi hugging at the bar.]
How did this happened?
I didn't see Fu Boya yesterday.
Alright, stop talking.
Get changed.
I'm heading to your place now.
I'm afraid the reporters
will block your door later.
Where is Gu Xicheng?
He went to Huayan with Situ
to deal with it last night.
What are you thinking about?
Hurry up.
What can I do?
An'an!
Xixi, get in the car.
Seatbelt.
They're out of the house now.
They should be going to her friend's place.
I'll send you the address.
Situ Shuo said many reporters
are rushing over to the House of Gu.
I'm afraid you can't handle it alone,
so I'll take you home first.
Situ Shuo and Gu Xicheng
went to the company to deal with this last night.
I believe everything will be fine soon.
Don't worry.
What's with the photos?
You were with me yesterday.
Have you seen Fu Boya?
But I did go out for a while.
Maybe the photos were taken at that time?
But why?
Don't think about anything now.
You'll find out sooner or later.
[Lucid waters and lush mountains are invaluable assets.]
It'll be fine. Let's go.
I heard Mr. Gu has a fiancée.
[Huayan]
Really?
Of course.
I heard that his fiancée cheated on him.
[Huayan]
She even cheated with someone from our rival group.
The landlady is really amazing.
[Huayan]
-Vice President. -Vice President.
Don't mind what they say.
They don't know anything and still talk nonsense.
It doesn't matter what they say.
What the media says is most important.
I've invited some familiar media
and reporters.
There will be a conference this afternoon to clarify this.
Everything will be solved.
As for Grandma,
I asked Aunt Mei to go out with her.
I hope everything can be solved
before she comes back.
[Huayan]
Thank you, everyone. I'm Gu Xicheng.
Miss He!
Miss He, who is the man in the photo?
How long have you known each other?
Stop filming!
No, I didn't.
Stop filming! Stop filming! You, stop filming!
I didn't!
Stop filming! Stop filming!
Xixi!
No, I didn't. It's not like that.
Say something, Miss He.
Miss He, please say something.
Miss He, can you accept our interview?
Xixi, let's go.
Who is this?
Miss He! Miss He!
Miss He, please say something.
Stop filming! Stop filming!
Miss He!
Stop filming.
Miss He, can you explain?
Miss He.
Go away! Go away!
Stop filming.
Miss He! Miss He!
Please say something, Miss He!
Miss He!
[Shocking Truth. Huayan's Miss He Cheated with Rival Group. Latest Updates.]
I'll leave this to you.
Everyone,
I have something personal to deal with.
I'll see you tonight.
Sure, Mr. Gu.
Did anyone follow us?
Don't worry.
It's safe here.
I'll call Xicheng first.
I want to talk to you alone.
Those photos?
There's no need for that.
Boya, I trust you completely.
We haven't met
in the past few nights.
How could there be
such scandal photos?
It must be made by someone with ulterior motives.
Or the reporters just came up with it.
They wrote it casually.
Casually?
We never have
any scandalous relationship between us.
Boya, you are my friend.
You also kept all my secrets for me.
Someone not only wants to sow discord
between me and Xicheng.
They even want to hurt our friendship.
I'll call Xicheng now
to clarify on it.
Su Yanxi!
Why do you always think for others?
Can't you be selfish?
Can you think for yourself?
Boya.
What's wrong with you?
Or...
you know something?
I did it.
What do you mean?
I did all this.
Yesterday, at the bar,
I changed the wine that you and Lu An'an were drinking.
I sent her away.
I took the intimate photos with you
and sent all the photos
to more than ten media and reporters.
I also told them you were at Lu An'an's place.
I did all this.
Fu Boya, what are you talking about?
You did all this?
Why?
For...
Nangong.
Nangong Liuli?
She is the one
I love most.
Let's go! Let's go!
Go!
Hello. Hello.
Are you Chinese?
Hang in there.
Don't sleep.
Don't be afraid.
I'll call an ambulance for you.
Hello.
Someone was hurt.
I'm on the 5th Street.
Get them over.
Don't sleep. Hang in there.
Talk to me.
What's your name?
Those years abroad
were the hardest days in my life.
I almost gave up on myself.
Until the moment Nangong appeared,
a ray of light shone
into my dark life.
I fell in love with her.
Although I know
deep down in her heart,
she loves someone else.
But it doesn't matter.
As long as I can stay by her side,
that's enough
for me.
I get it now.
I want her to be happy.
I hope she can be happy.
Even if in the end,
I'm not the one by her side,
it doesn't matter.
My life belongs to her.
No matter what I need to do to repay her,
it would never be too much.
When she knew Gu Xicheng had a girlfriend,
she was in great pain.
Seeing her in pain,
my heart feels like its being pierced by needles,
being cut by a knife.
I... I felt worse than her.
So,
I decided
to destroy the relationship
between Gu Xicheng and his girlfriend.
Are you still the Fu Boya
I know when I was young?
I'm sorry.
I let you down.
So,
I tried everything
to get close to Gu Xicheng's girlfriend.
I even drove around your house
to find a way
to establish a relationship with Gu Xicheng's girlfriend.
Miss? Miss! Miss, are you alright?
That day,
you crashed into the taxi I took.
You even planned an accident.
I calculated everything.
But I didn't expect
Gu Xicheng's girlfriend to be you.
This is ridiculous.
So you joined the collaboration
between Huayan and the German company
on purpose?
I heard that Gu Xicheng
intended to collaborate with Lipman.
I knew they were lacking a third party general consultant.
So I went to Lipman
and offered him
a price he can't refuse.
You really put all your effort into it.
But I never
expect you to
fall in love with Gu Xicheng.
No matter how I treated you,
you don't feel anything.
I had no choice.
So I had to find someone
to take photos of us at the bar.
Stop talking!
I really don't understand.
You hurt others
to make the person you love happy.
Is this your so-called love?
Are you crazy?
Do you know
you've hurt others?
You'll cause a mess in Huayan.
Why do you have to do this?
I don't care about others.
I only did it for Nangong.
Xixi,
if you are willing to give up Gu Xicheng
and return him to Nangong,
I will announce to the public that
it was all my plan.
I'll take full responsibility.
Fu Boya!
Xixi, you and Gu Xicheng are not suitable for each other.
As long as you give up your love for him...
Fu Boya, I treated you as my friend.
I didn't expect you to be such a person.
From now on,
I don't want to have any contact with you anymore.
Just pretend that we
never knew each other.
Xixi. Xixi!
[Camp Coffee]
Xixi! Xixi!
Xixi,
let's talk about it.
Let go!
I have nothing to say to you.
Xixi, don't forget
you have another big secret.
Let go!
Fu Boya!
Gu Xicheng, no! Gu Xicheng!
Fu Boya, I don't care who you are.
I don’t care what you did.
If you keep pestering Xixi,
I'll beat you up every time I see you.
Gu Xicheng, please don't!
We're not done.
I'll settle it with you slowly.
[Camp Coffee]
Don't be angry.
I'm not angry.
It's just too messy today.
I'm confused too.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
I shouldn't have trusted others so easily.
I shouldn't have gotten drunk outside.
Because of me,
this mess happened.
I'm not afraid of the mess outside.
I'm just...
I'm just afraid that they'll hurt you.
Xixi,
I won't let them hurt you.
No matter what happens,
no matter what it takes,
I will always protect you behind me.
Xicheng,
I want to
tell you something.
Go ahead.
Wait for me in the car.
I'll be right back.
Go.
Hello, Boss.
What happened?
This is serious.
A reporter told me that
Fu Boya just called the reporters saying that
he wants to make a statement about the situation.
Fu Boya?
What is he up to?
He's making a scene.
He seems to have more than one trump card.
I don't understand it either.
But we have evidence that shows
Fu Boya and Nangong Liuli
studied abroad together.
Nangong Liuli?
I was also surprised when I found out.
And we have evidence that shows
they are friends.
But I don't know if they have
any other relationship.
Situ, go and check
the whereabouts of Nangong after she joined Huayan.
Gather all the evidence that we can get.
And send more manpower
to the conference tonight.
Don't let them get close to Xixi.
Okay, got it.
Is everything okay?
I'm here, everything will be fine.
Relax.
There will be a news conference in Huayan's hall tonight.
I'll clarify everything.
News conference?
Let's go.
Miss Nangong,
your boyfriend asked us to give you a letter.
[Liuli,]
[It hurts me to see you lying on a hospital bed.]
[I can risk everything. This time, I will succeed.]
[But you saved me that winter night.]
[Liuli, I really like you.]
[You work hard in your academics and designs.]
[I stayed by your side to protect you. I felt very happy.]
[You're always so sure of what you want, and you would go after it.]
[Boya.]
Boya.
Mr. Gu is here! Mr.Gu!
Mr. Gu is here! Mr. Gu is here!
Mr. Gu! Mr. Gu!
Mr. Gu!
Mr. Gu, what do you think about this?
Mr. Gu,
is your relationship with He Jinxi real?
Mr. Gu.
Xixi.
An'an, why are you here?
The live streamers are also here.
Look at the camera.
Please say something, Mr. Gu.
Mr. Gu, don't go. Mr. Gu.
[News Conference]
Please say something!
Tell us what happened!
Please give us an explanation!
Mr. Gu, is it true? Mr. Gu!
What do you think about this, Mr. Gu?
Do you want to clarify it, Mr. Gu?
[Huayan]
Please stay calm.
I'll tell you
what you want to know.
[Huayan]
The scandal regarding my fiancée cheating on me is fake.
She and Mr. Fu, who is in the photo,
are just friends.
My fiancée and I
have a very stable relationship.
[Huayan]
As the President of Huayan Group,
[News Conference]
I assure you that
this fake news
will not affect the launch of our new product,
nor the fluctuations of the company's stock.
[News Conference]
You're all talk.
How can we trust you?
Do you have evidence?
Can you explain it in detail?
[News Conference]
Fake?
What's going on?
What do you want to say?
Why would you say
my relationship with Xixi is fake?
Can you tell us in detail?
Tell us more.
I'm the other person in the photo.
If you want to know the truth,
shouldn't you interview me?
Then please tell us.
Do you have anything to say?
Tell us.
What's going on?
[News Conference]
Tell us something.
Just as you thought,
Mr. Gu's fiancée and I
are exactly what you imagined us to be.
Miss He Jinxi likes me,
not
Mr. Gu Xicheng, the President of Huayan Group.
Fu Boya, you!
Just stay here and leave it to me.
Do you have anything else to say?
I have more to say.
He Jinxi used
her identity as the fiancée of the President of Huayan Group
to steal everything that belongs to Miss Nangong Liuli from
the R&D department of Huayan Group.
All her designs and
everything else came from plagiarism.
It's all fake.
Do you have any evidence?
How could this happen?
Can you tell us in detail?
[Huayan]
Are you done?
[News Conference]
[Huayan]
Situ.
[News Conference]
This is the CCTV picture of my fiancée
at the bar on the day of the incident.
It clearly shows that
[Huayan]
after she and her best friend ordered the wine,
someone switched it.
After she was drunk,
someone sent her best friend away.
While she was in an unconscious condition,
someone secretly took photos of her and Mr. Fu.
Also,
this is from a few weeks ago.
A private meeting between Nangong Liuli
and a private car driver.
Because of Nangong Liuli's personal grudges,
she tricked my fiancée to the suburbs
and almost put her life in danger.
[News Conference]
When I got the evidence,
I never wanted to make it public.
But my tolerance and compromise towards you
doesn't mean you can keep pushing me
and hurting the person I love.
Fu Boya, you and Nangong Liuli
[News Conference]
have reached my bottom line.
From now on,
she's no longer an employee of the Huayan Group.
I'll give this evidence to my lawyer.
You will take
full responsibility of the things you did.
[News Conference]
Don't worry.
Is this true?
[Huayan]
Do you have anything to say?
You were criticizing Mr. Gu on the stage just now.
Please explain. Do you have any evidence?
Please explain.
Please say something.
Please explain, Mr. Fu. Please explain.
It's fake. These are all fake.
[News Conference]
These materials...
are all synthesized.
You have to believe me!
I'm telling the truth! I'm telling the truth!
Trust me! I'm telling the truth!
Trust me.
Do you have any evidence to prove it?
Please explain.
No.
I can't give up like this.
I can't give up.
Nangong is waiting for my good news.
Please tell us in detail! Yes, please tell us, sir!
Please tell us. Please tell us.
Do you think this is over?
It's impossible.
[News Conference]
Listen, Gu Xicheng.
Listen carefully.
Your beloved fiancée
is not...
Boya!
Who is this? Who is this?
Don't.
Do you have anything to say?
Please tell us something.
Please tell us something. Please say something.
Let's stop this.
I did it. It's all my fault.
I'll take all the blame.
Miss Nangong, what did you do?
It wasn't her.
It's not her. It's not like this. It's not her.
No, it's not like this.
I did it, not her.
[News Conference]
I did it. I did it.
It has nothing to do with her.
Boya!
Framing Mr. Gu's fiancée,
putting her in danger
Boya!
and all those things I just said,
I did all of them.
Boya!
I did it. It has nothing to do with her.
What's wrong with you, Boya?
Miss Nangong, don't you know anything?
Boya!
Have you never been involved?
Don't give her a hard time. Please don't give her a hard time.
No, no!
Boya! Boya!
Miss Nangong, you really don't know?
I'll take the responsibility now.
How are you going to take the responsibility?
I will take the responsibility. I will take the responsibility!
[News Conference]
Boya!
It's fine now.
I'll turn myself in, I'll turn myself in.
Boya, wait for me!
Nangong!
Boya. Boya.
Boya. Boya. Boya.
Are you okay, Boya?
Boya. Boya.
Boya!
Don't... don't cry,
If you cry,
I'll be sad.
Why did you do this?
Because...
I... I love you.
Since that day when
I lay in your
arms like this.
Don't be afraid.
I'll call an ambulance for you.
From that moment on,
I love you.
I'm on the 5th Street.
Get them over.
My heart
has never changed.
Boya, hang in there.
The ambulance will be here soon.
I'm...
I'm sorry.
Promise me.
In the next life,
let's...
meet...
each...
other...
first...
♫ You know it ♫
♫ I don't know much loving words ♫
No, Boya.
♫ Plant a flower ♫
No.
♫ Wait for it to sprout slowly ♫
♫ Wanted to leave ♫
♫ But still can't let go ♫
Boya!
♫ Betray myself ♫
♫ Is the price for falling in love ♫
Boya!
♫ You are my dream ♫
♫ You also know my heart ♫
Liuli, I'm sorry.
♫ Walking through the crowd ♫
♫ Only your voice was there ♫
I hope in my next life,
I'll meet you before Gu Xicheng.