[English subtitles are available]
[Time to Fall in Love]
[Episode 1]
[Hong Kong Island Bridge]
Speak.
Boss,
we received feedback on the collaboration with the Germans.
They request for us to raise the price by 3%.
[Situ]
What do you think?
Tell Lipman that
the price we gave them is more than the average
market price by 1.28%.
It's impossible for us to give in anymore.
If they sincerely want this collaboration,
then we'll do our best.
If they are still hesitant about the price,
then let's not waste each others' time.
Boss.
It's settled.
Don't worry, babes.
We have enough stocks today.
We guarantee you can get
the color that you want.
That's all for
today's livestream.
We'll see you tomorrow
at the exact same time. Bye.
Xixi, are you here?
There's only ten minutes left.
I'm almost there. Just one more street to go.
The traffic was bad.
I ran all the way from home.
You're not going to be in the Hanfu you wore for your livestream, right?
I have no choice.
I really can't miss this interview.
If I can't get this Huayan series's promotion opportunity,
I won't be able to afford my mom's
hospital bills next month.
Xixi, you are too...
I need to go now. I'll call you later.
[Pedestrian crossing]
[Lucid waters and lush mountains are invaluable assets.]
[Qilin Street]
What is this driving?
You almost hit me, and you didn't even apologize.
My interview...
[Qilin Street]
[Haiyin Road]
You're so slow.
If Mr. Gu gets angry,
none of us can escape.
Tidy up yourselves.
[Jiahui Street]
[288]
Welcome, Mr. Gu.
Boss.
The meeting is set
as per your request.
We can start right away.
Are you sure you're fully prepared this time?
Of course.
I'm not good at dealing with new products,
but I'm good at finding you a girlfriend.
I promise I'll find the best girlfriend for you in five minutes.
Grandma won't be nagging you again.
[It'll be done in six minutes]
Six minutes, it'll be an even number.
Let's start then.
I don't want to waste my time
on these useless things.
Okay.
The regular meeting will be held in two hours.
I finally made it.
I hope I can get
the new Huayan series's promotion.
Are you the hiring manager, Ms. Miqi?
I'm here to interview for the online broadcaster role.
The quota is full for today.
I immediately ended my livestream and rushed over
once I heard Huayan is holding the interview.
This is my resume.
Online account.
Pretty Xixi.
I'll go through these.
Go back and wait for the notice.
But, wait...
again...
I really don't want to go to the interview.
How long do I need to wait?
I'm really afraid of Mr. Gu.
Is it over for me again?
But this interview is a rare opportunity.
It's a pity to miss it.
You're number six anyway.
Why don't you reconsider it?
Okay.
Interview?
They are here for the interview too.
Maybe Miqi was in charge of the first screening.
The one inside is the real final interview?
Hold on.
Are you here for the interview too?
Yes.
Can I ask you
for a favor?
What is it?
If you are my girlfriend,
what do you want from me?
I've never thought of gaining anything from a relationship.
Mr. Gu, I like you because I like you.
I don't want much.
Please.
What do you want?
You and your heart.
Please.
Number six.
Here.
Hello.
I'm here for the interview.
Isn't this the guy
who almost hit me on the road?
You're here for the interview?
I'm here for the interview. I'm number six.
What kind of strange hobby is this?
Tell me, what's your condition?
Condition?
Is he asking me about the stock quantity for my livestreams?
50,000.
20,000 per month is fine too.
Every month? Are you sure?
Although I don't usually work long hours,
my monthly amount
is at least 100,000.
So 20,000 per month
is not an issue for me.
Of course, if you show me mercy,
I can take 50,000 too.
Okay, it'll be you then.
Hand me your ID card.
I'll get someone to draft the contract.
From now on,
you'll be by my side 24 hours a day.
So I'm accepted?
Great!
ID card.
This is my ID card.
Wait.
You said I have
to be by your side
24 hours a day?
I'm paying you 50,000 yuan per month
so that you can serve me 24 hours a day.
Is there a problem?
You want to be
my sugar daddy?
I don't think you should use this word.
Sorry.
I'm here to interview
for the online broadcaster role of Huayan Group.
I'm not here to be your sugar baby.
Online broadcaster?
My sugar baby?
50,000 yuan? 20,000 yuan?
You thought that I'm here to
place a price on myself.
Didn't you place that price on yourself?
I...
You are the president of this company.
I don't want to say anything harsh.
Why should the female interviewees
be humiliated by you?
Humiliate?
Anyway, I won't be working for you
and your company.
Boss.
How were the roses that I've prepared
for you?
What happened?
Boss, did you fight?
No.
How could you fight? I think it's...
If you don't have anything to say, keep your mouth shut.
Remove the roses.
If it weren't for Grandma,
there's no need
for this interview for best girlfriend.
And no need for these troubles.
I don't think you should think that way.
What if you meet your true love?
Grandma and I have the same thought.
You need someone
to care and protect you.
Your even number obsession, obsessive-compulsive disorder...
I'm going to meet a client. That's all for today.
[Huayan]
Grandma.
I have to meet a client this afternoon.
I may not be able to accompany you to the hospital.
But I've informed Aunt Mei.
She will take good care of you.
It's just a routine checkup.
You don't have to come.
But Xicheng,
you know what's on my mind.
You're not young anymore.
I always hope to see you get married while I'm still alive.
I want to see my great...
Grandma.
My client is calling. I have to hang up.
Why am I in the basement garage?
I pressed the first floor.
It's so hot.
Don't move.
♫ If the weather is good tomorrow ♫
♫ If the shoelaces are always tight ♫
♫ Maybe I'll ask you out tomorrow ♫
♫ Let's go for a walk ♫
♫ Three pedestrians wearing floral dresses on the street ♫
♫ Colorful colors like your eyes ♫
I'm sorry.
♫ Saw three contrails ♫
But I just wanted to remind you that
there are many high resolution infrared cameras here.
You can't...
♫ Implies that the process will go well ♫
Just pretend that I didn't get to know you today.
♫ Need more proofs of luck ♫
♫ Had a hunch that you'll promise before I ask ♫
What's going on with today?
♫ Promise that we'll continue tomorrow ♫
Ms. Su,
your mother's surgery is scheduled for next month.
[Outpatient Department]
Please clear the bill as soon as possible.
Your driver is at your service, my lady.
Please hop on.
I thought you weren't coming.
When a fairy goes out,
she needs time to dress up.
By the way, I haven't asked you.
How was your interview just now?
Don't mention it. That interview is really unlucky.
It's okay. We still have
a small contract.
No matter how small a fly is, it's still meat.
Right.
An'an,
I just went to see my mom.
The doctor said her illness can't be delayed.
She needs surgery as soon as possible.
And the hospital bills
have to be cleared as soon as possible.
Otherwise,
my mom has to be discharged from the hospital first.
It'll be fine, Xixi. Don't worry.
We'll find a way.
Ouch! It hurts so much!
You hit me! It hurts!
You threw yourself at the car.
Ouch!
Help!
Why are you acting like a rascal?
I'll call the police if you don't get up.
Help!
You hit someone, and you're not taking responsibility.
Come and see, babes!
She was hit by a luxury car,
and her life is at stake.
What are you doing?
I'm doing a livestream.
I've recorded the entire process.
I can't let you be bullied.
I'll call the police now and give them the video.
You might be able to make it on the social news.
Yes, on the news.
You're crazy.
Stop!
Thank you, Miss.
Without you,
Madam and I
wouldn't know how to deal with this kind of situation.
Don't worry about it. It's nothing.
Next time, you can install a dashcam.
Yes, thank you.
I'll get going then.
Let's go.
How is it?
It's fine.
Let's get ready for the livestream then.
I'm fine.
What a good girl.
She's beautiful and kind.
If Xicheng can find a girl like her...
Madam, you should worry about
your own health first.
[Outpatient Department]
All these years,
I just want Xicheng to
find a girlfriend, get married,
and have great grandchildren.
Today
seems promising.
Congratulations, Madam.
Your wish has finally come true.
Look at this girl.
Does she look familiar?
Isn't this the girl just now?
It's fate.
This is also a blessing in disguise.
Exactly.
Xicheng, you're back.
Grandma, Aunt Mei.
Look at this girl.
I don't know her.
Take a good look. You don't know her?
We are just...
If I didn't ask Situ to keep an eye on you,
are you planning to keep it from me?
Situ, you traitor.
What are you trying to do?
Are you trying to make me angry?
Do you want me to die early?
You're really...
Madam.
Grandma.
Grandma, calm down. Grandma.
Madam.
Grandma.
Xicheng,
my body can't take it anymore.
Grandma, don't think too much.
The doctor said you just need some rest.
I'm old.
I'm afraid I can't accompany you for long.
You're the one I'm most worried about.
You've been tough since you were young.
You're stubborn even when you're in trouble.
You never tell me anything.
But I hope you find
a considerate and gentle girl.
Get married.
Even if I die in the future,
my mind would be at peace.
Grandma, don't say that.
Xicheng...
Xicheng,
listen to me.
If you really like someone,
bring her home and let me meet her.
Get married soon.
Grandma.
I'm fine.
Come in.
Boss, don't be angry.
I sent the CCTV footage to grandma
because I can't stand seeing her so upset.
I'll accept any punishment.
But, please don't fire me.
Really?
How about this? This month's salary,
submit it all.
This month? Isn't that too much?
Then, how about the whole year.
I'll submit this month's salary.
Have you found the person I asked you to find?
Of course.
I looked through the interview materials
and found out that she wasn't the applicant for number six.
[He Jinxi]
I think she met you for the wrong interview.
But it doesn't affect a thing.
The last word in her name is Xi.
From the CCTV footage I've investigated, her name is He Jinxi.
[He Jinxi]
She's a famous local celebrity.
She likes social parties.
She's a high-end VIP of various luxury stores.
[Biography]
She likes to collect designer shoes.
Whichever shoes are the most popular
will appear on her feet first.
Are you sure it's her?
Isn't it? Look at Xi and the picture.
It's exactly the same.
Why do I feel that
there's something different?
It's the same.
Boss.
Grandma is pushing you.
It's not easy to find someone she likes.
Just try to get her.
[He Jinxi]
Then Grandma won't have to nag me anymore.
She doesn't have to nag you.
You can also focus on your work.
Grandma can rest with a peaceful mind too, right?
[He Jinxi]
Do you know how to wear it? Are you trained?
I'm sorry.
Go away.
Sorry, Miss He.
She's only been here for two days. She's clumsy.
It must have hurt. Let me help you.
It's fine. Don't touch me.
All these,
I'll take them all.
Okay.
Miss He,
your temple
has been infected due to excessive filling.
We need to have the restoration surgery as soon as possible.
Otherwise, it may cause
damage to the entire facial nerve.
You'd better go abroad for this.
Abroad? How much would that cost?
Restoration surgery and post-op care would
probably cost over a million.
Sorry, Miss He. Your card has exceeded the limit.
Do you have any other cards?
What?
Miss He, all your cards
have exceeded the limit and were frozen.
Can you pay in cash?
I don't want them anymore.
What kind of stupid bank freezes my card?
I said I would pay it back in a few days.
I didn't say I wouldn't.
Hello.
Hello, Miss He.
If you don't pay me my money back,
it won't be paint
on your door next time.
I told you I would pay you back
with interest next month.
Why are you still doing this?
Next month?
We haven't even received the interest for this month.
We can't wait until next month.
I said I would pay you back and I will.
I will.
I said I would pay you back.
What else do you want from me?
He Jinxi.
Who are you?
I'm Gu Xicheng, President of Huayan Group.
Mr. Gu?
I have allergic reactions in my eyes.
You don't mind, do you?
Let's get straight to the point. I'll sign a contract with you
and make you my contract girlfriend.
I'll also sign you as the online broadcaster of Huayan.
Contract girlfriend?
Online broadcaster of Huayan?
Why?
Do you have any other requests?
Just fool him first.
I want to know
how far will we be cooperating?
There won't be any real relationship between us.
We won't make our relationship public.
If you have other requests,
you can ask.
I'll try my best to satisfy you.
If you break the contract,
I have the right to terminate the cooperation.
[Contract]
Gu Xicheng can help me
with the restoration fee.
I need money.
You can write down the exact amount on the contract.
How long do I need to cooperate?
There must be a time frame.
It's stated in the contract that
it would be based on Grandma's health condition.
I want 50 percent of the deposit.
I'll transfer the rest of the money to you.
Don't forget to match your signatures.
[Party A Stamp Gu Xicheng]
[Zhongdao Road]
[139]
What happened?
Could it be Su Yanxi?
Did Su Yanxi and Gu Xicheng
know each other?
Su Yanxi, we, sisters haven't seen each other for so many years,
but we still have a special bond.
Hello, An'an.
What's wrong?
Why did the hospital call you in this morning?
The hospital said there are limited beds.
They asked me to pay the debt.
If I still can't pay it,
my mom will be transferred
out from her room to the corridor.
What? This is too much!
Wait for me.
Don't come over.
The key now is to get the money.
I have to go now.
Let me think of a way.
Long time no see, Yanxi.
We haven't seen each other for so many years.
Do you have to treat me like this?
I need to talk to you.
I don't want to care about your business, He Jinxi.
But this is beneficial for you.
Don't you want to hear it?
I don't care.
Yanxi!
Can't you just spare me a few minutes?
I'm sorry. I'm not interested in your business.
Are you really going to let me die?
Su Yanxi.
What happened to your face?
To be honest, if I don't do the surgery soon,
my face will be infected.
I'll lose my life.
Those debt collectors are also pushing me.
We're both mom's daughters.
Do you really want me to die?
I'm sorry about your situation, but
I can't help you.
You can as long as you are willing to.
Look at this.
[Contract]
[Party A Gu Xicheng]
[Party B He Jinxi]
Now, Gu Xicheng
needs a contract girlfriend.
If we work with him, we'll get a lot of money.
Then I'll be saved.
You were the one who met Gu Xicheng that day, right?
He mistook me for you.
Fortunately, I didn't have heavy makeup in the photo
I pasted on the document, so it's not much different from you.
So yesterday,
he was really choosing a contract girlfriend.
This is between you and Gu Xicheng.
It has nothing to do with me. I refuse.
It's not just for me.
I know you need money for mom's surgery.
As long as you fulfill the contract,
I can pay for mom's surgery.
I know you need money.
I've cleared the hospital bills for you.
[Jiangcheng People's Hospital Billing Receipt]
How is that?
Sincere enough?
I don't want to con someone.
Con?
Gu Xicheng was looking for someone
to pretend as his girlfriend and to put on
a show for his grandma.
Yanxi, think about our mom.
Are you really going to watch
her surgery be delayed?
Fine. Just wait.
Just wait and see.
Maybe you'll just have to see Mom die.
Wait!
I promise you.
But...
But this money,
I'll borrow it from you.
I'll pay you back later.
Yanxi, you did the right thing.
I'm doing this to help you
and our mom.
From now on,
you are me.
The real He Jinxi.
Gu Xicheng is smart.
Don’t let him find out.
If he knows we are using him,
we won't get anything.
Mom will also have no hope left.
What do I need to do?
Gu Xicheng should be waiting for you here.
Go now.
[Aowei Hotel]
Hotel?
What's the meaning of this, He Jinxi?
Don't worry. You're smart.
You can handle him.
You...
Su Yanxi.
Don't be afraid.
It's all for mom's surgery.
[Aowei Hotel]
Perform well.
Come on. You can do it.
You're late.