[English subtitles are available]
[Time to Fall in Love]
[Episode 16]
Xixi, where...
Come on.
Are you okay?
Brother.
Little fool.
Xicheng, you're back.
Why did you touch that box?
Don't get me wrong.
I didn't mean to touch your stuff.
I was looking for a lighter.
I saw this box, and
I thought it was in it.
Get out.
Xicheng.
Get out!
Gu Xicheng!
Xicheng, what's wrong with you?
You can tell me anything.
I can help you.
I don't need others' help.
But I'm not someone else.
These photos
are the reason for your even number obsession,
right?
The boy in the photo
is your elder brother,
right?
It has nothing to do with you.
Put it back.
Gu Xicheng,
stop avoiding it.
Since I saw it,
why can't you tell me?
Didn't we agree to take care of each other?
I can help you.
I don't need your help.
I've been carrying this
for 20 years.
I'd rather suffer every day.
I don't want anyone to come and tell me to
open up.
I can bear it with you.
I don't need it. I can bear it myself.
I don't need others' help at all.
Nonsense!
If you can bear it alone,
all these things in the house won't appear.
Gu Xicheng,
the even number obsession
has become a huge burden for you.
You'll collapse if you keep carrying it.
Just let it collapse and die.
Xicheng.
You want to know about him?
Okay.
I'll tell you.
He's my elder brother.
He's the one who everyone in the Gu family
cherishes,
the smartest and most loved eldest son,
Gu Nanzheng.
He was Gu family's everything.
He was the only heir to Huayan Group.
It was me.
I caused his accident
when he was seven years old.
It was me.
I watched him
lie in the hospital for seven days.
Seven days.
In the end...
Xicheng.
I ruined everything for the Gu family.
I'm the one who caused my mom's depression.
Dad had to go faraway with her.
It's my fault that grandma is sick.
She had to bring me up alone.
I killed my elder brother.
I ruined everything for the Gu family.
Are you satisfied with this answer?
Satisfied?
[Green Onion Knows]
The weather is not so good.
Let's go home early.
What are you doing?
There's a sudden itch in my back. I need to scratch it.
Let's go.
Hey, wait for me.
[Novotel]
We're home?
An'an...
Drive safe. Bye.
Are you happy, Madam?
Yes.
It's not bad. Not bad.
Xixi,
why are you going out so late?
You...
Why are you crying?
This...
Xixi!
What's going on?
What's wrong?
Xicheng!
This...
What's going on
with them?
Madam.
Here.
Come and catch me, brother!
Brother, wait for me!
Are you okay?
I'll give you this kite.
You're a man. You can't cry easily.
Understand?
Nanzheng, Xicheng.
Come and eat.
Come, sit down.
Hurry up.
Grandma,
I want the same as what brother is having.
You and your brother have the same thing.
They're all the same.
Okay, eat this.
Here.
For you.
Thank you, Grandma.
Thank you, brother.
Brother, I won!
Xicheng!
Brother!
Don't play on the road, Xicheng. It's dangerous.
I know.
Watch out, Xicheng!
Brother!
Brother, wake up.
Brother. Brother. Wake up!
Brother!
It's all my fault.
I'm sorry, brother.
Xixi? Xixi!
Xixi.
An'an.
Gu Xicheng.
Calm down!
How dare you bully my best friend?
An'an, calm down!
Grandma is still at home.
Gu Xicheng!
Calm down, An'an!
Gu Xicheng! Gu Xicheng!
An'an! An'an, calm down!
Gu Xi...
An'an, don't...
An'an!
Gu Xicheng!
Grandma, what happened?
It's all because...
What a sin.
Grandma, please calm down.
An'an...
Gu Xicheng! Gu Xicheng, come out!
Gu Xicheng! Gu Xicheng, open the door!
Gu Xicheng!
An'an, listen to me.
The fight between Xicheng and Miss He,
he didn't do it on purpose. He has his reasons.
Even if you break this door today,
he won't come out.
Grandma is already like that.
Let's not cause anymore trouble.
But I...
An'an, let's take it slow.
How about this?
Let Aunt Mei find a family doctor to keep an eye on Grandma.
Then I'll go
and check the nearby streets.
Miss He can't drive, so
she won't be far off.
Situ.
Fell in love with me? Let's get down to business first.
Let's go.
The number you have dialed is unavailable.
Please try again...
Where did she go?
Excuse me.
Have you seen a girl
as tall as you who has fair skin and
full bangs?
Sorry, I didn't see her.
[Property Room]
Excuse me.
Can you check
the CCTV for the entrance of Block A?
See if there is a girl about this tall
with a round face.
Excuse me. Have you seen a girl
[Three meals]
around this height with full bangs?
She's kind of cute and has fair skin.
No.
[Live for the spiciness]
Excuse me. Have you seen a girl
around this height with full bangs?
She should be in a low mood.
Sorry, I didn't see her.
An'an.
Your side?
Nothing.
Me neither.
Let's go over there.
Okay.
[An'an]
[Phone]
[Gu Xicheng]
[An'an]
[Unknown Caller]
[Reject][Answer]
Hello?
Xixi, it's mom.
Mom, you finally called.
Jinxi went out.
I borrowed the phone of the lady in the next bed
to call you.
How are you doing? Where are you?
How are you?
No matter how I asked Jinxi,
she wouldn't tell me.
She said you're doing well.
And you have a boyfriend. So I don't need to worry about you.
Mom.
I...
I'm doing well.
Really?
Yes.
I got a new job.
I often do livestreams.
The sales from the livestreams' room are also in the top ten.
I also joined a new company.
I can do what I like.
Mom, don't worry about money.
Just take care of yourself.
No matter how much it costs, I'll send the money to Jinxi.
As long as you get better,
all my efforts will be meaningful.
Xixi, why are you crying? Are you wronged?
Are you still outside?
My child, it's all my fault.
It's all my fault. I did this to you.
Don't think too much, Mom.
Mom, I have people around to take care of me.
My boyfriend treats me
really... really...
well.
Really?
Yes.
Mom,
you just need to recuperate
and come back early.
Mom,
I really...
really...
I really miss you.
Mom,
when are you coming back?
I miss you so much.
I'm not doing
well at all.
Stop avoiding it.
Since I saw it,
why can't you tell me?
Didn't we agree
to take care of each other?
I can help you.
I don't need your help.
If you can bear it alone,
all these things in the house won't appear.
Gu Xicheng,
the even number obsession
has become a huge burden for you.
You'll collapse if you keep carrying it.
Xixi, answer the phone.
Xixi!
Hello?
Gu Xicheng,
not going over to hit you now
is my last tolerance towards you.
What do you mean?
Don't you know?
In such a severe weather,
why is Xixi out alone?
Do you not have common sense on the danger of
being on the beach while there's a typhoon?
Let me tell you.
If anything happens to Xixi,
I will come for you.
What?
What's wrong with you two?
Why is she in a low mood?
She came to the beach alone.
Hello, Gu Xicheng?
Hello,
the subscriber you have dialed is powered off.
Xicheng.
No matter what happens in the future,
we need to give each other time to talk
and give each other a chance to explain.
Let's not argue. Let's not turn our backs and leave.
♫ Admit it ♫
♫ I just can't help missing you ♫
♫ Don't tell him ♫
♫ But eyes don't lie ♫
♫ Time can tell ♫
♫ Is this my wish? ♫
♫ Maybe insomnia ♫
♫ Is the price for falling in love ♫
♫ You know it ♫
♫ I don't know much loving words ♫
♫ Plant a flower ♫
♫ Wait for it to sprout slowly ♫
♫ Wanted to leave ♫
♫ But still can't let go ♫
♫ Betray myself ♫
♫ Is the price for falling in love ♫
♫ You are my dream ♫
♫ You also know my heart ♫
♫ Walking through the crowd ♫
♫ Only your voice was there ♫
♫ You are my dream ♫
♫ Walked here ♫
♫ Left with the final sentence saying you're also willing ♫
I'm sorry. Just now, at home,
I shouldn't have lost my temper.
I'm at fault too.
I shouldn't have looked through your stuff.
I shouldn't even have
tried to unveil your wound.
You're right.
It has been 20 years.
I've also shouldered it
for 20 years.
If I don't let it go,
I will be crushed one day.
Before I met you,
I didn't know how I survived.
The medicine at home
is the proof that I can't hold on.
I can never let go of the knot in my heart.
I can't face that
my brother passed away because of me.
I also can't forgive myself that
the whole Gu family was ruined because of me.
No.
No one blames you.
No one asked you to take the responsibility.
It was an accident.
Even your six-year-old self couldn't have controlled that accident.
But my brother really passed away.
I'm the only one left in the house.
Everything is only for me.
A pair of chopsticks, one cup,
one piece of clothes, a pair of shoes,
and only me.
You still have your grandma.
You still have me.
Xixi,
will you always be by my side?
Will you never
leave me?
There are too many obstacles between us.
We...
Xixi.
I don't care how many obstacles are between us.
Nangong Liuli, Fu Boya,
our past,
or my even number obsession.
These are not our problems.
Xixi.
I like you...
more than you can imagine.
I like you more than I expected.
I just want you to stay by my side.
Xixi!
Gu Xicheng!
♫ Admit it ♫
♫ I just can't help missing you ♫
♫ Don't tell him ♫
♫ But eyes don't lie ♫
♫ Time can tell ♫
♫ Is this my wish? ♫
♫ Maybe insomnia ♫
♫ Is the price for falling in love ♫
♫ You know it ♫
♫ I don't know much loving words ♫
Oh my god.
♫ Plant a flower ♫
Luckily I stopped you just now.
Otherwise, the boss would scold me to death.
♫ Wait for it to sprout slowly ♫
I didn't expect the president to
kiss in the rain
♫ Wanted to leave ♫
so passionately.
♫ But still can't let go ♫
♫ Betray myself ♫
An'an.
What do you think I want to do now?
♫ Is the price for falling in love ♫
♫ You are my dream ♫
♫ You also know my heart ♫
♫ Walking through the crowd ♫
♫ Only your voice was there ♫
♫ You are my dream ♫
♫ Walked here ♫
♫ Left with the final sentence saying you're also willing ♫