♪We'll face life's problems, always♪
♪Beautiful moments help us
along the way♪
♪I see your pain♪
♪And your bravery too♪
♪Some things we cannot just erase♪
♪And there's no time
to get stuck on the past♪
♪Greet the daylight♪
♪Go to the free♪
♪Let's cross the wind,
dance in the rain♪
♪Let the stars illuminate♪
♪In either way♪
♪Tears and fears, happiness♪
♪They are all part of the journey♪
=Double Happiness=
=Episode 10=
It really is Qian Hao
who's behind it.
He wants
the custody of Xiaomi
and wants to ruin my store,
leaving me penniless,
unable to support two kids.
Then he's really
shooting himself in the foot.
Since he won't stop,
then we won't be polite either.
What do you want to do?
Sue him.
Redistribute marital assets.
This stingy rooster, Qian Hao,
I'll pluck his feathers one by one
from him.
What's going on?
How did it become 2.7 yuan?
Why stare at me?
I didn't monitor it.
The backend is...
Who put up the link? Yao?
Yao, you were monitoring the backend.
Yes, but I locked the orders promptly.
Why?
Locked to this price?
Ten thousand orders!
What's the cost?
Alright, stop arguing.
What's the point?
Think of a solution.
How to solve this price?
Cheaper than wholesale price.
Quickly call Mei.
Let me.
Tell him to come.
Get him back.
What's going on?
Hurry up.
(Incoming call, Yao.
Answer, Reject)
Hello, what's up?
Mei, where are you now?
The project has a problem.
I'm almost there, just a bit of traffic.
The livestream link
was put up wrong.
It's supposed to be 27 yuan.
But now it's 2.7 yuan.
Over 10,000 orders have been placed.
Mei, what happened?
Nothing. Let's go upstairs.
- Rest assured.
- We'll...
- We'll come up with a solution today.
- Confirm the issue again.
Mei, you're finally here.
Alright, don't worry.
Mei, you're back.
What exactly is going on?
Mr. Chen blames
our new assistant broadcaster's
unclear communication with the platform.
The product was originally 40.
Livestream price
should have been 27.
Now suddenly, somehow...
- It has suddenly dropped to 2.7.
- Yes.
All the fans went crazy.
In one minute,
10,000 orders were placed.
When we realized it
and locked the orders,
over 300,000 yuan had been lost.
But...
Have they given an explanation?
Yes.
But they only agree to cover half.
They said when the link was up,
we didn't notice
immediately.
We share some responsibility.
Alright.
I'll contact the manufacturer.
No need, Mei.
The manufacturer
is surely overjoyed.
Someone covers the price difference.
And they got high sales
and gained advertising.
Exactly.
Mei Chengyi,
come to my office.
What should we do, Mei?
Alright.
I'll handle that old fellow.
Do you need me to come?
There are no vegetables.
No eggs, either.
I'll order some in a while.
Don't.
I'll just go to the market.
It's fresh and cheap.
Mr. You.
Grocery shopping.
That's a misconception
of your old ideas.
Foods sold on the apps
are fresh and convenient.
It can also save time.
If any issues,
you can contact them.
Save time?
For what?
Games?
As if your time
is so valuable.
I mean...
Youyou, you drive.
You come shopping with me.
Just think of it as
spending some casual time with me.
You're the customer
and you have the final say.
You...
Why are you stepping on my foot?
Smells good.
Then buy one of these.
Here to buy groceries?
You too?
Isn't this Youyou?
Didn't go to work?
Accompany your mom here?
Hi, auntie.
Youyou is beautiful.
Back in the country, still adjusting.
I let her stay at home
to spend more time with me.
I'm going over there to buy meat.
- Alright
- Talk later.
- Alright.
- Go ahead.
Goodbye.
Let me tell you.
It's a pity for Mr. You's family.
The eldest daughter
was both capable and sensible.
She fell ill and died early.
They spent lots of money
on this second child
to send her abroad
for a mediocre university.
It's of no use at all.
Now she is staying at home.
When
playing chess downstairs,
Mr. You always complained to others.
So young.
Living off parents at home.
Wasn't studying in vain?
Do you know?
Now many
young people
are all lying flat.
What do you want to eat?
Let me try it.
That one.
Okay.
Don't tell me
that you have no responsibility.
Two groups put forward
so many proposals.
The company trusts you.
I have the thought
of wanting to help you.
Such an important proposal
was handed over to you.
Your chosen partner erred.
It's your mistake.
Understand?
I understand, Ms. Li.
I won't shirk responsibility.
But now I think
it's not the time
to pursue responsibility.
I'll have the team
come up with a PR plan quick
and a plan to recover losses.
Is that okay?
Later,
I can take responsibility
or pursue accountability.
What do you say?
Now there's a problem with one client.
Then aren't other
clients afraid?
Let me tell you.
I only give you one day
to solve this.
For all subsequent losses,
the company isn't liable.
Keep that in mind.
If not handled well,
I can't protect you this time.
I know, Ms. Li.
Thank you, Ms. Li.
Mom.
Hello, I'll have this piece.
Chop it finer.
Angry?
What I mean is,
after Xu left,
we notice you have
some emotions to Mei Chengyi.
We have also reflected a bit.
Did we overlook your feelings?
We've been discussing it for ages.
Keep the best in the family.
We've always wanted to match you two up.
But who would've thought
that Xu
would suddenly appear.
Though,
we think she's nice,
but we definitely support you.
As long as you're happy,
then we can
break up any couple.
Mom, I was wrong.
I was wrong.
I don't like
Chengyi at all.
I'm angry
because I feel Mei Chengyi
is lying.
He seemed so set
on mourning
my sister forever,
that I wanted to
give him a chastity arch.
He even said Xu Kaixin is just...
Just what?
It's done, 68.
68.
Okay.
Just playing.
And now look,
they've quickly gotten together.
I just feel pity for my sister.
I know
he has to move on.
But knowing and seeing it
are two different things.
When you were with street boys,
we've seen you
kissing and hugging many times.
Now you let
a man in his thirties engage in
a spiritual relationship?
Don't mention street boys.
Mom, I'm sorry.
Let me take it.
Go, go, go. Let's go.
Seriously.
Ms. Xu,
you got divorced three years ago.
And now you remembered
to pursue the re-division
of divorce assets?
In these three years,
my ex-husband has never contacted me.
But recently,
their whole family
wants to get
the custody of my son.
They often make their presence known.
They've also
done many despicable things.
Since they won't stop,
then let it be so.
Yes, take the initiative.
They're addicted
to bullying good people.
Moreover, Kaixin
isn't someone they can bully.
She was kind of blind back then.
If you can't praise, don't.
Legally speaking,
if one spouse hides,
transfers, sells, or damages
and squanders
the couple's joint property,
during divorce,
this party can receive less or nothing.
After the divorce,
once the above behavior is discovered,
the other party can file a lawsuit
within the statute of limitations,
that is three years from the day
they know or should know it,
and request once again
to divide the couple's joint property.
That's even better.
Let's let go of three years'
resentment all together.
But there's an issue.
Legally speaking, there's no such thing
as a fake divorce.
So, the agreement you signed
to buy a cheaper house
in a good school district
is not valid.
But the two children are yours.
You, however, left with nothing.
Unless your children and your ex-husband
have no blood relationship,
this is indeed unusual.
So, we have a chance of winning.
A paternity test is necessary.
Additionally,
if there's evidence
to prove that during the marriage,
your ex-husband indeed used
improper means to gain profits
and invaded your property,
then it would be even better.
Are you saying
that we need to gather more
evidence to file a lawsuit?
That's right, but I want
to remind you that
if it's audio evidence,
it must be obtained legally.
Do not infringe
on other people's personal privacy.
Otherwise, it can't
be used as evidence.
You can record in public places,
as well as in your home or car,
using legal devices
to make normal audio and recordings.
These can be used as evidence.
Alright, we'll discuss it.
Thank you.
Okay, then discuss it yourselves.
It's been three years already.
Where to find the evidence?
Qian Hao is as cunning as a monkey.
He won't easily
leave evidence to you.
We must absolutely not alert him.
At the class reunion,
I have to endure him?
No, don't.
If you
speak gently
to them,
then Qian Hao and Xiaojiao
will be so scared,
that they can't sleep.
Makes sense.
These despicable people,
if not scolded a bit,
would overthink at home.
So, you see.
Just do whatever needs to be done.
Just don't mention the word
"lawsuit".
As long as we
collect all the evidence,
we'll file a lawsuit right away.
Didn't the lawyer just say,
public recordings
don't constitute an invasion of privacy,
and those done at home and in the car
are considered legal surveillance?
In this case,
there are still many opportunities.
This is good for us.
You seem quite carefree.
Not worried at all.
What's there to be upset about?
Think about it.
I originally didn't have these assets,
and I have been
living happily.
If I win this case
and get that money back,
it will bring me a fortune.
Life is already tough.
People at our age,
middle-aged beauties,
shouldn't make life more difficult.
Our cheekbones will sag.
Who's middle-aged?
I'm not even married yet.
Do you know why
I love you so much?
You're like a walking
emotion converter.
No matter how upsetting
things are to you,
you're positive
and output emotional value.
You can love,
but please don't love deeply.
I won't tease you.
You and Mei Chengyi,
what's going on between you two?
A twice-divorced man of his level
is sought-after
in my field.
I'm telling you.
He'll attract many female clients.
If you miss this chance,
I might take him away
to earn my membership fees.
You give it a try.
See if I dare to try.
Yes.
That's right.
You're right.
Well...
We can't
shirk responsibility
onto each other now.
We need to think
how to minimize this loss.
Please.
Just apologize in the live stream.
Call to request a refund.
I believe many netizens
won't take advantage of this benefit.
Isn't that right?
And I
am going to apologize
to the manufacturer now
and see if they can accept
our latest compensation plan.
Okay?
Alright.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Mei, how is it going?
What can be done about it?
The anchor said,
before listing it,
they confirmed it with us.
Who was coordinating at that time?
Mainly because it was
past 2 a.m.
Everyone was groggy
and didn't expect
to make such a mistake.
Alright, stop.
Don't cry.
Sorry, Mei.
Stop.
I've troubled you.
I know.
You go busy yourself.
Go be busy.
Go.
Last night,
he just sent me a question mark.
I was asleep and missed it.
I came here in a hurry
this morning.
I forgot about that.
Just send a question mark?
Is he
playing hard to get?
You know, ever since I saw
such a scumbag like Qian Hao,
I don't even
think my dad is innocent.
Why are you thinking so much?
About dating.
You have to date first.
I got divorced,
and I'm fine.
How did it stress you out?
Afraid of men and marriage.
There are many scumbags
and scumbag women.
If you stay clear-eyed,
then you're fine.
That actually rhymes.
Besides,
if we're still
troubled by love right now,
that proves we're still young.
Do you know the biggest audience
for these idol dramas?
It's us,
middle-aged beauties,
who are dreaming of romance.
In this world,
these women are scolding men.
If there were no men,
and all women,
then how boring is it?
Look at me. These past three years,
I've been vegan.
I've become out of shape.
I used to worry about you,
but now I'm worried about Mei Chengyi.
Middle-aged worker,
abused by the boss,
two kids,
parents
and former in-laws.
And now you
are staring with tiger-like focus.
No idea if he
has enough energy.
I hope he has a good gym routine.
(Xu Kaixin)
Five, four, three, two, one.
(Xu Kaixin
You have withdrawn a message.)
What's this trick?
Why did you redraw it?
This is playing hard to get.
Tease and run,
making him anxious.
Childish.
Every time
I come to this store,
sees everyone with bags big and small,
buying and leave,
I'm very envious.
I have to say.
That master
was actually quite accurate.
The things for good luck
were there for under a day,
and Hu Xiaojiao actually got pregnant.
This money was well spent.
I'm thinking about
finding him again in a couple of days.
Spend a little more money.
Maybe my illness will even be cured.
Mom, stop messing around, okay?
That's just a coincidence.
Coincidence.
Let's save some money
for medical expenses.
Why did you buy it anyway?
The child is still just a cell nucleus.
Talk about it later.
Son.
What's been wrong with you lately?
You've been glum
and easily irritable.
Are you hiding something from me?
No.
I don't want Hu Xiaojiao
to be too smug.
Why tie her worth to
having children?
What if
she'll be arrogant?
Look at you, son.
I know
that you're a filial son.
Hu Xiaojiao
does have a lot of faults.
But she'll pregnant for ten months.
It's not easy, is it?
Let's accommodate her if we can.
For the child's sake.
This illness of mine...
I could land
in the hospital any day now.
I'm thinking
that when my body could still move,
I can prepare things for my grandson.
Come.
Buy it.
This one.
This one is also good.
(N ways of natural miscarriage)
Oral medication.
It has no side effects.
Luckily, Hu Xiaojiao
is able to conceive.
If Xu Kaixin
really doesn't give Xiaomi back to us,
then with this baby,
I can also rest assured.
I even thought of a nickname.
Call him Duoduo.
Qian Duoduo.
I still want to do
a heritage certification.
Half of the inheritance
will definitely be yours.
The other half is Duoduo's.
I want to infuriate Xu Kaixin
and make her regret
losing the mountain of gold.
Mom, this money can't be his.
Why?
Isn't this your son?
Who knows
whether if it's a boy?
Right?
That's true.
I was too excited.
Right,
if it's a girl,
then what should we do?
Right, Mom, Xiaomi
is your grandson for sure.
Just consider Hu Xiaojiao's
kid as a backup.
Okay, don't take it too seriously.
But you were right about one thing.
We must take advantage of this,
to knock some sense into Xu Kaixin.
Let her
give back
Xiaomi's custody.
Right, she must know
Qian family's money
is all Xiaomi's.
Right?
Yes.
What should we do now?
Stop talking nonsense.
Our demands are very clear.
Triple compensation.
The original listed price
plus the original price,
multiplied by three.
Send this to my company's account.
Then this is over.
Otherwise,
see you in court.
Calm down.
Calm down for me.
Calm down, have some water.
- I'm furious.
- Come on.
Have some water.
I'm furious.
Do you think
it's simply these losses
on the books?
What's the situation now?
It's the peak sales period now.
If you don't want to cooperate,
then I can get other big influencers
to promote products.
Sales will shoot up
rapidly.
This year's sales could also potentially
break records.
And what happened?
Triple compensation
is even going easy on you.
And you still try to bargain with me?
Such an ungrateful thing.
Such...
I got mad.
Come on, calm down.
Calm down.
- Sit down.
- I'm furious.
Sit for a while.
Calm down.
(When I was a kid
playing Street Fighter,)
(defeating enemies,)
(I felt like the hero
of the entire world.)
(Only after growing up did I know)
(that was just)
(projection and outlet)
(for adults' failures
in the real society.)
(Being abused yet powerless to resist.)
(Hanging on.)
(Smiling while being maltreated.)
(This is often the adult world's)
(cruel truth.)
Class one go.
(Bindong Sunshine Kindergarten Kunde Campus)
Let's wait.
Wait until class one has left.
Catch up.
Has he come out yet?
Yes. Over there.
There.
Let's go.
Wang Ziyi.
Wang Ziyi, your mom?
I see him.
Yes, the second one.
Goodbye.
Alright, goodbye.
Wang Yuexin.
Great-aunt.
Are you happy?
Xiaomi.
- Xiaomi.
- Great-aunt.
Grandma.
Great-aunt.
- Xiaomi.
Xiaomi.
I know you, you're Dad.
Sister secretly gave me
a look at your photo.
Yes, I'm Dad.
Your dad.
Lili.
- Bye.
- Xiaomi.
We're leaving.
You can't just take him away like that.
How's it going?
Sorry.
Did I hurt you?
Sit down and let's talk.
You've been struggling all day.
Alright, it's fine.
That's how it is, Ms. Li.
About the live streaming.
Sixty-seven percent
effective refund.
I'm still continuously
communicating with them.
The original manufacturer
insists that we pay triple compensation.
I really negotiated the whole afternoon.
They've temporarily agreed
our live streaming team
will work double shifts
for three days straight.
The original slot fee
also remains unchanged.
It's effectively
triple compensation as well.
If the company stays profitable,
then it's easier to explain.
But this isn't considered settled.
Okay, I understand.
We need to watch the next three days
for our erroneous orders'
refund situations
and the sales results
of this double working time.
I'm currently working
on a new promotion plan.
Okay.
This overtime is justified.
But don't expect any overtime pay.
Where are your group members?
Live streaming room and platform.
I'll send the plan
to the group in a bit.
Alright.
Better late than never.
Keep it up.
You...
Your back is bad.
Get it checked promptly.
Don't blame others.
Come on, be good.
Eat and play.
Let's eat a bit.
Come over and have some.
Come on, Yule.
Listen to me, have a bite.
Be obedient.
After eating, you can play.
I'm telling you,
I'll complain to your dad.
Did you hear that?
That's a good.
Come.
Let's eat.
So good.
Look, your sister is eating.
She's eating too.
Right, let's have a bite too.
No.
Eat if you want, forget it if not.
What's wrong with you?
You two spoiled them.
Let his dad manage the kid himself.
He's off the hook,
dumping the kids
and going out to have fun.
Bad auntie, you're wrong.
Dad is working overtime.
It's very tiring.
Bad auntie.
Yes, bad auntie.
Working overtime every day?
Your dad is the only busy person.
Alright?
Okay.
Don't cry.
What are you doing? Alright.
I'll talk to her.
Don't cry.
Is this how you work
as the household manager?
Is this the family you manage?
Can't care for kids.
Made all the kids cry.
Caused chaos.
You do anything all day
but cause trouble for me.
This month's salary
is zero for you.
Don't think about scamming money
from me again.
What?
Are you rebelling?
Alright.
Isn't it like this every day?
Why make a fuss today?
Stop it.
You...
Fine.
Don't come back
if you step out this door.
Support yourself.
It's okay.
Let's eat, stop crying.
- Come.
- Why not stop her
and chase her?
You just toss out
"stop arguing"
and that's all?
Is she your daughter or not?
I bet you two are relieved now.
You just leave me to suffer alone.
I think I understand now.
None of you two
are good people.
Serves you right.
Listen to me.
I won't intervene today.
Without my intervention,
I want to see how you two vent.
You...
Fine.
Aren't you capable?
Why come back?
Dad.
Come, take a look.
What did I buy for you?
Come.
Do you like it?
- Yes.
Mom.
Dad.
Did you see anyone
downstairs?
Who?
My auntie.
She argued with Grandpa
and ran out.
Grandpa's very angry.
He asked Auntie never to come back.
Isn't that because of you two
don't eat properly?
It's not that.
Auntie spoke ill of Dad.
Yes, Auntie is bad.
I don't want Auntie anymore.
Auntie didn't mean that.
Come on.
You two go play.
Come, play.
I'll call Youyou.
Build blocks.
She left her phone
in her room.
Then...
When she went out,
she was very emotional.
So, what should we do now?
What do you mean?
Isn't it caused by you?
Caused by me?
- You.
- Don't, dad.
She can't go far
without her phone.
I'll find her.
Don't worry, she's not a child.
Not your daughter,
of course, you're not worried.
Did you forget when her sister left,
she swallowed many sleeping pills
and was sent to for a stomach pump?
Dad, that was an accident.
Accident?
If something happens, then it's real.
Are you a mad dog?
Isn't it always because of you?
Me?
Why me?
Dad.
I'll go find her.
- I want to go too.
You two stay here.
- No.
- I want to go.
Don't make me repeat it.
Go back.
You see, as the saying goes,
parents' words,
are the feng shui of their children.
Can't you give the kids
some verbal blessings?
Well, now it's good.
Chengyi is even angry.
You...
You've done a lot
and gets no good out of it.
Just because of your foul mouth.
Sorry.
It's fine.
(Only three seconds in the elevator)
(are when adults)
(show their truest emotions.)
(What's funny)
(is that most of us)
(even find these three seconds)
(a luxury.)
Let's play a game.
Dami, do you like it when I come?
Xiaomi.
Want to fly on a plane?
Come on, take off.
Flying.
Fly up.
(Happiness)
(It must be the way)
(I opened it.)
(Or, did I)
(enter another)
(parallel universe?)
You are back.
(This is my daughter.)
(This is my son.)
(And this is Lili.)
(That's right.)
(But these two...)
(Why are they here?)
(Can anyone tell me)
(in this space,)
(what's our relationship?)
- Mom.
- Mom is back.
Kaixin.
Why come back so late?
I called you and you didn't answer.
I picked up Xiaomi from school today.
I saw Qian Hao with his mom.
I didn't want to pay attention
to him at all.
But Xiaomi saw his dad
and seemed very happy.
I thought I was in
a parallel world.
Nonsense.
I mean...
But you can't
let them come here.
Qian Hao and his mom
said they want to talk to you
about the future inheritance issues.
I've called you, but you didn't answer.
I recalled
Dami said before
"Do you want money or face"?
My mind got confused
and I brought them back.
You old lady.
Always about money.
Then I...
Did I make a mistake?
It's okay, I'm here.
Well,
we've had enough fun, right?
There's not much food.
So, I won't keep you for dinner.
Kaixin, can you let the kids
stay with my mom a bit longer?
Let's go out and talk.
Kaixin.
You know my condition, right?
Let me spend more time with them.
How about it?
(Really a good actor.)
(If I hadn't found out)
(the filthy things you did secretly,)
(maybe)
(you would have fooled me again.)
Okay, let's talk.
Let's go.
Xiaomi.
We can play now.
Your mom has left.
(Joy)
Go ahead.
How have you been lately?
Just be straight.
Hu Xiaojiao is pregnant.
Congratulations.
I don't know why
but I just can't be happy.
I keep thinking about
you with Dami.
That was one of the
happiest times of my life.
When you had Xiaomi,
you were so beautiful.
Qian Hao.
Your desire to perform
is strong.
But don't do it
in front of me.
Lili told me
you need
to talk about our property distribution.
Kaixin.
Xu Kaixin.
Or Ms. Xu.
Alright.
Xu Kaixin, okay.
I know.
I know in your heart,
I'm just
a complete scoundrel.
But I regret it
very much now.
Especially today,
I spent an afternoon with the kids.
I truly realized
what I've really missed over the years.
My mom wants a grandson.
She's gone crazy, you know?
She's even going to make a will now,
to leave everything
to the child in Hu Xiaojiao's belly.
Can I agree to this?
Impossible.
I have to stop her.
We need to chat.
Right?
In my heart,
Hu Xiaojiao's kid
will never compare
to Dami and Xiaomi.
Qian Hao.
I think
you're really outstanding.
You keep refreshing
my understanding of the word shameless.
I suggest you go to the hospital,
to get treated
well
for your schizophrenia.
I don't know what
happened between
you and Hu Xiaojiao.
However,
it is you who tripped up my cake shop
and show loyalty here,
my ex-husband.
I wonder does
Hu Xiaojiao know
she has such
an excellent husband?
We're talking about us.
Why mention Hu Xiaojiao?
Hu Xiaojiao.
Did you hear that?
(Hu Xiaojiao)
Please manage your own husband
stop him from trying to
make him presence in front of me.
Say hello.
Xu Kaixin.
You have no sense of chivalry.
This is called shamelessness.
But I learned it all from you.
What a joy!
I...
She has improved.
I think I should also go find her.
Stop.
If you can't find my daughter,
then don't come back.
(Come on, sis, you go first.)
Good.
Look at me.
Okay?
Sis, you're amazing.
See, like this.
Not bad.
I hit two this time.
Two!
Come on, again.
Great job, sis.
I'll find another one for you.
Okay.
Youyou.
Where did she run off to?
Chengyi?
I'm here.
Where?
Chengyi.
I'm here.
Oh my.
I finally found you.
I mean...
Without a phone,
you run away from home.
Do you know that your mom and dad
are worried?
They won't be.
They can't wait
to get rid of me, this burden.
I'm afraid the burden isn't you.
It's the three of us.
Alright, let's go back.
I'll try my best
to trouble your parents less.
They're getting older.
And it's quite hard.
Let's go.
That's not what I meant.
Chengyi, do you
want to cut ties with us,
because
of your new girlfriend?
I know women can be unreasonable.
I didn't expect
they can be this unreasonable.
You were afraid that your parents
would meddle in this
and told me a girlfriend
would break their hopes.
Why are you
blaming me now?
I have no feelings
for you.
I'm just standing up for my sister.
You changed your heart too fast.
You kept telling me that you
were only on a blind date with Kaixin,
and just asking her for help.
But you got involved so quickly.
Don't you feel sorry for my sister?
Once people leave,
feelings fade quickly.
At least transition a bit.
I know your feelings for your sister.
I don't want to lie.
I did indeed have some feelings
for Xu Kaixin.
However,
I didn't feel I did wrong
by your sister.
Your sis left
three and a half years ago.
No matter who I'm with in the future,
your sister
is the irreplaceable love of my life.
On the other hand,
I'm not a saint.
I'm not some kind
of idol drama male protagonist.
I'm just an ordinary,
middle-aged man.
How could I live in
widowerhood for a lifetime?
No, if you...
Help!
Someone jumped into the river.
Hurry, help!
I can't swim.
I'm afraid to go in.
Help!
Did anyone call the police?
- Go down there.
- Find a pole.
Pull him up.
I'll call.
- Well...
- Save him.
Dad.
♪A river connects
the two ends of the city♪
♪A lamp illuminates the day and night♪
♪A memory marks the passage of time♪
♪Always half lost, half happy♪
♪Who is not struggling yet optimistic♪
♪Whose life is not lively yet lonely♪
♪Whose story is intense yet ordinary♪
♪Always half perfunctory, half sincere♪
♪How many of us
have wandered through the chaos♪
♪How many nights
have you seen thunder and lightning♪
♪Looking left and right throughout time♪
♪I luckily turned the tide
when I met you♪
♪If youthful courage
had never been exhausted♪
♪Fearless simplicity
wouldn't have become a regret♪
♪In our long story,
nothing is a coincidence♪
♪The sky is always half night♪
♪Half dawn♪