A wind that only seems gentle
Your gaze shimmers with a dark undertow
Who is laughing at my madness
yet indulges my startled heart
I see through your mask
and let you probe my limits
It is I who indulge
Love blazes like fire
spreading
Hard to say who crossed the line first
and who is waiting for whom to yield
Sharing rouge-scented smoke
and the flame that collides at our lips
fiercer than any tender lingering
a duel that stakes our pride
whether a calamity decreed by fate
or sweetness bestowed by heaven
I still choose craving, wrath, and folly's
mad notion
made real
To hold your gaze is far too perilous
I walk devoutly toward my ruin
You are my abyss
You are my
sunshine
"To My Shore"
Shulang.
Don't go.
Please.
Don't go
I'm the kind of man
who can't stand seeing people “being nice.”
I only believe people are born evil.
Kindness never survives a test.
Once self-interest is involved,
no one can truly be kind.
At first, I thought you were a fake saint,
So I played dirty,
I tried to force you to
reveal your true nature.
But
I realized you really are a good person.
You're too selfless for your own good.
You want to fix everyone's problems.
The more you did that,
The more I felt ashamed of myself.
I don't believe that shit.
I wanted to drag you through the mud.
But I found out.
I've already fallen for you.
And
I just want you to be kind only to me.
But I won't admit that I love you.
I thought that if I just got you into bed,
It would burn through
this tension inside me.
I could walk away easily.
But when you...
started uncovering my lies slowly,
I panicked.
I don't care who ended the relationship.
The warmth I had just felt,
the joy I had just experienced,
the thought that all
of this would disappear...
And vanish,
I didn't expect it to hurt this much.
I started...
threatening you again and
again to keep you close.
Again and again.
I was wrong.
But what else could I do?
What else could I do to make you stay?
Shulang.
I'm willing to pay any price.
Please give me one more chance.
Let me atone.
Shulang.
Let's start over, okay?
Okay?
Fan Xiao
I used to rack my brain...
why would you treat me like this?
Turns out it was just because
I'm a “good man.”
All of that.
My work.
My family.
You wrecked my life.
You destroyed all the little
comfort and happiness I had.
Fan Xiao.
All of this.
Was just because I was kind?
Fan Xiao.
When I poured my heart out for you,
what were you doing to me?
Insulting me.
Lying.
Contempt.
Threats, again and again.
Where do you get the
nerve to ask for a fresh start?
Don't you think...
that not killing you is...
already the biggest mercy you'll get?
I deserve to die.
I know I belong in hell.
Shulang.
Save me one last time...
please, one last time.
Fan Xiao.
You're right about one thing:
I overestimated myself.
I thought I could save you.
But in the end,
You dragged me down with
you into the abyss.
No way back.
No one can save you...
except yourself.
You mean…
Fan Xiao.
If you truly want to atone,
let me go...
and let yourself go.
I can't.
Exactly as I expected.
Fan Xiao, do you know?
You've proved every bit of
the “human evil” that you preach.
Fan Xiao.
I can already see our ending.
If you don't push me to death,
I'll make sure you die first.
Fan Yu.
Give me the drive.
(Episode 12)
Handle it yourselves.
And send me the other party's file.
I want to see it now.
I simmered pork-bone soup.
It's good for healing.
You've lost too much weight.
Drink it while it's hot.
I'll take you to the hospital.
I won't go.
- Cold water will do.
- No, it won't work.
If we don't treat the
wound, it'll get infected.
I'm not going to the hospital.
Shulang, please listen to me.
It will really get infected
if we don't treat it.
I'll go buy burn ointment.
Don't move before I come back.
Shulang
I'll apply the medicine for you
I'll do it myself.
Shulang.
Are you going out?
Shulang, can you tell
me where are you going?
Are you meeting someone?
You're good at tailing people, right?
You can come with me and see.
Go ahead.
I won't follow you anymore.
And I won't interfere in your affairs.
As long as you allow
me to stay by your side.
Your greatest harm to me is...
that you still won't leave.
How did you lose so much weight?
That bastard Fan treated you like this?
- I'm going to call the police.
- Don't be rash.
The video captured by the
dashcam doesn't count as spying.
And he didn't distribute it.
The video was hacked and taken out by you.
If you really report it to the police,
it isn't clear who would
take responsibility.
Then his imprisoning you
doesn't count as a crime?
He didn't imprison me.
It's just that I...
Whatever.
What's your plan now?
If you need help, just let me know.
Say whatever you need.
That video.
Was it hacked from Fan Xiao's computer?
I majored in computer
science and applications.
If my dad hadn't forced me
to take over the business,
I wouldn't have given up my dream.
Now all I can do is deal with scumbags.
Can you hack into any computer?
Not every system can be breached.
Depends on the security level.
Can you check if this
program can be modified?
Let me see.
This?
Sure, easy.
Are you planning to
use it against Fan Xiao?
How should I thank you?
Thank me?
I...
You watched the video too?
No.
I...
I just saw the beginning.
When I realized something was wrong,
I closed it immediately.
I'm not as twisted as Fan Xiao.
You know that.
I'm spiritually a platonist.
No physical contact for me.
Then tell me how I should thank you.
No need to thank me.
But.
If you leave Fan Xiao,
can I go after you?
It's not a quid pro quo.
Just a request.
Could you give me a chance?
Sorry.
I'm not looking to date right now.
Then I'll wait till you are.
I'm young.
I can wait.
I'll send this to you when I'm done.
I'll leave now.
Director You.
When will Fan Xiao die by your hand?
I'm dying of impatience!
Second Young Master.
What grudge do you have with Fan Xiao?
Why so desperate to bring him down?
No need to spell it out, Director You.
It's just a struggle for power and profit.
Three brothers, three mothers.
The eldest's mom was the wife.
The third's mom was the old man's favorite.
But my mom was kept outside.
Of the three sons, I'm the least promising.
Even that old fellow Xu Zhong
wouldn't even look at me
when choosing his son-in-law.
Either the unmarried third,
or the divorced eldest.
So if I don't fight for it,
Do you think that in this family,
I would even have a place to stand?
Director You.
Third brother has been working
from home most of the time as of late.
He also took his work laptop home.
Just use the drive I gave you.
Insert it into the computer.
Enter a simple command.
All the data on his computer
will automatically transfer to me.
Then everything will be done.
But Director You
I've waited so long.
How come I haven't received any data yet?
Second Young Master.
You might as well change the path.
Send the data to me.
Then I'll file the report.
Not only will it vent my anger,
but it will also clear
you from the situation.
And you'll avoid other people
criticizing you for inter-family fighting.
Wouldn't that be even better?
Good.
This third one really
hurt Director You badly.
Don't worry.
As long as I get the evidence
I'll definitely make a copy for you.
Then you can do whatever you want with him.
However you like.
Second Young Master.
I guess you're so eager to get the
evidence from Fan Xiao's computer,
not to bring down Fan Xiao,
at least, not only to
bring down Fan Xiao...
Could it be that there's some
secret of yours hidden in this data?
I have no power in the company.
What secrets could I possibly have?
Just a little joke.
Don't take it to heart,
Second Young Master.
I tried.
Fan Xiao's computer is password protected.
I couldn't get in.
So.
I had the intention,
but lacked the ability.
How come?
You've changed your mind?
Limited ability.
Sorry to disappoint you,
Second Young Master.
Director You.
Don't rush off.
It's only been a few months.
You've triggered three acute
stress episodes in Fan Xiao.
He's about to knock his head bloody.
And you call that “limited ability”?
He's only 18 years old.
When he saw the sea again,
he had such a severe stress reaction.
So, Director You.
Don't be modest.
Try again.
Whatever conditions you want,
I'll try my best to meet them.
Don't be polite with me.
Alright.
Then I won't force you, Director You.
Since the first path didn't work out,
there's still the second path.
You want revenge, right?
Then why don't you come with me?
We'll go together as a pair.
When Fan Xiao sees us,
he'll definitely explode with rage.
How does this plan sound?
We'll finish it right away.
Okay.
As long as the Second Young
Master is willing to lie down,
let me take the top position.
Director You
I didn't mean it that way.
I meant we...
could just pretend, not to actually do it.
I was with Fan Xiao before
only because he was good in bed.
I didn't expect to end up with a madman.
So my advice to Second Young Master is—
Don't start the game lightly.
Or you'll end up with nothing.
Everyone loses.
That You dares to trick me.
He's really hard to deal with.
But this time wasn't a total loss.
Back then, I was with Fan Xiao
just because he was good in bed.
I didn't expect to end up with a madman.
So my advice to Second Young Master is—
Don't start the game lightly.
Or you'll end up with nothing.
Everyone loses.
Fan Xiao, oh Fan Xiao.
You hopeless romantic.
If you hear this and then
bash into a wall again,
doesn't that mean it's the end for you?
Shulang.
Can you help me with something?
Can you look at these files on my computer?
They are two similar drugs.
I'm not sure which one
has better market potential.
You're an expert in this area too.
Why ask me?
All I know is sales.
The rest is just superficial.
These two drugs are
based on the same formula,
But one uses authentic ingredients,
the other uses northern herbs.
The price difference is significant.
I'm not sure how to judge it.
Can't we leave Mr. Fan
if we don't take a look?
Give it to me.
The information's all here.
I'll go get you some water.
Do you still have yesterday's
pomegranate juice?
There's still pomegranate.
I'll juice it for you.
Take your time to look.
Just follow the code I
gave you and input it.
The data will automatically
save to your email.
Yesterday's pomegranate
juice was a bit sour, you said.
You barely drank it.
This time, I added some honey.
See how it tastes.
Though the authentic herbs are more
expensive because of their higher quality,
their price has remained
high over the years.
But the price they
quoted you is still inflated.
To find out how much higher,
we need to check the historical
price trends of the herbs.
And the planting output for this year.
We can analyze that comprehensively.
If President Fan has no other business,
I'm going to sleep.
Shulang.
Can we tonight?
Didn't President Fan always
do whatever he wanted?
When did he ever care
about others' intentions?
I don't want to force you.
"Don't want to force?"
Fan Xiao.
You've messed up my whole life.
But now you want to imprison me.
That might take more effort.
Do you know why I didn't leave forcefully?
Because, since I couldn't
escape your control,
you've become nothing
more than a tool for me.
An adequately functional piece of bedding.
As long as I still serve
some purpose to you,
I'll be content with that.
Shulang, you've been drugged.
Shulang
I will find that sick
bastard who did this to you.
You must get payback for this.
So your partner is actually a man?
Shulang.
You are sent by heaven to save me.
I wish to prostrate myself
beneath your lotus throne for all eternity.
Am I not trustworthy?
Or have you developed a
habit of making things up?
Have you gone paranoid?
I should've killed you.
Don't get your hands dirty because of me.
Don't stain your hands with blood.
It's not worth it.
It'll happen soon, just like you wanted.
It won't be long.
What do you mean?
Mom.
I haven't come to see you for a long time.
Last night I dreamed of you again.
And Chen.
He followed us.
He was shouting “Brother, Brother.”
He was fighting to get the
wooden windmill you made for us.
Today's the grand opening.
Uncles and aunties are
coming to visit the welfare home.
How should the children behave?
Be good.
Great.
Parents, please come in.
How cute!
Let's go.
This child looks handsome and elegant.
Let's take him.
I'm about to give birth.
When will you send him away?
Speak softly.
You just fell asleep.
We just adopted him less than a year ago.
How should I talk to the welfare home?
Then just drop him at
the welfare home's door.
He's already this big.
He can walk in by himself.
From now on, you can live with us.
Come here.
From now on, this is your
little brother Chen.
Chen.
He will be your older brother from now on.
Come.
Put on your little brother's clothes first.
Look at your hands, they're freezing.
Mom.
Sorry.
If you hadn't adopted me...
Silly child.
This was just an accident.
Accident.
No one is at fault.
Mom.
The best decision I made
was bringing you home.
Mom had selfish reasons too.
Because I was worried about Chen.
He was lonely by himself.
So I went and found a
good older brother for him.
From now on,
you'll be the one in charge
of taking care of Chen.
Mom.
Don't worry.
Lang.
From now on, if you like someone,
remember to bring them to me.
Let me see them.
Male or female.
Doesn't matter.
Mom.
Sorry.
I didn't take good care of Chen.
Maybe you really shouldn't
have adopted me back then.
Then you and Chen would be
living happily now.
But Mom.
There's one thing you were wrong about.
Living your best life, until the end...
doesn't mean you'll find happiness.
Mom.
I'm a bit tired.
I always feel that the you in
my dreams is the real world.
You in the portrait.
Chen on the railing.
And the vicious Fan Xiao.
They're all fake.
Whenever it gets to this point,
I wake up.
I wake up from the beautiful dream.
Mom.
I miss you.
Can I come find you earlier?
I want to eat the dumplings you made.
The fennel filling.
When did you stop playing with matches?
Switched to skewers.
Come in.
Fan Xiao.
What's been going on with the cleaning
at my place these days?
What's the situation?
The hotel meals have barely been touched.
The guest room door's
been closed the whole time.
I knocked as per your request.
They said it was for housekeeping.
What did the person inside say?
Said no need.
All right.
You can go.
Yes.
Wait a moment.
When the hotel delivers the meals,
ask them to send some pastries too.
They should be the kind
that tastes fine even cold.
Also,
don't make them too sweet.
Got it.
Why don't you like sweets?
How do you know I don't like sweets?
The first time I bought you milk tea,
you said you didn't like sweet drinks.
The first time you smoked Rouge,
You said it was too cloying.
When I was in the orphanage,
the conditions were bad.
We didn't get to eat sweets.
Later, when the leaders came to inspect,
the orphanage bought tons of candy.
They gave it to every class.
We were all really looking forward to it.
We waited the whole day, excited.
But after the leaders left,
they took the candy back.
I got stubborn and thought,
“It's just sugar.”
“It's just candy.”
"How good can it be?"
I told myself I didn't like sweets.
After a while, I tricked myself.
And eventually, I
really didn't like sweets.
You never stayed at the office before.
You were always watching
over me like a bodhisattva.
How is it that now,
you've started staying in the office?
Maybe only when I'm not
around him can I keep him safe.
Boss.
Your guest has arrived.
All right.
Good luck.
I'll leave now.
Mrs. Boss.
You're looking for me?
Young You.
You finally turned on your mobile phone.
It's about your Mr. Huang.
You can't just go in like that.
Move aside.
I'm not done yet.
Mr. You.
You can't go in by yourself.
I need to report to the boss first.
You'd better move out of the way.
Shulang.
Huo.
No one can stop Mr. You
from doing the things he wants.
Stop following him.
Yes.
Go prepare some snacks.
Nothing too sweet.
Yes.
Why?
What do you mean, why?
I've already left Changling Pharmaceutical.
Why did you still sue my teacher?
You came to find me?
Are you here to demand an explanation?
No reason.
I'm just in a bad mood.
Bad mood?
Yeah.
Bad mood.
Your Mr. Huang keeps
opposing me on certain issues.
Then let's forget everything.
Who told him to run
into the barrel of the gun?
Do you know?
Because of this incident,
Professor Huang was
disoriented and fell down the stairs.
He fractured his ankle.
What?
You're going to blame me for this too?
Shulang.
If you're here to plead
for Professor Huang,
I'll withdraw the lawsuit right away.
You know that.
Anything you want me to do,
I'll get it done immediately.
Other than coercion,
what else do you have?
Yes.
I've pleaded.
But you've already made up your mind.
To be honest,
I didn't sue Huang Qimin
to force you to compromise.
It's just that I felt awful inside.
If I don't do something,
I'll suffocate.
Shulang.
Let's stop torturing each other, okay?
All my mistakes, I admit.
You can punish me however you want.
As long as you come back to me.
Fan Xiao.
Coercion and threats aren't your specialty.
I've got something in my hands right now.
If I release it,
it should cause quite a stir.
You Shulang.
Whatever you have,
Huang Qimin signed the contract with me,
It's real and valid.
Even though I'm not the GM of this company,
Huang Qimin and his
team are all legally liable.
What's more,
he probably can't afford the
penalty for breach of contract.
If he dares to scam
me with unfinished work,
I'll sue him for commercial fraud.
That way,
it won't just be about
paying money anymore.
If Professor Huang goes to jail,
the project will stop.
The compensation won't be enough.
Your initial investment won't be recouped.
What's the benefit for you in doing this?
You Shulang.
You said it yourself,
I'm a madman.
What reason does a madman need?
I just want a quick fix.
If I'm not happy, no one else gets to be.
Anyone I can drag down, I will.
As far as I know,
the lawsuit has reached mediation.
The mediator suggested
both sides take a step back.
If Changling Pharmaceutical can complete
process optimization within three months,
they'll hope you withdraw the lawsuit.
Yes.
But if I don't agree to sign,
the case won't last two days in mediation.
And three months isn't enough
to complete the optimization.
What's more,
three months isn't enough
to finish the optimization.
Even though I'm an outsider,
but I roughly how much time
each step of the process takes.
If Changling Pharmaceutical can finish
the optimization within three months,
will you let it go, Mr. Fan?
Why?
Because you once promised,
you'd unconditionally grant me one request.
Director You, why are your lips so pale?
What do you think?
All brute force.
No technique at all.
No wonder you broke into a cold sweat.
Sorry.
I didn't think it through.
I shouldn't have done that.
Okay, okay.
It's fine.
Director You.
You're really good to me.
From now on, I'll go through
hell and high water for you.
I'll die a thousand deaths if I must.
What are you laughing at?
You don't believe me?
I'm serious.
I believe you.
Director You.
I'm really serious.
As long as you're willing to ask,
I'll take the moon for you,
I'll dive into the five oceans
to catch a turtle if you wish.
I've really taken it to heart.
Then from now on, unconditionally
grant me one request.
Come here.
Come into big brother's arms.
Three months—no more, no less.
I'll wait for your good news.
Director You.
Professor Huang.
We got three months.
Though it's tight,
But if you and your
team work day and night,
there's still a glimmer of hope.
Shulang
I've hurt my foot.
We have a few key members in the team.
I heard we've been sued.
People were already uneasy.
Now they've all left.
No soldiers, no generals.
Even if you get us three months,
I don't have any hope left.
Young You.
Come help me.
Help me hold the fort.
Professor Huang
I'll go back and help you.
I'll hang up now.
Then I'll call you again later.
Okay.
Fan Xiao.
I'm really not used to your bunker.
You really love paying
the electricity bill, huh?
How's it going?
What I said on your phone...
is it okay?
Mr. Huang.
You still need to work on your acting.
Don't blow your cover.
Oh, you young people...
I really don't know
what you're all fighting about every day.
You scared me half to death
just now in the next room.
I've never done anything wrong in my life.
Now I'm old,
and I'm tricking my own student.
Thank you, Mr. Huang.
We reap what we sow.
I'll head out.
Your leg was tripped by your dog.
It has nothing to do with me.
Why are you adding extra drama?
Essentially,
there's no difference.
In the crowd
I was spotted in an instant
The desolation in your eyes
Hiding the same fire inside
No need for words
No need to ask what's right or wrong
The moment we drew close
The outcome was already destined
Is the moth drawn to the light
Or the whale sinking into the deep
With nothing but solitary courage
I wager it all on tomorrow
The walls of the world
What does it matter if I break them down
My chest burns with heat
Screaming only for you
I'll love you until it boils over
Loving without a care for the world
Like two stars
Colliding and shattering in the night sky
Even if it's just for a moment
It's more than enough to surpass forever
Hate and love both burn brightly
Loving until the sky falls dark
Loving until we reach the end of the road
Before the altar
We burn all the incense
Not asking for the next life
Only desiring this moment
Drowning together with you in
This blazing fire of fate