A wind that only seems gentle.
Your gaze shimmers with a dark undertow.
Who is laughing at my madness
yet indulges my startled heart.
I see through your mask
and let you probe my limits.
It is I who indulge.
Love blazes like fire
spreading.
Hard to say who crossed the line first
and who is waiting for whom to yield.
Sharing rouge-scented smoke
and the flame that collides at our lips
fiercer than any tender lingering
a duel that stakes our pride
whether a calamity decreed by fate
or sweetness bestowed by heaven
I still choose craving, wrath, and folly's
mad notion
made real.
To hold your gaze is far too perilous
I walk devoutly toward my ruin.
You are my abyss.
You are my
sunshine.
"To My Shore"
Rarely does a gift affect
me right to my core.
I've got a meeting in half an hour,
so I can give you ten minutes before that.
I brought Lu Zhen to
apologize to you, Ms. Shi.
Apologize for what?
Men and women—love is about chemistry.
If Little Lu isn't into me,
I can't force it.
Honestly,
at my age,
if I try hard enough I could
probably give birth to him.
Lu Zhen,
What are you waiting
for? Apologize to Ms. Shi.
Ms. Shi, I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
I have let you down egregiously.
I didn't know better.
I didn't understand the situation,
I...
Lu Zhen,
If you're apologizing, show some sincerity.
Is Ms. Shi's time just for
you to waste by rambling?
Ms. Shi, I was wrong.
I accepted the date without
understanding the situation.
Please forgive me.
Why does everyone make
me out to be the villain?
If I were you that day,
I wouldn't have let Lu Zhen
walk out of that club in one piece.
And I wouldn't have
waited around all day today,
carving time out of a
packed schedule to see him.
So “villain” doesn't suit you at all.
Lu Zhen,
Who told you to get up?
What...
did they assign Little Lu a new agent?
Ms. Shi,
I'm Lu Zhen's ex...
You Shulang.
Ex what?
Boyfriend?
So the agency recommended a gay guy to me?
Please don't be upset
it has nothing to do with the company;
this was all Lu Zhen's fault.
He wanted the endorsement
and wanted to build connections,
but he didn't communicate
clearly with the agency.
He accepted your request while in a daze,
but he knew he shouldn't pretend
to be straight and deceive anyone.
He chickened out that night.
The company was furious...
and wanted to teach him a lesson.
That wound on your
forehead—someone hit you?
I had it coming.
At least you've got a conscience.
Better than the ones who pop pills and still
pretend to be straight to get the job done.
So, Little Lu was your…
ex-boyfriend?
Yes.
And you still step up
when your ex is in trouble?
This is the last time I'm doing this.
I'm paying him back for what we had,
and after today,
I'm done.
Why did you break up?
He's such a good boyfriend.
Guess you weren't satisfied.
Some men
can't share hardship;
some can't share riches.
If I'd met a decent man,
I wouldn't be booking pretty little boys
every night to pass the time.
Lu Zhen is young.
He idealizes everything...
love, work.
He stumbled this time,
and I hope that he'll
definitely learn from it.
So.
Please, do us this kindness
and forgive him.
Not many men will lower
themselves for an ex.
I'll accept this favor from you,
Mr. You.
I won't replace the spokesperson.
Lu Zhen...
I liked you
because you reminded me
a bit of my ex-husband when he was young.
Just don't become as black-hearted
as he turned out to be.
I'm sorry—really sorry.
What a pity, Mr. You.
If you liked women,
no matter the cost,
I'd make you mine.
You're kind
and beautiful,
You'll meet the right person.
The right person…
have you met yours?
Before that night,
I thought I had.
(Episode 9)
Sawadee ka.
This way, please.
There you are, Director You.
Second Young Master,
Sorry to keep you waiting,
Not at all...
you're ten minutes early.
Refined taste...
finding a traditional
troupe like this in Bangkok.
Just putting on airs.
I'm learning from our third brother...
sampling the sights, cuisine,
and beauties of Hua culture.
Let's be direct.
What did you want to see me about?
I heard
you and Fan Xiao broke up.
Is it true?
It seems like you have something to say.
If we're going to talk in circles,
we might as well enjoy the show.
Fine...
Then I'll lay it all out on the line.
After what he did to you,
you really don't want revenge?
What's funny?
So Second Young Master
has sounded the war drums...
and wants a blade to wield.
We each get what we need.
Don't say I'm using you as a blade.
And in your view,
how should I take revenge?
There are a million ways.
I've found you the
simplest, quickest path...
to vent your anger
and make some money.
To vent my anger? How?
I'd love to know.
Don't you want to hear
how you profit first?
I heard you've been selling
your apartment to repay Fan Xiao.
No need.
Help me with one thing...
and everything on this cheque is yours.
All the money in this
cheque is yours.
It's more than enough to cover
your brother's debt
and then some.
You get your anger out and walk
away with cash—best of both worlds.
That much?
What do you need me to do?
Nothing hard.
Just slip this drive
into Fan Xiao's work laptop—quietly.
And that's all.
And then?
Then we wait.
He's doing something illegal?
Director You,
If he ends up in handcuffs,
won't that make you feel better?
I watched him build the tower high;
I watched him feed his guests;
I watched the tower collapse.
[TN: Quote from the classic play "The
Peach Blossom Fan" by Kong Shangren]
Second Young Master,
there's nothing left between us.
Settle your family feud yourselves.
Thank you for the tea...
but
it's gone cold.
Director You,
Director You, wait. Sit.
I never took you
for a man who stands idle when insulted.
I've got a recording of Fan Xiao...
don't you want to hear
how he talked about you with others?
You wiretapped him?
Our third brother is
too careful and sharp...
I can't wiretap him.
I bought the audio from the Shi family...
It seems like they have someone on call.
I thought it was interesting,
so I bought the audio they
recorded while spying on him.
I didn't expect what I heard.
Even I thought he went too far.
Director You,
Wanna hear?
No need.
Not interested.
When life gets boring,
I used him to kill time.
When I've had my fill, I get rid of him.
Since he's being ungrateful,
then I'll coax him back,
then dump him hard.
Director You,
You can accept that?
I wouldn't be able to at all.
As far as I know,
Fan Xiao still has a thing for you.
Why don't you pretend
to make up with him...
earn his trust...
and then
slip this drive
into his laptop?
Then it'll be mission accomplished.
You'll make money
and vent your anger.
Why not?
Second Young Master,
If you like the recording,
keep it.
You're brothers...
special hobbies aren't surprising.
I'm going after that pervert.
Have fun.
For now, it looks pretty good.
You wait, You Shulang
I love you.
I mean it, You Shulang.
When life gets boring,
I used him to kill time.
When I've had my fill, I get rid of him.
Since he's being ungrateful,
then I'll coax him back,
then dump him hard.
What's the matter?
Bai Ting,
I need a favor...
get someone drunk for me.
How come I've never seen you...
Are you new here?
New?
I'm just not enough for you to see me.
I'm hurt.
Isn't Bai Ting the sweet-and-pure type?
Look at her outfit.
Those lashes on her
lids could rake my face.
She wants to latch onto Third Young Master.
Everyone knows
he likes 'em curvy and bold.
How can my sweetie stop feeling wronged?
Want me to buy you a bag?
How could I make you
spend money, Young Master.
How about
three penalty shots instead?
Fine, fine.
Tonight
I'll drink with you till you're happy.
But before we drink, let me have a kiss...
What the—who are you?
It's you.
You're...
It's me.
Don't remember?
Didn't you try to kiss me like that once?
So…
Third Young Master swings both ways?
The hell I am!
Don't try that extortion crap.
I didn't so much as put a finger on you.
Young Master,
How could you be so heartless?
I came today
to relive old times with you.
Get lost.
I don't do men.
The hypocrite who ruined you
was Fan Xiao.
You want nostalgia?
Go find him.
What,
you get addicted to being molested?
You're sick.
I just pitied you.
Didn't you used to think
he was a “good guy”?
Young Master, you're scaring me.
Come on—let's keep drinking.
Party on. Don't mind him.
Freak.
Come on—don't mind him.
Let's drink.
Mm.
Bai Ting...
let's go.
The hell is your problem?
Young Master,
It's fine—really.
You go. It's fine.
Come on, keep drinking.
Come on—cheers.
Come on...
I envy you—you found your soulmate.
“Soulmate”?
Bit much, isn't it?
What do you want...
to sleep with me?
You just want to fool around...
you're just itching for something new.
You Shulang,
I love you.
I'm serious.
My future—everywhere I look, I see you.
I don't think
I ever did anything to hurt you.
I put you first in everything.
I thought of you in all things.
So why...
why do you hate me so much?
Fan Xiao:
If you're going to lie
to me—then lie forever.
I'm not lying.
Don't reject me.
Hello?
Lu Zhen:
Let's meet tomorrow afternoon.
Bring the painting Fan Xiao gave you.
You didn't come out
before when I called you.
Ever since you dumped that You guy,
I can finally ask you to come out.
You should've dumped that You guy earlier.
Let's go.
Get in my car and let my
assistant drive us back.
No, thanks.
I'll call a chauffeur.
You're as stubborn as a mule.
Drive safely.
Okay, okay, let's go.
Let's go.
Fan Xiao.
Shulang.
In didn't expect you'd come to see me.
I went to see Bai Pengyu.
How'd you find him?
He haunts these bars too.
Do you remember what you said that day?
The day after I was assaulted,
you sat in the car and told me,
This one must be paid back.
Today I used the gloves you bought me.
Guess that makes your word good.
I also prepared a pair of
lambskin tactical gloves.
I know you're happy with my hands.
How about tonight?
Fan Xiao.
Can I trust you?
Even though I'm no one special,
I have my dignity.
You're going to lie to me?
Then lie forever.
Don't let me find out.
This is the greatest mercy I can give you.
Fan Xiao.
You're my high-stakes gamble.
Can I win?
Looks like there are
no winners in this game.
Only losers,
and those who lose worse.
I can't run anymore.
Mom...
Fan Xiao.
It's just a dream.
It's not real.
I'm here.
Fan Xiao:
It's really over between
me and You Shulang.
Shulang.
What will it take for you
to let it all out?
Fan Xiao.
You're nothing special.
Back then I beat Bai
Pengyu for ten minutes.
And I'd do the same to you.
Something's changed. You always pulled your punches.
Now every hit lands.
That means you're not doing the same to me.
You want special treatment?
Then I'll oblige.
Fan Xiao.
That painting you gave Lu Zhen...
it seems like you left me a line of text on it.
A bodhisattva never falls into sin;
If he won't fall,
drag him down.
Here,
translate it...
in Thai.
You're my bodhisattva
and my god.
Fan Xiao.
Now I really can't imagine
what all the Thai you
whispered in my ears everyday meant.
What did they mean?
Fan Xiao.
You're in hell and still want to drag me
down there with you, huh?
Is that so?
Where'd this loser come from...
daring to lay hands on my brother.
Get out!
I'm really minding other people's business.
Fan Xiao.
If I ever interfere in your life again
I'll eat my hat.
Thanks for that just now.
Now I'll take a minute off.
Fan Xiao.
One last time, I'll ask you...
why did you treat me this way?
It's all my fault.
Here's the money my brother owes you.
The PIN is written on the card.
Fan Xiao.
Do you believe there's a god in this world?
I've always thought the
pendant on your chest
looked ominous.
Now that I'm really looking at it,
it turns out that it looks like you.
But it was originally
meant to guard the house.
And you...
should belong in hell.
I know I'll go to hell.
But I don't want to go now.
Because there's no you in hell.
You Shulang:
I'll be in hell,
but I won't find you there.
My god.
I don't want to go down.
Is it too late now?
Xiao.
Come to mom.
Mom.
Don't be afraid, baby.
I'm here with you.
Mom.
Fan Xiao.
Dear, don't be scared.
Come to mom.
Mom, where are you?
I only have one match left.
I...
If I light it, will I see you?
Mom.
You told me to live,
But you didn't tell me
who I should live for.
Fan Xiao's Mother?
Let's go.
We can't wait anymore.
We can't wait—hurry up and drive.
Mom.
I miss you so much.
I want to come find you.
What happened?
Has our Xiao been wronged?
Mom.
Dad is so scary.
Brother and the others
don't like me either.
Yes, the people who
deserve to die are still alive.
How can I die?
I have nothing.
Then no one gets to be happy.
You won't have nothing.
You still have me.
You Shulang:
I'm here—it's okay.
You Shulang.
Fan Xiao.
From now on,
Don't show up in my life again.
And don't let me see you again.
You Shulang.
Come back.
Come back here.
You really don't care about me anymore?
You said you loved me.
You told me not to care about any of it.
You said you'd protect me.
Why don't your words count?
You say you love me, then love me.
If you say you don't love me, then don't.
Are you not a bodhisattva?
Where is your compassion?
Didn't you come to save me?
Why are you abandoning me?
You Shulang.
Who gave you permission to leave me?
Did they all leave?
You all left?
No one wants me?
I can finally die as I wished.
Huang Qimin.
Hello?
Mr. Huang.
The equipment on the left will arrive soon.
Come on, come on.
Send it over.
Hurry up.
What are you doing?
Can you do it?
You Shulang.
What's Director You doing now?
Don't worry about the game.
Looks like staying in the
dorm won't work long-term.
Better move out soon.
Mr. Huang...?
Hello, Mr. Huang.
You're in Thailand now?
You little rascal.
You love teasing me.
Back in school, you were the
one leading the “Boss Huang” chant.
Now that you've graduated,
no one will call me
“Professor Huang” anymore.
Here,
Got the best Tieguanyin from
the factory manager's office.
To make it up to you.
Try it.
Joking aside,
you're still the thoughtful one.
You remember I like tea, huh?
You said you needed me
for something on the phone.
While I'm in Thailand,
this R&D team wants to invite you to join.
To invite me to join the R&D team?
Yeah.
Did you read the materials I sent you?
You mean the honeysuckle drink, right?
Yes, that project.
Once we can optimize the process,
it'll be quick to produce and launch.
No other pharmaceutical companies involved?
There's some support.
But the focus is on
developing the Changling brand.
Once we get this project up and running,
we'll be able to roll out other projects one by one.
For all of these popular products in Thailand,
we'll can use the Changling brand
and bring them to market.
The investors say,
as long as marketing is done right,
we can easily make the brand a success.
The investors?
There's already funding?
Yeah.
Where else would we get the money?
And besides, we only know R&D.
We're not in sales.
Hmm.
Shulang.
You're my best student.
You were overqualified for our school from your exam scores back then.
You had such great graduate scores.
But you rushed to work to
support your younger brother.
You couldn't continue your studies.
And you ended up in a
job that wasn't in your field.
And in my heart of hearts,
I've never let it go.
So, now this must be a result of our unfinished
teacher-student bond.
I'm in Thailand.
I can't do it here without someone I trust.
Come and help your teacher.
Teacher.
The thing is, my job...
"Though none may lend a hand to lift my lofty dreams,"
"I shall tread through snow and reach the mountain's peak."
I know that you've relied on yourself
to make it to to where you are at Bohai.
And it wasn't easy.
But really ask yourself...
do you like this job?
Can't say I like it.
Toasting and chatting.
Welcoming and sending off.
I've long grown tired of it.
But right now,
you're worried about the pay?
Don't be.
Didn't I tell you we have investors?
Come be my deputy team lead
and manage all the external affairs.
I'll pay you… this much.
My, you've certainly changed a lot.
Boss Huang has really become a boss!
Right.
I heard you sold your apartment,
and need a place.
The investor's covering more than money...
offices and housing are included.
If I stay at Bohai,
I'll inevitably see Fan Xiao again.
He's unpredictable,
and I've already
been far too irrational in this relationship.
Maybe leaving now
is the smartest move.
Well?
You in, Shulang?
Sir...
I'll follow however you plan it.
Good.
Then it's a deal.
The project's already started.
I need you on-site ASAP.
So...
hurry up and resign tomorrow and come over.
Tomorrow?
I'll need time
to hand over my work.
And...
who's the investor behind this team?
It's…
Xinruida.
Funding stuff isn't your lane.
You definitely wouldn't know them.
Mm.
All right, sir.
I'll get on it quickly.
Sir.
Ah, Shulang...
have a seat.
Sit.
Shulang,
thanks to you leading the cleanup,
this room finally looks
presentable, hahaha.
Professor Huang,
what's the deal with the investor?
I still know nothing.
You just arrived; your
to-do list is a mile long.
Investors are just money men.
No need to study them.
Anyway, they'll be here in a minute...
we'll talk as we meet them.
Mm.
Mr. Huang...
your guests are here.
Please.
In the crowd
I was spotted in an instant.
The desolation in your eyes.
Hiding the same fire inside.
No need for words.
No need to ask what's right or wrong.
The moment we drew close.
The outcome was already destined.
Is the moth drawn to the light.
Or the whale sinking into the deep.
With nothing but solitary courage
I wager it all on tomorrow.
The walls of the world.
What does it matter if I break them down.
My chest burns with heat.
Screaming only for you
I'll love you until it boils over.
Loving without a care for the world.
Like two stars.
Colliding and shattering in the night sky.
Even if it's just for a moment.
It's more than enough to surpass forever.
Hate and love both burn brightly.
Loving until the sky falls dark.
Loving until we reach the end of the road.
Before the altar.
We burn all the incense.
Not asking for the next life.
Only desiring this moment.
Drowning together with you in.
This blazing fire of fate