Oh man, what's going on?
They took over your room.
- Coming through!
- W-Watch out!
It's so heavy.
Did you wipe the box? Is it clean?
Yes and yes.
I thought my fingers would rip off.
- Watch out.
- Be careful.
There.
Hey, don't slam it down like that.
I have neighbors downstairs.
- Sorry.
- Shinpei, where does this go?
Just put it near that Hikone-like figure.
Where?
Here?
- Stop!
- What?
- Watch it!
- Fine, sorry!
H-Hey!
Oh, no.
Could you put this somewhere over there.
Got it.
A NEW CHALLENGE IN BED
A NEW STAGE: THREESOME
So heavy.
There.
My lower back is killing me.
We have more?
This is a story about
these three and their marriage.
Two Husbands One Wife
We have no place to go back to.
We didn't renew our contract
for our apartment.
You idiots.
Sorry.
Think of it as a part of the trial.
We'll look for a new place,
so let us stay for a little while.
Living together
will only end up in disaster.
You don't know that!
Oh, I know for sure.
Okay, for example.
Shinpei.
What do you think of this?
What do I think?
You went to toilet earlier.
Why did you leave it like this?
Why didn't you change
the toilet roll for the next person?
There's some left.
Hear that? This is why.
This is too little for one sitting, right?
This isn't enough
to wipe your butt, is it?
That depends on each person.
One more thing.
It's been bugging me since the trip,
but when you leave the toilet
you don't close the toilet lid.
Why is that?
It is so that
others could smell your excretions?
- No.
- No?
No, right?
Then why leave it open?
U-Um...
Shinpei.
A person's true colors
really show in how they use the toilet.
There is your weird toilet theory.
You see, during the two and a half years
I dated Mia, I was constantly troubled
by her arrogant selfishness.
That's why I gave in
and followed your rules, didn't I?
You gave in reluctantly.
That doesn't mean you changed.
I promise.
I'll change the toilet roll
and close the lid.
We'll see.
It's easier said than done.
Oh, then how many times a week
do you do your laundry?
When it piles up?
See! That's what I'm talking about!
Why do you have to wait
for it to pile up? Wash it everyday.
Wait. Then,
what about the dishes?
When do you do them?
When they pile up.
Why? Why do you let them pile up?
You don't earn any reward points for it.
Right?
When do you clean the room?
When it gets dirty.
Don't let it get dirty.
You idiot!
Don't call him an idiot!
Idiot. You're both idiots.
I bet you two live in a messy room
like nothing's wrong.
You sleep on garbage bags
as you get bitten by ticks.
Oh, then.
How many times a year
do you wash your bedding?
Bedding?
We have to wash them?
This can't be happening.
This is a nightmare.
Okay, that's it.
I'm assigning you chores
for each day of the week right now.
You have to stick with it, okay?
Do it every day!
If you're assigning chores,
that pretty much means
you've accepted to live with them.
I'm so tired.
I didn't think
it'd take five hours to set rules.
Do not underestimate Takuzo.
Wait.
We shouldn't do it today.
Come on. I just want to cuddle.
Don't you two dare make out in my room.
We won't!
Goodness sake.
So, just out of curiosity,
if we're doing the three-person marriage,
are the three of us
going to have sex together?
Yeah, about that.
I thought that might be a possibility too,
so I've been gathering information on it.
But let's take our time to decide on this.
It's a sensitive topic after all.
I see.
So until we decide on it,
the two of us can't have sex either?
Well,
judging by the way he was,
I think we should show some respect.
- Wha...
- I forgot something.
Nothing. We're not doing anything.
Two Husbands One Wife.
Feeling aroused.
Very aroused.
Very very aroused.
Even more aroused.
Stay strong.
A samurai glories in honorable poverty.
ROYAL RESIDENCE KYOBASHI
Arousal
turned to disgust.
Game of tag with our fingers.
With your requirements,
we can only
offer you a one-room apartment.
If it's a wooden building,
the neighbors could hear...
Very disgusted.
Hey, don't say that here.
Very very disgusted.
Sorry, I have something stuck in my teeth!
- We just had lunch.
- Yes, that's right.
Something's stuck.
- Hey, Takuzo.
- Yeah?
Have you ever had a threesome?
My friend with benefits
wants to give it a try.
But I'm not really into adventurous sex,
you see.
A NEW STAGE: THREESOME
No.
I could never do stuff like that.
Well... There's no way I can.
This conversation is over.
What?
I'll go get a coke.
Takuzo, you say
"I'm home" when you come home.
- Welcome home, Takuzo.
- Hi!
I-I'm home.
- Come and sit.
- Come on.
Wait, I haven't washed my hands.
- Wet towel.
- Thanks.
Sit down.
- Hurry.
- What is this?
Shinpei, did you make all this?
I've been cooking
since I was a kid. Go on and eat.
- Hurry.
- Right.
Then, thank you for the meal.
Th-This is so good.
What is this?
Oh, I just bit into something very tasty.
Oh? What was it?
I used whatever was left in the fridge.
- Leftover ingredients?
- Yeah.
To make this?
That's impressive.
You're really amazing.
You're praising me so much?
You'll make me blush.
- We should eat too.
- Let's eat.
Ready?
- Let's dig in.
- Let's dig in!
Okay.
It really was tasty.
Huh? You seem to be enjoying this.
Maybe everything will work out well.
Two Husbands One Wife.
Oh, darn.
A week later.
DUTY ROSTER
A WEEK AFTER THEY MOVED IN
SHOPPING LIST
TEA (2L)
- You're drying them outside today?
- Yes.
I like how the clothes feel more fresh.
I know what you mean, I like it too.
I'll help.
Sure. If you want.
Takuzo, your phone is ringing.
Hello? What's up?
What?
Sounds like I should deal with it.
Okay. I'll be there in a bit.
- Is it work?
- Yeah.
I need to go to the office.
I haven't done
any of my chores today though.
Don't worry about it.
You have to go to work, right?
Yeah. Thanks.
Sorry.
- Hey, Shinpei.
- Hmm?
The TV's remote control
isn't working properly.
Which is the right one?
They ended up going with the initial plan.
I'm going to take it as a compliment
that my blueprint was perfect.
I'm sorry.
How about I treat you to dinner
after this? To make up for today.
- Welcome home, Takuzo.
- Hi!
Thanks, but I'll go home today.
Really?
That's a surprise.
Right?
See you.
You're leaving already?
You even bought cakes for them.
You must have liked
being welcomed home by them.
We're home.
Hi, we're back.
Was everything okay at work?
Where were you?
At a dance event.
He performed at the last minute.
Just a little.
What about dinner?
You haven't eaten? We ate on our way home.
What's that?
It's nothing.
- You want tea?
- Yes.
Do we have enough?
There isn't much left.
I wrote it on the shopping list.
When I was leaving
you said not to worry about the chores.
Huh? Yeah.
If you're busy, you can do it tomorrow.
A normal person would think
that you'd take over the chores
from the conversation
we had earlier today.
But it's your turn.
A normal person would be
considerate enough to help.
What normal person?
You could've just
asked us to do it for you.
Actually, I thought
we should take over for him.
What? Now you tell me?
I thought we'd do it when we got home.
And that?
Oh, I forgot.
Are you kidding me?
I said I'm sorry. I'll do it now.
It's fine. I'll do it.
You go dance, okay?
Hey.
- What's with you?
- Who cares?
Why don't you two just play around?
- I'll do it.
- Stop!
- Hey, what are you doing?
- There's no point doing it now!
Did you buy those... for us?
They're ruined.
Mia?
It's good.
I want one too.
Thank you.
It's delicious.
Open up.
What?
Take a bite.
Come on.
It's so sweet.
Takuzo.
I'm sorry.
Me too.
I'm sorry too.
Then...
Let's shake hands and make up.
Are we good?
Yeah.
Do you think
we'd have worked out
if we just apologized like that back then?
We used to get stubborn
over trivial things, didn't we?
It's just a little, but I thought
that maybe
this three-person thing is not so bad.
Okay.
Then, can I ask you one more thing?
What is it?
What should we do about sex?
This is just one of the options, okay?
What are your thoughts on
having a threesome?
What about you?
Can you do it with me?
Does that mean, you can't?
Sorry.
To be honest, I don't know.
Well, of course.
We can take our time to figure it out.
Right.
Damn it.
I won.
- One more game?
- Why?
- Why not?
- You're too obvious.
You don't get jealous?
Why would I? They're both men.
Friendship is love too.
I want to know how you felt.
It's hard for me to be around you.
Subtitle translation by: Aya Kudo