Takuzo, your beer!
Oh, crap!
Are you okay?
Wait.
What was that?
What was what?
Oh, the kiss?
No particular reason. I just felt like it.
What?
So...
You do stuff like that for no reason?
Well, I guess so.
It's a casual way to show affection.
But...
What's going on
with you youngsters these days?
You really surprised me.
But don't do that again.
You idiot.
My bad.
Are your shoes all right?
The next morning.
Oh, my.
Last night,
this happened.
We're home.
Hey, be careful!
Guys! Wh-What happened?
You reek of alcohol!
- Mia!
- Welcome back!
We're going fishing tomorrow.
Let's go.
What?
When it comes to family activity,
it's gotta be fishing. Right?
I'm going to bed.
We're going to the beach tomorrow!
What are you talking about? Huh?
- Tuna!
- Huh?
You can't catch Tuna.
Good night.
Wait for me, Takuzo! Takuzo!
Huh?
It's great they've gotten closer.
Isn't it, Mia?
Yes, for now, at least.
Two Husbands One Wife.
What fishing?
They decided without me.
I already have plans, you know?
Swaying.
Please
don't hate me, okay?
Shush. You'll scare the fish away.
Sorry.
Actually, this wasn't what I had in mind.
But...
We woke up past noon,
we're hungover
and we have no fishing gear.
We can leave if you want.
No.
Why did it have to be fishing?
You forgot?
Huh? Oh.
Well...
I had a lot to drink
so my memory is a bit...
Fine, then.
My family... didn't get along so well.
My dad was pretty abusive.
So, fishing is the
only good memory I have of my family.
Mom, help.
Shinpei, careful.
What a shame.
They just bought that for you.
Wear this.
Are you sure?
It looks good on you. Keep it.
Not fair.
You look cool, Shinpei.
It was fun back then.
Soon after that,
our mom got sick and died.
In the end, our dad became an alcoholic.
One day, he just left us and disappeared.
Did you have anyone to rely on?
Like a relative.
Some relative took us in.
But it was horrible there.
When my older brother turned 20,
he rented an apartment for the two of us.
He got through college on scholarship
while taking care of me.
Now he's doing really well
as a businessman.
That's impressive.
Yeah.
He's incredible.
He always said he never wanted to
inherit that scumbag's genes.
Over and over again.
But I did.
I'm stupid, you see.
I think he can't forgive me
for being a loser like our dad.
Shinpei, you're not a scumbag.
Thanks.
But to my brother,
dancer isn't a real job.
He thinks I'm playing around.
He said he doesn't want to see me
until I get a proper job.
It'll be okay.
He'll understand some day.
You think so?
Of course.
I'm sure of it.
- You got a hit!
- Oh!
- Wh-What do I do?
- Hold the rod and pull.
- Pull? How?
- Hold it.
- It's big.
- It's huge!
- It really is.
- Well done, Takuzo!
- Wow, look at that!
- I caught one! In here?
- Yeah.
- I did it!
- Great job, Takuzo!
Yes! Yay!
- Look at the size.
- It's so big!
Fishing sounds fun though.
You really think so?
Why go through all the trouble?
You can buy fish at a supermarket.
You're so mean.
Why are you angry?
I'm not angry!
Thank you.
It's not your ex's hobby, is it?
Takuzo is an indoor man.
Shinpei's never mentioned
fishing before either.
I don't get it.
Well, it's great
your husbands are getting along, right?
Come on, cheers.
Cheers.
But it's also baffling
to see them get close so suddenly.
- You jealous?
- It's not that!
I just feel a little left out. That's all.
Forget it.
Don't mind me.
What is it that you wanted to talk about?
- Right.
- Yeah.
We decided to become foster parents.
Foster parents?
Same-sex couples can become parents too.
I thought
our family bond will be stronger
if we have a child after all.
We had a
pretty serious discussion about it.
Wow. You guys have
really thought everything through.
Of course.
What about you guys?
You want kids?
I've thought about it.
When you actually have a child,
one of your husbands
will probably end up getting hurt.
What?
Give me a bite.
What are you doing?
Thanks.
Eat yours.
The wife and one of the husbands
can be their biological parents,
but I think
the other husband will feel alienated.
They might not be related by blood,
but if they live together it won't--
Sure, in an ideal world.
You won't know until the time comes.
That's why it's best for your husbands
to build a strong bond while they can.
But it's great, huh? Now they're
even going out on dates together.
I wouldn't call it a date.
Why not?
If it's a three-person marriage,
the husbands
can have a sexual relationship, right?
Hey!
It stinks.
Smells like fish.
Ugh, mine too.
Hey, don't do that!
It stinks! Stop it!
Your hands are freezing.
I'm sensitive to the cold.
You sound old.
So warm.
Nice and warm.
No way. Never.
It's Takuzo we're talking about.
That hard-headed,
stubborn as a mule, Takuzo.
That's never gonna happen.
Sorry.
It's getting cold.
Should we head home?
Were you able to
relive your memory a little?
I guess.
You need help?
No.
I told you
not to fool around like that.
You know, you're...
Never mind.
Now I really understand how Mia felt.
What does Mia have to do with this?
I told you two to go live together
if you like her so much.
That's harsh.
Ouch.
You cut yourself?
Come on. Give me your hand.
I'll do it myself.
Just let me.
I'm sorry.
If I made you angry,
I apologize.
Do you know what I'm upset about?
Forget it then.
No.
Please.
I'm really bad at this.
I don't understand
other people's feelings.
But...
I want to change.
I...
I want to know more about you.
It's not fair.
Mia knows so many different sides of you.
I want to know too.
Different sides of me?
I wonder what you're like
when you're having sex with Mia.
I just wanna try it.
I promise not to hurt you.
I...
I can't.
I mean...
I've never even imagined
doing things like that.
Then, try imagining it.
Well...
But...
I'm getting hungry.
I'll go cook something right now.
Your hands.
They're cold.
So?
What do you want?
It hurts me
to see you cry.
Don't make me cry then.
Okay.
What's wrong?
Well,
I can't get in bed with dirty socks on.
They are moving on
to the next step without you.
Are you going to be okay, Mia?
Takuzo and Shinpei?
Yeah, right.
I can't do this!
I totally misunderstood
and thought both guys were into me!
I always went along with what you like.
If Mia doesn't come home...
It's for Shinpei, isn't it?
I've always been selfish.
Subtitle translation by: Aya Kudo