Home alone.
Morning alone.
An unmarried man, having a coffee
he made for himself, on his own.
Takuzo Mitsuda.
TAKUZO MITSUDA
FIRST-CLASS ARCHITECT/SINGLE
He is a protagonist of this story.
He's trying to think about marriage
like a grown-up.
DIVERSIFIED MARRIAGE
THE CONCEPT OF MARRIAGE
HAS CHANGED SIGNIFICANTLY
Domestic partnership, same-sex marriage,
weekend marriage, and roommate marriage.
His thoughts on marriage are...
It's become so diverse.
Nothing original.
He's not interested at all.
Well, not yet, at least.
Let's shift our focus to her.
ANAGUMA REAL ESTATE
Now, the contract is complete.
Great.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, too.
She, Mia Yanoguchi, is also unmarried.
MIA YANOGUCHI
REAL ESTATE AGENT/UNMARRIED
She's sort of the protagonist too.
This is for everyone.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
Thank you so much!
Hope you like it.
The first episode
is mainly from her point of view.
I'm so glad I met you, Ms. Yanoguchi.
Your words just extended my lifespan
by ten years!
She's pretty good at her job.
A customer gave us curry bread.
I'll make coffee.
Thanks.
She's the type
to enjoy the latest trends as well.
But aren't you a vegan?
No, I'm a flexitarian.
Let's eat!
But...
CELEBRATING YUKI
FINALLY, THIS WEEK
SHE'S GETTING MARRIED TOO, HUH
When it comes to relationships
and marriage, she's no good.
She suddenly becomes outdated and useless.
Here.
Thanks.
Something wrong?
That's the problem with you.
To be frank, our group hasn't disbanded
because Keiko is here.
It's all thanks to her.
That's true.
Don't fight.
For starters, our group name is...
Useless Mia is dating a younger man.
A dancer with an annual income
of 2.4 million yen.
Shinpei.
Huh?
I have my friend's wedding this weekend.
I know.
You told me.
I'm sorry I'm spending
a lot on wedding gifts recently.
Everyone seems to be getting married.
Sending a "maybe we should too" beam
to her uninterested boyfriend.
Oh, by the way,
he's also one of the protagonists.
Shinpei Satomura.
SHINPEI SATOMURA
DANCER/UNMARRIED
Isn't it rare?
Not many people get married these days.
Yeah. They're all so old-fashioned.
I mean, hello? It's the 21st century.
I know.
Marriage isn't the only way to happiness.
I've heard that a million times.
I really do get it.
But...
But still.
Hey, Shinpei.
Are you free this Saturday?
Huh?
Yeah.
WELCOME
YUKI AND EMIKO
OUR WEDDING RECEPTION
Now, please exchange your rings.
Congratulations, Yuki!
- Congratulations, Yuki!
- Congratulations!
They're beautiful. And they look so happy!
Take the hint.
Feel the pressure.
You two are now a married couple.
It's a little different, but that's that.
This is amazing.
Right? They look happy.
How does this work legally?
It's pretty formal.
They sign contracts and everything.
- Contracts?
- Yeah.
It's called an agreed contract.
They decide what to do
with their assets or if they have a child
and submit it to the city hall.
So, marriage is pretty flexible.
That's right.
It's like signing a contract for a house.
Marriage is not a burden.
I see.
Whatever happens in the future,
let's face it together hand in hand.
So that I can protect your smile
and to live our lives happily ever after.
With all my love.
I look forward to our lives together.
Mia.
I've come up with an incredible idea.
I might be able to handle marriage,
if it's not two people.
What?
If it doesn't have to be male and female,
it doesn't have to be two people, right?
Um. Wh-What kind of logic is that?
An odd number is better, right?
I wouldn't want too many people, so...
Three.
A marriage of three might work for me.
Yeah? Congrats on your great discovery.
Yeah. That will work.
I don't think I can support you by myself,
but I can if there's another person.
That way we'll also
be more stable financially, right?
Um, hang on.
Are you actually serious about this?
Of course.
I mean, you want to get married, right?
What? Did I say that?
You didn't, but I can sense your beams.
I'm struck by them every day.
Just so you know,
I want to get married too if I can.
Really?
But a two-people marriage is so hard.
There's so many responsibilities.
Wouldn't you be scared
to trust your life to me?
Think about it.
But if it's three people...
Yeah, I see it.
I can see the light.
- What? No.
- It'll work.
No, no.
Why--
Huh?
Congratulations!
Congrats!
Let's look for someone
who's willing to get married to us.
I'm home.
And so...
- Let's find someone. Yeah?
- What? No, no.
Someone who'll marry us.
This is a story
about these three and their marriage.
Two husbands, one wife.
Three people? What does he mean?
She's been distressed since that day.
What's wrong with him?
Very distressed.
RENTAL APPLICATION FORM
What kind of situation is that?
Very distressed.
Very very distressed.
They do say
two heads are better than one.
I can understand the logic.
No, I don't! This is crazy!
We don't need you!
Who are you anyway? Geez!
What?
- Hey.
- Yeah?
My ex-boyfriend just messaged me.
Okay.
His pet died
and he's holding a funeral tomorrow.
Oh, I see.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Um, I took care of it
when I was with him. So...
Oh, of course. You should go.
What?
Y-You don't mind?
Not at all. You should go say goodbye.
Oh, right. Yeah.
Ten percent of me thinks he's kind.
Ninety percent is thinking,
show some jealousy!
And so.
MITSUDA
I brought him with me.
It's been a while.
Yeah.
Oh, he's the guy I told you about.
I'm Shinpei Satomura.
Hello.
Maybe he'll get jealous
if he actually meets my ex. Or not.
Sorry. He really loves animals
so he wanted to pay his respect.
I-I do?
Can we come in?
- Sure.
- Then maybe
he'll change his mind
about that idiotic idea.
I'm happy you came, Mia.
Even if you have such ulterior motives.
It's been in the hospital
for about a month.
I see.
But it was almost 100 years old
in human years. It lived a good long life.
Apologies for the late introduction.
I'm the rabbit, Pakkun.
PAKKUN
RABBIT
For a while, I've been watching over
Takuzo, Mia, and Shinpei
from up above in heaven.
The opening footage
is a video of me when I was still alive.
Thanks to Takuzo,
I was able to live a happy life.
Now, let Mia's
I'll-make-him-feel-jealous plan begin.
Why did you choose a rabbit?
Because Ushijima in
Ushijima the Loan Shark had a pet rabbit.
Right?
Jealous yet?
I see.
Who'd think that after reading that comic?
You're such a weirdo.
- Jealous yet?
- Oh, shush.
Where's the jealousy?
But I like the rabbit scenes too.
It's kind of therapeutic.
- Don't force yourself to be nice.
- No, I really mean it.
Zero jealousy.
What? You made all these?
Well, I wouldn't say I made them.
I just paint and modify them.
Wow.
You've always been
good with your hands. Right, Takuzo?
Takuzo?
Complimenting and calling my ex
by his given name. How's that?
I really admire you, Takuzo.
I'm terrible at these things.
Can you show me more?
It didn't work.
Okay.
I've had my eyes on the one over there.
Which one?
H-He's warming up to him instead.
One hour later.
I prefer the SEED series too.
Right? I'm so happy to hear that.
Everyone seems to have
a different opinion on that.
Why did it turn out like this?
In the end,
she's distressed. Very distressed.
Hey, Mia.
What?
Why did you
break up with such a great guy?
Excuse me?
Well, he's funny and reliable.
He's awesome.
Hey, um...
You shouldn't say that.
Why not?
Well...
Hearing you say that
kind of makes me feel bad.
Huh? What do you mean?
Because he was annoying.
He always came to pick me up
in his car if I was out drinking,
or when I missed my last train
no matter how far it was.
He drove in the rain
to come get me with an umbrella.
He always came to pick me up!
I really hated that!
That's why I broke up with him!
Huh?
I don't get it.
Don't get what?
Um...
That's just being kind. Isn't it?
No.
I'm too much.
I get that a lot.
Even in this situation,
Takuzo offered to drive them home.
Takuzo is such a nice guy.
Say, Shinpei.
Did you say that
because you don't want to get married?
The three people thing?
What else?
It's the opposite.
I want to be with you forever,
so I want to figure out a way to do that.
I want to carry my weight
as much as I can.
I said it on a whim,
but I've been thinking about it since.
And now...
I'm pretty serious.
Oh, he's here.
What happened?
Sorry, this happens a lot these days.
What?
Well, obviously.
Look at your mileage.
It's over 180.000.
Sorry.
Should we call road service?
Let's push it to an car-repair shop.
What?
There's one nearby. You take the wheel.
Th-There's no need to cry about it.
Pakkun...
is dead.
I'm all alone now.
You drove 180.000 kilometers, huh?
This ridiculous distance you covered
was all for Mia, wasn't it?
Well, not all of it.
But,
I'm too much, right?
You're kind.
Takuzo,
I'm sure this is
what Mia is thinking right now.
That your overwhelming kindness
might have been comforting
if it was shared with someone else.
- Oh, good morning.
- Morning.
Can we talk?
Thank you for waiting.
Wow! This looks so delicious!
- Let's eat.
- I'll serve.
Ooh, this is great.
It's good.
- Here.
- Thanks.
Hey.
What is this dinner for?
- I-I'll try this.
- Yeah.
I mean...
If you're doing this to cheer me up,
you didn't have to.
Takuzo.
Yes?
Would you like to
get married to us?
Please.
What?
I'll do it.
The distance we couldn't fill
could be bridged by someone else...
I think she really wants to marry you.
Time to promote yourselves!
What?
Do you want to do it after work today?
Subtitle translation by: Aya Kudo