[Shadow Love]
[Episode 11]
Are you alright?
I'm glad you're alive.
We lost?
We could've
annihilated the Changfeng Army
with your approach.
However,
a man in black just showed up
out of nowhere.
He has extraordinary martial skills.
He not only bailed Lucheng out,
but also killed General Shi Du
in collaboration with Li Shuang.
Who is this man?
He doesn't seem
to be from the Changfeng Army.
Besides,
the spies we planted in Lucheng
don't know anything about him,
as if he just
appeared out of thin air.
A man in black...
That was indeed beyond my expectations.
Counsellor,
General Shi Du already died.
What can we do now?
Shall we retreat?
This a must-win battle.
We can't go home without triumphs.
I will petition the court to appoint
a new military commander.
Hard though it is,
we must conquer Lucheng.
Stop!
My Lord.
I'm reduced
to this situation
because of that hateful Li Shuang.
When I'm back to the capital,
I'll definitely lodge a serious complaint
against her to Prince Li!
My Lord,
we'd better hurry.
I've had fast horses arranged ahead.
Let's go.
Go.
Lord Li!
It's quite late now.
Where
are you two heading?
Lord Li would like a night stroll.
You're a mere military advisor.
How dare you question
an imperial military supervisor?
I dare not.
However,
I'm afraid I might have to
ruin the night for you.
Lord Li,
the general requests your presence.
General.
You should be grateful
that you were captured by me
instead of Li Zhangyi.
Otherwise, you would've died by now.
Kill me if you want.
Why the gibberish?
As someone brave enough to sneak in
and burn our granaries alone,
you'd never fear death, would you?
Other than you, how many people
are on death missions in Lucheng?
Why did the Yao State send you here?
What exactly
is your relationship with Li Zhangyi?
Since you know I don't fear death,
I bet you're also aware
that you can't get
any information from me.
Resistance won't bring you any good.
I know people like you
aren't dreaded by death,
but survival.
I just came back
from the Fragrance Garden.
In order to catch you,
Li Zhangyi ordered
all the people there to be killed.
Twenty-odd living souls just perished,
including Yanzhi.
There's a sachet.
You recognize it, don't you?
All of you are evil.
Take my life now, I dare you!
Don't move!
Kill me!
The herbs in this sachet have
nerve-soothing and sleep-inducing effects.
I guess you have trouble sleeping.
So, Yanzhi put such herbs in this sachet
for you to carry it around.
That shows she truly cared for you.
But it didn't occur to her
that this very gesture of kindness
would cost her life in the end.
I was trained to sacrifice myself
for missions in childhood.
Crawling out from piles of corpses,
I've long forgotten
what it feels like to be a human.
Why on earth
would there be such a silly girl?
She sympathized with me,
trusted me and cared for me.
She gave me the only bit
of genuine love
I've ever got in these 20 years.
Now that you know
Yanzhi's affection for you,
you should avenge her unjust death!
Unjust deaths happen every now and then,
don't they?
How foolish of Yanzhi,
for choosing me
to be her inseparable confidant.
She always looked forward
to us leaving the brothel
and leading a carefree life.
To this day, I still don't understand
how much courage it'd take
for someone
to completely trust another person
in such chaotic times.
But it's fine.
I'll ask Yanzhi myself.
Before Miss Yanzhi died,
she still believed you were innocent.
You've already failed her.
Committing suicide
will only let her down even more!
Spill out Li Zhangyi's evildoing
to avenge your dead bosom friend now.
You've already completed the mission
assigned by the Yao State.
Li Zhangyi
refused to open the city gate
just to cover up
his mistakes,
resulting in the numerous deaths
of Lucheng soldiers!
I swear to drag him...
down to hell.
Li Zhangyi confessed
that he lost his token
as a result of staying overnight
in the Fragrance Garden.
Plus Yunge's testimony,
this time,
he won't get away.
For such a despicable man,
even death can't redeem his sins.
Have Li Zhangyi escorted
to the capital by a troop.
I've written
a memorial detailing this incident.
Deliver it to the capital, together with
these two testimonies,
for His Majesty to make a ruling.
Yes.
By the way,
has Yunge's funeral been taken care of?
Miss Yanzhi's and her bodies
have been buried together.
But, General,
she was a spy
from the Yao State after all.
Is what we've done
somewhat inappropriate?
In such turbulent times,
does anyone truly
have control of their lives?
All are unfortunate beings.
Mr. Ji,
there's a visitor for you.
You shouldn't have come here, Miss.
Please leave.
Don't take it wrong.
I'm not here to pester you.
Hearing you got wounded
on the battlefield,
I just wanted to bring you some medicine.
How has
the general been?
She's doing great.
But now,
she's busy sending people
to look for Jin'an in the city.
I don't think she'd have time
to worry about you now.
A loyal aide though you are,
you end up in prison.
Is it worthwhile?
I've followed the general for years.
Whether this is worthwhile or not
can't be explained in just a few words.
Indeed.
Over these years,
you've never
disobeyed Shuang.
Knowing clearly
that Jin'an has her complete trust,
you still made that hasty decision.
Is Jin'an really
an unbearable eyesore to you?
As head of the Guardians' Unit,
I'm obligated to protect the general.
I can't help but suspect
that man's peculiar identity.
Is it suspicion or jealousy?
Maybe
you envy him for sharing Shuang's worries
and solving problems
for her.
Do you remember
how we first met three years ago?
That day,
I was collecting herbs alone
on a mountain.
I made a blunder
and early fell off a cliff.
Grab tight!
Careful.
I always remember
how gallant you looked
when you saved my life.
General,
this lady says she has medical skills
and the herbs
that can purge your body of toxins.
Of course, I also remember
the panic and worry in your eyes,
when Shuang was poisoned.
At that moment,
I should've realized
that was the way you look
when you truly love someone.
She's the general I work for.
I have nothing for her
but lifelong loyalty
and sworn allegiance.
No other feelings are involved.
Miss, I must ask you to refrain
from saying those remarks again,
in case those with ill intentions
hear them
and tarnish the General's reputation.
You know what?
One's fondness for another person
is like running waters
that can't be stopped,
even if it's left unsaid.
I'd better get back to my patients
at the clinic now.
Don't forget to
regularly apply the ointment.
I'll get you out of the prison.
I must repay you
for saving my life.
[General's Residence]
Miss Lu.
Where have you been?
Shuang had her people
look for you everywhere.
She was worried sick.
Did you get injured?
No, I'm fine.
The Changfeng Army entered the city.
People swarmed the streets
to welcome them.
I was separated
by the hustling crowds,
but I managed to find my way back.
That was a serious matter,
yet you're still smiling.
I thought
you were harmed by Li Zhangyi.
I'm perfectly fine.
Are you okay?
Of course I am.
I'm glad you're fine.
It's good news.
I heard on my way back
that Ji Ran had been thrown into prison.
Were you loitering
for that matter?
I did come here to plead with Shuang.
I pondered it over and over,
but just couldn't bring myself
to utter a word.
Now that you're safe and sound,
would you please do me a favor?
Can you ask Shuang
to release Ji Ran?
If you're mad,
then beat me up.
Vent your anger
right at me, okay?
Miss Lu,
I doubt
if Ji Ran will appreciate your help.
Is it worthwhile
to go to so much trouble
for a man who always gives you
the cold shoulder?
Whether it's worthwhile or not
doesn't matter.
When you love someone,
you're ready to do anything
for him or her.
You'd put yourself in their shoes.
Their concerns are your concerns.
A simple smile of Ji Ran's is enough
to make my day.
What's more,
he once saved my life.
If I can do something for him,
I'll be content.
Ji Ran did make a mistake.
But he behaved that way
only out of concern
for the general's safety.
As you said,
pursuing this matter further
when I'm safe and sound
would only make me seem petty.
Does it mean you've agreed to help?
Actually, I owe him a thank you.
I gained something important
thanks to his acts.
Come in.
Waiting for someone?
Yes, I am.
You're smirking. Seriously?
You broke into the city tower
and held an official hostage.
You wanted to die or what?
I offered unsolicited advice
at the military camp that day.
Then
an accident kept me
from returning to the General's Residence.
I thought you'd find me suspicious.
But now it seems like
you're worried about my safety instead.
I'm just happy.
Happy?
Only living people get to feel that.
You fell off the cliff
when fighting Ji Ran.
Yet you didn't get hurt at all?
I was lucky enough
to have landed on a tree under the cliff.
Do you not believe me?
I'll undress for you to see my body.
You've seen it already.
Never mind!
You've come back safely anyway.
Now that I'm safe and sound,
will you
just drop the matter
and release Ji Ran?
There is strict discipline
in the Changfeng Army.
For taking action without permission,
he deserves punishment.
But my identity does seem peculiar.
It raises suspicion,
especially from his perspective.
It'll be a huge loss
to fail a devoted warrior
for this matter.
Every time I was in danger,
you always showed up.
and rescued me from peril.
Why can't I choose you over him?
General.
With the enemy confronting us,
I shouldn't have put you in detention.
After working with me for years,
you still went for that reckless action.
Do you admit you did wrong?
Yes, I do.
My fault
was acting against Jin'an
without orders
and nearly causing his death.
That said,
General,
camouflage often looks real.
Jin'an can't be cleared of suspicion
until his identity is verified.
I admit I did wrong,
but I don't regret taking action.
See you later, General.
To this day, I still don't understand
how much courage it'd take
for someone
to completely trust another person
in such chaotic times.
He's honest about everything,
except for his real identity.
Perhaps he has his own reason.
Even if I keep probing,
I might not get the truth.
Maybe sometimes,
trust
is the greatest truth of all.
General!
Word from our scouts
says the Yao Army hasn't withdrawn.
Instead,
they've set up camp 20 li from Lucheng.
Reportedly,
they have a new commander now,
named Zhao Jingyuan.
These vile creatures
won't stop haunting us.
We'll run out of
supplies in four days.
They can starve us out
simply by putting us under siege.
Qin Lan,
take three soldiers with you and set out
for Yongcheng
right now to ask for help.
Yongcheng is nearest to Lucheng.
Reinforcements and supplies
can reach us in two days.
All we need to do
is hold out for two days.
Then there will be a turning point.
Got it, General.
To General Zhao!
Everybody,
drink up!
General Zhao is the best
military commander of the Yao State.
Under your leadership, General Zhao,
I believe
our army will be an unstoppable force.
You're just being modest, Counsellor.
It is known to all that you are
a brilliant military strategist
with unmatched intelligence.
This time,
with our joint efforts,
we'll definitely conquer
Lucheng
with ease.
General,
I wish you every success.
We wish you every success!
The general is dead!
Counsellor...
Scram!
Greetings, My Lord.
The battle in the south
was proven a failure.
You lost the Battle of Lucheng as well.
I'll make up for it with hard work.
Make up for it?
Your life is worth nothing.
Forgive my ignorance.
Considering my loyal service
to the Empress Dowager,
would you enlighten me, My Lord?
Rise.
Thanks, My Lord.
I came here
to give you an opportunity
to redeem yourself.
You've seen that man in black.
Do you find him
familiar?
He...
He does resemble someone I know of.
But Prince Annan already died, didn't he?
How is it possible...
Good news, General.
At dawn today,
the Yao Army's general
was killed.
The killer has even placed a flag
in the center of the battlefield.
Now,
the Yao Army
is fluttered.
Who's the killer?
It's not clear yet.
Report!
General,
someone dropped this box
at the entrance to the office,
along with a letter.
Open it up.
[This head is a gift for you]
Could this
have been done by the man in black?
Report!
Military Advisor Qin,
a carrier pigeon brought back a message.
The Yao Army stormed Ninglan.
Ninglan has fallen.
How can we not fight them?
We have to wait.
Do you have a better plan?
-Are you getting cold feet?
-We have to preserve our strength!
Zhao Jingyuan's head
is still hanging outside,
dripping blood!
Who led the Yao Army to attack Ninglan?
Enough.
What's the use of bickering?
Ninglan
is the most important transportation hub
connecting Yongcheng and Lucheng.
Military Advisor Qin has to pass through
that city when he brings back
weapons, horses,
reinforcements,
and supplies.
Now, we've lost Ninglan.
Military Advisor Qin
must be in a tough spot.
Besides,
I'm afraid all our deployments
are within the enemy's expectations.
Now, our provisions can only
sustain the army for three days.
We must recapture Ninglan,
or we will be doomed.
I'm worried
we might lose Lucheng too.
Easy for you to say.
The Yao Army stormed Ninglan
with 20,000 soldiers.
We can merely match that number
only if we commit all our forces.
How do we fight them?
What's more,
it's already hard for us
to keep Lucheng intact.
If we divide up our forces now,
by the time the reinforcements arrive,
Lucheng will have been lost!
Then what do you suggest?
Sitting back and waiting for doom?
At least we get to live longer that way!
Listen up,
Changfeng warriors
would rather die fighting
than die waiting!
That's right!
Enough!
Liu Yun coped brilliantly
when the military commander
was replaced at a critical time.
He's no ordinary man.
This is
the map of Ninglan?
How did you get hold of this treasure?
This will
largely increase our chances
of recapturing Ninglan!
Right.
Yes. Things are looking up now.
Indeed.
We have to take Ninglan back.
Lucheng
must remain ours too.
How visionary of you, General.
We all admire you!
Cheers!
Drink up, guys!
Absolutely!
What a delight!
Drink up!
Let's drink!
Sure!
Stop eating!
Have a drink!
Come on.
Here it goes.
Fill it up.
Guys,
conquering Ninglan
is equal to sounding the death knell
for the Taijin Army.
Next,
all we have to do is wait and observe.
By simply besieging them and waiting
till they run out of supplies,
we can easily
conquer Lucheng,
even if we don't launch attacks.
Victory is within reach!
Come on.
Drink up!
Guys,
the credit goes to our counsellor,
this wise strategist
who turned the tables!
We swear to
faithfully
follow
the counsellor's lead!
We swear to
faithfully follow the counsellor's lead!
Hubris
leads to downfall.
I dare not be your sole leader.
Captain Jiang,
why not share this responsibility with me?
Under the influence of liquor,
I got carried away.
Please forgive me, My Lord.
Why the panic, Captain?
It's an honor to be a general.
I dare not.
I dare not play this role.
But the army
desperately needs a new general.
Well then...
What about the rest of you?
Greetings, General.
General Shi Du and General Zhao Jingyuan
died heroically for our country.
His Highness has decreed
enormous support for the bereaved
in honor of the departed.
Our army lost two generals consecutively
all because of the man in black.
But we're not daunted
by his trivial stunts.
Look at our formidable forces.
How is that man alone able to
shake our 50,000 valiant Yao soldiers?
To boost the morale,
His Majesty decided to
promote Tian Daweng
to Guardian General,
who shall command all the troops.
Hopefully,
under the new general's guidance,
our army will capture Lucheng
and bring triumphs to the Yao State!
Capture Lucheng
Capture Lucheng!
General.
The Yao Army
has selected a new general?
Strong though their momentum is,
after losing two generals,
they've been frustrated.
Boosting morale is their priority.
They must've picked this new general
with extreme prudence.
But given that they're making
quite a splash now,
I think they're up to something.
At this moment,
it's the best for the Yao Army
to take no action.
They're only making these noises
to attract the man in black.
General, you think
this is a trap for that man?
Liu Yun is indeed a marvelous strategist.
He calculates every step.
He has anticipated each of
our moves.
The only thing he couldn't expect
was the appearance of the man in black.
If I were him,
I'd also like to eliminate that guy soon
to clear all menaces.
Ji Ran!
Yes.
Have 2,000 elite soldiers
follow me to Ninglan with light gear.
You and Luo Teng
will stay put.
General,
this is not a good idea.
The Yao Army has
laid siege to the entire Ninglan.
Though we have the map of Ninglan,
we're still no match for them.
Please think twice about it, General.
The Yao Army
is determined to win this battle.
We have to fight them
till our last breath.
Select 2,000 soldiers.
Record
their names
and family backgrounds.
Send the registry
to the General's Residence.
They'll all be rewarded.
General...
No more talking.
Do as I said.
Even sky-reaching wings
won't save me from impending danger.
At this point,
I only wish to devote my life
to Taijin
and to the Changfeng Army.
Please
send my corpse to my father.
This undutiful daughter
wishes her father and her brother Ting
lifelong safety and tranquility.
I'm not even
mentioned in your last words.
You're taking
only 2,000 soldiers
to the besieged Ninglan.
If the Yao Army learns of it,
they'll strike at you
and hunt you down.
General, are you planning
to use yourself as bait?
I am a general.
There are
certain duties I have to fulfill.
Moreover, I promised Zang Budu
to protect Ninglan,
once the war broke out.
I'm a woman of my word.
However slim the chances are,
I have to take this gamble.
What if you lose?
If I lose,
the blood pact between us will break.
Then you'll be free.
At this point,
you still think that so-called freedom
is what I value most?
My life is bound with yours.
If you are to gamble your life,
I'll make sure you don't lose.
Take 10,000 soldiers with you
to recapture Ninglan.
I'll stall the main Yao forces for you.
You figured it out long ago, didn't you?
Are you waiting for me to tell the truth?
I'm sorry...
I kept it secret from you for so long.
The Yao Army has taken action.
They remain resolute
in capturing Lucheng and Ninglan.
Whether you show up or not,
they won't easily back off.
I'd hate to see anyone die in vain again.
I also resent the idea
of you risking your life.
The moment I went on the battlefield
and barged into the enemy's camp
to slay their general,
I already left myself no way out.
You hate for me to risk my life.
I bet you surely understand
I care about you...
just as much.
♪ Take a glimpse at the sweet memories ♪
♪ They accompany me
in this long journey of life ♪
♪ Distances don't bother me ♪
♪ The memories will linger on ♪
♪ I hope my love will finally find you ♪
♪ I hope my prayers will be answered ♪
♪ Let me hold your hand ♪
♪ Wish us to be an ordinary couple ♪
♪ May we walk pass
the hustle and bustle ♪
♪ To the end of the world ♪
Promise me...
you must stay alive.
I wish you a great victory, General.
General,
♪ Though covered by frost ♪
The troop is ready.
♪ I'm ready to salvage
the tattered world ♪
But 2,000 soldiers are far from enough.
I forfeit my life to implore you...
♪ My passion is like blazing flames ♪
The general will take
10,000 soldiers with her
♪ No obstacle can hold me back ♪
to reclaim Ninglan.
Jin'an?
Where is the General?
♪ This love leaves me no regret ♪
♪ May the world be filled with romance ♪
♪ May people be with
their beloved ones ♪
Is it really the general's order?
♪ Holding your hand,
I'll pray for peace ♪
General!
♪ No regret, no sorrow ♪
♪ When the gilding wears off ♪
Ji Ran,
select 10,000 soldiers.
♪ We'll still be together ♪
I'll take them to Ninglan.
Yes.
Ninglan is easy to defend,
but hard to attack.
There are 20,000 Yao soldiers there.
We'd better get this battle over with
as soon as possible.
Ji Ran,
protect Lucheng.
New supplies will arrive within two days.
Yes,
General.
I will defend
the city with my life.
Attention, soldiers!
March to Ninglan.
Defeat the Yao invaders!
Charge! Charge! Charge!