[Coroner's Diary]
[Episode 38]
Attack!
It's me,
Yan Ze,
an orphan whose parents
both died because of you.
How did you know?
It must be you wretched lackey.
I...
I trusted and valued you so deeply,
yet you dared to collude with traitors
and betray me!
As they say,
evil deeds will eventually
lead to self-destruction.
Yuan Qing,
serve tea to the sinner.
Yuan Qing...
Your Majesty, don't worry.
I've added the same amount of
Dream Butterfly Poison to this tea
as was given to the late Princess Xin.
Your Majesty will have plenty of time
to savor
and watch,
to see clearly
how the late Princess Xin died!
The Dream Butterfly Poison you found
back then was made from the wing powder
of the Five-colored Butterfly
from the Southern Frontier.
This poison is colorless and odorless,
only detectable after it takes effect.
My poor mother.
She saved your life,
yet became the first person you used
to test poison.
Poor me. I tested the water temperature
for my dying mother,
yet got my eyesight ruined
with just one sip!
My Father followed my mother in death,
surely also your doing.
This is
as heartless as it gets.
Don't you
celebrate too soon.
I
still have two palace guard divisions
standing by on full alert,
as well as the Huaiyang Army,
which will soon
enter the capital to protect me.
Has Your Majesty forgotten?
The one who delivered your verbal orders
to the Palace Guard Division
was me.
You won't be seeing the Huaiyang Army.
You...
You bastard!
I'll kill you!
Traitor Yan Han,
such an end for you is only proper,
showing that justice prevails!
Yuan Qing!
Read the Self-reproach Edict.
Yan?
-Li.
-What are you doing?
Why are you here?
You've come at the perfect time.
A son pays for his father's debts—
that is the eternal way of heaven.
You...
Li.
Li, leave now!
They...
They're all rebels!
Hurry, Li.
Li!
Yan Ze!
Yan Ze,
what are you doing?
Li! Li!
Yan Ze, you've gone crazy!
What exactly are you trying to do?
Yan Li.
Listen carefully to
that Self-reproach Edict
and see the true colors of
this emperor before you.
Yuan Qing!
By Heaven's mandate, I issue
this edict of self-reproach to the world.
I,
Yan Han, the second legitimate son
of the late Emperor,
incited Fu Chengye to rebel,
attempting to seize the throne,
-pretended to surrender
-Yuan Qing!
to lure my twin brother
Yan Huai to Storm Ridge
for a private meeting,
where I murdered him
and destroyed all evidence, after which
-I took the throne in my brother's name.
-What wrong did I do? I'm innocent!
-From then on, the order was overturned,
-I'm the chosen one!
the sun and moon darkened,
and all conscience lost.
End of the decree.
How dare you, a usurper of the throne,
claim you're the chosen one?
These are all just ravings
and nonsense.
Whether it's nonsense or not,
he himself knows best.
Isn't that right,
Prince Yi?
You...
You heard it right.
He is your biological father,
Prince Yi, Yan Han.
My dear son, Li.
My dear son, Li!
Li.
Father...
Impossible.
This is impossible.
Otherwise, why do you think he allowed
Prince Cheng and the Crown Prince
to turn against each other,
yet treated you better than his own sons?
So what if I am Yan Han?
I
am also the Empress Dowager's
biological son,
still of the royal bloodline.
Just because
I was a twin,
the Yan family
cast me aside like worn-out shoes!
Who has ever sought justice for me?
Heaven's justice is clear.
What the Yan family
owed me
should naturally be repaid
with the throne!
I have no shame before Heaven and Earth,
nor before my parents!
What about me and my mother?
Do you also feel no guilt toward us?
Li.
Why don't you ask your biological father
how Chi's mother died,
how Consort Jin
met her end,
and what caused
Prince Jin and Shen Yi's deaths?
No way...
Li.
Everything I've done
is for you.
I didn't want you to suffer
a life of hardships like I did!
Li.
I did it all for you,
clearing away all obstacles,
just so you could ascend to the throne!
No.
This can't be true.
Li!
No!
This can't be true!
Yan Li.
My dear Li!
You wretched lackey!
You... You...
I'll kill you!
Yan Han.
Even your own son,
whom you have such high hopes for,
doesn't believe your lies.
When you abandoned your wife and child
back then,
did you ever think it would come to this?
You...
Yan Ze.
Yan Ze!
Li, wake up!
To use your son's blood
to complete this unrighteous flower
and send you to your death—
I suppose it can be considered
me granting a final favor
to you and your son.
Body sacrifice,
heavens tremble,
with flying dragons' protection,
immortal and indestructible!
Spare...
Spare Li.
I will immediately draft a decree
to
pass the throne to you.
Yuan Qing,
tell me,
should I take the throne?
Leader, your virtue shines bright
and your noble spirit reaches far.
You are the heaven-ordained sovereign
of the...
You lied to me...
You're all...
The same...
You're right.
Sooner or later, you'll be
discarded like a tool
that's served its purpose.
I only want the throne
so that everyone who enabled Yan Han
will pay for my parents' deaths.
You've helped me achieve my goal.
Rest in peace now.
How cruel is fate,
so many die with regrets.
May he in his next life
never again believe in
carrying out heaven's justice.
Let's go!
Bai Feng!
Hurry up and go!
Let's go!
The ringleader of
the Heavenly Way Society,
Yuan Qing, has been eliminated.
After today,
no one will know about my connection
to the Heavenly Way Society.
People will only remember that
you died at the hands of  Yuan Qing,
the traitor from the Heavenly Way Society,
and that Yuan Qing
and your precious son killed each other.
Except for your crimes
that will be made public,
all the truth
will vanish into thin air.
Li!
Are you alright?
I never thought
that I, Yan Li, would end up
dying alongside you.
I wonder if I'll ever
have a chance to see Ning again.
If she sees me like this,
she'll surely be disgusted.
I'm here with you, Li.
Good.
I'll let you fully experience
what it feels like to watch
your loved ones die right before your eyes
and be powerless to save them—
that heart-wrenching, gut-twisting pain.
Li!
Wan.
How is
Li?
I can save him.
You liar! Murderer!
Young Marshal,
hurry and go protect His Majesty!
Leave this to us!
Master.
How is Sui?
He's all right,
probably just choked a bit.
Someone set a fire inside.
I've already put it out.
Princess Wan and Yongning
are already in the bedchamber.
Take good care of Sui.
I'll go save Princess Wan.
Yes.
Yan Li!
Chi.
He's not the Cousin Yan we knew anymore.
He wants to kill us!
Chi.
My father...
He killed His Majesty
and your mother.
And also...
For these sins,
let me pay with my life.
You and he are different people.
You must live on.
Master!
The rebels are retreating.
Take them all out of here.
-Yes!
-Be careful.
Here.
Don't worry about me.
Take Li away.
Take Li away first.
Here.
Chi.
Yan Han killed our parents.
Why are you trying to save him?
His crimes
will be judged by the law.
We cannot watch someone die
without helping.
The law?
Yan Han's crimes
are too numerous to list,
utterly devoid of conscience.
How can mere laws fully punish such evil?
Yuan Qing's body
is hardly cold,
yet you...
You're already
putting on
this righteous act
to cover up your crimes.
What a selfish and cold-hearted
hypocrite.
So it really was all carefully calculated.
Yan Ze
used the pretext of divine justice
to manipulate people.
But in fact, he used
the Heavenly Way Society
to cultivate power,
in order to plot for the imperial throne
and avenge
his personal grudge.
I...
Though I may have gained my throne
through improper means,
serving as
the ruler for years,
I've been
a diligent and benevolent emperor.
Diligent and benevolent?
Everything you've done
was to prove
that the Empress Dowager
was wrong to have abandoned you.
To satisfy your selfish ambition
to rule the world,
you even abandoned your wife and children,
betrayed your brother-in-law,
and plotted against
your own blood relatives.
You
are truly
the most vicious and cruel villain
in this world!
You...
-You both, shut up!
-How dare you...
What hypocrite,
what vicious villain,
you're birds of a feather.
No matter what reasons you have,
you're both nothing but murderers
with blood on your hands!
Those I killed
were all guilty!
They deserved to die.
I've told you,
their crimes should be judged by the law.
You're in no position to judge them.
Don't think you can use this
as an excuse to escape your guilt.
Think about your father.
Think about our mothers.
Are you still going to save
a sinner like Yan Han
and aid the wicked?
Yan Han must die!
I'll kill you...
Why
did you kill my mother...
You...
Who are you?
Don't come any closer.
Go away.
Go away!
Stay back!
You...
Don't come near me!
Stop pretending.
Come with me to Zichen Hall now
and expose that person's true colors.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I...
Stop playing dumb with me.
You think I've tolerated you
all these years
because I'm afraid of you?
I simply didn't bother
to make an enemy of a wretch like you.
That bastard of yours
caused my Che to die tragically.
And what fate did he meet in the end?
When you sought favor every day
and surrendered yourself to that traitor,
did you ever think you’d end up like this?
What's wrong with me
surrendering to the traitor?
Don't you want the same?
Acting all proper and dignified.
If he hadn't been so guarded around you,
you would have dragged him
to bed long ago.
Do you think all women in the world
are as debased as you?
Ever since discovering that impostor
wasn't His Majesty,
I've been making plans,
just to make sure His Majesty's bloodline
inherits the throne.
And what about you?
All you care about
is your own power and wealth.
Your own son died by his hand,
yet you still pretended to be crazy
and fooled around just to survive.
How could there be a Mother like you
in this world?
I'm not to blame for Qi's death,
so why should I follow him to death?
What's wrong with me wanting to survive?
All these years,
he's treated me like I'm invisible,
lying beside me
without even removing his undergarments.
For Qi's sake,
I've lain beside an impostor,
living as a widow for over a decade.
What more do you want from me?
To preserve His Majesty's bloodline?
You raised your son
to be weak and incompetent,
just so he could be your puppet,
allowing you to be
the regent empress dowager.
Everything you've done
has been for yourself!
Shut your mouth!
The Empress is trying to kill me!
Remember this day.
I'll finish you
on behalf of the late Emperor!
If I'm to die,
you won't live either!
I thought
I met a benefactor
when my career was over.
Who knew it would still
all be for nothing?
What a pity that I,
a man of such great talent,
have no place in this imperial court.
I'm leaving.
Stop right there!
Mr. Li.
Where are you going?
My defeat today
is due to the injustice of fate,
allowing a mediocre person like you
to succeed at every turn,
while I placed my trust
in the wrong person.
You
are not worthy to mock me!
You colluded with rebels
and betrayed your mentor,
yet you dare claim
our Prefect Zheng succeeds at every turn?
Our Prefect Zheng serves
with absolute integrity.
He didn't even have the money
to save his wife.
It was us bailiffs who chipped in.
I may not be as good an official as you,
but as a person, you're beneath me.
Take him away!
-Yes!
Please...
I beg you...
Don't
harm Li.
Li is my brother,
my own flesh and blood.
I shouldn't have...
I shouldn't have
let Yan Qi
kill your father.
I regret it,
but it's too late.
What about the late Emperor,
Consort Jin,
Prince Jin,
and Lord Shen's deaths?
Do you regret those too?
I...
If you hadn't been blinded
by imperial power,
none of this would have happened.
My parents would still be alive.
Your parents?
You are...
My father
is Shen Yi,
the Minister of Judicial Review.
I am Shen Yi's daughter,
Shen Wan.
My father and Prince Jin
concealed the weapon
to cover up your murder of Consort Jin,
to prevent it from becoming public
and avoid causing turmoil in the court.
Yet you wrongfully killed a loyal official
who saw you as a wise ruler.
It was my fault.
My fault.
I was wrong...
One wrong step
leads
to many more.
I...
I've...
I've
wronged...
[Prince Yi's Mansion]
[Fu Residence]
♪ If my tears could speak ♪
♪ If you could hear my heart melt ♪
♪ If I no longer needed ♪
♪ To hold onto the broken dreams ♪
♪ Maybe then I could finally
let go of regret ♪
♪ Don't sigh for me ♪
♪ Or for our love song
that's come to an end ♪
♪ Memories feel just like
the songs I once sang for you ♪
♪ I sigh for the dark night
and the cold moon ♪
♪ I sigh for all the loneliness
in this world ♪
♪ Even true love
can't resist the passing of time ♪
Ever since he returned to the palace,
I knew he wasn't Huai.
But what difference does it make?
I'm not only a mother,
but also the Empress Dowager
of our country.
He's diligent and disciplined,
with decisive authority.
He's more suitable
to be emperor than Huai.
I had thought
if the court could truly be well-governed,
then passing the throne to Che
would be returning to
the rightful succession.
Who would have known
that one wrong step
would lead to mistake after mistake?
Grandmother, you've done nothing wrong.
It's the imperial rules that are wrong.
My mistake was with Han.
First mistake,
I shouldn't have been so soft-hearted
and spared his life.
Second mistake,
after he returned to the palace,
I shouldn't have deceived myself.
I was wrong from the very beginning.
Grandmother, please don't blame yourself.
If you hadn't made these two mistakes,
Yan Li and Sui wouldn't be here now.
Letting Sui
inherit the throne
is also for the sake of the empire.
You two won't
resent me
for making such a decision, will you?
Li and I never desired that position.
We have no resentment at all.
In fact, it's exactly what we wanted.
All I want is Wan as my wife,
and Shuoxi as my domain.
I ask for nothing else.
Good.
Help Sui for a few more years.
I'll surely fulfill your wishes.
Have a seat.
How is the Empress Dowager doing?
Grandmother still grieves,
but her depression has lifted.
She will get better.
That's good.
With you two by her side,
I can return to Jingzhou
with peace of mind.
Great Aunt, why are you
in such a hurry to leave?
Wan and I haven't had the chance
to properly care for you.
You don't need to care for me.
Just treat Wan well.
That's what matters most.
Grandma.
Thank you.
Thank me for what?
If anything,
you saved my life twice,
and I should be thanking you.
Actually, at first,
I had intentions of using connections.
But Grandma, you've always been
sincere and genuine with me,
never showing any suspicion.
I don't like
hearing such talk.
What do you mean by "using connections"?
Using connections means taking advantage
of others for personal gain.
You rely on your own abilities,
and you're so kind-hearted.
That's why I love and cherish you.
This is the bond between us.
Whether you're Qin Wan or Shen Wan,
you will always be
my most beloved granddaughter.
♪ A deep mark you left,
etched in my heart ♪
Grandma.
♪ Now and then it aches,
stirring old memories ♪
Alright, alright.
♪ Turning into something
I'll never forget ♪
♪ In the long journey of life ♪
♪ The meaning of encounters
can never be defined ♪
Your hand.
♪ The story isn't over yet,
and tears are not the only part of it ♪
From now on,
I'll entrust Wan to you.
♪ Turn love into a secret,
hidden deep inside ♪
Remember, I'm not too old to walk yet.
If
you dare let my Wan
♪ Collecting moments
as we pass by each other ♪
suffer even the slightest grievance,
I'll show up in front of you
anytime, anywhere
♪ To look back on when I grow old ♪
to teach you a lesson.
Great Aunt, if that's your only reason
for returning to the capital,
I'm afraid there won't be
such an opportunity.
♪ Turn love into a secret,
hidden deep inside ♪
Wan! Wan!
♪ If you unveil the mystery ♪
♪ And walk through this journey with me ♪
♪ That would be the best ending for love ♪
Go ahead.
The late Emperor's edict:
My young son, Yan Sui,
is naturally kind and generous,
filial and sincere.
He now succeeds to the throne,
rules over the realm,
bestowed with the mandate of Heaven,
assumes the imperial position
in this world,
hereby proclaimed to all under heaven.
Prince Rui, Yan Chi,
is of noble character,
wise and filial,
quelled chaos and laid down arms,
defended the palace
and saved the late Emperor,
and achieved great merits.
He's hereby
appointed as Regent,
to assist the successor,
united in purpose,
following the path of past sages.
Rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
When you return to Jingzhou,
take good care of Grandma,
and take even better care of yourself.
Forget all those past events and people.
Don't worry.
I won't make things hard for myself.
Yan Ze lost his life
due to his own inner demons.
I no longer owe him anything.
I just need some time
to figure out what kind of life I want.
That's the best way to think about it.
Could you help me deliver something?
To whom?
If you don't come down soon,
the boat's going to leave.
Coming!
Ning.
I'm here.
So this is what she meant.
I've always seen Yan Li
as a sister since childhood.
You must treat him well.
Sister?
You can slap his face,
but don't bruise it,
or he'll cry.
Don't worry, Chi.
Just for the sake of his pretty face,
I'll go easy on him.
While he's still young and beautiful,
hurry up and get married,
or you'll miss his prime and regret it.
Is there something on my face?
Little Wan'er is right.
I shouldn't miss your prime.
Don't worry, my beauty is timeless.
So do you want to get married soon or not?
Of course I do.
We'll be leaving now.
Have you set a date?
-Yes.
-No.
Princess Wan, please don't mock us.
You've always been so wishy-washy.
When asked about marriage,
you flatly deny it.
Do you believe
I'll send you to guard the border?
No, please don't.
The date is set.
Just wait for the wedding banquet.
Setting sail!
♪ Having walked alone through
wind and rain for years ♪
♪ Never having encountered this love ♪
♪ Until you came to my world ♪
♪ And wrote our destined bond ♪
♪ The sunshine you gave me ♪
♪ Painted pictures of the future ♪
♪ Only when I drew near to you
did I realize ♪
♪ This love was already deep and endless ♪
This is the first year of Decheng.
To follow heaven's mandate
and serve the common people,
I hereby reform the Criminal Code.
There's a new article
added to the Criminal Code:
Anyone who kills due to emotional reasons
and anyone who beats to death
a cohabitant,
whether married or not,
shall have their punishment
increased by one level.
Anyone who deliberately
kills a cohabitant,
whether married or not,
shall be sentenced to death
with immediate execution.
Anyone who molests a young girl
shall be exiled 3,000 li
to a remote, harsh province.
Anyone who rapes a young girl
shall be strangled.
Anyone who,
under the pretext of medical treatment,
removes organs from a living person
or causing injury
shall be strangled.
Those who commit murder
shall be beheaded immediately—
the crime is beyond forgiveness.
Anyone who violates the law
while resisting unjust harm
shall receive reduced punishment
based on circumstances,
so the righteous will not suffer unjustly.
Anyone who gathers crowds
to promote evil occult practices
or spreads rumors to deceive the public,
shall, for minor offenses,
be relocated for three years
and detained for reeducation
until they understand proper principles.
[Fortune-Telling]
Anyone who causes physical harm or injury
to another person through beating
shall be exiled for 3,000 li.
Anyone who murders or rapes
women or children
shall be beheaded immediately.
The new code has received
His Majesty's approval
and shall take effect immediately.
All previously concluded cases
shall be reviewed and punished
according to the new, stricter standards.
Great!
Great! Excellent!
[Zhaoxue Hall]
Bring the medicine box.
Yes.
A new case?
Let's go.
[No Injustice in the World]