[FEUD]
[Episode 15]
Why can't I help Meng Changqin,
but you can?
There is a difference.
What's the difference?
Meng Changqin will get you in danger.
When Meng Chi showed up,
I had the same feeling.
First, you saved his life.
Then, he spent decades
working as your housekeeper.
You're aware of
the many rumors in those times.
Hua Ruyue,
every being in the world has its destiny.
Reckless interference
will bring you serious trouble.
Why do divine beings go
through tribulations here?
Because there's too much
suffering in the mortal realm.
Mortals are faced with
problems at all ages,
like separation, hatred
and unattainable longing.
Even if they try their best,
they are bound to have
regrets about some things.
Divine beings have spiritual energy
and the ability to control mortals' lives.
If all divine beings
empathize with mortals,
they can't refrain from
interfering with heaven's will
with their power, can they?
But won't that be to
the detriment of heaven's order,
the mortal realm and
the divine race?
Hua Ruyue, you've set
off on this dangerous path.
I promise I won't do it again.
After saving Meng Changqin,
I won't go to anyone's rescue anymore.
What about you?
Me?
Will you still be in quest
of the next partner
to pass the love tribulation with?
Don't you know
what I'm thinking?
I've always been committed to you.
You're the only one I want
to pass the tribulation
with.
Okay. You have my word.
I'll be with you all the time.
I won't leave even if you're sick of me.
We'll weather through
the love tribulation together, alright?
Let's go.
A portion of fried chestnuts, please.
Got it.
You want chestnuts?
You were busy doing other things
at lunch time.
I'm buying these chestnuts for you.
We'll have a meal at home later.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Shall we go home now?
Sure.
We've been in the mortal realm for years.
Why hasn't
the love tribulation come to an end?
Are you not into me?
Or do you hate me?
Is this an admission, Bai Jiusi?
You'd better make it clear.
Say something!
Explain it now.
You're awake. Come help me.
[Meng Changqin, from Huai'an County,
Yu Prefecture]
There's a spiritual connection
between the bamboo and his life status.
Ruyue,
you're still worried about him.
You've agreed to let me
help him for one last time.
Heavenly Lord Dacheng,
you made me a promise.
You can't go back on your word.
Fine.
I'll hope for the bamboo
to stay strong and green
in all seasons.
[Chen's Lantern Shop]
Come on.
Be careful.
Why are they selling white lanterns?
I remember those we saw in
the last lantern festival were colorful.
These are soul-guiding lanterns.
Soul-guiding?
Some people died in a foreign land
and couldn't find their homes,
so their souls would linger.
Given that, their families
would light up such lanterns
to guide them back to their homes.
Afterwards,
the souls will gladly
leave for the afterworld.
I see.
Bye.
You seem to have a poor appetite today.
You ate much less at dinner than before.
It's muddy after the rain.
Let me carry you on my back.
Hop up.
Do the soul-guiding lanterns contain
the spiritual energy that can
bring souls back home?
These trinkets made by humans have
no spiritual energy at all.
Humans do it to comfort themselves.
♪ I embrace the wind
and drink a jar of wine ♪
♪ The willow in my dream
has withered in autumn ♪
My vision is perfect in the dark
even without this lantern.
♪ I say everything is fine with a smile,
despite the shedding tears ♪
I know. I didn't light it up for you.
Who is it for then?
♪ Melancholy takes up half of my life ♪
Those who can't find their way home.
♪ I wish tender love
can last more than a moment ♪
♪ Love cannot be retracted ♪
What's wrong?
For some reason,
you seem different now.
♪ Thoughts crowd up
my mind, but I can't say any ♪
Anyway, no matter what,
♪ I'm not ashamed to be in
the prison of my own making ♪
you must remember who you are
and never get lost, alright?
♪ Only when I'm drunk
can I dream about my beloved one ♪
♪ Across the magpie bridge,
I see the bright river of stars ♪
♪ As I look at the mountains,
your smile is everywhere ♪
[Songhe County]
♪ How can I easily let go? ♪
♪ Drink this up, for butterflies
shall keep us company ♪
♪ I'm missing you on
this breezy spring day ♪
♪ The moon rises above the willow tree ♪
♪ It is dusk again ♪
[Three years later]
Ruyue!
Master?
Master!
Silly me.
Master wouldn't come to such a place.
Seriously?
Master?
Master!
You did come here.
We haven't met for three years.
Why would you become like this?
Enough said about me.
Let's talk about you.
To what do I owe
this sudden visit from you?
I'm here to pick you up.
Pick me up?
I happen to need a housekeeper now.
You're educated and were once an official.
I'm sure you can do this job well.
Don't worry. You can have
three bowls of mushroom soup every day.
You won't starve.
Didn't you say,
"living well means everything"?
Follow me,
and you'll live a long happy life.
The soup is not enough.
I've traveled far and wide,
with wine and meat keeping me company.
I'll provide those too.
What about chicken
and fish?
Anything you want.
I still won't take this job.
Why?
Master,
I need to finish an important mission.
About the Drought Dragon?
Yes.
Pardon me for the rejection.
Goodbye, Master.
See you later.
Meng Changqin!
Can't you just give up?
Since I'm your master,
I'll do my best to protect you.
Just come with me.
I'll find you a job,
so you can make a living.
Instead of toiling and moiling,
you can live a stable life.
Master, I'm having a good enough life now.
Does "good" refer to
bustling about and endangering your life?
Master, you don't understand.
Since the day I was born,
droughts have happened every year,
with no end in sight.
I saw people starve to death
in this messed-up world.
That's why I chose to become an official.
I once worshipped the gods,
putting all my trust in them.
But then I realized
that officials and gods
couldn't be of help.
People need to have faith
in something, right?
So, now, I believe in myself.
Master,
save that housekeeper job for me.
After I slay the Drought Dragon,
I'll come to you.
What if you can never
find the Drought Dragon?
In that case,
I'll have to see you
again in my next life.
You can also believe in me.
What?
Trust me.
I'll help you slay the Drought Dragon.
This is Mount Wuju,
where the Drought Dragon resides.
Will the droughts be ended
if I kill the dragon?
The Drought Dragon is driven
by its nature to disturb the mortal realm.
Perhaps it doesn't mean to cause droughts.
Maybe it doesn't have to die.
What else can we do?
Chishui River purges all evil.
It can neutralize
the Drought Dragon's dryness.
If the dragon agrees to go back
to the north of Chishui River
and stop harming the mortal realm,
then we won't have to kill it.
But what if it disagrees?
Then we'll slay it without mercy.
Go!
Master.
Divine Lord Siling?
Droughts have prevailed
and taken many lives.
You are responsible for it.
If there is a shred of sympathy in you,
you should go back to Chishui River now
and stop harming the mortal realm.
I made a huge contribution by
quelling the water demon unrest
in the North Sea.
The celestial realm rewarded me
with the privilege
to travel the Three Realms
with no restraint.
I'm afraid I can't follow your command.
Your freedom must
make way for the wellbeing
of the Three Realms.
The Three Realms?
You're only talking about humans.
Just like fallen leaves
and withered flowers,
their lives
don't matter at all, do they?
I thought you weren't
aware you were doing evil.
But in fact, you're knowingly
doing it without remorse.
In that case,
your life must be ended.
Master!
Heavenly Lord Dacheng.
Heavenly Emissary.
Is there a decree from the Empyrean?
You're adventuring with Siling
in the mortal realm.
Do you know what she is up to right now?
She is trying to kill a divine being.
Things form, exist, decay and vanish.
The circle of life never ceases to be.
That's the law of heaven.
Now, by attempting
to slay the Drought Dragon.
she's not only committing
the crime of killing a divine being,
but also obstructing the cycle of life
and breaching the law of heaven.
You came here with her.
You must do something
when she makes a terrible mistake.
What do you want me to do?
To stop her and to bring her
back to the Empyrean for punishment.
Master!
Master, it's dying.
Go. Kill it now.
Got it.
Hua Ruyue, how dare you
kill a divine being?
It should be punished by the heaven
for the crimes it may have committed,
instead of you.
What did the heaven do
when droughts happened?
when people starved to death?
If the heaven is as merciless
as you make it sound to be,
why not defy it?
Master!
Meng Changqin, what are you waiting for?
Both mortals
and divine beings
must obey the heaven!
Master, I'm unable to kill it!
Changqin, this is a justifiable killing.
Believe in yourself, and you'll succeed!
As a divine being, you're
harming the mortal realm.
If all divine beings are like you,
mortals have every right to kill them!
Finally... I did it!
Bai Jiusi, where is Meng Changqin?
He's in a coma, but he's fine.
Good.
I'm relieved.
You know what?
We slayed the Drought Dragon today
and ended the droughts.
From now on, people won't starve anymore.
I know.
Do you think I did wrong?
Yes.
Why?
I offered you my advice,
but you didn't heed my words.
You said mortals were as insignificant
as ordinary animals.
But that is not true.
I saw Meng Chi
creating colorful paintings,
though he was born
color-blind.
I saw Meng Changqin,
a mortal though he is,
slaying the Drought Dragon
with a blunt blade.
Even divine beings can't achieve these.
So what?
"So what"?
Bai Jiusi, do you know what you're saying?
I'm always clear about what I'm doing.
You're the one who is not of
sound mind.
We came to the mortal realm
to overcome the love tribulation.
I told you
not to recklessly use your power here
and not to cause trouble.
But what have you done?
You've used your power
to save lives several times.
You even killed
the Drought Dragon for mortals!
The dragon was at fault!
Right and wrong can't be easily judged.
I only care about the results.
Hua Ruyue, you promised
that helping Meng Changqin
was an one-off thing,
which made me agree to pass
the love tribulation with you.
But now you've broken your promise.
You've violated the heaven's rules.
I can't be tolerant of you anymore.
What are you going to do?
I'm going back.
What did you say?
I'm going back to the Nine Heavens
to atone for my sin of coming to
the mortal realm without permission.
You're going to kill me?
No, I'm not.
But I'll seal the spiritual energy in you
to show the Heavenly
Emissary what stance I take.
I have nothing to do with
what you've done.
Bai Jiusi!
You like mortals, don't you?
Your spiritual energy
will be sealed for ten years,
so you have to live as
a mortal here for a decade.
Meanwhile,
I can go back to
the Nine Heavens, all innocent.
This is the best for us.
You can't do this to me.
I thought
you truly loved me
during the several decades
we spent together in the mortal realm.
But as it turns out,
that was all a delusion.
You're actually
heartless and selfish!
Now I understand...
It's no wonder that you don't
want to have a baby with me,
and that you've never helped me!
Am I also an insignificant
being in your eyes?
You're sweet and nice when you need me.
But you would discard me instantly
when I go against your interests!
I did give you options.
And this is the one you chose.
It will be over soon.
You won't be in pain for long.
No...
Let go of me!
Let go!
♪ You said the stars were beautiful ♪
♪ You wanted to cuddle
with the brightest one ♪
♪ It would gladly fall for you ♪
♪ It would be covered by dust
in the mortal world, till it regretted ♪
♪ But you kept making it cry ♪
♪ Kept breaking it down ♪
♪ Kept letting it slowly shatter
from the inside out ♪
♪ With no light to guide the way ♪
♪ It turned cold and dark like a stone ♪
♪ And you threw it away,
left it to suffer alone ♪
♪ You made it feel it all ♪
♪ The torment of a living hell ♪
♪ The kind of pain that makes you
want to tear yourself apart ♪
♪ It looked around at all the others ♪
♪ But somehow, only it was wrong ♪
♪ As if love was just
its own foolish fantasy all along ♪
♪ In my world,
there's never been room for mercy ♪
Master Qing Yang,
Do you really not know anything?
Why did Master Xuan Wei, the Sect Leader
and others suddenly head to and come back
from the Nine Heavens?
How am I supposed to know why?
It makes sense for disciples
not having the answer.
But, Master, you hold
an important position.
How could you not know the truth?
-That's right.
Zip it, lad!
Senior Zhang?
Senior Zhang, you're back.
When did you come back?
In the early morning.
Early morning?
That is to say,
you returned with
the Sect Leader and the others.
Do you know what Master Xuan Wei
and the Sect Leader went
to the Nine Heavens for?
Yeah. The fellows we hang out with
suddenly changed.
Their power became stronger,
and their demeanor
and temperament different!
Senior Zhang, did the Sect Leader
feed them magical
pills or elixirs in secret?
I don't know.
What? You're highly valued by the sect.
How can you not know?
Everyone here is
a top disciple of the sect.
Except me.
Yes, except you.
Those who went up
are small-time outer-circle disciples,
including cleaners and food servers.
Indeed.
Yeah.
Right.
The Heaven-Turning Seal
contains immense power.
It broke and left no trail.
It could be in the Empyrean, the Hell,
the Three Realms, the Six Paths,
the Eight Desolations
or the Four Seas.
Just because we can't find it
doesn't mean those
in Canglei Palace can't.
Long Yuan is Heavenly Lord
Dacheng's closest disciple.
He must know how to find the lord.
Grandmaster and the lord
disappeared together.
They must've gone to the same place.
As long as we find Heavenly Lord Dacheng,
we'll find Grandmaster.
Senior, during the battle at Tianmu Peak,
I placed an All-Hearing Tag on Long Yuan.
I'll know whatever happens
in Canglei Palace.
Excellent.
Master's safety is of vital importance.
No mistake is allowed.
Yes. I'll send the disciples
out for a thorough search
in all the 12 states.
Dan Yang, since you've
placed an All-Hearing Tag,
you should stay in the sect
and monitor the activities
in Canglei Palace in real time.
Yes.
Zi Yang, tell your fellows to split up
and search every corner.
I'll be in seclusion in the back mountain
to see if the Spirit Inquiry Formation
will reveal Master's whereabouts.
Everyone, be keen aware
that this matter
related to Divine Lord Siling
decides the fate of Jingyun Sect.
We must find her at all costs.
I have a question.
Go do your work, everyone.
You may leave now.
-Yes.
[Prosperity]
What do you want to ask?
[May your spirit shine across all realms]
Master, you know what it is.
You already have the answer,
don't you?
I want to hear you say it, Master.
There is no such a person as Li Qingyue,
a disciple of Jingyun Sect.
But Divine Lord Siling,
an immortal, truly exists.
300 years ago,
Grandmaster battled
Heavenly Lord Dacheng, Bai Jiusi,
in Canglei Palace.
Her body was destroyed,
but her primordial spirit lingered.
With humiliation, she hid
in the mortal realm
for 300 years
because those in Canglei
Palace tried to hunt her down.
Then, she became a mentor to
Master Xuan Wei and some others,
namely the top members
of the previous generation.
She taught them techniques and helped them
establish Jingyun Sect.
That was when she was
reborn in Li Qingyue's body,
who drowned in a flood.
She then became a disciple
of our sect as a disguise.
It's fair to say that helping
Grandmaster get her power back
and return to the Nine Heavens
is the original purpose
of founding Jingyun Sect.
Well...
What about Qingyue?
This mediocre girl, Li Qingyue,
is just Grandmaster's disguise.
Qingyue already died
in a flood in her childhood.
Zhang Suan, you're deeply involved.
Your judgement is inevitably clouded.
Once you extricate yourself from it,
you'll see the truth.
How silly of me.
Zhang Suan,
you went to the Nine Heavens
by climbing the Sky-Reaching Ladder.
I didn't expect that at all.
It's the sect's fault for
delaying your development.
That's not what I care about.
The shining sun is far beyond your reach.
Why stare at it and hurt yourself?
I've overestimated myself.
There's no such thing as perfection.
You're already blessed
to be in the same sect
as Grandmaster.
When Grandmaster comes back,
you'll be rewarded.
Now,
I understand.