[FEUD]
[Episode 17]
Are you not happy
that I'm feeding you?
I'm too disgusted to eat.
There's no problem.
If you ask me,
Mrs. Bai must be feeling shy.
She's probably secretly happy right now.
Bai, trust me.
Just keep going like this,
and Mrs. Bai will surely be moved
by your thoughtfulness.
Bai.
Bai, don't be impatient.
I haven't finished speaking yet.
Didn't I tell you to
come to me every month
to ask for the antidote?
Why did you delay for so long?
If you die,
Mr. Meng will be angry with me.
I was delayed by some matters,
so I'm only coming for the antidote now.
I can give you the medicine,
but don't forget what you promised me.
[Savage]
Senior Meng has already been released.
You can go find him yourself.
Would that old-fashioned Zi Yang
really release Mr. Meng?
You might as well say
that the rats of Jingyun Sect dug a tunnel
for Mr. Meng to escape on his own.
You'll see for yourself when you go there.
The Sect Leader doesn't intend
to stop you anymore.
What nonsense are you talking about?
That old-fashioned Zi Yang
always goes on about good
and evil not coexisting.
How could he possibly not stop us?
Could it be that you're lying to trick me
into going to Jingyun Sect,
and then kill me?
You helped me ascend before.
I have no reason to deceive you.
Give me the antidote.
I have important matters
to attend to next.
I don't have the leisure
to come find you
once a month for the antidote.
I don't believe you, unless you accompany
me back to Jingyun Sect.
I want to see with my own eyes
that Mr. Meng is safe.
Only then will I give you the antidote.
I don't have time to accompany you.
If you don't give me the antidote
and something happens to me,
see how Senior Meng will treat you.
Stop right there.
Fine, I'll give you the antidote, okay?
Why are you following me?
I didn't expect that you, a mere mortal,
could go to such lengths
for the Divine Lord.
It's truly surprising.
What do you want to do?
And what do you want to do
after leaving Jingyun Sect?
I guess you'll go
find the Divine Lord, right?
You didn't listen to
what I said last time, did you?
Do you really think
the Divine Lord needs you?
Whether she needs me or not
is her business.
Whether I look for her or not
is my business.
If that's the case, count me in.
Don't look at me like that.
My friendship with the Divine Lord
is no less than yours.
You useless thing.
I've wasted my time teaching you.
You'd better stay at home obediently.
[Qu Ke]
Let that stinky boy come to you himself.
Mother, but...
No buts.
If a man doesn't even know
to take the initiative to find you,
then what do you want him for?
[Simple Joy]
Boss, is the food ready?
Mr. Bai, please wait a moment longer.
There's still one dish left.
Here.
Bai,
what grave mistake did you make
to make Mrs. Bai angry
for two whole months?
I did nothing wrong.
Waiter, pack up all of Mr. Bai's dishes.
Alright!
Boss.
Mr. Kong.
Two bowls of plain noodles.
And I'll have my usual.
Got it!
Two bowls of plain noodles
and two flatbreads.
Coming right up!
This is where you're wrong.
Why nitpick with your own wife?
If you've made a mistake, just admit it.
Enjoy your meal.
If you don't mind,
I'd like to treat you both
to some noodles.
Mr. Kong, have you struck it rich?
Not really.
Today is my birthday.
Look at my forgetful mind.
Mr. Kong, you're 53 this year, right?
Yes, I have no family left.
Thinking about it,
you two are the only ones
willing to have a meal with me.
Come,
please.
Then I must partake in this joy.
Bai, eat up.
Thank you, but I'm not hungry.
Bai understands me best.
One bowl isn't enough for me. I need two.
Alright.
[Guo's Songhe Noodles]
Mr. Bai, take care.
Thank you.
Mr. Bai, please wait.
Mr. Bai.
Thank you.
What's this for?
I will never forget your kindness.
Mr. Kong has been taking
the imperial exam for over 30 years.
His savings have long been exhausted,
so he usually has a very tight budget.
I told Mr. Kong
you and I will cover
the expenses for his trip
to the capital for the exam.
After he passes the exam,
he can pay us back.
Don't worry, Bai.
I've covered your share of the money too.
Consider it a favor from me.
Why give me this favor?
Mr. Kong's family is very poor.
He's usually struggling to make ends meet.
The fact that he spent money
to treat us to noodles this time
is enough to prove his affection for us.
I was worried
that he would feel sad and upset
because you didn't eat his noodles,
so I let you have a good name.
So troublesome. I don't need it.
What do you mean?
This is about human connections.
The meaning of life lies in this.
Bai.
Bai!
Bamboo baskets, take a look!
Bai,
it's been two months
since your wife moved in.
She hasn't been out at all.
My wife was thinking of inviting her over.
I hope it's not too presumptuous.
Why don't you let your wife
chat and do some needlework
with my wife?
They say close neighbors are
better than distant relatives.
Plus, our two families live so close.
We should visit each other more often.
If your wife cheers up,
she might stop being angry with you.
Needlework?
Bamboo baskets! Bamboo baskets!
-Dried fruits and candied fruits!
-Sir, have a look.
[Zhang's Flatbread Shop]
Hey, Goldie,
why are you here again?
Look, I'm about to close up shop.
You...
Why do you keep coming here every day?
Go on, get out of here. Go on, go on.
Go on, hurry up.
Go on.
Goldie, go on.
[Zhang's Flatbread Shop]
You know what?
You've been begging for food here
since you were little.
You've eaten more of my baked flatbreads
than I've even sold.
Quick, quick, come here.
Here, eat this.
Old sir.
Gentlemen.
Give me four...
Give me eight flatbreads.
Alright.
Alright, alright.
Here, here, take these.
Hold them carefully.
Thank you.
You take it too.
Why are your hands so cold?
Don't think you can handle the cold
just because you're young.
You'll suffer when you're older.
Wear more clothes when you go out.
These are still warm.
Warm up your hands.
Warm them up.
Here, old sir.
Alright, alright.
Thank you, thank you both.
Goldie.
Hurry up and go, Goldie.
Don't block the way here.
Alright, Bai.
So, we've agreed on this, right?
I'll take my leave.
Lin.
I'll pay the money for
Scholar Kong to take
the imperial exam in the capital with you.
I knew you were a man of honor, Bai.
You're just not good with words.
I'll be going then.
I brought you some flatbreads.
I'll go inside first.
I didn't expect you'd be
willing to help mortals.
After all these days,
this is the first time you've
voluntarily spoken to me.
Why did you do this?
As you said,
I'm living like a mortal.
I'm doing what mortals do,
and I haven't used any power.
I'm not talking about power.
Then what do you want to say?
You still don't understand.
Don't understand?
Mrs. Bai, are you ready?
Ready for what?
Going to my humble abode
for embroidery!
Mr. Bai said you also enjoy needlework
and made plans with my husband
to visit my humble home today.
I couldn't wait, so I came over first.
Did I disturb you two?
Not at all.
I couldn't find suitable silk cloth.
I was delayed.
No need to look. I have
plenty of silk cloth at home.
I'm overwhelmed by the choices.
It's perfect that you're coming.
You can help me choose.
Mr. Bai, no need to buy dinner
from the restaurant tonight.
My husband has prepared plenty of food.
Let's eat together tonight.
Let's eat together!
Sounds good.
Let's go.
Bai, look.
These are all the books I've collected.
And some ancient paintings.
This one.
This is "Cranes and Bamboo"
by master painter Yuan Danqiu.
When I first arrived in Songhe County,
I discovered this painting
seemed to have a special connection
with this county.
So I spent a lot of money
at a pawn shop
and bought it at a high price.
Look at this painting hanging here.
Doesn't it match this room perfectly?
Feel free to look around.
Here.
Bring it over.
Like this.
You're looking at this?
You think this is quite good too,
don't you?
I happened to read this phrase
in an ancient book.
The ancients often said,
every word and character has its power.
When I read this line of poetry,
I finally felt
that reading excellent poetry
can truly inspire one's spirit.
What do you think, Bai?
"Strategies from Ancient History"?
You like this book too?
I really like this one.
It seems we're like-minded.
Lin,
you must be thirsty after talking so much.
How about...
Let's go. This way.
Bai, let me tell you,
my family has served as officials
for generations.
But most of them became court historians
in the capital,
writing and engraving books.
Later, my grandfather faced
setbacks in his career,
so he left behind a family precept,
forbidding his descendants
from becoming officials.
So my father started a business
and became a merchant.
Later, he discovered he had
a natural talent for business.
He made a fortune
and started supporting my education.
It's a pity. I studied
very diligently back then.
I was so intelligent.
My father told me
if I could take the imperial examination,
I would surely come out on top.
I could even become a prime minister.
But I don't think so.
I think studying is just studying.
What does studying have to do
with being an official?
Being a good student doesn't mean
you'll be a good official.
Instead, one must have a sense of justice
to be a good official.
Bai, what do you think?
That makes perfect sense.
That's right.
Bai, you truly are my kindred spirit.
Come, Bai.
Try this.
This is the Zhaoyan tea.
Although this isn't that precious,
there are high requirements
for the water used to brew it.
It must be brewed with morning dew.
Every morning, I go to
the back of the mountain
and collect this dew from
the banyan tree's south side.
You'll find that this tea
is very clean and clear.
And when you smell it,
there's a strong grassy fragrance.
Bai, how do you find it?
It's quite good.
Bai,
we are both scholars,
but we can't just focus on
studying with our minds.
We also need to diligently
exercise our bodies.
As the ancients say, study at midnight
and rise at dawn.
That's exactly what I do.
I wake up at midnight to study
and at dawn, I go to the back mountain.
This way, not only can I
collect morning dew,
but I can also exercise.
It's killing two birds with one stone.
That's excellent.
Excellent.
You think it's good too, don't you?
In that case, come with me
to the mountain tomorrow.
I said, come with me
That's really not necessary.
Bai, I see that you're quite thin.
If you come with me
to the mountain every day,
your body will surely become stronger.
People say women are like vines,
and men should be like rocks.
Women have always liked
men who can make them feel secure.
If you bulk up a bit,
perhaps your wife
won't look so stern every day.
This tea is quite potent.
-I'm drunk.
-Dear.
Dear, look.
Mrs. Bai's embroidery is really good.
I thought
my wife's skills were already quite good,
but I didn't expect your wife's
to be even better.
It seems Bai wasn't exaggerating.
Your wife is truly skilled in needlework.
Look, isn't it adorable?
Did you embroider this?
I just did it casually.
When did you learn to
embroider these things?
Mrs. Bai, I have a presumptuous request.
Please, go ahead.
My wife really likes
this little tiger hat.
I wonder if you could give it to her?
Of course.
But what do you need this for?
I...
I want it for my unborn child.
My wife is already four months pregnant.
We haven't told anyone yet.
Yes, but today we've shared the news.
It's also to share some joy with everyone.
What did you do?
Your clothes are all wrinkled.
By the time the child is born,
I suppose this peach tree
will be bearing fruit.
Mrs. Bai, do you like eating peaches?
Yes, I do.
It's a pity we can't eat them now.
We have to wait until it blossoms
and bears fruit.
But that's okay.
Once it blossoms and bears fruit,
I'll send some over to you.
You want to eat peaches?
Lin.
This peach tree in your yard
must be over 100 years old, right?
I'm not sure.
We've only been living here
for less than a year.
But the previous owner said
their family had lived here
for three generations.
This peach tree was already
here back then.
So maybe it is quite old.
Being an old tree, it should
have a spirit.
It knows when to bloom
and when to bear fruit.
Bai, listen to yourself.
Don't peach trees always bloom in March
and bear fruit in June?
Not necessarily.
Since someone wants to eat peaches,
it should bloom and bear fruit.
If it can't satisfy one's craving,
what's the point of keeping
this old peach tree?
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
I'll go get you a new set of clothes.
Wait a moment.
It's windy outside now.
You should put on your outer robe.
Don't catch a cold, okay?
Don't move.
♪ I see you standing
in the dark of night ♪
♪ Reaching out to me with arms so warm ♪
♪ Telling me, you're not afraid ♪
♪ Even if we part, these memories ♪
I...
♪ I want to get drunk in your embrace ♪
I've often seen Mrs. Lin
bite off the thread
for her husband like this.
So I just...
♪ And tell you I love you ♪
I'll go open the door.
Mrs. Bai.
Yes.
What are you...
Mrs. Bai, isn't it amazing?
We just mentioned yesterday
that we wanted to eat peaches,
and today, they've grown on our tree.
Look, they're this big.
This is what we call an auspicious sign!
Here, take it.
We should report this to the authorities.
Who knows, there might even be a reward!
In my opinion,
some immortal
has blessed Mr. Lin's home.
I don't think it's an immortal.
Look.
Scholar Kong, Mr. Lin, and Mr. Bai
are all educated.
This is a sign that our area
is about to produce a literary god.
-It's a good sign.
-Yes.
Scholar Kong,
I think the one most likely
to become the literary god
is you.
In this imperial exam, you'll
surely receive high merits
and reach success.
-You're right.
-No, no.
These are all peaches from Mr. Lin's home.
It has nothing to do with me.
Mr. Kong,
I'm only responsible
for teaching and educating.
I'm not taking the imperial examination.
When you pass the exam with high honors,
I'll definitely host
a celebratory feast for you.
-Count me in.
-Me too.
Mr. Lin.
Mr. Lin, thank you for the peaches.
Thank you.
-Bye.
-We're leaving.
Goodbye.
It was you again, right?
So much fruit.
Recklessly using power
may lead to backlash.
I didn't do anything.
It must be that old peach tree
that's almost become a spirit
that wanted to bloom
and bear fruit on its own.
Bai Jiusi, watch out.
You're going to lose.
Of course I won't.
Even trees understand feelings
better than humans.
Bai Jiusi,
have you forgotten that you're not human?
Why does it sound like
you're insulting me?
Mrs. and Mr. Bai,
my wife and I brought you some fruits.
♪ I pretend to stroll with ease ♪
♪ Avoiding the gaze of your eyes ♪
♪ I'm already in tears, though ♪
♪ Wetting a dragonfly in mid-flight ♪
♪ I wish I could ♪
♪ Travel back to the past ♪
Take a bite.
♪ Forget all the grudges and griefs ♪
♪ Lean against you, and watch us smile
in the glistening mirror ♪
Hurry up.
[Peaceful Dwelling]
Mr. Bai, this letter is for you.
For me?
Yes, it's for you.
And this too.
I'll take my leave now, Mr. Bai.
[Peaceful Dwelling]
[To my friend, Bai Jiusi]
Mr. Kong wrote you a letter too?
Bai,
Mr. Kong started his education at six.
He vowed from childhood
to serve the country.
Unfortunately, he kept failing the exam.
He kept trying until he was 53
and finally passed the exam.
But he died of illness
on his way to take office.
Why was heaven so unfair to him?
Life and death are just a cycle of karma.
It's not about fairness or unfairness.
How can you be so cold-hearted?
Mr. Kong considered you as a friend.
He even treated you to birthday noodles.
If only I had...
If only I hadn't sponsored
him for the exam.
Then he wouldn't have
fallen ill from exhaustion
and died away from home.
Life and death are all predestined.
Even if he hadn't gone to
the capital for the exam,
he might still have died from illness.
That's different.
If Mr. Kong were right in front of me,
I would've definitely tried
every means to save him.
I certainly wouldn't have just
watched him die.
Then let me ask you.
If you knew his life was destined
to end this year,
would you still try to save him?
I would.
But he was fated to die on that day.
Then it's heaven's will for him to die,
not because I let him die.
I wanted him to live.
It would be my wrongdoing if I
saw him dying and didn't help.
If I tried my best to save him but failed,
then it's the fault of the outcome.
♪ The legends passed from ear to ear ♪
♪ Are full of confusion ♪
♪ You and I, always caught in the mess ♪
♪ Stuck in the cycle of loneliness ♪
♪ They all say it's karma ♪
♪ The flower bloomed but bore no fruit ♪
♪ Just a mistake, tides rise and fall ♪
♪ Everything gets washed away ♪
Come in.
Your wine was left in the courtyard.
[To my friend, Bai Jiusi]
Are you upset about Scholar Kong?
There are many hardships in this world,
but the power of mortals is very limited.
Who doesn't have a few
lamentable things in their life?
Should I feel sorry and upset
for all of them?
Though there are many people in the world,
there's only one Scholar Kong.
What are you trying to say?
Nothing.
The wine jar is small,
but the friendship is deep.
Drink it.
This is qiulubai from Shangjing,
a wine for kindred spirits
among scholars and gentlemen.
It's very famous.
♪ Vows of love till death ♪
♪ We say them every day ♪
♪ But once tonight is over ♪
♪ Our love will just fade away ♪
Enjoy.
♪ They all say it's karma ♪
Okay.
♪ Shooting stars fall in the moonlight ♪
♪ This blazing fire
scorches wide and far ♪
♪ Love burns till it fades ♪
♪ The legends passed from ear to ear ♪
I knew you just have a sharp tongue.
You must be upset about
Mr. Kong, right?
I'm not.
I didn't say anything
out of line yesterday, did I?
Actually, besides Mr. Kong's matter,
I've been troubled by
something else recently.
I feel suffocated inside.
Why are you looking at me?
As a friend,
shouldn't you ask me what's wrong?
Not interested.
Not interested?
You know,
you're great,
but you're just a bit cold-natured.
Look, besides me,
who else would want to
be friends with you?
Do others want to get close to you?
Birds of a feather flock together.
How can one force
different people together?
Fine, fine. You're the most noble.
Come.
Tell me.
My wife is about to give birth.
I'm about to become a father.
But I'm not ready yet.
I don't know how to be a good father.
You'll understand once you've done it.
Why create problems for yourself?
I'm not creating problems.
This may seem trivial to you,
but it's very important to me.
My parents died early,
only leaving behind some family property.
My wife married down to me.
Her family wasn't happy at that time.
What if the child grows up
and discover that other children
are all loved by their
relatives and elders,
while only he isn't?
Then,
will he feel lonely and sad
because of this?
When he asks me about this,
what should I say?
Say the truth.
I don't want my child
to understand these harsh realities
at such a young age.
But that won't change the fact.
Yes,
there are many things in this world
that can't be changed.
Then why
do some people still try despite the odds?
Because they don't accept fate.
Can that give them the ability
to change their fate?
Mortals have very little power.
If you can't change it,
accept it gracefully.
Otherwise, you'll only struggle
in endless pain.
I don't agree with you on this.
No pain, no gain.
If you don't even dare to struggle,
how will you know
whether there's paradise or peril ahead?
You'll understand when you have children.
As a father, I'm willing
to give everything for my child,
even my life.
By the way, I don't have relatives,
but I have you as a friend.
When my child is born,
you'll be his godfather.
While he's still young,
I'll make more friends
to give him more godfathers.
This way, he won't be lonely.
Do you think I can become
a good father?
You will.
Bai,
after knowing you for so long,
you've finally said something
pleasing to hear.
Bai, let me tell you something sincere.
I'm friends with you
because I think you're
different from others.
Actually, I have very high standards.
Not just anyone can be my friend.
Since I moved here, I've only
made three friends in total.
One is you,
one is Mrs. Liu who sells insoles,
and one is Old Wang
who transports human waste.
But
among all these friends,
you're the one I value the most.
They all say you're a scholar
and call you Mr. Bai,
but I don't think so.
I think you're a
spoiled rich kid
who can't tell rice from wheat,
who has a nasty temper
and a blunt way of speaking
with no filter whatsoever.
You're not likable at all.
But that's okay.
It's enough that I like you.
In the future,
don't always be so solitary.
If you encounter any difficulties,
feel free to come to me.
What good would it do to go to you?
I'll drink with you!
[Guo's Songhe Noodles]
[Prosperity and tranquility
for the people]
Fire!
[Peaceful Dwelling]
-Fire! Fire!
-Put out the fire!
The flatbread shop is on fire!
Come quickly and help put out the fire!
Wake up! There's a fire!