[Under the Cover]
[Episode 26]
[United hearts bring loved ones home]
Here.
Pass these around.
[Missing Person Notice]
Here.
You don't have one.
[Sang Chuan, Contact (Mr. Sang)]
Let me introduce myself.
Well,
my surname is Sang.
The person in this photo
is my younger sister.
Her name is Chuan.
We're actually half-siblings.
Her birth mother passed away early.
My parents never liked her.
We only had each other growing up.
Later, when my parents
went away for work,
I stayed home
to take care of her.
Five years ago,
on her birthday,
she told me
she wanted a piece of cake.
She was always so thoughtful.
She said,
"Brother,
I'll just take one bite.
You can have the rest."
The weather was beautiful that day.
But the moment I turned to get the cake,
she was gone.
It's been five years.
I've searched everywhere
but still can't find her.
You've all looked
for so many missing children.
Has anyone seen my sister?
Please think carefully.
Does anyone remember her?
Sang,
don't blame yourself too much.
We'll work together.
Don't worry.
We'll find your sister.
We'll find all our children.
Alright.
Let's keep our spirits up.
I'll start, okay?
- Keep going, never give up!
Thank you, everyone.
Uh,
there's a website for missing children.
Not sure if you've heard of it.
Han Chuan.
This is Mr. Han Chuan.
Sir, hi.
You'll need to come with us.
Master.
Mr. An!
New lead on Sang Tuo from Dongbang.
What lead?
They caught a human smuggler.
He confessed
to smuggling someone
into China recently.
He identified Sang Tuo
from a photo.
Did Ne Zha come with him?
No sign of her
so far.
The compound
Sang Tuo fought tooth and nail
to reclaim
has been completely eradicated by us.
He won't let this go.
We have to track him down fast.
Yes, sir.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Zheng Jiahe.
Look, this is my son.
His name's Zheng Chenchen.
He's nine now.
Went missing three years ago.
He has an oval face,
single eyelids, and full lips.
There's a mole here,
under his right eye.
See?
If anyone has any information,
please contact me.
Thank you in advance.
Thank you.
Take a look. Does this work?
[Ne Zha]
No problem.
Sang,
everyone's finished recording.
Do you think there's much hope
of finding the children this way?
As long as there's the slightest chance,
we can't give up!
Right, never give up.
Never give up.
The approval process
on this website takes forever.
But we will get results.
Let's all be patient, alright?
Okay.
Zha.
Stand right here.
When I tell you
to come over,
then you come, alright?
[Personal Information]
I'll begin now.
Take care.
[Unknown Caller]
[Incoming Video Call]
Hello, is this Ms. An Ning?
Yes, who is this?
I'm Han Chuan
from the Anti-Fraud Center.
We need your cooperation
in an investigation.
Cooperation?
Over the phone?
The situation is unusual.
Your husband Zheng Jiahe
just led a group
in a brawl with villagers
in Anliu Village.
A... A fight?
What happened?
He received a clue about
your missing child, came to identify him,
and got into a conflict
with the homeowner.
I was nearby doing anti-fraud outreach
when it happened.
So I helped the police handle the case.
Take a look at this child.
Could your husband have made a mistake?
Come here.
Chenchen.
It's my son.
Where are you now?
[Connection Lost]
I... I'm coming to you.
Mr. Han Chuan,
your situation
is very complicated.
I can't make
a definitive judgment right now.
We'll inform you
of further steps, alright?
Mr. An,
A warning call just won't go through.
Send me the address.
Yang Yang, come with me
for in-person interventions.
Yes, sir!
Mr. An!
I've got a victim
who won't answer either.
Mr. An, same here!
Me too.
Same here.
What's going on today?
A sudden surge in fraud cases.
This could be targeted mass fraud.
Yaqi,
map victims' social networks soon.
Coordinate with local precincts
to dispatch officers
for in-person interventions.
Understood!
All responders,
keep calling the victims!
- Yes, sir!
Son.
My son.
Ms. An, please calm down first.
You're sure he's your child,
right?
He's my child.
How could I not recognize my own son?
Which village did you say you're in now?
Ms. An,
[Face Replacement Completed]
coming here won't help right now.
Calm down and listen to me.
The protocol prohibits
online case handling.
But with both parties in confrontation,
this could turn violent.
Emergency override authorized.
Now I need you
to provide
identification and birth certificates.
I'll arrange for DNA testing procedures.
Okay, no problem.
Alright.
I'm sending you the internal reporting
mini program now.
Mr. An, still can't get through.
[Please Complete Verification]
[Completed]
Don't believe it. This is a scam call!
What are you doing?
Ms. An.
- Ms. An, listen to me.
- Give me back the phone!
That's a scam call.
What scam call?
My son.
My son is found. My son...
No.
Ms. An, listen.
You can't call that number.
They're scammers!
Ms. An, listen...
Let go of me!
Ms. An!
Chenchen, answer the phone.
I miss you so much.
Answer the phone.
Answer the phone!
Ms. An.
They're scammers. That's not your son.
That was a scam call!
[Jianghai Bank: Online transfer
from card ending 2678]
Call Yaqi now!
Freeze the payment! Hurry!
Done!
Great!
Kid,
well done.
Mr. Wu,
we've confirmed.
All today's victims
are members
of the same missing children
support group.
They had a gathering today
at Xinye Garden Restaurant.
But everyone who attended
is unreachable now.
Team One!
- Yes, sir!
Head to Xinye Garden Restaurant.
Move out!
- Yes, sir!
Master.
I'm going too.
Observe only.
No interfering with enforcement.
Understood!
Let's toast with tea
to thank Sang
for giving us another chance
to find our children.
Thank you.
Oh, don't mention it.
It's alright.
- Thank you.
Well, I need to take this call.
You guys carry on.
Don't worry, everyone.
Let's wait a little longer.
[United hearts bring loved ones home]
Hello?
Sang,
it's all done.
What?
You found my sister?
They found his sister.
If his sister was found,
that's good news for us too.
Maybe our children can be found as well.
Right?
At least there's more hope now.
Alright.
Stay where you are.
Send me the address. I'm coming now!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
They really found her.
They found her?
They found my sister!
Congratulations!
Thank you. Thank you!
I don't even know what to say.
No need to say anything.
Go. Just go.
Okay, alright.
Well, I'll head out now.
Alright.
Be careful on the road.
You'll find your children too!
I'm leaving.
Go ahead.
Hello, honey?
No way.
The money's gone?
Hello?
- What?
That money was for finding our child!
Call the police!
What's going on?
We're finished.
You go that way!
[People's Public Security]
In this
missing children group scam case,
we successfully froze payments
for three families.
The other twelve families
[Personal Information]
suffered varying financial losses,
totaling 2.12 million yuan.
We've confirmed.
The mastermind behind this is Sang Tuo!
This time, he impersonated Han Chuan
to commit fraud.
Clearly an act of revenge.
How are the victims holding up?
They're furious.
No amount of explaining helps.
And...
And what?
They're demanding Han Chuan be punished.
Try to calm them down.
Avoid a mass incident.
Understood.
Any new leads on Sang Tuo?
When we arrived at the restaurant,
we saw him leaving.
I chased him
but lost him at an intersection.
He's highly slippery.
We cross-checked fingerprints
from everyone at the gathering.
But his weren't there.
Of all the victims present,
only Zheng Jiahe
had met Santuo before.
All the information Zheng Jiahe had
about Sang Tuo
was fake.
We're reviewing nearby surveillance.
A wanted notice has been issued.
No new leads yet.
Sang Tuo is quite cunning.
Han Chuan,
for now, you'll assist the investigation
as a civilian.
Understood.
Remember,
you have no law enforcement authority.
Hand over Han Chuan!
Get Han Chuan out here!
Han Chuan, come out!
You corrupt cop!
Give us the corrupt cop!
Calm down!
Calm down, my foot!
Everyone, listen to me!
Hand him over!
♪Silver starry sky♪
♪Winding into a dream♪
♪An undercurrent in the riverbed♪
♪A glimmer of light between the fingers♪
♪Melts the cold winter♪
♪We hold onto the fire♪
♪In our palms♪
♪In the fog♪
♪There's a nameless boat♪
♪That understands where to go♪
♪When the shadows are dispelled♪
♪Fireflies will flicker♪
♪Illuminating the twists and turns
along the journey♪
♪Intertwined with you
in the wind and waves♪
♪In the midst of ups and downs♪
♪We drift together♪
♪No matter how cold the glacier is♪
♪No matter how deep the vortex is♪
♪The dawn has never♪
♪Fallen♪