[Under the Cover]
[Episode 10]
[People's Public Security]
Hello.
This is
the Jianghai Public Security Bureau,
Anti-Fraud Unit.
[Wang Jincheng]
[Billionaire Wang Jincheng.
Work with me. Target amount ?]
Why would Han Chuan
target on Wang Jincheng?
Target amount…
How big is he aiming this time?
Mr. An.
Wang Jincheng didn't pick up.
He's the richest man in Jianghai,
with billions at his disposal.
Do you think he'll take a random call?
Mr. An, we've withdrawn the money.
Return it
to the folks who reported a case.
And tell them,
next time when they get one of those
9,999-yuan scam calls,
having been scammed or not,
contact us immediately.
Got it.
[Billionaire Wang Jincheng.
Work with me. Target amount ?]
By the way, Yaqi.
There will be more reports coming.
The amount is unknown yet.
Keep a close eye on it.
See if anyone shows up.
Okay.
Mr. An.
Do you have enough balance for it?
Alas. It's for Han.
Until the last penny.
Yang Yang.
Come with me to Wang's place.
Okay.
Mr. An,
we can handle
those 9,999 yuan calls.
But if Mr. Han's asking for a million…
are we going to sell our apartments?
Han Chuan went through a lot
to send us the hint
about scamming the richest guy.
He must be in trouble over there.
Let's go.
Okay.
[Anti-Telecom and Cyber Fraud Center]
Officers,
it's not that I won't let you in.
We have rules here.
Without the owner's consent,
I can't let you enter.
Look,
this isn't some normal residential area.
And Mr. Wang isn't back yet.
When does he usually get back?
I wish I knew.
But how would I know that?
That's Mr. Wang's car.
Don't let him know I told you.
Stop! Stop!
Why is he running away?
Wang Jincheng!
Stop!
Why are you running, Wang Jincheng?
You're…
Yeah,
why was I running?
I didn't break the law.
Why did you chase me?
Because you ran.
I ran because you were after me.
Alright, alright.
Wang Jincheng,
we're here
to ask for your cooperation.
Co-cooperation?
This guy, Wang Jincheng,
refused to cooperate.
I tried to convince him
as much as I can,
telling him he'd only have to fake it,
just playing along.
But he kept saying no.
I know this guy.
We've dealt with him before.
He's a total penny-pincher
and won't spend a cent.
And he likes pocketing little things.
He's so rich but steals from others?
It's a mental problem, I think.
If he doesn't take
something from others,
he doesn't feel like himself.
The stuff he took wasn't pricey.
We detained him a few times.
He said he had changed.
No wonder he bolted at the sight of us.
But that habit lives in him.
I've got an idea.
Okay.
Alright, babe.
Buy it.
We'll buy them all.
It's only several hundred thousand.
I'll pay.
I'll spend it on you.
Don't be mad, okay?
Hey, babe.
I need to take this call.
I'll buy them. I promise.
Hello?
Buddy,
I know your voice by now.
Stop calling me from new numbers.
You're a scammer.
You can't fool me.
Even my dumbest move
is smarter than yours.
Do yourself a favor, find another job.
You're not cut out for this.
Tsk!
Got hung up again?
I thought you were quite capable.
I've been dying to find a chance
to learn from you, respectfully.
Less than six hours left.
At this rate,
it's bye-bye for you two.
Have fun.
What a jerk.
Shisan.
I heard your sister had a high fever,
and they wouldn't treat her.
Any discount?
Sorry, sir.
This is the latest collection.
No discounts.
A good knock-off will do.
I'm really sorry, sir.
Okay, okay, got it.
I'll take it.
Seriously,
a rich guy with billions at hand
swipes bottled water?
Mr. An, is this really necessary?
Wait a bit more.
Sir, your bag.
And your card, please.
Bye.
Sir,
one moment, please.
A belt that was placed here is missing.
We may need to check your bag.
Do you think I stole it
from you?
Forget your stupid belt.
I could buy your store
or even this whole building.
Sir, sir.
Sir.
You… you can't leave!
Hands off, you hear me?
Hello.
Police.
Mr. An.
Perfect timing.
They're framing me for stealing a belt.
Why do I bother? Stealing a belt?
Isn't that ridiculous?
We heard your talk just now.
That belt wasn't stolen by him.
He did it.
Look, he's the one who stole it.
If nothing went wrong,
An Fei should have received
the clues I sent back.
Did he fail to crack it this time
and fail to find Wang Jincheng?
How's Xiaoxiao right now?
Shisan,
there is no time to zone out.
We've got only five hours left.
I handed you a whole list.
If this one won't bite, try another.
Why cling to this guy?
You!
No need.
I'll try again.
Gosh.
Stubborn as a mule.
Sihai,
I'm bringing the boys here
to learn from Shisan.
Do you mind?
I might miss the show
if I come any time later.
Why are you so mean?
Can't you say something nice?
Take notes.
Watch and learn.
Learn well.
Mr. Wang,
let's have a video chat.
You'll know I'm not
a scammer when you see me.
Oh, it's real.
I'm so sorry.
My apologies.
I swear I didn't mean it.
I've got too many scam calls lately.
My apologies.
Let me confirm your info again.
Wang Jincheng,
legal rep and chairman
of Jianghai Jincheng New Energy Group,
right?
Yes.
According to the tax system,
your company's involved
in tax evasion or avoidance.
You need to pledge assets
and let the Tax Bureau
audit your bank flows.
Alright.
[Hesitate]
It feels like…
No.
That can't be right.
I always pay tax strictly by the book.
Every time.
Have you ever tried to reduce tax?
[Yes.]
Well...
That was legal at the time.
What used to be legal
isn't necessarily legal now.
Wang Jincheng,
you've got a sister, right?
S-sister?
It doesn't say anything
about a sister here.
Which sister are you talking about?
You know exactly which one.
You used her company as cover
[Xiaoxiao]
to evade taxes.
Do you think we can't trace it?
[Admits it.]
Officer, I was wrong.
I got greedy.
Wang Jincheng,
listen up.
What I say next is critical.
The state is cracking
down hard on tax evasion.
Penalties are severe.
Han Chuan's in danger in that place.
[He's at risk.]
You must pay all dues by 6 p.m.
Otherwise,
not just you,
we'll go after your sister, too.
If the money isn't in by six,
both he and Xiaoxiao are in danger.
[Six o'clock. Xiaoxiao.]
But
as long as you stop doing it again,
the government
won't make it hard for you.
[After this challenge...]
Getting past this,
Han Chuan and Xiaoxiao
will be safe for now.
My superiors have made it clear
that once the penalties are received,
you don't need to worry
about anything else.
We'll take care
of the rest of the procedure for you.
You'll be fine.
[Intercept laundering]
Han needs the funds in,
so we can intercept
during money laundering.
Got it?
Got it. I got it.
Officer,
how much do I need to pay?
Twenty million.
[Billionaire Wang Jincheng.
Work with me. Target amount ?]
Twenty million!
[Agreed]
Twenty million.
[Calling…]
[Call declined]
That's it?
You scared him off.
Trying to get twenty million
out of one guy.
How dare you!
No one here could pull this off
but you, huh?
Now look at you.
Look at you!
Keep your mouth shut, will you?
Your failure isn't his.
My failure?
That's fine.
Shisan,
if you can't do it,
people will die.
Two people.
Two.
Let's go.
You lot.
Nothing good ever comes
out of his mouth.
Shisan,
don't let him get to you.
We've got time.
Wait it out.
Mr. Wang, listen.
I really can't do this.
Pack up. Please leave now.
I'm telling you,
Officer,
sorry, I can't help you.
Find someone else.
Mr. Wang, please.
We'll do everything we can
to keep your funds safe.
This is about my colleague's life.
But you didn't say twenty million!
Mr. An, it's not that I won't help.
If Mr. Han said
two or three hundred thousand,
even two million,
I'd say yes,
not without hesitation though.
It's a rescue, right?
But he said twenty million!
I'm rich,
but money doesn't grow on trees.
Do you know my annual profit?
Mr. Wang.
Mr. An,
sorry for being honest.
Mr. Han is your buddy.
But
I don't know him.
We're not relatives or friends.
Why should I risk it?
Honestly, why should I?
You guys,
find someone else.
Please leave now.
Sorry, Officers.
Pack your things.
Go, go, go.
Please leave.
Sorry about that.
♪Silver starry sky♪
♪Winding into a dream♪
♪An undercurrent in the riverbed♪
♪A glimmer of light between the fingers♪
♪Melts the cold winter♪
♪We hold onto the fire♪
♪In our palms♪
♪In the fog♪
♪There's a nameless boat♪
♪That understands where to go♪
♪When the shadows are dispelled♪
♪Fireflies will flicker♪
♪Illuminating the twists and turns
along the journey♪
♪Intertwined with you
in the wind and waves♪
♪In the midst of ups and downs♪
♪We drift together♪
♪No matter how cold the glacier is♪
♪No matter how deep the vortex is♪
♪The dawn has never♪
♪Fallen♪