[Under the Cover]
[Episode 24]
[File transfer in progress.
Estimated time remaining: 14 minutes]
Fourteen minutes.
No.
If the data isn't transmitted
within nine minutes,
the computer will activate
its self-protection mechanism.
Then all this will be for nothing.
This speed is still far from enough.
But how do I speed it up?
At this point,
we might as well go all in.
Overclock the CPU.
But that could easily cause overheating.
No choice now.
We have to try.
[Overclocking mode activated]
The time shortened again!
No.
Something's wrong.
What's wrong?
ZP high compression
is already the limit.
To speed it up further,
he'd have to overclock the CPU.
But that's extremely risky.
If the CPU overheats,
all the servers will crash.
Then everything will be for nothing.
He must be running out of time
to resort to this.
What do we do?
Overclock the CPU.
Gosh.
Please.
Overclock the CPU.
Got it.
If that's the case,
let's burn it all down.
[Estimated time remaining: 5 minutes]
Yes.
Perfect.
You read my mind.
Dual overclocking!
That's it.
Good.
Now give me a little time.
Just a little.
[Black box breached]
[Estimated time remaining: 9 seconds]
[Estimated time remaining: 0 seconds]
Sang Tuo!
What are you doing?
The data transfer is complete, right?
Who put you up to this?
I did! Let him go!
You know what?
I've been waiting for this day forever.
I could've done nothing
and lived safely.
I don't need money.
Especially not your ill-gotten money.
But
I've seen every vile thing you've done.
Countless families
have been torn apart by you,
left in ruins.
I'll only ask you one thing.
Who put you up to this?
You might as well ask
why I want to take you down.
I'll tell you,
it's conscience.
The most basic sense of humanity.
Sang Tuo,
I was never the coward
you thought I was.
Today,
I'll trade my life
for the destruction of this compound.
It's worth it.
Rui,
I'm sorry.
Sang Tuo!
Let him go!
♪An undercurrent in the riverbed♪
♪A glimmer of light between the fingers♪
♪Melts the cold winter♪
♪We hold onto the fire♪
♪In our palms♪
♪In the fog♪
♪There's a nameless boat♪
♪That understands where to go♪
♪When the shadows are dispelled♪
♪Fireflies will flicker♪
♪Illuminating the twists and turns
along the journey♪
Sang,
we've identified the repairman.
It's that Chinese cop, An Fei.
What?
He's trying to get Emmett out
to deal with us.
But Emmett's wife didn't dare agree.
Well, well.
What a great
"seriously ill and hospitalized" act.
A classic diversion.
Rest assured.
I'm at the hospital right now.
We have our people at every exit.
An Fei won't escape this time.
Pin something on them.
I want them
stripped of their badges.
Understood.
Track them down.
Find them!
- Yes, sir!
All the evidence
on the scam compound is here.
I've already made backups.
Good.
Send another copy of all the data
back to China.
Understood.
Let's go.
We're meeting Mrs. Emmett.
Got it.
We meet again,
Mr. An.
Catch them!
Stop!
Stop running!
Ma'am,
we've obtained all the evidence
against Sang Tuo.
It completely proves
he's the boss of the Red Obsidian Island
scam compound.
Mrs. Emmett,
on behalf of China's 118 Task Force,
I formally request once again
that you present this evidence
to the mayor
to save Mr. Emmett
and Mr. Han Chuan.
In that case,
I'll try again with the mayor.
Thank you, ma'am.
Shisan.
I trusted you completely,
yet you set me up.
I hate traitors the most.
Han Chuan,
I won't let you die so easily!
Sang Tuo,
you can't escape.
Oh, I can't?
Fine.
If I'm going down...
Mr. Dahn,
the director general
is waiting for you in his office.
The director general is here?
Yes, he arrived early this morning.
Heard there was some trouble
with the mayor, so...
Alright, I understand. You can go.
Boss, you...
You?
Surprised?
Arrest him!
Emmett!
You're no longer the director general!
You corrupt criminal!
What authority do you have to arrest me?
Mr. Emmett,
this guy tried to escape
through the window,
but I caught him.
Good.
Not a single corrupt cop
walks free today!
You don't know yet, do you?
We've got
all the evidence on Sang Tuo's fraud,
as well as proof
that he framed Mr. Emmett.
Your arrest
was ordered personally by the mayor.
We're splitting into three teams
for this operation.
We'll attack the island simultaneously.
Team A,
you will land at the dock
for a frontal diversion.
Heavy gunfire, explosions.
The key is to draw
all their firepower to us.
- Yes, sir!
Team B,
you'll take hovercrafts
and land on the north side
of the island.
Cross the swamp
and head straight for the main building!
- Yes, sir!
Team C,
you'll airdrop from helicopters
onto the main building.
Destroy their elevators
and trap them on every floor.
- Yes, sir!
Finally,
we must thank
the Chinese police officers
who came from afar.
Without your fearless efforts,
we couldn't have rooted out
the corruption in the police force
and dismantled
the scam compound so swiftly.
Mr. Emmett,
we appreciate your full support
for this operation.
I believe justice will prevail.
Well said.
Justice will prevail!
Move out!
- Yes, sir!
Shisan,
your cop friends are here.
You won.
But
you're going to die too!
♪Silver starry sky♪
♪Winding into a dream♪
♪An undercurrent in the riverbed♪
♪A glimmer of light between the fingers♪
♪Melts the cold winter♪
♪We hold onto the fire♪
♪In our palms♪
♪In the fog♪
♪There's a nameless boat♪
♪That understands where to go♪
♪When the shadows are dispelled♪
♪Fireflies will flicker♪
♪Illuminating the twists and turns
along the journey♪
♪Intertwined with you
in the wind and waves♪
♪In the midst of ups and downs♪
♪We drift together♪
♪No matter how cold the glacier is♪
♪No matter how deep the vortex is♪
♪The dawn has never♪
♪Fallen♪