[Under the Cover]
[Episode 23]
Mr. An.
Mr. An, are you alright?
Stay still.
They're still watching us.
Play along.
Get me to a hospital now.
Then spread the word
that I'm critically injured,
on the brink of death.
Understood.
Mr. An,
you're as bold as you are brilliant.
With this move,
Sang Tuo will believe
Mr. An is severely injured.
And he won't come after us for a while.
But I still think this was too risky.
What if the coordination failed...
It wouldn't.
My brother and Mr. An
have been partners for nearly a decade.
He's spent more time with Mr. An
than he has with me.
Your brother would surely
pick up on my cues.
Knowing him,
he'd rather die
than press the detonator otherwise.
But
Sang Tuo is ruthless.
Would he actually kill my brother?
Relax.
Your brother's sharp.
He'll be fine.
By the way,
I already gave the jade pendant
to your brother.
Sang Tuo's not likely
to suspect a thing.
That's great.
I just hope he discovers
the secret inside it.
Shisan,
look who I brought.
Shisan.
Xiong.
Sit.
Before Xiong's family went bankrupt,
they were in the jade trade.
Let him take a look.
Really?
They gave me this piece of jade
when I was on the island.
I don't know much about it.
Help me check it.
Sure.
Let me see.
Shisan,
who gave this to you?
Doesn't matter who.
Just tell me.
This jade is fake.
Look,
this is a seam.
Two jade pieces are fitted together.
But the craftsmanship is exceptional.
Only a seasoned expert,
with a high-powered flashlight
at the right angle,
could spot it.
Most people would never know.
This is strange.
Such high-end work
on low-grade material.
The labor cost alone
wouldn't justify it.
Dahn gave me fake jade?
Mr. Dahn gave this to you?
You didn't hear this from me.
I was never here.
Never saw any jade.
I've got patrol duty.
Shisan,
nice move.
Saved yourself some hush money too.
Two jade pieces are fitted together.
Shisan!
There's a whole hidden world inside it.
We need to find a way to read it.
Such a tiny chip.
We need a special interface
and a computer.
But we've got nothing.
What do we do now?
Shisan,
I'll figure something out.
You?
Sang Tuo framed Mr. Emmett.
That's why Mr. Emmett
is under investigation.
What's the point of saying all this now?
I hope you can help us
report to the mayor that Sang Tuo
is the mastermind
behind the compound.
Mr. An Fei,
you're a Chinese police officer.
Yet Sang Tuo has pushed you so far
that you have to disguise yourself
just to meet me.
And I, as the director general's wife,
am also being pressured
by them to the point
that I'm too afraid to step outside.
That's why
we can't let him keep running wild.
He has connections everywhere.
All the evidence has been tampered with.
Right now,
I just want my children
to grow up safely.
I don't want
to offend those people.
You bunch of losers!
Were you all raised in a pigsty?
Clean this mess up now!
Damn it!
Four-eyes,
you really don't treat your men right.
Nothing but instant noodles?
Business has been slow.
Just make do with this.
I knew you were craving something.
Look what I've got here.
Nice.
Guys!
Come on, take it.
Come on!
Dig in!
I brought you all some good food.
Great. Great.
It's still hot. Eat up.
You'll work better on a full stomach.
Here, chopsticks.
Share it among yourselves.
Alright.
Tastes good.
Rui.
You're serious?
I thought you were just bragging.
You bet.
Told you
I was a top student.
A cutting-edge tech talent.
Don't underestimate me.
Shisan,
your sister...
What about her?
Anyone who can write code like this
is remarkable.
She's a pro.
The chip in this jade pendant
is a key to activate a Trojan program.
Previously, when she was forced
to develop scam programs
in the compound,
she secretly implanted
a Trojan in the black box.
But she was rescued
before she could finish it.
Now, what we need to do is
connect this chip to the black box.
Then we can activate the Trojan
and transfer all the data
from the black box.
So now we need to find a way
to connect to the black box.
Shisan, here's the plan.
You figure out a way
to draw Sang Tuo away.
I'll go implant the Trojan.
No, it's too dangerous.
I'll do it.
Shisan,
this isn't as simple
as just plugging it in.
You really can't handle it.
Any updates
on Mrs. Emmett?
Just a repairman came by yesterday.
Everything was normal.
She stayed at home
and didn't go to the mayor anymore.
We've scared her into submission.
Repairman?
What repairman?
Just a regular worker.
Her fridge broke down.
She made calls yesterday?
According to our phone surveillance,
no.
Then how did she call for a repairman?
Dig into it!
Come in!
Shisan?
I know my sister isn't with you.
Come have a drink with me.
Let's talk.
Shisan.
How did you know
Xiaoxiao isn't with me?
Bottoms up.
Here.
What are you trying to say?
Turn yourself in.
Shisan,
is that all we have to talk about?
How old were you in 2017?
Twenty-two.
I was twenty-three that year.
I had just joined
the police force for half a year.
Once, I was sent to arrest a thief.
That thief was 17.
Skinny and short.
His eyes were frighteningly bright.
A repeat offender.
He'd been stealing
from the same supermarket
for a month
before he got caught.
Then he was really stupid.
To keep stealing
from the same place for a month.
By the time I arrived,
he'd already run to the rooftop.
Nowhere left to run.
He stood at the edge,
clutching the money he'd stolen.
He said he didn't want to be arrested.
Said he'd rather die than go to jail.
I tried to talk him down.
It took forever,
but he finally listened.
Then he loosened his grip,
and the money slipped.
He reached out to grab it.
And then?
He fell?
I caught him.
He was dangling in mid-air,
regretting it.
He begged me through tears,
saying he didn't want to die.
He asked me to save him.
People only feel real fear and regret
when death is staring them
in the face.
So what happened in the end?
You pulled him up?
When I lunged forward,
my arm got cut.
I couldn't hold onto him.
And he couldn't climb up.
Once the blood started dripping,
we both lost our grip.
For the next two or three years,
I kept dreaming of him.
In the dreams, he'd beg me to save him
and say he didn't want to die.
That wasn't him begging you.
Just you blaming yourself.
[Trojan program activated.
Awaiting instructions...]
[Data transfer request received]
[Accept/Decline]
My brother activated the program.
Take it easy. Your foot...
My brother cracked
the jade pendant's secret.
He connected to the black box.
Once I confirm the command here,
the Trojan on their end
will automatically transmit all the data
from the black box.
[Trojan program activated.
Awaiting instructions...]
[Connection successful]
Qi, help me close the curtains.
I don't want any light at all.
Got it.
[Connection successful
Loading progress... 0%]
[Estimated transfer time: 60 min]
Why does it take so long?
No choice.
The file is too large.
This long?
Sang Tuo and Biao
could come back anytime.
I can't wait.
How can I speed it up?
Got it.
No.
The receiving end needs
to modify the program simultaneously.
Can Han Xiaoxiao understand this?
Never mind. No time.
Let's try anyway.
[File transfer paused]
Xiaoxiao.
What... What's going on?
What is he doing?
Han Xiaoxiao,
you have to understand this.
You have to.
What happened?
He's using a new technology.
ZP high compression.
Cuts transfer time
from an hour to 15 minutes.
But it requires my cooperation
to receive it.
[File transfer in progress]
She understands.
She really does.
[Estimated time remaining: 14 minutes]
Mr. Han knows programming too?
No.
That's not my brother on the other end.
But it's definitely a top-tier expert.
Someone this skilled trapped
in a scam compound.
What a shame.
Once the compound is taken down,
he'll be free.
Sang Tuo,
I'm not trying to arrest you
just to put you in jail.
You're young.
There's still a chance.
Shisan,
if you're here
to talk me into stopping,
then I'll pass
on the drink.
♪Silver starry sky♪
♪Winding into a dream♪
♪An undercurrent in the riverbed♪
♪A glimmer of light between the fingers♪
♪Melts the cold winter♪
♪We hold onto the fire♪
♪In our palms♪
♪In the fog♪
♪There's a nameless boat♪
♪That understands where to go♪
♪When the shadows are dispelled♪
♪Fireflies will flicker♪
♪Illuminating the twists and turns
along the journey♪
♪Intertwined with you
in the wind and waves♪
♪In the midst of ups and downs♪
♪We drift together♪
♪No matter how cold the glacier is♪
♪No matter how deep the vortex is♪
♪The dawn has never♪
♪Fallen♪