[♪ ominous music]
[♪ theme music]
REVENANT
THE CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
CHILD ACTORS WERE FILMED
IN SAFE SITUATIONS
SCENES INVOLVING ANIMALS WERE STAGED
AND FILMED IN COMPLIANCE WITH
ANIMAL WELFARE GUIDELINES
[Sanyeong] You've grown a lot.
You were just a kid then.
[♪ ominous music]
Do you remember...
that day?
[rustling]
[♪ ominous music]
[seatbelt clanks]
[car door opens]
-Put that down.
-Mom?
I said put that down!
What's wrong?
Mom, where are we going?
[♪ ominous music]
You're scaring me.
I want to go home.
I don't like this.
[Haesang's mom] No, Haesang.
-No.
-[lighter clanks]
[gasps]
[♪ ominous music]
[Sanyeong]
Who do you think killed your mom?
Me?
Or was it...
you?
[gasps]
[♪ sinister music]
[pants]
[giggles]
[giggling]
[exhales]
[sniffles]
[breathes shakily]
The pear seed hair accessory...
was gifted to little girls
whose hair had just begun to grow.
[Haesang]
It wasn't just another accessory.
It was a talisman
that carried one's wishes
for safety and good health...
for the girl.
[♪ pensive music]
[Haesang exhales]
Who was the owner...
of this hair accessory?
I don't know if it was you
or someone else yet,
but I'll find them.
Then I'll be able to find out your name.
[♪ pensive music]
Twenty-one.
[♪ music fades]
[♪ pensive music]
Twenty-one.
One hundred seventy-six.
Ms. Sanyeong.
Twenty-one.
One hundred seventy-six.
[♪ music stops]
[♪ dramatic music]
[groans]
[Sanyeong gasps]
Why...
am I here?
[car horn honking]
[loud honking]
Why am I here?
Did we come here together?
Take this.
Nothing happened, so take this.
[sniffles]
[♪ dramatic music]
[Haesang] "Twenty-one.
One hundred seventy-six."
Do you remember saying those numbers?
What are they?
I don't know.
[Sanyeong]
The numbers just popped up in my mind.
It felt as if someone inside me...
was saying them.
[Sanyeong] "Twenty-one.
One hundred seventy-six."
EPISODE 4
"Twenty-one. One hundred seventy-six."
What could they be?
I'm certain they're related
to the evil spirit.
I'll look into it.
You should go home and rest.
[sighs]
Did I really...
not do anything back there?
No, you didn't.
[exhales]
This anxiety is eating me up.
I don't remember
how I left the aquarium store.
I swear...
I was home but I found myself
on the bridge.
[Sanyeong]
I keep seeing and hearing strange things.
I don't know what else I might do.
[sighs]
I'm scared.
You'll be fine during the day.
Ghosts avoid light.
[Haesang] But you should be wary
of bodies of water, even in the daylight.
They are full of negative energy.
You should be especially careful
on rainy days.
[sighs]
Wait here.
[♪ somber music]
[tires screech]
What is this?
I heard you needed money.
No, thank you. I'm okay.
Evil spirits target
their victim's biggest weakness.
It'll continue to do that,
so just take it.
THE BEST, GARAM
GARAM BANK
[♪ pensive music]
Thank you for driving me.
[Haesang] Bye.
[car door opens]
[engine revs]
[Sanyeong] Wait!
Take this with you!
I told you to take this!
[panting]
[♪ dramatic music]
[♪ music stops]
[Sanyeong panting]
[knocks on window]
-[breathing heavily]
-[window whirring]
[Sanyeong exhales]
Just think of it as a loan.
[Sanyeong] It's too much.
[panting]
It's too much.
Our house isn't as big as yours.
Five million is enough.
Fifty million is too much.
[Sanyeong] I took five million.
I'm returning 45 million.
I'll definitely pay you back.
[Sanyeong] I'll pay you back in full
with interest too.
[car horn honking]
[Sanyeong] Thank you. I'll use it well.
[car horn honks]
[♪ dramatic music]
What? That professor gave you money?
[Gyeongmun] Why?
He didn't just give it to me.
I borrowed it.
I'll pay him back soon.
Hey, I don't like him.
I don't want you to see him anymore.
Is it because he studies folklore?
Mom.
Why do you hate Dad so much?
[Gyeongmun] A no is a no.
You'd better listen to me.
[♪ dramatic music]
[door opens]
-[door closes]
-[sighs]
[exhales]
[associate] What's gotten into you?
You're throwing away your favorite.
That's right.
Evil spirits target
their victim's biggest weakness.
If I want to put up a good fight,
I should eliminate all my weaknesses.
"Twenty-one. One hundred seventy-six."
You're going to look into those numbers?
[Haesang] Chae Su, a civil official,
wrote The Tale of Seol Gongchan
during Jungjong of Joseon's reign.
He said that ghosts were left-handed.
[bottles clinking]
It was fiction, but it portrayed
the thoughts of people back then.
That woman took the accessory
with her right hand.
That means she was sane at that time.
But it was the evil spirit
who told her those numbers.
The evil spirit could have leaked
the numbers on purpose.
I know,
but it started the fight first.
I can't back down now.
-[Hongsae] Hello.
-[Munchun] Hello.
What did the aquarium store owner say?
He's still not in his right mind.
[Hongsae] Even the doctor said
he needed more rest.
[sighs]
You handed over that loan shark case
to Gwangcheon Police Station
when we did all the work.
Why are you reading up on that?
[Hongsae] They were scumbags
who targeted poor college students.
I'm sure blackmailing
and threatening were their forte.
He probably fabricated everything
thinking he could threaten Gu Sanyeong.
Hey, can you zoom in on her face?
[Munchun] Stop.
Look. She's smiling.
[pen clacks]
[♪ tense music]
You saw it in the footage.
He put on that show, and she just watched.
That's all there is to it.
[sighs deeply]
VIOLENT CRIMES INVESTIGATION UNIT 4 TEAM 3
[Hongsae] Where are you going?
The bruises on his wrists
keep bothering me.
I need to dig into this.
Sir, we agreed
that I'd choose the next case.
This case isn't over yet, you punk.
[♪ music stops]
[sighs]
[door opens]
[door closes]
-You guys go ahead.
-[student] Sure.
[background chatter]
[Sanyeong] They must've run around
very passionately.
Aren't you embarrassed?
No, I'm not.
-[friend 1] Sanyeong. That's Sanyeong.
-[friend 2] You haven't left yet?
-You're still working?
-[friend 1] See you at school.
-[friend 2] See you tomorrow.
-Bye.
PEANUT CHOCOLATE STICKS
[boxes thud]
To your right.
-Sorry?
-[Hongsae] You're going to crash.
[♪ dramatic music]
[Sanyeong] Thank you.
[panting]
[exhales]
What?
It's snowing.
[♪ dramatic music]
What on earth happened to you?
-[officer] Sir, hello.
-[Munchun] Hey.
Hey, did you say
Professor Gu's mother's death
will be concluded as suicide?
Yes, sir. We still have many questions
about the case,
but there's no proof.
[Munchun sighs]
What about the burnt notebook?
Did you restore anything?
[officer] Right.
They could only salvage this.
But it was irrelevant to the case.
[Munchun]
"Young Girl Missing for Two Weeks."
Hey, can I take this with me?
You have the original, right?
Sure.
[grunts]
[♪ suspenseful music]
[door rattles]
[door lock clanking]
HWAWONJAE
[♪ suspenseful music]
[grunts]
[grunting]
[shrieks]
[groans]
[panting]
[breathing heavily]
[pants]
[♪ music stops]
[switch clicks]
[♪ dramatic music]
[Sanyeong] The one who knew the most
about evil spirits.
Dad.
I'm sure he knew
what 21 and 176 meant.
GHOSTS EXPLAINED IN FOLKLORE
BY GU GANGMO
AUTHOR GU GANGMO
[♪ dramatic music]
"January 16 in the lunar calendar,
the 16th day of the new year.
The shrine was set up
in the Office of State Rites,
which oversaw memorial services
during the Joseon Era.
Six spirits were sealed toward the east
and nine were sealed toward the west."
[♪ tense music]
"Juvenile ghosts are ghosts of children
who died of smallpox or starvation."
[door creaks]
[♪ ominous music]
[♪ music rises]
[door creaking]
[♪ music intensifies]
[shrieks]
[♪ music stops]
[Sanyeong pants]
[pants]
[breathes heavily]
[Sanyeong sniffles]
You look very startled.
I am.
[exhales]
I'm guessing you were also looking
into the meaning behind those numbers.
I must've come to the right place
seeing how you're here too.
[Haesang] This book was published in 1998
and it was his only book.
I'm not sure why.
He continued to write theses,
but never published any more books
after this one.
[Haesang] I know the details in this book
like the back of my hand.
But neither this
nor other folklore books
ever mentioned those two numbers,
numbers 21 and 176.
[♪ suspenseful music]
-[book thuds]
-[exhales]
Then where should I begin searching?
[Sanyeong]
There was nothing in the drawers.
Maybe my grandmother got rid of them.
Let's look
for any memos that could've been left
inside the books.
[Haesang] I'll look here.
You can look over there.
[Sanyeong] Okay.
[exhales]
[♪ suspenseful music]
[Haesang]
Were you not scared of coming here?
I am, so we should hurry.
I'm scared that it'll happen to me again.
[Sanyeong] I need to resolve this
if I want to pay you back.
By the way,
were you not scared?
I saw my dad's book.
It mentioned all kinds of ghosts.
You must have seen them
since you were young.
Not all ghosts are scary.
At times, it's nice to see them.
Because you can see those
whom you miss so dearly.
[♪ pensive music]
Let's get back to work.
[♪ music stops]
[sighs]
Did you find anything?
No, nothing stands out.
Twenty-one. One hundred seventy-six.
[Haesang] Twenty-one.
One hundred seventy-six.
Twenty-one.
[Sanyeong] What is this?
It looks like a straw rope.
It's a Line of Prohibition.
That straw rope
is probably twisted to the left,
unlike a regular straw rope.
[Haesang]
It's used to ward off misfortune.
You hang them on those hangers.
Do you hang them like this?
[Haesang] Yes.
You normally hang them outside the door.
This is different.
But I don't think this has anything
to do with the numbers.
[Sanyeong sighs]
[mutters]
What do we do now?
Where was his bedroom?
I wouldn't know.
Let's search the other rooms.
[Sanyeong] Professor Yeom.
[♪ suspenseful music]
[clatters]
[Sanyeong grunts]
[door opens]
[switch clicks]
[♪ pensive music]
[chuckles]
This is...
[Sanyeong] It's my mom's handwriting.
They must've lived here together
before they got divorced.
[Haesang]
You'd think someone still lived here.
I don't know why they got divorced,
but I think he truly missed you
and your mother.
[Sanyeong] She still despises him.
She never tells me anything about him
no matter how much I ask.
I wonder why.
[♪ pensive music]
HIGH SCHOOL REUNION
MOM'S BIRTHDAY
FATHER'S MEMORIAL SERVICE
SANYEONG'S VACCINATION
"Estimated due date?"
What is it?
Isn't that your birthday?
No, I was five at the time.
[phone vibrating]
MR. LEE FROM JANGJIN-RI
Hello, Yeom Haesang speaking.
[Taeyoung's great-uncle] I wonder
if you've tried corn during the winter.
Thank you.
By the way, you could've taken your time.
[Haesang] That's okay.
Are you feeling better now?
Yes. I'm sorry about last time.
I was so out of it
that I even forgot to thank you.
Go on and tell them.
Here. You said you remembered him.
Are you sure it was him?
Maybe you confused him with someone else
since you saw him when you were little.
[Taeyoung's great-uncle]
Take a closer look.
It wasn't when I was little.
It was about a year ago.
[Taeyoung] My grandfather was at
a sanatorium before he passed away.
And that man visited us.
[Gangmo] Do you perhaps remember her?
A girl who went missing
in our village a long time ago?
Yes, she was in the newspaper too.
Here.
[Gangmo] Do you recognize her?
[Taeyoung's grandfather gasps]
This is Mokdan.
Mokdan?
Yes. Lee Mokdan.
He was looking for a girl
named Lee Mokdan?
[♪ pensive music]
Did he tell you why?
No, he didn't.
I think he was talking about that girl.
Do you know a girl named Mokdan?
I don't know her name.
But the entire village
was turned upside down
a long time ago
after a girl went missing.
YEAR 1958, JANGJIN-RI
[crickets chirping]
I'll count to ten.
[child] Ready, set, go.
One. Two.
-Mokdan, you should hide too.
-[child] Three.
Four. Five.
Six. Seven.
Eight. Nine.
[panting]
[♪ suspenseful music]
[child] Here I come!
[♪ eerie music]
Some said she went missing
while playing hide-and-seek.
Others said strangers came by
and kidnapped her.
[Taeyoung's great-uncle]
Rumors were rampant.
I don't know what happened afterward.
Was that girl never found?
What about her family?
Did you know any of them?
I wouldn't know.
[Taeyoung's great-uncle] I lived
with my uncle once I started school.
Did you say Professor Gu
showed your grandfather
a newspaper excerpt?
Yes.
NATIONAL LIBRARY OF KOREA
[Haesang] It happened when Mr. Lee was 14,
so that would've been 1958.
He said it was hot,
so it was between May and September.
It's more likely that the article
was published in the local newspaper
instead of a major one.
[clattering]
[Haesang] I'll show you how to use this.
Both the pear seed hair accessory
and Dukdali Tree
point toward a girl.
We must find Lee Mokdan.
Okay.
Are you familiar with Chinese characters?
Of course.
JANGJIN-RI, MISSING CHILD CASE, KIDNAPPING
[♪ tense music]
[machine whirring]
CAVE
SEONAM DAILY
AUGUST 4, 1958
[♪ music continues]
[machine whirring, beeping]
YOUNG GIRL MISSING FOR TWO WEEKS
Are you sure that news excerpt
has something to do
with Gu Sanyeong's grandmother?
Of course.
The culprit intentionally committed arson
to get rid of that notebook.
[Munchun] Why?
Because there was
an important lead inside.
When will this case end?
Do you seriously not know?
We need to find out why
and how the victims died.
Sir, promise me that
I'll get to choose our next case.
Look ahead.
[Munchun] The crosswalk law changed,
so it's very confusing.
YUJIN GO CLUB
There he is.
Hello, sir.
I'm Seo Munchun,
your junior by several years.
[♪ suspenseful music]
It was such an old case
that I could find nothing in the archives.
I did a lot of legwork,
and everyone mentioned you.
I heard there's not a single case
you don't know about.
They say you're a walking archive.
[Munchun chuckles]
Please sit here.
[grunts]
[slurps]
[exhales]
YOUNG GIRL MISSING FOR TWO WEEKS
You're right. I recognize this case.
June of 1958.
A girl had disappeared from a village
and was found later.
Her body looked
very gruesome.
How did it look?
It looked like she had been starved.
She was nothing but skin and bones.
And one of her fingers was missing.
Was it a wild animal?
No. Someone did that to her.
[♪ ominous music]
YEOMMAE, SHAMAN
NEARBY, KIDNAPPING
Professor Yeom.
[Sanyeong] Can you take a look at this?
This is strange.
A COLD-HEARTED SHAMAN WHO CREATED YEOMMAE
"Yeommae."
[Sanyeong] "An old shaman kidnapped
a girl from a nearby village
and starved the girl for 17 days.
She then put some rice balls
in a bamboo tube and offered them to her.
When the girl was focused
on grabbing the bamboo tube,
she killed the girl with a knife.
Then the girl's finger
was used as a host for deities.
When the girl was focused
on grabbing the bamboo tube,
she killed the girl with a knife."
So the shaman killed the girl.
Did this really happen?
I know it's gruesome,
but this sorcery was practiced.
It's even recorded in Veritable Records
of the Joseon Dynasty
that the creation of yeommaes
was forbidden.
Yeommae can mean
the act of cursing someone
by making a doll
using hay or parts of a tree.
Or it could also mean
the act of starving and killing a child
to turn them into a ghost.
It's a type of juvenile ghost.
Juvenile ghost?
Juvenile ghosts generally mean
vengeful spirits who died young.
In other words, they come
from children who died of smallpox
or starvation.
Lee Mokdan, the girl we're looking for.
It's highly likely
that she turned into one as well.
I've read about those ghosts.
I studied up on them in case it'd help us.
[♪ ominous music]
Look.
JUVENILE GHOSTS ARE GHOSTS OF CHILDREN...
[Sanyeong] There's more.
Professor Yeom.
[♪ music intensifies]
[♪ tense music]
Twenty-one. One hundred seventy-six.
They were page numbers.
JUVENILE GHOSTS ARE GHOSTS OF CHILDREN...
YEOMMAE IS RELATED TO JUVENILE GHOSTS
THE BAEKCHAGOL STRAW DOLL RITUAL
IS AN EXAMPLE
[Haesang] "Baekchagol."
[rain pattering]
BAEKCHAGOL VILLAGE
[thunder rumbling]
[knocks on door]
[♪ suspenseful music]
[thunder rumbles]
[elder's daughter] Mom! Mom!
[bangs on door]
Can you not hear me?
Mom, open the door!
Do you not hear me?
[knocking continues]
Mom!
[rain pattering]
[♪ music stops]
[Haesang]
Why did you suddenly offer to drive?
[Sanyeong groans]
I felt bad that you always had to do it.
I've done a lot of chauffeuring,
so I'm good at driving.
Don't worry about me and just relax.
[♪ ritual music playing on radio]
By the way, do you not listen
to other music like K-pop?
-No.
-I see.
I prefer the Deureonggaengi rhythm.
PURIFICATION RITUAL OF JINDO
[Haesang] I agree.
[sighs]
[navigation system beeping]
[navigation voice distorted]
Is this broken?
[navigation voice] Turn right. Then...
-[Sanyeong] Why isn't it working?
-Let me.
The second...
[navigation system distorting]
-What?
-Turn right ahead.
I'll pull over and take a look at it.
Turn right...
[♪ suspenseful rhythmic music]
[keys clacking]
We're almost here. It's that way.
That's Baekchagol Village's Sacred Tree.
[♪ eerie music]
You remember the path really well.
I thought you came here years ago?
I did a month-long investigation here.
Baekchagol Village is known
for its rituals.
Do you think my dad...
also visited this village?
We'll have to find out.
Since all the villagers are elderly,
there will be someone
who remembers Professor Gu Gangmo.
[birds chirping]
[♪ ominous music]
[elder 1] They're tangled.
[shrieks]
What are you doing?
You should be more careful
about a centuries-old tradition.
You've been ordering me around
since morning for the memorial service.
Stop bossing me around
when I'm not healthy to begin with.
Do you think I'm slacking off?
BAEKCHAGOL VILLAGE HALL
Put them back up before sundown!
[elder 2] Fine!
Why are you getting annoyed?
I should be the one getting irritated.
What a way to ruin my morning.
[elder 2] My back hurts.
You should be preparing food
for the service. Where are you going?
What do you think? I'm going home.
-Gosh.
-[elder 3] My body is aching all over.
I'm out.
[elder 1] Come on now.
What? Are you leaving too, Ms. Park?
Sir.
Let's stop doing this.
Every single villager is over 70 now.
And we're slowly dying out.
Must you force us to do this?
You should know better.
This ritual is our pride--
Enough with that. It's not our pride
if no one acknowledges it.
[Ms. Park]
Stop this before we all fall ill.
[elder 1] Gosh, but I need you.
[birds chirping]
What a pleasant surprise.
It's you, Professor Yeom.
Gosh. Long time no see.
It's been ages.
[elder 1] Are you his pupil?
Well...
We're here to watch the straw doll ritual.
You're here for the ritual!
[elders laughing]
Why are you looking around?
-Hello.
-Goodness, it's been ages.
-[elder 1] Thank you for coming.
[elder 1 laughing]
[ritual playing on TV]
[Haesang] This came out well.
[Sanyeong]
So that's the straw doll ritual.
I'm surprised that someone
as young as you knows about this ritual.
[Sanyeong chuckles]
It's a way of warding off
wandering ghosts.
Mm...
Wandering ghosts can latch onto you.
A ghost that died away from home
could latch onto a human
and make them ill or bring misfortune.
This ritual casts them away, right?
You've done your research.
I heard that
this village's straw doll ritual
has been going on
for an unfathomably long time.
That's what I read.
Right, Professor Yeom?
Yes.
[elder] It's all over.
We're the last ones to do this.
No one else will perform the rituals,
including the straw doll ritual,
once we're all gone.
Both that ritual
and this village will be gone
once we die.
How's the village nowadays?
Are the villagers healthy?
Well...
We're all old now,
so it's just as you'd expect.
[elder] Our bodies ache all over.
But why did you really come?
Are you really here to check on us?
[ritual continues playing on TV]
Actually, I have a question.
What is it?
Do you know Professor Gu Gangmo?
[Haesang] He also studied folklore.
He must've come to do research
on the straw doll ritual.
I'm not sure. It's not ringing any bells.
[Hongsae] I get that this case is bizarre,
but it's already been over 60 years.
How can we possibly find anything?
-[doorbell rings]
-[Hongsae sighs]
Unbelievable.
[doorbell rings]
[door unlocks]
Who are you?
Did your father write that?
Yes. My father wrote this article.
[Munchun] Do you remember hearing anything
about that incident from him?
For example, about the culprit's identity
or the victim's family.
He couldn't tell me anything.
Because he passed away
on the day this was published.
[Munchun mutters]
I'm sorry.
What happened?
He hanged himself
on our house's ridgepole.
[elder] I came home from school
and found him first.
[♪ suspenseful music]
He committed suicide?
Yes.
I remember it like it was yesterday.
Look. Did he perhaps...
Weren't there bruises
like these on the wrists?
How did you know?
[♪ music continues]
Ma'am, please take a good look.
Did he really have
these red bruises on his wrists?
Yes, he did.
By the way,
did you get this excerpt from that man?
Sorry? What man?
[blows air]
I believe his name was
Professor Gu Gangmo.
[elder] He came by about a year ago
and also asked me about this.
He asked me
for the original copy of the article.
[♪ music intensifies]
[♪ music fades]
[door closes]
[♪ suspenseful music]
What is going on?
[Hongsae] Gu Sanyeong.
Professor Gu Gangmo.
Suicide cases with bruised wrists.
I'm still lost,
but they all seem to be connected.
Professor Gu Gangmo.
Let's dig deeper into him.
He's at the center of this case.
[elder 1] How's the food?
It's delicious.
[elder 1 chuckles]
[Sanyeong] It's so scrumptious. Thank you.
[elders] Enjoy the food.
[laugh]
-Eat up.
-[elder 2] Professor Yeom.
Do you still see ghosts?
[Sanyeong] Yes, he does.
I thought he was strange
when I first met him.
[elders laugh]
[elder 3] You pretty little thing.
You must suffer a lot because of him.
[laughs]
Are you folks really okay?
Yes, we are. Why do you keep asking?
Right. Who was it again?
-Gu what?
-Professor Gu Gangmo.
Do any of you recognize that name?
[elder 4] Who is that?
Professor Yeom is here because of him.
He also studied folklore.
-I'll show you his photo.
-[elder 1] Sure.
Gu who studied folklore? Isn't it him?
He married the daughter of the family
living in the bamboo tree house.
-Pardon?
-I lived across from them.
I remember him because something bad
happened to the elderly lady.
[coughing]
Her daughter worked at the town office.
I believe her name was Gyeongmun.
[♪ pensive music]
[elder 2 coughs]
Yoon Gyeongmun?
Yes, you're right. Yoon Gyeongmun.
[line ringing]
[Sanyeong] Why isn't she picking up?
Mom.
-Mom, was Baekchagol your hometown?
-[Gyeongmun] What?
Is this where you met Dad and married him?
You said Seoul was your hometown.
Did you lie about that too?
[Gyeongmun] How did you know?
Don't tell me you're there right now.
Are you in Baekchagol?
Answer me first.
Get out! Leave that place immediately!
-What?
-[elder 1] Hey, what's wrong? Mr. Yang!
-[Gyeongmun] Hello? Sanyeong!
-[elder 1] What happened?
-[Sanyeong] Mom, I'll call you back later.
-[elder 3] What's going on?
[elders' overlapping chatter]
Mr. Yang!
-Call 911!
-Can you hear me?
-Hello?
-Mr. Yang!
[elder 4] Hey! Are you okay?
[♪ ominous music]
[♪ music stops]
[Sanyeong] What was that just now?
Wandering ghosts.
Is that why he passed away?
It's highly likely,
if his condition suddenly worsened.
[elder] Thank you.
[vehicle door closes]
[♪ eerie music]
[Sanyeong gasps]
How many of them are here?
There are four more.
I need to look around the village,
but I'm sure there are many more.
[♪ ominous music]
Doesn't this mean...
that all of them are in danger?
Goodness, we've been losing
one villager after another these days.
Maybe we should postpone the ritual.
This is bad luck.
We should...
just get rid of it entirely.
[Ms. Park] Take that old man for example.
He was forced to prepare for the ritual
despite being unwell
and look where that got him.
Stop this before another one of us dies.
That's enough!
Professor Yeom, say something.
[♪ ominous music]
[Haesang] I think it'll be best
if you all went home tonight.
What do you mean?
We still have so much to do
before the ritual.
But there's something you must do.
You must never look behind you
on your way home.
Keep your head down.
And lock the doors
once you arrive home. Understood?
[elders murmuring]
[elder 2] Wait for me.
[elder 1] How could you side with them?
[Haesang] Sir.
There are wandering ghosts in the village.
Wandering ghosts?
You're saying we have ghosts?
Are you serious?
-Yes.
-[elder 1] But why?
We've been painstakingly carrying out
the ritual every single year.
[elder 1 sighs]
So tell me.
[elder 1] What should we do?
Where are the straw dolls?
[elder 1] What are you going
to do with them?
The straw doll ritual
will ward off wandering ghosts.
We must cast them away.
[door opens]
[elder 1] They're here.
What? Where did they go?
Are you sure you put them here?
Of course.
I brought new sorghum rice cakes
and liquor here every morning and prayed.
It was here this morning
when we cleaned the room.
Then maybe one of the villagers took it
after cleaning the room.
Why would they?
We should ask those who cleaned
the room just in case.
[elder 1] But...
All right.
[Ms. Park] Goodness, I almost forgot.
[♪ tense music]
Goodness.
[grunts]
[♪ ominous music]
Come on. Why aren't they picking up?
Jeez.
[Ms. Park] Oh, no.
[phone vibrating]
[knife thudding on chopping board]
[elder 2 gasping]
[phone ringing]
-[line ringing]
-We'll go to them ourselves.
Whom should we visit?
Ms. Park, Ms. No, and Mr. Kim
were in charge of cleaning today.
You should go to their houses.
[♪ tense music]
-[♪ music stops]
-[elder shrieks]
[Sanyeong] Ma'am!
[tires screeching]
[breathing heavily]
[driver] Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
No, I'm okay.
VILLAGE HEAD
[electricity crackling]
[♪ ominous music]
[Sanyeong] Drink some warm water.
[blowing]
[slurps]
[exhales]
You must've been very startled.
Are you better now?
Thank you so much, young lady.
[Sanyeong chuckles]
Don't mention it.
I have a question.
The village head said
you cleaned the shrine this morning.
Did you see the straw dolls by any chance?
I couldn't clean today.
[Ms. No] My back was killing me.
Mr. Kim couldn't go either
due to an emergency.
I heard Ms. Park cleaned by herself.
Ma'am, are you in?
[wind gusting]
[Haesang] Ma'am.
[♪ suspenseful music]
[♪ thrilling music]
Stay still, ma'am.
Why are you here?
[♪ suspenseful music]
[♪ thrilling music]
You can see her too.
Yes, I do.
I can see what you see.
Then why aren't you avoiding her?
Why should I?
This is my first time
seeing my daughter in decades.
[Ms. Park] She felt suffocated
in the countryside
and ran off to the city.
I don't know what troubled her so much,
but she committed suicide.
[♪ somber music]
[Ms. Park] Not a single day goes by
that I don't think of her.
So why would I avoid her?
[♪ music stops]
[wind gusting]
[♪ ominous music builds]
[line ringing]
[phone beeps]
[Sanyeong gasps]
[evil spirits murmuring]
[♪ ominous music]
[♪ music rises]
[♪ tense music]
[♪ music stops]
Her wandering ghost can latch onto me.
I've lived a long life anyway.
I'd rather die and be with her.
Did you get rid of the straw dolls?
Because the ritual
would make your daughter disappear?
[♪ suspenseful music]
Yes, it was me.
I burned them.
[♪ tense music]
[clatters]
It's okay.
Now that the dolls are gone,
nothing can harm you.
[♪ tense music]
[groaning]
[banging on door]
[♪ music intensifies]
[Sanyeong whimpers]
[sobbing]
[♪ ominous music]
[breathes heavily]
STORE
[grunts]
[♪ music intensifies]
[gasps]
[♪ tense music]
[♪ music stops]
Dad.
REVENANT
[♪ closing theme music]
I won't let anyone harm my daughter.
[Haesang]
Do you want all the villagers to die?
[Hongsae] I connected the lead
we recently found to these cases.
-A new lead?
-Professor Gu Gangmo.
[Haesang] I thought
it was strange from the start.
I'm sure that child is the evil spirit.
[Sanyeong]
All the villagers took part in her death.
[Haesang] Do you desire Sanyeong's youth?
No matter how much you take,
you'll never be satiated.
[Sanyeong screams]
Be quiet!
[sobbing]
Translated by Sooji Kim