[Alarm]
Am I going crazy?
I’m screwed.
[Yeom Minhyeok as Han Jiwon]
[Choi Jaehyeok as Kwon Jeongwu]
[Choi Rakyeong as Byeon Seungjin]
[Kwak Geonhee as Yang Eunoh]
[Ballboy Tactics]
What, did you catch a cold?
See? Keep your clothes on at home.
You're one to talk, you nudist.
Yeah.
You don't even freaking wear pants.
What can I do?
I was born with a good bod.
Why should I hide it?
Oh my god.
If Jiwon knew you were like this,
would he still be your friend?
What?
Hey, the great Han Jiwon
can't hear about such unholy stuff!
Ew. What's wrong with you?
Shouldn't you go to the doctor's?
Do you have the flu?
Gosh.
Go home and rest.
Hey, wait for me.
What are you doing here?
What?
Oh.
I'm on my way home.
Don't you have class today?
No.
I'm not feeling well.
What's wrong?
Are you sick?
Does your heart hurt?
Shouldn't you go to the hospital?
No.
I'll just rest at home.
Can you go by yourself?
Want me to take you home?
Where's your car?
No!
No, I can go by myself.
Don't you have classes?
Go.
Don't be late.
But I can't leave a sick person behind.
No.
Can you leave?
I'm fine as long as you're not around.
Really?
Okay.
Seriously!
What's wrong with me?
Did I do something wrong?
I feel...
entranced by you.
Has anyone ever told you that?
What?
Those exact words.
Has anyone
told you that?
People say they like me, sometimes.
From guys too?
N-No, why would they?
You know...
A guy liking a guy's a bit...
Right.
What's the point of guys getting together?
I'm so tired.
Goodness.
You're here.
Medicine and congee.
Have it.
Are you feeling better?
I'll be fine after taking the medicine.
Oh my god!
Han Jiwon posted something!
Really? Show me!
[h.jiwon04: Thank you]
[hyo._.seok58: As your guardian angel,
I'll be there whenever you need me, Jiwon]
Jiwon must have made friends.
That's nice.
Jiwon hasn't even posted
anything about me...
Who the hell is he?
No idea.
He's good-looking.
I must go look for Jiwon tomorrow
and make him post photos with me.
Wow, Han Jiwon sure is popular.
Is that a surprise?
He's the nation's grandson, Han Jiwon!
What are you saying?
He is the nation's grandson
and the nation's son.
He is not just kind of popular.
My mom, dad, aunt, grandpa,
and even distant relatives—
Who doesn't like Han Jiwon?
W-What's wrong?
This is pissing me off.
Hey.
Don't provoke Jiwon's fanboy.
Who will stop his rants?
Deal with it.
What the hell?
Why is he always so riled up whenever
Han Jiwon is mentioned?
Working hard for the exams?
Yeah, of course.
I knew it.
And you?
Me too.
[Yang Eunoh]
Hello?
Yeah, I am.
Why?
All of a sudden?
He's hurt?
Jeongwu got hurt?
It's been a while.
Anyway, he's in a really bad state.
But we have practice now.
Please take care of him.
We have practice now?
Where are you going?
Ah, something urgent came up.
Sorry.
Can you leave?
I'm fine as long as you're not around.
Can I go in?
[Dorm password: 1818]
[Thanks for helping, Jiwon]
Guess you took your medicine.
Why aren't you dodging this time?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I thought I was still dreaming.
Ah! You didn't expect
me to be here, right?
Eunoh told me to come take care of you.
Do you have a fever?
Your hand is so cooling.
Is it because I'm sick?
What?
Being like this
is nicer than I thought.
I just think
being with you
has made me realize some things.
About what?
That I'm really doing bad right now.
So,
will you comfort me?
How?
Whatever you say will work, I think.
Hmm...
It was an ordinary day.
I woke up at eight
and went to school.
I thought a bit about a project.
Then I ran into you.
Then,
I went to a cafe with Hyoseok.
And then Eunho texted me.
Hyoseok?
Yeah.
He's in Photography too.
Are you two close?
Closest in the faculty, I think.
More than me?
What?
Closer to him than me?
How do you compare something like that?
Since you can't answer,
I guess I'm not the closest to you.
I have to work harder.
No, that's not what I meant.
Other than friends,
is there anyone you like?
I've never thought about dating.
You sound so innocent.
I should get going.
I shouldn't bother you when you're sick.
Just leaving like that
after you woke me up?
Why don't you just sleep over?
What? W-Why should I?
Remember to eat
and have your medicine.
Get well soon.
Bye.
What was I doing?
[Kwon Jeongwu]
Did you take your medicine?
Are you feeling better?
[Kwon Jeongwu]
Are you asleep?
[Answer] [Reject]
What's up?
Just wanted to hear your voice.
This is the first time
you texted me first.
Do you have class tomorrow?
When are you going to school?
Classes?
Hmm...
I have class in the first period
at nine.
Then...
Meet me outside your place at 8:30.
Let's go together.
No, it's okay.
I can take the bus.
A direct bus.
I can drive you there directly too.
See you tomorrow morning.
Okay.
Morning.
Are you feeling better?
What do you think?
But...
you said you won't hide anymore.
Did I?
I mean your cap.
Do you always wear a cap?
Can't you not wear it?
Why?
I'm taller than you.
When I stand upright,
I can't see your face.
Ah...
People bother you a lot, don't they?
Yeah.
A bit.
If you run into someone like
that annoying senior again,
just tell me.
You're so sweet.
I'm only like this to you.
We'll be late. Let's go.
Thanks for driving me to school.
Um...
What are your plans after class?
Hmm...
For a photography project,
I need to research locations.
Locations?
Do you also go location scouting?
Don't you need someone driving you?
No, not really.
I just need a gymnasium.
So like a sports hall?
Yeah, but...
I can do it myself—
See you tomorrow.
Where did Jeongwu go again?
I'm sure he got a new girlfriend.
What?
You're assuming things again.
He hasn't been picking up his phone
and disappears right after practice.
Are you jealous of him?
What the hell?
-Hey!
-Hmm?
Don't move.
Thank you.
Hey.
You're so inexperienced.
What do you know?
What do you mean?
Don't act like you're so experienced.
Whatever.
Forget about Jeongwu.
You still have me, your bestie.
What bestie?
There's only cutthroat
competition between us!
Wow, that was so cringey.
If your idol Jiwon finds out
how childish you are,
he'll distance himself from you.
No.
Jiwon won't shun me for that.
He and I
have a special bond.
Really?
How about a game today?
I'll teach you a lesson
and crush your soul.
You're dead. Come on.
Curly Hair! Wait for me!
Don't call me that!
Seriously.
Hey.
Curly Hair?
It's a fact.
I mean the cap.
Can't you not wear it?
When I stand upright,
I can't see your face.
You're here.
No cap today.
Yeah. What are you doing?
The location fee.
What?
I rented the hall for today
by offering to clean it.
By the way,
can I ask you something?
What is it?
Your jersey number.
Why number 17?
Is there a special meaning?
No, not really.
Just the number of strokes in my name.
Wow, I didn't expect that.
Did you come up with it?
An ex came up with it for me.
Oh...
How many strokes are there in your name?
Eighteen.
Right after mine.
Yeah.
Actually,
I don't even remember who that ex is.
I'm saying,
she is insignificant to me.
Remembering everyone in my past
is just a waste of time.
Don't you think?
You're so cold.
I don't know how to do that.
If you break up, it's over.
It's upsetting to dwell on it.
I see.
Thanks to you, I'm all done already.
Shouldn't you take your photos?
The sun is setting soon.
I need to take a shower.
Take your time.
Okay.
Thank you.
Are you done?
Almost.
Yeah?
Why a gymnasium though?
Ah.
The theme is something that represents me.
Is this it?
What's with the basketball?
There's no one here.
So that's why.
So does the ball represent me?
Maybe.
You used to practice gymnastics every day.
Don't you feel restless?
A little.
That's why I jog every morning.
Let's play.
The loser buys dinner.
How can I beat a basketball player?
If you get one point
within the time limit,
you win.
Don't underestimate me.
Come on then.
Woah.
You've got some skills.
Don't let your guard down.
You might lose.
You think?
I just need to score one point.
Sure.
Good luck.
See?
I told you not to underestimate me.
It's your treat tonight.
I've never seen you smile like that.
You're truly a gold medalist.
So competitive.
Let's go.
Han Jiwon.
Still not interested in dating?
W-Wait...
Why did you suddenly...
It's not sudden.
You know it.
I like you.
[In the next episode]
I'll try my best to win your heart.
One month.
One month?
I'm gay.
I like men.
Why are you here?
Want to watch a movie?
Want to kiss?
What?
Finally, anything to say
to Gymnast Han Jiwon?
Only two days left.
[Ballboy Tactics]