(Sakuma)
I'll be taking charge of this class
in place of Suzugi-sensei.
I'm Sakuma Takayuki.
Please welcome me well.
Excuse me.
Yes?
There's something on your back.
I see.
Yesterday, my niece came to visit me.
She draws well, doesn't she?
All right then. Let's check the attendance.
(Students List, Sixth Grade Class C)
(Sakuma)
I think I mistook
a TV remote controller for my phone.
Still as goofy as ever.
(Minato Shouji Coin Laundry)
Minato Shouji Coin Laundry,
the laundromat loved by the locals.
(Closed for three days due to personal reasons.
Minato Akira, Owner and Operator)
Currently...
Minato Akira, the owner...
is on a three-day-two-night trip
to heal his heart.
Hello.
It's been a long time, Akira-kun.
At the time,
upon seeing the face of Sakuma-sensei.
Uh, I...
My stomach hurts as well as my head.
Excuse me.
Minato-san.
I ran off just like that.
I'm such a loser.
Minato-san, are you alright?
Aren't you feeling well?
Are you at home now?
Minato-san, where are you?
I wish to talk to you.
Do I...
still like him?
Isn't time supposed to make it any better?
"Minato's Laundromat"
Sakuma-sensei.
What is it?
You're Shintaro-kun.
May I ask...
what you think of Minato-san?
Minato...
You mean Akira-kun?
- What do I think of him?
- I mean...
Shin.
That's too rude of you.
I'm sorry, Takayuki-san.
Let's go.
Tell me.
What's between Akira-san and Takayuki-san?
It has nothing to do with you.
Come on, just tell me.
These two hang out together a lot lately.
Yes.
(Minato Shouji Coin Laundry)
Why have you been taking so many breaks recently?
What happened?
It's nothing.
Have you...
done it with Shin?
Ouch!
Gosh.
What nonsense are you talking about?
I already told you.
Shin and I aren't dating.
So Shin's love is still unrequited.
Hey, Akira-san.
Don't you like younger guys?
Do you find us too unreliable?
Or don't you trust us?
What about me?
What do you think of me?
What's with you?
Are you trying to copy Shin?
Or are you looking for some advice on love?
Listen.
You can be quite frivolous
but you're a good guy.
If you sincerely confess your love,
that person will understand your feelings.
Minato-san.
What are you doing alone with Hanabusa?
Having an affair?
Are you crazy? Stop it.
He was just seeking some advice on love.
Right, Asuka?
Well, if you say so.
See you later, Akira-san.
Bye.
What's with you?
Are you mad at me?
Yes, I'm mad.
You didn't reply to my texts again.
And you weren't at the laundromat.
I'm sorry.
Can you not make such a scary face?
I just went on a trip for a change of mood.
A trip?
It's good to take a break
once in a while, right?
I have a souvenir for you too.
Here.
(Bean Sprout)
So? It's cute, isn't it?
Thank you.
Come on.
So even that can't cheer you up?
Well, it can't be helped then.
Alright.
I'll treat you
to a watermelon shake the next time.
Watermelon shake?
That's right.
Back in high school, I always had it
on the way back from the club.
It's good, you know.
Let's have it together next time.
Together?
Yes, together.
Yes. Definitely a yes.
I'll hold you to that, Minato-san.
Sure.
I promise.
So it's a date.
No, it's not.
Minato-san.
About Sakuma-sensei...
No matter who it is you like,
I still like you.
Besides,
whoever that person is...
I won't be giving up.
I'm glad I got to meet you today.
I'll be off now.
Even though...
he's so straightforward,
But...
nothing has changed for me at all.
Damn it.
How much longer am I going to hesitate?
It's time I have to...
(Sakuma Store)
Finally...
I'm here.
Hello.
Could this be...
Sensei's nephew?
Shuu-kun, right?
You startled me.
I heard you went abroad for a while.
Are you already back?
Want cigarettes?
Uh...
I quit smoking.
Sakuma-sensei...
No, I mean...
Where's Takayuki-sensei?
Takayuki lives by himself now.
All right.
Thank you.
(Takayuki)
If I'm to visit him at his personal residence,
it seems a bit...
By the way...
what am I to say when I meet him?
(Katsuki)
You know the new teacher
at the tutorial school is so cool.
He's so quiet and aloof
that you can't tell what he's thinking.
But he is even cooler that way.
Hey, Shin.
Sorry, what?
By the way,
aren't you making too many of it?
Shin.
You were supposed to return home by now.
I've brought you some fried mackerel
to thank you for the gift.
You didn't have to.
Anyway,
thanks.
Should we eat it together?
(Bean Sprout)
Where have you been today?
Are you all right?
Yes.
You dropped something.
Hey, that's...
Takayuki...
This is...
Sakuma-sensei's address.
Well...
actually...
I was thinking of meeting Sakuma-sensei.
So I went to his shop.
But I didn't find him there.
It turns out he lives by himself now.
Are you going to meet him?
Well...
Just go.
It's all right.
If something were to ever happen to you,
I'll come and find you immediately.
You're always exaggerating it.
All right.
It's not because you told me to.
But I need to settle things once and for all.
I'm going to meet him.
Thank you.
Even when I said it like that...
but when I finally arrived at his place,
I felt so nervous that my stomach started hurting.
I'm sorry, Shin. I don't feel good at all.
I should back off for today.
Akira-kun.
Please, have a drink.
I'm sorry for coming over so suddenly.
No problem. I'm glad you came.
Are you all right?
I'm all right.
Just a little choke.
Sensei.
You haven't changed one bit.
Oh, right.
I have something to show you too.
If I'm not mistaken,
it should be somewhere here.
Oh, I found it.
Here.
While you were still in tenth grade,
and I was just hired to teach
at Keyaki High School.
No.
I was so young back then...
It suited you though.
Even if it was against the school rules.
I, at the time,...
was still young...
I was still a teenager.
Hey, Yamaguchi from class A is so cute.
I know. She's super cute.
Don't you think so, Akira?
Yes.
Right? She's the cutest ever.
I was good for nothing.
I was reckless.
Hello, Akira-kun.
Do you remember me?
I'm Sakuma Takayuki from Sakuma Store.
Sakuma Store?
When you were little,
I was often asked to babysit you.
We played together all the time.
I don't remember such a thing.
Hey.
Are you all right?
Yes, but barely.
Akira-kun.
Yes?
(Club Application)
Would you like to join the swimming club?
Sakuma-sensei...
helped pull me up to the light.
Sensei.
Well...
I...
What should I do?
What's the matter?
Shin. You're here.
Have you met Sakuma-sensei?
Yes, I met him.
Have you talked?
About that...
Sensei.
Well...
I...
like...
I like...
Hmm?
I...
You like?
Uh, well...
I like...
You like? I see.
You like watermelon.
No, it's not that.
- Like...
You like...
This is hard.
- I like...
- You like...
I know.
Swimming club.
Actually, I'd like to ask you
about that as well.
Akira-kun.
Would you like to join the swimming club?
What?
As the swimming club coach?
Yes.
Did you say yes?
I thought you were to going to
settle things with him.
It seems like an important period
as the tournament is near.
He insisted that I should help him.
It can't be helped.
So you're happy that he asked you for help.
Let alone settling things with him.
You came back
without telling him how you feel.
Am I right?
It can't be helped.
But my past and being a coach
are two different things.
What about sensei?
Shut up already.
I can't understand myself either.
When you're an adult,
there are things you can't decide
whether it's black or white.
Oh, right.
I'm washing my bed sheet.
It smells so good.
Here, you can try sniffing it.
It smells so nice.
You really can't stay still.
Are you really an adult?
Sorry.
No, no, no.
Not like this.
You can't do this.
You're right.
It smells so nice.
Hey.
Stay still.
I'm just sniffing the linen.
What?
Don't sniff it like this.
You rascal.
Stop it.
I'm just feeling the sheet.
Please.
Please stop.
No, don't go further.
What's with that scream?
Thanks to you, now I have to wash it again.
Shin, you silly punk.
You crazy, handsome punk.
I'm sorry, Minato-san.
Can I borrow it?
Come on.
I'll be waiting.
Make sure you settle things with him.
I know.
Even the toughest of bedsheets,
can be taken care of, over at
Minato's Laundromat.
Yaho.
(Sakuma Store)
So you're back.
Asuka.
Being wrapped in gentle and soft touch...
Katsuki.
I need to talk to you about something.
Is definitely a bright morning welcome.
Welcome.
It's been a while, Akira-kun.
Saki.
Please continue to support us next week.
(Next Episode)
Can you give me some advice?
(New love rival)
What are you doing?
What is it you want to talk about?
(The meeting of the past and future)
I see, you still can't figure
what's on one's mind.
I hope I get to see Shuu-sensei tomorrow.
What's the reason
you don't want to leave your hometown?
(This drama is fictional)
Please tell me the truth.