Who said it was hard for me?
Look.
Does it look like it?
No.
It's not just similar.
This is exactly it.
This is even more refined than a noble lady.
Elegant and magnificent.
As beautiful as a fairy.
It's like a fairy descended to earth.
I think just relying on clothes isn't enough.
I still need to learn how to act like a noble lady.
I think
those young ladies on the stage
are all
like this.
Linlang,
don't make things hard for yourself.
Just be yourself, that's good enough.
What did you say?
Don't move.
That's the feeling.
What feeling? Pain?
Exactly like Miss Hua.
It looks like it.
That's the spirit.
Miss Hua.
This Miss Hua
Although she was stunningly beautiful,
she was also exceptionally tough.
She once married the newly appointed top scholar.
Because of conflicts with her in-laws,
she forced her husband to write a divorce letter.
She inherited the Hua family estate herself.
In a few years, she became the richest person in Shanxi.
So,
she could be considered a heroine among women.
Isn't that just like you,
except you don't look the same?
That old Taoist has seen you all.
Put this on.
Not just him,
even you yourselves
won't be able to recognize yourselves.
Human skin mask.
Miss Hua comes from a merchant family.
How did she get involved with the underworld?
Miss Hua's godmother
is the head of the One Flower Five Leaves Hall in Jiangnan.
She has always had dealings with these human traffickers.
And this Miss Hua
doesn't run her business as honestly as her father did.
As long as it's profitable,
she dares to get involved.
So this time,
it's not an ordinary deal.
It's about drugged people.
Drugged people.
Master Taoist.
Miss Hua sent word that she'll be here soon.
Hmm.
This Miss Hua
is our major employer.
And yet someone sneaks in at this time.
We have to be on guard.
Pass down the order.
Everyone needs to keep their eyes wide open today.
Go.
Yes.
Master Taoist, Miss Hua has arrived.
Miss Hua is here.
Forgive me for not greeting you sooner.
I'm not here to exchange pleasantries.
Where is what I want?
Please rest inside for a moment.
I'll make the arrangements right away.
Please.
Our rural area here
certainly doesn't have
tea that would catch Miss Hua's eye.
Am I here to drink tea?
This matter of the drugged person
is of great importance.
I still have something to ask Miss Hua.
What is it?
Last time, thanks to Madam Liu's righteous help,
she used five moves of Black Sand Palm
to kill my enemy
and saved my life.
I wonder if Miss Hua at that time
happened to see it.
That would be an unforgettable memory.
It seems my godmother, Madam Liu,
since she retired from the martial world,
has been forgotten by everyone.
Her reputation in the martial world
is no longer worth much.
I should go back and advise her
not to show herself in public anymore
so she doesn't bring trouble upon herself.
This person's hands are clean and delicate.
How could they possibly be a slave?
Someone, come!
Miss Hua's godmother
is the head of the Wuye Hall in Jiangnan.
She has always had dealings with these human traffickers.
And this Miss Hua
does not run her business as honestly as her father did.
As long as it's a profitable business,
she dares to get involved.
So this time,
it's not an ordinary deal.
It's about drugged people.
Why are you helping me?
I'm not helping you.
I'm helping myself.
Tomorrow, pretend to be Miss Hua.
The woman who is trading with you—
I want her to disappear from this world.
Miss, it's obvious you're well-trained.
For something as simple as killing,
do you really need someone else to do it?
Could it be that you,
are afraid of being seen?
My affairs
are none of your concern.
If you succeed in this matter,
Tianluo will not treat you unfairly.
Tianluo?
Thank you, Master.
For helping me see this person's true nature.
Fei Ying.
So,
Master, you have other guests here.
Miss Hua's Black Sand Palm
has truly inherited Madam Liu's skills.
I am truly amazed.
But as for this young lady,
I do not know her.
I want you to make him pay with his life.
Stop!
Are you alright?
Fortunately, Miss Hua was wise enough
to know that someone
didn't want this deal to go through.
That's why she had me prepare in advance.
Could it be
that Master still doubts my identity?
Actually, who I am doesn't matter.
The business of drugged people is extremely profitable.
Everyone wants to get involved.
Not just you,
even King Tianluo
wants to monopolize this trade.
and keep it all to himself.
Why would Tianluo care about this?
Several years ago,
Tianluo had already acquired a large number of drugged people.
to search for treasures for him.
These living dead
are naturally the best candidates to enter tombs.
Treasure hunting in tombs?
Are you talking about seven years ago?
Master.
This person knows nothing about the drugged people.
Yet he dares to pretend to be one of Tianluo's men.
I hope Master will think twice.
This young woman who calls herself Tianluo
Her identity is indeed suspicious
But Miss Hua's Black Sand Palm
can't be faked
Since that's the case
There's no point in keeping you here
Fei Ying
You actually fought me because of her
I told you
No one is allowed to touch her
Today, I insist on touching her
Lu Jiu
Geng Zhao from the Diancha Division led people in and broke through
The young lady acted on her own without permission
If you don't want Tianluo and the Diancha Division to clash directly
Please withdraw immediately
Just the few of you
think you can catch me?
I’ll make all of you die with me.
Sir, are you alright?
If you want us to die with you, you have to die first.
You—
What you said is true.
My younger brother is already dead.
My condolences.
If he were still alive,
he would surely want you to live freely.
Take your household registration papers.
Leave this place.
Before you go,
I have one more thing to do.
Didn’t you say
you wanted me to help you?
Tomorrow, I’ll help you.
I’ll put on a good show.
Sister, I knew you would come to save me.
Go.
In a moment, take that road.
You’ll be able to get out.
What about you?
I still have things to do, you go first.
Where are you going?
Don’t you want me anymore?
It’s not that I don’t want you.
There are others here just like you.
I need to save them too.
Be good.
Don’t leave me behind.
No.
Be good.
Listen to me.
Sister.
Linlang
Young Master
You finally woke up.
Old Yan
That look on your face
really makes me lose face.
But you’ve finally regained consciousness.
I lost consciousness?
Why can’t I remember anything?
I can’t remember anything at all.
But you still remember the person you want to see.
You were right about that.
I developed feelings I shouldn’t have.
This time, my foster father sent you to rescue me.
I’m afraid it’s my last chance.
No.
The ones who saved you this time
were Xu Linlang and Lu Jiu.
What?
Your identity has already been discovered by the Diancha Division.
Even the news of your disappearance
was passed on by Geng Zhao
directly to the Sect Leader.
The Sect Leader did it for the sake of everyone in Tang Sect.
He had no other choice.
It’s understandable.
What about them?
Them?
Something happened to Linlang.
No, no, not her.
It’s Lu Jiu.
What happened to him?
You're awake.
That's such a relief.
How is he doing now?
I've already treated his wounds.
But his condition
is not very good.
Who poisoned him so severely?
She was targeting me.
Lu Jiu did it all to save me.
In the end,
it's still because of me.
If it weren't for saving me,
he wouldn't be in this situation.
Don't say that.
Your medical skills are better than mine.
Please check on him quickly.
This poison is very tricky.
If we can't get the antidote from the person who poisoned him,
I'm afraid we can only use ginseng soup to keep him going.
And then try to find another solution.
I've already tried.
But I just can't get him to swallow it.
His pulse is very weak now.
If he doesn't get the ginseng soup soon,
I'm afraid he won't last much longer.
He drank it.
He’s dead.
He still has a breath left, but
I’m afraid
he only has a few days left.
All these years,
I’ve traveled far and wide.
I’ve also collected some secret medicines.
He’s just like me.
After all, we’re both your sons.
We can’t just stand by and watch.
Fool.
I don’t want him to die.
Because he hasn’t revealed the clue to the treasure yet.
But
if we offer the medicine now,
I’m afraid it will expose Father’s plan.
No rush.
This was caused by the daughter of that old Dugu.
For the sake of the Wuxiang treasure,
I’m sure he won’t just stand by and do nothing.
Father, you are wise.
This...
He’s already taken two of my pills.
There’s no effect at all.
What a waste... Shut up!
His poison
not only hasn’t lessened,
it’s actually getting worse.
It’s as if it already knew
how I would try to counter it.
Then what should we do?
Only the one who tied the bell can untie it.
She probably hates me now.
Even if I want to see her,
she doesn’t want to see me.
Then I’ll prescribe him some medicine.
Linlang.
You’ve watched over him all day.
He hasn’t had a drop of water.
Go get some rest.
The rest
leave to me and Lao Yan.
As long as he doesn't wake up,
I won't leave.
But you...
It's all my fault.
If it weren't for me,
you wouldn't have acted impulsively.
If I were a bit stronger,
I could have cured your poison.
Lu Jiu,
please wake up.
Can you please wake up?
Who?
I know you're here.
I also know
Lu Jiu is the most important to you.
Otherwise, you wouldn't have risked yourself to save him.
Lu Jiu is deeply poisoned now.
Please, save him.
Otherwise, he'll die.
What do you need to save him?
As long as you're willing to save him,
I'm willing to leave him.
I'll never appear by his side again.
Do you think I would trade his life
for your departure?
What do you need to save him?
Just say it,
I'm willing to do anything.
Say something.
What will it take for you to save him?
Do you think I don't want to save him?
There's no cure for this poison.
I don't believe it.
How can there be a poison with no cure?
Please, save him.
At least you can still be by his side.
But I
don't even have that right.
Linlang
Why are you soaking wet?
I'll go boil some hot water for you.
No need.
I just want to be alone with Lu Jiu for a while.
I heard your poison can't be cured.
Surprised?
Unexpected?
They say you become red when close to cinnabar,
and black when close to ink.
After spending so much time with you,
I've become unruly myself.
Forget it.
Since you're poisoned,
I won't hold it against you.
Do you still remember
the last time
you thought you were poisoned?
Sima Kong's hawthorn pill
tricked you.
This time,
whose poison did you fall for?
Who fooled you now?
I owe you so much.
How should I repay you?
How about
I give myself to you?
Let me tell you a secret.
I've liked you for a long time.
So long that I don't even know
when it started.
Maybe
it was when you risked your life for mine with Jia Changyi.
You traded your life for mine.
Or maybe
when you rushed in to save me from Li Mu.
Or perhaps
it was the first time I saw you.
You were already in my heart.
Lu Jiu,
please wake up.
Wake up.
I haven't heard your answer yet.
Please wake up.
Young Master
Where are you going?
Tang Sect
He was poisoned by the special toxin Master made for Tianluo years ago.
An incurable poison.
Master is a cautious person.
He must have left a backup plan.
This concerns the Tang Sect's loyalty to Tianluo.
Do you think the Sect Leader would, for the sake of
someone completely unrelated,
abandon the Tang Sect?
He is not unrelated.
He is my friend.
Just because he's your friend?
He is also the one my beloved cares for.
The person in her heart isn't you.
Why are you doing this?
I don't expect her to care for me.
Everything I do
is just to keep her from being sad.
Do you realize
there's no turning back from this?
If you have no companions,
even if the road ahead is smooth,
what does it matter?
Young Master
I finally caught up with you.
You...
Master
Sect Leader
You still remember me as your master.
When Master heard I was kidnapped by villains,
he didn't send anyone to rescue me, did he?
How dare you!
The Tang Sect has always put personal interests last.
Master did nothing wrong.
I broke the rules.
I accept the punishment myself.
Young Master
At least you still remember the rules.
Come back with me.
You are still the young master of Tang Sect.
The position of young master means nothing to me.
I hope, for the sake of our years as master and disciple,
you will give me the antidote to the incurable poison.
If I give you the antidote now,
wouldn't that be telling Tianluo
that Tang Sect is disloyal?
Sima Kong.
I have painstakingly trained you all these years,
yet you care nothing for the fate of Tang Sect.
If Tianluo investigates,
I will take all the responsibility myself.
Can you really bear it?
I came to Mist Town this time
on the orders of Tianluo's leader,
Dugu.
I'm afraid
he already knows I have the antidote.
He's just waiting to see what I do.
Then it's simple.
As long as I'm not a disciple of Tang Sect,
I can resolve Tang Sect's crisis.
You—
What are you trying to do?
While the young master was kidnapped,
he was forced to take a mind-altering drug.
He still hasn't recovered.
No.
Every word I say
comes from the bottom of my heart.
Master, for over ten years you raised me with kindness.
I, Sima Kong, will never forget it.
Now, I return all the martial arts of Tang Sect
back to you.
From this moment on,
with Tang Sect,
I will have nothing more to do.
Don't!
Young Sect Leader!
You...
You actually crippled your own martial arts for their sake?
The bond between us as master and disciple for over ten years
is it really not as strong as the few days you spent with them?
There's one more thing I forgot to report to you.
When I was imprisoned this time,
I saw, from my childhood,
the drugged puppets you used to train me.
Actually... actually, in your eyes,
I am no different from those walking corpses,
those drugged puppets you control.
There's really no difference, is there?
We're all just tools of the Tang Sect.
Since that's how you see it,
then I, your disciple, am of no more use to you.
From now on,
the relationship between us as master and disciple
is completely severed.
Sir
You can't do this.
Lu Jiu was helping our Diancha Division save people.
That's how he got injured.
We can't just stand by and watch him die.
But using your vital energy to keep Lu Jiu alive
is basically trading your life for his.
I don't want anything to happen to you.
It's not that serious.
It's just
using up some vital energy.
If it's only a small amount of energy,
then it's fine.
But judging by Lu Jiu's current injuries,
it will definitely drain almost all of your energy.
At that point,
you might not be able to save Lu Jiu,
and you might not survive yourself.
I don't want you to go.
As Geng Zhao,
I only act out of righteousness.
If you don't understand,
then from now on,
don't follow me anymore.
Sir