I am Lu Jiu.
Are you having a fever again?
Didn't you promise not to do anything to her?
I...
Even Lian Bu Ci...
Can't even handle two kids.
What a useless person.
Don't say that.
With this fever,
your martial arts have actually improved a lot.
Weren't you the one who said it?
You have to learn to control your body, don't let him control you.
All of you, be careful.
Behind us.
Linlang.
Let her go.
The person you're looking for is me.
She's worth more than you.
I'm really curious.
This little girl,
why is she worth such a high bounty?
Wait.
If there are more assassins behind us,
Linlang is injured now.
I can't protect her completely anymore.
Who needs your protection?
Didn't you see just now?
I'm so strong.
This isn't the time to be stubborn.
From now on,
I won't allow you to leave my side, not even half a step.
Pass down the order.
When pursuing Xu Linlang,
do not harm her life.
You're actually doing this for Xu Linlang.
You want to use people from the Diancha Division.
She hasn't even agreed to be our informant yet.
Li Chu, on the Assassin Alliance's hit list,
Fei Ying,
are all connected to the Fengleitang case from twenty years ago.
Xu Linlang is inexplicably involved in this.
There must be a connection.
Excuses.
I think you have ulterior motives.
You always only take on cases assigned by the court.
But in Luoyang County,
you took on Xu Linlang's case file.
And now you're going easy on her.
I think
I...
I think you clearly have a thing for her.
I just think
she's good material for investigations.
I want to recruit her into the Diancha Division.
Although the Diancha Division accepts talent regardless of gender,
all these years,
very few women have been able to join.
Still won't admit you like her?
You're being unreasonable.
Don't think I don't know.
From my very first day in the Diancha Division,
you've never liked me.
You're always looking for excuses to send me back to the capital.
I just won't do as you wish.
Now I'll give the order to protect Xu Linlang.
So you can't find a single fault with it.
Cold.
Lu Jiu.
How are you?
Cold.
Sima Kong went to get some medicine.
He hasn't come back yet.
Young Master.
Let me go in and check the situation.
Have you found out who was after Linlang?
We finally found out.
The one behind this secret plot
is actually the eldest son of the Lu family, who has been missing for a long time.
Lu Mingcheng.
Father, please calm your anger.
You've grown up and become bold.
You dared to order the Assassin Alliance to kill your own brother.
Father, I am innocent.
I specifically told them
not to harm Xiao Jiu's life.
Just bring him back, that's all.
I went to find the Assassin Alliance
only because I was worried our people
might expose your whereabouts, Father.
If you truly cared about your brother,
why did you leave him in Luoyang County in the first place?
I received news
saying that
Geng Zhao from the Investigation Bureau secretly entered Luoyang County
to investigate our Lu family.
I was afraid
it would reveal Father's true identity.
That's why I came up with a plan to escape at the last minute.
Xiao Jiu being captured
was truly an accident.
So it's both a misunderstanding and an accident?
I've raised him for seven years.
And almost lost everything because of you.
Tang Sect
Before I faked my death, the Tang Sect
had already taken action.
This Tianluo
Tianluo is also a major client of the Tang Sect.
It's very likely
that this old villain Dugu is scheming behind the scenes.
Then
he conveniently shifted the blame onto Father.
Dugu
and that Xu Linlang
Dugu clearly knows
her father was a former member of Fenglei Hall.
Yet he still appointed her
to stay by Xiao Jiu's side.
I'm afraid
they have ulterior motives.
That's why I ordered someone to kill her.
You and I are father and son.
If we are united,
we can seize the Wuxiang treasure together.
Yes, yes.
Fortunately, the fever has gone down.
Come in.
Lu Jiu wasn't feeling well all night.
He kept tossing and turning.
So,
yesterday,
you stayed by the bedside the whole time.
Thank you for your hard work.
Oh, you mean that?
It wasn't hard for me.
By the way,
didn't you say you were going to get medicine for Lu Jiu last night?
Why didn't you come back?
Did you really want me to come back?
Of course I wanted you to come back.
After all, you went to get medicine for Lu Jiu.
Lu Jiu's fever is gone,
but why hasn't he woken up yet?
I haven't been paid yet.
I won't let him die so easily.
Sima Kong.
Are you crazy?
Wrong.
You're the crazy one.
Lu Jiu, you're finally awake!
I...
Did I get a fever again?
I didn't faint this time.
Why
do I still get a fever?
No matter the reason,
anyway,
Linlang stayed by your side all night.
As long as you can recover,
nothing else matters.
But,
we...
how did we end up at the inn?
If we rashly come to the inn,
then the Assassin Alliance
would easily find us, wouldn't they?
That's what I said too.
But Linlang insisted for the sake of your health.
She was determined to do it this way.
It's fine.
Someone will protect us.
Near the inn,
I found signs that the authorities are watching us.
They're just watching us from a distance.
They don't seem to want to arrest us.
They even seem to want to protect us.
Protect us?
Yes.
It should be related to this.
What is this?
A bounty notice from the Assassin Alliance.
Your bounty is now ranked third.
It's two hundred chiwen more
than the two of us.
How much has he actually recovered, Fei Ying?
In one person's mind,
there are memories of two people.
How could such a miraculous thing exist in this world?
Maybe he's just pretending.
Let me test you.
Sima Kong, what are you doing?
Looks like you're not pretending.
Pretending? What do you mean?
Your martial arts today
have improved a lot compared to yesterday.
It seems you're awakening deep memories in your body.
But back then, you were clearly
a useless person with no martial arts at all.
Sima Kong.
You can analyze all you want,
but stop calling people useless all the time.
Stop calling people useless all the time.
Sima Kong
Look at what you've done.
You just had to test my strength in the bathroom.
Linlang is a girl, after all.
You made her so embarrassed.
I tested you
for your own good.
As for Linlang,
I didn't expect things to turn out like that.
Easy for you to say.
Don't you want to know
who the other person inside you is?
Do you know who it is?
I don't know yet.
But one thing is certain:
You are still yourself right now.
You haven't been taken over by that person yet.
I'm just afraid
I'll completely become that person.
The authorities are investigating. Everyone, come out!
Linlang
Let's go.
Did someone just pass by?
I don't know, did you see anyone?
Let's go.
Lu Jiu
Get a hold of yourself.
Don't be like this.
Lu Jiu
Linlang
Are you okay?
Sima Kong
You almost killed me just now.
The inn was just undergoing a routine inspection.
You suddenly transformed and took Linlang away.
I followed you out of concern, but you...
You forgot about us again.
These days,
it's happening more and more often.
I feel like
I'm becoming someone else.
Someone else...
Did you remember something?
Ever since thirteen years ago,
when I fell into the river,
I haven't remembered anything.
When I woke up, they told me
my name is Lu Jiu.
The second young master of the Lu family.
But in my heart,
there's always a voice telling me
I'm not Lu Jiu.
Maybe
your memory was faulty from the very beginning.
Do you still remember
how you lost your memory?
Ever since I fell into the river
and had a fever,
I haven't remembered anything.
Fei Ying disappeared in Mist Town.
There's a river nearby.
According to what you said,
all your memories are what others told you.
Have you ever tried to confirm with other relatives or friends?
In my family,
there's only my elder brother and my father.
As for my mother,
my father said
he and my mother were only briefly together.
After I was born,
she abandoned me.
It was my father who went to great lengths
to find me and bring me back.
This Lu Kun is truly shameless.
He even made up
such a mask of loyalty and righteousness for himself.
Everyone knows he first abandoned his original wife,
tricked someone into marriage to gain status,
and later left the third master of Fenglei Hall
without a second thought.
He even abandoned his child.
I am my father's illegitimate child.
So,
I'm not close to him.
The last time I saw him
was when he
left me with my elder brother.
But I am still grateful to him.
If it weren't for him,
I would have died long ago.
You said you lost all your memories from seven years ago.
And suddenly, you possess unparalleled martial arts skills.
On this wanted poster,
there happens to be someone just like that.
Who is it?
Fei Ying.
The top assassin of Tianluo.
He excels at stealth and theft.
He kills without a trace.
He dominates the martial world with Tiger Claw Fist.
He vanished without a trace seven years ago.
He's about the same age as you.
Tiger Claw Fist?
There's a portrait of him on here.
Do you still want to see it?
Yes.
This child's features,
do look quite similar to mine.
If it weren't for this black mole,
there might really be a misunderstanding.
So if someone asks you in the future
whether you are Fei Ying,
you can confidently tell them
that you are not.
If you're not, then you're not.
Why are you taking it so seriously?
The young sect leader used Fei Ying's wanted notice
to test Lu Jiu.
That's right.
It's just a pity
that although Lu Jiu possesses the martial arts of Wuxiang City,
his childhood appearance
does not resemble Fei Ying.
So it's more likely that
all these years, Fei Ying
has been staying with the Lu family.
Lu Jiu's martial arts
were taught by him.
Do you doubt what I said?
No, not at all.
I just feel that
it's been quite a while since we left the Miasma Forest,
so why is the young sect leader only contacting me now?
Don't worry.
About borrowing your medicine,
I haven't forgotten.
I've followed you for so long,
how could I possibly fuss over a mere medicine?
How could I care about that?
Is that so?
I didn't realize you were so loyal to me.
I am deeply loyal to you.
But the one you should be loyal to is not me,
but Tang Sect.
Master chose you to help me accomplish great things
not only because of your outstanding skills,
but also because of your unwavering loyalty to Tang Sect.
You set aside personal gain and loss,
and put the interests of Tang Sect above all else.
That is the duty of a Tang Sect disciple.
The Sect Leader has high hopes for you.
Though he may be strict,
when he sees you
considering everything for the benefit of Tang Sect,
he will surely be gratified.
Since Lu Jiu isn't Fei Ying,
there's no need for you
to waste time on him.
Why not come back with me to report?
Although Lu Jiu isn't Fei Ying,
he is Li Chu's son.
Li Chu, under the alias Lu Kun, has been hiding for a long time.
He must have a plan.
Now, both he and Fei Ying
and Luming City
are all missing.
So Lu Jiu
is our only clue.
You are truly thoughtful.
I, Lao Yan, will take my leave.
Alright.
Lu Jiu
I can only help you this far.
Take a look at the lanterns.
Please have a look at the lanterns.
Little trinkets.
Come and have a look.
Miss, take a look at these little trinkets.
Here, have some candied hawthorn.
How is it?
It tastes good, doesn't it?
It's delicious.
Can you buy it for me again next time?
No problem.
I'll buy it for you every day from now on.
The past was beautiful.
But what if Lu Jiu gets sick again in the future
and forgets me again?
I'll give you this notebook.
Notebook.
You can write down whatever you want to remember
and all the most important things in it.
That way, you won't forget.
Linlang's hands are used for dissecting corpses.
I didn't expect her to be so skilled at making notebooks.
Could it be
made from human skin?
I've just been nice to you for two days and you're already asking for trouble, aren't you?
Lu Jiu
Where are you going?
Where did they go?
Where is that fragrance coming from?
Here, hold this.
Here you go.
Let me put it on you.
How is it? Looks nice, right?
Yeah.
I knew you'd like it.
Let's go.
Flowers for sale!
Sir, buy some flowers.
Buy them for your beloved.
I'm back.
You're back.
I went into the woods
and hunted some game.
We'll have an extra meal tonight.
You can't even tell a lie.
You suddenly went out just now
because you were afraid you'd hurt me when you transformed, right?
I...
I'm afraid I'll forget you.
It's not what you think.
Besides, every time you forget me,
it's only for a short while.
Once you regain your memory, you risk your life to save me.
That makes up for it, doesn't it?
But I feel
I'm about to be completely controlled by that person.
So
I'm giving you this notebook.
Write down the most important things you want to remember
in it.
That way, you won't forget.
Okay.
I will.
It's getting late.
I'll go make dinner now.
So you remember the most important thing.
Why are you drawing me?
Because
the thing I can't forget the most
is you.
Then can you give me this drawing?
Sure.
I'll definitely treat it as my most precious thing.
I'll keep it safe.
Um, Linlang, I...
There's something in my eye.
You don't have to tell me.
Really.
Who knows what dirty thing he saw.
Let me help him.
No, that's not it.
You can't insult yourself either.
I'm just trying to cooperate with you.
Let me do it.
Let me see what's in your eye.
That's really not necessary.
Let's be serious.
Seriously.
Every time you transform, you hurt Linlang.
We need to find a solution.
Are you sure
this is the method you mentioned?
That's right.
It's so uncomfortable for Lu Jiu to be tied up like this.
Besides,
with his strength when he transforms,
this rope can't possibly restrain him. Don't worry.
This is a special rope I made.
Not even ten oxen could break it.
I...
Sir,
sorry to bother you.
Please, go on with your business.
No, it's not that...
See? This was your terrible idea.
Do you have a better idea then?
Alright, alright.
Let's hurry up and eat.
Okay.
You've worked hard taking care of him these days.
You should really take care of yourself.
I...
Don't listen to him.
You look well-off,
but actually,
when he comes back,
he'll make you pay him back double.
Starting today,
you'll be in charge of all the money.
What do you mean by that?
Until you explain clearly,
I don't dare take it.
I'm not as shady as some people say.
I'm giving you the money
because I think it's more appropriate.
Um...
I'm hungry.
I want to eat chicken.
Sima Kong.
Add more money.
Alright, alright, let me feed you.
Wait.
You've worked so hard.
This is just a small thing.
Let me handle it.
Eat chicken.
Is this really how you feed someone?
No extra charge.
This is the only service available.
Alright, alright.
You two are still like children.
Let me feed you.
I don't know if hiding Lu Jiu's background from Master
was right or wrong.
But at this moment,
having friends like this by my side
is truly different from being alone in the past.
No need.
Let me do it.
No extra charge this time.
Did he really say that?
The young master always has his reasons.
Old Yan sent a message.
He said he didn't dare to speculate.
Old Yan
reported this to me in private.
I suppose
he's already figured it out.
Raising a child
is like making this mechanism.
Sometimes there are rough edges.
Just smooth them out.
As long as Kong'er completes this mission successfully,
he will still be our young master.
If you're really uncomfortable
I'll untie you
It's fine
With you by my side
It doesn't matter how I'm tied up
I feel safe
Then get some sleep
I'll be right there
Call me if you need anything
Okay
What is this place?
White Pagoda Temple.
Linlang
Shopkeeper, could you please take a look for me?
I need to get some medicine.
Miss, you're here for medicine again?
Your husband’s health isn’t very good, is it?
He’s always taking medicine.
He’s not my husband.
He’s just a friend.
Then he must be a very important friend to you.
You’re willing to use such expensive herbs for him.
I just made a new discovery about his illness last night.
I adjusted the prescription according to medical texts.
I didn’t know these herbs were so expensive.
Shopkeeper,
How much do these herbs cost?
Ten taels of silver.
Ten taels?
That’s so expensive!
Good thing Sima Kong gave me money.
Oh no.
My purse is missing.
Shopkeeper,
I didn’t bring enough money.
Could you let me buy on credit for now?
Once I get to Mist Town and find my family,
I’ll bring you the money then.
Mist Town is so far from here.
If I wait for you to pay me back,
Who knows how long that will take?
Miss, I run a small business.
I don’t give credit.
I hope you understand.
Doctors are supposed to be compassionate.
Can’t you make an exception just this once?
Stop trying to fool me.
You quack doctor.
My face is just a bit stiff.
I got two prescriptions from you and it didn’t help at all.
It actually got worse.
Please don’t get upset.
The medicine takes time to work.
I told you that when I gave you the medicine.
I have an important business deal coming up.
But now I look like this.
How am I supposed to do business like this?
Sir, please don’t get angry.
I know some medicine too.
Why don’t you let me see the prescription the shopkeeper gave you?
Let me take a look.
You, a young girl, know medicine?
Go ahead and take a look.
You’ve got nothing to lose anyway.
Alright.
You two don’t seem to be working together.
Here’s the prescription.
The prescription uses the right medicine.
The dosage is fine too.
Then why am I not getting better?
If you trust me,
I can try acupuncture for you.
Alright.
I’m a grown man.
I’m not afraid of a few needles.
Shopkeeper,
Can I borrow your acupuncture kit?
Alright.
Alright, alright, really.
It really is.
My face isn't stiff anymore.
Miss,
you're truly a miracle doctor.
These few acupuncture needles I used
were just for emergency treatment.
They'll only last for half a day.
But it's enough for you to meet with your boss.
For the rest of the treatment,
you need to follow the prescription the shopkeeper gave you
and take your medicine properly.
Make sure not to leave any lingering illness.
Alright, alright.
Miss,
you've really helped me a lot.
When my restaurant opens in the future,
you must come and visit.
I have to thank you properly.
Wait a moment, Miss.
You haven't taken the medicine you just picked up.
Didn't you say you don't allow credit?
Not allowing credit is indeed our shop's rule.
But the money for your medicine
comes from your consultation fee.
Really?
Doctors are compassionate by nature.
Thank you, shopkeeper.