Ae Jin!
Are you okay?
Did something happen?
Ae Jin!
It's okay.
(coooolguy777: Good morning, Genie)
(Shadow Beauty)
(Episode 2: Face In The Darkness)
Have a great day, everyone.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Who could it be?
Can someone recognize Genie by just looking at me?
He recognized me as Genie even before I posted anything,
and took a picture of me?
No way.
Or did he get lucky when he was trying to ridicule a suspicious-looking girl
with full makeup and a wig,
taking a selfie at a cafe?
This is so frustrating!
Not responding?
You're probably thinking of a way to get out of this.
Hey, loser!
What are you going to do about this?
I got a rash because of you!
Don't you have to go to the hospital?
What should I do?
How much does he know?
Hey!
Crap… how should I reply?
Don't try to be clever.
Just answer me.
Hey.
Are you ignoring me?
I just have something on my mind right now.
What is she saying?
What are you going to do about this?
You purposely gave me a fake, didn't you?
Then why don't you just buy one yourself?
What is wrong with you this morning?
Are you crazy?
Will a good beating wake you up, loser?
- You f**ker… - What's going on?
Come out to the field!
- It hurts! - Should I call an ambulance?
- Not an ambulance! - Then what?
Hey, hey.
What are you going to do about my wrist?
How are you going to make it up to me?
If I get a scar from this,
are you going to cut off your wrist for me? Are you?
Answer me.
Hey, answer her.
She keeps ignoring me.
Still not answering?
What are you doing during class?
Hey, what are you doing?
Why are you sweating so much?
Are you okay?
Who is it?
It must be someone here.
Koo Ae Jin.
What?
Why did she faint all of a sudden?
She's Yang Ha Neul's friend, right?
Koo Ae Jin! What's wrong with her?
It wasn't me!
Hurry up to the infirmary.
That doesn't suit her at all.
Why is he acting like Prince Charming?
Yeah, how goddamn absurd.
How do you feel?
Do you want to go to the hospital?
Should I write you a pass?
No.
It's because I have anemia.
I'll just leave after I lie down for a bit.
Okay.
Let me know if you don't feel better.
I will.
(People Who Chase Their Dreams For A Long Time Will Eventually Make It A Reality)
A ghost account.
Coooolguy?
A guy?
Or someone pretending to be a guy?
Dammit. What should I do?
"Please save me?"
"Please keep my secret?"
How did he know my name?
Koo Ae Jin.
You all right?
Do you feel better?
I carried you on my back.
I must've been really heavy.
Do you know how scared I was when you fainted like that?
Girl.
You got me worried.
I wanted to contact your parents.
But your phone was locked.
- What's the password? - It's fine. I'll do it.
Are you really all right?
If you feel better, let's meet up for lunch.
Get some rest.
I'm sorry.
No worries. Just get better.
(Grade 2 Teachers' Office)
I'm telling you. It really wasn't me!
Koo Ae Jin just fainted all of a sudden.
The other students are saying they saw it.
I heard you usually hit and take things from her.
I didn't take it from her.
She gave it to me as a gift.
- This is so unfair! - Ha Neul.
If you keep taking things from Ae Jin and hitting her…
I swear I didn't bully her!
- Why won't you believe me? - Yang Ha Neul!
You're in the wrong here. Why are you answering back to me?
We're getting nowhere.
Call your mom.
Excuse me?
I'm really sorry.
Please give me another chance.
Hey.
If this happens again, then we'll have to call your mom.
I understand.
Go apologize to Ae Jin.
Answer me.
I will.
What is that?
Where's your lunch box?
I'm just going to have some bread today.
Hey! What are you doing?
This is all you're eating after fainting like that in the morning?
Forget it.
- You can have this. - No, I'll just eat that…
As soon as I'm found out, what will you think of me?
You're a terrible person!
Hey!
Don't talk to me anymore!
Like that?
You're ugly enough as it is. And this is how you act?
I feel like throwing up.
I won't steal your food.
Eat slowly.
Even he can act like that.
If the other kids find out…
You think I'm joking around?
You think you can play with me, loser?
You ugly bitch!
Wait! From this face
to this face?
Mirror, mirror on the wall, who is the ugliest of them all?
- It's you! - It's you!
What's wrong?
Do you feel sick again?
I'm going back first.
Thanks for lunch.
So, now…
we'll have a discussion about ethnic wars.
The difference between man and beast is this, understand?
In other words, it's…
You loser. I apologized, okay?
F**k.
Human sacrifice is a prerequisite to everything.
That's why, I…
(Why are you sweating so much? Are you okay? Koo Ae Jin!)
Koo Ae Jin!
You had evening classes today?
Yeah.
For the time being, they'll be redoing the interior of our dance practice room.
So…
it's my day off.
But…
isn't your house in the opposite direction?
I wanted to walk you home.
And it's been a while since I've had a night stroll.
You sound like an old man who lives in the countryside.
How did you know?
All my teachers call me an old man.
You pay for something like this?
You're very strange.
There's a convenience store in front of our practice room.
During our overnight dance practice, everyone would have coffee.
I can't drink coffee or energy drinks because of my weak stomach.
That's how I became addicted to milk tea.
You'll soon realize the charms of milk tea.
- It's really good. - Right? I told you.
This is what I like about you.
- What do you mean? - "It's really good." That's it.
It sounds more genuine than expressive words.
I can believe whatever you say.
Strange, isn't it?
I lie very easily.
You?
Whatever!
It's true.
It's a full moon.
It's beautiful.
Right?
Because you're good-looking yourself,
the whole world must look beautiful.
I wish…
I was beautiful too.
Well.
It looks flat.
If you actually saw it in person,
it'd probably look ugly with all those big holes.
A half-moon or a crescent would probably look better.
But… you know what?
Half-moon or crescent, they're both the same.
It's just hidden in shadow.
A real thing is laid bare without anything hidden.
That's why I like the full moon.
It's the real thing.
Just like you.
That's not true.
I'm just… darkness.
The darkest of the dark.
Did you get drunk off milk tea?
It's late.
We should go.
Koo Ae Jin!
Wait for me!
Why did you leave this behind?
Came to refresh my eyes, but there's nothing new. So sad.
It's been a week since Genie posted a picture.
What's going on?
Why is her profile picture showing her back?
She's making us all feel worried.
I heard she was drafted into the military.
We'll have to wait for 100 days.
Who is she to keep defending her?
He'll go nuts if I post a new picture.
(lambsky: Are the anxiety attacks coming back? Did you take your meds?)
Yes.
(The comments are crazy! I'm like your manager.)
Thanks.
(Then get better soon)
Why are you late on the post? We can't even reach you.
Genie, please check our package.
If you don't post within the promised time,
you'll have to pay the fine for breach of contract.
What should I do?
First comment!
Unni, I missed you!
What a goddess!
Just take my money!
Seriously, she's dazzling!
Hey, loser!
Do you know where this bag is from?
Hey!
Are you ignoring me again?
Why, this loser…
She's ignoring us again!
Hey.
Koo Ae Jin, do you have a death wish?
She really must be crazy.
Hey!
I'm talking to you, you bitch.
Give that back!
(coooolguy777: You posted another picture.)
Wow! You really must be crazy!
Ignoring me? You better respond.
Answer me. Answer me.
Answer. Answer.
Answer.
- Just leave her alone! - Answer.
Let her be.
Answer. Answer.
What is she, a zombie?
- Answer. - Look at my arm!
Answer.
She left a mark!
I'm so mad!
Answer.
- How dare she? - Answer.
Don't do that again.
What are you looking at?
What do you want from me?
Finally, an answer. We should meet first.
At the lounge after school.
(Lounge)
It was you?
Did I startle you?
How did you know I was here?
I was waiting for you at the school gates.
But you never came out.
I looked for you everywhere.
By the way, what are you doing here?
I have to send him away.
Or even Jin Sung will find out.
What? What's going on?
My mom said she'd pick me up.
Go on.
- Then I'll wait with you. - No, just go.
I have lots to think about.
Fine, fine, I'll leave.
Why is he still there?
Could it be Jin Sung?
When are you coming?
I'm in the lounge by myself.
When do you think I'll be there?
Curious, aren't you?
(Shadow Beauty)
What do you want from me?
What are you expecting?
I'll give you a mission.
Tomorrow, put on the hot pink tint you used two weeks ago.
Daebak!
Friend!
Even if you put lipstick on a pig, it's still a pig!
Is he making fun of me?
Is he playing with me?
Jin Sung!
Tell me it isn't you!