I'm going for lunch.
You guys should too.
- Thank you!- Thank you.
Thank you.
(JIN-SUNG)
(JIN-SUNG)Is something going on?
You're coming to the rooftop today, right?
I'm going to checkyour homework next class.
- Thank you.- Thank you.
I don't see the point of homework.
(GRADE 2, CLASS 3)
Hey.
Can you call over Goo Ae-jin for me?
Hey, orc!
Your prince is here.
Didn't you hear? Your prince is here.
Hey. Are you playing hard to get?
You're one amazing orc!
Daebak.
You of all people…
I hoped you of all peoplewould be different from others.
Do you want to do…
something naughty?
Simply because Genie's pretty,
she was the targetof sexual harassment on the Internet.
(I'M A 30 YEAR OLD MALE LIVING IN SEOUL)At first, it's a light greeting.
(YOU CAN EARN TEN MILLION WON PER HOUR)Then, they'd send me sponsorship offers.
And if I ignore both,
they'd send me photos of their naked body
with words that left me speechless.
I wanted to think Jin-sungwas no different from those perverts.
I blurted those words outin hopes I might be able
to pour my heart out all at once.
But I shouldn't have done that.
What? What do you mean by naughty?
Send me a video.
I shouldn't have done something I wouldn't be able to handle.
Oh…
Hold on a second.
What are you doing?
Don't send it!
You're not that kind of guy!Refuse it point-blank!
You should curseat me with all you've got!
Don't send it!
I was just joking. Don't send it.
(JINSUNG_176 SENT YOU A VIDEO)
(SHADOW BEAUTYEPISODE 5: I LIKE YOU)
Why aren't you picking up my calls?
You even ignore my texts.
And why didn't you cometo the rooftop during lunch?
What is it?
Goo Ae-jin.
I'm busy. Bye.
What's going on?
Did I make you angry?
Don't do this to me, please.
Goo Ae-jin, please don't.
Why?
Are you upset you got blocked by Genie?
I have something I have to tell you today.
I told you I'm busy.
Then come after you're done.
Remember the bench at the parkwhere we drank milk tea together?
I'll wait until you come!
I'm back.
Ae-jin! Ae-jin, come here for a minute.
Here, drink this.
You father was worried about you,so he bought some restoratives.
I don't need it. I'm fine.
Stop lying!
Aren't you having nightmares again?
He heard you scream.
It's all because you lack energy.
If you're healthy--
Ae-jin. Ae-jin!
Let's talk.
Ae-jin.
(JINSUNG_176)
(REPORT, UNBLOCK, CANCEL)
Are you busy, Ho-in?
You're not picking up my calls.
I can't get in touchwith you for the whole day.
Nothing happened, right?
I'm worried.
Hurry up and reply to me.
I'm in front of your house.
I'll be waiting.
(MY BOO)
(I'M IN FRONTOF YOUR HOUSE. I'LL BE WAITING)
Four quarters of square root of 2Y is L.
X is a part of it,so you must solve X when Y is seven.
(12:30 A.M. August 17, 2021)
Goo Ae-jin!
Why? Is Genie not replying to you anymore?
Genie?
What are you talking about?
Are you going to ventat me, because you're upset?
- What are you going on about?- That's what you always do.
Stop grumbling. I'm not a trash canyou can dump your feelings into.
Goo Ae-jin.
What's
Make up your mind, Goo Ae-jin.
Hiding what I've done and keeping our friendship is being greedy.
I know you're pretending to be nice when you're actually pitying me.
It's really obvious.
It's nasty, and I'm sick of it.
When we're together, you make me realize how ugly
you make me realize how ugly
and pathetic my life is.
I…
- really…- But you're nothing special either.
We're both losers.
Failures huddling upand comforting each other is stupid.
So get lost already.
Goo Ae-jin!
I came to get your ID photo.
I don't know whyyou're doing this to me out of the blue.
The date of my debut has been decided.
So…
I'm transferringto an arts high school two days later.
Great.
It would've been better if we didn't get involved from the start.
Why do people have to meet other people?
Even while enduring such pain,
why do people haveto involve themselves with others?
It might not be one.
(JINSUNG_176 SENT YOU A VIDEO)
Ha-neul.
What do I do if the person I like
turns outto be different from what I thought?
Like how?
A two-timer?
A punk?
Don't tell me… a pervert?
I'm not sure.
How about taking a break?
A break?
Misunderstandings can clear up over time,
and it might not be that big of a deal.
If you don't have the courage to ask, just keep it to yourself.
Will I be able to do that?
We've got no choice.
We're the ones who like them more.
(1AMBSKY)
(BLOCK ACCOUNT)
(DO YOU WANT TO BLOCK THIS ACCOUNT?)
(BLOCKED)
(LEE JIN-SUNG)
Jin-sung is transferringto an arts high school for his debut.
He's transferringfor the best, so please wish him well.
And get his autograph in advance.
Say some final words to you classmates.
It's a shame.
"It's a shame."
That's it?
That was so lousy.
I totally knew that jerkwas going to transfer soon.
Nobody's curious.
Are you?
Can't you be niceto your classmate who's leaving?
Just get ready for class.
(TO AE-JIN)
(HAPPY BIRTHDAY)
Goo Ae-jin.
Happy early birthday!
I don't think I can be with you on your birthday, so happy early birthday!
Goo Ae-jin, you're my one and only good memory.
Thanks…
for eating lunchwith me. I didn't feel lonely.
You know what, Jin-sung?
I'm stupid, so I ruined our relationship.
What was so importantabout that video you sent me?
I'll never have a friend like you again.
I tried really hard not to.
But I kept getting greedy.
And in the end I messed up our relationship.
You did nothing wrong from the start.
It was all me.
Goo Ae-jin. It's all right.
Don't cry.
I like you.
So I'm sorry.
What the hell?
A monologue?
Has she finally gone mad?
Goo Ae-jin. You're really interesting.
Come on… Stop making me feel more excited.
Didn't I tell younot to wait in front of my house?
I stopped by while I was passing by.
Did something good happen?
No.
Where were you?
Nowhere special. Just on a walk.
It's late.
Let's go.
I'll drop you off.
Let me drink this. I'm thirsty.
- You can't.- Why?
You can't even take in caffeine.
I'm going to drink it.
I told you you can't!
(NARAE MAEUL)Ho-in.
How do I look today? I'm wearing a new dress.
I don't know.
Your bangs are all I can see.
- My bangs?- Yeah.
It's super weird.
Bye.
I'm exhausted.
Seriously?
Even if I skip dinnerand work out, it won't go down below 40.
She's all skin and bone.
How plain.
I want to get prettier.
I want to become a better me.
I want to be loved by Ho-in more so that…
I don't feel lonely.
- Have you had dinner?- No.
But it's way past dinner time.
I don't need it.
I'm on a diet.
You'll get sick if you don't eat properly,especially since you're still growing.
Mom!
Mom! Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Should I make you some fried rice?
Forget it.
What about the hospital?Have you gone to one?
I will.
You didn't again?
How about some fruits?
How many timesdo I have to tell you I don't need it?
My baby, you even cleaned the whole house.
Thanks.
You have to go to the hospital tomorrow.
Okay.
(MY BOO)
What? I've never seen this photo before.
Who took this profile picture for him?
(SHADOW BEAUTY)
I thought you'd betoo depressed to eat anything.
- But you're really digging in.- Do you have a death wish?
Are you going to tell the others
Hey, you bitch!
I must've eaten something weirdat your mom's shitty restaurant.
What are you doing?
Why are you laughing at me?
Do you think we can really be friends?
Hey, do I lookthat easy and stupid to you?
Apologize properly.