Ae Jin!
What are all these packages?
Where did you get the money?
So pretty!
(Shadow Beauty)
(Episode 1: After School, A Double Life)
(Grade 2, Class 2)
Mirror, mirror on the wall,
who's the fairest of them all?
The mirror is throwing up right now.
Who is the prettiest?
Dapjeongneo. (T/N: Expecting a fixed answer)
She's at it again.
Yang Ha Neul.
Really?
Stop bullshitting.
My face is so puffy from the ramyeon I had last night.
What's with your face?
My facial expression… has always been like this.
What about your expression?
Look at you smiling!
Say it again.
- Say it again! - It hurts.
- Say it again! - Let go.
F**k! Your saliva!
That's disgusting as hell.
Hey.
Are you the Joker?
I know that…
no one has any interest in or empathizes with my tears.
Just because no one cares about my looks,
that doesn't mean that I feel any less shameful.
Hard-working entity.
Rational entity.
Social entity.
Look it up on the internet. It's all there.
Humans are inherently hard-working. But…
It's my one and only bracelet.
#nomakeup
#typicalday
#selfie
#snapshot
#beonewithme
#nophotoediting
I'm an outcast in school.
But when I come home…
I'm Genie, a social media star with 770,000 followers.
Inside a small screen, I am loved by so many people.
Genie, how does it feel to live with your face?
I'm curious too.
You're so amazing!
I'd feel full just looking at the mirror.
I heard I can make people lose their appetite.
Would they say those things if they saw the real me?
(lambsky: You're my Jjin*!) (T/N: Short nickname for Genie)
(Bling, bling! Oh, my eyes!)
(Is the Pink Moon brand new?)
(What a cute dolphin!)
So cute!
If you look carefully, the dolphin is smiling.
(It would be pretty in silver.)
(Jjin! Did that evil snow white bother you again?)
Umm… Lots to say but won't.
(Pretty girls like us have lots of enemies.)
Ugly ones have more.
(Cheer up my friend. I wish I could beat her up for you!)
lambsky,
my best friend whom Genie met a year ago.
My mom always asks how a student like me,
has enough money to order so many things.
But, I didn't order these with money.
My beauty.
To be exact, Genie's beauty.
If you're pretty and have enough followers,
you get sponsorships from all over the place.
Since I get so many offers right now,
I only accept ones that will pay me for posting a product review.
The pay rate ranges widely and so do the types of sponsorships.
I receive cash as payment.
The only way of contact is by DM*. (T/N: DM is short for Direct Message)
This is the only way to protect Genie.
At first, because of this one-sided method,
lots of places refused to work with me.
But after a while,
the response was overwhelmingly positive because of the unique method.
Now, the sponsors say, "Genie,
please refrain from appearing offline."
Now they prefer the veiled Genie.
People might wonder how life could be fun for someone so ugly.
It's a thrill I've never felt in my life.
Living in a sense of superiority no one else has ever felt before
might be a better way of living.
Showing off my face, my body,
and my fashion sense will help satisfy all my vanity.
They even send me books now.
(What Did You Expect)
Aw-f..., this book is crap!
Do people want to follow what pretty people read?
From food for the mind to bluffing.
Is this the new product from Pink Moon?
Daebak! (T/N: Korean slang for awesome)
The dolphin is smiling.
Let me try it.
Let me help you.
- What do you think? - It's so pretty!
What do you think? Does it suit me?
Sure, it suits you.
Do you want it?
- It looks perfect on you. - Yeah, I agree.
Hey, this is yours. I can't accept it.
No, I mean it. It looks better on you.
Really?
Thank you!
Hey.
Where's mine?
- Let me take a picture. - Make sure it shows the dolphin.
I wore it so she'd take it from me.
Hopefully, she'll leave me alone for a few days.
(lambsky: My friend gave me this silver dolphin)
(Look at the dolphin smiling! We have matching bracelets now!)
What is that?
You scared me!
What were you looking at?
Is it something really fun?
It's nothing, really.
Huh, you've already eaten all by yourself?
I'm sorry. Sorry.
I was really hungry.
Oh, come on.
I wanted to have dessert together.
Our timing is off.
Sorry. I'll leave some for you.
He's the only one I can relate to in school.
This is Lee Jin Sung, a guy from the next classroom.
Jin Sung is a trainee at an idol agency.
Both of us are outcasts.
But there is a huge difference between us.
Hey, wake up!
- Are you close with oppa Heo Yeong? - Not really.
- Is Jua from Break Girls pretty? - I don't know.
Man, he's so stuck up.
Hey, do you think he even considers us friends?
One is too cool.
And the other… is a loser.
Are you okay?
Hey, stop it. That tickles.
I'm just patting you. How does that tickle?
Even this?
I said stop!
What's the big deal?
I'll buy you more tomatoes tomorrow.
You…
remind me of someone.
- Who? - Ah...
There was a rerun of a drama on cable yesterday.
A drama?
Oh yeah! It was "Dokkaebi"*. (T/N: He means "Guardian: The Lonely and Great God")
Dokkaebi?
I look like a dokkaebi*? (T/N: She's referring to the Korean word for 'goblin'.)
No, that's not it. You know what I mean.
You know…
Kim Go Eun. (T/N: Lead actress from "Guardian: The Lonely and Great God")
Just because I have two eyes, one nose, and a mouth?
No, I'm serious. You resemble her.
The way you smile and your grinning eyes.
You really look like her.
Thanks.
It's just the two of us here, but it's still embarrassing.
Can you please shut up?
Why? I was complimenting you.
-Honestly, you're the prettiest in your class.
Hoel*... I think you're really sick. (T/N: *Korean Slang used to express a mild shock or surprise)
Let's go to the hospital.
No, it's true.
Ask the other students.
You'd better not say anything stupid!
I'll tell everyone that you speak in a dialect.
You're such a mean girl!
Today was a lucky day. (Sangil High School)
Ha Neul didn't bother me.
And Jin Sung
complimented me by saying I look like Kim Go Eun.
Maybe just a little bit…
just the tiniest bit, my smile resembles her.
No social media for me today.
Even without Genie, I can happily fall asleep tonight.
I'm prettier than Yang Ha Neul!
So pretty!
Did you have your lunch?
Not yet, right?
Please tell me you didn't.
There's a new family restaurant on Nahyeon Road.
Let's go together.
Let me know when you're ready.
Okay!
Where are you going? It's lunchtime.
Dad wants us to eat out today as a family since it's been ages.
Family?
And where is my dad?
Ae Jin.
Don't act like a caring Mother.
It makes me sick.
Are you going somewhere, Ae Jin?
It's been a while since we ate out together.
I'm having lunch with a school friend.
I'm coming home late tonight,
so you should have a nice dinner together.
See you later, mom.
Enjoy your meal.
What?
You didn't even try it yet.
Just looking at it is a treat.
Let's dig in.
Oh, hang on.
Let me take a picture.
Make sure you send me that picture too.
You should go on Wingstagram.
Who doesn't do Wingsta these days?
I'm not really interested.
Let's eat. I'm starving.
- Is it that good? - It is.
We should hang out more often.
There are so many delicious things in this world.
I… don't like you.
After lunch, shall we go to a kono*? (T/N: Short for coin karaoke box)
And then the arcade next?
I'm sorry.
Why? Do you have other plans?
I'm supposed to have dinner with my parents.
It's kind of far.
- I'm sorry. - Is that so?
All right. That's fine.
It's too bad, though.
It's more disappointing for me.
There's something really important today.
(Three Hours Ago)
What is this?
It's so noisy.
Aside from the Photoshop ones, she has zero outdoor pictures.
Can we ever see her in real life? Or is she not real?
Man… what's with the black curtain?
Genie, are you a hikikomori*? (T/N: Someone who lives in isolation)
It's easy to Photoshop these days, isn't it?
Dammit. How did they know?
They're not wrong.
If the background is complex, I can't use the pictures at all.
That's why natural editing is hard.
So…
Do it outside?
Did you have lunch?
Not yet, right?
Please tell me you didn't.
No, not yet.
There's a new family restaurant on Nahyeon Road.
Let's go together.
Nahyeon Road.
I don't know anyone there so…
it should be fine.
Next time,
we'll go to the kono and the arcade together, all right?
- I'll see you later. - Bye.
I… don't like you.
I did it.
It looks natural!
Reading a book every day.
I'm still a little shy about taking pictures outside.
(#Nomakeup)
(#Reading)
(#Can'trevealthecafe)
(#Didn'twashhair)
Where are all the a**holes who called her a hikikomori?
Are they all dead?
She looks like a goddess.
How can she look that natural?
She's dazzling in natural light!
Do dolls drink coffee?
(#Must-eatplace, #Healing, #Recommendeddishes, #Pasta)
(lambsky: Did you go with your boyfriend?)
Yeah.
(Was it hard being seen together?)
(I saw that hikikomori comment.)  I saw your response. Thanks.
(They don't know what they're talking about.)
(The power of love sure is amazing.)
Haha.
(I want to have brunch and coffee with you too.)
(Sure, let's go later.)
(Oh! So exciting. I'm always ready whenever you are. Hope you get well soon!)
I was lying about being sick.
As time passed, she kept wanting to meet me in person.
So I told her I had an anxiety disorder which makes it difficult for me to go out.
She seemed naïve enough to believe my words.
Instead, she began worrying about me.
This girl absolutely trusts Genie.
I'm really tired.
I just took my meds so I'm getting a little sleepy.
(Go to sleep! I'll see you in your dreams.)
(coooolguy777: I saw you today, Genie.)
Yeah right.
You looked very different from your pictures.
Who is this?
I've never seen this ID before.
Who is he trying to fool?
I even have the front view.
Do you want to see it?
(Shadow Beauty)
Who could it be?
Can someone recognize Genie by just looking at me?
Koo Ae Jin.
Why are you sweating so much?
What do I do?
How much does he know?
You think I'm joking around?
You're a terrible person!
I'm talking to you, you bitch!
What do you want from me?
Let's meet first at the lounge after school.
It was you?