[LEE CHO HEE]
[CHOI JI WOO]
[LEE JOON GI]
[PARK HAE JIN]
[JI CHANG WOOK]
[KAI]
[TAEC YEON]
[LEE JONG SUK]
[LEE MIN HO]
[7 First Kisses]
[A blockbuster romance]
[Episode 5 - Kai "I'm a Teacher, You're a Student!]
I'm supposed to interpret for them?
What kind of situation is this...
Could I get a discount if I used my VIP card,
coupon, and prepaid card all together?
Yes, you would receive a discount
for your VIP Gold Card,
and an additional discount for this coupon.
And you can use the amount
on your prepaid card like cash.
That's great!
(What did I just say?)
I heard I could also make purchases
through your online duty free shop.
Could you show me how to do that?
You can download the "LOTTE DUTY FREE"
mobile app on your phone,
and easily order the same items
you could get at the off-line shop.
That's very convenient.
What in the world...
What am I saying?!
I'll order through my phone next time.
- Thank you.
- Thank you.  - You're welcome.
Chinese, huh?
I wonder who I'll get to meet next?
Oh, that's right, I'd gotten a call earlier...
Do you know how many times I called you?
This time it's Kai of EXO...?
It's so hard to go on a date with you.
A date?
Come on, what else would you call a dinner
appointment between a grown man and woman?
When are you going to quit
seeing me as a student you tutor?
Oh, so I'm a teacher, and you're a student...
Let's go!
I'm starving.
- This one looks like you.
- No, it doesn't.
Wanna get a picture?
Here's a "V"!
This smells so nice!
- Doesn't it?
- This one smells even nicer.
It's raining.
What do we do?
You didn't bring an umbrella, did you?
I didn't.
We just have to get over there.
Should we buy an umbrella?
Or maybe we could go like this...
We could run over...
Let's go.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
He looks like a prince
even when he's eating a burger.
What?
Are you cross because
I'm buying us burgers for dinner?
Not at all!
Burgers are my favorite food!
I guess you didn't know that!
What's "burger" in Chinese again?
"Burger" is "han bao bao".
I guess I tutored him in Chinese.
Anyway, since it's a student-teacher relationship,
it's unlikely that we'll end up in a kissing situation.
That means I'll get to see him longer.
It's going to be hard to see you next year
since I'll be in China often.
Yes, you'll be in China...
Why will you be there often again?
What do you mean?
I started learning Chinese from you
so I could go perform in China.
I was only in high school back then.
That's right.
Teacher.
I'm not going to call you "Teacher" anymore.
We're only 5 years apart.
We'd be considered friends out in society.
No.
I'm a teacher and you're my student.
Alright.
I have a bad feeling about this.
I hope I could be with him for longer...
Enjoy your meal.
- The rain didn't last long.
- No.
They're doing something over there.
Do you want to go see it?
Do you want to go out there?
No, I'm a terrible dancer.
- Come on!
- No!
It's okay.
If this is a dream,
I never want to wake up!
I don't want to call you "Teacher" anymore.
Then what do you want to call me?
"You".
Stop playing around...
I'm not playing around one bit.
If you don't like it,
you can say "no".
What will happen if I say "no"?
I'm not going to see you anymore,
even as a student.
You're not going to say that
you didn't know about my feelings, are you?
I mean... I guess I did...
Okay, I understand.
But not now.
Later on...
So it's not a rejection?
No way!
It's not a rejection...
It's just that right now...
It's just...
Can we talk about this again later?
No, we can't.
I've waited for so long.
Now I only have two more guys left...
Sorry!
We're a little late for our shift, aren't we?
You can go see your boyfriend now.
My boyfriend?
Go on!
Just go!
Go when we let you!
I've missed you all day.
It's Ok Taec Yeon!
[Taec Yeon]
[7 First Kisses]
[A blockbuster romance]
Mother, I'm going to marry Soo Jin.
She really must have been an angel!
There's no way I'll approve of it!
What is this bizarre set-up?
How much more will you take
before you know your place?
- Taec Yeon...
- Secretary Choi, please set up a press conference.
In order to marry her,
I'm going to give up everything I have.