=Penthouse 2=
"All characters, locations,"
"incidents, and backgrounds"
"of this drama are fictitious."
=Episode 5=
Why are you here?
You said I was your daughter too.
Can't I visit my mum to hang out?
I'm busy.
Just say what you need and leave.
I have many reports to go through.
Cheonga Arts Festival is in a few days.
I've waited so long for it.
What kind of dress should I wear?
I'm really excited.
The notice should be up by now.
At the meeting today,
the teachers decided to disqualify you
from entering.
You got yourself in big trouble,
so I had no choice.
Please don't crack such jokes.
My dad asked you, remember?
Just let me enter.
You have the power as the chief director.
Oh, did I surprise you?
I was imitating Eun Byeol.
I don't need to respond anymore, right?
Well, since you're being nice,
why don't you
just give me the grand prize?
- What?
- If you truly love my dad,
you can do that for me, right?
Are you kidding me?
You have no skills.
How can you ask for the grand prize?
You know
I can't beat Eun Byeol with my skills.
That's why I'm being shameless
and asking you for this favour.
Must I call your dad
to make you shut your mouth?
Get out.
Now.
You'll regret kicking me out like this.
I know a big secret,
lady.
What?
When Mr. Cheon Myung Soo passed away,
you were on the staircase with him.
Why did you run away?
Instead of saving your dad?
What did you just say?
You seem shocked.
All right, then.
Shall we restart our discussion?
Seok Kyung.
What kind of nonsense is this?
Do you want to compete
in Cheonga Arts Festival that badly?
No matter what you do,
you're already disqualified.
Do you think the parents of the victims
will just sit on their hands?
This proposal isn't just for me.
It means I'll keep your secret too.
A win-win situation, so to speak.
Stop this crazy talk right now.
Do you think I'll play along
with this absurd threat?
So you have to see the evidence yourself.
Fine.
If you want it, I'll send it to you.
But if you see it,
it'll torment you even more.
You should have some water.
You look so pale.
You should look after your well-being.
That brat.
What did she see?
Wait.
Did she blackmail me with that text?
No.
No, it can't be her.
If she had the video,
she would've shown it to me right away.
Stay calm.
"The 28th Cheonga Arts Festival, Finals"
"Sang A"
Hello?
Ms. Cheon, things have gone crazy here.
How can you do this to her?
What did Je Ni ever do to you two?
Wasn't turning her into an outcast enough?
You forced her to eat until she threw up,
took videos of her, and humiliated her!
How do you call yourself a human?
How will you take responsibility
for all the pain Je Ni went through?
Please stop.
What are you doing at my house?
You shouldn't be like this, Ms. Cheon!
You're trying to cover up this case
by suspending Seok Kyung.
But don't think of me as a joke.
I won't let anyone who's involved
get away with this.
I'll make sure they're all punished!
Both Eun Byeol and Min Hyuk
won't be an exception.
The only thing other kids did was
just standing there at the scene.
We already checked everything!
Right.
So you'll use Seok Kyung as a scapegoat?
Why?
Because your daughter is
one of the bullies?
It's very uncomfortable
to hear you call them bullies.
They're also my dear students.
Will you only let this go
if we punish all of our best students?
Please consider the school's position too.
Of course.
My innocent Min Hyuk had no choice
but to take part because of Seok Kyung.
This is unfair for us too.
How dare you lie to me?
Je Ni told me everything.
She said no one helped her
while she was getting bullied.
Standing by there is violence too!
So we let Je Ni compete in the finals.
That's a given!
I want everyone
who was involved to be punished severely.
I won't settle for anything
or make an exception!
Goodness.
How can you be so stern?
After all, we're old friends.
Darn you.
Exactly.
We can't let you go on about this.
We'll continue to see each other
living in the same building,
so why don't you compromise on this
at an appropriate level?
I am
telling you this
for the sake of our future relationship,
Ma Ri.
Don't do this.
Our relationship?
Darn you.
Relationship, my foot.
The war begins now.
I won't associate with anyone
who bullied my daughter.
I've completely lost it.
- You!
- Goodness.
If you don't apologise to Je Ni now,
I'll break your legs in half.
You too!
And you'd better get a grip too.
Don't stop me. Don't.
- She already left.
- Where? What?
Is she a thug or what?
Fine. This is a war.
Goodness. My goodness.
My dear,
you've grown so much.
My son.
Make sure you're prepared
for Cheonga Arts Festival.
Dad will manage this situation--
Be quiet.
Look at your face. Okay?
Seriously...
You're such a disgrace.
I thought you'd be more powerful
as an assemblyman.
Gosh.
Kang Ma Ri.
How dare you treat me, Lee Kyu Jin,
as if I'm a huge pushover?
It's me, Kyu Jin.
Yes, Kyu Jin. I mean, Mr. Lee. Yes, sir.
There's this woman named Kang Ma Ri
in Unit 4503 of this building.
Find everything you can on her.
Yes, of course, sir. Don't worry.
All I need now is Eun Byeol's phone.
Are you out of your mind?
I heard you were suspended.
Bullying someone goes down on your record.
Then you won't even get to apply
for the early admission!
Do you know how much money
I've given to your school to this day?
I could've built a new building with that!
Why does everyone blame me?
Your awesome fiancee's daughter
bullied Je Ni when no one was around,
and what she did was way worse than me.
You shouldn't have been caught either!
How is Eun Byeol always better than you?
You have a great house, good tutors,
and all kinds of support money can buy.
Why can't you ever win?
What can I do? I was born as a dimwit!
I'm sure my birth mum was stupid.
You little...
It's unfair for me to be punished alone.
That sly brat hid under her mum's shadow.
I won't let this end with me.
Just go study abroad.
I never expected you to win
the grand prize anyway.
Why should I go abroad?
I can get into Seoul University.
I'd rather have you go abroad and graduate
than to be humiliated
by applying for some second-grade college.
It'll be much cheaper
to get you the SAT ahead of time.
I don't need your help any more, Dad.
I'll compete in Cheonga Arts Festival
and win the grand prize,
so make sure you keep your promise
and let me move out.
Joo Seok Kyung.
Come here!
Joo Seok Kyung!
I'll talk to her.
I...
Why did you blow up the situation?
Making Dad angry won't get you anything.
I told you to be patient for a while.
Then I'll find a way to take you--
Stop pretending like you care about me.
Ro Na came back to school.
Aren't you horrified to see her face?
Don't be so stubborn.
Her mum wasn't the real culprit.
Do you believe that?
Do you really think Ms. Yang killed Mum?
That's...
I didn't expect to get paid for it.
Just take it.
You've become
an important person to me.
"100 million won"
I do know that it wasn't Ro Na's mum.
So stop blaming other people
just because you feel guilty.
How can you say something like that?
You're no different from Ro Na.
We're even now,
and I don't owe you anything anymore.
You gave me an apartment
to cover up what you did to my husband.
Shall I expose what you did?
It's not a good idea to bring that up,
Ms. Kang Ma Ri.
He agreed to go to jail instead of you
for Je Ni's sake.
But your daughter
ripped her heart to pieces.
Brace yourself.
I may...
just kill your daughter.
Yoo Dong Pil is rather quiet
and doing well in prison.
I don't think he heard about his daughter.
When was he getting released again?
In about two months.
Two months.
I can't let him come out already.
Your wife
dared to provoke me, Joo Dan Tae.
Why did you want to see us?
The girls have to go to school.
If you're trying to ruin our mood--
I'm sorry.
Je Ni, Ro Na.
I want to make a sincere apology.
Stop putting on an act.
You can't pull that on us.
I know that
everything I did was wrong.
But ever since what happened to my mum,
things have been so hard.
I wasn't even ready to accept her death,
and my dad was getting engaged.
Then Eun Byeol and I will become family.
I couldn't deal with everything.
Do you think that passes for an excuse?
Why did you take it out on them
just because your life is tough?
I still hated Ro Na and Ms. Oh a lot,
so I got very angry when Je Ni
became friends with her.
So...
I'm sorry.
Something like that won't happen again.
Please.
Please forgive me this once.
I'll gladly accept my punishment.
It was my dream to compete in the finals.
So please.
Please just let me do that.
Please.
You don't think Seok Kyung meant
what she said, right?
It's obvious that she tried to trick us.
Her eyes still showed a lot of confidence.
She didn't look sorry.
But that proud girl even kneeled down.
She's still a kid.
Shouldn't we give her one more chance?
No. I can't forgive her.
"It was my dream to compete
in Cheonga Arts Festival"?
That's the more reason to stop her.
She needs to lose something
that's the most meaningful to her.
That's what you call a punishment.
At the very least,
shouldn't you apologise to me
for what Seok Kyung did to Ro Na?
The district school board is
also taking this very seriously.
Do whatever you want.
Make her transfer by force or sue us.
But I'm not going to bow my head to you.
If Soo Ryeon saw
what Seok Kyung had become,
what would she say?
How dare you bring up her name?
You begged me to get rid of her.
Is that why...
you killed her?
For me?
What?
Forget it.
I don't want to nit-pick over the past.
I also wanted Soo Ryeon
to disappear from my sight.
Why did you come back?
Do you want to get back at me
for getting used and abandoned?
Do you think that's actually possible?
You must've thought I'm that easy.
Stop wasting your time
and leave with Yoon Chul,
unless your kid has another life to spare.
Thanks for your concern,
but you should look after
your company first.
The rumours of your financial difficulty
made your stock prices plummet.
I saw an article on a financial newspaper.
They advised against
investing in your company.
It looks like your merger
with Cheonga Foundation has failed.
Your relationship with Seo Jin
isn't looking good either.
The banking world might cut you off soon.
You must be under a lot of pressure
to finance your business.
Will you be all right?
I refuse to accept
your presumptuous meddling.
"JKING Holdings"
We already lost five per cent today.
Who let the word out
on our financial difficulty?
It wasn't the bank.
Ms. Cheon's scandal had an impact--
My business might fall apart
unless I announce the merger right now.
"Non-disclosure Agreement"
"I, Park Young Ran, hereby promise"
"to not disclose anything regarding..."
"Signed by Cheon Seo Jin, Park Young Ran"
Do I have no choice but to pull this move?
All ready to give me the grand prize?
Have the trophy engraved with my name.
That's enough cheekiness from you.
Don't worry.
I'll send you the evidence you wanted
very soon.
You can look forward to it.
What does that girl know?
"Cheonga Foundation"
You're here.
Yes.
Long time no see, Seo Young.
Yes, we came without calling.
You must be very busy.
I was in the auditorium
to prepare for Cheonga Arts Festival.
What brings you here?
Your 20th anniversary concert was
so moving.
I wanted to celebrate, but it's belated.
There's no need. We're family.
Especially the first song.
It almost didn't sound like you.
It was that perfect.
Your dad would've been thrilled
to see such a performance.
It was such a shame.
What are you trying to say?
I can't believe this.
Open it.
"Non-disclosure Agreement"
How dare you?
How dare you use a shadow singer
during such an important concert?
I was really shocked.
The best vocalist of Korea
deceived the entire nation?
You give me the creeps.
Where...
did you get this?
We received it anonymously
through the foundation's ethics committee.
What kind of a disgrace is this?
Do you know how hard I had to try
to shut up the committee members?
I'm sure you didn't do it for me.
If you're a mother,
you would've asked about my vocal health
and how badly I was ill
before you did that.
If you were a real mother.
Isn't that so?
What did you say?
Step down from your office
before you're humiliated any further.
Hand over the foundation to Seo Young.
What did you say?
Do you know how much damage
this could do to the foundation
once it gets disclosed?
Your father worked his entire life
to build up this foundation,
and it'll all collapse at once.
Is that what you want?
Taking away your stepdaughter's position
to give to your birth daughter?
That's the only way you'll find peace.
Now that Dad isn't around,
you won't have to play my mother anymore.
You wicked brat.
How dare you speak to me like that?
I've looked after you
for the last 30 years,
but you never accepted me as your mother.
There's no mother in this world
who can love a daughter who won't open up.
It's all because of you.
You lived your entire life
trying to make Dad hate me!
Resign,
before I expose this myself.
Right.
And sell off Cheonga Art Centre
as soon as it's finished.
How much did you spend from the foundation
to make that useless opera house?
That was Dad's long-cherished ambition.
I'll operate it no matter what!
I'll stop you.
I have 30 per cent
of the foundation's shares.
You believe you're the only one
who's cut out for this job.
You should get rid of that idea.
"Cheonga Foundation"
Oh Yoon Hee.
You really exposed this?
There's a lot of moisture in...
Why did you want me here so early?
I'm too distressed to be here.
There are no reservations from the ladies.
She was referred here by one of them.
She really wanted you to work on her
and asked me to give this to you too.
Really?
She's waiting, so get ready in a hurry.
And she paid the membership fee in cash.
Is she
in the scrub room right now?
All right.
"Mari Sauna"
Hello.
I wonder who referred you here.
I rarely ever take
reservations on the same day.
But since you were referred here
by one of our members,
I decided to...
So this was the reason why
you always smelled fresh and soapy
whenever you went out, Ma Ri.
I thought you were having an affair,
but this is way more shocking!
You're such a nobody of Hera Palace!
How did you find me here?
You'd better get dressed.
Assemblyman Lee isn't used to waiting.
My gosh.
Sorry.
"Sauna"
Honey.
My gosh, what is this?
This looks perfect on you
now that I see it in real life.
When my aide said
you work as a scrubbing lady,
I didn't believe him.
But this is why people need to live
with an identity they're born into.
You look great.
Doesn't she, honey?
Exactly.
I knew she seemed awkward when she got
all haughty back in Hera Palace,
and this was the reason.
So what?
I don't feel ashamed about this.
I lived a more ethical and decent life
than you two.
I worked hard to make money,
so I got no reason to feel inferior.
Then why did you hide it to this day?
It's...
Because of your girl, of course.
But, you know,
your sauna looked a bit too shabby.
Since you slave away in a place like this,
Je Ni should study very hard.
That's why I told my aide
to send a few photos back home
for Je Ni to see.
It's about time she grew up.
What?
You need to start dashing,
Ms. Kang Ma Ri!
That was awesome.
My stomach hurts.
Ro Na.
You're home.
Did anything happen at school?
Ms. Oh.
May we practise for the finals together?
It's nerve-racking to practise alone.
Yes, of course, you can.
Let's go. I'll make some tteokbokki.
- Goodness. I'm sorry.
- Sorry.
- Oh, I'm--
- I'm...
- Ouch.
- Why is her head so hard?
Goodness, I'm sorry.
It's all right.
Excuse me.
Who are you?
It's a secret.
A sauna?
Who is this?
Hey, it got to the wrong house.
It's for us.
Je Ni!
Je Ni.
Je Ni, are you okay?
Was... Was anybody here?
- Mum.
- Yes?
Why are you dressed like this?
Where are you coming from?
Right.
I rushed out while I was at a sauna.
I forgot that I had a dinner engagement.
You and Je Ni should go out for dinner.
I'll make tteokbokki for you next time.
- Mum, may I do that?
- What?
Yes, okay.
- Okay.
- I'll be back.
- Let's go, Ro Na.
Are you looking for this?
That scumbag.
Darn it.
Lee Kyu Jin, you jerk.
Is this why you became an assemblyman?
Darn it.
Who's calling me?
"Dubai"
Hello? Yes, warder.
Did something happen to my husband?
What?
What do you mean?
He's hurt?
There was a fight between inmates,
and Mr. Yoo was badly hurt,
so he's in hospital right now.
He got into a fight?
What's going on?
He has been trying to stay away from that.
This has never happened before.
We're trying to find out what happened.
I thought you should know.
He should've watched out
for the smallest conflict
as he was days away from leaving.
If anything happens,
his release may get delayed.
Hello?
Warder. Warder?
What in the world is going on?
Who did he get into a fight with?
Wait, could it be Joo Dan Tae?
That scumbag.
Was this your plan all along?
How dare you try to topple me over
with this darned shadow singer deal?
What are you talking about?
You need to help me understand.
Why did you take it to my mum?
Why did it have to be my sister?
You must have thought
they would make me the most miserable.
But no matter what you do,
no one can take
Cheonga Arts High from me.
I won't let anyone take my office!
I don't know what's going on,
but whenever your life goes wrong,
will you come and take it out on me?
Sadly, I haven't done anything yet.
You must have
a lot of other enemies other than me.
Shut up.
What are you doing?
Get out of my house.
I thought I warned you.
I'm not going to stay still
if you treat my wife without respect.
You knew, didn't you?
You knew what she had been up to.
Since you live with her,
I'm sure you knew everything too.
You must have had a good laugh.
Did you have a lot of fun?
Did you have fun laughing at me, you jerk?
What are you talking about?
No matter how much you hate me,
how can you join hands with Yoon Hee
and stab me in the back?
You know
what Cheonga Foundation means to me.
Are you all right?
What happened between you two?
Nothing.
I think there was a misunderstanding.
I can't let her do this anymore.
She does this because we always let her.
Don't do anything.
If you blow this up,
it'll only make your life difficult.
You need to stop letting her do this!
When she comes at you, attack her back!
I'm right here
to protect you.
You aren't alone anymore.
It's nothing.
Stop overreacting.
Dinner is ready.
I have to go out for a moment.
It won't take long.
Be careful.
Why is it so hard to reach you?
I've been worried sick.
Why were you worried?
Your mother called.
She said
you're resigning from the foundation.
Is that true?
Did my mum say that
to you?
What's going on?
Is there a problem I don't know about?
Tell me. I need to know to help you.
Is everything going smoothly
with Cheonga Art Centre?
Of course.
It'll turn into the most prestigious
opera house in the world,
just as you dreamed.
Please speed up
the merger.
Is it because of your mother?
You don't have to rush.
It's an important decision, so give it--
No, I've given it enough thought.
There's no reason to put this off.
You can announce our merger.
I'll let Mum and Seo Young take over
the department store and the hotel.
All I need is Cheonga Art Centre.
I'll entrust you with the entire process
of the merger.
If that's what you want,
I'll get started.
It'll be a huge issue in the stock market.
You might become much richer
than anything you have ever imagined.
I've already satisfied
my desire for money long ago.
I don't know. Is that
something that can be
fully satisfied?
Even if you live in the penthouse
on the 100th floor,
you'll want to go up higher and higher.
That's human nature.
Isn't that why you chose me?
Let's not put off our marriage.
Move into the penthouse
as soon as Cheonga Arts Festival is over.
Your daughter, Seok Kyung.
Do you think I can deal with her?
If we move in together...
What about her?
Did she get in trouble again?
No.
Let's talk later.
I'm sorry.
Could you please leave?
I need to get some rest.
Sure.
"Joo Dan Tae Village"
Seo Jin will make my dream come true.
"Cheonga Art Centre"
"27, Cheonsu District"
I just need to find that wench, Hye In.
Then I can take over this land
for myself.
If it hadn't been for Soo Ryeon,
it would've been mine already.
Stop drinking.
Will you be drunk in front of Je Ni?
Don't stop me.
I'll drink until I die. Actually, no.
We'll all die together.
Because you're embarrassed
that you work at the sauna?
You saw?
You saw, didn't you?
Why did you see that? Why?
What's wrong with working there?
It's not like you stole something.
Are you making fun of me now?
Those who are threatening you with that
should be embarrassed.
You have no reason to be embarrassed.
Min Hyuk's parents
sent the photos, didn't they?
That jerk.
He doesn't care that his son's at fault.
Instead, he's busy threatening me
using my weakness.
That jerk deserves to suffer.
There's no point in grumbling.
When you're weak,
you get trampled all over.
I've been through that many times.
The people at Hera Palace did that to me.
You probably can't stand me
for only apologising now,
but I must've been out of my mind.
This is how people are, you know.
I had no idea
until I experienced it myself.
If you're still angry, just sue me.
Of course,
this is how you'd apologise.
As for this bullying incident,
you don't have solid evidence.
If you keep pushing forward,
you'll be the one getting hurt.
Why don't you
just settle things with them?
I know
that I'm being stubborn now.
But you see,
until my daughter ended up in that mess,
I had no idea whatsoever
even though I'm her mother.
I can't forgive myself for that.
I feel horrible.
Let them have one,
and make sure
you get one too.
Get what?
I want to go to school with Eun Byeol.
Where is she?
She's in the shower now.
Then I'll wait for her.
It'll take a while.
Take a seat and wait here.
What? Why isn't it here?
Did she take it into the bathroom?
Eun Byeol, aren't you ready yet?
What are you doing here?
- Come.
- That hurts!
I get it, so let go.
What are you plotting?
What are you doing in Eun Byeol's room?
I'm here to go to school with Eun Byeol.
Why don't you trust me?
Since when did you care so much about her?
Mum, what's going on?
Come out!
You know you're overreacting, right?
Didn't you say you were innocent?
At this rate, you'll get caught.
Joo Seok Kyung.
I guess I came too early.
I'll see you at school.
Mum, what is going on?
Keep your distance from Seok Kyung.
If she talks nonsense, just ignore her.
Do you understand?
Yes, I understand.
"Personal Practice Room"
Eun Byeol, stop.
Did you know?
Seok Hoon and Ro Na are back together.
What?
Who said that?
I saw them together last night.
Gosh, they seemed quite serious.
I don't think Seok Hoon
is over Ro Na yet.
Do you know anything about it?
No, not at all.
Let go!
What are you doing? Let me go!
Stop making a move on Seok Hoon.
Do you and your mum have no conscience?
Do you enjoy stealing someone's boyfriend?
Watch your mouth.
What on earth are you talking about?
Seok Hoon is my boyfriend.
We're dating.
So don't talk to him.
Don't even look at him
or hover around him.
It really irks me.
But your mum is engaged to his dad.
How can you two be dating?
I don't want to explain it to you.
I've clearly warned you.
If you're seen with him once again,
that will be
the end of us.
You got that?
They're dating?
It must be a lie.
That can't be.
What did you just say?
The bullying incident.
I'll just let it go.
Let's just drop it with Seok Kyung
on probation.
That's what you should've said
from the start.
Have you finally come to your senses?
And let Seok Kyung participate
in the festival.
Why did you suddenly change your mind?
I wonder too.
Isn't it better for Je Ni
that Seok Kyung isn't there?
The more participants there are,
the lower her rank is going to be.
Je Ni can easily beat Seok Kyung.
I want everyone to see that.
And after all, I did receive
a so-called apology.
Anyway,
thank you for making this decision.
Ms. Oh, you agree with this, right?
I do,
but on one condition.
What is it?
I'll join Cheonga's Parents' Committee.
As a member,
I'll have the right to observe school life
and check the security footage as well.
There's no guarantee that the kids
won't harass Ro Na any more,
and it makes me anxious.
Are you saying you'll monitor them?
I have to protect my daughter, don't I?
And that being said,
let the committee choose
the judges for the upcoming festival.
Only the school
has the authority to do that.
Isn't that why
there has been all the corruption?
Including some
questionable grand prize winners.
You're out of line.
It's true that the fairness
has always been questioned.
If you want to avoid such suspicions,
you just can proceed with her suggestion.
I think we should.
What about you, Ms. Ko?
I have no reason to oppose.
Oh, right.
I'll notify the district school board
that we'll settle and drop the case
only after my request is granted.
What do you say?
"7 days before the festival's final round"
Nothing too salty.
You have to eat balanced meals
with all the nutrients.
You need to eat well
to have the strength to sing.
Here, open wide. Good, that's my boy.
No, no!
- Mum, my throat.
- No.
Here, wrap this around your neck.
Again!
Is that all you can do?
The higher you sing,
the lower your breaths should be.
You also need to raise your pitch
and make your upper lip vibrate.
Okay, I'll try again.
"Mi Yeon"
What's wrong, Mum?
Is something wrong?
It's nothing.
Just focus on the song.
Why can't you hold your breath longer?
You can't win the grand prize with this!
If you let Ro Na win the grand prize,
my life will be over.
Beat Ro Na no matter what,
even if you must kill her.
I can do it.
I'll win the grand prize.
I won't lose to Ro Na.
Your singing must be flawless
so we can squash the idiots
complaining about fairness.
Practise non-stop
until you can do it.
Start over with the diaphragm breathing.
Flex your abs.
More!
I was worried for nothing.
She has no evidence.
Why did I let a kid scare me?
That was very unlike me.
More!
It'll be hard not to win the grand prize.
Was I really okay?
Yes.
Just take good care of your throat
until the finals.
Congratulations in advance.
Thank you.
"Cheonga Foundation"
"CEO Joo Dan Tae"
"Merger Agreement Signing Ceremony"
"JKING Holdings, Joo Dan Tae"
"Cheonga Foundation, Cheon Seo Jin"
"JKING Holdings, Cheonga Foundation"
"Cheonga Group"
"Merger Agreement Signing Ceremony"
"Cheonga Foundation, Cheon Seo Jin"
"Cheonga Group"
"Merger Agreement Signing Ceremony"
I wanted to celebrate quietly,
just the two of us.
We're engaged
and merged the companies.
I feel like we're really one now.
I'm relieved too.
It took me a while to decide,
but now that it's done,
I trust you.
Cheonga Group will focus on construction
and investment.
They're your specialities.
I already have a detailed business plan.
Here.
"Joo Dan Tae Village"
This is what I'm developing.
It's only 20 minutes away from Gangnam.
Your Cheonga Art Centre
will be at the core of it.
The construction will be completed soon.
I'm excited.
The moment the development is announced,
it'll be impossible for anyone
to buy the land.
It'll be worth more than Hera Palace.
This will become
the wealthiest neighbourhood,
surpassing Dogok-dong.
If it's worth that much,
big corporations must've wanted it too.
This was possible because I'm Joo Dan Tae.
I'm hungry.
I have to eat light and get going.
The festival is tomorrow.
Right.
I know you worked hard to prepare for it.
And thanks for letting Seok Kyung enter.
Of course, don't mention it.
Between Eun Byeol and Seok Kyung,
I don't care who wins the grand prize.
I can give my sincere congratulations.
Cheers.
I'm excited about tomorrow.
"Alarm in 6 hours"
"Use Smart Device to wake up"
"Turn on TV, Turn on air filter"
"I hope you win the grand prize"
"You can do it! From Dad"
I hope you win the grand prize.
You can do it!
"From Dad"
From Dad.
It'll be a sunny day.
The fine dust level is average.
If you're going to the East Sea,
be careful of strong waves.
Expect a wide range in temperatures.
The temperature in Seoul is...
Good luck, Ro Na.
I'll see you later.
See you.
Okay, bye.
Bye.
Hey, Ro Na.
Here, it's red ginseng.
Drink it. It'll give you energy.
Just do what you've practised.
You were good.
Keep this in your mouth
until you have to go up.
It'll keep your mouth from getting dry.
Thanks. I'll do a good job.
You should have a banana at least.
Where's that drug?
You said you wouldn't take it this time.
I can't do it.
I need to get my anxiety under control.
Take just one.
This is for heart disease,
so one's enough to calm your nerves.
"Alpranax"
Okay.
We're short on time.
Please hurry!
Okay!
I can still see fingerprints.
Wipe it down thoroughly, please.
"28th Cheonga Arts Festival"
"JKING Holdings, Chairman Joo Dan Tae"
"CEO Ha Yoon Chul"
"Assemblyman Lee Kyu Jin"
All right, it'll begin shortly.
Everyone, head over to the auditorium now.
Don't be nervous.
Cheonga Arts Festival,
vocal music category.
The first contestant
is Bae Ro Na.
"28th Cheonga Arts Festival"
- You look stunning!
- Go, Ro Na!
- Go for it!
- Ro Na!
Ma'am.
What's wrong?
It's not the right key.
"28th Cheonga Arts Festival"
"Judges"
That was perfect.
She pulled it off flawlessly.
Amazing job!
That was insane.
That was good.
- Next up is
- Thanks.
Ha Eun Byeol.
My gosh!
What happened?
I'm sorry.
I didn't think Ro Na would pull it off.
Our deal is over now.
Keep your lips sealed.
Don't worry about that.
I hope Eun Byeol doesn't get too nervous.
"28th Cheonga Arts Festival"
"I'm rooting for you."
Don't forget
that there are always people on your side.
I'm rooting for you.
From Yoon Chul.
"28th Cheonga Arts Festival"
- Je Ni!
- Nice.
You did it, Je Ni!
- My gosh.
- Well done!
- Brava!
- Good job!
"Green Room"
Well done, guys.
Everyone sang way better than usual,
so this year's grand prize winner
will win by only one point.
Enjoy the festival
while the judges make their decision.
That's all.
I worked crazy hard for this day.
This is all Ro Na's fault.
"28th Cheonga Arts Festival"
You did an amazing job today.
I was blown away.
Here.
Thanks.
"28th Cheonga Arts Festival"
What? Why isn't this working?
"Incorrect pattern"
Did she change the pattern?
"28th Cheonga Arts Festival"
"Judges"
"Score sheet"
"28TH CAAF 2022"
"Judges' Room"
Have we decided
on the grand prize winner?
Yes, just now.
The decision was based on
the contestant's potential
and the tone of the singing voice.
Here's the final result.
Thank you very much.
Let's get ready to hand out the prizes.
Yes, ma'am.
"28TH CAAF 2022"
"28th Cheonga Arts Festival"
Eun Byeol, it's me. Are you okay?
Why were you so nervous?
Your voice cracked a little,
but it wasn't a crucial mistake.
Don't worry too much.
I'm not sure
if I can agree with that, lady.
It was a crucial mistake.
Why...
Why do you have Eun Byeol's phone?
"Cheonga Arts High School"
Seok Kyung!
That was quick.
I'm getting the grand prize
as we agreed, right?
Don't be ridiculous!
I don't know who's getting it.
The judges decided fairly
based on who sang best.
"Fairly"?
Ask anyone you see in the street
if anything at this school
is ever done "fairly".
You bluffed that you'd bring evidence.
Was this all you could come up with?
The results will be announced soon.
I didn't mean to be all dramatic,
but you want to see it so desperately,
so let me show you the evidence.
Here it is.
The evidence.
What are you talking about?
Eun Byeol had it all along.
The evidence
that you killed her grandpa.
I'm not interested in knowing why
she kept it and what she was planning
to do with it.
I just want the grand prize trophy.
Even without it, Eun Byeol
can get into Seoul University of Music.
So all you need to do
is call my name regardless of whose name
you find in the envelope.
I feel like we've finally become
a real family.
See you in a bit,
Mum.
Seo Jin.
Help...
Where are you, ma'am?
We have to announce the winner.
"JKING Holdings, Chairman Joo Dan Tae"
"28th Cheonga Arts Festival"
What did you and Seok Hoon talk about?
He congratulated me for doing a good job.
They'll announce the winner soon.
I have to go.
Why?
Do you think you can win the grand prize?
That will not happen.
My mum will never
give it to a loser like you.
"28th Cheonga Arts Festival"
Like what she did to my mum?
- What?
- Even back then,
she stole the grand prize trophy from her.
Your mum stole
what was rightfully my mum's.
She could do it thanks to your grandpa.
My mum won it because she deserved it.
Do not insult my mum.
After that, she slashed my mum's throat.
Because of your mum,
my mum had to give up on college
and had her trophy
and her dream stolen from her.
No.
My mum would never do that!
You can deny it, but everyone knows
that even back then,
my mum was much better than Ms. Cheon.
And she still is.
You lost to me, Eun Byeol.
Your dad
bribed my pianist, didn't he?
I bet you asked him to do it.
To ruin my performance.
Did you want the grand prize that badly?
But I can't let you have it.
I must win this year's grand prize
no matter what.
You know, right?
No matter what anyone says,
you're my only daughter, Eun Byeol.
I know that you'll win
the grand prize today.
Trust me.
Do you
really mean it?
Yes, of course.
Why? You don't believe me?
Then prove it.
Prove that I'm your only daughter.
Sure, what can I do?
I'll do anything you want.
What must I do?
Ruin Ro Na's performance.
Break the piano
or bribe the pianist.
Make sure Ro Na doesn't win the prize.
Eun Byeol, that's--
You promised me to do anything I ask.
You'll do it for me, right?
If you don't,
I'll never talk to you again.
Eun Byeol.
Eun Byeol, what's wrong?
If you let Ro Na win the grand prize,
my life will be over.
Beat Ro Na no matter what,
even if you must kill her.
Stop.
Stop!
You lost to me, Eun Byeol.
Your dad, Seok Hoon,
and the grand prize
are all mine.
No.
Shut your mouth!
Eun Byeol, what are you doing?
We'll now bring our chief director,
Ms. Cheon Seo Jin, to the stage
to announce the results.
A round of applause, please.
"28th Cheonga Arts Festival"
Bronze Award, vocal music category.
Cheonga Arts High School seniors,
No Ji A and Cho Bo Mi.
- My gosh!
- Nice!
"28th Cheonga Arts Festival"
Congratulations.
Silver Award, vocal music category.
Yoo Je Ni.
What? Je Ni?
Je Ni!
Go, Je Ni!
My gosh.
Congratulations.
- Je Ni!
"28th Cheonga Arts Festival"
Now,
we'll announce the grand prize winner.
Our chief director will announce
the winner of the grand prize.
"28th Cheonga Arts Festival"
"28TH CAAF 2022"
This is the highlight
of the 28th Cheonga Arts Festival.
The grand prize,
which is given to the singer
with the most divine voice,
goes to...
"28th Cheonga Arts Festival"
Our chief director
must be very nervous as well.
"28th Cheonga Arts Festival"
The winner of the grand prize will receive
a free pass to Seoul University of Music.
Ms. Cheon, please announce the winner.
"Grand Prize, 28th Cheonga Arts Festival"
"12th grade, Cheonga Arts High School"
"Bae Ro Na"
Bae Ro Na!
You were wrong.
I will not let you
take anything away from me.
Not my dad,
not Seok Hoon,
and certainly not the grand prize trophy.
Cheonga Arts High School senior...
"Bae Ro Na"
"28th Cheonga Arts Festival"
I just want the grand prize trophy.
So all you need to do
is call my name regardless of whose name
you find in the envelope.
The winner is Bae Ro Na.
"28th Cheonga Arts Festival"
=Penthouse 2=
Is it a murder case?
The killer was at the school that day.
Seok Kyung tried to kill Ro Na!
What happened?
Tell the truth!
Seok Kyung isn't the killer.
Did you do it?
No.
I'm telling you the truth. Believe me!
I will protect her with my life.
Even if you must kill Ro Na?
Yoon Chul, you can't do that to Ro Na.
The culprit in Ro Na's case...
Who are you?