=Penthouse 2=
"All characters, locations,"
"incidents, and backgrounds"
"of this drama are fictitious."
We'll now bring our chief director,
=Episode 6=
Ms. Cheon Seo Jin, to the stage
to announce the results.
A round of applause, please.
Where did Eun Byeol go?
She seemed heavily medicated today.
Maybe she fainted somewhere.
I don't see Ro Na either.
Bronze Award, vocal music category.
Cheonga Arts High School seniors,
No Ji A and Cho Bo Mi.
"28TH CAAF 2022"
Why won't Ro Na pick up her phone?
They're announcing the winners.
Be quiet.
The ceremony will go well without her,
so keep your mouth shut.
You did an amazing job today.
"28TH CAAF 2022"
I was blown away.
Here.
Thanks.
Do you want to go eat some pasta tomorrow?
I'll wait by the gates after class.
I'm busy tomorrow.
Then I'll just wait until you come.
"28TH CAAF 2022"
"28th Cheonga Arts Festival"
I missed you too,
Ro Na.
This is the highlight
of the 28th Cheonga Arts Festival.
The grand prize,
which is given to the singer
with the most divine voice,
goes to...
I just want the grand prize trophy.
So all you need to do is
call my name regardless of whose name...
"Bae Ro Na"
you find in the envelope.
Bae Ro Na.
"28th Cheonga Arts Festival"
Over here!
Hey, over here!
Hey, someone...
Someone just...
Someone just died!
- What?
- Someone just died!
- How can this happen?
- Goodness.
"28th Cheonga Arts Festival"
Min Seol A?
I'm sorry
for taking your spot.
Please forgive...
my mum.
You don't have to be sorry.
Over there! Come this way!
Down there!
Goodness, stop pushing.
- What?
- What's going on?
What is this?
Who's that?
- What's going on here?
- Who is it?
Ro Na!
What happened to you?
No, Ro Na.
Ro Na. Ro Na, open your eyes.
Why are you lying here like this, Ro Na?
You're scaring me. Open your eyes.
What's wrong, Ro Na?
What happened to her?
Yoon Chul, do something.
What's happening to Ro Na?
Ro Na.
Ro Na, open your eyes.
No, Ro Na...
Ro Na, can you hear me?
You have to stay with me.
Ambulance. Someone call an ambulance!
- An ambulance.
- Hurry up!
- I'm on it.
- Ro Na.
Hello? Yes.
Please send an ambulance in a hurry.
We're at Cheonga Arts High School.
A kid got hurt.
She's all bleeding--
Ro Na.
- What happened?
- Ro Na.
- That's Min Hyuk.
- Don't come!
Ro Na, are you okay?
- No.
- Ro Na.
- Don't look!
- Ro Na will be fine.
- Ro Na!
- What's going on?
She has no pulse,
- and she's not breathing.
- Oh no.
Move aside!
- Do something.
- Lay her down!
Ro Na, no...
Ro Na.
It looks like she was killed.
Isn't this a murder case?
Shut up!
My daughter isn't dead.
Why would she die?
She's still warm.
Her body is still so warm!
Shut the gates right now
until the police get here.
Don't let anyone here leave the school.
Until we catch the culprit,
you will not move an inch out of here.
What are you doing? Lock the gates!
Yes.
What the heck is this?
"28th Cheonga Arts Festival"
No, don't come this way!
Stop!
You can't come down here! No!
There's a person down there!
- No, stop it!
- My gosh!
Don't come this way!
No, please stop!
No!
Wasn't Eun Byeol back there with you?
You can't leave!
- You can't leave the grounds!
- Move aside!
No!
No, please!
"Emergency Response"
What am I going to do, Yoon Chul?
I'll follow after I wrap things up here.
You should go there first.
It'll be fine, okay?
Please leave right away.
"Emergency Response"
Don't touch that.
It could be used as evidence.
What?
Aren't you hungry?
Do you want something to eat?
I don't need anything.
Why did you lock the door?
Are you in a bad mood?
I'm fine! I'm okay!
I need to get some rest.
I'm just too tired.
All right.
Then get a good rest.
"28TH CAAF 2022"
She's not dead. She's not dead.
I need to go home.
"28th Cheonga Arts Festival"
"Ha Eun Byeol"
"Hand Sanitiser"
Check her blood pressure.
Doesn't look good.
Get the defibrillator ready.
Charge to 150 joules.
Shock.
Get an OR ready immediately.
And page a neurosurgeon!
Get her to an OR!
Ro Na, don't leave me!
Ro Na, please stay with me.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry for everything, Ro Na.
Ro Na, please don't leave me!
"28TH CAAF 2022"
"Police"
"Fire Alarm"
Did you find anything?
Too many people poured out at once,
so it's impossible to detect
any meaningful footprints or evidence.
"Green Room"
Did the girl die?
I heard it's a murder case.
How long will you hold us here?
Do you think we have that much time?
Would you say that if it's your daughter?
Some might think you're her birth father.
What are you so worried about that
you want to run before you're questioned?
You did something, didn't you?
- What did you say?
- Come on.
- What's wrong?
- Seriously.
- Do something as an assemblyman.
- Geez.
- Darn it!
- You.
Let me go!
How dare you assault
an assemblyman in office?
Mr. Ha!
Do you know what time it is?
Let us go home already.
Everyone in this room is
all very famous and highly reputable.
They aren't going to run away.
And the investigation will be done--
That was a teenage girl!
A teenage girl got hurt.
She's between life and death right now.
I'll catch the culprit myself.
No matter who did this,
I'll hunt down the culprit
and make sure they're punished.
Not even a single ant
will be allowed to take a step outside
without an alibi.
So you all had better cooperate.
I was sitting in the concert hall
even before the festival began.
I only went to the toilet once.
You can check with everyone else.
I was sitting in the same row
as my husband all along.
Chairman Joo, were you the first
that was on the scene?
Is it a problem that I'm a fast runner?
And to be exact,
the one who found her first was
the school janitor.
I just ran after I heard Mr. Park scream.
We all saw each other in the concert hall,
isn't that so?
- Yes.
- Yes, you're right.
And we had coffee together
while they were judging, right?
- Yes.
- I stuck around to the end.
Je Ni didn't see
Eun Byeol in the green room.
Shouldn't you begin there?
Come to think about it,
why haven't I seen her?
I didn't see her in the schoolyard either.
She wasn't feeling well,
so she went home early.
She went home?
She went home before the announcement
of the grand prize?
She wouldn't do that.
She was one of the strong competitors.
Even if she ended up passing out,
she wouldn't have gone home.
Did she take
those drugs again?
You all know, right?
She relies on calming pills
before any performance.
She got too nervous and didn't feel well.
Wait.
Are you suspicious of her?
No one is an exception,
including you and Eun Byeol.
Don't worry.
I'll have her questioned straightaway
after I check on her at home.
And I mean your daughter,
Eun Byeol.
Happy now?
Let's dismiss people
with a solid alibi.
"Police Line: Under Investigation"
This looks like the weapon,
the wing of the trophy.
The trophy?
She was hit twice with the trophy
on her shoulder and head.
And there was severe bleeding
from the wound on her head.
What about the rest of the trophy?
We couldn't find it at the scene.
We'll focus our investigation
on finding the missing weapon.
The school needs to be closed for a while.
I'll take measures to help
as much as I can as the chief director.
Is there anyone affiliated with the school
who held a grudge against the victim?
Someone set off the fire alarm
to remove the evidence.
They must be familiar with the school.
Is there anyone that comes to your mind?
What do you think of
the great Cheonga Arts High School?
Are you saying we tampered with the case?
Well, that's not what I meant.
Please cooperate with the investigation.
Of course.
Why are you so sensitive?
Then why are you doing this?
Are you a detective?
Or are you Ro Na's biological father?
Fine, find the culprit for Ro Na.
Go search everywhere through the night.
"Intensive Care Unit"
"Restricted Area"
This is for Ro Na.
How is she? Did she wake up?
"Intensive Care Unit"
Are you Bae Ro Na's guardian?
The patient just regained consciousness.
Ro Na.
Ro Na, it's me, Mum.
Open your eyes.
Ro Na.
Ro Na, I'm here.
Do you recognise me?
Ro Na?
Who did this?
Who did this to you?
Ro Na.
This is yours.
You won the grand prize, Ro Na.
You should get up soon
so we can celebrate, okay?
Hang in there, okay?
Hold on. Hang in there.
That trophy is for Seol A.
Give her that trophy.
I'm sorry
I've been so mean to you.
I'm sorry.
Ro Na.
Ro Na, wake up.
Ro Na. Ro Na. Ro Na!
Over here. Over here!
Ro Na, wake up!
Ro Na, no!
Ro Na, I'm right here.
- Please, don't go, Ro Na.
- Please move.
Ro Na, I'm right here. Please, Ro Na.
Ro Na, don't die!
Please just stay alive.
I won't ask for anything else.
Please, no.
- Ro Na, don't leave me.
- She's in arrest.
Ro Na, no, please. Don't leave me.
- Ro Na, no!
- Bring a defibrillator!
- Yes, Doctor.
- Yoon Hee.
- Yoon Hee!
- No!
The defibrillator!
No, Ro Na! Ro Na, don't leave me!
Don't leave me alone!
Please come back. I'm so sorry.
Charge to 200 joules.
Please, Ro Na!
Don't leave me. No!
Please don't go, Ro Na!
Please don't leave me.
Why aren't you asleep?
I have a question.
Ro Na.
Did you do that to her?
What are you talking about?
Why would I do something like that?
Stop lying.
This has something to do with you.
You always kept your poise
when Seol A and Mum died.
But I know.
I know you killed...
both Mum and Min Seol A.
Why did you
kill my mum? Why?
To marry a woman like that?
Or what? Because she gave birth to Seol A?
If you did
something to harm Ro Na--
I never imagined my son would be caught up
with such wild imagination.
How dare you say this nonsense to me?
Don't hurt Seok Hoon!
Seok Hoon and I aren't your belongings.
There's no reason for us to get beaten.
I'm glad you're here.
I had a question for you.
Do you know
whose necklace this is?
Eun Byeol.
She was wearing it during her performance.
Why do you have that?
I found it in the concert hall.
Go back to your rooms.
Don't touch that.
It could be used as evidence.
- Mr. Assemblyman.
- If you know who I am,
you should get your act straight!
Do you know how much it costs
to get a bunch of spinach?
So this necklace belongs to Eun Byeol?
What's going on?
I remember putting it in here.
Where did I drop that thing?
You're back.
It's pretty late.
Something came up.
Did Eun Byeol eat dinner?
She didn't.
She washed up and fell asleep right away.
She must've been too tired to eat.
It's late. You should get to bed too.
But
I couldn't find her dress.
She came back wearing it,
but it's not in her closet.
I'm sure she left it somewhere.
Is that so important this late at night?
I understand. Please get some rest.
Could it be...
No, it can't be.
Eun Byeol...
can't be the culprit. Never.
"Mr. Do"
Mr. Do.
What happened to Ro Na?
What?
There's no chance
she'll wake up?
Was it...
really you?
What are you talking about?
I got mad I couldn't win the grand prize,
so I wanted to throw it out.
Then how do you explain this?
The blood on your dress!
Tell me every single detail.
What did you do to Ro Na?
Did Ro Na
really die?
No, right?
She couldn't have died.
She's a tenacious kid.
No.
No, no.
Pull yourself together and answer me!
Did you do that?
You have to tell me, Ha Eun Byeol!
She
keeps taking my things.
She kept lurking around me
speaking ill of you.
She said you slashed her mum's neck.
She said
you lost to her mum.
But I really didn't mean to kill her.
I mean it. Please believe me.
It's all right. Pull yourself together.
Pull yourself together, Eun Byeol.
Calm down.
Everything is over.
I'm a criminal.
The police will soon come for me.
No.
I'll just head over to the police station
and tell them everything.
I'll tell them that I did it.
Forget university and singing now.
Everything is over.
No!
Your life won't go wrong.
I won't let that happen.
I'll protect you.
I don't care if Ro Na is dead or alive.
That's not what's important.
You just need to stay clear of that case.
If someone asks you,
tell them you don't know anything.
Do you understand?
What if someone saw me?
There are CCTVs at school too.
I'll take care of that,
so you don't have to worry.
I'll get rid of this dress.
Then it'll be fine.
There won't be any evidence.
The trophy.
The trophy?
Your trophy
from Cheonga Arts Festival.
Where did you put that?
In my locker at school.
What?
Please stay away.
Another unfortunate incident broke out
yesterday at Cheonga Arts High School.
Cheonga Arts Festival is
the most prestigious event
with a long tradition in the school.
A senior student who won the grand prize
fell unconscious before she got a chance
to hold the trophy in her hands.
The police believe she was most likely
attacked by someone with a grudge.
They plan on narrowing down the suspects
on the list of people who were at school.
Chief Director Cheon Seo Jin
of Cheonga Foundation announced
all of their classes will be held online,
and that she will
actively cooperate with the investigation.
The damage to her brain is severe.
I don't think she'll make it.
You should get ready to face the worst.
Yoon Hee.
Yoon Hee, this isn't good.
I'll get you a hospital room.
Go lie down for a little.
No.
I need to find the one who did this.
What did the police say?
They haven't found any evidence yet?
They're under investigation,
but not yet.
The culprit was there at school.
How could there be no evidence?
It's also weird how the fire alarm
went off without any fire.
I don't trust the police any more.
I need to head over there myself.
You're not well enough to do anything.
Let's trust them and wait.
I asked a friend of mine
to ask the police for help.
They'll call when they find the evidence.
I can't trust anyone!
I'll catch them with my own hands.
Do you think I'll let this one live
after they hurt my daughter?
Yoon Chul.
What if the worst happens to her?
What if something bad happens to her?
I'm about to go crazy.
What am I going to do?
No, this can't be real.
Please let Ro Na live.
Please let her live.
Yoon Hee. Yoon Hee.
Yoon Hee. Yoon Hee. Yoon Hee!
What are you doing? Get Dr. Jung!
- Yoon Chul.
- Bring an Ambu bag!
Soo Ryeon.
Please don't take Ro Na from me.
Just kill me
and let Ro Na live. Please.
Please.
"Sleep Inducer"
Clear your mind and sleep well.
Have you seen my phone?
I discarded it just in case.
I'll get you a new one.
Stay out of touch with your friends
for a while.
Remember.
You must forget everything in the past.
Once you wake up, it'll be all over.
Eun Byeol had it all along.
The evidence
that you killed her grandpa.
Did you enjoy the video I sent you,
Ms. Cheon Seo Jin?
Who is this jerk?
Don't hide like a coward.
Show yourself!
What about you? Have you moved on?
I'm talking about Grandpa's death.
What do you mean?
I took
those pills because
I missed Grandpa too much.
What are you talking about? Explain!
"No SIM card inserted"
"Authorised Persons Only"
When did you arrive?
Today.
How's Ro Na?
Is she still unconscious?
Seo Jin and Eun Byeol
are acting suspiciously.
Tell me everything you know.
I took this at 5 this morning.
Where was she going so early?
What's that bag in her hand?
What's weirder is that
she came back empty-handed.
And on top of that,
she came back with Cheon Seo Jin.
Does that mean...
The trophy...
I need to get the trophy first.
If I get caught, I'll be doomed.
The police have finished
investigating the scene.
Are you sure?
The preliminary investigation failed,
so they're struggling to find evidence.
There's minimum manning,
and most are gone.
Let's go.
- Cheon Seo Jin?
"Ha Eun Byeol"
It is her, right?
Ms. Cheon.
What brings you here?
Look who's talking.
What are you doing here at this hour?
In this dark classroom with no lights on.
Were you looking for something?
I wonder too.
Something smells very fishy here.
What were you
rummaging through like a thief?
I wasn't rummaging through anything.
What?
Those lockers behind you
look like the perfect spot
for hiding things.
Move.
That's right!
Let's open them up and see.
You start from the left.
I'll start from the right
and break them open.
Hold on!
I'll open Eun Byeol's.
What?
There's nothing out of the ordinary.
There's only a few left now.
I found it!
Whose locker is it?
"Joo Seok Kyung"
Joo Seok Kyung!
I knew it.
We have to get her.
Let's go. Come on.
What are you doing here?
Let go!
I said, let go!
Do you know who my dad is?
You can't take me against my will!
Dad, where are you? Seok Kyung is...
The police are taking her.
What happened to your hand?
I was rushing to open the locker.
How did you know?
Eun Byeol
called me.
Did you set off the fire alarm too?
No.
I had no idea then.
Did Eun Byeol really do it?
Did Eun Byeol
do that to Ro Na?
It's not true, right?
I don't want to believe it either.
Why didn't you tell me?
You should've told me first!
How could I?
You are
Yoon Hee's husband now.
I don't believe this.
How...
How could our daughter do such a thing?
It already happened.
You may not want to believe it,
but just accept it.
No.
This can't be.
This cannot be true.
You're the one who put the trophy
in Seok Kyung's locker,
which means you also don't want Eun Byeol
to get arrested.
You've been a disappointing dad
all her life.
Don't tell me you'll just let her
ruin her own life.
They'll find out very soon
that Seok Kyung didn't do it.
Right, so get yourself together!
Yoon Hee
will not give up.
She'll keep digging
to find out who really did it.
And in the end,
she'll find out that it's Eun Byeol.
Then Eun Byeol's life is over.
Save her.
You're the only one who can save...
our dear Eun Byeol.
You're Eun Byeol's dad.
What do you expect me to do?
I can't help Eun Byeol any more
because I feel so bad for Yoon Hee.
Seeing Ro Na like that
drives me crazy!
Ro Na...
She has no hope anyway.
Dr. Jung told me
she'll be pronounced brain-dead tomorrow.
Then shouldn't you save
the one who's not on the verge of death?
What?
What are you trying to say?
There's only one way to stop Yoon Hee
from digging further.
While Seok Kyung buys us some time,
we must frame someone else for the murder.
Seo Jin!
Right now,
I only care about Eun Byeol.
I'll only think about Eun Byeol.
I am her mother,
and a mother
must protect her child.
If anything bad happens to her,
my life is also over.
Darn it!
Why did you do that to Ro Na?
Did you hate her that much?
You should've just hated me.
Why take it out
on my innocent daughter?
Why?
Have you lost your mind?
Why in the world would I do that?
Why did you do that?
What are you doing?
Who are you
to accuse my daughter?
You stay out of this.
Seok Kyung tried to kill Ro Na!
The trophy was found inside her locker,
covered in blood.
We suspect that it was used
to assault the victim,
so we had to interview her.
The trophy?
We heard
there was bad blood between you and Ro Na
due to the recent bullying incident.
You dumped some kind of paint on her
and locked her in the lavatory.
- That's...
- They are
completely unrelated.
I assure you. Seok Kyung didn't do it.
I can prove it.
Detective.
We got the fingerprint analysis results.
"Analysis Report"
There were many prints on the trophy,
but none of them
belongs to Seok Kyung.
See? What did I tell you?
I said I didn't do it!
I bet someone
put it in my locker to set me up.
Who'd do that? And why?
Someone who's holding a grudge against me.
Seok Kyung didn't do it.
Just before the grand prize announcement,
we took this picture in the green room.
Look.
Seok Kyung is there too.
Is this enough proof?
Who's missing?
Ro Na and Eun Byeol.
We deduce that the incident
took place just before the announcement,
which means it wasn't Seok Kyung.
What do you take our family for?
This is a clear case of defamation.
I will not
let this go unpunished.
Let's go.
So Eun Byeol wasn't there...
Come to think of it,
Ms. Cheon
picked up a necklace at the scene.
A necklace?
What did it look like?
A very fancy one with a huge stone.
Maybe it was a sapphire, but...
Not sure. I only took a glance at it.
Sapphire?
"You can do it! From Dad"
You didn't know about it?
I thought it was handed off to the police
as evidence.
Oh, gosh.
Yoon Hee.
Why are you so jumpy?
Oh...
I assumed no one was home.
Didn't you go to the hospital?
I came to get some things.
Where were you?
I was at the office.
I didn't go in for a few days,
so I have a lot of work piled up.
How did it go at the police station?
Seok Kyung's prints
weren't found on the trophy.
Oh, I see.
Is there any other evidence?
It wasn't Seok Kyung.
I think
someone tried to frame her for it.
But who would do such a thing?
I wonder too.
Anyway, I should go see Ro Na.
Stay home and get some rest.
All right.
Yoon Hee, let me know if you're tired.
I'll come and relieve you.
It's not you, right?
Yoon Chul.
You can't
do that to Ro Na.
You can't.
Eun Byeol.
Why did you do that?
Why did you do that to me, Eun Byeol?
Eun Byeol.
Why did you do that to me?
Come with me.
Ms. Cheon isn't home yet.
It doesn't matter.
I'm here to see Eun Byeol.
But she's not feeling well...
How are you feeling?
I heard you weren't feeling well.
You really don't look well.
I'm okay.
What brings you by?
You must've heard
about Ro Na.
Yes.
I came to ask you something.
Were you with Ro Na
just before the announcement?
No.
Only the two of you
weren't in the green room.
Where were you?
I was feeling a little queasy,
so I went to the infirmary.
Really?
You saw Ro Na, didn't you?
Tell me the truth.
What happened?
Tell the truth!
What is going on?
She's not feeling well.
What are you doing?
Why is Eun Byeol not feeling well?
What?
She used it as an excuse
to get out of the police interview.
So I came here to ask her myself.
Ha Eun Byeol, answer me.
You saw Ro Na, didn't you?
Tell me the truth.
What did you do to Ro Na?
Tell me now!
I don't know.
I don't know anything.
Stop it!
Stop harassing my daughter.
Leave at once.
Get out!
Get out now. Out!
I know you're lying.
- Tell me!
- Get out!
What did you do to Ro Na?
- Let go.
- Get out!
Get off of me!
Are you suspecting every single kid
in Hera Palace?
First, Seok Kyung. Now, it's Eun Byeol?
Seok Kyung has a solid alibi.
Your daughter is the only one
without an alibi.
That is for the police to decide.
Oh, right.
Why hasn't Eun Byeol
returned her dress yet?
What?
I went to the dress shop earlier.
Her dress is the only one
that hasn't been returned yet.
Can I see the dress?
You're insane.
Why must I show it to you?
You're right.
I'm insane.
My baby's lying in the hospital like that.
How could I not be?
I have to see that dress.
I'm sure you have it.
Why?
Do you think you'd find some blood on it?
You also like being thorough.
Where is the dress?
Ms. Jin!
Bring Eun Byeol's dress.
Yes, ma'am.
Here it is.
You're delusional
and paranoid.
If you have time for this,
take better care of your daughter.
Ms. Jin.
Our guest is leaving.
Make the exact same dress.
I have to pick it up tonight.
Yes, ma'am.
Yoon Hee just came by.
She even asked to see Eun Byeol's dress.
She suspects Eun Byeol.
What if the truth comes out?
Please!
Please do something.
Find a way, please!
Regarding the Cheonga Arts High incident,
Gangnam Police Station
- has stated that a school janitor
- Sang A.
- Sang A!
- turned himself in and confessed
- to the crime.
- What is it?
- The janitor, Park, claims
- Stop yelling.
- that he had been
insulted by the victim
- on numerous occasions
- I can't even
- and committed
- go to the loo at night.
- the crime
- The culprit turned himself in!
- on impulse.
- I mean, Ro Na's case.
- What? Who is it?
- Having worked
at the school for many years...
You know, the sharp-faced man
who smiles a lot. The janitor!
You mean, Mr. Park?
No way!
Why would that nice man do such a thing?
This is why
you can never judge a book by its cover.
He must have a split personality
or something like that.
Oh, that makes sense!
I'm relieved
that the culprit has been caught.
Otherwise,
Yoon Hee and Yoon Chul would've gone mad
and grilled every kid at Hera Palace.
The school needs to be
considerate of the 12th graders.
But I have to say,
I can't believe Mr. Park did it.
He was too scared
- to even touch a dead sparrow.
- The police
will inspect the scene.
He'd never harm a person.
What was your motive?
A personal grudge?
Or were you after money?
That kid looked down on me
and insulted me on an ongoing basis.
So I got angry and...
It was done on the spur of the moment?
What's going on?
Why did you hide the trophy
- in the locker?
- Mr. Park is the culprit?
- Since I couldn't...
- It's okay.
Don't worry about anything, Eun Byeol.
Why him of all people?
He was always so nice to us!
I feel terrible...
- Hold on!
- A comment, please!
What am I going to do now?
Park has admitted to everything.
According to Gangnam Police Station,
Park has confessed
to both his motive and method.
The results of the investigation
- Mr. Park...
- will be announced soon.
Stop drinking.
Leave me alone.
I can't stand being sober.
So you used Mr. Park.
Why didn't you give me a heads-up?
I was closer to him
than to my own father.
I know.
That's why I'm trying my best
to minimise his sentence.
I feel like a monster, and I hate it.
I feel like it's all my fault.
It's driving me insane.
If you want to criticise me, go ahead.
I bet you want to ask me
why I hid Eun Byeol away if I was going to
end up like this.
Fine.
Maybe you were right about everything.
Even I loathe myself.
I told you to stop drinking.
This won't change anything.
Every night in my dream,
I see Ro Na waking up.
The anxiety is driving me crazy.
If Ro Na wakes up,
all our efforts will go down the drain.
And Eun Byeol
will be arrested.
I'm so scared.
I'm terrified.
It's killing me.
Neither Eun Byeol nor I
will be able to handle it.
You must pull yourself together
so we can protect Eun Byeol.
What are you doing?
Are you sure
you can protect Eun Byeol?
I will protect her with my life.
Our daughter, Eun Byeol.
Even if you must kill Ro Na?
Promise me that you'll protect her.
That you'll do whatever it takes
to save Eun Byeol's future.
If you can't do it,
I will.
I'll kill Ro Na if that is what I must do
to save Eun Byeol.
Seo Jin!
You know,
this is our fault.
That's why this happened.
We're both responsible.
Even if there's a 1-in-10 million chance
that Ro Na can wake up,
that slim chance
could bring misery
to both Yoon Hee and us.
Do you want that?
"Yoon Hee"
"Violent Crimes Unit 2"
Mr. Park.
I'll wrap up our interview here.
Is that okay?
Yes.
You did it?
Was it really you?
Did you really do that to my daughter?
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Why did you do that?
Why?
What did Ro Na even do to you?
Why did you do that?
Why? Why?
Answer me! Tell me why you did it!
You can't do this, ma'am.
If I lose Ro Na,
I will never forgive you.
I will kill you!
I will really kill you.
I'm going to kill you!
I'll kill you...
I'm sorry, Yoon Hee.
I guess
this is it for us.
I thought I'd never betray you again.
Do not forgive
a jerk like me.
"Restricted Area"
My gosh!
Dad, you need to see this.
All the comments are bashing Ro Na.
Everyone feels sorry for the janitor
and thinks he must've had a reason.
Gosh, I get it.
But that's too harsh,
considering she's dead now.
Do you know what irks me the most?
Seeing small fry who try to bully others.
How dare she act like she belongs
to the upper class?
After moving into Hera Palace,
she forgot that she came from nothing.
She's being bashed even after she died.
My dear son.
Focus on preparing for early admission.
You're following my advice, right?
Of course.
I already have
over 500,000 followers!
Amazing, right?
Will following your advice really get him
into Seoul University of Music?
Do you not trust me?
Why do you think I made sure to become
an assemblyman before this year?
Assemblyman Kang and I have been
working hard to propose this bill
since last year.
Special admission for influencers.
But it might disappear next year.
Min Hyuk, you have to get in this year.
My aide is managing your account well,
so just follow your mum around
and do a lot of volunteer work.
And take good pictures.
- Okay.
- Got it?
Yes, got it.
Because of Ro Na, all the other kids
are in a state of panic.
I hope Min Hyuk can use this as his chance
to get ahead!
This is why they say every crisis
is an opportunity.
That's right.
"Grand Prize, Bella Voce"
Hi, Ro Na. Mum's here.
My poor Ro Na.
You must be cold.
"Bae Ro Na"
"Become a bright star in the sky"
It took me some time
to sort through your things.
I have now
finished everything I had to do.
I'll come to you,
my dear daughter.
"Bae Ro Na, April 8, 2004 - April 3, 2022"
Why are you in such a rush to die?
Let go!
I want to be with Ro Na.
I can't let my daughter be all alone.
Did I save you so you could do this?
Please let me punish myself.
I'll punish myself for killing Seol A!
Sure, but before you die,
you need to find out
who did this to Ro Na!
The real culprit
is someone else.
The real culprit?
Who is it?
Ha Eun Byeol.
Do what you need to do
and come back by three.
- Yes, ma'am.
Who are you?
Soo Ryeon?
How have you been?
It's been a while,
Joo Dan Tae.
=Penthouse 2=
I'm seeing red now.
Can we start over?
No!
I know Seo Jin's weakness.
It's the only way.
I think I really like you.
Who dares to mistreat Lady Jincheon?
You need to work on your personality.
Hello, I'm Sim Soo Ryeon.
She knows all of Joo Dan Tae's secrets.
Logan Lee, that jerk?
Beg, again and again.
Get on your knees!