Today is the last trip of Music Adventure
by Accident's big journey.
- It's a shame.
- I agree.
Hold on. Who is he?
I thought he was a standing signboard.
Hi. I'm Lee Si Eon.
(It's been a while.)
I've always been cheering...
- for Music Adventure by Accident.
- Right.
I watched the first episode with Kian84.
He caught the premiere.
Si Eon also took part
in the "Dandelion" challenge.
- Right.
- I did my best...
in the challenge.
(Joined the "Dandelion" challenge)
(Si Eon voluntarily promoted
the challenge.)
I'm confused about whether
your Instagram account belongs...
to you or Kian84.
The hashtags on the posts you upload...
have Music Adventure by Accident
and catch the premiere.
- You promote the show more than Kian84.
- He's loyal.
It belongs to Kian84.
- Right?
- Yes.
You two are a family to adore him so much.
You two went to
the Amazon Rainforest together.
- Aren't you the first jungle brothers?
- Yes.
- We are.
- There were unforgettable moments.
After a swim, we were taking a shower.
Kian84 told me the water was clean.
I asked where it was from,
and it was from the Amazon River.
- You remember it clearly.
- Yes.
Traveling in Jamaica...
reminded me of the Amazon Rainforest.
It was like watching
the very first season of this show.
- I agree.
- Me too.
We have Si Eon,
Kian84's trusty backup, here with us.
Kian84 has gone into Jamaica's
mysterious mountains,
the Blue Mountains.
Shall we check out
what happened on his last trip?
Let's go.
One more time.
I think it's enough for me.
But it was refreshing.
(Scrubbing)
His hair is so cool.
I want to try that hairstyle.
(Naturally taking a shower in nature.)
With dreadlocks, the water...
needs to be as strong as that waterfall.
(The water needs to be
as strong as the waterfall.)
(Sitting down)
(Having fun while waiting for him
to finish showering)
(Standing up)
(He puts the camera in his pocket...)
(and enters the waterfall.)
- Didn't that hurt your head?
- The water pressure looks too strong.
(The strong current makes him leave.)
(Being kind)
(Rummaging)
(It feels empty.)
(What?)
My camera!
(My camera!)
- What is it?
- What happened?
- Something has happened.
- What?
(I lost my camera.)
(The camera went missing
in the split second.)
(He was having fun under the waterfall
just a while ago.)
(The camera inside his pocket...)
(fell into the water.)
Oh, no.
No!
- My camera!
- Goodness.
(Turning)
(I'll find it for you.)
My camera!
- The current is too strong.
- It's hard to see anything.
(Joseph willingly helps Kian84.)
(The owner desperately searches
the ground.)
(He searches every nook and cranny,)
(but the camera is nowhere to be seen.)
And the water is murky too.
I have had this thing
since "Adventure by Accident."
When my travel mates leave...
or when I'm alone,
the camera becomes my friend.
I talk to it.
Since Teo and Pani Bottle left,
the only friend I had left was the camera.
So it was like losing my best friend.
Right. The camera had all your memories.
My family and friend
got lost in the water,
and I had no idea where it was.
Where did you go?
I'm sorry.
(Where did you go? I'm sorry.)
Please.
(Please.)
(They desperately search for his friend)
(but it's nowhere to be seen.)
- I thought it got washed away.
- You should still find it.
(Blinking)
(On the verge of the memories formatting)
No.
I bid farewell with that camera
at the Uyuni Salt Flat.
Kian84 treasured the camera
more than he treasured the people.
Where did it go? Good grief.
(Staggering)
(Instead of Kian84
who is not steady from the shock,)
(Joseph searches for it
while flipping his dreadlocks.)
(Diligently looking for it
in the strong current.)
(Pulling up)
(Could it be?)
(He caught something with his hair.)
(The camera)
(Amazed)
- Look.
- Joseph found it.
- It got caught in his hair.
- Nice.
(Fascinated)
(The camera was lost in the water.)
(It got saved by the dreadlocks.)
(I found you)
(Walking over to deliver the good news.)
(Hey)
Goodness. You found it?
(I found it)
You found it?
(Feeling proud)
Wow!
- Thank you.
- I had already given up.
- You two must've grown closer.
- Thank you.
(Smiling)
(Reunited with his friend)
Thank you.
(Laughing)
I thought finding it would be impossible,
but Joseph pulled it up with his hair.
How he found it like that
is still a big mystery to me.
There's this thing called
spoonworm fishing.
Two gaffs are dropped into the mud flat
and dragged up.
The spoonworms
would be caught on the gaffs.
- That's how it's done.
- Like spoonworm fishing?
Joseph's...
spoon-worm-gaff-dreadlocks
found my camera.
It was amazing.
I never thought we'd find it.
(Laughing)
Joseph!
- Thank you, Rothman.
- No problem.
Okay, let's go.
(Calling the hero whatever he wants.)
(Now they head to Joseph's house.)
(Rustling)
Do you know what this is?
- No. What's this?
- It's peach.
"It's peach?" I see.
(Taking a bite of Jamaican peach)
It tastes just like Korean peach.
- Was it sweet?
- Slightly less than Korean peaches.
- My country farms peach.
- Peach?
- Yes.
- Okay.
They're very big.
Big. These are natural.
- No chemical. No fertilizer.
- I see.
(Organic)
(Heading to Joseph's house
in clean Jamaica)
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
- Does your camera still work?
- Yes.
Okay.
You must've been so happy.
You're a very lucky man.
I'm blessed.
- Your hair...
- Yes?
- Your hair fished it.
- Yes.
- It fished my camera up.
- Yaman.
(Wild)
Unbelievable.
(Laughing)
- You found it.
- Yes.
- It's a very important camera.
It was so heavy.
Rothman. Thank you!
- He's not Rothman.
- His name isn't Rothman.
Do many people shampoo...
- in the waterfall?
- Yes.
Wow.
- I'll tell them not to take a camera.
- The camera?
(Laughing)
- Your English has gotten a lot better.
- Right?
- You can fully communicate with him.
- He's almost a native speaker.
- I know, right?
- Anyone can do it.
I'll teach you some English
next time, Si Eon.
Si Eon, do you know what
"Like a Friend" means?
- "Like a Friend."
(A trio song, "Like a Friend")
(I like a friend.)
(No, just like a friend.)
(Kian84 made everyone laugh
with the wrong translation.)
Si Eon, do you know what
"Like a Friend" means?
- "Like a Friend."
- I like you?
- It's the same answer.
- You've got a strong opponent.
- They're the same.
- Am I wrong?
- They sure are friends.
- "Like a Friend."
- You two are like a friend.
I like you.
- Isn't that what it means?
- These two are like a friend.
- What does it mean?
- Just like a friend.
I see.
(True best friends)
(Continuously driving...)
(deep into the Blue Mountains)
- So I park here.
- Okay.
Then we walk up.
This is the parking lot.
- I see.
- Yes.
Thank you for driving us.
So when you see Blue Mountain Coffee,
it's these.
These are green now.
- When they ripen,
- Yes?
- they become red.
- Red.
- Do you harvest when it's red?
- Yes.
- You harvest when it's red.
- Oh, my.
He grows coffee in his front yard.
So that's the coffee plant.
Blue Mountain Coffee
is one of the world's top three coffees.
They're also called the King of Coffee.
- One of the world's top three. I see.
- It's one of the world's top three.
It's grown in high-altitude areas
with abundant soil moisture,
which gives the beans
a rich flavor and aroma.
(It's famous for its smooth flavor
with no bitterness.)
- That's...
- I wonder how it smells.
What season catch?
What's... By September.
- Do you harvest in September?
- Yes.
- In September.
- I see.
(On the way, he also
checked out some coffee.)
School of Vision?
- There is school?
- Yes.
- School of Vision.
- Wow.
Rasta Camp.
- Rasta Camp.
- Rasta.
I thought it was a school
but it was a camp.
You get to experience
the Rastafarian life.
It's like the Cheonghak-dong Village,
- or a temple experience.
- A temple retreat!
I think it's something
like a temple retreat.
Rasta Camp.
- Yes.
- Rasta Camp. Yes.
Yes, so you're now climbing 700 steps.
- Seven hundred steps?
- Seven hundred steps from here.
It's not bad. It's 70 steps.
That's not bad at all.
You're fit.
The air feels fresh.
(He starts with a huge misunderstanding.)
This is the track to my home.
Your home. Thank you.
Joseph, are you 46?
- I'm 49.
- Oh, 49.
- Forty-nine.
- My goodness.
He was older than I thought.
He looked so young.
He's a big brother.
(As he continues to hike diligently)
(Amazed)
(Something makes him laugh.)
- My gosh.
- Beautiful.
Very beautiful.
- Way over there is where I live.
- It's gorgeous.
When we go up, we will see better.
- My gosh. It's wonderful.
- Yes.
(Setting off again after a short break)
(Breathing heavily)
(Gasping for air)
It feels like Porphy...
(Breathing heavily)
This reminds me of his home.
(He was deceived when Porphy said
it would take just ten minutes.)
He said it would only take ten minutes.
- But I walked for an hour.
- You're right.
Let's take a break.
(That day when he laid down
on the endless mountain path.)
People living in the mountains
always say it'll take less time.
(I agree)
(Panting continuously)
(Sweat glands are widely open)
Tired?
No. No tired.
I found the cameraman so I'm...
I'm power.
Okay. So this is our farm.
- Yes.
- These are raspberries.
- Oh, raspberries.
- Yes.
- Oh, yes.
- Do you want to see them?
- What?
- Raspberry.
Why is the color different?
Because this isn't ripe yet. This is ripe.
It's ripe.
- So you can eat that.
- Kian84 understands everything.
- I improved a lot.
- How did you understand "ripe?"
- What?
- How did you understand it?
- He spoke in English.
- The color was different.
I see.
- The color changes when it's ripe.
- That's true.
(Are there red beans in the bread?)
(Around 50 minutes)
(It's 50 minutes?)
(It's 15 minutes)
(They have a history
of misunderstandings.)
You should travel abroad.
You improved a bit in South America.
Yes.
Since no pesticides were used,
they eat them right away.
(It's nice)
I liked how we just picked things
and ate on our way.
I loved it.
We did that when we were young.
It's sweet and sour.
- Nice. Vitamin C!
- Raspberry.
Yaman. There's a lot of vitamin C.
Vitamin C!
- See this?
- Yes.
This is hibiscus.
- Hibiscus?
- It's good for nerves.
- Nurse?
- Nerves.
Like if you're shaking...
- Yes.
- Oh, it's good for palsy.
- How did he understand?
- Yes. It's good for your...
- Steady the nerves.
- I see.
When you eat this, your palsy will stop.
You boil it and drink like...
- Like tea.
- I should bring it for Simon Dominic.
He has shaky hands.
Oh, do I?
- Yes, Simon Dominic has a tremor.
- I guess it's gotten better nowadays.
His tremor is quite bad.
- He's always thinking of his friend.
- In Jamaica...
I should've picked some for you.
You should've.
I should tell Simon Dominic about it.
I'll tell him to come to Jamaica
and try it.
(He's only thinking
about his wife in Jamaica.)
- We'll reach soon.
- Okay.
Yes.
Oh, this?
Rasta village? Rasta communication?
- This is the Rasta Camp.
- We're here.
- Yes.
- Finally.
He truly lives in the nature.
I think they took about 1700 steps.
My goodness.
- It's nice.
- Yes.
It's nicely decorated.
It looks very nice inside.
(The three colors of Rasta,
green, yellow, and red.)
Yes. Greetings.
Nice to meet you.
- Yes.
- Nice to meet you.
- Look at their hair.
- Even the kids.
- Yes.
- My goodness.
Yes, you're...
Okay.
He needs to suck his fingers later.
Nice to meet you.
(He says hello to the kids first.)
My goodness.
This is the observation deck.
Yaman. This is a cooler spot.
- My goodness.
- Yes.
My gosh.
- So you see.
- It's an observation deck.
- After a whopping 700 steps.
- He lives at the top of the mountain.
We came from there.
That's where I met you today,
way over there in the clouds.
Gosh, the camp is huge.
It's on the top of the mountain.
(Rasta Camp)
Rasta Camp is...
where Rastas live.
It's where they continue
the culture and spirit of Rastafarianism.
(They pray together)
They pursue a natural lifestyle,
farming for themselves
and living simply...
through self-sufficiency.
This place is a community village
equipped not only with living spaces...
for its members
but also with a place of worship...
and school facilities.
(A community village
where Rastas live together)
That's amazing.
- All Rastas?
- Yaman. All Rastas.
- Only Rastas live here. Yaman.
- Yes.
See. See them here.
- This is the priest and the minister.
- Nice to meet you.
- Yaman.
- Yes.
Yes. Rasta.
- Yaman.
- Yes.
- Nice to meet you.
It seems unlikely
that Asians would normally visit.
- I think they're...
- It would be quite unfamiliar to them.
Are you all related?
Are they all your blood family?
No, spiritual family.
Spiritual family.
I thought they were blood-related,
like actual relatives, but they weren't.
He said they were a spiritual family.
They're not related by blood
but close as a family.
They're a community with strong bonds.
Some people were born and raised there,
while some joined later
after becoming a Rasta.
- Voluntarily, just like that?
- Yes.
So this is the temple.
- Temple.
- Yes.
- This is where we'll worship tonight.
- Okay.
(Rasta temple)
There are a lot of vibrant colors.
All the colors are shouting Jamaica.
This is the school.
- School?
- Yes.
- Oh, this is a school.
This is a school for the little children.
Oh, children. Yes.
- From age 3. No, from ages 2 to 6.
- Okay.
- Seriously.
- It's a kindergarten.
It's not an official school.
They're cute.
We start them off here
and send them all to...
primary school, high school,
- college, and university.
- University, yes.
This is my home.
Your home. Oh, wow.
The place looks so cool.
- I raise fish too, you know.
- Fish?
How does he raise fish
at the top of the mountain?
- Is it your pet?
- Yes.
It's cute.
These are the small ones.
(His camera enters the water again)
They're guppies!
- Are they his pet?
- They're cute.
Do you eat them?
- What?
- Yes.
But they're very small.
They're small, so I eat them
when they get bigger.
- He raises them to eat.
- He waits for them. to grow.
(They weren't pets.
They were being raised as future food.)
So this is where I live.
This is Joseph's house.
- Oh, this is your room.
- Yes.
I was curious about it.
- Thank you for inviting me here.
- You can take off your shoes and come.
- Oh, they take their shoes off.
- It's the same as Korea.
This is my home.
- Oh, my!
- Yes.
- It smells good.
- Yaman.
My wife is here.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
(She's shy)
- She's in the kitchen.
- She's cooking.
It smells delicious.
- Rice?
- Kitchen. Yes.
I like rice.
You like rice?
(He's drawn to the kitchen
by the smell of rice.)
What kind of rice is this?
- What rice?
- Turmeric rice.
- Turmeric rice?
- It looks tasty.
- Nice. Turmeric rice.
It looks delicious.
Thank you for inviting me.
Thank you very much for the invite.
They both look so kind.
- Do you want a banana?
- Yes.
- We've got a pineapple too.
- Okay.
I like bananas.
- I will eat rice.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- Yaman.
We have a pear, we have a tomato.
We have... All of these
came out from the farm.
- Your farm. Yes.
- Yaman.
- My goodness.
- He harvests.
(He has a bunch of fresh fruits
harvested in front of his house.)
It's completely self-sufficient.
They grow their food and eat it.
They cultivate everything they eat.
- They cultivated it all?
- It's all self-sufficient.
(Rastafarians maintain an organic life.)
- Jamaica tomatoes.
- Do you want some pineapple too?
- No, I'm okay.
- Okay.
Joseph is offering so many things.
(He offers everything.)
- Good. Nice.
- Nice.
(Taking a bite)
- Is this your bed?
- Yes.
If you want, you can sleep here tonight.
No.
(Laughing)
(Letting out a contagious laugh)
(Why are they laughing?)
That's just like a guest bed.
But it's still...
My wife's bed is in there.
- A big bed.
- A big bed, I see.
Since it's a house used by a couple,
I feel a bit awkward.
We have a guest house too, you know?
- A guest house?
- Yaman.
He even has a guest house?
I think it would be better
if I slept in the guest house.
(Laughing)
I wanted to spend the night there.
They had a whole house for guests,
so I asked if I could sleep there.
They could get into a quarrel,
- him and his wife.
- You never know.
"Why did you invite him?
I feel uncomfortable!"
"I cooked only for two people."
(He chooses to stay in the guest house
for the couple.)
Do you do pull-ups?
- Do you do pull-ups?
- Yes, it's my exercise.
- So you do pull-ups?
- Yes.
There was a reason why he was built.
There's a home gym here too.
I think it'll break.
Pull-up.
- You have to show him.
- Show off!
One, two,
- three,
- Nice.
four, five.
(Laughing)
I'm tired.
(You're good)
Yaman.
(His pull-up skills are quite good.)
It wasn't bad.
(Eating)
How many can you do?
Two, three.
- My gosh, five,
- Wow.
six, seven,
eight, nine, ten.
He's too good.
- My gosh. Good.
- Okay.
(He's a pull-up master.)
- You're so strong.
- Yaman.
He's like the Jamaican Dex.
You can sit down if you want.
Yes, sit down. I'm...
Come and relax, man.
(He quickly replenishes his energy
with the banana.)
- Oh, thank you.
- Yaman.
I think I’ve eaten
more fruit today than ever.
Oh, no.
No, give me. I'll throw it away for you.
You could just ask him
to throw it away for you.
Did you feel bad asking him?
Visiting his house itself was a favor.
How could I give him trash too?
It's more rude to put
the banana peel in your pocket.
- Exactly.
- It's a food waste.
But you're more hygienic now.
Of course.
- No, give me. I'll throw it away for you.
- Oh, no.
Why would he throw it away?
He puts the skin in his pocket.
(What an unusual man.)
At this hour, after six...
what do you usually do before you sleep?
We're going to celebrate in the temple.
- Okay, temple.
- Yes. We're going to the temple...
at 8 p.m. and celebrate and then...
we eat dinner together.
- So we worship at 9 p.m.
- Yes.
Then I'll go to the guest house.
I'll unpack my bag there.
All right. No problem.
See you soon.
- All right.
- See you soon.
Take it out and leave it here, please.
All right. We're going to
your guest house. Come.
My gosh. Big natural!
Yes, man. We used to have
a tree house here.
But because of the hurricane...
- Hurricane.
- The hurricane blew it away.
- My goodness.
Yes, this is the guest house.
Is that the guest house?
It would've been nice
if there were people from other countries.
But it was only me.
This is where you'll stay tonight.
- Oh, yes. Thank you!
- Yaman.
There's a lot inside.
There's no electricity here.
Oh, thank you.
Is there no electricity?
Yes, we have solar.
A solar generator.
- Yes.
- There's no electricity.
Shall we meet at 8 p.m.?
- Yaman.
- I'll take a short break.
- Yaman, that's it. All right.
- Yes.
(Waving)
Tired man. All right.
(Screaming)
(Groaning)
He's exhausted.
(Laughing)
(He takes a short break
to charge his energy.)
(Before he knew it, the sun had set.)
(Rasta Camp has turned dark.)
(Pitch-black)
It's pitch-black.
(He's not a ghost.)
There's no light.
I've been to so many...
corners of the world.
Like floss, reaching into every nook
and cranny between the teeth.
I've traveled around many countries.
I thought about it.
(In the darkness, he goes on
a Memory Adventure by Accident.)
Porphy of Bolivia,
(My Bolivian friend, Porphy)
Porphy Junior,
Porphy's wife,
and Porphy's sister.
The guest house owners of Peru.
I remember Si Eon
who cooked seaweed soup for me.
- Mother Si Eon.
- Look at my hair.
CEO Modi.
(His Indian friend, CEO Modi)
The female CEO who wore a fried egg dress.
A fried egg.
We almost died...
camping above 4000m sea level.
- The crying monk.
- My goodness.
And the saliva monk.
He walked back to all his trips.
Yerpe and Flora of Madagascar.
He made a lot of friends.
The smiling whale...
I'm curious if it's traveling in the sea.
I remember the food we had
at Madagascar University.
We went to various places.
Maybe it's time for me to go.
I'm being reminded of all the trips.
The guest house makes you
walk back to your past.
I'd been lying there for an hour,
or maybe two hours.
There was no light and it was humid.
- It was hot.
- There were mosquitos too.
So I could only stare at the ceiling.
There's no line there.
Looking at the ceiling, I could only...
- do that alone.
- You were reminded of your trips.
I was okay yesterday, but...
being alone is lonely.
I don't think I can sleep alone here.
If it's not too impolite,
I think it'd be better to sleep on the bed
that Joseph suggested.
I think I'll see a ghost here.
(Escaping before seeing a Jamaican ghost)
The fear of being judged
was overpowered by my fear.
- Joseph?
- Yaman.
Come in. Take off your shoes.
Well, the guest house...
is very scary. Scream.
- You can sit down.
- Sorry.
- I will make you something.
- Yes.
He packed and brought his bags.
- He came back with all his things.
- He did.
He was seriously scared.
He has everything with him,
even the banana skin.
Today, I live here.
- You can stay here. Yaman.
- Thank you.
- That's okay.
- It's so scary there.
This house is very lonely.
Lonely and scream. Scared.
- Yes, scary.
- Scary.
Oh, well.
- I was so scared back there.
- So I told you to stay here.
I look ghost!
(I saw a ghost!)
- So you can sit down.
- Sorry.
I will make you something.
I will make you some juice
and guacamole with avocado.
Guacamole is delicious.
(He's making a snack for Coward84.)
He's using fruits again. Okay.
This is the peach
we got from the waterfall.
- Oh, from the waterfall.
- Is it a peach juice?
- My gosh.
- I bet it was really fresh.
(Grinding with water in the mixer)
I think the main food there is fruits
instead of carbohydrates.
Seriously, they only eat fruits.
Yes, only fruits.
- Plenty of vitamin C.
- Seriously.
He's putting in ginger too.
With peach and star fruit...
- Ginger.
- Star fruit?
Is that a star fruit?
It's a tropical fruit
that looks like a Korean melon.
As it gets ripe, it becomes sweet.
- It looks pretty.
- It does.
You can taste it.
- Eat it?
- Yes, eat it.
It's unusual.
It tastes like a tangerine.
I grow that right here.
(A finely blended, truly organic juice)
Is there anything I can help?
(He wipes it down.)
Wife? Here?
- What's your name?
- Lisa.
- Lisa, yes.
- Lisa?
You have the same name
as Lisa from BLACKPINK. You know?
Why would you mention BLACKPINK there?
My goodness.
- Lisa!
- Lisa.
- Does he know?
- No.
Finding common ground.
Wash your hands. Wash your hands first.
Crush this.
- This is where you will crush...
- Okay.
- the guacamole.
- It's avocado.
- Avocado. It was light and clean.
- This is tomato and onion.
- Yes.
- That's nice.
- It's delicious.
- Did he harvest those himself?
- Yes.
There's no need
to purchase groceries then.
That looks delicious.
(He adds various spices like an expert.)
(Satisfied)
(While Joseph
quickly prepares the food...)
So he puts that on top of it.
(Well...)
Aren't we not having rice today?
- No rice?
- She was cooking turmeric rice earlier.
He didn't serve that to me.
We're going to eat rice later.
- Tomorrow?
- Yes, when we come back from chanting.
- Okay.
- Oh, later.
I'll digest this really fast.
He looks pale.
He thought they were going to eat...
- the next day.
- He looks so thin.
I only ate fruits. That drove me crazy.
I felt a sour taste.
- But your face looks better.
- It does look better.
You eat a lot of food like me.
(So please give me some rice.)
(Glancing)
Joseph is amazing.
He's vegan and he only eats fish...
but he has such a good body.
(Natural-made muscles)
(Feeling shy)
- This is for you.
- Okay.
(Fruit juice as well)
Thank you.
- You can sit.
- Fruit juice.
This really is the vegan life.
(He drinks juice first.)
It tastes good.
Thank you.
What about your wife?
Jennie?
- Jennie?
- Did you eat?
- It's Lisa.
- Come on.
Lisa became Jennie.
He gave them new names.
(Laughing)
- Lisa.
- Oh, Lisa.
I'm sorry.
Lisa.
Do you have a girlfriend named Jennie?
- No.
(Jennie is just...)
(someone who he's always proud of.)
(A phone friend who he talked to
on the phone just once.)
Right.
(That's funny)
Thank you for the food.
Thank you.
Let's eat together, Lisa.
(He tries the guacamole first.)
- Do you like it?
- It's delicious.
Come and try this.
(Sweet Joseph cares about his wife.)
(Enjoying)
(Hold on)
Spicy. It's very spicy.
It's cayenne pepper.
Cayenne pepper...
is cultivated in subtropical regions
of Central and South America.
It's much spicier
than Korean chili pepper.
(I eat it often.)
(Coughing)
(The spicy taste came up.)
Is it...
(Coughing)
- The cayenne pepper is hot.
- Cayenne pepper.
You put in too much, right?
(Coughing)
- Gosh.
- Doesn't he eat that every day?
He put in too much.
- He's crying.
- Cayenne pepper...
(Coughing)
Sorry.
(I can't help it.)
I thought he added a lot
because he liked spicy food.
(Eating)
(He's at peace alone.)
(He comes back with a towel.)
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
(Laughing)
Man.
That pepper...
It's my time.
The one by the waterfall was your time.
(Laughing)
We took a shower together.
- Water.
- Yes.
I lost my camera.
And Joseph...
used his hair...
to fish it out.
(Joseph fished it with his hair.)
- Hair fishing.
- She understood.
Yes. He said it right.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
(Laughing)
She burst into laughter.
(Why...)
Why does she like it so much?
You're having fun.
(He fished out the camera.)
(Falling behind)
She's reacting so well.
Seriously.
It's nice to hear her laugh.
It's nice that she's laughing
when it wasn't such a funny story.
I bet you were content.
(Joseph and Lisa laugh a lot.)
(He also laughs with them.)
How long have you been married?
Eight years.
- Eight?
- Yes.
Forty years? Where did you two meet?
We met at Nyabinghi.
We met there.
Oh, yes?
Did you make a move?
Did you make the first move?
She did.
He understands everything.
(He understands Kian84's English.)
I think she should tell the story.
Let her tell you the story.
Well.
A bus came,
and I saw him come out of the bus.
He came out of the bus and stood up.
(Standing up)
He's tall.
- Yes, like King Kong.
- King Kong.
(King Kong Joseph
who Lisa fell in love with)
It makes sense.
(Muscular)
Like...
- Like King Kong.
- King Kong.
I was like...
- Right.
- The's the one.
(I like him.)
That was it.
She told the story very well.
Wow. Congratulations.
Even today, he's still my King Kong.
I can feel the love.
- He's feeling the spice.
- He keeps wiping his face.
- King Kong is feeling the spice.
- He keeps crying and drooling.
(Laughing)
Sweet.
Sweet King Kong.
(Laughing)
This is crazy.
She's enjoying it so much.
Lisa is driving me crazy.
Joseph's house was interesting.
My grandparent's house
was in Taehwa-dong, Ulsan.
I could smell the Ulsan house smell
from there.
There's a scent
that Gyeongsang-do houses have.
The smell of wardrobes
of Gyeongsang-do grandmothers.
- You smelled that there?
- Yes.
Was it not the smell of the banana peel
inside your pocket?
(Was that what it was?)
Well...
Seeing them laugh made me laugh.
It was very humane.
You were in an unfamiliar place,
but it didn't feel unfamiliar.
- That's right.
- Right, the cozy sensation.
- Yaman.
That's Jamaican people's favorite word.
"Yaman."
- Yaman.
- What's yaman?
- What does it mean?
- Something like "good."
They pronounce "man" like that.
It uses "yes," so it's yaman?
- What does it mean?
- It means everything is okay.
- Everything is okay.
- It's a positive word.
- Right.
- Yaman.
This is yaman.
(The guacamole is nice!)
We should go.
It's time to go. Let me get dressed.
- It's time.
- I'll come back soon. I'll get dressed.
Shouldn't I change into better clothes
if we're going to a service?
(He quickly got changed.)
- Hold on.
- What's that?
He looks hip no matter what he wears.
That's cool.
He wore white clothes.
(He wore white clothes.)
You're a fashionista.
Let's get the clothes.
It looks cool.
Fashionista King Kong.
- Fashion show model.
- He looks good.
- Ready to go?
- Okay. I'm ready.
They always have service in the evenings.
It's the most important ritual...
for the Rastafarians.
I'm quite interested...
in religious things like funerals.
Right, you went last time too.
I told him I wanted to see it,
and I went with him.
- We're going into the temple now.
- Okay.
(They enter the temple.)
There are lots of people.
Take off your shoes and your socks.
- Barefoot? This place...
- He became very serious.
Yes.
They're all wearing white clothes.
Have a seat.
(The Rastafarians show their respect
by wearing white clothes.)
They can only wear white clothes.
Everyone in the village had gathered.
- This is the big man.
- The big man.
That's the priest.
He's the one who officiates everything.
The priest.
- Thank you for having us.
- You're welcome.
(He greets him and enters.)
Bless all.
(They're all happy
even in the reverent atmosphere.)
It's not a heavy atmosphere.
There's a red carpet.
(There is a mysterious red carpet...)
(and a bonfire burning next to it.)
They light it before they pray.
It's a spiritual fire.
This fire purifies the atmosphere.
I see.
The temple was like a ssireum stadium.
You had to go barefoot.
That was interesting.
They had lit up a bonfire,
and they were all dressed in white too.
I was excited about experiencing...
a new culture.
(Excited about the new culture)
I should at least wear a white shirt.
(Looking around)
(He follows the dress code
out of courtesy.)
I'll keep Buddha away for now.
(Putting the Buddhist
prayer beads on his wrist.)
(Chanting)
(The service begins
with the priest's chant.)
(Standing up)
(Jah! Rastafari.)
(They start praying rapidly
in a mysterious language.)
(He can't dare to interrupt it
in this atmosphere.)
(Gulping)
It's about thanking their god
and nature...
and returning to nature.
It was something like that.
(After offering their thanks,)
(they all stand up.)
What?
What's going on?
(As soon as the prayer ends,)
(they play the drums from everywhere.)
Oh, my.
(Part 2 of the service begins with music.)
That's amazing.
(What is going on?)
(The music gets louder.)
Is this a hymn?
It doesn't sound like reggae.
It's Nyabinghi.
(This is Nyabinghi music.)
Nyabinghi?
Nyabinghi is music created
by striking three drums...
of different sizes and tones
to produce rhythm.
Rooted in Rastafarian culture, which
emphasizes living in harmony with nature,
it is said to be the first form
of Rastafarian music.
It's so primitive to make music
only with drum sounds.
Yes.
This is cool.
(Spotting a cool boy believer)
(Carefree)
He's groovy.
(Finding him cute)
(Let me try it too.)
(He's motivated by the boy believer
to try dancing.)
(The foreigner's dance
brings joy to everyone else.)
(Dancing hard)
(They've all become one.)
The deeper I get involved
with other cultures,
the more I realize
that they have their own religions.
Looking back at all the other cultures
in the series,
half of them are shamanism and praying.
Half of the show is practically me
filming "Exhuma."
It's like "Praying by Accident."
I've always been praying.
(The prayer expert is on
"Praying by Accident.")
The reason
that they're always praying is...
that they're trying to find
peace of mind...
by having religious ceremonies...
in their tough and difficult lives.
(They want to find peace of mind
through religion.)
I'm sure it's the same for everyone.
(Won't we all feel the same?)
He's right.
- It runs through the whole series.
- Right.
(If you get to know them,
they all have the same nature.)
(And this foreigner
shows his respect within them.)
(A dance of respect)
(He's passionate enough
to sing the lyrics too.)
I also wanted to be possessed,
- so I was focused.
- "Possessed?"
Squats.
(Showing respect to their culture
with his whole body)
This is how we worship.
(Proud)
This is where reggae music...
- originated from.
- I see.
(Nyabinghi is the root of reggae,
the music of nature and healing.)
- This is...
- Yes.
- This music frees us in nature.
- "Free."
- Yes.
I love it.
- I can see that, man.
- Yes.
We'll all return to nature, after all.
I'm starting to feel holy.
I'm getting that holy energy.
With this holy energy...
Please bring success to Teo.
Bring success to Pani as well.
Bring success to Dex and Si Eon.
Bring success to everyone.
He even prayed for us.
Now...
(He tries the drum too.)
Get rid of Simon's hand tremor!
My hand tremor?
He even wished for his friend's health.
And Do Yeon.
Please find her a good man.
- Another good energy.
- Yaman.
And Seung Hoon.
Make his new album successful.
Thank you.
I hope your song, "Dandelion,"
is also a success.
(He blesses everyone with all his heart.)
When I was singing death metal,
I told them to die.
(Simon, Do Yeon, Seung Hoon,
Si Eon, and Pani.)
(Die!)
"Die?"
Why?
He cursed us when he was in the US!
(Sorry about that.)
If you keep listening to Nyabinghi,
it somehow relaxes you.
It sings about happiness and not worrying.
It relaxed me for some reason.
I danced and prayed with them
for about 50 minutes there,
and I hoped...
for everyone's success.
It relaxes your body and mind,
so it's almost felt like eating food
without flavor enhancers.
That's how it felt.
That was the best part of the trip for me.
(It's the type of music he needed
at the end of his long trip.)
Thank you for letting me...
get here safely and soundly.
Goodness.
(Offering blessing and thanks)
Rastafari!
(The foreigner's Rasta worship ends.)
Yes.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
From Joseph's point of view,
he must've been thankful...
- that a foreigner was...
- He showed respect.
showing respect for his religion.
Blessings to you.
(The Rastafarian night grows deeper.)
We need something to eat, no?
Eat?
- Finally. It's dinnertime.
- Dinnertime.
- Dinnertime?
- Food!
- Yes.
- Okay.
Dinner together? Here?
Oh, wow.
Oh, that was food for everyone.
- We share our food here.
- This.
Yes. Those are veggie chunks.
- Okay.
- Veggie chunks.
It looks like meat, but it's not meat.
It was soy meat.
Oh, soy meat.
That looks delicious.
It looks like actual meat.
I bet it was similar to what you had
back in India.
- Yes.
- That looks good.
- Let's go.
(A short prayer for the meal)
Okay.
(Nom)
(What do you think?)
Texas beef.
It's the same as Texas beef.
- Did it taste the same?
- You like it?
I like it.
I didn't really crave meat...
as I had that.
(Cleaning the plate)
- Delicious.
- Yes.
You only eat vegetables,
but you don't have a problem...
- with getting big?
- No problem.
Working on the farm, building things,
going down the hill,
and bringing up stuff...
Right.
You'd naturally get in shape
if you farm on a mountain.
The farming muscles.
Yes, it comes from everyday life.
When you're barefoot in the sand,
- you become one with the earth.
- Oh, they walk around barefoot.
- A lot of people walk barefoot nowadays.
- It heals you.
I see.
That's why I like going barefoot.
I like floors.
- I always eat on the floor too.
- Yaman.
- Goodness.
- They're connected.
(They have a lot in common.)
All you need is will.
(Laughing hysterically)
Good.
I hear Lisa's laughter.
(Now, he can tell from her laughter.)
She's got a huge presence.
(Lisa's laughter...)
(makes him laugh too.)
Laughter is contagious, after all.
(The laughter epidemic)
Any juice?
Water. Crystal punch.
- What's crystal punch?
- It's water.
There's a spring water.
- Natural spring water.
- It's mineral water.
They call water from mineral springs
crystal punch.
That's a cool name.
Do you also have a beer?
- "Beer?"
- I doubt that they have beer.
Not beer yet.
Okay. Sorry.
You can't drink and eat food
at the same time there.
- Oh, you can't drink while eating?
- Really?
That's unacceptable for Rastas.
I guess they do have alcohol, at least.
Oh, the service hasn't ended.
When we go home after this,
we can have beer.
I see. We can drink at home.
It's still a holy service.
Yes.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
- Crystal punch?
- Crystal punch.
(Drinking)
Isn't it nice?
- Is this spring water?
- Yes.
- From a mineral spring? It's good.
It wasn't kept in the fridge.
(It's not beer, but he's satisfied.)
- Delicious.
- Yes.
He cleaned the plate.
He's a big eater.
Thank you for the food.
I'm sure I'll sleep well tonight.
(Feeling full)
- Here's your beer.
- Thank you.
- Beer!
(Drink up, pal.)
I'll go and get some rest, then.
- Yes. If you're ready, we can go.
- Yes.
(He goes home with a beer in his arms.)
- Thank you, Joseph.
- Yaman.
Now,
it's my last night here.
Today was...
a dreamy experience.
Meeting Teo...
feels like ages ago.
- I bet it did.
- On his last night...
They were only apart for a day.
Be safe out there.
(His day began with a nonchalant goodbye
with the brothers.)
(And he met new people...)
(and new experiences.)
I can't help but think about
how well he adapts to all cultures.
The world is expansive,
and it's full of things to experience.
That's what I'm thinking...
(He filled a whole page of memories
in one day.)
before going to bed on my last night.
(Let's hope for a new day and good night!)
I hope there aren't too many mosquitoes.
(Scratching)
- Oh, no.
- He can't sleep?
- The mosquitoes.
These darn mosquitoes.
- Were they buzzing in your ears?
- Yes.
- In the summer...
- I hate that.
- It drives you insane.
- Can't he do anything about that?
Kian84.
(Ta-da)
- Oh, he brought the net.
- Goodness.
Thank you.
Joseph is installing
a mosquito net for me.
He's such a good friend.
He came and set it up?
He must have been tired,
but he got up for me.
Thank you, Joseph!
- What a nice man.
- He's very warm-hearted.
When was the last time
I slept in a mosquito net?
I'm deeply indebted.
(Feeling bad)
I'm so thankful for Joseph.
He got up and set up
a whole mosquito net for me.
But more importantly,
the mosquitoes came through the net.
- Mountain mosquitoes are tougher.
- I still got bitten.
I'm sure one of them
was locked up in the net.
No, I think it was ripped.
I'm still thankful for the gesture.
Whether I was bitten or not
doesn't matter.
What matters is that Joseph came
and set it up for me while he was tired.
He keeps scratching.
- Thank you, Joseph.
- Here you go.
Yes. Thank you.
I'll go to sleep now.
(His day ends
with the mosquito net of love.)
(The bright sun rises,)
(and the animals have already
started their days.)
It's a morning in the wild.
It finally feels like we're watching
"Adventure by Accident."
(Jamaican morning is full
of nature sounds.)
(Waking up)
(He busily greets the morning.)
(He furiously brushes his teeth
with his eyes closed, as always.)
(Rummaging through)
(Carefully taking out his yellow socks)
(Sniffing)
He smells his socks first.
(He checks them
and irons them with his hands.)
(Good to go)
(His socks may be yellow,
but not his teeth.)
(He brushes his teeth
after a long time...)
(and organizes his bed.)
- He even cleaned up.
- He made the bed.
(Dazed)
(While he was busily moving around
in the morning,)
(Joseph approaches him
with something in his hands.)
- Work gloves.
- Yes.
Even their work gloves have
Jamaican colors.
(Rummaging)
(A big knife?)
Where are they off to?
You look pretty cool.
(A cool worker of the day)
- We're going to the banana farm?
- Yes.
Oh, bananas.
- Then, I can go...
- sweep with me...
- Okay.
- and do some stuff on the farm.
It's hot in the afternoon,
- so they work in the morning.
- That's right.
If I can help you...
- Yes, you're going to help me.
- Okay.
They fed me,
so the least I could do was help.
Right, with the farm.
Give me this. I have to use it.
- Take your time.
- Okay.
Take your time.
Why?
It's too steep.
There aren't even any trails.
It's not even flat.
They should break a trail
before they farm.
It's too rough.
That's the farm?
- It's practically a gym.
- A gym?
It looks tougher to work than in Amazon.
It was at least flat in Amazon.
- Make your step.
- Okay.
That looks tough.
It's a gym in the mountains.
Uphill and downhill were 45 degrees...
It wasn't even 45 degrees.
His farm was on an actual cliff.
That's too dangerous. No!
- I had to stay alert.
- Careful.
(After a steep slope...)
Gosh, the mosquitoes...
And mosquitoes?
- Mountain mosquitoes are tough.
- These mosquitoes.
Mountain mosquitoes.
I shouldn't have worn shorts.
(His day at Joseph's farm
is off to a rocky start.)
The gloves have holes.
(A cliff mountain)
- You okay?
- I'm okay.
All right.
So, you're going to weed out here.
- Here?
- Yes.
(His job is weeding.)
- That's...
- Aren't those all weeds?
- How would he handpick all of them?
- He wanted me to pull all of them.
Yes, go up more.
(Grunting)
The roots are long.
Go up more.
(He pulls from higher,
but it's not enough.)
(Shouting)
(Struggling)
These weeds have such long roots.
You would naturally gain muscles there.
- You all right?
- All right.
(While he's fighting the weeds...)
Joseph pulls them as if they're tissues.
(He's got a whole bundle.)
When you're finished,
you're going to be strong.
- Okay.
- Yes.
This is a Rastaman's exercise.
Like going to the gym.
I like...
(Ragged)
He's tired.
Poor him.
(I was once a warrior.)
- Oh, no.
(Joseph is still dominating the weeds.)
(The true warrior never gets weary.)
He doesn't even look tired.
Joseph has to be in good shape...
because he's doing deadlifts...
- while he pulls the weeds.
- "Deadlifts."
He's constantly doing squats.
His stamina... And he's muscular.
(The alpha in the area)
Oh, hey, look here.
- Yes?
- Kian84, look here.
(What is it?)
(Even Joseph struggles)
I guess something is stuck.
(What on earth is it?)
What is it?
(What's the tough one
that's making Joseph struggle?)
Oh, my gosh.
What is it?
- Oh, goodness.
- What is it?
Cassava!
(A giant cassava)
(It's enormous.)
- Look at the size.
- I've tried that in potato chips.
- Right. They're so tasty.
- I love them.
(Thrilled)
(Glancing)
He spotted another one.
One minute.
(Where are you going?)
(Dashing)
What?
Careful.
(He went all the way down here.)
(Pulling)
Oh, it's a pineapple.
He got a pineapple.
(He ran downhill for this pineapple.)
(Precious)
(He proudly comes back.)
Pineapple again.
(He runs as soon as he spots one.)
He's practically a squirrel.
(As fast as a squirrel)
(Collecting one)
(Cheering)
(A handful of pineapples)
(He keeps looking around
even as he climbs down.)
He must have found another one.
(Turning into a squirrel)
He's busy.
(Wherever the fruit is, he runs over.)
(It's not over yet?)
- Oh, he climbs a tree like that?
- Oh, my.
He must be so muscular.
- Ethiopian apple.
- An apple?
Yes.
(His jaws drop.)
He should be competing in the UFC.
(He's physically and mentally prepared
for the UFC.)
(Throwing)
(He eats the harvested fruits
on the spot.)
- He eats it right away.
- I wonder what it tastes like.
(Kian84 also takes a big bite.)
It wasn't exactly an apple.
- What did it taste like?
- Like a fig.
(Bringing the pineapple
he picked up earlier)
- You want something to eat?
- Sure.
(He cuts it with his long knife.)
- He cuts and eats it on the spot.
- I'm sure that tasted good.
Thank you, Joseph.
(Slurping)
- It sounds so juicy.
- I'm drooling.
It's sweet.
It's good.
(Slurping)
That was the best one I've had
in the US and Jamaica combined.
- That pineapple?
- It was incredibly sweet.
It was sugar itself.
It's good. I won't starve to death here.
Everything grows here.
Isn't an avocado like 5,000 won in Korea?
Those avocados grow here.
I've seen mangoes,
bananas, and pineapples grow here.
They've got everything.
Money grows from their soil.
There's a whole fruit aisle
from Emart over there,
and a fruit aisle from Homeplus
growing over there.
You'd be self-sufficient
with just the food that grows here.
That's incredible.
(Kian84 also finds something.)
(Reaching out)
This is a pineapple.
Yes, you can make juice.
Put it over there.
(Where is he going?)
It's itchy.
- Mosquito...
- With the pineapple?
(He scratches the mosquito bites
with the pineapple.)
- That's awesome.
- Seriously.
(This open-minded man
makes you admire him.)
All right. Leave that
and grab your machete.
Okay.
(They climb down with both hands full.)
- Nice work.
- Nice.
(No, they climb up with both hands full.)
(Kian84 repaid their kindness.)
- Put it over here.
- Okay.
It looks like he caught a pig.
Are you sure that's not alive?
(It's not alive, is it?)
- Put it over here.
- Okay.
(Sweating buckets)
(Though he's tired,
he peels the fruits right away.)
It looks like a human leg.
(The fruits fill the basket.)
He cooks a meal with only fruits.
(A full basket)
(Scoffing)
Those were fruits for that day.
(Welp)
- You look very excited.
- Good for you.
You only get rice for dinner.
Rice is rare over there.
(A happy fruity life)
(They come back home after morning work.)
(A full basket)
(He puts the freshly harvested basket
in the kitchen.)
Oh, yes.
(He nonchalantly tosses the towel.)
(And something catches his eye.)
(A cat)
There was a cat.
Your pet?
- Your pet?
- What?
He said, "Fat."
Yes, our cat.
He still understands.
(He understood perfectly.)
(It scurries outside...)
- Oh, there are a lot.
- Oh, my.
- It reminded me of my cat.
- They look alike.
Go and eat some fish.
(He's worried that the cat
might be starving.)
(He gets changed...)
(and quenches his thirst.)
(After some time to get organized,)
(Joseph prepares breakfast.)
(He turns on the stove first.)
(Looking for something)
(Getting the enormous cassava)
Oh, the cassava.
(Breakfast made
with freshly harvested ingredients)
I know it tastes good.
(Breakfast made
with freshly harvested ingredients)
(Let's see)
(He thinks while trimming
the ingredients.)
What?
(Turning on music)
It's reggae.
(With the song playing,)
(he grooves.)
(This man of excitement
can't stand silence.)
(He peels the ingredients
while humming his work song.)
(The pot is full.)
It's a fruit party!
(Putting them straight into boiling water)
Are those bananas that he's boiling?
- What was it? Plantain?
- Plantain.
Oh, they weren't bananas.
(The chopped vegetables...)
(go straight into a frying pan.)
(Adding various spices)
(Stir-fry them and they're ready to go.)
- That looks good.
- It looks like Thai papaya salad.
(Tasting it)
(That's good)
(It tastes good!)
- He's dancing by himself?
- He must like it.
(He expresses the taste
with his dance moves.)
He was having this much fun by himself?
(Fascinated)
(Humming)
(Enjoying the taste,)
(the dance machine has fun
in the kitchen for a while.)
He finds fun in whatever he does.
(Checking the food every once in a while)
(He follows the music into the kitchen.)
What's good?
(He's almost done cooking.)
Oh, he boiled them.
Wow.
- Nice.
- That looks good.
(A local dish made
with natural ingredients and care)
(He smells it first.)
It smells good.
Gosh.
Good.
This is chocolate tea.
- Chocolate?
- Yes.
- Chocolate!
(Chocolate tea to raise
the blood sugar level)
That has to taste good.
(He takes them outside.)
(Getting his favorite speaker)
(He follows Kian84.)
Let's go.
(Off to have breakfast)
(Following the trail outside of his house)
He's so full of excitement.
(He hums as he moves.)
- Hey.
- Hi.
(They arrive at the table in no time.)
Great.
(He admires the place
as soon as he arrives.)
(Halfway up the Blue Mountain)
That's a great view.
(You can enjoy the green nature.)
(Made of healthy ingredients
that they picked themselves)
Delicious food.
(A vegetarian meal made with care)
They have a big breakfast
only with vegetables.
- Thank you for the food.
- Yes.
Thank you.
Nice.
(He tastes the chocolate tea first.)
I wonder what it tastes like.
(Another sip)
(What do you think?)
This is good. This is amazing.
Yaman.
Is this made of stuff you farmed here?
With actual cacao?
(He ground cacao that he farmed...)
(and boiled it with other spices.)
- That looks really good!
- That was so tasty.
This is cassava...
- Cassava?
- Yes.
(Telling him he cooked
the cassava that he picked)
I know what cassava is.
And plantain...
There's a legendary food made of cassava.
(Chewing)
(Spitting)
(Dizzy)
(The legendary drink, masato,
made from chewing fermented cassava)
The shock must still be vivid to you.
I still won't be able to drink that.
I've never tried cassava
that's not in masato.
(How does cassava taste in a solid state?)
(What do you think?)
(It's good!)
(Enjoying the taste with a frown)
(Enjoying the taste with his beard)
- Do you like it?
- Yes, I like it.
That's good.
(They enjoy the meal
by using all their senses.)
It tasted like chewy and moist potatoes.
That must be good.
(Shooing away)
He's so sweet.
(He's sweet enough to shoo away flies.)
(Thanks to him,
Kian84 gets to enjoy the veggies.)
- Plantain?
- Yes.
(Plantain)
(He sees Kian84 enjoy the food,)
(and he's pleased.)
That's good.
(Gobbling up)
(He's starting to feel full.)
(Rustling)
(Joseph takes something out.)
(What is it?)
(He keeps wriggling his fingers.)
What?
(Without a word,
he puts a bracelet on Kian84.)
He got a gift for you!
(A little gift for Kian84 before leaving)
It's a gift for you.
So you can remember Rastafari.
(He laughs it off.)
(Kian84 takes some time to think.)
Shalom?
(What?)
- Was it Shalom?
- Shalom. Peace.
Just like that?
Your name?
(He already forgot his friend's name.)
Don't tell me you forgot!
- Your name?
- Joseph.
Joseph.
(He's Joseph, not Shalom.)
Was Shalom the one in the Amazon?
Joseph?
- No problem.
- Yes. No problem.
- Thank you.
(He forgives him right away.)
His name was Joseph,
but I called him Rothman
all day on the first day.
(Yes, I'm Joseph.)
(He clearly said his name was Joseph
on the first day.)
(Rothman!)
(What?)
Rothman?
(He called him Rothman all day.)
Joseph must have thought
he was saying, "Yaman."
I asked him again,
and his name turned out to be Joseph.
(He finally figured out the name
right before his leave.)
But...
Joseph?
I have a present...
(Actually, I also have a present for you.)
- I have a present for you.
- What?
- Let's go.
- Alright.
Do we go this way?
(He just follows Kian84.)
Lisa, come over here.
(He has a present for Lisa too?)
- Oh, Lisa.
- Yes?
This is...
I feel a bit shy. This is...
As I wish you two happiness,
I drew a picture of a happy family.
This is it.
- This is...
- That looks so cool!
(Laughing)
(Look at this)
- He drew you so well.
- Yes.
It looks exactly like her.
(While Joseph was cooking breakfast,)
(he was drawing a picture of them
to express his gratitude.)
That is awesome.
(Recalling the time
he spent with the couple,)
(he drew them with sincerity.)
He's smiling while drawing it.
(Oh, my)
I'm sorry, Lisa.
Your face looks bigger here.
- Because I couldn't check...
- No problem.
the details while drawing.
- So, here you are.
- It looks nice, man.
- Yes.
- But the letter, "e..."
- What's wrong?
- Something's wrong?
The spelling is incorrect.
It's "Joseph."
The letter should stand on the other word.
(He got the wrong spelling of theirs.)
- This is...
- This "e" should stand here.
- Here...
- I mean, this "e."
It should move to here.
Joseph will probably tell others,
"There was a fool from Korea."
"He wrote the wrong spelling
while drawing."
- "But he was good at drawing."
- "He was talented, at least."
This "e" should stand here.
This is love!
"This is love!"
There's a meaning to it.
Love will be mixed together.
- This is my sign.
- Yes.
Even your beard looks like a heart.
- Love.
- Yes, the love.
It truly has some details.
- Thank you.
- It looks nice.
Thank you.
I'm not going to wear it.
I will frame it and put it in the house.
Oh, thank you.
- Thanks a lot.
- Thanks.
(She sees it one more time)
May your family be full of love
and prosperity.
- You too.
- Now I see...
why G-Dragon does this gesture.
It became my habit as I stayed abroad.
- Thanks.
- They do it too.
Yaman.
(It suddenly became a ceremonial time
to put their hands.)
You can come again.
You don't need to bring a camera.
Just come and make yourself at home.
- I got it. No camera.
- That's it.
- But I need the camera for YouTube.
- Okay.
It seems like Joseph
finds his peace at home.
They keep away from capitalism,
and they live within their community.
They seemed satisfied.
The US is the strongest of all...
and has a lot
of cutting-edge technologies.
But they don't provide a restroom.
(Finding a restroom downtown
was a challenge for him.)
But in Rastafari,
it was hard to use the electricity.
My stay here was very tough.
(They never lost their smile.)
- Thank you.
- Come and try this.
I read somewhere before...
that for most of the people in the world,
family is the most important thing.
But in Korea, people answered
that money comes first.
In Bolivia, Porphy also said
family is the most important thing.
It was the same in Texas.
- Family means a lot to all, right?
- Yes.
I'm not sure if this is because
I've lived alone too long.
I'm afraid to get married.
That's...
why I'm obsessed with material things.
I'm not sure, really.
But whenever I meet someone
living in nature,
I feel what matters in our lives.
I get closer to the essence of life.
It makes me feel good,
as I realize what matters in life.
This is the greatest asset...
I've gotten through this program.
Yes, it's important to know that.
It was the same lesson there too.
I came here because of music,
but it gave me a life lesson.
Rasta, bye!
(Rasta, you gave me
an important lesson in my life. Bye!)
(After having been touched,
he heads back home.)
(The sorrow of parting
forced him to find a spot.)
This place is...
the coast that Bob Marley loved.
This is nice.
- It's the name of the beach itself?
- It's the Bob Marley Beach?
The color of the sand is black.
I've heard pelicans live here.
- I see one!
- Oh, pelicans?
Seriously?
As soon as they find a prey...
(Diving into the water)
That looks amazing.
- Gosh.
- Oh, my.
(Laughing)
Look at it!
It catches like that?
As I finish my journey here,
I will stay here,
reflecting on the last days.
There is...
a stylish desk and a chair.
As long as I can take a seat
and write something, it's okay.
(He opens his lyric notebook.)
(It's full of letters now.)
"New York,"
"Denver, and the Rocky Mountains."
(Enjoying the sea breeze,)
(he recalls his 11-day journey.)
"The fragrance of a woman,
with a German lady."
(It was an impressive memory to him.)
(Looking back on it,
the start of this journey was...)
(a piece of dream to be a singer.)
(In my yearbook, I can still see it.)
My future dream was to be a singer.
(Whenever I sing a song,)
(it still touches my soul.)
(Even after he grew up,
music touched his heart.)
(So, he started his journey
to be a singer.)
I took a look at what happened...
in the last 15 days.
First, I arrived in New York...
(He arrived in the city
full of excitement.)
(The city was not friendly to a stranger.)
Okay!
- Oh, yes. He did Cypher.
- It was very fun.
(But thanks to his brave challenge,)
(he became a part of a family
with others.)
Oh, family.
- It looks like it happened a long ago.
- Indeed.
(In a city resembling a chessboard,)
(he felt affection from the strangers...)
(and wrote his first song, "Dandelion.")
And brothers from Houston. The cowboys.
Of course, it was enjoyable
meeting the cowboys.
But for me,
watching the fully absorbed Teo...
- among them was more fun.
- He was a true cowboy.
As I watched him,
it made me feel happy too.
(Rolling)
(Falling)
(And riding)
(He experienced what it means
to be a true cowboy.)
- Look at him.
- Gosh.
(He learned their pureness and
a romantic view of life.)
- I remember it.
- The kid too.
What a nice memory.
Although it was a short trip,
it changed my life in many different ways.
And...
PKT with YHi.
- It's Yay Hi.
We three gathered together to sing a song.
We did it in a live bar.
- It was very touching.
- Yes.
I didn't expect such a nice song.
(They hung around like friends.)
(We are pure!)
(Teo's purity made them all laugh
all throughout.)
(Pani Bottle's support around the clock
became a great asset to all.)
It's like an epic story of an idol group.
That's right.
(We shined as if we were
a popular idol group.)
It's "Like a Friend."
Lastly, Joseph and Lisa.
Be happy!
Until Joseph's hair
that's like a 100-year-old wild ginseng...
becomes a 10,000-year-old one.
May their love last forever.
Thank you so much!
(Thank you, everyone!)
I started to travel
without a specific theme.
But as music became the theme,
I felt more...
than I did something new.
I found such passion and excitement
while singing.
(His journey blossomed with songs.)
That's the power of music, I think.
(From a simple trip,)
(but transformed by the magic of music...)
- The new song...
- This is your last song!
("Tornado" by Kian84)
(Dive into the storm)
(Just crash into it)
(You are a tornado now)
(You're at full speed,
colliding head-on with your dreams)
(There are no coordinates)
(You left your map behind somewhere)
(But you'll find it)
(The Oz-like world you dreamed of)
(Call for me inside the tornado)
(For you, who were full of dreams)
(Rush into it to escape your boredom)
(You are a tornado now)
(You're at full speed,
colliding head-on with your dreams)
(There are no coordinates)
(You left your map behind somewhere)
(But you'll find it)
(The lead role's life that you envisioned)
- It sounds like a theme song for a drama.
- Yes.
He didn't get to see a tornado,
but he created a song.
(From the inspiration
of chasing a tornado,)
(he wrote a song about a journey
chasing a dream.)
"You are a tornado now."
That's nice.
("Tornado" by Kian84)
Good job.
- Yes!
- I like the song.
It sounds like he opened his diary...
- and telling those words to himself.
- Yes.
I can feel your soul.
Thank you.
Actually, you get used to...
your everyday life
and get stuck in the rut.
I think a tornado
signifies a kind of fantasy.
Making music...
and traveling, as I think back,
felt like my life was trying...
to enter a tornado.
You can understand it
as escaping the daily life...
and dreaming of a life of fantasy.
(The song expresses his will
to live a life that thrills his heart.)
- Kian84 challenged himself.
- Yes.
I cheer for him, whatever he does.
- That's nice.
I was so happy to be
a part of Kian84's dream.
If he thinks he hasn't achieved enough,
as his partner in music,
I will support him in music.
You're like Joseph and Lisa.
- Yaman.
(Simon Dominic's support
reassures Kian84 already.)
Honestly, so many people helped me...
in making the songs, so I appreciate that.
I hope it doesn't remain my dream only.
I hope people will see it...
and get inspiration.
- This show made that wish come true,
- Yes.
so I can't thank you enough.
(Very thankful)
I hope those who have
a new challenge coming...
prepare it well and get a good result.
That's my wish for everyone.
Everyone, now that you're
born into this world,
I wish you could do everything you want
and enjoy everything,
and then travel to the next world.
Okay. Bye.
(Music Adventure by Accident is over.)
(We have a post-credits scene.)
- Thank you for your work.
- Thank you for your work!
(There's a post-credits scene.)
(A post-credits scene is coming soon.)
I wonder which country we'll go to
for the fourth season.
I want to go somewhere
with diverse races...
or even minority groups.
I want to go to a place
where I haven't seen at all.
That's the place I'm curious about.
Can't we go to such a place...
for the fourth season of
"Adventure by Accident?"
We can enter the country secretly.
It doesn't matter to me.
We need to find a hidden area...
where there are Indian, South American,
and African people.
(Adventure by Accident will return
in a real raw element in a hidden land!)
Dramaday.me