(What's going on?)
(The two walk to where Teo is.)
(Climbing over)
- How cool.
- You two are cool.
What are we doing next?
(The chores brought
the cowboy brothers together.)
I think we need to go in.
- "In?"
- Yes.
Yes, come on!
You two are missing out on the action.
- Come on.
- Hey! Over here, Johnny.
- Johnny!
- Jump this way. Come over this way.
Eddie. You've got to help with it.
No. I don't want to break a leg.
(There's suspense in the ranch.)
(Feeling nervous as well)
(At that moment, the calf leaves the pen.)
Jose's got it. Get in the gate.
You all can go ahead.
Hey. There you go.
- Turn it back up. Stand it back up.
- Are you okay?
- So, come up here.
- There you go.
- Like this?
- Just like that.
- Put it about midway right there.
- Right here?
Yes, perfect. Squeeze it harder.
Doing that is called tagging.
So that's tagging.
The ear tag is an identification number
attached to the cow's ear.
With the ear tag, the cow's
vaccination record and such...
can be checked.
It helps take care
of the cow's health systematically.
- Korea does that too.
- Yes.
- I saw those in Korea.
- Right?
We have to lock the cow's head in place...
to prevent it from moving
and tag it in the right place.
If not, the cow can get hurt.
That's why we had to subdue it.
Real quick.
- All right. Now get onto its head.
- Turn its head to you.
- Stand back up.
- Like this. Look.
Even if it's a calf,
I'm sure it's really strong.
- You need strength and technique.
- Right?
(Tagging complete)
(The calf can return quickly.)
(He did well
despite it being his first time.)
(He has adjusted just fine!)
(Meanwhile, the two who were watching.)
(Groaning)
(Closing his eyes tightly)
- What is it?
- Hey, you two.
Hurry.
(They hesitantly enter the pen.)
- Young lad!
- Watch your back!
Watch out, okay? It'll run into you.
- Watch it.
- It'll eat your bum.
They go out that way. You're good.
(Will I be able to do it?)
- All right. Remember. Go down the rope.
- Here?
Get on that rope, Teo.
(Running)
- Come on. Grab the tail.
- I'll try.
Come on!
(Teo got overpowered and flown off!)
(Pani Bottle takes a hit as well.)
(Struggling)
- Good grief.
- The balance.
They lost balance.
- Get it, boys.
- It's okay. Calm down.
Take it down, boys.
- Oh, no.
- The calf was really strong.
- I'm pinned under.
- Right now!
- Five men weren't enough.
- We couldn't subdue it.
- Are you okay, Teo?
- Are you okay?
- I'm good.
- Grab the back leg.
- All right.
Put this to the back leg?
- Regroup yourself.
- No.
Back leg.
Teo.
(Escaping again)
Hang on it, boys!
Don't let him go!
(Being dragged around)
Ready?
(Everyone calms it down.)
Ross. Get that front shoulder.
- Bear with it for a bit.
- Do you want to tag it?
Ross, you've got it.
Three people won't be enough.
It was extremely strong.
(The five barely tagged it.)
- Finished?
- Yes.
- Go.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Good job, guys.
- Did you get the color for the tag?
(In a daze)
We've got eight left.
(Shutting his eyes tight)
"Eight?"
- I understood why they needed help.
- Right.
- It's no joke.
- The job looks exhausting.
- That was...
- It was the main event.
Right?
Be careful of its back leg.
- If you get kicked by it...
- Teo fell down earlier.
- No, the cow overpowered him.
- Right.
And it's not like Teo is weak.
Get ready! We've got a rider.
Grab the tail.
Right in front?
(Kian84 goes after it.)
The tail.
- Get the tail.
- Be careful, Kian84.
- He's rolling on the ground.
- Careful.
There was cow dung everywhere.
- Teo's leg is under.
- It's okay. I'm still okay.
- You okay?
- Yes, I'm good.
- Yes, we're good.
- Go ahead, boys.
(Charging without hesitation)
There you go.
(Kian84 gets pinned down.)
- We need to turn its head to our side.
- This side?
(Pani Bottle is...)
Watch your legs.
(Don't overdo it, brothers!)
Good.
All right, boys. Get over here.
- Three, two, one.
- Two, one.
How are you that good
when it's your first time?
Goodness.
(Smiling despite the tough job)
(Completely synchronized as a cowboy)
After watching a demonstration,
Teo gave it a shot.
That itself was very scary.
Teo got pushed out 2 to 3 times
while catching the calves.
But...
when I saw Teo's face,
his eyes...
were like the eyes of a wolf.
- How wild.
- He's a wild horse.
At that time, Teo was a beast.
(The handsome guy crazy about cowboys)
Hang in there, boy!
(The crazy handsome cowboy)
Get ready!
We've got a rider.
(Meanwhile, he looks unwell.)
He does look unwell.
(Candy and Aeong's brother)
(An animal lover
who willingly gives his lips away)
- I can't look at it.
- It's okay.
- You don't like it?
- I saw it.
I already saw it.
I'm sorry!
Humans are sorry.
- "Humans are sorry."
- All right.
- Step back.
- Watch your back.
There you go. Double in the front.
Go. Go backwards.
That's it.
(Falling down)
All right. I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
(The animal lover apologizes.)
My heart is sick.
(My heart hurts.)
- Watch your back!
- Watch it!
(Staggering)
Putting aside how tiresome it is,
I just can't do it.
Can't we give...
the other three...
special selections?
Raise the three with...
special selections.
It was painful.
But there was no other choice.
Am I going to go vegan? No.
That's how life is.
We've been eating meat...
throughout our lives.
It's been done
for a long time historically, as well.
I've been ignoring the red pill until now
and finally faced it.
But it's because of their hard work...
that we get to eat delicious meat.
Teo understood it was livestock...
and a job.
It was surprising how fast he adapted.
That made me respect them more.
It's a mixed feeling.
Good grief. I pig out on meat,
and yet, I'm unnecessarily soft-hearted.
(A deep self-reflection)
I shouldn't pig out on them.
- Get ready, boys!
- Come here!
(The animal lover's voice changed.)
Okay. Turn over a new leaf.
Right there. Move. Get on it, boy!
- Okay.
- Hold on. Let me get it.
(Surprised by Kian84's spirit)
- That's a wild one.
- It was super strong.
(Watching for an opportunity,
then taking it down in one go)
Yes. That's it.
It's okay.
(Bear with me!)
Kian84 subdued it properly.
- He's gotten better.
- That guy.
We've got an American pitbull right here.
It's nice to have a little break.
- Hit it.
- One, two, three.
(Not a problem!)
- Nice. Good job.
- Let's go.
- Kian84 is getting better at it.
- That guy.
He doesn't know how to do it,
but he's hitting it.
Yes, he is. He ran a marathon.
- Really?
- Yes.
Help them.
(Determined to finish it
as quickly as possible)
(Grabbing)
Don't worry. It'll be over in a second.
(Patting)
We'll be done after that one.
I'll try it.
(Throwing himself onto it,
he's become a legit cowboy!)
- Hang on to it, cowboy!
- Hold on.
We'll make it quick.
(Patting)
One, two, three.
(After tagging it quickly)
- Finished?
- Yes.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Good job. Really good job.
- Everyone.
A really good job.
Yes, sir!
(He's proud but also confused.)
Kian84.
You don't need a gym here.
- I have no thoughts of hitting the gym.
- Right?
Yes.
(A mess)
You know how all the jeans...
- look like that in Texas movies?
- Yes.
It was because of that.
I thought cowboys rubbed dirt on it
on purpose.
- But it happens naturally.
- Yes.
- I was curious.
- You're bound to become dirty.
When we have a break,
let's come here to work out for a month.
- Okay.
- Teo.
- You look really happy here.
- I am happy.
(Teo is meant to be a cowboy.)
- So what time is lunch?
- Right now.
- Okay!
- Let's go.
You've got to ride a horse to the cabin.
- Lunch.
- It'll take about ten minutes.
- Yes, sir.
- Let's roll.
I don't want lunch.
- Okay.
- Put this hand here. Pull it up.
- Easy.
- Thank you.
All right, cowboys. Let's go this way.
(Heading for lunch)
(Looking back)
(Following Teo's signal)
Come on!
(Let's ride!)
(Galloping)
A little bit more. That's it. Right there.
Okay. There you go.
Yes, sir!
You're about to become a rider!
Spin him in a circle. Yes!
This is exciting.
(With speed like wild horses,)
(the cowboy brothers return
to their accommodation.)
Teo doesn't want to clear from riding.
(Attached to the horse)
- Nice.
- Teo didn't want to come down.
Good job.
(Patting)
- They've become friends.
- Here's a pork chop in a can.
- Awesome. Thank you.
- Yes.
(Quenching his thirst with a cold drink)
Nice. Cheers.
Because it's scorching hot, the cowboys...
stuff drinks in an icebox
and have them now and then.
It's delicious.
It's ice cold.
(Refreshing)
(Slamming it down right away)
- That heat makes you drink.
- Gosh, Kian84.
(Screaming)
Goodness. What a shocking taste.
- Didn't it feel like 40째C?
- It tastes sweet.
The sun was hot.
It was fine under the shade.
It most likely felt like 40째C.
(Ice arrived to cool the cowboys down.)
(Eating one)
Pani Bottle's ice-eating show.
(Grabbing)
(Washing his face with ice)
- An ice massage.
- That's good for your skin.
(Putting in)
That must've felt amazing.
Good. Yes!
Okay, ladies and gentlemen.
What we have here right now...
are some cows we worked earlier.
We've got to feed our bellies
because we just did all the work. Right?
- What?
- Are those tacos?
That's a lot of meat.
What's up for dinner?
I'm going to get some.
- Can I try a little piece?
- Yes.
(Eating)
(Licking)
It's delicious.
It's charcoal-grilled short ribs.
There's something similar in Chuncheon.
Charcoal-grilled short ribs.
Were those venison sausages?
They probably hunted
and made it themselves.
It's made with everything
grown and raised there.
- Yes.
- That's right.
(The three cowboy brothers
are taking a break.)
(Snapping)
- What's that?
- What was that?
It gets very loud.
- Gosh.
- Is it a whip?
It sounds like a gun.
You can hear the swishing
if you hear it in person.
It sounded like guns.
(What made people nervous?)
(By whipping it hard)
Cowboys threaten the animals
with the sound. They don't hit them.
- To turn the direction?
- Yes.
- Can I try?
- This is natural.
- Pani Bottle gives it a shot.
- It's hard.
(Snap)
Pull it straight down.
(Do it like this.)
I kind of figured it out.
Give it to me. I'll try.
Be careful. It's really strong.
(Kian84 gives it a go.)
I should take shelter.
- That looks scary.
- It is scary.
And it's heavy.
The Indiana Jones cowboy.
(It sounds quite right.)
There you go!
(I'll show you how cool I am.)
(Screaming)
Oh, no.
- That looks painful.
- I thought I was going to die.
Oh, no.
(Oh, my gosh)
- That must've hurt.
- Shoot.
That must've left a scar.
- I knew it.
- Not my style.
- You want some more?
This isn't my style.
"Not my style."
That's kind of South Texas brand.
(This scar)
They get you.
- That's...
- A tattoo.
South Texas branding.
Like a tattoo.
- Right.
- Like a tattoo.
I've always had a pimple there.
(Between two pimples,)
(there's a clear line.)
(In the meantime)
(The taco ingredients are ready.)
- So grab a plate.
- Oh, setting.
This.
(First meal in the cowboy farm)
Oh, that looks good.
(Toasted)
Get your tortilla and make your taco.
One, two,
- three.
- I like it.
Do you make it yourselves?
That looks good.
(You put what you like
in your cowboy taco.)
What is that? Avocado?
- Avocado.
- Chicken.
(One more piece of meat)
It's hot.
That's amazing.
- That must've been really good.
- Yes.
(Pani Bottle likes...)
It's freshly grilled.
My mouth is watering. That looks so good.
(A bite of a meat wrap)
(Exclaiming)
(Munching)
Here's your plate.
That reminds me of you
having curry in India.
(Nom)
(He still munches on his food.)
(It tastes even better after working.)
Gourmet.
(It's delicious.)
(Chewing)
Underground.
The underground water?
I wasn't going to have beef.
- It's so good.
- I ended up eating it.
- You were planning to avoid beef?
- Even before I knew...
I wasn't going to eat it at least today.
He wasn't going to have beef.
I couldn't help it when it was there.
I'm sure they enjoyed their lives.
- Don't worry.
- I ate it even before I knew it.
(Closing his eyes tightly)
Eating it again? Is it that good?
We'll meet again in the inferno.
(One day)
Gosh.
(Teo heads outside with a taco.)
(Enjoying his taco under the Texas sun)
(Exclaiming)
(He begins inhaling it.)
Oh, that looks good.
I'm enjoying it so much.
It's delicious.
That looks good.
You should live here. It suits you.
If they need a hand, I'd come back.
I know.
- Gosh.
- Teo.
I love it here.
(Teo's become a real cowboy.)
- It matches him.
- It really does.
It's perfect.
He looks perfect with that taco.
- It's perfect.
- Yes, it's perfect.
Stop eating already.
It's like a letter to yourself.
It's so cute.
- Are you okay?
- Are you looking in the mirror?
(Side effect from eating too much?)
Who are you doing that to?
(Glaring)
(Ta-da)
- A baby.
- It's a baby.
Oh, my gosh.
(It's not a side effect from eating
too much, but he's babysitting.)
Who's the baby here?
(Turning)
(Smacking)
It's salty.
- Come here, boys.
- Hello.
Nice to meet you too.
They're JP's sons...
and Eddie's sons.
It's cute to see the boys...
- in cowboy hats.
- Yes.
Hey, this little cowboy,
he'd been bucked off a horse
harder than you've ever had,
and it took him a minute,
but he got right back up.
And he's been
getting back on horses again.
- Cowboy.
(He's a real cowboy.)
- Yes.
- How old?
- Seven.
What's your name?
- Jace.
You have a dream?
- A dream?
- Yes, your dream.
- My dream.
- What do you want to be when you grow up?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
I'm a Korean painter.
Painter. Cartoon. Comics.
- He draws cartoons.
- You like cartoons?
- I like SpongeBob.
- Spider-Man?
- SpongeBob.
What kind of music do you like?
- Country.
- Country?
- Even kids grow up listening to country.
- Same as him.
K-pop?
- No K-pop? They don't know.
- No K-pop?
Do you know "Gangnam Style?"
That's the worst question ever.
Come on.
I only asked because you were
talking about K-pop.
You more or less asked the same question.
K-pop?
I wasn't planning to ask to that extent.
What else is famous?
Baby shark, doo, doo
- Do they know this song?
- "Baby Shark."
They probably know.
He's already smiling.
This is like a famous Korean song.
(Grinning)
(Interested)
- It's "Baby Shark."
- "Baby Shark."
They all smiled as soon as it was played.
- They know "Baby Shark."
- Yes.
That's more popular than "Gangnam Style."
Seriously.
(Old guys are happy.)
That's my jam.
That's Preston!
(Excited)
They're so cute.
This song is the best.
That's what we should make...
- instead of anything else.
- Something like that.
Kian84, doo, doo
(Good.)
Let's get some rest under the AC.
It's so hot.
- You have to take a nap after lunch.
- Because it's so hot.
It's a routine to rest indoors...
before the sun sets.
- Inside.
- About three hours.
They need to cool down.
It was way too hot.
(3 hours of nap time)
(Kian84, Pani Bottle, Teo)
I want green tea shaved ice.
Are you sleep-talking?
- After eating so much.
- I think you're sleep-talking.
It sounds like you're having a good dream.
"Green tea shaved ice."
(Dreaming about having green tea shaved
ice while cleaning the water tank)
(While resting with a good dream)
(It's time for the afternoon work.)
All right, men. It's time to get up.
We did the morning work.
Now we got to go in.
- All right.
- I'll wait for you outside.
Three hours went by so fast.
It felt like a minute.
We went to work right away.
(The afternoon work begins at 5 p.m.)
- It's warm.
- It's hot.
(Heading to work)
All right. We're going to go...
(Young cowboys joined them
for the afternoon work.)
The kids joined them too.
(Staring)
(Laughing)
He's cute.
(Waddling)
- So cute.
(Approaching immediately)
(Laughing)
(Adorable)
(Grabbing)
So cute.
Oh, my gosh. He's so cute.
(The next generation cowboy)
He's practicing.
So what are we going to do?
Take care of the horses, put them up.
- Take care of the horses?
- Yes.
(Exerting)
(Switching to a horse)
Everything is leather.
(The young cowboys appear on horses.)
The kids are good at riding horses.
They're so brave.
Now, straight for a little bit.
Going to look.
Stop.
Pull hard. Harder.
(Horses become second feet for cowboys.)
(Young cowboys grow up
watching the life of a cowboy...)
(and learn to ride horses
before a bicycle.)
(Setting off with a cowboy family)
Good. Okay. Real good.
(In the beautiful scene...)
It looks amazing.
There you go.
(Kian84 is riding smoothly.)
Get behind him, Jace.
Kian84 looks good on the horse.
I rode this horse this morning. Seiry.
Seiry.
Yes.
It must be hot for them too.
(While worrying about horses
from heatstroke)
Right in the middle.
No, we'll help you tie.
Because the horses came a long way,
we give them a bath.
Are they taking a bath?
(Exerting)
- It's soaked.
- My goodness.
- It's hard.
- It must've been so hot.
- My goodness.
- They sweat a lot.
Hey.
Its back is bent.
There he goes again.
- He feels bad again.
- But really, its back is bent.
- Isn't that normal?
- Not that much.
No?
Bad humans.
(The animal lover is furious.)
(It's normal to be bent.)
That's normal?
- Bring the horse, Kian.
- Yes.
- Bring the horse.
- Okay.
It's nice to give him a cool shower.
Okay. So...
Just water?
- That looks refreshing.
- Does the horse like it?
- Up here.
- Does it like it?
(Puff)
It's flaring its nostrils.
I think it likes it.
The horses liked it so much.
It must be nice.
(Kina84's first guest enters.)
He looks cool.
You remind me of...
"The Lord of the Rings."
You're right.
- Like the horse the elves ride.
- Yes.
(He has an awesome blond mane.)
His hairstyle...
- It's Teo's horse.
- It's Vaquero. I rode him.
The dirt.
(Scrubbing)
Look at his muscles.
Could you feel it?
I could. It's no joke.
- Are you happy?
- This is...
- He likes it a little too much.
- He likes it. He's flaring his nostrils.
I should loosen his trapezius.
- You're massaging him too.
- Massaging?
You provide good service.
- Trapezius.
- His trapezius was stiff.
It would take about three hours
to loosen up his trapezius.
Loosening his trapezius...
You're loosening a horse's trapezius.
You might be the first person
to give a horse a massage.
I guess he really likes it.
He's not moving even a bit.
- He likes it.
- He liked it.
Spray water on him.
- I'll give him a massage.
- Okay.
- It's a full course.
- Massage.
(Massaging)
- He should be tipped.
He provided a full service.
(An animal-lover's full service)
He's getting proper service at a salon.
This is a Korean-style massage.
- Does it feel good?
- He likes it.
- He's not even getting nervous.
Kian84 took good care of him for me.
(He's very happy.)
- It's done.
- In the trailer.
(He's done with his first customer.)
(Under the 37째C heat)
- You worked hard.
- Goodness.
(He takes good care
of the other customers too.)
You'd be sweating
even if you stand still if it's 37째C.
You feel thankful and sorry...
when you look into their eyes.
We caught them when they
should be running around freely...
to use them as transportation means.
So I tried to give them a massage.
That's all I could do for them.
I liked it because the horses
were really cute.
I could sense that they were happy.
They flared their nostrils.
I think they felt refreshed.
(Rumbling)
It was worthwhile! Oh, my, the lightning.
(Exclaiming)
Pani Bottle goes crazy
whenever he sees lightning.
(Sprinting)
Okay.
(He took care of the last customer.)
Thank you.
Gosh. Have you been
to the Waterbomb festival?
- Once.
- Was it fun?
I was there to do a gig.
- What's wrong?
- Come here.
- Did you fall?
- Oh, dear.
What happened?
Why?
(His dad checks on him.)
I guess he's hot.
- Hot.
- Hot. Yes.
- He was hot.
- Really?
Oh, no.
Goodness.
I think he felt dizzy
because it was so hot.
- Goodness.
- I was really shocked.
(He's in a bad condition
because of the hot weather.)
He should drink some water.
Here.
- What will he do?
- Here. Get some water.
Put it on your hands.
- He should go home.
- Right.
You should go home.
(JP calmly tries to lower
his temperature.)
He raises his son strongly.
He's hot.
- You should go home.
- He didn't pamper him.
He raises him so strongly.
- What's your name?
- Jace.
Jace? Come here.
- Let's get some rest under the shadow.
- Jace.
Are you hot? Do you have water?
(Eddie came to check on Jace.)
- I'm okay.
- Inside of your arm.
- He's so brave.
- He's a child.
He was brave. He didn't cry.
- I know.
- He doesn't whine.
He didn't.
Candy?
- Right. His blood sugar went down.
- Nice.
Don't swallow it. Suck on it.
(Licking)
- Thank you.
- "Thank you." He's cute.
(Dropping)
- He dropped it?
- Oh, dear.
He just needs to eat it
within three seconds.
- No.
- He's so cute.
- Goodness.
- I didn't see that.
(Dropping)
(Disappointed)
He gave his son tough love.
Jace didn't feel well.
Perhaps he got exhausted from the heat.
But he didn't make a fuss.
JP also told him,
"It's okay. Drink some water."
(The cowboy dad took care of him calmly.)
He was raised strong,
and a cowboy's life is wild too.
He never said he was hot.
- That's right.
- He's so cool.
I think he'll grow up to be
a very cool person.
Go home.
He needs rest.
What should I say?
Just a moment, Jace.
Go home and turn on the air conditioner.
Coke and air conditioner.
- Sleep.
- Get some rest.
- I think he understood you.
- Yes.
Can you walk?
Can you stand up?
(Fortunately, he's feeling better.)
(They head home, just to be safe.)
We went home because we thought
it would be better for him to rest.
- Are you okay, Jace?
- Yes.
Be careful.
What is Teo doing?
(Teo is picking prickly pears.)
He said he wanted to eat prickly pears
as soon as he came to Texas.
(The day they came to Texas)
(That's a prickly pear!)
(He found some cactus by the road.)
(Teo wanted to try prickly pears.)
(Swallowing)
(He finally gets to taste it!)
(Ouch!)
(He was pricked.)
- Be careful, man.
- Were you pricked?
It'll be like
getting snapped with needles.
Goodness.
(He's used to it.)
It was like getting an injection.
Does it hurt that much?
There are at least 20 to 30 needles
on those cactus in one spot.
It's like I got acupuncture.
It hurts.
That many?
You get those big leather chaps that
you put on and they'll block a needle.
That's why we wear those chaps...
- that JP and Eddie were wearing.
- Right.
Kian84 just grabbed that...
and ate that thing.
I said, "Boy, you're crazy!"
- The fruit...
- They said you have to be careful.
You won't be able to work later.
(Even cowboys are careful
with the spines.)
Kian84 was great.
What about the spines?
There are spines.
He was shocked.
I see a few over there.
- Do you see some?
- Yes. The darker ones, right?
There are a few more behind.
Yes. They're like in a spot
and you have to look.
Let me get these ones first.
(He keeps picking.)
(They picked many purple prickly pears.)
They're ripe and purple.
We're going to cut the prickly pears
to make jam.
(They're going to make prickly pear jam.)
The best thing to do
is to hold it up like that.
Shave that.
You prepared them.
Yes, but it was simple.
Just try to get the skin.
You can leave the skin here.
I'll go get us a little...
hammer and kind of...
Teo also cooks well.
Yes. It's a lifetime.
A lifetime of commitment.
You're doing better than me, baby.
You spent some time in the kitchen.
I did.
(Feeling proud)
(His speed goes up
after getting a compliment.)
(After peeling the prickly pears,)
You have to mash them too.
(you mash them with a hammer.)
(Only natural ingredients are used
without adding any sugar.)
- They don't use sugar in this jam.
- Yes.
Do you just put it in the fridge
and eat it right away?
Yes.
(What will the sugar-free
prickly pear jam taste like?)
(While Teo was making prickly pear jam)
Here?
- There?
- Yes.
It's good.
We went there
after giving the horses a bath.
I'll dive in.
- What is that?
- Goodness.
(There's a large pond in front of them.)
Good.
(It's the pond they saw
while taking a tour around the ranch!)
(The horses enjoy a bath.)
- There were fish.
- It's a catfish.
You can fish or take a shower
or play in the water with the horses.
(Even ducks swim in it.)
- This is...
- It's rejuvenating.
He's going in while riding the horse.
(He goes in while riding the horse.)
Just like that? Oh, my.
The horse and the person all go in
because it's so hot.
(It's a rare sight.)
It's a flood-damaged car.
A flood-damaged horse.
It's really deep.
(It reaches the horse's neck.)
The water...
(Exclaiming)
(He stands on top of the horse...)
(and dives in.)
(Jumping)
(Come in, brother.)
Kian84 can't stay still
in front of the water.
He has to go in.
(He's already unbuttoning.)
(His friend also enters the water.)
(Throwing)
It's cooler when he goes in
without his shirt.
(Extremely cool)
(He skillfully tumbles.)
(Fascinated)
I shouldn't undress too much this time.
"I shouldn't undress too much this time."
He's saying that
while taking off his pants.
I didn't take my shirt off.
Should I just wear my underwear?
I should take off my pants at least.
Don't people normally
take off their shirts?
I think it'll be better to wear it.
- Really?
- Goodness.
(He took off his shirt.)
(I don't want to see this.)
The pants are too thick.
I'll go in like this.
(Why do you keep taking your clothes off?)
It's not because I like exposing myself.
Why is he there?
(Laughing)
- What is that?
- It was raining.
It was worthwhile! Oh, my, the lightning.
This is crazy. This angle is too funny.
It's not because I like exposing myself.
I'd have to dry my clothes
if I wear them when I swim.
(He's innocent.)
I'll go in like this.
(He places his precious jeans there.)
- That stings.
- Why is the grass so prickly?
- Underwear Bottle.
- Gosh, it stings.
- Jump.
- Jump?
(Right here)
(The horse is as tall as Pani Bottle.)
(Will he make it?)
(Slipping)
(He jumped up...)
(and fell.)
Goodness.
(Laughing)
(Embarrassed)
(His short legs disappoint him.)
Okay. I'll try.
- It's okay. I'll do it myself.
- You got it?
Okay.
(He takes a deep breath.)
Go.
(Exclaiming)
It's slippery.
(Goodness)
(He refuses to give up.)
Do it. That's right.
- He did it.
- Good.
There you go.
His legs are quite pretty.
(He shows off his beautiful legs.)
(He succeeds after three tries.)
(He's happy.)
(Behind the brother who took off
only his pants...)
(comes the older brother
who took off only his shirt.)
(Jumping)
There.
- Kian84 as well.
- He did it at once.
(He struggles but manages to get on.)
Over here.
- Over here.
- Go.
You're going in with the horses.
There you go. Keep going!
(They go in the water on horseback!)
Yes! Cowboys!
Hey.
He jumped.
He got on the horse after so much trouble,
but he just slid down.
(After watching him)
Steady.
Wait.
Just a moment!
(Wait!)
(Get in there too.)
(He was thrown into the water.)
The water is black.
It's not dirty, though.
There's a lot of mud inside.
It's a mudflat.
You even picked up water plants.
(A wild pond full of water plants)
(Laughing)
(Kian84 is in the water.)
(He adapts and swims with the horses.)
I've never seen someone swim
with horses before.
(While Kian84 was becoming one
with the pond)
(Watching)
Why is he so good at swimming?
(The little cowboy entered the pond.)
(Swallowing)
I guess it's deep there.
It's not five feet.
(Even the kids are playing.)
Hey.
(I can't stay here!)
- Underwear...
- Pani Bottle. Right.
(He enters the water again
after seeing the children.)
(An overwhelming face)
Cowboys are honest, you know?
The children are good swimmers too.
(It's a playground in nature.)
(Even Jace who was exhausted
in the heat joins them.)
If this were Korea,
there would have been some adults saying,
"Don't go inside!"
because the water looked dirty.
But they didn't make a fuss like that.
They just swam.
(The cowboys enjoy nature as it is.)
It looked nice.
(It looked nice.)
(The cowboys enjoy the afternoon
while being one with nature.)
There's nothing much to a cowboy's life.
You work hard and rest hard.
It goes from bitter to sweet.
(They enjoy a good rest after hard work.)
(You can also just lay down.)
Is it refreshing?
This is paradise.
You must have really enjoyed that.
(Enjoying a wonderful nap too!)
(The location of the hat...)
- That's manners.
- It's weirder.
It's weirder.
- Manners.
- His expression is weird too.
Right.
That's all I can see.
(They enjoy a sweet rest
using the grass as their bed.)
Let's go, Pani Bottle.
Okay.
(They return to the cabin...)
(to meet Teo.)
I'm so happy.
(He's overwhelmed with happiness.)
- Are you?
- Yes.
I might tear up. I'm really happy.
It makes me think
I missed this sort of thing.
(He's just happy because he got to
live his dream as a cowboy.)
- I can feel that he means it.
- It's real.
I'll do some laundry.
Laundry.
- Laundry?
- Laundry.
(Pani Bottle came out to do laundry.)
- Is he washing the clothes that got wet?
- Looks like it.
(He washes his precious underwear too.)
(He rinses it with water.)
(Squeezing)
Pani Bottle is done with laundry.
It dries quickly because it's hot.
(The sun sets.)
(Texas' sky turns orange.)
Quatro said we should go for dinner.
(They head out for dinner.)
Let's get on.
Okay. Let's go.
(Where are they going during sunset?)
(Excited)
(They get off with excitement.)
Goodness.
Gosh.
It's amazing. You see the horizon too
since there are no mountains.
(The sunset stretches wide
along the horizon.)
(The pink sunset that looks like
a painting covers the sky.)
(The sun is setting at the ranch.)
(Well done.)
(It's time for the horses
to go back home.)
(Following the setting sun)
This really made me feel
like I was in the US.
New York is like Seoul.
(Their dinner is getting cooked.)
Goodness.
Mac and cheese.
That's really a home meal.
(He eats a piece of meat
at a sunset restaurant.)
(Eating)
(Their eyes and mouth
are fully enjoying it.)
- It's so good.
- Right.
Was it different
from what you ate in Korea?
- It's incomparable.
- That's right.
I thought it wouldn't taste good because
we had meat for lunch, but it was so good.
Did you like that pork chop?
This is my favorite spot, brother.
My favorite spot.
I guarantee you this is something
all of us will have...
in our memory. We will remember it.
- Memory.
- Yes.
(The cowboy family gathers together.)
(Both adults and children come together
and enjoy the relaxed time.)
It's so beautiful.
It's different.
The colors.
It was like in the animations.
Everything looked like a painting.
You could see the unrealistic colors
you see in animations.
(Kian84 stores them in his heart.)
- It's that kid.
- Jace.
He seems better.
Look here.
- Grasshopper.
- Jumping.
- I'll keep it as a pet.
- He'll keep it, not eat it.
Yes. That's what I said.
(He's cute.)
(Laughing)
- Jace was very...
- I guess he wanted to become friends.
He came and talked to me first.
Do you like studying?
- Yes.
- I don't think so.
(He becomes a mischievous uncle.)
You like studying?
(Let's just move on.)
I don't like studying.
- You don't like studying?
- No.
Right. I hated studying too.
In the future,
people who don't like studying...
succeed.
(What?)
There will come a time
when people who don't study succeed.
How do I say that?
That's too difficult.
There will come a time
when stupid people succeed.
(While Kian84 kept on prophesying)
Look at the moon.
- The moon is so beautiful.
- It's a crescent moon.
(Staring)
(He slowly walks to the horse.)
I don't know why I did that.
I felt very comfortable.
(The friend who roamed around the ranch
with Teo...)
(and bonded deeply with him
over a short time)
(They've become close friends
within a short time.)
I believe that we communicate
with someone...
through our souls when we can't use words.
I genuinely believe that.
So, I think that was one of those moments.
(They communicated through their souls.)
I miss it.
Is your life in Seoul tough?
(Joking)
He's worse than me.
(He shows his affection for Teo
who resembles him.)
It's a lizard.
- Is it alive?
- A lizard.
- Really?
(Jace caught another insect.)
Where did you get that?
- Why don't we let the lizard live?
- Over there.
Why don't we let the lizard live?
(I feel bad for the lizard.)
I see.
You know, when we caught
dragonflies and stuff, they all died.
Lizard. Go home?
What do you say?
(He hears a shocking suggestion
after coming to brag about it.)
He shouldn't have bragged about it.
Lizard's mama is waiting.
I didn't see the mama.
He didn't see the mama.
I'll keep it.
- He's going to keep all of them.
- You'll keep them?
Then, let's trade with me.
Okay?
You want the lizard to eat it?
- No.
- No. I'm not eating it.
How about this...
(He gets all the coins he has to trade.)
Trade.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
(That's good to hear.)
The deal has been made.
(A dramatic deal)
That's cute.
It's so tough to save a life.
It is.
(While the zoophilist is hard at work...)
- What?
- Goodness.
He's inspired.
(He's immersed in the atmosphere
and plays something on the spot.)
That's why you need to be handsome.
"That's why you need to be handsome."
(The handsome guitar sound...)
(Joining)
- Oh, my.
- Goodness.
That's so romantic.
Are they playing together?
(They start an impromptu jam.)
I heard that JP used to be a musician.
(Teo naturally responds.)
- Time keeps dragging on
- Dragging on
That was ridiculously cool just now.
- Now, this is all imagination.
- Yes.
(They play in perfect harmony
when it's the first time.)
That's improvised?
He's practically a singer.
(Admiring)
(They suddenly sing a cowboy duet.)
(Their harmony...)
(brings people together one by one.)
(Kian84 is sitting in the middle.)
- Knock, knock, knocking on heaven's door
Pani is shaking something behind them.
(Pani is shaking a soda can.)
It's going to pop!
(His excitement popped instead.)
Hey, JP!
Look up "Amarillo by Morning."
Ready? Here we go, boys.
(He starts playing
as soon as he hears the title.)
This is equivalent to "Busan Seagull"
in Texas.
- I see.
- Air violin!
- Yes.
(Good teamwork)
What did they take in Houston?
- They took my saddle in Houston
- Oh, my gosh.
(Laughing)
(Seeing how skilled they are,
they burst into laughter.)
What did you lose?
- I lost my wife and a girlfriend
(Laughing)
In Texas,
the place turns into a karaoke bar.
(They can sing in harmony
with just one guitar.)
Morning
(Friends and family all come together
to enjoy this romantic night.)
It felt like their work and leisure times
were combined into one.
Work, camping, leisure,
and karaoke were all one.
But when they sing country songs,
they can express the joys and sorrows
of their lives.
They drive cattle in the morning,
(They wake up early at dawn
and work hard.)
they cut hooves on their horses
in the evening,
(They sweat until the sunset.)
and there are joys and sorrows
in their lifestyle.
And it felt like they were
coughing it out.
(They cough it out through music!)
(Throwing away the burden
on their shoulders,)
(they finish the day with laughter.)
All right, boys!
You may think it's done,
but you'd better get some good sleep...
because, tomorrow, we've got to get up,
ride some horses, check the cows,
and do it all over again.
That's the cowboy life.
It's a good thing...
(Something just went by.)
At 4 a.m.?
- At 5:30 a.m.
- At 5:30 a.m.?
(Dizzy)
I think he said something like,
"You can sleep when you're dead."
What's scarier is that
they actually get up at 5:30 a.m.
- Good night!
- Good night.
- Ciao.
- All right.
- Good night, guys.
Goodness.
- Let's head inside.
- Good work, guys.
Oh, my.
(Tired)
I finally see what liquor tastes like.
- A cowboy's day is...
- I'm so sleepy.
(A day as a cowboy
was as long as a month.)
Tomorrow, we'll have to...
leave this place by noon.
Right.
He doesn't want to go.
I'll just stay here. You can go.
You?
(Pulling his hat down)
So, tomorrow night...
- is our last night together.
- Yes.
- Tomorrow is our last night?
- Already?
It is.
- You're leaving in two days.
- You leave the day after tomorrow.
- Seriously?
- It's already their last night?
- Yes. I have to go too.
- I forgot about that.
You're going back to Korea
the day after tomorrow, right?
Then...
(Their trip is going to end in two days.)
When you go back,
I'm going to another place...
to look for a new genre of music.
(Your trip...)
(is going to continue?)
Where are you headed?
(Where is he going by himself?)
I'm going to Jamaica.
- What? Jamaica?
- What?
(Jamaica)
Jamaica? Why are you going there?
Jamaica?
(He's going to Jamaica by himself?)
I don't know...
how it will begin and end.
But I want the last part of the trip...
to be a solo trip.
I want to finish the trip alone.
I reckon there will be
more masterpieces if I dig deeper.
- He's going to Jamaica alone?
- From the US to Jamaica?
I've been to South America,
India, and Madagascar,
which are very far places, right?
(He set off to unfamiliar lands
that were hard to reach.)
(He felt deeper emotions
in unfamiliar places.)
I felt like I was getting too used to
the city while traveling in the US.
So, I decided...
to go to the wild.
I thought about ending the trip
by myself...
and talked to the crew.
(He talked to the production crew
about going to Jamaica.)
(Jamaica)
(An island in the Caribbean Sea)
(An untouched and unexplored wilderness)
(A vibrant place full of people...)
(where music is a part of everyday life)
Look at that.
(He goes deeper into the uncharted land.)
This should be fun.
Gosh.
I never expected to go to Jamaica.
How are you going to get there?
- Jamaica?
- Yes.
- Probably on a plane.
- From where?
After checking the flights...
Where exactly do you have to go?
I'm tired, so let's look into it tomorrow.
If you miss the flight,
you can always come back here.
(He's unstoppable.)
I'm going to bed.
- So am I. I'll wash up.
- I'll sleep here.
(Turning the lights off before bed)
(Pani also goes to bed.)
(Teo is left alone.)
- I didn't know you stayed up.
- He kept looking around.
(He steps outside.)
(Flopping down)
(Teo can't seem to go to sleep.)
It was dark, but I went outside.
I looked up at the sky,
and I had never seen
such a sky before in my life.
- The night sky was stunning.
- All those stars!
(Teo was looking up at the sky.)
I was so happy.
It made me feel sad, actually.
Are you sleeping?
- The night sky is...
- Yes.
stunning.
The stars are gorgeous.
(He wanted to share the view with others.)
(He goes back outside...)
(and sits down.)
(He stared at the night sky
for a long time.)
(The wistful night goes by,)
(and morning breaks in the ranch.)
(Groaning)
Pani.
Oh, he's topless.
You either have your shirt or pants off.
I'm constantly taking my clothes off.
- He's Naked Bottle.
- Naked Bottle.
Should we...
get a tattoo today?
Seriously?
Are you trying to get matching tattoos,
or what?
(He shyly suggests matching tattoos.)
Which tattoo? The thing from earlier?
- The Longhorn.
- I see.
- It's pretty cool, though.
- Where should I get it?
- Hold on.
- Maybe here...
- A spot where people can't see.
- I think you'll look great.
Like here.
Where people can't see? Right here.
Isn't that too visible?
But you can't see it.
(Laughing)
Why not on my forehead?
Let's ask Kian84 too.
- Sure.
- Okay.
Let's wash up for now.
(They'll discuss it with Kian84 later.)
(Already exhilarated)
(He wakes up by the sound.)
(He wore the shirt to sleep.)
- He slept with that shirt on.
- What?
- Did you wash the shirt?
- You didn't do the laundry?
Did I wash it and dry it?
I can't remember.
- I don't think he did.
- That's not important.
Right. What's important is that
I was tired.
- Right. As long as he got a good sleep.
- I guess you dried it.
Shall we go?
(They go up the stairs to the rooftop.)
The flag is all torn.
Check out the flag.
- You're right.
- It's all torn.
- Goodness.
- It's weathered.
The color is beautiful.
- It's a violet...
- It's purple.
(A violet sky is beyond the flags.)
It was picturesque in the morning.
(They're dazed
in front of the overwhelming view.)
When are we getting a tattoo?
Oh, no.
(The crazy handsome cowboy
still wants to get a tattoo.)
- You should actually consider it.
- What?
- Becoming a cowboy.
- A cowboy.
(You should be a cowboy.)
Turning to a cowboy lifestyle.
Wait. So, when are we getting the tattoo?
- You still haven't gotten their answer.
- But...
Why don't all six of us get it?
Why are you dragging us into it?
- Let's all get it.
- We didn't even go!
Do Yeon, you should get one here.
The studio members aren't part of it.
It's rising.
- It's so pretty.
- Goodness.
- Oh, my.
- The sun is rising.
I see it through the trees.
They wake up to find themselves
in Jeongdongjin.
The sunrise.
(The ranch turns red.)
It's beautiful.
Shouldn't we go down there
and get to work?
I'm over here cooking breakfast.
- They're already...
- They're all out.
We're going to put salt and pepper.
They may not like salt.
They're diligent.
What are they making?
- Morning.
- Good morning.
- Hey.
- Did you get some sleep?
- Yes. Good morning.
- A little bit?
- They weren't sleeping.
- Good morning.
- All right.
- Good morning, Sunshine.
Yes.
- Morning.
- Cowboy!
- Still tired.
- Cowboy Pani.
- Yes.
- Pretty sore?
I think so.
(While the cowboys make breakfast...)
Everything, right?
He's the ultimate.
- He is the ultimate. He's the rider...
- Why do they have this in the kitchen?
- He's the...
- Hey!
- What's this?
- What is that doing here?
- What is that?
- What?
It's a hippie...
Why do they have this?
It suits you.
Eddie.
- Look at him.
- It's pretty.
Oh, that's why...
I was wondering why his hair was long.
You look like you'll play the guitar
with your teeth.
He looks like a one.
What is this?
It's a costume.
(He looks like a veteran.)
There won't be too many people
who play the guitar better than you.
(The mad guitarist
overwhelms people with his looks.)
Did Teo like it?
This is the jelly we made yesterday.
Oh, it's the jelly.
From the prickly pears, right?
(Teo and Quatro
made this prickly pear jam.)
- It's the jam.
- The one they made yesterday!
Oven inside the house.
- Inside?
- JP.
I had never seen that before.
(Freshly baked buns)
- Open it up.
- That looks good.
- Goodness.
- Should I try it?
(Steaming)
(Filling it with jam made by Teo)
- It's like eating a scone...
- A scone.
- with strawberry jam.
- Right.
This is the color magenta.
(A big bite)
(The mad guitarist also takes a bite.)
Why? You don't like it?
- It's not exactly sweet.
- No.
It wasn't jam.
This looks like...
(They give honest reviews.)
(But Teo is enjoying it.)
The cowboy doesn't have a problem with it.
- The bun is salty.
- Yes.
I like it. Oh, my gosh. It's good.
I wonder what it tastes like.
It's like mashed watermelon and cucumbers.
Did they boil it down?
- Yes.
- They must have.
- Guys.
- Yes?
Let's go eat outside.
- Okay.
- Sure.
- Should we bring this too?
- Yes.
(There's more to eat?)
Oh, nice.
In the morning...
They're having a barbecue at 6 a.m.
(A barbecue party early in the morning)
T-bone steak!
- They're eating steak in the morning.
- They actually eat it in the morning.
(Yesterday's lunch: Meat)
They have barbecue parties
three times a day.
- Seriously.
- That's insane.
(And T-bone steak this morning)
Bacon.
Steak and eggs?
Eating steak in the morning
doesn't sit well with me.
All right, guys.
(Nibbling)
They're sick of it.
(They only eat bacon as they've eaten
meat three times in a row.)
I was fed up with it.
(Welp...)
(A big bite)
This is crazy.
(He puts a T-bone steak between the buns.)
(Admiring)
- That looks good.
- He made a burger.
- Teo is so...
- It was so delicious.
(He can easily handle a morning steak.)
I was able to eat it.
The food suits you,
and the lifestyle suits you.
This is so good, though.
(He even wipes the sauce off the plate.)
The owner doesn't drink coffee,
- so they don't have coffee.
- I have coffee.
- You do?
- Yes. Do you want me to bring it?
- Let's have a cup of coffee.
- Sure.
(Pani makes coffee.)
- You're done eating, right?
- Yes.
- I'll make coffee, then.
- Good.
(He makes coffee right away.)
They served us breakfast,
so I thought it'd be a good idea
to give them coffee.
This is Korean coffee.
- Coffee.
- Thank you.
(Cups of coffee
for the hardworking cowboys)
- Here.
- I appreciate you.
You always have to bring these
when you're traveling.
- It's a necessity.
- Gosh. What is that?
It's Korean coffee.
That's some good stuff right there. Gosh.
He's enjoying it.
- Is it...
- There's no one who'd dislike this.
Like in a K-Town mart.
They should have it.
- He's taking a photo.
- He's taking a photo of it!
- He must love it.
- Yes.
(I need a photo of this.)
That is some good stuff. Gosh, darn it.
(The cowboys love Korean coffee.)
That was a good meal.
Shouldn't you paint something today?
You promised them yesterday.
- Yes, the kids.
- The kids.
I should paint the kids before I go.
- The flag was all torn. It's so old.
- Yes.
We always made a flag, right?
- Right.
- Yes.
We ate and slept in the cabin,
so it was like a gift for them.
I like that.
The kids have their paintbrushes
and paint.
Okay. I should draw their faces too.
- You could.
- Okay.
- There's the little cowboy!
- Little cowboy.
Adorable.
- Good morning.
- Good morning. Nice shirts.
- Nice shirts.
- Good morning.
He's friendly.
The kids are getting their stuff.
Yes.
- All of it?
- All, yes.
The kids gave him tools after they heard
he was going to paint something.
Okay. Come here.
I'm going to draw you guys.
You can draw the three of us.
(Us?)
- They're so cute.
- No?
I don't know how to draw.
- That's okay.
- That's fine.
You can draw whatever you want.
It's just for fun.
- He's shy.
- How adorable.
Sit comfortably,
and feel free to draw anything.
Where's gray?
You can draw their faces,
- and I'll draw the props.
- Okay.
Like an assistant.
It's been so long since I last painted.
I only paint when I'm on this show.
- Nowhere else.
- But you went to art school.
I was a flunker. I was a terrible painter.
- I...
- What's that photo?
- That's my graduation photo.
- That's you?
- What are you wearing?
- A gas mask.
Were you able to graduate
after that photo?
Fortunately, yes.
(He calls himself a flunker,)
(but Kian84 didn't even graduate.)
This is a poor painting environment.
(Next to the poor artists...)
- The tattoo.
- The Longhorn.
- That's all he thinks about.
- He's hooked on it.
Do you all recognize this?
That's a Longhorn.
A Longhorn! That's right. Exactly.
- He drew it so nicely.
- It's cool, though.
(He draws the symbol of Texas
as if it's a tattoo.)
Maybe I'm going to get a tattoo.
Put some ink on my skin.
Why is Pani drawing it?
I could do that much.
It wasn't a permanent tattoo.
- Doesn't that mean you want one?
- No, not at all.
- No?
- You try to convince me every time.
(He finds the opportunity
to sneak his way in.)
I got a pretend tattoo. What do you think?
- "HB?" Houston Bros!
- Yes.
To remember this trip.
It's a friendship doodle.
I'm satisfied with that.
- Are you?
- Yes.
What was your favorite part of the trip?
My favorite part of the trip was
coming here and meeting you guys.
- That's so sweet!
- It's poetic.
What he said was a gift in itself.
- Are you going to miss us?
- Yes.
Let's make a beautiful painting.
(It's time to make a beautiful painting.)
That looks the same as me!
- Look at that. He's got a picture.
- You!
- That's me!
- Yes.
It already looks the same.
That's you. He's amazing, right?
That's why he's a professional.
- You're really good.
- Come on.
It was my first time seeing Kian84 paint,
so I wanted to show off to the kids.
The kids are good too.
I like how they draw it randomly.
That's so cute!
That looks like SpongeBob.
It looks like...
Jace is the main character.
This is
Jace's Music Adventure by Accident.
That's amazing.
(The main character is here.)
He got curious and sat next to you.
It's you.
You're bigger than the older ones.
It means that you need to be a big man.
(Touched)
Do you want to try it?
- I can do it?
- Yes.
I love his attitude.
Do you want to paint the color of the hat?
- Paint the hat with this color.
- Do you want to fill out the hat?
Okay.
- Is there a correct answer to painting?
- There isn't.
- There's no correct answer.
Okay. Do it.
(Charing into the world
without correct answers)
He picked gray?
He's bold.
(Hesitant)
But yellow seems better, doesn't it?
You said there were no correct answers.
Maybe it seems gray to you.
Okay. Good! Come on!
- Whatever you want.
- Come.
Come at it.
- It looks good, though. He's an artist.
- It does.
You can fix it.
Okay.
(He pours his soul into it...)
- He's really bold.
- He's got potential.
(with the little artist.)
Man, I'm tired.
I shouldn't have drawn all four of them.
I thought the other three might be
disappointed if I only painted one.
Exactly.
(Lying down)
What happened to him?
There are too many.
What did he say?
I thought you were a professional.
- He thought you were a pro.
(The remark cuts deep.)
That was great.
A pro can't get tired.
- Professionals are not tired.
- There you go.
Oh, my.
Who taught you to say that?
- They were brought up in a tough world.
- That was sharp.
Okay. I'll keep trying.
I'm learning a lot from you.
(He experiences
how a cowboy raises his child.)
His butt is showing now.
Kian84, he can see your butt.
Thanks for looking out for me.
- I think he's a genius.
- He's adorable.
Kick his butt.
(Sure!)
(He was feeling lazy,)
(and the kid gave him energy.)
(He's recharged.)
- Hey.
- He's adorable.
- I think Jace likes him.
- I know!
- I guess he wanted to be friends.
- Kids get playful when they like you.
You wanted me to work hard.
He's the happiest I've seen.
- He was tired earlier.
- Yes.
- He said you got tired too soon.
- Did he? Try being my age.
He thought you got tired too soon
when you were a pro.
You know, he's older than your dad.
- How old is he?
- He's 41.
(Surprised)
I thought he was 22.
- He halved your age.
- He thought you were 22.
- Who said that?
- Him.
- Okay.
- How old are you?
I should draw him better.
Great. The main character is replaced.
(What?)
I thought he was like 20.
- Jace thought you were 20.
- He understood!
It's a competition now.
- This is an auction.
- Yes.
I thought he was one.
- He thought you were one year old!
- One year old.
- He thought you were one.
- He lost.
- One year old.
- How do they learn to make such jokes?
What seven-year-olds make jokes like that?
(Moved by the high-quality jokes)
- They should be in our studio.
- I know.
They've got what it takes.
- I have a question.
- You said you were seven years old.
Why are you laughing
and shaking your butt?
He asked why you were laughing
and shaking your butt.
That's because my body is shaking.
How does a seven-year-old make
such a joke?
- His butt laughed with him.
- They know how to tease you.
It's taking a while,
- so I'll start writing their names.
- Okay.
Man, I'm tired.
You got bored?
- "You got bored?"
(Yes.)
It's not easy when you're old.
- He's too old.
- You must want to be seven again.
I'm jealous of your age.
(Jealous)
But it won't be easy.
You need to study, go to middle school,
go to high school,
make friends, go to work,
find a girlfriend,
- and serve your parents.
- Right.
- Life is tough, Jace.
- What are you saying to him?
- Yes, that's true.
- Jace?
He says it's true.
Is that right?
He's seven, but he's mature.
When he said you weren't a pro,
- No.
- you were offended, weren't you?
"Offended."
- That's not it.
- They're extraordinary.
I can't believe he's teaching me things.
Give me 30 minutes, kids.
(He's enlightened and tries again.)
- Sure.
- They're nice kids.
It's got his style.
The painting shows his style.
I don't think
I've ever seen you like this.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
You're really distracted,
but this is quite surprising.
- You look different.
- He looks the coolest in his main field.
I can tell that you're immersed
when you're doing your main job.
I'm done.
(He's done in no time.)
Finished.
Oh, he's done. Let's check it out.
- It looks good.
- That's awesome!
Jace. You don't do well with heat.
(Jace, the youngest
who's easily affected by heat)
Jace's older brother.
- You got his ears right.
- Yes, the older brother.
Preston, do you like it?
- He likes it.
- That's nice.
- And the handsome guy.
- He drew them so well.
And then, your names...
are on the outside and below.
In English, and then, in Korean.
The letters look so cool.
- That was Teo's idea.
- Yes, I love it.
He knows how to add the American touch.
Who drew this?
- Who was it?
- Me.
- This is you.
- It's me?
- That must be Teo.
- And that's me? Yes, it's my shirt.
This is Pani Bottle?
- Are you sure that's a person?
- What's that?
- Isn't that a prickly pear?
- A prickly pear!
At least he's smiling.
The eyes resemble mine, though.
That one's you.
- This is me?
- Yes, he says it's you.
- My face?
- Oh, it's your face.
(An abstract face)
What's this?
- It's this.
- Oh, my Buddhist prayer beads?
- They're huge.
- He's very observant.
What's this?
The hair.
- Is this Pani Bottle?
- Yes, his hair.
- That's a rocket.
- That's a thick head of hair.
- That feels good.
- This is...
But his face... The hair and the hat.
It's floating?
- Why? Why is it floating?
- Why is the hat above the head?
You're right.
(Bursting into laughter)
- Because my head is big?
- He loves it.
(Kian84's review made him laugh.)
- Why is it floating?
- Why are you making fun of me?
Is this a rocket?
- It's that...
- Someone should answer him!
- Good.
- He saw you earlier and drew you.
- No!
- A rocket?
I used to draw it like this
back in kindergarten.
- Oh, no.
- What's wrong?
Why?
Why are you crying?
What's wrong, Jace?
He got upset that we were laughing
at his painting.
He misunderstood.
He thought we were making fun of him.
- Right. We weren't, though.
- Oh, boy.
He's so innocent and tender-hearted.
- Did I do something wrong?
- What is it?
(But it somehow seems familiar.)
What did I do wrong?
(When he gave out pocket money
in Brooklyn...)
(You need to say thank you.)
(No, thank you.)
(He has a record of making kids cry.)
- What did I do wrong?
- You're making a lot of them cry.
Why do you make kids cry
everywhere you go?
I didn't. We were all talking about it.
Yes, we were all talking about it.
Why do you make kids cry
from all over the world?
No. I didn't do it.
"I didn't do it."
(Please tell me it wasn't me, Jace.)
- You can tell me. It's okay.
- It's okay.
I'm not crying.
You're not crying?
I'm checking what kinds of guns there are.
You're looking at the guns?
He's talking about the guns.
(Looking away at the guns)
- He's lying.
- It's a cowboy joke.
He's thinking about
which gun to use to shoot you.
That was why he was looking at them.
- He was selecting which gun to use.
- He's thinking of which one to use.
(Don't kill me.)
That's how mad he was?
I'm looking at the guns.
You're looking at the guns?
(But the trace of tears is too obvious.)
He's not saying it since he's embarrassed.
- What's the reason?
- He must be sentimental.
Did we tease him?
- Is it...
- Is it about your drawing?
He did his best, but we teased him.
- I think there was a misunderstanding.
- Right.
I was trying to get close to him,
but I did it the wrong way.
I understand how he feels.
When I was a student,
I got annoyed when a teacher teased me.
(Sighing)
He sighed.
- He sighed.
- You're branded for your big mistake.
Gosh. You made a seven-year-old boy sigh.
But he is...
You revenged him for what he said earlier.
- What are you saying? Revenge?
- To a seven-year-old boy.
- He's a...
- You won, Kian84.
No, he really is a smart boy.
Honestly, I don't know why.
I don't know the exact reason.
I'm going to get ready.
I'm going to prepare things in advance.
(Opening the door)
I'll load the car...
- and put up the flag.
- Yes.
They got awkward.
(Jace comes out timidly.)
(Drooped shoulders)
But he's still following Kian84.
(Following with a distance)
Oh, my.
Let's see what you boys did.
What did you get? What did we get?
Each one of them drew us, you see.
Oh, yeah?
They drew you? Oh, JP!
You think that's JP?
His mind is drawn to Jace.
That's beautiful.
He lowered his head in front of me.
It made me feel so heavy-hearted.
- Goodness.
- Why...
That one was such a nice one. If you want,
keep that one. I guarantee,
if that's for the boys, let them keep it.
- We can hang that one.
- He says this is so beautiful,
- so he wants to hang that one.
- Okay.
Okay. Perfect. Thanks.
- Perfect.
- That's nice.
Your painting...
will be hung now as a flag.
(Making peace before putting up the flag)
(Attaching carefully to the pole)
Let's do it together.
- Like all one hand.
- Together. Okay.
You're all right?
(They put up the memory in unison.)
Yes, boys.
I like the painting.
You three are left there on the flag.
That's nice.
Hey, cowboys! Come here.
- Pocket money?
- Uncle is giving you pocket money.
(Giving pocket money as he feels sorry)
You should give pocket money to the kids.
- Study hard.
- Thank you.
All right. Be good to your parents.
- Here. All right.
- Thank you.
Jace can't stop crying.
- Is he crying again?
- Yes.
You need to cover your tears. Come here.
Cover your tears with these.
Okay.
- Is it a gift?
- Cover your tears.
I gave it to him because boys don't cry.
Good. Real men don't cry often.
Okay. Good.
- He's so cute.
- All right.
A Texas man doesn't cry.
You shouldn't cry.
(However...)
(Jace leaves as he can't stop crying.)
Earlier, Jace cried because he was teased,
but now, he cried because he heard
that we were leaving.
- Because you were saying goodbye.
- Yes.
- He was sad.
- I guess he cried for that reason.
Please assist me with the interpreter.
Jace? Come here.
Come here.
Oh, my.
(Jace hid himself
because he was sad to say goodbye.)
Are you okay?
- Yes.
Come here, Jace.
Uncle is giving you pocket money.
(He wants to give the kid something
as he feels sad.)
- Thank you.
- Yes.
- He's sweet.
- He said thank you.
- Goodness.
- Oh, my.
- He went to him.
- All right.
Jace, grow up well.
I'm going back to Korea now.
Be good to your dad.
Grow up to be a great person.
He keeps falling into his arms.
I'm not sure if we'll meet again,
but that's what all encounters are like.
(It doesn't mean
that your connection ends here.)
Excuse me. Can I ask you one more thing?
Yes.
Do you like Uncle Teo...
- or Uncle Kian94 or Uncle Pani Bottle?
- Seriously.
- I was just curious.
- Gosh.
(Which uncle is in your heart, Jace?)
(It's Uncle Kian84!)
Him.
- It's Uncle Kian84.
- He's cute.
Is that so?
Come here.
- One, two, three, four...
- He has nothing to give other than that.
I'm giving you ten dollars more.
Don't tell your brother that you got this.
- Thanks.
- Okay.
(Kian84 cares about him more.)
There you go.
I knew you liked me the most.
- He's giving him another hug.
- He keeps falling into his arms.
They're hugging once again.
Jace is on my mind.
He kept approaching me.
The previous day, he caught a grasshopper
and showed it to me.
Then he showed me the lizard he caught.
He tried to communicate.
(The little cowboy
kept trying to communicate.)
It was so cute.
(Going through difficulties together...)
(and laughing together)
He made me feel a lot of things
although he was little.
I hope he doesn't lose
that pure sentiment as he grows up.
I wish I had a son like that.
- He's cute.
- Yes.
(And...)
Oh, my.
- They're the boys.
- Oh, my.
All right.
- He doesn't want you all to go.
- I guess he really feels sad.
- He's sad that you're leaving.
- Yes.
- Jace.
- Give him a hug, Jace.
(They still feel sad
even after hugging many times.)
Be happy.
He said you're going to be okay.
You're a cowboy.
- He doesn't know when he'll see you next.
- He doesn't want you to leave.
Stop crying.
He said you all were so much fun.
Is this a gift for me?
- He gave him the snack he was eating.
- Is this a gift for me?
When a seven-year-old gives you
a snack, that's everything he can give.
- He's so cute.
- Thank you.
- He feels sad.
- So cute.
- This is your horse.
- He says we can say goodbye to horses.
Safety?
- Seiry.
- Seiry?
Safety?
Safety. Are you safe?
You have sleep on your eye.
(He cleans the horse's sincerely
even if he can't remember its name.)
Okay. The other side.
Great job, buddy.
(Saying goodbye sincerely to the horses)
Have a good life.
Safety.
"Safety."
He wants the horse to live in safety.
(Meanwhile, Pani Bottle...)
See that? You didn't get bucked off.
He got on the horse in one go.
(Saying goodbye intensely)
In the past, I thought about...
becoming a farmer.
It was a very healthy lifestyle.
That's what I thought.
I was lucky to have experienced it.
I want to get on again.
Yes, last time.
How can Teo leave here?
I think Teo will feel the most sad.
What if he runs away on that horse?
- He almost did that.
- He was serious.
He might run away just like that.
Pani Bottle, let's leave Teo here.
He seems really sad to leave.
I don't think he wants to go home.
(The cowboy is sincere to the end.)
I don't want to leave.
We feel sad too.
Vaquero!
(My friend who ran with me
like we were one.)
Thank you for your work.
Time for me to go.
Bye.
(Pulling himself together)
Did you cry?
It's his back, but I can see
the look on his face.
(Knowing how genuine he was about this,)
He grew so attached in a day.
(they can feel how sad he is
deep inside their hearts.)
Darn it.
(His genuine emotion explodes.)
- You know...
- I mean,
it's been a long time since I teared up.
But the tears stopped in an instant.
- He really didn't want to go back.
- Seriously.
- That was shocking.
- He stunned me.
(He really didn't want to leave.)
Darn it.
(As this moment won't come back again,)
(he tears up in sadness.)
I can't believe how I can develop...
so much affection in such a short time.
Everything felt like a lie.
It was a short moment for me.
(The cowboy life felt like a dream.)
The cowboy lifestyle was so pure,
and the emotions I felt there...
were beautiful.
(The emotions he felt for the first time)
And when I said goodbye in the end,
(Precious moments...)
He has that innocence like a true artist.
(His innocent heart
didn't want to say goodbye.)
- I can't stop tearing up.
- Oh, no.
I guess he still feels the emotion
he felt back then.
I see.
(The memory is still clear.)
I think they have the humanity
I forgot about.
(He felt the humanity he forgot about.)
Looking at the cowboy ranch,
I got to think a lot about
what romance is.
Insisting on a tradition isn't romance.
It can bring you more difficulties.
They're not maintaining it
only for romance.
I think they're people...
who live to find balance
and happiness in nature.
So I think their romance has a reason.
- Thanks. Keep in touch.
- Yes. Thanks for everything.
You're a good man.
Yes, you too. Likewise. Thank you.
- Adi처s.
- I'm going to be back.
- Yes, sir.
- One day. Yes.
- Adi처s!
- Bye!
- Ciao!
Jace! Be strong!
Okay!
Have a good life, Quatro!
- Bye!
(Goodbye until we meet again!)
- Gosh.
- Oh, my.
- Goodness, he cried again.
- Oh, no.
- Jace.
- It's not easy...
experiencing such a farewell at that age.
(This summer may have been...)
(the most memorable summer
of his life yet.)
- Goodness.
- I feel sad.
The people here are so nice.
- I guess it's this song.
- It's the song.
(This song is...)
(A song inspired by the cowboy life)
- It sounds so nice.
- It's going to be released today.
It's Teo's song.
(The second song
of Music Adventure by Accident)
("Texas Summer" by Yoo Teo)
(The video Teo filmed in Korea)
(The cowboy life lingers on him.)
(The season colored with romance
they can't forget.)
(It was summer.)
What a summer.
(The summer in Texas was hot!)
- Texas summer!
- It's so perfect.
- The song sounds nice too.
- It's catchier than "Dandelion."
Watching your trip and then listening
to the song creates storytelling.
- Yes.
- It's more touching.
What we felt together...
was expressed as simply
and honestly as possible.
Although the lyrics are simple,
the song moves our emotions more deeply.
- It was so nice.
- Right.
If you go to America for filming,
you can visit them then.
I plan to go there again to help out.
- You should go.
- They'd be happy to see you again.
Seeing Teo falling for the cowboy life,
I realized that every person
has a different dream.
I realized it more seeing Teo.
In fact, as I traveled,
I got used to meeting
and saying goodbye to people.
But Teo wasn't used to it like I was,
so that surprised me.
I realized it more seeing how Teo was.
He had such sincerity.
But I got emotional from the beginning.
I envied their lives so much.
(The last journey of three brothers)
(A live bar?)
(Are they making a debut in America?)
(However...)
(The stage is huge.)
(Can they handle this stage?)
(The pressure increases.)
(Is Pani Bottle running away?)
(Emergencies continue.)
(The leader feels pressured.)
(I can't step back!)
(Getting hyped)
(After frantic efforts,)
(the last part of their journey
in America...)
(is highlighted
by three brothers' debut performance.)
(And a song that tells
their challenges...)
(and sung by three of them is created.)
(And the leader alone...)
(goes somewhere
looking for new inspiration.)
(Green nature...)
(and instinctive energy is alive
in the soil.)
(Jamaica)
(Reggae teachers everywhere!)
(Please be my teacher.)
(Follow me.)
(The reggae teacher's
music training camp...)
(is in the Blue Mountain rainforest?)
What's that?
(Truly original)
(Should I run away?)
(He arrives at a natural waterfall
to train his vocals.)
(Beside the teacher hesitating,)
(the beginner doesn't spare himself.)
(Shouting)
(Oh, my)
(The teacher is deeply moved.)
(You can be my best pupil.)
(Pupil84 surpasses his teacher.)
(Vocal training in the wilderness)
(Music Adventure by Accident)