Last week, the three turning into cowboys,
also known as the wilds' outlaws,
was a big hit.
In particular,
viewers said Teo's "Texas Summer..."
- was a big gift.
- Thank you.
(Music Adventure by Accident's
second song, "Texas Summer")
(Teo's cheerful country music is great.
I love you!)
(Songs with stories are so touching.)
(The challenge is as hot
as the Texas heat.)
(Song Joong Ki, Let's make a hit!)
(Please love "Texas Summer.")
It feels quite empty today.
Where did you go, Pani Bottle?
(Where is Youngest Bottle?)
Pani Bottle already had plans.
- I see.
- That's why he's not here.
It's his full-time job. Let's excuse him.
- We understand.
- Yes.
Let's watch
how the boys spent the last day...
after the tearful farewell
with the cowboys they grew fond of.
Today, we'll go to Houston.
- Let's go.
(To Houston!)
- Tell us when you get sleepy.
- Okay.
- Let me drive next.
- I'll tell you.
- I'll drive as much as possible.
- You shouldn't if you get sleepy.
But dozing off will be dangerous.
I'll miss the beer at this place so much.
It's going to make me cry.
I'll really miss the cowboys.
(The night with the cowboys
was unforgettable.)
The cowboys showed me the grasshopper
they caught.
They were very open with us.
(What was it like to you, Kian84?)
- He's sleepy.
- Kian84 is passed out.
How cold-hearted.
Tell us when you get sleepy, Pani Bottle.
He's sleeping like a baby.
Houston. The way to Houston.
(Discovers something)
"Buc-ee's."
(The rest area sign appears just in time.)
Kian84.
Yes?
It's the rest area. We're heading inside.
Let's grab a meal.
- Okay.
- Our lunch.
(Glancing)
Look at that.
Goodness.
I've never seen...
- so many gas pumps.
- What? Is that a gas station?
- What a big gas station.
- Yes.
Everything in Texas is huge. I'm serious.
(Texas-sized gas station)
Guys.
We stopped at a rest area
on our way to Houston.
This is said to be
the biggest rest area in Texas.
Let's check it out.
Do you see all of that, Kian84?
Goodness.
- It's crazy.
This place is huge.
- My goodness.
- Rather than a rest area,
- isn't it Costco?
- I know, right?
How nice.
(The place has everything.)
- How is this a gas station?
- Seriously.
Oh, my.
It must have everything.
There's a food court over there.
You're right.
Let's pick out some food.
You must be hungry.
(They add to the shopping basket
without hesitation.)
These are all beef jerky.
This place has Korean BBQ-flavored
beef jerky.
(He spots the Korean BBQ flavor.)
- Can I get a quarter pound of that?
- It's for you.
- Thank you so much.
- Take care.
I appreciate it.
Pani Bottle...
and Kian84 must be
picking out their food, right?
What should I get?
(Looking around)
The clothes here are all so nice.
How much is it?
It's 24 dollars.
I want to buy one.
Gosh, look at this one.
- A "Star Wars" shirt.
- That's a style Pani Bottle likes.
You're right.
It's like Pani Bottle's closet.
(Sure enough,
Pani Bottle is exploring his closet.)
Pani Bottle is having a blast.
Texas hunting style.
I don't like it.
Americans will love it if I wear this one.
I'll buy this one and the US flag.
These two.
It's quite big.
I'll get myself a shopping basket.
(Adding a pair of socks)
These pants. Those shirts.
I bought socks.
You're buying some clothes.
- I couldn't help it.
- Me too. Right?
Because I like shirts too.
(Shaking his head)
The display is nice.
- Teo.
- Did you not get any food?
- I will do that now.
- Now?
Yes. Look at some clothes.
I'll be right back.
- Got it.
- Choosing clothes won't take long.
- I'm in for some brisket.
- Burgers.
- Cherry flavored, please.
A cherry coke.
This will be my treat.
- You will?
- Yes.
There was so much I wanted.
I'm even buying socks.
Because Pani Bottle had the most to buy,
- he said he'd pay for it all.
- How generous.
- It's 193.90 dollars.
- Okay.
He's got it.
(Pani Bottle's card)
Thank you, Pani Bottle.
This is a travel credit card.
I don't need to exchange money.
- Really?
- You just need to pay.
As expected of you
to bring such a card overseas.
I should make one when I return to Korea.
I bought some food
we could share while driving.
You're leaving with hands full of bags.
Take that to Jamaica.
(The big brother
takes care of his siblings first.)
(Try this too.)
(Amazed)
(Digging in)
There are no vegetables inside.
- Here.
- It's all meat.
(The meat is thicker than the bread.)
- Look at the patty.
- It's more or less just meat.
- Texas sure loves meat.
- They fight everything with meat.
(Stops)
Even so, I'm happy to eat meat
for every single meal.
(The real cowboy
loves everything about Texas.)
What will we do in Houston?
- Either way, it's our last night.
- Yes.
Let's go to a live bar.
- "A live bar?"
- Let's go to one...
and sing together
to celebrate our last night.
I went to a camp in elementary school.
My friend sang...
"Come Back Home" by Seo Taiji and Boys
while dancing.
The kids went wild back then.
I realized that the stage
had such ecstasy.
Since then,
my dream was to become a singer.
(He showed his desire to perform
before the trip.)
(He dreamed of becoming a singer
for 41 years.)
(He met a producer.)
(Shall I sing on stage in the US?)
(Something fun.)
(I like how the lyrics are simple.)
(The song he chose was...)
("September" by Earth, Wind, and Fire.)
(A cheerful punk music
released in the 1970s.)
(It's a song that is still loved
by Americans.)
(He practiced hard in Korea.)
(Diligent)
(Sharing his bucket list
with his brothers)
(Let's give it a shot!)
(Gladly)
As Kian84 said, singing "September"
sounded like a lot of fun.
Right.
(That was how the US trio was formed.)
(Throughout the trip,)
(they practiced to the point
they could easily sing "September.")
(The day before in their room)
Shall we sing "September"
in a karaoke in Houston?
Have you been to an American one?
Yes, I have. The karaoke is an open bar.
- That's nice.
- Right?
"A live bar? Can ordinary people sing?"
"Okay. Then let's go."
It's a music adventure. We can't
just leave after listening to music.
We should also sing.
Because I didn't know the US well,
I asked musicians if there were
recommended live bars in Houston.
As I belong to a music agency,
- getting such information is easy.
- He's in AOMG.
- Is this trash?
- Yes.
(Putting on his new item)
You bought sunglasses for the stage.
- Is everyone buckled up?
- Yes.
Let's get going.
- Let's go!
Goodness, the weather is great.
- The sky is a piece of art.
- It is.
Let's go to a nearby hotel first.
- There's a little problem in Houston.
- Yes?
- There's a power outage.
- What?
Was there a tornado?
- No. A hurricane, not a tornado.
- What?
It passed by, but Houston got struck.
It must've been a bad one.
(A hurricane hit Houston two days ago.)
Two days ago?
Is everyone okay?
(Houston became a wreck.)
That's really bad.
It might not be a complete blackout,
but they have a power shortage.
I'm the type to save up money.
But the hotel has no power.
- I looked up some places.
- Okay.
Let's head to a place
with a low possibility of a power outage.
To think we'd experience
a blackout in the US.
But it could be better than we thought.
(What's that?)
The hurricane must've been bad.
The sign boards are wrecked.
(Tattered)
The things on the road
must've been from the hurricane.
(Traces of the hurricane
can be seen everywhere.)
(Houston is a metropolis
with skyscrapers...)
(and a cutting-edge city
famous for its space industry.)
Apollo 11 now. This is Houston.
Houston clear.
(Currently, there is severe damage
in various places.)
The utility pole has fallen.
(The collapsed utility pole
has been left unattended.)
Many utility poles have fallen.
- It's bent.
- My goodness.
Many areas had been swept away
and left unrepaired.
It must've been strong.
- They're bent.
- Yes, you're right.
My goodness.
We're here. This is the place.
It looks expensive.
It must cost around 500 dollars per night.
- Look. All the trees fell.
- You're right.
My goodness. They're all knocked down.
- My gosh.
- Oh, my.
They're all broken into pieces.
- My goodness.
- Look at that.
At this point, it's a relief that
they're even managing to operate.
- Oh, my.
- Let's go rest first.
- Thank you for your efforts.
- You must be tired.
- My gosh.
(They arrived after a 4-hour drive.)
Let's check in first.
(Groaning)
(It hurts.)
(Their bodies feel stiff
from the long-distance travel.)
In the US, you spend a day traveling.
You look exhausted.
Your face is full of tiredness.
I rolled around at the ranch
and haven't even had a shower yet.
You're drenched.
My pants...
feel like a salt field.
It tastes salty.
I better get a shower.
(He's going to shower first.)
(They enter the hotel.)
- Oh, my.
- It seems like the electricity is out.
Or not. It looks dark inside.
- Is it? Yes, it's dark.
- I know.
- It seems to be emergency power.
- Right?
(Not sure)
- There's no electricity.
- I guess there's no electricity.
- There’s a power outage here too.
- I see.
It can't be this dark.
They're using emergency power.
- Hello.
- Let's check in first.
Yes, we have a reservation.
I can't see.
It's dark here, right?
Yes, it is.
Is the light from emergency electricity?
Generator.
- Oh, they're using a generator.
- They're using a generator.
- Yes, it’s just backup power.
- They’re only using the minimum.
You got any idea how long
the electricity's going to stay like this?
Hopefully tomorrow...
- it will come back on.
- Tomorrow?
How long will the power outage last?
Then,
I think I will need to check the live bar.
We're not sure...
if there's a power outage there too.
You two can rest here.
If everything is fine, I'll text you
to take a taxi or Uber.
- My goodness.
- In a developed country...
(Even though he's tired from driving,
he volunteers to check the live bar.)
Four, zero. It's here.
My goodness.
(What will the room situation
be like for the three people?)
What?
Is there no air conditioning?
- If there's no air conditioning...
- Let me try.
- It's this one, right?
- Yes, let me try.
But it should be on automatically.
The power is on.
No.
(Pressing the button)
My goodness. Nothing is working.
- Is there no air conditioning?
- No.
TV.
(Pressing the button)
We can't turn it on?
The lights, the fridge,
the air conditioner, nothing was working.
Everything was out of service.
(Everything was out of service.)
- Nothing is working.
- How about the lights in the toilet?
It's weak, but it's on.
(Completely dark)
- Hey.
- Is it not turning on?
There's no light here.
You can use your phone.
I'm tired.
(So tired)
(Falling on the bed)
(Groaning)
(Why are we facing such trials?)
He's tired.
- Natural light.
- But...
- Wait.
What kind of hotel is this hot?
I want to go back to Devine.
(Laughing in despair)
(They've both lost it.)
Will the live bar be open
when there's a power outage?
It's not easy.
(Worried Pani Bottle)
- I'll get going. I'll call you.
- Goodbye.
- Let's listen to the song several times.
- Let's do that.
(They warm up their voices
while waiting for Pani Bottle.)
(When they were practicing
for quite some time)
- Hello.
- Yes, Pani.
- Kian84, this place...
- Yes.
- You should call a taxi here.
- Okay.
- I guess it's open.
- Come and...
Is it a place
where people can sing freely?
It's very free.
At least that's what it seems like.
Okay. We'll be there.
- Yes.
- Okay.
That's a relief.
Let's go.
- Go.
- Let's go!
(They traveled 15 minutes by car.)
Finally,
(They arrive at the bar.)
- the day has come.
- Finally, the day has come.
(Feeling nervous)
- Howdy.
- Hi.
- This is for the runners.
- Yes.
- A runner?
- Yes, did you go running?
- Houston Marathon?
- No, we didn't run.
- Yes, the UT health event.
- No.
It's for the people
who participated in the marathon.
It's an open mic for them.
It's called an "Open Mic Night."
Anybody can hold the microphone.
Some people recite poems,
- some rap,
- Some people rap.
- and some play instruments.
- Really?
(It's like the "National Singing Contest"
where anyone can be on stage.)
(Open mic means
it's an open stage to the public.)
There are still people running.
Hello.
(Hello, Pani Bottle.)
- We're doomed.
- Why?
(Kian84, we're doomed.)
There are too many people.
(It's crowded.)
It's their first stage.
The air conditioning was working here,
so there were many customers.
My goodness.
There are many people.
It's a good thing
that there are many people.
- We're doomed if there are no people.
- Let's practice.
I registered.
There are quite a lot of people
who registered.
Should I write pop for the genre?
I'm not sure.
- If you want to...
- You wrote that?
participate in a talent show in the US,
you can register like this.
The microphone sound is
slightly distorted, so they won't know...
- if we can’t sing well.
- They’ll be forgiving.
A manager came and said...
we could go upstairs and practice.
- Let's go upstairs.
- Yes, we can go upstairs.
There's no space here.
They said we could go this way.
Oh, the musicians are all waiting here.
It's here.
(They stumbled upon
the second-floor terrace.)
Gosh, what a great vibe.
(Why do I hear someone singing?)
(It's crowded.)
Is it here?
- My goodness.
- Oh, my.
(Laughing)
My goodness. This is crazy!
(It isn't an indoor stage.)
- I mean...
- I see.
- The stage is huge.
- I know.
It's not just a bar.
Are you singing in that square?
My goodness. This is too big.
I thought the bar would be the same size
as the bar we went to in Texas.
I was surprised that it was so big.
My gosh.
I was worried...
that no one would be interested
in our singing.
(It's big, but maybe there will be no one
interested in hearing us sing.)
(The square is full of people.)
It's a good chance,
but they must be nervous.
Why is it so big?
(Singing)
The microphone is clear.
- My gosh.
- He's so good.
He's a professional singer.
He's very good at singing.
The microphone sound
is not distorted at all.
It's so clear.
(He lost his motivation.)
It's so nice.
The previous team
needs to mess up a bit for us.
Then, we can make it work.
(Pani Bottle and Kian84 are shocked.)
Why is he so good?
Let's just think of it
as coming to have fun,
- and lift the mood.
- Yes.
- Let's practice now.
- Yes, let's go inside.
(Practice makes perfect!)
(They arrive at the practice room
with a mix of anxiety and excitement.)
You know the person
who offered to help our practice?
I'll go and find them.
- The house band here?
- Yes.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Yes.
- Oh, yes?
Do you need a band to back you up?
- Can we? Can we use...
- Yes! We can.
We're going to sing a song.
- This song, "September."
- "September?" Okay.
- Yes, we can do that. Yes.
- Yes. Okay.
They are a band associated with that bar.
You call that a house band.
They play music for all the participants
if they want.
- They back you up.
- They're a band.
In the last session of "Gag Concert,"
- Yes.
- they're a house band too.
I'll ask if they can play for us.
- We can practice together.
- Yes.
- That would be better.
- I'll go and ask.
- Pani.
- Yes.
- You look very stressed.
- I'm...
There's a reason for that.
I have a severe fear of stages.
So I usually refuse to be on stage.
I won't do it even if they offer me
thousands and thousands of dollars.
- I won't.
- Right? You're usually...
I don't do it.
Pani's face was frozen.
He doesn't sing when we go to karaoke.
When we were singing
for Kian84's birthday, he was...
(I'm seriously...)
(I have a severe fear of stages.)
(The stage that Pani was afraid of)
(A karaoke session with three people)
(To me, this is a stage.)
(In the end, he sat...)
(and sang with his eyes closed.)
(A surprising high-pitched shouting)
(He's quite good at singing.)
(He ended up sweating a lot.)
I'm a bit...
I hate going on stage.
But...
I'm reminding myself of Kian84's dream.
(He knows that
it was Kian84's long-held dream.)
I just kept telling myself
that we had to show our best performance
no matter what.
I felt...
less nervous than usual.
(He returns after finding the house band.)
How did it go?
- Oh, hello.
- What's up, guys?
(Nice to meet you!)
How's it going? My name is Teo.
- Teo?
- Yes.
- Kenny.
- Oh, nice.
- Hi.
- Teo, Tyler.
- Having a house band is a great support.
- My name is Kian84.
- Yes, nice to meet you.
- It's my friend.
You look like John Lennon.
Don't they all look like
they play the guitar well?
How do you call yourselves, all three?
- It's called "Yay Hi."
- "Yay Hi?"
- Yes.
- Y-A-Y-H-I.
- You can sing however you want.
Their band name is "Yay Hi."
- "Yay Hi?"
- "Yay Hi."
PKT!
- PKT.
- "PKT" and "Yay Hi."
Later, you can do the thing.
- What?
- The introduction on stage.
"Yay Hi" with "PKT,"
a collaborative stage.
He's mixing Korean words.
- We're here.
- My gosh.
- Shall we?
- Yes.
(They're going straight to practice.)
(He is determined.)
All right.
Attention!
(They practiced singing
"September" the whole trip.)
Okay.
- They must be nervous.
- Even I'm nervous.
- Ready? All right. Let's go.
- Let's go!
(PKT Band, let's go!)
One, two, three, four.
Oh, that works with a guitar.
(Kenny's clean guitar lead)
He's using an icebox as a drum.
- He is...
- They played a good harmony.
(With a trembling heart,
the first rehearsal begins.)
(Do you remember)
(Teo's steady start)
(Let's focus.)
(Missing the beat)
(It's unstable
starting from the first chorus.)
- Chasing the clouds
- It's his first time.
(Next is Kian84's part.)
(He missed the beat.)
(But he tries to fix it fast.)
(Blue talk and love)
He's playing with the beat.
(He misses the beat again.)
(Screaming in crescendo)
(It's a disaster.)
(He steadies his mind...)
(and sings the chorus.)
(Pani)
(Cover for me.)
(The last Pani Bottle's part)
(The bell was ringin')
Oh, gosh.
- His throat isn't warmed up yet.
(His voice sounds metallic because
his throat isn’t warmed up enough.)
(He quickly clears his throat.)
(He starts sweating.)
(Ba-du)
(Teo makes a small mistake too.)
This is difficult.
It's their first time.
It's a rehearsal too.
- You can do well on stage.
- Of course.
(PKT Band focuses seriously,
matching the harmony.)
(With tension at an all-time high.
the first rehearsal...)
(is complete!)
- My goodness.
- Yes.
- That helped so much.
- I'm the weak link.
Yes, we were getting on. Oh, my gosh.
I practiced for more than a week!
It gets us together.
Yes, you bring them together.
I can't believe I forgot the lyrics
during such a great performance.
I'm worried about myself.
I forgot the lyrics.
I practiced for about a week in Korea.
It didn't show during the rehearsal.
We're in trouble.
We need to perform in an hour.
Will everything be all right?
We had no time. We had to practice more.
That's what filled up my mind.
I'm sweating.
(The atmosphere in the practice room
is becoming tense.)
- When you miss the beat,
- I practiced for a week.
- it drags everything.
- Why am I missing the beat?
(The atmosphere in the practice room
is becoming tense.)
Their morale has dropped.
- The important thing is that...
- Say, do you remember
it's better to sing comfortably
in a way that suits you rather than...
forcing yourself
to do something you can't.
That way, the audience will also have fun.
I try not to force myself to sing...
in falsetto because it always cracks.
So find what's comfortable.
Just find comfortable tones
and sing comfortably.
- Yes, let's do that.
- Yes.
For the ba-du part, don't say ba-du.
Let's just cater it to him.
You're singing the best right now.
You're getting completely better, right?
Yes. Praise breeds willingness!
Of course.
Teo's presence has been a great support
from beginning to end.
"Don't worry about this."
"I experienced it,
and you don't need to worry about it."
He said it in a charismatic way.
I have had a lot of stage experience
through theater.
I tried to set the environment for them,
so I did my best in the practice room.
Teo is definitely the big brother.
(Thanks to him,
PKT Band practices even harder.)
It's done.
What's going on?
We made a choreography too.
- They have a choreography.
- Yes.
(Wait for me, my debut stage!)
(The prior stages finish one by one.)
(Now, it's the 11th stage.)
(The audience's excitement
gradually rises.)
(And everything is being watched by...)
"A lonely musician."
- His gaze.
- The gaze.
I look like some master artist.
You look like Na Hoon A
before going on stage.
- Are you guys ready?
- Yes.
- Yes? All right.
- Kind of. Yes.
How many teams remain now?
- Oh, I think there's two.
- Two.
This is the most nerve-wracking moment.
Okay.
Oh, gosh.
I got nervous
when it was almost our turn to perform.
(As the stage approaches,
they get more and more nervous.)
Of course, that makes you nervous.
I'm going to perform a song,
something I never expected to do.
You knew this was about
Music Adventure by Accident.
- I'm sorry.
- No, let's go.
I didn't know it would turn out like this.
(It's fine.)
We need to go to that side.
Yes?
(They go backstage to wait.)
(The previous performance
comes to an end.)
He's good.
He continues to practice.
- Just now.
- Cramming practice.
(Rookie singers are struggling to relax.)
(The bell was...)
- The bell was ringin'
- Pani, don't be nervous.
Thank you to everybody
who came out to sign up.
- Is it our turn?
- Yes.
- Oh, shoot.
- On every Tuesday is the...
- I'm nervous!
- Thank you, guys.
Don't be.
(He relies on Teo more than ever today.)
All right, guys.
Thank you for being here tonight.
We want to introduce our new friends.
They're from Korea.
It's their first time performing live
on a stage.
So make sure you give it up for them.
We'll play a little classic here.
(The audience applauds in support
at the mention of their first stage.)
(They finally go on stage!)
- Oh, my goodness.
- Finally.
(Groaning)
Yes, thank you.
(PKT Band is on stage.)
Thank you.
(Good luck with your first stage!)
From that moment on,
the tension begins to fade,
and your mind goes blank.
You're right.
(Feeling hopeless)
(Kian84, introduce our band!)
Oh, well. Oh, yes.
(A 4-combo of nervousness)
We're from Korea.
Ki, Pa, and Dex.
Dex?
Oh, I said Dex.
- Gosh.
- My goodness. I'm sorry!
- He didn't even go there!
- Ki, Pa, and Dex.
I didn't know you loved Dex so much.
He introduced Pani Bottle as Ki
and himself as Pa.
- He was very nervous.
- Because he was nervous.
- I guess I was nervous.
- He's saying something different.
He suddenly speaks of Dex.
(Soothing the anxious mind with Dex)
With Lee Hi band and...
- Lee Hi?
He's in the same company as her.
Houston people, nice to meet you!
(Houston people are kind-hearted.)
Do you want to say something?
Thank you for... With us.
- Pani is usually good at English.
- I've never seen him like that.
He's nervous.
Thank you. Okay. I think we're ready.
(They finished the stage greeting
with great difficulty.)
(Now, it's the main performance!)
I was worried about forgetting the lyrics.
I'm singing once
and if I forget the lyrics, I'm done.
(This can be his first and last stage.)
But I can't back out now,
so I might as well just enjoy it.
Right. You're strong on stage.
But I couldn't say I couldn't do it
when we went all the way there.
I thought I should do my best
until the end...
to make Kian84's dream come true.
There was no backing out now.
I went up thinking, "Let's just do it
even if I forget some parts."
(Just going head-on like always)
I think we're ready.
Yes.
(His signature booster move)
(One, two, three, four!)
("September" by Earth, Wind and Fire)
Let's go.
(Kian84 as main vocal)
(Yoo Teo as main dancer)
(Pani Bottle as sub vocal)
(PKT Band)
PKT Band.
(Let's make a hot debut.)
(Let's go!)
Do you remember
Nice.
- The 21st night of September
- September
(The chorus enters at a perfect timing.)
He's relaxed.
(Kian84's solo part follows.)
(The part where he kept
missing the beat...)
(and rambled alien language)
(Neat)
(Charming)
(Only blue talk and love)
(Remember)
- He's showing off.
- He's good.
(Boosting in happiness)
(Singing)
(Ba-dee-ya)
(The "ba-dee-ya" he's been singing
all throughout the trip)
That's a neat falsetto.
(People are moving with the beat!)
- Ba-dee-ya
- People are enjoying it.
(It's PKT's highlight part.)
(Let's go, Pani Bottle!)
(The nightingale with a hoarse voice)
The bell was ringin'
- He's good.
- All the souls were singin'
- He sang a high note.
- That's amazing.
(Our youngest is the best.)
(They carry on with that energy.)
(Are you all ready?)
(Ba-du-da)
Look at the dance.
(Their cute dance)
People there have started
to enjoy the music.
They start dancing.
(People come in front of the stage
in excitement!)
Was that an improvisation?
(They're no longer nervous.)
It just feels like a club.
- You did well.
- It's cool. This is like the climax.
(Playful Bottle unlocked)
- Ba-dee-ya, say, do you remember?
- Ba-dee-ya-dee-ya-dee-ya
- Ba-dee-ya, say, dancing in September
(Ba-dee-ya!)
(Golden dreams were shiny days!)
- Ba-dee-ya
- We're from Korea.
Amazing.
Nice to meet you, Houston people!
You filled in that part.
(It ends with the youngest's shout.)
(PKT Band somehow made its debut.)
- What a relief.
- Thank you. I love Houston!
(Bowing)
- Thank you. It was awesome.
- Thank you with...
- Thank you with Lee Hi.
- "Lee Hi?"
- Yay Hi.
- Thank you.
I loved that moment the most.
There was...
a dopamine rush.
People recognized me and talked to me.
There was a strange excitement
that felt good.
(The dream of becoming
a singer one day...)
(that made young Kian84's heart beat)
(But others...)
(found that dream immature.)
(But today, in the US,)
The opportunity really came to me.
(he really stood on stage!)
He did so well.
It's not easy for people who have
no stage experience to do that.
While we were singing,
people came out to dance.
It was thrilling.
I realized we were doing something
people could enjoy.
I started enjoying myself
from that moment.
(The stage spoke to him as well.)
I was touched by Pani Bottle.
- I think he overcame his fear.
- He did.
I was personally satisfied.
It feels like I completed
a difficult task. I felt good.
Thank you. I love Houston!
(It may have been a poor stage to some,)
(but it was the most valuable experience
for those who were in it together.)
- How was it?
- It was fine.
Thank you!
It was great.
Thank you. It was great. Great support.
(Their first stage
that made them nervous has ended.)
I kept forgetting the lyrics.
- I don't even remember if I did well.
- Only "dancing in September."
- It didn't show.
- No one noticed that.
(Thankful)
- I did my best.
- It made such a great difference.
(The second brother
still hasn't come back.)
(Relaxed)
(Kiss)
I did it without realizing it.
I think I was overwhelmed with emotions.
I came to my senses when he kissed me.
(He kissed him
so he could wake up from his dream.)
(Feeling shy)
You did well.
It's a relief...
I didn't forget the lyrics.
It was so nice. Everything was great.
Do you guys want some beer?
I want to buy for you.
- I'll take that.
- Okay.
- Good.
- I said I'd buy them a beer.
- That's all right, right?
- Beer.
- Great.
(Cheering)
Yes. Have a nice day!
Thank you very much. Have a good night.
- Have a good night.
- They have fans.
- Good night. Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
I feel happy watching Pani Bottle
because he looks so happy.
- I'll buy the drinks.
- Beer.
- I got it.
- You will?
Over there...
I won't stop him from buying.
(Immediately takes the offer)
You're very close to him.
You're friends, right?
- You were good.
- You too.
I was very worried,
but it was way better than I thought.
(Feeling proud)
- Very satisfied.
- I feel relaxed.
- We haven't had dinner yet.
- Let's have dinner.
Order anything.
Good job.
(They have an afterparty
with a small dinner.)
Thank you so much. It's actually...
It ended so well.
How...
I honestly thought I'd keep feeling bad
if I missed a line.
But I missed the "dancing in September"
part a few times.
It didn't show, though.
It's because there were three of us.
That's why bands are charming.
We three went up there
and covered each other's weaknesses.
- That's right.
- So we could improve together.
If it were just one person,
it would have shown
if there was a mistake.
(Touched)
I'm very happy.
It's like you won a golden medal
at the Paris Summer Games.
- Right. It felt like that too.
- "You did well."
"No. You did well."
It's like we went on a world tour.
- But I understand.
- Right.
I mean...
- I'm so annoying.
- No, you're not.
- It was your first stage.
- It makes sense.
So, what time tomorrow...
When do you leave?
- We leave at 4:45 p.m.
- At 4 p.m.
We only have eight hours left.
- It would end if we sleep.
- It's the last night.
We're going to the same airport anyway.
We could take you.
- No. Don't take me there.
- Why not?
Don't do that.
(An unexpected refusal of kindness)
- Why?
- Sleep more.
- You didn't get much sleep.
- He's considerate.
You drove the whole day.
You woke up at 5 a.m. today.
But when you go to Jamaica, make sure...
you stay healthy.
I'll get more inspiration there.
Make sure you stay healthy.
He keeps picking up weird things to eat.
- I didn't pick them up.
- You did.
- I just ate. I didn't pick them up.
- That's hilarious.
He picked them up.
You still haven't
eaten the parasiticides, have you?
- He's worried he'd eat weird things.
- I have to eat.
And I'm very thankful.
- I'm thankful too.
- For this moment.
(They're good friends
who joined his journey to his dream.)
You sang it with me.
The last one? Cheers?
- Cheers.
- Cheers. Great work.
Great work.
- I want to go there again.
- You ended the last night well.
It's nice.
(They return to the hotel
with no electricity.)
Gosh.
We can't sleep here.
- It was dark.
- It was boiling in there.
Charger.
(Wearing his pants)
They had air conditioning in the lobby.
All the guests came
and slept in the lobby.
(The guests evacuated to the lobby.)
- You paid for the rooms...
- Right.
- and slept in the lobby?
- In the lobby.
I've never seen such a sight in Sheraton.
But that also became a memory.
- It's a memory.
- Right.
It felt like I was in a public bathhouse.
It was nice.
- It's a bonding experience.
- Right.
(I'm here too.)
(The youngest also joins
the lobby bathhouse.)
(They make an unforgettable memory
even on the last night.)
(The day ends like that.)
(The last morning in the US)
It's the morning of farewell.
Would you really be okay
even if we don't take you there?
Am I six years old?
Are you taking an Uber?
- A taxi?
- It's okay.
Can you take a taxi?
Goodness.
Why wouldn't he be able to take a taxi?
- Do you think I'm stupid?
- No.
I wasn't looking down on you.
I was just worried.
It's becoming an obsession of yours.
That's pretty offensive.
I can take a taxi, man!
- I even know how to call an Uber!
- Okay.
I'm just worried, that's all.
He's so tired
that his shirt is inside and out.
He must be exhausted.
Okay. Thanks for worrying.
Thanks for thinking so far ahead.
Sending you to Jamaica
feels like I'm sending a child away.
We were bickering,
but it felt pretty weird...
- to send him away alone.
- Right.
- They didn't want to part ways.
- Yes, you've grown so close.
- I called an Uber.
- Did you?
- We can just wait, then.
Don't get hurt.
People always told me...
(People have always told the two
that they were different.)
(Strangely enough,
they were on the same wavelength.)
Kian84 and I...
seem like people of the same kind.
So, I feel so comfortable around him.
I really do.
(He feels comfortable around Kian84.)
It was so nice...
that I could be myself.
(He was able to show his innocent side.)
A lot of people said that they found...
Teo's new side through this show.
We were able to show
our true selves to each other.
(Precious moments
of finding their true selves)
They both welcomed me...
and open-mindedly embraced me...
so that I could play my role properly.
I was so grateful for that.
(He's grateful for them.)
Pani...
is a cute and adorable younger brother.
He works so hard that he inspires me.
(There's pizza in the back. I bought it.)
(Didn't you say
you wanted to see a tornado?)
Without having to tell him...
Pani worked so hard...
so that the trip
could be smooth sailing for everyone.
That's his way of being considerate.
He drove the whole time
so that they could rest.
He feels like a tour guide of Earth.
An Earth guide.
- An Earth guide. That's cool.
- An Earth guide.
He's indispensable.
We went on a trip,
as Kian84 wished.
(He was getting bored of traveling alone.)
(He realized the value
of doing things together.)
(I love Kian84's ideas and everything.)
(I obviously root for him.)
(Wherever he wants him,)
(he runs to him and joins him.)
To me, Kian84 is someone...
who's sincere about everything.
That sums it up.
(He supported Kian84's sincerity...)
(and found the joy of traveling,
which he had forgotten.)
So much has happened.
- That was so...
- That's the last scene.
I hope Kian84 stays safe in Jamaica.
He can either find musical inspiration...
or not.
I just want him to come back in one piece.
(Stay healthy and enjoy the trip!)
Feeling things through traveling
was all good,
but I also liked that I had
achieved something in the end.
The three of us...
had one goal and became one.
(They became one during this trip.)
I obviously felt a sense of belonging,
and they were reliable.
I'm so thankful that I almost feel sorry.
(I love the days we've spent together)
What?
- No way.
- It must be a follow-up song.
- It's a follow-up song!
- By Kian84.
Keep your head up.
- Are you crying because you're moved?
- Are you crying?
Is it a group song?
It's a group song called "Like a Friend."
("Like a Friend"
by Kian84, Pani Bottle, and Yoo Teo)
(Let's paint the endless stories
once again)
(Like the stars filling up the dark night)
(Remember)
(In this long journey called life,)
(a friend whom you can always rely on.)
(The happy moments that they shared...)
(will be a memory
that can console them in hard times.)
It's "Like a Friend."
Though their trip is over,
- we have a new song.
- We do have a new song.
- "Like a Friend."
Liking a friend.
- No, it means that it's like a friend.
- It's like a friend.
Like a friend.
You even went to the US!
There can be various interpretations.
- Is it Teo's kiss from earlier?
- Yes, it has a double meaning.
- Yes.
- It has a double meaning.
- He said it was liking a friend.
- I never thought of that.
You're right.
The group song, "I Liked a Friend."
(I liked a friend of mine)
Are you all listening to it?
- Yes.
- Please show your love.
You're going to miss the flight. Go on.
(I'll be back!)
- See you in Korea!
- Okay!
Let's go to bed.
The living should keep on living.
- "Let's go to bed."
- I love that.
- It's perfect to the finish.
- Get some more rest.
(The second chapter begins.)
He's back to being alone,
like the start of the trip.
I can't wait to watch it.
(Houston Airport)
(Flight time: 3 hours and 21 minutes)
(Sangster International Airport
in Montego Bay)
(To Jamaica)
I'm on my way to the final destination,
Jamaica.
I wonder what kind of country it is.
(He starts to see the unknown land.)
(The emerald Caribbean Sea)
That's lovely.
- Oh, my.
- Awesome.
(An island covered
with green tropical trees)
Goodness.
No way.
It's different from Madagascar.
(Jamaica)
(A Latin American island
with a population of 2.82 million,)
(6 times the size of Jeju Island)
Jamaica, an island nation
in Latin America,
boasts cultural diversity
and stunning natural beauty.
(They have ancient traditions.)
It's a vibrant and wild country
with the emerald blue Caribbean Sea...
and the lush, green Blue Mountains...
that stay verdant year-round.
Jamaica is familiar to us
as the homeland...
of sprinting legend, Usain Bolt,
and the birthplace of reggae,
made famous by the legendary Bob Marley.
(The homeland of Bob Marley,
the legend of reggae)
(Kian84 in Jamaica)
(Sangster International Airport
in Montego Bay, Jamaica)
I've finally arrived.
Now,
I'm going to exchange the leftover cash.
(His trip begins by exchanging money.)
Jamaican money.
I was so thankful that they collected...
their remaining cash...
- They did?
so that I could use it in Jamaica.
What's their currency?
- They use dollars. Jamaican dollars.
- Dollars.
- Jamaican dollars.
One thousand Jamaican dollars...
is 9,000 Korean won,
which is 9 US dollars.
So, 1,000 Jamaican dollars is 9 dollars.
(He exchanged about 540 dollars.)
The largest bill is a 5,000-dollar bill.
(Looking gaunt)
I arrived in Jamaica on a tight schedule.
I should get a cup of coffee.
Most people here are Black.
- Taxi?
- Sorry.
Someone's coming to pick me up.
- Come on, man. Taxi.
- No, my fam...
(He says no as he needs to get coffee.)
It's been a while since we...
It's been a while since we last saw this.
- You're right!
- I've missed this so much.
- We haven't seen it in so long.
- I missed it so much.
Back then...
That's right.
He used to be the Pied Piper.
(The pushover used to have
taxi drivers follow him everywhere.)
It had been so long
since I last felt annoyed.
- It feels exactly the same.
- You never get used to it.
It was a fixed-price system in New York.
- It was.
- But now he has to bargain.
- So he must be tired.
- It's another thing to deal with.
- I was.
- You need coffee right now.
- Yes.
- Come on, man.
- Taxi.
- No. My fam...
He needs coffee immediately.
Yes.
"Sure?"
My family. No taxi.
- Sorry. No taxi.
- "No taxi."
No taxi.
- I'll take you anywhere you want.
- Sorry?
- My family is on the bus.
(Looking)
I told him like ten times
that I didn't want a taxi.
- He keeps asking me if I need a taxi.
- You sure?
- No, thank you.
- "Eleventh time."
He's persistent.
(He still won't go.)
I thought I'd be fine,
but without Teo and Pani,
- it feels pretty lonely.
- It must.
(Poor him.)
I feel lonely.
(I miss Teo and Pani.)
Coffee will be my joy.
(He finds a shop.)
"Red Strap?"
What's your name?
(What is that?)
- "Red Strip?"
- Red Stripe.
Red Stripe? Jamaican beer?
Okay.
I should try Jamaican beer.
- How much?
- It's 700.
Why? Because it's so cheap?
Goodness. Unbelievable.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
This is a Jamaican beer.
- This looks like a pesticide.
- Gosh.
People in Yeoju prefer this design.
It's used as a weedkiller.
It helps with rice farming,
so they like it.
Guys, guess how much this is.
It was 700 Jamaican dollars,
so it's like 55 or 60 cents.
What?
- I don't think so.
- How do you always get it wrong?
- It's because you're tired.
- She's right.
- You haven't had coffee yet.
- It's not as cheap as you think.
Every time I drank it,
I thought, "I'm saving money."
It's better to drink it with that thought.
It's one less thing to worry about.
That's true.
What you believe in is correct.
I can't help but feel joyful
if their beer is 55 cents.
That's good. "How lucky I am!"
"It's 55 cents if I think it's 55 cents."
(Deeply satisfied)
Let's get a taxi first.
I bet he's excited.
- Taxi!
- Taxi?
- Taxi, yes.
- Come on.
- Wait. It's the same guy.
- No way.
It's him, right?
What's your name?
Kian84 went back because he felt bad.
We were going anyway,
so I just agreed to go.
- What's your name?
- Blue.
- Blue. Your name is Blue.
- Blue?
- Are you a taxi driver?
- Yes.
- Nice to meet you.
- You're welcome.
- What's your name?
- My name is Kian84.
- Kian84.
- Yes.
- Okay.
Turn on the AC.
It's 34 degrees Celsius?
It's summer all year long.
(Let's fasten the seat belt.)
Wait. Where's the seat belt?
The belt.
It's not Adventure by Accident
with a working seat belt.
It has to be a rocky start.
It's not Adventure by Accident
if the car is normal.
You can't even have windows that open.
- What's with the seat belt?
- You bet.
- No. It doesn't work.
- No belt?
- No.
- Okay.
- I'm a good driver.
- Yes.
You're the best driver?
- Okay.
I believe you.
That's Adventure by Accident to you.
MBC, please understand.
It's tied up.
It was fair. Both seat belts
in the back seat were broken.
- "Fair?"
- Yes.
And the seat belt in the passenger seat
was also broken.
Only his belt worked.
(Trustworthy)
I'm familiar with not wearing
a seat belt when I'm abroad.
It happened in India too.
The missing seat belt wasn't
the problem in Bolivia.
They didn't have side-view mirrors.
(During his last trip)
(No side-view mirrors)
(The car stopped out of nowhere.)
(He manually got rid of the sign.)
Missing seat belts is nothing.
It finally feels like
Adventure by Accident...
now that I'm in a taxi
without any working seat belts.
This is Adventure by Accident.
I'm sure he'll drive well.
Is Kingston Jamaica's number-one city?
Kingston?
There's Seoul in Korea
and New York in America.
- Kingston in Jamaica?
- Kingston.
I see.
There are more locals than tourists
in Kingston.
(It's the capital of Jamaica,)
(but you can experience
the lifestyle of the local people.)
I wanted to experience
the local lifestyle.
That is a fishing village.
- "Fishing?"
- Yes.
He's your tour guide too.
- What a beautiful sea.
- Yes.
- Very nice.
- Okay.
(He rolls down the window.)
(The first thing he sees in Jamaica)
That's fantastic.
(Blue Jamaica)
- Goodness.
- Beautiful.
(The ocean view dazzles you
as it's a country of nature.)
(Facing its nature,)
(Kian84 appreciates the smell
with his entire face.)
Is it nice?
Nice. Very beautiful.
(The taxi keeps driving
through the beautiful scenery.)
(He books a hotel on his way.)
(He checks how much he has,)
(and the taxi is still going.)
(Knocked out)
(They drove across Jamaican nature
for 2 hours...)
(to get to the end of the island.)
He went to the other side.
Finally. The sun is down.
Kingston is pretty far.
What's the time?
I feel like we've been driving
for three hours now.
(The taxi is in Kingston now.)
- Everyone, I'm in Madagascar...
- What?
(No, he's in Jamaica.)
He's too tired.
He said, "Madagascar."
Just think it's Madagascar.
He might start saying, "Pani," in the air.
(He's going to start talking
to imaginary friends.)
I'm in downtown Madagascar.
(The taxi heads
to the center of Kingston.)
(But the deeper they go in...)
It looks pretty dangerous at night.
It's so dark.
- It looks...
- You said you were scared...
when you first went to Brooklyn.
It seemed far more dangerous
than Brooklyn.
(Laughing awkwardly)
This does not look easy.
It's like a mixture of Varanasi
and Iquitos.
This smells familiar.
(Dynamic things are about to happen.)
Yes. Let's stop here.
(The taxi stopped at last.)
Yes. Thank you, driver.
(He arrived in Kingston after 10 hours,
including the standby at the airport.)
This is the most popular city in Jamaica.
(But for the most popular city,)
(the streets look pretty desolate.)
The capital isn't...
I've been in the US for too long.
I thought there would be tall buildings
as it was the capital.
But this is Adventure by Accident.
(He walks to his hotel for a long time.)
(Sighing)
Let's get some food and go to sleep.
(Tired and filthy)
- He's so tired...
- Poor him.
when he's in a new place.
(He's drained from traveling all day.)
What's this? A local shop?
(On his way to his hotel,)
(he walks by a street stall.)
What's that?
Nice to meet you.
- Hello. Good night. Jerk chicken?
- Hello.
- Yes. Chicken?
- Yes, it's chicken.
Jamaican barbecue is incredible, you know.
I didn't know jerk chicken
was Jamaican food.
- How much?
- It's 1,000.
One thousand Jamaican dollars?
(It's about 9 dollars.)
It's only 90 cents?
What is wrong with you?
I was thinking, "How does she make
a living if she sells them for 90 cents?"
(He's even worried about the seller.)
That's cheap. I'll take one.
It's so cheap.
(His 9-dollar chicken is being cut.)
That looks nice and plump.
It looks good.
(Excited)
Nice. What's the sauce?
I have ketchup,
- and then I have pepper.
- Ketchup.
- Pepper.
- Yes. What sauce would you like?
Spicy.
- Tell me when to stop.
- Okay.
- That's it?
- Yes.
Their prices are the lowest
among all the countries I've been to.
Should I get one more?
I don't think it's big enough.
- I'll have one more chicken, please.
- Okay.
- One more.
- Another one?
Yes.
It's only 1 dollar and 80 cents
for 2 chickens.
(No, it's 18 dollars.)
No. Not the spicy one.
Very cheap.
Thank you. Good luck.
- Thank you.
- Good luck.
(He happily walks to his hotel
under a huge illusion.)
Where's the hotel?
(He happily walks to his hotel
under a huge illusion.)
I woke up at 6:30 a.m. in Houston
and went to the airport.
There were so many people at the airport,
so I waited about three hours there.
Then, I flew here.
I should check in first.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Hi.
All right. Here you go.
- Thank you.
- All right.
(He swiftly checks in as he's tired.)
It's cool in here.
Nice!
(He feels better
as his room is spacious and pleasant.)
I'm sure you've noticed,
but my hotel rooms are getting better.
- The more tired you get...
- It's tiring.
You slept on the ground at Central Park
on your first day in New York.
I could do it at first,
but now I can't sleep
unless it's a five-star hotel.
- That's what I'm talking about.
- Look how big the bed is.
- That bed is...
- You could fit five people on it.
(Large)
(Taking off)
(Charismatic)
(He shows off his charisma
while he's still tired.)
Man, I'm wiped.
(He washes down his fatigue
from moving for hours.)
- As expected, he sits on the floor.
- It's perfect.
It's what we're familiar with.
I missed this so much.
I hope the chicken is good.
(His jerk chicken
looks properly marinated.)
A bowl of instant rice would be perfect.
- Chicken and rice.
That would be chicken and rice.
- That looks delicious.
- It was delicious.
- It looks like it.
- And it's only dark meat.
That's what I loved about it.
(Deboning)
We have marinated chicken in Korea,
- and they have jerk chicken.
- That looks scrumptious.
(He licks his fingers
out of satisfaction.)
(Toothbrush)
What's he doing?
- With a toothbrush?
- It's a beer.
He popped his beer with a toothbrush.
(Nonchalantly opening his beer
with a toothbrush)
(That's what I'm talking about.)
(He can't stop exclaiming.)
- How many times...
- It felt so good.
Weren't you the happiest then?
This is paradise.
Chicken and beer.
It felt so nice. To be honest,
whether I'm traveling, working,
or staying at home all day,
I finish the day...
with food and a glass of beer or soju
before bed.
That's what I live for.
- That takes up half the joy in life.
- It's the little things in life.
I figure it's the same for everyone.
(The small satisfactions
give him the drive to live.)
Men who like drinking
and late-night snacks.
(After a long day of traveling...)
He eats on the floor
wherever he is in this world.
(It's time for bed now.)
This is so nice.
- It was so pleasant. Nice and soft.
- It must feel good.
Good for you.
(He dives on the bed.)
(His tough first day in Jamaica goes by.)
(Day 10 of the trip)
(He meets the morning of Jamaica
for the first time.)
His first morning in Jamaica.
(Swollen)
I guess that chicken was pretty salty.
(Exclaiming)
(Is he nodding?)
What's this?
(He's turning the camera around
out of the blue.)
Is this a panorama?
(He's turning the camera around
out of the blue.)
I never imagined I'd come to Jamaica.
I woke up, and I was in Jamaica.
In Jamaica...
(He unexpectedly greets
his morning in Jamaica.)
I slept,
and it's time to start the day.
(He gets ready to head out.)
(Lying down)
(Checking the room service menu)
- You're looking at the room service menu?
- Yes.
Excuse me?
Two fried eggs...
I meant to pack my lunch
by ordering room service.
Thank you.
(He orders his food and steps out.)
Excuse me?
I ordered takeaway food...
through room service.
I should go to the beach
that we talked about yesterday.
- Taxi.
- Where would you like to go?
I'm going to...
- Hellshire Beach.
- Hellshire Beach?
(It's the beach
that his taxi driver recommended.)
(Hellshire Beach)
(It must be like Haeundae Beach in Korea.)
(There are a lot of Rastafarians.)
(Rasta?)
(Like Bob Marley...)
(The local people wearing dreadlocks?)
I'm going to Hellshire Beach
which he recommended.
I'll check out the beach
now that I'm here.
Jamaica with the beautiful Caribbean Sea.
Thank you.
(He gets his takeaway food.)
He's going to tell you.
You're the driver?
(He moves to take the taxi.)
Here? Taxi?
What...
- Oh, my!
- They called him a limo.
I was annoyed
that the taxi didn't have a seat belt.
It's so fun to watch him
forget about his original intention.
That's what all hotel taxis look like.
They're all big.
Yes. Hellshire Beach.
(He heads to Hellshire Beach
in a luxurious taxi.)
He even has his collars up.
(His collars are up.)
(The taxi keeps moving
while Kian84 enjoys modern society.)
(It finally stops after a while.)
Yes.
Here?
- You can walk down...
- Okay.
- to the beach. It's mostly...
Is this the beach?
- Straight down.
- Straight?
- To your right.
- Okay.
The number-one beach in Kingston,
- I hope it's good.
- Hellshire Beach.
(He gets out of the taxi.)
(Closing automatically)
- It's an automatic door!
- It is.
That's so high-tech!
I loved it.
(Enjoying the sweet technology)
"Welcome..."
(Welcome.)
(Only a sign welcomes him
on this empty road.)
Is it because it's hot?
There aren't as many people as I expected.
- Right. I thought it was number one.
- He said it was number one.
What?
(Peeking)
Gosh.
Do they naturally get dreadlocks?
They all have dreadlocks.
(Born with dreadlocks)
(Surprised)
That grandpa...
- Check out his aura.
- He's...
- Hello. Come in.
- A hundred years... Hello.
- Come here.
- "Come here?"
What?
- What are you guys videoing?
- Sorry?
What are you videoing?
- "Video?"
- Yes.
This is for a Korean TV show.
So, you're an actor?
Actor... Maybe.
(Giggling)
He said, "Maybe," again.
His "maybe" worked on Nicole
and the Jamaican woman.
It came in handy.
(He flirted with Nicole, the Texan woman,
by saying, "Maybe.")
(The magic word also works in Jamaica.)
She looks kind.
- Rasta?
- Yes.
We're getting a cool breeze.
(We're resting under the shade
as it's so hot.)
We're here taking in the breeze.
It's like the countryside in Korea.
- Is this Hellshire Beach?
- Yes.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hi.
I'll come back when I'm bored.
(He keeps moving.)
Oh, this is it.
(Looking around)
Gosh.
This must be it.
The water looks fabulous.
- Look at the ocean.
- The color is amazing.
That's insane.
I hear that Hellshire Beach
is less crowded than other beaches.
It's a hidden beach
that's mostly visited by locals.
That's nice.
I love that.
(Hellshire Beach)
(He safely arrives,
thanks to the locals' help.)
Beautiful.
(He looks for a spot to eat his food.)
Hello.
- Can I eat lunch here?
- Ya Mon.
He said, "Ya Mon!"
(It's a Jamaican expression
of saying, "Okay.")
No cash? Is it free to eat here?
- It's okay.
- Okay.
(He gets permission and sits down.)
(Taking out his lunch box)
Gosh, he's eating there?
That's plentiful.
(He's excited about his first meal today.)
Rice.
It was so good to eat rice
after such a long time.
(He gobbles it down.)
He eats so well.
(A bite with rice)
That looks tasty.
(This is what I'm talking about.)
(He must have liked the food.)
(He goes through the bag
to see if he has more.)
He's a good painter.
(There's a painter next to him?)
There are good painters everywhere
in the world.
(He finds a man of common interest
and keeps looking.)
(He can't stop looking back.)
That old man looks just like Leroy.
(A character from a video game)
(The same hair?)
From "Tekken?"
- They all have dreadlocks.
- Their styles...
- are amazing.
- Is that hair trending in Jamaica?
(He takes a close look
and gets back to his food.)
(Let's see.)
He should go for a dip.
- Yes, he loves water.
- Yes.
(He's calm in front of the water,
which he loves.)
- What's wrong?
- Is he too tired?
How should I put it?
It was kind of like swimming
at Aewol Beach in Jeju.
It didn't feel so special.
But behind me...
You know, there was this movie
back in the day.
- Was it called "Alien Family?"
- "Coneheads?"
- Oh, I remember! It was a fun movie.
- You know, right?
They had large heads
like the characters in the movie.
(He's interested in their hair,
which he's unfamiliar with.)
(He finishes his food.)
He's painting.
- Nice to meet you.
- Yes, man.
- Yes. Is it acrylic?
- Yes.
Yes.
This is a Rastaman in Jamaica.
Rastaman. Is this you?
The first Rastaman in Jamaica.
- The first Rastaman?
- Yes.
- He's the first one?
(Is that right?)
- Are you a Rasta?
- Yes.
- Rasta...
- Rastafarian.
(Who are Rastas with their unique hair?)
Rastafarianism is a religion
that reinterprets the Bible to reflect...
the aspirations of Jamaicans,
- and notable followers are called Rastas.
- Rastas.
It promotes a naturalistic way of life,
striving for self-sufficiency...
and minimizing artificial influences
while living in harmony with nature.
The colors that represent Rastafarianism
are red, yellow, and green,
which have greatly influenced
Jamaican culture and art.
Bob Marley himself was also a Rasta.
(Bob Marley, the singer
who represents Rastas)
What does a Rasta mean?
What's the lifestyle of a Rasta?
Natural. It's living in nature.
- "Natural."
- Yes.
Nature.
It was sort of like a monk in that sense.
- They're like cowboys.
- They are.
- No meat?
- No meat.
- No fish?
- Really? They're vegan.
(Most Rastas are vegan.)
But they still eat fish.
They don't eat meat.
(Exclaiming)
What's with your hair?
Why is your hat so big?
Because it locks.
- Locks.
Does that mean I can't be a Rasta
without thick hair?
No hair, no Rasta?
(You're not supposed to cut it.)
It has to be natural.
- Natural.
(They suddenly take it off
after they finish talking.)
(Falling)
(What is that?)
What's that?
(Why are tree stems falling...)
(from their heads?)
Unbelievable.
Yes, it goes down to the ground.
You're a real Rasta.
Real.
- Amazing.
- It's Rasta.
(He was hiding thick hair inside the hat.)
People with...
People with thin hair can't be a Rasta.
How long have you been growing it?
- Sixty years locks.
- Sixty years?
Sixty years.
That has a history.
(The Rasta hair consists
of a decades-long history.)
There's probably
a whole ecosystem in there.
Amazing.
(Cat's cradle?)
Like Rapunzel.
"Rapunzel."
- It's not Rasta but Rapunzel.
- Rapunzel.
- How old are you?
- Seventy-eight.
- Seventy-eight?
- Yes.
You've never had a haircut before
in your life?
No.
Not even for once?
No cut.
Because on the ground,
I was walking on it,
stepping on it, and it dried up.
(Rasta's eco-friendly beauty treatment)
That's one way to get a haircut.
(Keeping the rest of his hair with care)
I have a long way to go.
Wait a minute.
Wait. You can't see anything.
- "Jamaican hermit crab."
He must be really sad.
It's a huge hermit crab.
- I can still see you.
- Can you?
- Yes.
- Impressive.
That's impressive.
(Glancing)
Wearing the beanie deep down
used to be a trend in the past.
(Thinking)
Rasta?
Come on.
Where do I go to see them?
I wanted to see their lives...
in Jamaica.
Like the last time
you got to experience Buddhism...
- when you met young monks.
- Yes.
I decided to visit more Rasta people.
(He expected Rasta
to inspire him big time.)
My friend is...
from the Rasta community.
- Rasta community?
- Yes.
You can meet them there.
This isn't the base for Rasta,
so I have to go there?
I'll take you to the community.
- Community? Rasta community?
- Yes.
Rasta's community?
That's the land of Rasta.
- So if...
- But...
My friend, we'll take you to
the Rasta community.
- Your friend?
- It's in Kingston.
Are we going together?
(I'm busy,
so I'll introduce you to my friend.)
- Okay. Let's go?
- Let's go.
I was expecting you to talk about drawing.
The unexpected Rasta.
- This is...
- What's your name?
My name is Future.
- Future?
- Yes.
Future. My name is Kian84.
- How old are you?
- Fifty-seven.
- Fifty-seven?
- Ya Mon.
The elders there are so hip.
- He's cool.
- Yes.
- This is Joseph.
- Joseph.
- Nice to meet you.
- Yes.
- He's from South Korea.
- My name is Kian84.
- Ya Mon. I'm Joseph from the Rasta.
- Joseph.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Joseph too.
- Joseph too?
- Yes.
Joseph too? Are you his father?
- Two Josephs.
- No.
It looks like...
his hair is...
(Something big must be hiding inside.)
You can guess their spiritual energy
from it.
- The bigger it gets...
- The longer, the bigger.
I see.
What's this?
- These are lots of stuff that I sell.
- Wait.
- I sell... These are like shampoo.
- He made the stuff.
- Shampoo?
- Yes.
- Natural soap.
- Soap.
Ya Mon.
He must've made the shampoo
with natural oil.
- It looks like it.
- Natural shampoo.
- How much?
- A thousand Jamaican.
One thousand Jamaican.
One? I should get one.
(Sniffing)
It smells like garlic.
People might think it's a sauce.
He wants to go to the Rasta community.
(Asking Joseph)
Yes.
- He'll take you to the Rasta community.
- He said you're interested in Rasta.
- Yes. All right. Thank you.
- So up in the mountains.
I'll take you there and show you.
Then I should...
(He feels bad to ask for a favor.)
Well...
Should I pay him?
- No, money. It's a friend thing.
- No money?
(Rastas don't take money.)
- Really?
- Ya Mon.
- Okay.
- Liberty.
It's our way of life. The way we live.
- You live...
- Yes, we live a communal life.
- It's love, man.
- Community.
Oh, nice.
- No charge.
- Thank you.
- Let's go.
- Okay. All right.
Peace out.
(Have a safe trip.)
- This... This car?
- Come around.
Yes.
- The car is...
- You can go in there.
- Here?
- Yes, you go in there.
- Put this in the back.
- Okay.
- What's wrong?
I'm not getting kidnapped, am I?
- Kidnap?
- He's doubtful.
You never know. He said Rasta, but...
- It could be gangsters instead of Rasta.
- True.
Before I followed him,
the production crew checked it.
- Checked Joseph?
- Because it could be dangerous.
He wanted to share the Rasta culture...
- with the Korean production team.
- I see.
That's how we set off.
(Joseph's car's about to set off.)
- It's hot.
- Yes. Very hot.
No AC?
You can get AC if you want.
- AC?
- Yes, do you want AC?
- Oh, the AC.
- Yes.
It's all broken.
That's naturalism.
- Even the AC is natural.
- Yes.
- Very cool.
- Ya Mon. Cool.
(They set off with the blessing
from the natural AC.)
How many Rastas are there?
- Twenty families.
- Yes.
- Are you a vegetarian?
Yes, I only eat fish.
- Cool.
- Yes.
So what do you eat?
- I eat all.
- What?
- All.
- What's all?
Beef, pork, chicken...
- Pork is not good.
- Crocodiles.
Piranhas.
- You had that in South America.
- Piranhas.
Crocodile and pork are not good, man.
- Crocodile?
- Crocodile.
- Are crocodiles clean?
- No.
My arm.
(Two drops of his spit)
Did it land on you?
He's warm-hearted.
(He wipes the spit on his pants.)
(Laughing)
- Joseph is a fun guy.
- Like a friend.
(I like Joseph.)
I have a feeling you'll make good friends.
You got a call.
Hello?
How are you, buddy?
Good. We met recently.
Still, I decided to give you a call.
(Laughing)
- Look to the side.
- What?
- Side?
- Maybe he's on the other lane.
He was right next.
What's going on? Oh, he's right there.
Nice to meet you.
It's like a sitcom.
The camera.
Yes.
He's so happy.
His friend's car has no bumper.
His car is destroyed.
(Destroyed)
- That's natural.
- Go.
Is he your friend?
Yes, that's my friend.
We're stopping here.
(They stop for a second at the red light.)
Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- He's Korean.
We're going to Rosman's house.
- We're going to Rosman's house.
- Who's Rosman?
Drive safe.
- I got a new engine.
- What?
Are you testing me?
(Speeding up)
He has nice reactions.
(Screaming)
- No.
- He suddenly sped up.
No.
(Laughing)
Why is he so happy?
You should sing "Like a Friend" together.
What's so funny?
- Your best friend?
- Ya Mon.
(Laughing)
I like the way he laughs.
(Like Toox from Brooklyn)
- He kind of reminds me of Toox.
- Yes.
Yet they're different.
Look to your left.
Way up. That mountain, right there.
You see up there?
- This mountain peak?
- Yes, that's where we're going.
- Road?
- Yes.
- Is there a road?
- The mountain.
- I hope we're not hiking.
(Laughing)
I hope we're not walking.
It's not too hard.
Just probably over 700 steps?
Seven hundred steps?
(Laughing)
No, no.
I don't want to walk for seven hours.
No, not seven hours.
I said 700 steps, not the hour.
No, man. You're crazy!
I thought he said seven hours of walking.
I was surprised to hear that.
I thought he meant seven hours.
It doesn't take long to walk 700 steps.
It's the mountain now.
(They came near the mountain
while talking and laughing.)
There are houses on the mountain.
- See?
- Yes, mountain houses.
- That's where we're going.
- Yes, very beautiful.
There are many houses.
Is this a store? A supermarket?
Yes, everything is there.
Is your house at the mountain peak?
My house is not at the peak.
It's in the Blue Mountain area.
- Is the mountain's name Blue Mountain?
- Yes, Blue Mountain.
Isn't the mountain green and beautiful?
Yes, beautiful.
The scenery is a piece of art.
(The scenery is a piece of art.)
(Blue Mountain)
Blue Mountain boasts dense rain forests.
Thanks to its high altitude
and tropical climate,
Blue Mountain produces coffee renowned as
one of the top three in the world.
Blue Mountain.
It looks like where Taoist hermits live.
This house came down due to a hurricane.
- A hurricane?
- Yes.
Goodness.
When the hurricane came, it came down.
That's significant damage.
(Surprised)
(There are many damaged vehicles.)
A hurricane hit the area
about ten days before I arrived.
- So that's what happened.
- But...
Are the people okay?
- No accident.
- Nobody got hurt.
- No people.
- No one was hurt.
- Not people.
(The car runs fast on a steep road.)
How high are they going?
(Sick)
- I felt sick...
- Goodness.
because the road was so twisty.
(Terrified)
(Holding tight)
The road was so rugged...
enough to be a death road.
It was dangerous.
It's hard to get to a house there.
(Scared)
Very high.
- I see America.
- Ya Mon.
(Welcome to the death road.)
Ya Mon!
(Laughing)
He's happy.
How do you say fire in Korean?
- Fire, in my language?
- Yes.
What kind of fire?
- Fire, like fire.
- Fire.
I see. "Bool."
- Bool!
- I see.
- Bool.
(He likes the pronunciation.)
- You say, bool!
- Bool!
- Bool.
Joseph is very positive.
Joseph laughs a lot.
I wondered,
"How can someone be so excited?"
Yes, I envy that you're happy.
(Laughing)
Fair is fair.
- Fire, bool!
- Yes.
I'll park here.
And we walk up.
This is a parking lot.
(They arrive at a parking lot.)
- Your home?
- Yes.
(Kian84 gets off safely.)
- See? Isn't this place nice?
- Yes.
Is that a mango tree?
Yes, that's another mango tree.
This is what a mango tree looks like.
A mango tree?
Many mangoes.
It fell on the ground. It's rotten.
(A mango fallen on the ground)
There are mangoes on the ground?
- That's good.
- Is this okay?
(Kian84 obtained a mango.)
Yes.
(He eats it without washing it.)
It's good.
- It was good.
- Was it sweet?
- It was sweet.
- It looks good.
It's delicious. It tastes sweet.
It's got a bug.
That one has a worm.
(The mango Joseph was eating.)
It's a worm. It's a medicine
when eaten without being noticed.
"A medicine when eaten
without being noticed."
A worm is a source of protein.
It must be delicious
since a worm ate it too.
(Laughing)
- Do you like it?
- Big nature.
- Yes, man.
- Jungle.
Real nature.
(As they walk along,)
(an unknown world unfolds.)
It seems like they're entering
another world.
It looks like CGI.
There must be a waterfall.
Sound.
- Yes, the water sound.
- You hear the water?
Waterfall.
(Going to Joseph's home
while listening to the water sound.)
It's a jungle.
I'm an hour away from a city,
and it's a jungle.
I was so curious about
what kind of place he was living in.
(Exclaiming)
That's the water.
- Waterfall.
- There's a waterfall?
What kind of waterfall is it?
It must be a big one,
guessing from the sound.
(As they walk along
with the sound of the water,)
What's that?
(a real waterfall appears.)
- Waterfall!
- Yes!
It's big!
It looks like Porfi's backyard.
It looks like the way to his home.
Yes, it looks similar.
(A secret waterfall behind Porfi's home)
It's been a long time.
(Kian84 sees a much bigger waterfall.)
- It was bigger.
- It looks refreshing.
- Is there fish?
- What?
- Fish?
- No.
I'm wet because of my sweat anyway, so...
Do you want to go in there?
- Is it very deep?
- It's about this.
- Here?
- Yes.
Okay. I'm going in.
(He throws his bag down.)
- Together?
- Are you going there?
All right.
It's so hot there, so you need to
go into the water once you see it.
It felt so uncomfortable.
Hopefully, the stones won't fall down
while I'm in the water.
(He's scared,)
(but he strides ahead.)
(Screaming)
Be careful.
(Glancing)
(Joseph gets ready
to go into the waterfall.)
(Falling)
(Waving long hair)
He has such a nice physique.
He has such a nice body
even though he's a vegetarian.
(Unfolding)
(Joseph unfolds his beard,)
(and they enter
the natural shower room together.)
They don't need to build a shower room.
(Screaming)
It feels refreshing.
Here I go!
(Shouting)
The water hit his head.
He's going out of his mind.
I was attacked.
But it feels good.
Do you shampoo here?
He's washing his hair.
He's like Kian84.
(Applying homemade organic shampoo)
Let me use your shampoo too.
- It's made with natural ingredients.
- So you can use it there.
(Sniffing)
It smells good.
(They share shampoo...)
It feels so refreshing!
(They share shampoo and wash themselves.)
(Shouting)
It felt so refreshing. It was nice.
(Washing his hair in one second.)
He's...
He's almost being beaten up by the water.
That's true.
(Screaming)
(He's so happy.)
Good. It's good.
- It's good.
- Ya Mon.
Yes, good.
(He sits down, satisfied.)
He's used to it.
As the water hits me...
(He shampoos his hair...)
(and waits until Kian84 is done.)
(Now it's my turn.)
(Shaking his head)
He looked like an ascetic.
(Charismatic)
(Cleanly washing his hair)
Watching him made me feel refreshed.
You're amazing!
Ya Mon.
(He puts the GoPro in his pocket...)
(and enters the shower room again.)
(After putting his hands together
politely)
(Training in the waterfall)
Is he training?
Is he okay? It looks painful.
It looks really painful.
Goodness.
(Staggering)
(Sweet)
What? My GoPro!
- Is it gone?
- Oh, my.
(He lost his camera!)
Goodness.
My GoPro!
He's in big trouble.
I lost my camera.
It has all his travel records.
That's scary.
It's really a big problem if I lose it.
No, my GoPro!
(When did Kian84 lose his camera?)
(He was taking a shower
with the camera in his pocket.)
(Kian84's camera)
(Save me)
He has to find it.
How can he find it in that place?
(I should help.)
(My Kian84 camera)
(Quickly trying to locate Kian84 camera)
Is it possible to find something
lost in there?
- Did you find it?
- Yes.
I'm fine.
(Okay.)
(He searches again
after talking nonsense.)
His eyes must sting.
(No...)
The water would carry it away
if I didn't find it within three minutes.
(My Kian84 camera...)
(Staggering)
(Give me a minute.
Let me rinse off the shampoo!)
Wash it off first.
(Screaming)
It's a mess.
No.
(No.)
- I had already given up.
- Look at him.
No, you should find the camera.
(No matter how hard he searches,
Kian84 camera is gone.)
(Devastated)
I've had this thing
ever since Adventure by Accident.
Teo and Pani Bottle have left.
The only friend I have left is the camera.
It's my friend.
I talk to it.
(It's my friend. I talk to it.)
(South America, the first destination
of Adventure by Accident)
(The awkward first meeting
with Kian84 camera.)
(The two got closer
as they traveled together.)
(Bonita!)
(Even when he fell down and got back up)
(Even when he was happy and sad)
(In every moment of his lonely trip,)
(Kian84 camera was with him.)
My family. My friend.
It fell into the water and was gone.
And it was a special friend.
I lost my best friend.
Aside from all the footage,
the camera was like Wilson in "Cast Away."
(Like Wilson in "Cast Away")
(Chuck's only friend, Wilson)
(Wilson)
(Like Wilson that fell into the water)
Where are you, Wilson?
(Kian84 camera is long gone.)
Wilson!
They look identical.
(Wilson!)
They look the same.
(Kian84 camera)
Wilson!
Where did you go?
Where did you go, camera?
Return to me, and I'll be good to you.
I'm sorry.
(I'm sorry.)
You should still try to find it.
(Where did you go, Kian84 camera?)
- I hope it got caught by something.
- I feel bad.
(The end of "Spirited Away Kian84 Camera")
- What?
- How can you end it like that?
- I feel terrible for saying this.
- What is it?
But that upset me more than when...
Teo and Pani Bottle left.
Had I known that would happen,
I would've treated it better...
and fully charged it
before sending it away.
(I should've fully charged it.)
But you still found it, right?
- You did, right?
- You'll find out next week.
(Following Rasta Joseph
deep into the mountain)
(A mysterious community
within the Blue Mountains)
(Rasta Camp)
(Do you like rice?)
(I love rice.)
(A feast from nature)
(Ya Mon!)
(Thanks to the energetic people,)
(the day in the camp
is filled with happiness.)
(Is this place paradise?)
(Where did it go?)
(Suddenly,)
(a mystical ancient rhythm
starts playing.)
(With the Rastas' spell,)
(Kian84 falls into a daze?)
("Exhuma" in Jamaica)
(And at the edge of the Caribbean Sea,)
(Music Adventure by Accident's
last story unfolds.)
(It was more than just a trip.)
(It was a journey to pursue his dream.)
(Since we're already born,
do adventurous things as much as we want.)
(And then let's travel again
to the netherworld.)
(A playlist to the pit)
(The last song
encompassing the 11-day journey.)
(Music Adventure by Accident's Last Story)