I will...
I will go back to work now.
I need to familiarize myself with my new job as soon as possible.
Today after work, come home with me,
and we can have dinner together.
I...
need to go home and have dinner with my mom.
Then are you planning
to continue going back and forth like this in the future?
Given my family's situation,
I can't let my mom live alone.
Then how about this?
You can leave for home early today
and have dinner with your mom,
then come to my house
to have some snacks with me.
I should go back to work now.
[Dine with Love]
[Episode 10]
[Soft Bean Curd, Sweet or Salty]
An Jie,
is the Marketing Department looking for a new spokesperson?
Yes. Now that we are preparing to go public
we need a promotional campaign.
They're so mysterious and don't discuss anything with us.
Do they have a problem with us?
Let's go.
Earlier when Director Su entered the office,
she wasn't wearing that outfit, right?
All right. That is fine. No problem.
In addition, when President Yu entered the office
he wasn't wearing those clothes, either.
I...I'm not sure.
Director Wang,
shall we go over the project
with the PR Department?
Instead, why don't you submit an application
requesting a transfer to the PR Department?
The PR Department
is full of Su Kelan's people.
If she finds out about this matter,
our project will be ruined.
Instead, you should contact the other company directly.
- Okay.
- All right.
Why is he so afraid of Director Su finding out about this project?
Everyone knows that President Yu and Director Su are in a relationship.
If you were the boss' girlfriend, would you approve this project?
[Proposal to invite Zhang Bi and Yu Hao to join hands to endorse "What to eat next"]
[Draw Up | Marketing Plan]
Hello?
What do you think? Isn't this pretty?
Didn't you tell me on the phone that you were dying?
That's right.
I am about to die of happiness.
Yuhan told me that
Yu Hao contacted our company to look for a new PR spokesperson for "What To Eat Next."
I want to reignite the fire between us.
Are you crazy?
Listen carefully,
next time, don't call me even if you are really dying.
Don't go.
I put a lot of energy into helping you change your style.
I almost walked my legs off, yet you show me such a rotten attitude
when I need your advice?
How can you be like this? Biting the hand that fed you.
That makeover didn't work at all.
But now, at least...
her mother likes you.
So it is still too early to give up. Fighting!
Come on. Now is the time for you to repay me.
Tell me, how does this look?
Since when did you value my opinions?
- For better or worse, you're still a man.
- What?
If I want to win Yu Hao over, I obviously need to know what guys like.
Help me figure out which dress is better.
You are the spokesperson for the seller,
and your job is to attract more female buyers.
Those dresses will make you look like someone trying to flirt with their husbands.
You'd be lucky if the women don't beat you up.
Yu Hao must've been out of his mind to let you be the spokesperson.
What do you think?
Very professional.
Isn't this pretty, innocent,
and professional?
Why are you leaving again?
What's the matter with you?
Yu Hao and Su Kelan are already together.
That doesn't mean they can't break up.
There is no way Su Kelan and Yu Hao can stay together.
Why not?
I heard that she didn't move into his apartment.
Who is the most important person to Su Kelan?
It is not Yu Hao
but her mother.
She needs to take care of her mother,
so it is impossible for them to live together like regular couples.
And what's the most important thing to Yu Hao?
It is his work, not Su Kelan.
So do you think their relationship can last?
Since Yu Hao loves work so much,
of course, he and I are
a perfect match.
He's a workaholic, and so am I.
I'm also the spokesperson for his company.
As for Su Kelan...
What about Su Kelan?
Of course, she's best suited for you.
She loves cooking, and so do you.
She cares about her mother, and you do, too.
Most importantly,
her mother also likes you.
That's what makes you two a perfect match.
I've got an idea.
Hello? President Zhao.
What will the Marketing Department be doing for the next round of financing?
Will they keep trying to boost sales?
Yes.
They are working on a plan right now.
I will report back to you once it is finalized.
All right.
Okay. See you.
Director Wang, can we talk for a bit when you have some time?
Make sure to check this data carefully.
Don't make any mistakes.
Okay.
And these too. Okay?
Director Wang.
Draw up a plan based on this. Give it to me by tomorrow.
No problem.
Director Wang.
Please include me in the next meeting of the Marketing Department.
Some investors want to know about our plans for promotion.
I'd like to join the meeting so that I can brief them.
Director Su, you don't have to use the investors as a front.
You can just notify me whenever you want to call a meeting.
Director Wang, I didn't mean that.
I will join the meeting as just an attendee.
You are the VP who's in charge of the Marketing Department.
How can you be just an attendee?
Then I will discuss the time with you later.
Have you handled the problems with the contract I mentioned to you?
Are you still working on it?
Get it done as soon as possible.
Especially the sixth article.
We can't let them write it that way.
Otherwise, it'll be too much of a risk for us.
That's right.
Discuss this with the lawyer
and find a middle ground.
Get this done as soon as possible.
We'll review it in the meeting next week.
What's wrong?
You didn't inform Wang Yi that I'm not taking the VP position?
I didn't.
Why not?
With your competence,
you are the perfect fit for the VP position.
Besides, you deserve a better career development path.
This way, we will also have more time to be together. Isn't that nice?
What about my mom then?
If you keep me at work, who will take care of her?
I'm not saying that I'll keep you from taking care of her.
I just think...
Kelan,
your life has been revolving around your mother,
and you didn't care about yourself at all.
Neither did you plan for your future.
I sincerely hope that you'd start thinking more about yourself and pay more attention to your career.
After all,
your mother can't stay by your side forever.
What do you mean my mother can't be with me forever?
I'm going upstairs.
[Su Kelan]
- Thank you, Director Jin.
- Auntie, please don't mention it.
- Please take good care of yourself.
- I will.
Director Jin, what brought you here?
With the right tool,
you can poach anything you want.
Go to Kelan's home?
Wouldn't that be troublesome for her?
She's so busy with work.
If you help take care of her mother and keep her company,
she'd be really grateful to you.
If you think it is too awkward,
I can wait for you downstairs.
I will help you stall her when she comes back.
You can leave as soon as you get my message.
Director Jin noticed last time that I like fish,
so he brought me some.
Thank you.
You are welcome.
Auntie, Kelan, I won't disturb you anymore.
I'm leaving.
Director Jin,
thank you for helping Kelan.
When you are free,
Kelan and I would like to treat you to a meal.
Okay.
Kelan, see him off.
Don't bother.
I can find my way out.
Auntie, see you next time.
Take care.
Why didn't you see him off?
Would you like me to come upstairs?
Don't bother. I'm fine.
Please go home. You don't have to wait for me.
Please don't mind what I said earlier.
I will have dinner with my mom,
and then come over to your apartment.
How to please your mother-in-law?
President Yu, go upstairs.
Go upstairs and make it a competition.
That would be very thrilling.
Why did you come back?
Why didn't you stay longer?
Why didn't you text me that Kelan came back?
I got distracted and didn't see her.
Where's my phone?
Go upstairs to get it back, and you can even stay for dinner.
Don't let my big plan go to waste.
Big plan?
Which big plan?
I'm just trying to help you.
So you didn't tell me Kelan was back on purpose?
I can't believe you...
Su Kelan?
- Kelan.
- Director Jin.
You forgot your phone.
Here.
Thank you.
I should thank you.
I'm sorry that I resigned so suddenly
and caused you trouble.
It is no trouble at all.
How have you been doing?
I'm good. Just a little busy.
What about you?
I've been busy with the program.
Kelan, can you please visit the site to coordinate the shooting next time?
Peng Xiao said he's gotten used to working with you.
Han Meng has come back from her honeymoon.
She's very easy-going.
There shouldn't be a problem working with her.
Then...
Then can you visit the site during the shooting next time?
If Yu Hao makes a scene again, you are the only one who can calm him down.
She can't.
My mom forgot to pick up her medicine at the hospital today.
Director Jin stopped by to bring it to her.
He forgot his phone, so I came down to give it to him.
Got it.
Then I should thank you, Director Jin,
for coming all the way here.
Auntie is the most important person to Kelan,
So, of course, I had to come here.
Unlike you,
I'm not that self-centered.
Director Jin, I appreciate your help today.
My mom and I will treat you to a meal one day.
Then we are leaving.
Let's go.
Sure.
See you, Director Jin.
Come on. Follow them.
Confront him head-on.
It must be very awkward for Yu Hao to have dinner with Mrs. Su.
You'll definitely win this round.
Zhang Bi,
you are being really silly right now.
I'm being silly for the sake of your happiness.
How dare you blame me?
Don't make it sound like you don't want to steal her away from him.
Open the door.
Jin Xuan! Jin Xuan!
You are a jerk!
- Let's eat.
- Let me.
It is okay. I can handle it.
Sit.
Mom, let's eat.
Help yourself.
These are just some home-cooked dishes.
- Here.
- Auntie.
Mom, have some meat.
Mom, have some soup.
The soup
is delicious.
Then have some more.
Mom.
Auntie,
is this tofu?
Yes, it is tofu.
I thought it looked like tofu.
I didn't know you were a conversation killer.
I'm not as good as Jin Xuan in terms of having casual conversations.
When are you going to invite him over for dinner?
- Are you angry?
- No.
- Jealous?
- Not really.
Come on.
I will teach you how to have casual conversations.
What do you want to cook for the next episode?
You can come over. My mom and I can teach you together.
Okay?
I don't want to attend the next episode.
You've been doing very well. Why not?
I don't know what to say.
It is okay.
- I will draft a speech outline for you.
- Please don't.
I don't want to give that Jin Xuan another chance to get close to you.
We are talking about work. Why are you thinking like a lover?
Kelan,
to be honest,
it is not like I don't want to be a part of your life.
I just…
need more time to get used to it.
I can see that.
Don't worry.
In our relationship,
both of us will have to learn to compromise,
until we can find the right rhythm that works for us.
So stop obsessing over who should be
making the compromises, okay?
That doesn't sound right.
What's wrong?
You're the one who got upset first. Remember?
All right, then
whoever gets upset will be punished in the future.
What's the punishment?
The punishment...
will be...
to be kissed by the other.
Have I been punished enough?
Nope.
Divorce?
[Marriage Certificate]
What on earth is going on, sister?
Are you serious?
How come you got divorced right after the honeymoon?
What did you do exactly?
[Car Maintenance]
Hi.
Please help me maintain the car.
Sure. This way, please.
Honey.
We are back home now. Why are you so upset?
You didn't have enough fun?
You forgot to pack lots of stuff
and even got us lost.
Can you be a little more "reliable" than that?
But
if we had not been lost and gotten stuck on the way,
we wouldn't have encountered those herders,
and embarked on a true adventure with them.
Getting the opportunity to live with the locals,
is much more interesting.
They even gave you a hand-made, consecrated bracelet.
Isn't it pretty?
As pretty as you are.
Where's your ring?
Since the beginning, you had your eyes on the bracelet,
and they didn't want to give it to you.
So the night before we came back, I had a drink with them,
and they finally agreed to trade.
Don't get angry.
I was planning on buying a new ring first thing tomorrow morning.
I promise it'll be the same as before.
Meng Meng. Meng Meng.
So that's why you divorced him?
How can you laugh at me?
Can I post a moment?
Are you laughing?
How can you laugh?
Don't you remember how I helped you chase Su Kelan?
Your uncle just got divorced.
How can you laugh?
When she said she wanted a divorce,
you could've said no.
It takes two to make a marriage work.
I have my temper too, okay?
I apologized and begged the whole way,
but she kept on becoming more and more unreasonable.
So I let it be.
Like I really care.
With your personality,
I bet in a few days
you'll be begging her to marry you again.
I bet that you two will get married again in a few days.
- No way!
How could he trade our wedding ring?
Do you think that I really liked that stupid bracelet?
He actually traded our wedding ring for it.
It is just a ring.
I can easily buy another one that looks exactly the same.
Who... Who would've thought she'd divorce me over it?
Do you know what "saying something out of anger" is?
The moment I said divorce,
he actually agreed without hesitation.
How could he trade our wedding ring?
Kelan.
Mom.
How is Meng Meng doing?
She fell asleep.
She didn't tell her parents about the divorce.
I think she still wants to get back together with him.
Oh!
Are you going to Yu Hao's to discuss this with him?
Yes.
Then will you
keep going back and forth like this in the future?
Then are you planning to continue going back and forth like this in the future?
Is he okay
with your current situation?
If he's not okay with it,
I will dump him.
All right.
About the Marketing Department's matter, you can talk to Vice President Su directly.
What are you doing in the office?
Gong Wenxing took over my apartment.
They are angry with each other right now.
Meng Meng didn't tell her parents about the divorce.
Gong Wenxing didn't tell his mother either, right?
No.
Then let's find a time
and have them sit down.
I think they'll forgive each other after they meet and talk it out.
Sure.
Then is there anything else?
If there's nothing else, I will
go home now.
Your mother is unhappy, isn't she?
My mother?
I bet your mom's unhappy.
[How does one get along with the mother-in-law?]
Talk about your slow reaction.
Are you worried about my mom now?
But I really didn't expect that
you would be so bad at having casual conversations.
How do you have casual conversations anyway?
Just talk about day-to-day stuff.
Haven't you ever chatted at home with your—
I'm sorry.
When my mother was still alive,
all she talked about was my father's work.
After my mother passed away,
my grandmother always
thought her death was my father's fault.
Therefore, she wouldn't let him see me.
Ever since then,
I have always lived with Gong Wenxing and my grandmother.
Maybe it was because I was so young at the time,
I didn't dare to say much, since I was afraid I'd say something wrong.
If I said the wrong thing and they got upset, it would have been so awkward.
Maybe that's why,
even now,
I can't really maintain casual conversations.
Then you...
Ever since then, have you never seen your father?
Once, at the beginning of middle school,
he came looking for me
at the school entrance.
It was my birthday that day,
and he brought me a pair of shoes.
But my grandmother threw them away.
Since then,
I haven't seen him.
So your hatred for your father...
is it because of your mother?
I'm not saying I hate him.
Then why didn't you meet him?
If I saw him,
I wouldn't know what to say.
You are not good at holding casual conversations,
and you are afraid of awkwardness.
Yet I still dragged you to have dinner with my mother.
It is okay.
I will learn.
Since you felt so uncomfortable at dinner,
I bet you didn't get enough to eat, right?
Then why don't I cook something good for you?
Here you go.
Thank you.
It is sweet.
Yes.
Why is it sweet?
It is supposed to be sweet.
Have you never had it sweet like this before?
Shouldn't soft bean curd be salty or spicy?
Spicy?
Isn't it normal for people from Chongqing to eat spicy food?
That doesn't mean that everything has to be spicy.
Would you make dark brown sugar sticky rice cake spicy?
That makes sense.
But soft bean curd isn't a dessert.
But people also make sweet soft bean curd.
Wait a minute. How can someone who created a fine food app be so uninformed?
Knowing it and accepting it
are two different issues.
Don't you think that
what we just talked about isn't very enlightening but is still quite interesting.
How is that interesting?
My father used to tell me that
food is the perfect topic to break the ice.
He said that
no matter how different the food is between the north and the south,
when people first greet each other, they all say,
"Have you eaten?"
Food reflects culture, one's character, life experiences, etc.
It is the best way to get to know someone.
If you are curious and truly care then,
having casual conversations isn't actually that hard.
Is the sweet soft bean curd tasty?
I still think it is a little odd.
I'm full.
Let's stay in the office tonight and work.
Don't you think that if someone suddenly came in to do some work—
No one will come.
Even if they do, they won't be able to get in.
I turned off the electronic lock.
Now, let's work.
I don't want to.
Yes, you do.
No.
Yes.
[President Zhao]
Hello? President Zhao.
Yu Hao,
President Zhao said he will come by next week.
Let's work overtime.
My phone is ringing.
[An Jie]
Shouldn't I answer my phone since we're working overtime?
Director Han, are you back from your honeymoon?
Yes.
You've got dark circles under your eyes.
Have you been under that much pressure at work?
Last night, he came back to the company to grab some documents.
Who knows what happened, but he somehow got locked in.
Don't talk about last night anymore.
What happened?
Oh...
Last night,
I was working overtime in the office.
Somehow I got locked in.
It is rare that President Yu doesn't want us to work overtime.
Why are you back in the office?
I still have some unfinished work.
I'm afraid I will get yelled at tomorrow if I don't finish it.
Okay, okay. See you tomorrow.
Okay, good.
I don't know what else to say.
Last night, were you really locked in the office?
Well, did anybody see my goji berries?
President Yu,
Kelan didn't come home last night either.
If I remember right, someone stayed at your house last night.
Yao Qian, please talk to the programming crew about the theme for the next week's episode.
All right, Sister Kelan.
Director Su,
last night I came up with a detailed plan for the commercial shoot.
Would you like to check it?
Director Su, let's check it.
What?
You went to the office,
and he locked the door?
So you two just sat face to face and worked together?
Yes.
Good for you.
As if you were two high school students preparing for the college entrance exams.
You have already worked the whole night. Now stop checking your phone.
I can't believe you wasted such a precious evening.
Or
is the office too small
for you to do stuff?
What are you talking about?
You know the intern with black-rimmed glasses from the IT Department,
don't you?
He also spent the whole night in the office last night.
Will you confess or not?
I've got a witness here.
Can you promise that you two
spent the whole night working
and didn't
do anything else at all? Not even a little bit?
Tell me the truth.
Come on.
[Director Wang]
Director Su, I'm free right now and am available to report the matters regarding the marketing department.
Director Su, are you there?
Director Su?
Give me 10 minutes.
If it is too late, I will find another time.
It is okay.
No problem.
I'm listening.
All right.
Director Su?
Hold on a second, please.
Sure.
You can start now.
If there are any changes,
I will have Yao Qian follow up.
You can also talk to Yao Qian directly.
Okay.
I see.
How many people?
When will the plan be finalized?
All right.
Any more questions?
That's not a problem.
Yes.
That's right.
All right, if you have any other questions, call me any time.
The number on the contract is incorrect. How can they send it over to me like that?
Could you get me a cup of coffee?
Su Kelan, I can't believe you.
You even brought along the toiletry kit, yet you didn't do anything.
Lower your voice.
Gosh.
New message. Hurry.
Try to get off work early today and have dinner with your mom.
Then come over to my apartment after dinner.
Oh wow, "Come over to my apartment."
Reply to him.
Hurry. I want to see it.
Are you going to ask me to be your assistant and make coffee for you again?
Then
are you upset with him?
You were the one who started the meeting.
How can you blame him?
I had the meeting for his sake.
He promoted me as the VP,
and Old Wang is very upset about it.
That's why he called me that late on purpose.
If I hadn't answered, he'd have made things more difficult for me.
Then you may as well ask him to follow your lead as the VP.
I didn't agree to be the VP.
What?
That's what bothers you?
I thought it was for something more important.
Most people can only dream of
being promoted and getting a raise.
You are the only one who's hesitating like this.
Is this your way of showing off?
No.
You already know my family's situation.
He refused to remove me from the position.
If I keep asking, he will get upset again.
I think,
if he really gets upset about this,
then he truly cares about you.
Look,
most men
would prefer their wife to stay-at-home full time.
But he promoted you,
because he hoped to spend more time with you,
and most importantly,
because he trusts you,
and appreciates you.
I know.
- But my mom—
- Kelan.
It may sound a little harsh,
but if you think about it,
for the rest of your life,
who do you think can stay by your side and accompany you
till the end?
Ever since that accident happened to your family,
you've been letting your life,
and relationships revolve around your mother.
You've completely lost yourself.
It is true that Yu Hao
should've discussed it with you first before making the decision.
But if you come to think of it,
this job
is important to you
mostly because of its value and meaning.
Meng Meng,
don't forget that we'll be having dinner together tonight.
Are you still angry with him? How long are you planning on staying at my house?
What?
What are you saying? Am I wasting your time?
Do you think changing the subject will solve the problem?
You are changing the subject as well.
Whatever!
Anyway, I don't want to see him.
There's no way I will talk to him first.
Such sulky thoughts are really unnecessary in a relationship.
- Do you also think it was just me being sulky when I mentioned divorce?
- Yes.
Then let me ask you.
If you were him,
would you trade your wedding ring for something so insignificant?
When he put this ring on my finger,
and laid his eyes on me,
I felt like he entrusted the rest of his life to me.
And when I put that ring on his finger,
to me the ring
was a symbol of my promise,
and loyalty. That I'd be with him
forever and ever.
And yet he, on the other hand,
thoughtlessly traded that ring,
and still doesn't get why I am so upset.
I'm heartbroken
because he misunderstood my sadness to be a willful act.
You didn't come home last night.
So consider this as my room rental.
As your uncle, I hope you can keep up the good work,
and achieve greater glories.
[Special for Men]
Han Meng is downstairs right now. She and Su Kelan go downstairs for coffee every day.
Who said I'm here to see her?
Listen, if you want to apologize to her and butter her up, then please go ahead.
But could you please stop disturbing me at work and staying at my house. Stop taking over my personal space, brother.
Call me "Uncle."
We used to live together, and you never had any problem with that.
So what's the difference now?
Wow.
I know you.
Home can be boring.
It is more exciting...
in the office.
What's the matter with you? Knock it off, will you?
- Don't talk to your uncle like that.
- Give it to me.
No! I won't! Hao Hao, stop it!
No! Don't!
Come on, you need to leave. Go, Just leave,
else I will call security.
Do you think that,
trading the wedding ring
is a terrible thing?
You should ask her. Why are you asking me?
Because you are rational.
There's no rationality when it comes to love.
Besides, if we are being rational here, the wedding ring belonged to both of you.
You shouldn't have made the decision by yourself.
Come home early tonight. I will join you for dinner.
You know what? If you don't leave, Han Meng will be back at work soon.
But I did apologize to her. I said I was sorry, and I begged for her forgiveness.
It was just a ring. Could it be more important than me?
She wanted a divorce over such a trivial matter. Isn't this partly her fault?
So... I'm the unreasonable one,
and you are completely innocent and have been tolerating me all this time.
So now you can't stand me anymore, right?
Meng Meng!
If you don't even care,
why should I still keep it?
- Meng Meng!
- Director Su,
Director Li from China International Capital Corporation will be here soon.
Please enter.
Director Li,
I will confirm with the law firm and the accounting firm as soon as possible,
so that we can avoid the potential compliance risks.
That's very thoughtful of you.
By the way, are you making Zhang Bi your spokesperson for your next marketing campaign?
- Zhang Bi?
- Yes.
Hasn't Old Wang been communicating with Zhang Bi's agency lately?
- Has Zhang Bi's agency confirmed it?
- They have.
- Did they make any—
- Director Wang.
Sorry to interrupt. May I have a word, Director Wang?
There's something I need to confirm with you.
Director Su, if it is about work,
we can talk here.
Are you going to make Zhang Bi our spokesperson?
About that...
Yes, I've communicated with her agency.
Do you have a problem with that?
I don't have a problem with finding a new face,
but Zhang Bi is not the right fit for "What to Eat Next."
Look, I almost forgot.
Kelan,
since you are President Yu's girlfriend, you may be feeling uncomfortable about this.
But if you let your emotions get the best of you at work,
don't you think that'll greatly affect your judgment?
Director Wang,
our potential target customers are female.
Have you thought about Zhang Bi's acceptance rate among female customers?
What if they don't accept her well?
Wouldn't it affect our sales?
I hope you can give up this idea as soon as possible.
For the sake of the interests of our company, I will not approve this proposal.
Has the spokesperson contract reached you?
Leave it for now. Thanks.
I heard Director Wang's proposal was turned down by Su Kelan.
Have you heard that Director Wang wanted to make Zhang Bi our spokesperson?
Really?
That's so interesting. No wonder Kelan went to the Marketing Department just now.
You know what?
Sister Kelan told him right away that she wouldn't approve this proposal.
I didn't expect Sister Kelan to be this tough.
Who could stand that?
If my husband did that to me, I wouldn't stand by either.
If I were her, I'd report it to President Yu directly,
instead of confronting Director Wang myself.
Do you think it is President Yu's idea to let Zhang Bi be the spokesperson?
Hey, what nonsense are you talking about?
Considering our company's interests, Zhang Bi is not the right face for us.
I think Sister Kelan is right.
If she let President Yu solve this problem,
people would think she's not competent enough.
Even if President Yu stepped up and objected to this idea, people would still think Sister Kelan made him do it.
You guys are so ignorant.
Would you like to have lunch with me?
Not today, I'm concerned about Meng Meng.
I will go look for her and keep her company today.
President Yu, Director Su is too busy to reply in time.
It'll affect our working process.
Could you please reply to us directly?
Is Wang Yi giving you a hard time?
President Yu, IT Department is facing some problems.
Do you have time for a meeting?
Sure.
Where are you? Are you okay?
Hello? Yao Qian.
Hello? Sister Kelan, bad news.
Someone leaked the information about Zhang Bi's spokesperson contract.
I told you to leave me alone.
President Yu, which dress do you think is more suitable for the endorsement?
What if he likes both?
[Yuhan]
What? I'm busy. Stop calling me.
Sister, didn't you see the news?
Then forget about it.
Hello? Hello?
I heard Zhang Bi wanted to be the spokesperson for "What to Eat Next."
I don't think she's the right fit.
She's not classy and graceful enough.
Not the right fit indeed.
Yao Qian, I thought the proposal has been rejected. How come the news spread already?
It must be Director Wang who leaked the news.
He wanted to provoke Zhang Bi into pressuring Sister Kelan.
Is he stupid or what?
- Hello? Sister Meng.
- Yes?
- Something bad happened.
Director Wang,
are you sure it is still not the time to have the advertising company change the plan?
Director Su said she wouldn't approve the proposal of having Zhang Bi as our spokesperson.
I asked you guys to leak the news to the media.
Have you done it?
Yes.
If she isn't in agreement,
she can tell that to Zhang Bi herself and shoulder the blame.
Anybody on Su Kelan's side,
[Han Meng]
cannot be good.
Sorry, the subscriber you dialed...
[Han Meng]
Are you out of your mind?
You think the media would take your side and help you pressure Su Kelan by leaking the news?
Check the news. Everybody is saying Zhang Bi is not the right fit.
[Su Kelan]
[Conference Call]
What's the big deal?
It has at least got us more exposure.
I will be in hiding for a while.
And now, Su Kelan will have to approve it.
What's the matter with Wang Yi? Why didn't he join the conference call?
Yao Qian, go to the Marketing Department and find him.
The people in the Marketing Department claim that they are having a meeting with the advertising company.
I've got tons of phone calls from the media, and I didn't answer any.
If I keep ignoring them,
it'll spark controversy, and our company's reputation will be negatively impacted.
Then make a statement and tell people that it was just a rumor.
As for Zhang Bi's agency, let that fool deal with that mess himself.
Director Wang,
please check this message.
you don’t normally deal with the media, so you don't understand the situation.
If we don't deal with this issue and clarify the facts right away,
this problem will escalate.
Our competitors will also take this opportunity to attack us,
and accuse "What to Eat Next" of leaking the news and lacking credibility.
Yao Qian,
if we clarify right now that we didn't invite Zhang Bi to be our spokesperson,
would they find excuses to attack our company?
If we act fast, it'll still be fine.
And after the clarification, they won't have any excuse to cause any more trouble.
But it will definitely hurt Zhang Bi's feelings.
Because many brands will think she's not classy enough.
If we make a statement...
It is totally unnecessary.
What's there to discuss?
They'd only say that it is fake news,
and state that I'm the one
who leaked the news.
These people...
They just can't wait to see me make a fool of myself.
Meng Meng,
please go talk to Director Wang and confirm the commercial plan with him.
Let Zhang Bi star in the commercial.
- You agree?
- What?
No.
Listen,
Yao Qian, please talk to the media,
Zhang Bi's agency and the Marketing Department.
Just say that President Yu and Zhang Bi are good friends and
President Yu wants to invite her to star in one of our commercials,
but somehow, it was misinformed as an endorsement instead.
What? Is there any problem?
No. This way,
the problems of both sides will be solved.
- But...
- Why do we have to clean up Wang Yi's mess?
It is all his fault.
We all work for the same company. No matter whose fault it is,
anything he says would represent our company.
If we made him the scapegoat,
people will think that we manage our people poorly.
Sister Kelan,
shall I call the media right away, or wait until after you have talked to Zhang Bi and President Yu?
Don't wait.
The one who's being criticized must be feeling very bad right now.
And the longer we wait, the less convincing our statement will be.
Do it right now.
All right.
[Zhang Bi]
Yes, Mrs. Han?
I believe that you just pity Zhang Bi because she got badly criticized.
At this point, why do you still care about her?
Is it appropriate for us,
to put her in the middle of our internal conflicts?
Then you'll just watch them shoot a commercial together?
Aren't you worried?
Mrs. Han,
if he's the type of man who makes me worry all the time,
I'd rather dump him.
If he doesn't make you feel worried at all,
either he is a really good person, or you are simply too broad-minded.
If you believe he's a good person,
then would he think that you are too broad-minded?
Let say
that he thinks you are too broad-minded,
then would you still think that he is a good person?
Is this a tongue twister?
It is too complicated. I don't get it.
You are just playing dumb.
Since you are such an expert, how are you doing yourself?
I... I'm fine.
Where are you?
Send me your location. I will come over.
Director Jin, sorry to bother you.
I hope you can do me a favor.
In the commercial, make Zhang Bi's role that of a friend of President Yu.
Do not include any sign of romance.
Otherwise, it'll cause another scandal.
If it happens again,
we won't clean their mess anymore.
[Fan Wenxing]
Sorry, the subscriber you have dialed can not be reached.
Please try again later.
Can't you stop bothering me?
Why are you calling me right now?
To laugh at me?
No.
I also think it is a good idea.
Let's do it. Goodbye.
I will be with Meng Meng tonight.
Okay.
♫  Who's hiding in a corner of their memories, talking to themselves?  ♫
♫  In the void of the night, no one answers.  ♫
♫  The moment the wind blows, it awakens me from my fatigue  ♫
♫  Looking at the city lights, I feel the contrast with reality  ♫
♫  But I still have to go down this road  ♫
♫  Upon taking a step further, will my dream develop into something more? ♫
♫  In this world full of fireworks, I see unexpected changes  ♫
♫  I feel reluctant to be swept away by the scenery  ♫
♫  How many more journeys will I undergo before I'm left astounded and speechless?  ♫
♫  Experiencing all the heartache  ♫
♫  As far as the eyes can see, sometimes it feels like I'm stranded  ♫
♫  When I see my future self,  ♫
♫  only then can I understand why I'm moving forward  ♫
♫  I will still be as stubborn as I've always been  ♫
♫  The uncertain suspense of this world  ♫
♫  Who has never cried their eyes out before?  ♫
♫  Self-reflection will diminish what may come tomorrow  ♫
♫  Let's reconcile with yesterday  ♫
♫  When the raindrops will sigh and cover the glimmer of the starry sky ♫
♫  I will look forward to the sunny days coming soon after  ♫
♫  Let's stop and look up to see if we're still moving forward together  ♫
♫  Is our pace the same as before?  ♫