♪I left a unique secret code♪
♪To play hide and seek with you♪
♪Found by you, fell into your arms♪
♪Your smile lights up my whole world♪
♪I left a unique secret code♪
♪Waiting for you to feel my heartbeat♪
♪Sweet games, cozy tones♪
♪My world is truly wonderful with you♪
=The Princess's New Clothes=
=Episode 21=
Bai Yu.
Bai Yu!
Lu Qi!
Call the ambulance!
Bai Yu!
Where am I?
Thank goodness.
You're alive.
You're not dead.
I'm alive.
Your Highness.
I knew you would be safe and sound,
blessed by the heavens.
Your back...
Where's the wound on your back?
What are you talking about,
Your Highness?
I don't understand.
Where am I?
Your Highness,
we're in Shishang Town,
three hundred li away
from the capital of Northern Liang.
Northern Liang?
Shishang Town?
That means
we had a time travel
and returned together.
A time travel?
What does that mean?
It has been a full seven days
since you fell into a coma
due to poisoning.
All the physicians told me
there was no hope for you.
But I had faith that you would wake up.
I…
I was unconscious for seven days?
So everything was all a dream?
Were you raised by your grandmother?
How did you know, Your Highness?
But
she passed away three years ago.
Your…
Your Highness…
What's this?
The…
The jade pendant
you gave me.
I'm asking you
why you kept it all this time.
Your Highness,
I…
I am aware of my lowly status.
I am unworthy of you.
But I swear I will love you
for a lifetime.
Only one lifetime?
I want you
in your next life,
and the one after that.
You'll always be mine.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Mengli,
whether those experiences
were real
or just dreams,
they no longer matter.
What matters is
you're still here.
(Shishang Village)
This is more convenient.
We won't get separated.
Your Highness is right.
Where would you like to go today,
Your Highness?
I intend
to do an inspection of the town.
I want to open a clothing store
and design clothes
for the people of Northern Liang.
You want to be a tailor?
How did Your Highness
become interested in tailoring?
What?
Do you have something against me
being a tailor?
No, no.
You can do whatever you want,
as long as it makes you happy.
That's more like it.
In fact, being a tailor…
In fact, being a tailor
isn't any easier than being a princess.
As for the details,
I'll tell you at a later time.
Where's Lu Qi?
Did he go the wrong way?
Let's go back and find him.
All right.
Sir,
please buy me.
I don't eat a lot, and I work hard.
I can do lots of things.
I can even make clothes.
You won't regret it if you buy me.
Please, sir.
I didn't say I wouldn't buy you.
Niu Qiang?
(Five years later,)
(the Emperor of Northern Liang
fell ill.)
(With the support of Duke Ying,
the Empress reigned the court.)
(And Long Mengli's
Dreamfinder Clothing Store)
(opens its 100th branch,)
(becoming a renowned premier tailor.)
♪How will you think of me then?♪
♪Strolling the streets,
listening to our songs♪
♪After feeling the tender sunset♪
♪Who will you be with at this moment?♪
♪After turning away, no one looked back♪
♪If we ever meet again♪
♪Will we still understand each other
like we used to?♪
♪Unfortunately, I'm not opinionated♪
♪I'll only wait for you to come my way♪
♪If we can't meet again♪
♪Let time put everything on hold♪
♪Flipping through those photos♪
♪And the seasons that have gone away♪
♪If we ever meet again♪
♪Will we still understand each other
like we used to?♪
♪Unfortunately, I'm not opinionated♪
♪I'll only wait for you to come my way♪
♪If we can't meet again♪
♪Let time put everything on hold♪
♪Flipping through those photos♪
♪And the seasons that have gone away♪
♪Looking back to those memories♪
♪Yet, we didn't get to say goodbye♪