♫ I just came from the forest not yet awake looking like a ginseng fairy ♫
♫ I’m full of skills, I broke into the Martial Arts World alone ♫
♫ I believe in destiny, looked everywhere but nobody specified what it is ♫
♫ Once again, I have hope and expectation of love yet who is my destiny is unknown ♫
♫ See, turns out that destiny has always been waiting for me ♫
♫ I believe that love really exists ♫
♫ Take a look at me, I’m open and candid, careful, and never doubting love ♫
Although I fan the flames and cause trouble everywhere, I came to the world just to ask about the whereabouts of love
♫ How do I find the ripple effect of my destiny? ♫
♫ What are the consciences of the proud me? ♫
♫ Why bother worrying too much? ♫
♫ I just know that wherever I go, you will be there with me ♫
[Wu Lin Heroes]
[Episode 2]
How long more do we have to walk?
Since we have nothing else to do, tell me more about the world.
I can tell you, but call me Young Master.
Keep your distance from me as well.
Young Master, please enlighten me.
The reigning martial artist right now is Lord Lin of Flowing Water Manor.
He dotes on his only daughter, Lin Xiaoxiao.
However, this man often goes into reclusion and doesn't care much about worldly affairs.
So, a number of sects in the martial arts world are restless.
Doesn't that mean trouble is brewing again?
Aren't you fond of having chaos unfold because of you?
I'm not like that. Those are just stories.
I think growing old with a nice partner is nice.
Growing old together?
Why?
Don't you ever feel lonely journeying in the martial arts world?
Geniuses are fated to be lonely.
I can't be free of this destiny.
I hate being lonely, and I want a companion.
I won't feel so lonely if I have a lit lamp waiting for me at home.
Well, what kind of person must they be?
Let's go. We're almost there.
- Trinkets!
- Fresh dumplings!
Young lassy, have a look at these trinkets!
We're finally here. It's really bustling.
Candied hawthorns!
Come over here.
Wait here for me. Don't move an inch.
Have a look.
Put this on.
- Are you being nice to me?
- You're overthinking.
I just think it's sunny.
The sun doesn't bother me. Why are you giving this to me?
I'm using your head as a rack.
It's so it's always within reach. Displeased?
If so, then don't enter the city.
- Move it.
- Hold on! I'm glad to do so!
- Where are you headed?
- We're visiting relatives.
- What's your name?
- Lin Qingqing.
- Are you two traveling together?
- Yes.
Young Master, what are they holding?
A travel pass. It's necessary to enter the city.
Are you lacking one? Without it, you can't enter the city.
I... clearly have one.
Stick close.
Take a look!
What's inside?
Just some grains.
Who told you I didn't have one?
Travel passes.
Are you traveling together?
Wang Tieshuan of Wang Village?
Remove your headwear.
Why is a pretty lady like you named Wang Tieshuan?
(Tieshuan means iron bolt)
I like this name. Got a problem with it?
Fine, get moving.
Inform the imperial guard immediately.
That young lady who just entered seems to have a bounty on her head.
Hurry up.
With your current condition, you can only eat plain noodles.
Madam, your dishes are ready.
Thanks.
Can't I have a bite?
No.
- A sip of the soup should be fine, right?
- No.
You can't finish so much. Why can't you share some with me?
My good looks are enough to satisfy your hunger.
You're already privileged to be in my presence for so long.
He's absolutely right!
Even I want to have a second glance.
And you are...
I'm Chu Yao, Young Master Bai's good friend.
I really want to be good friends with Young Master Bai.
It's rare for Young Master Bai to have a traveling companion. What is your name?
Wang Tieshuan.
An excellent name.
Since you're in Bailu City, I have to be a good host.
The chef at my manor whips up wonderful dishes.
Would you like to try them?
Of course!
Young Master Bai, come to my manor.
Preparations have been made in accordance with your preferences.
You saved my life when you were here last time.
I owe my life to your miraculous hands.
It's rare for you to leave the mountains and visit Bailu City.
We have to drink until we're drunk to celebrate our reunion.
Let's dismiss everyone first, so our reunion won't be disrupted.
Men!
What's going on?
- Hurry up and leave.
- Get moving.
Move it!
You haven't paid yet!
Don't worry, I'll pay for everyone.
Young Master Chu, since you're so generous, how about you pay for my meal as well?
I only ate a few bowls of noodles.
I won't interrupt your reunion.
Pay for you own meal if you want to leave.
I'll sit around for a little longer.
What's this?
A greeting gift for you.
If you can convince Young Master Bai to reside in my manor, I'll be deeply grateful.
Are you bought over with so little silver?
Don't you feel insulted?
If this is an insult, I don't mind suffering a few more.
Truth be told, Young Master Chu is such an enthusiastic host.
You should reciprocate the kindness of others.
Don't be so stubborn with your rejections.
You're right.
I can't be rude.
With tea in lieu of wine, I thank you.
Wine is fine, and so is tea.
If you're truly willing to come over, I'll be over the moon.
Chu Yao's place is a decent place for her to recuperate.
This is ginseng orange peel tea.
Excellent tea.
Forget it.
I'll drink my soup.
The sun is setting.
How about you follow me back to my manor first?
Fragrant herbal baths have been prepared there.
Y-Your face...
Young Master!
It's so itchy!
- Young Master.
- Stop.
- Don't hurt them!
- Are you all right?
Stand back.
Stand back!
Yes.
Young Master.
Are you all right?
- It's so itchy.
- You're the culprit, aren't you?
Do you have to be so brutal?
What do you know?
A rich family's son like him needs regular detoxifying.
Otherwise, he'll lose his life easily from dispersion-thirst.
This medicinal tea is my gift to him.
Young Master Bai is right. He's always right.
Fine, he's happy to suffer at your hand anyway.
I won't intervene.
Are you really going to leave?
Don't you want to know about your past?
One shouldn't linger on the past.
You sure are worry-free.
I'm sure you aren't fretting about threats in your future either.
I didn't drink your tea.
But you've eaten the noodles I ordered.
- You...
- Don't worry.
He's just joking with you.
I took a glance outside.
The sun has set, but it's still warm.
When you leave, I'll hold up an umbrella for you to avoid a heat stroke.
You're truly a fascinating lady.
No wonder Young Master Bai favors you.
I'm just adaptable.
Well said.
Life doesn't always go one's way.
For example, I have no wish to visit Young Master Chu's manor.
However, I have to.
Take our belongings along.
Young Master.
Wait. Don't mind me. Hurry and go take care of Young Master Bai.
I only know that his story is quite popular.
- Everyone knows it in Bailu City.
- Wait, what are you doing here?
Aren't you serving Young Master Bai in the Moon Viewing Tower?
Young Master Bai said he didn't need our help.
He prefers to be quiet and alone.
MIss, you can go wherever you want.
We're rushing to listen to the storyteller.
What's the story?
The story is about the top demoness in the martial arts world, and her men.
Hurry and go, or we'll miss it.
Miss, take it easy. We'll get going.
Take care, Miss.
- Quite a lot of customers here.
- Sirs, you're here. Come inside, please.
Didn't I tell you?
- This way, please.
- It's really popular.
Sirs, just let me know what you need.
All right. You can go.
Sure.
- Bring a pot of premium tea.
- Sure!
- Aren't the seats good today?
- They are good. We're facing the center.
Sorry to make you wait a while.
The wind blows, the war drums beat, the mountains and rivers vibrate.
The general is born brave, like the offspring of the Qilin from heaven,
and the enemies are like ants in a hole, how can they escape?
- Good!
The story we're talking about today is called,
Demon Spirit in the martial arts world.
This... Everyone, please excuse me.
My tongue got twisted.
It's called, Demoness in the martial arts world.
Demoness?
I am speaking of the most notorious demoness in the martial arts world, Ye Xi.
- Ye Xi?
- Relying on her superb martial arts skills,
this demoness stole many ancient martial arts books from numerous sects and groups.
She also stole their secret treasures.
Later, she went to Shuzhong and seduced without success the Young Lord Tang Yang of the Tang Sect.
Her love turned to hatred, so she killed his fiancee's entire family.
- Killed the entire family?
- So abominable and detestable!
This demoness even wanted to destroy the most powerful hidden weapon in the martial arts world,
Storm Pear Flower Needle!
Young Lord Tang Yang swore to avenge his fiancee.
The demoness Ye Xi deserved to be punished.
In the end, she was killed by the Storm Pear Flower Needle.
Her corpse was left unburied in the Jade Bamboo Forest.
Well said, she got what she deserved!
This demoness indeed deserved to die.
You're right!
Well said! She deserved to be killed.
- Well said!
- She can't be forgiven.
That's right. She can't be kept alive.
Justice is clear under Heaven!
Demoness Ye Xi, you can't escape!
Demoness?
S-She is the demoness?
That can't be.
Isn't that Miss Wang?
Miss Wang is the Demoness Ye Xi?
But isn't Ye Xi already dead? What's going on?
We're on duty for the Prince's Manor. Unrelated people should move aside!
Hurry, move aside!
Get out! Get out!
Officers!
- Officers!
- Hurry and tell Young Master Bai. Go! Go, go, go.
Customers, don't leave.
Official, what's going on?
Heroes and officials.
Please be kind. Don't get into a fight here.
If you fight, go outside to fight.
- This is a small eatery.
- We're on official duty.
Anyone who isn't involved, move aside to avoid getting hurt by mistake.
We're upholding justice for Heaven. If there is any loss, go ask Heaven for help.
Young miss, you must be Ye Xi.
By the order of Prince Regent's bounty award, we are capturing a woman named Ye Xi.
Behave and come with us, Miss Ye.
Are you talking to me?
Demoness! Quit pretending!
Everyone in the martial arts world said you stole ancient books from various sects and groups.
When I heard you were killed, I regretted that I didn't kill you myself.
I'm going to kill you right here today!
Aren't you mistaken? My name is Wang Tieshuan.
It's impossible that I'm that demoness you're talking about.
You are named Wang Tieshuan? Why aren't you named Wang Tiedan?
Demoness, you are clearly insulting our intelligence.
- Exactly!
Aren't you admitting who you are yet?
The Flying Frost Swordplay that you just used is that demoness Ye Xi's swordplay.
If there is any similarity, it's purely by coincidence.
There are many similar moves among the martial arts of many sects.
Based on that one move, how can you reach this conclusion?
Demoness, look closely here.
Stop your trickery! You are the one on this drawing, aren't you?
Announcing to all people, an award is offered to capture the woman in the drawing.
This beautiful woman is named Ye Xi.
If there are any clues of Ye Xi's whereabouts...
What else do you have to say?
I...
Maybe... she and I happen to look alike?
No more desperate attempts before you perish! You should obediently surrender!
Wait, everyone.
I have proof.
Miracle Physician, Young Master Bai, you are also here.
Young Master Bai came at just the right time. He can prove that I'm not Ye Xi.
She is
Wang Tieshuan.
Brothers, they are together! All of us, charge!
Go.
Quick, go after them!
After them!
Hurry up!
Hurry.
Shoot the arrows!
Luckily the arrows can't get to this place for now.
Is this good enough?
Over there! Capture them! Chase!
Don't Run! Stop right there!
It's useless to hide. We should rush out together.
Stop right there!
- Charge!
Go.
Young Master Chu? Why are you here so late at night?
Eldest brother, what is the official duty that you're on?
I happened to be strolling around.
Now that I've run into you, maybe I can offer some help?
By the order of Prince Regent's bounty award, we're capturing Ye Xi.
Did you release the smoke just now? Did you do it?
- This...
- You dared to ambush us.
You are opposing us.
I wouldn't dare to.
Eldest brother, she's already run away, so she's probably far away.
The bounty award that you're missing, I'll pay for it.
You work hard for your job.
On behalf of the people in the city, I'll definitely treat you well.
You aren't sleeping at home this late at night, but are gang-fighting on the streets.
So noisy!
She must be Lin Xiaoxiao, daughter of Alliance Lord Lin.
- Why is she here?
- I wonder, too.
On behalf of my fellow brothers, I thank Young Master Chu.
- Farewell.
- Take care.
Let's leave.
We don't care if the government will capture them.
We are here to uphold justice in the martial arts world.
We must kill the demoness Ye Xi and her partner,
Bai Yue. Isn't that right?
Yes, kill the demoness!
All the heroes here, please listen to me.
I am the most wealthy man in Bailu City.
I am also among the top ones in the whole world.
To eliminate evil from the martial arts world, you almost dismantled that teahouse.
I'm really impressed.
Therefore, I'll shoulder the cost of all the losses.
As for that demoness' partner, I'm looking for him as well.
To tell you the truth, my face was ruined by him.
But there is no rush, you must be tired after such much fighting today.
The injured brothers also need to be treated.
Why don't you all go to my manor to recuperate.
I'll dispatch men tomorrow to search for their tracks.
As soon as I get any news, I'll send a messenger to notify you.
At that time, you can make your moves together.
Wouldn't that be successful with half the effort?
- That's right.
He makes sense.
- Thank you, Young Master Chu.
Men! Take all these heroes to my manor.
Take good care of them.
- Yes.
- Please.
Thanks.
- Go.
- Let's go.
Go.
Isn't the demoness Ye Xi already dead?
How did Bai Yue become the demon woman's partner?
I don't care.
Whoever dares to harm him will be my enemy.
You are my friend, then.
Don't smile.
When your face smiles, it's even more scary. Did Bai Yue do this?
How did you offend him?
He was helping me to detoxify.
It looks scary, but it's really effective.
As to his current situation, I can't tell you much, either.
If you can't tell much, don't talk anymore.
I only want to know, is Bai Yue all right? Where is he?
With me around, they'll be fine.
As to where they went,
I don't know, either.
Eldest Miss, let's hurry and go back to the manor.
It's useless for you to chase after Young Master Bai. If you catch up to him, he'd still ignore you.
If you don't get back soon, Master will get angry.
Where do you live, Miss?
If I get any news, I can send a message to you.
Flowing Water Manor.
- Flowing Water Manor?
- Forget it.
I've been away for many days.
Exposed to the storm and the sun, I should just go home.
Whenever you get news, hurry and tell me promptly.
Sure.
So she is Eldest Miss Lin from the Flowing Water Manor.
This young lady that Bai Yue provoked isn't easy to deal with.
[Wisdom in Buddhism]
I already said there's no herbal medicine here, but you wouldn't believe me.
What if there is some? I had to search.
Didn't you see that I'm changing clothes? Stay right there.
Isn't that my hairpin?
Why did you take my hairpin? Put on your clothes first.
This hairpin is expensive.
I didn't know you have something like this.
Young Master Chu gave it to me.
I still need to exchange it for money. Where else can I get money for travel?
Don't move.
What are you doing?
How long will you keep touching?
Sorry, I didn't do it on purpose.
It's just that I saw on your back...
Let's go.
Fine, I won't touch you. So petty.
I won't hold a grudge since you saved me.
But those marks on his back...
This is strange.
Why do they look familiar?
Also, the storyteller in the restaurant said...
That demoness Ye Xi deserved her punishment.
In the end, she was killed by Tang Yang's Storm Pear Flower Needle.
Her corpse was left unburied in the Jade Bamboo Forest.
That means I'm really named Ye Xi.
But they kept calling me a demoness.
I'm Little Ginseng Fairy. A fairy, not a demoness.
Who is Tang Yang?
Although I've lost my memory, but I know a person should strive to be kind.
He wanted to kill me over this needle.
Then he... must not be a good person.
What's wrong? Are you poisoned?
And that thing on your back...
Nonsense. So far, I'm the one who poisons people.
No one can poison me.
Such a big boast.
Then, what's the matter with you now?
Are you betwitched?
Stop talking.
Stay away from me.
With the way you look, we should return to Bailu City to find Young Master Chu.
How do we go?
Didn't you see it's a thunderstorm out there?
Let's make do here for the night.
You can see your Young Master Chu tomorrow.
[Maitreya Hall]
[Wisdom in Buddhism]
Need some help?
[Guiyuan Temple]
- Who were you calling?
- You, of course.
My name is Ye Xi, not "Hey."
Come here.
Young Master Bai, what's the matter?
- Scratch here for me.
- You have hands and feet. Why can't you scratch yourself?
I know you definitely won't do a good job, but I'm still giving you a chance.
It's at least worth my effort to bring you into Bailu City, detoxify you, and help you out of trouble.
Why can't you scratch me a little? Hurry up.
You talk too much.
If you want help, then talk nice.
If you don't know how to use your mouth well, give it to someone in need.
Lucky for you that I'm generous and won't hold a grudge against you.
I'm not itchy anymore.
You can stop now.
You can stop. Go rest over there.
Where are you throwing that?
You recovered from your injuries too quickly.
You're so energetic after just one day.
That's because my internal energy is strong.
Haven't you heard about healing with internal energy?
That's probably a lie.
You should be the one telling me the truth.
You promise to tell me about my past as long as I entered the city with you.
I did say that, but are you sure you want to find out?
Why wouldn't I? Tell me everything right away.
Fine, I'll tell you.
Five years ago, Tang Yang deceived you.
You became a demoness hunted down by the martial arts world.
Tang Yang made you the scapegoat for all those evil deeds they spoke about.
In the end, you were killed
by the Storm Pear Flower Needle in Jade Bamboo Forest.
Are you saying that I died five years ago?
You reappeared three years ago.
The crown prince even ushered you into the palace.
He even dismissed all his concubines for you.
Not long after, the crown prince announced your ten sins to the world.
Ultimately, you were killed and hurled into the unmarked burial mounds.
I visited the unmarked burial mounds out of curiosity to check whether you truly died.
Could you really have nine lives?
Does that mean I have two enemies?
Tang Yang and the crown prince.
It's fine, I'll butcher them once I uncover the truth.
The crown prince is already dead.
Well, I'll look for Tang Yang.
Are you sure Young Master Chu will come here?
[Liubai Pavilion]
[written by Chu Yao]
If you don't need those eyes, donate them to those in need.
You...
Young Master, if Young Master Bai finds out that you stole his wine, he'll be furious.
I bet Young Master Bai has a drug to make someone mute.
By the way, that strange illness of yours...
Don't worry. I won't tell anyone.
I just want to find out more.
I'm curious, too.
How about I touch you again? Perhaps—
You can't.
So be it.
Seems like I had no reason to fret. You guys are fine.
You're even so spirited.
Why are you blushing?
He's shy.
The ginseng in your ginseng wolfberry tonic isn't top-grade ginseng, right?
Moreover, the taste of ginseng in yesterday's tea was odd.
I can buy the best ginseng available for you.
Why the heck do you have to brew ginseng?
I used a medicinal herb similar to ginseng to produce some health tonics.
Good ginseng is hard to acquire.
Even if I found them, they should be used to save lives.
The duty of a physician never leaves your mind.
You have bidding farewells at this pavilion.
Please enjoy your drinks.
I need to head to Shu's Tang Sect to interrogate Tang Yang.
I'll get going. See you.
Are you letting her leave?
Well...
P-Please don't be angry. You'll damage your health.
You sent a messenger to inform me of your arrival in the city, didn't you?
You drugged me and ruined my appearance in public because you didn't want to implicate me. I understand.
You're doing all these for her, right?
However, her journey will be treacherous.
Aren't you worried if she's all alone?
Stop blabbering nonsense.
Do you really want to be disfigured?
Calm down.
Someone like me may look unreliable, but I know where to draw the line.
I know what shouldn't be said before her.
You're a great man, but you refuse to be honest about your feelings.
You really need to
improve on this.
These are to be consumed. They're for your face.
Thank you.
You...
You've never thanked me before.
- Stop!
- Stay right there!
Stop!
Run, they're catching up!
- Stop right there!
- Don't move!
- Stop!
- My chicken...
Hey, my chicken!
Quick!
Atrocious!
Hurry up!
Stop!
Tang Huan, how dare you betray Tang Sect and defy your elders!
I didn't!
We're under the young lord's orders to kill you on sight.
Young Master, leave them to me.
Find a chance to escape.
I won't.
I won't ditch you and escape alone.
Young Master!
My puny life isn't worth much.
You're meant for grander horizons.
Be resolute.
As long as you're alive, there will always be another chance to retaliate.
Tang Yang corrupted Tang Sect and committed heinous crimes!
Even if I lose my life, I will fight to the bitter end!
Young Master!
They, too, bear grudges against Tang Yang.
You've run out of secret weapons. Stop this vain struggle.
Fine, let's see who shall be the last man standing.
Young Master, flee!
Stop!
Seventh Uncle!
Young Master.
Run.
Leave.
Seventh Uncle.
Seventh Uncle!
Stop!
”Waiting” - Li Hongyi
♫ How many stories have you heard of the Mortal World? ♫
♫ Dressing in light clothes, I've become forgotten in the horizon ♫
♫ I can’t bear to go home again ♫
♫ And I can’t seem to find your voice to accompany me ♫
♫ The sound of the melodious song leisurely stirs up the past ♫
♫ My long-cherished wish has not been fulfilled, how can I leave you? ♫
♫ How could destiny take me back to that city? ♫
♫ To find the warmth you left behind ♫
♫ A gentle dream becomes reality magnifying the roads I’ve taken ♫
♫ Laughing and sighing in this life, why bother asking if I’d be interested in it again? ♫
♫ Why is there someone willing to wait without knowing the pain and resentment? ♫
♫ It’s hard to tell stories of the past ♫
♫ Unintentionally, like the trees and grass, I’m foolishly hoping for true love ♫
♫ I will wait for you for the rest of my life ♫