What are you doing?
Isn’t the weather nice?
Stayed outside for a while longer
I just happened to buy you a cup of coffee
Put it here
What else is in the bag
In the bag
I went shopping secretly for a while
Okay Right
I am also half a boss after all
I have to explain everything to you
I bought it in the store
It’s so expensive You don’t need the coffee machine
You go out to buy coffee every day
I just like spending money randomly
Can you take care of it?
To be honest
I have been with her for so many years
There are many girls chasing me
But I rejected them all
Because I love her
Fascinating confidence
Since you can go to anyone
Why are you still pestering her
To save face
What did you give me for Valentine's Day
Valentine's Day
We don't seem to be together
Then after we got together
What did you give me
I gave you cat food
And socks
Warm baby
I want to give you a punch now
Send it away directly to you
Just look at my bag
Just My bag
I have been using it for four or five years
It’s already
scratched out
You can I never thought about it
Want to buy me a new bag
It’s not your bag
It’s not expensive either
But it’s a classic style Ah
Classic styles will also become outdated
Okay
Besides, you have several bags
Are you still buying them
How can I have so many bags?
Don’t you
You don’t know that women
are always short of a bag
forever Don’t you have anything to wear?
If you don’t give me a gift
I will make you feel the pain
I will let you
see it. To my sincerity
Then I will give it to you
Then what bag do you want
Can I give it to you
Then I I've found it
Zhao Jin is here
Where's Xu Nuo
Xu Nuo has something to do and he just can't come
What's going on
I don’t know, I didn’t tell me clearly
You eat first
I want to eat an avocado
Avocado
Niu Guoguo
Come
I like eating Niu Guoguo
It’s so boring
you Do you know what this is called?
Spreading dog food
This is called tit for tat
Let’s stop making trouble and let’s get down to business
Let’s talk b>
Peng Yuan’s side
has already started taking action
Are you ready?
That’s it
No Brother
You have no sense of crisis at all
Do you think you have won now
Really
Your girlfriend b>
Are you worried about me
Are you worried about him
Why am I worried about him?
I have nothing to worry about
Our Xu Yang
I am worried about Xu Yang, okay?
You think about it yourself
Peng Yuan over there
has already Start taking action
Issuing a challenge
In addition to Ms. Yitian, you
also have children's problems
You have a big problem Okay
Okay
Don’t make people so nervous
Let’s have a drink
It’s not about being nervous or not
I'm worried for him
This emperor is not in a hurry to kill the baby
Relax, relax
Eat another Niuguoguo
Hello
Where are you
Why are you asking?
Are you checking the post?
I’m afraid you’ll get into trouble alone
Do you want to get into trouble with me?
Be with you
I am willing to do anything
Zhao Jin
As long as I make up my mind
I will do well
Don't worry
Where are you
I'll find you
No need
Just wait for me where you are
I will come to you
Then I will do nothing
As long as you don't fall in love with other people
That's all right
You can fall in love
But I will separate you
Promise
You have to promise me
Whenever you need me
You will call me
Don’t worry b>
I will trouble you at any time
Don’t just talk
I am telling you this
just to tell you
How much I believe in you
Do you know
Okay
Waiting for your call
Then I will hang up first
So beautiful
This is the magic moment
What is it
Between day and night
It is the most beautiful part of the day Moment
This is the Magic Moment
Didn’t you show me a
Magic Moment movie
Do you still remember
That was a happy movie
Now is the magic moment
Hello madam
Hello
V2
Please come in here
Come in
Uncle and aunt are here
Both of you, please
come in Please take a seat
Okay
You're already here
You're welcome
Come on, come on, give it to me
I'm sorry
That
My father is temporarily busy
Can't come
Let me follow you
Say sorry
Wait until he is alone again some other time
Make an appointment with your two elders
It’s okay
I thought your mother was coming What
What is your mother doing recently
How is she?
Pretty good
She is busy with her business
Uncle
You're here
Sorry, sorry
The road is a little jammed
It's okay
I just arrived not long ago
I’ve been waiting for a long time
Why don’t you have something to eat first
I can do it, uncle, you can decide
Okay
Sit down
Waiter
Pour us two cups of tea
Today you asked me to meet alone
It must be something
It’s something particularly important
I want to talk to you
My personal thoughts
So I just
came here alone
How long have you been with Yuan
Ten years
I know
You have never recognized me
To be honest
I still feel quite hurt about my self-esteem
I didn’t expect that
You still speak upright
If there is anything
that offends you
I would like to You apologize
No problem, no problem
Young people
What do you want to say
Be able to clarify your thoughts
That's a good thing
Look at you two being together
It's been so many years
It's inevitable that there will be something wrong
Small oversights, small problems, etc.
As long as you two work together
These are not problems, right?
Auntie is right
As long as you two work together  With your support
I think any problem
can be solved
I listen to Yu An
He is I want to marry you
in order to get married
Have you discussed this matter?
Have discussed it
It seems so It’s not settled yet
You two are just short of getting a certificate
You have been together for such a long time
In fact, it has nothing to do with marriage
What's the difference
You still have to ask about this matter
What do you think of Xu Nuo
I
don't want to get married
You mean
you don’t want to marry Yu An
This is also
the reason why I came to see you alone today
If Yu An were here
he would definitely say it was his problem
But in fact it has nothing to do with him
We
We just lost to time
Marriage will happen sooner or later
But before that
I want to
help you two first
Get the new store open
I heard from Yu An
He wants to invest in your mother's
laundry
You should know about this
I don't know
But I know in my heart
My parents' side
I can't let go of Yu An
As a child
I should Respect their wishes
But
Marriage is a major event in life after all
I still want to
think more about myself
That’s why
I ran over to see you
regardless of the shame
There is nothing shameful about it
People are inherently selfish.
I am no exception
From this point of view
I also don’t want to do it
for other people’s children
Let your children be sad
Uncle
Yu An and I
will never get back together
Don’t be so You're welcome
Thank you
You can eat too
Use serving chopsticks
Serving chopsticks
Follow You don't seem to care about
using public chopsticks
actually we should
meet and chat earlier
before I made an appointment with you once
Later, you had something to do
and canceled it
Really?
It was all my fault
I'm just too busy
It doesn't matter
Whether it was before
or now
what I want to say is the same
You don’t have to take it too seriously
This is already
a thing of the past
Since
You have already decided
Why are you still coming to me
Because Yuan
may not have been clear about
his own Thoughts
He listens to you very much
So
I hope you can oppose me more in front of him
As an elder
I want to give you a piece of advice
Whatever we do
Don’t do it rashly
in advance Conclusion
I
have no feelings for Yuan
Who can guarantee
emotions
It is eternal
Everyone can understand this
But when we do things
we still need to rely on our brains
Rely on reason
Rather than relying on feelings
Uncle
I may not
have a mind like yours
nor enough sense
But I understand
What I really think in my heart
The mind may lie
But the heart does not
I choose to follow my heart
Who told you that the heart can’t lie
You are an honest child
I will not be obsessed with
Meaningless things
But
For Yuan
I am willing to understand you
I will too Give you more time
Of course
I also know how to wait
Uncle and aunt
This is the contract I have drafted b>
Take a look
What if there is a problem
Tell me now
I will go back and correct it right away
What if No problem
You can sign now
As soon as you finish signing
The money will arrive immediately
Auntie
Sooner or later we will be a family
This investment is nothing to me
It’s nothing
Just do it
yourself  Do what you mean
It doesn’t matter if you lose
Look at it
Look, Xiao Peng has said this
What else are you looking at
Hurry up and sign it
Come on, I’ll sign it first, I’ll sign it first
This is Ren Yuan
Carefully prepared for us
You must not be responsible for Ren Yuan
This is not in vain Yuan
My whole heart for us
Like this
Yu An
Where is this contract
Let’s take it back
Look at it carefully again
After you sign it
I will send it to you
It’s by the way
Let’s make a date with your parents
Let’s get together
Let’s talk about your marriage to Xu Nuo
Do you think this is okay b>
Listen to Auntie
Okay
That Xiao Peng
That
Don’t worry about Nono Ah
Let’s help you do it
What’s that guy’s name
I
Your tea has gone cold
Look at this tea
It tastes good. Try it.
Welcome to visit next time
Please walk slowly
You
Is there someone else I like?
I’m a little tired and I’ll go to bed first
Call me tomorrow and say
Promise me Do you
have another man?
Why do you ask this suddenly
Why
You can’t ask
You don’t even understand
this
She told me
between her and you
It’s irreparable She
is more confident than I thought
more intelligent
But I still feel
She is not suitable for you
What else did she say
What she said is not important
What matters is what you think
She said so
You still have to marry her?
I met her parents today
I met
They think
We should
get the wedding done as soon as possible
Her parents
Can they decide her affairs
Do you think it is useful
to invest in that laundry for her parents
You are here again
I feel like whatever I do
is wrong
I hope you
can confidently turn the situation around
instead of doing those things
Pointless things
Do you think I will definitely lose
Because I don’t know
What exactly do you want to win
But I hope
You have to understand one thing
When you know you have lost
you should give up without hesitation b>
Don’t lose yourself
Do you know what I’m talking about
It turns out that when boys are anxious
they also keep looking at their phones.
What are you doing
No wonder you are at home recently
You keep looking at your phone
Where am I
going
Have you gone to see Xiaobai?
What's going on with you two now?
Tell me
You have news
I have information but I don’t know
It’s getting louder
Slowly
It’s okay
I'm sure it's okay
I'm leaving
It's okay
Slow down
Zhao Qin
Ride slower
Hello
I’m not disturbing your sleep, right
I’m already awake
What are you doing
I was thinking about getting into trouble
Didn’t you already
get into trouble yesterday
Looks like you got into big trouble
What did you do yesterday?
I don’t want to tell you
Then don’t tell me
I didn’t mean to hide it from you
I just think
There is no benefit in saying it
That’s why I don’t want to say it
I know
That’s right
Do you want to meet my dad?
I'm looking forward to it
What's your expression now?
I don't have any expression at all
That’s fine
What if your dad doesn’t like me
What should I do
What are you worried about
My dad is such a nice person
You are so happy
Uncle and aunt
Aren’t you pretty good too
My mother is pretty good
But she disagrees
I am with you
What parent in the world
doesn’t want their children to be well
Although I still don’t
understand Auntie completely
But I still
understand it somewhat
Now it’s not just me Mom
And my dad
They reconciled
Maybe
Wouldn’t that be nice
You don’t seem worried at all I
am somewhat mentally prepared
for my uncle and aunt’s
attitude
I don’t know Why
Although
there are some problems now
but I feel that I
am very happy now
So don’t be too anxious
I think this is enough
I don’t want to
I want to have Zhao Jin now
I'm quite happy to be needed
Okay
I'll hang up first
What are you doing
Where are you running
Let me tell you
Running to a man’s house in broad daylight
The impact is not good
How did you know that I was going to his house
I’ll go find you
You said this yourself
Do you believe it yourself
I don’t know what’s wrong
I just want to see him
I don’t know
how he got here
It’s like sleepwalking
You are a bit perverted
Okay
I’m leaving
I won’t tell you anymore
I’m leaving too. I’m going to work
That
What are you doing
I think you are still
a little too excited
It is easy to commit crimes of passion
It’s better not to go up there
I think
You two know each other
No
But it seems like we met somewhere Passed
Your neighbor
Not my neighbor
I have never seen this person
Then that look in your eyes
Why does it look like I have a love rival?
How is that possible?
How can I have a love rival?
Xu Yang is obsessed with me
Okay
Then I’m leaving
That
I think you are still
not suitable to go up
Because
I think the influence is not good
I will go see him
I will not do bad things
No, no, no that
That Dr. Zhao Zhao
Dr. Zhao
Don't shout
Doctor Zhao
You wiped off my lipstick
Hello
Doctor Zhao
What are you doing
We are waiting for you to come down
Come down quickly
Come right away
Beat me to death
You are so energetic
You are in a hurry to go out
Uncle Hanhan
Why are you here b>
Visiting your dad
Your dad asked me to bring you seafood
Aren’t you sending him to kindergarten?
I’ll bring it to you on the way Coming here
You make a call
What if no one is home
Your dad told me the password
Say what if If you're not at home
just put it in the refrigerator
Okay, you can help me put it in it
I'm at work
Okay, hurry up and go
Goodbye uncle
Uncle bye bye
uncle
My birthday is tonight
Uncle must come
Okay, I'll go to work first
Hurry up and leave
You two
are not official yet  Together
You want to go up like this
Who do you meet
It will have a bad influence on you
And you saw b>
His clothes just now
have already been changed
He has to go to work
You two together
Go to work hand in hand
Isn’t it more romantic
The performance is over
What did I perform
Since the woman just now
After coming here
You are like a drama queen
You are the only one who is crazy if you don’t know her
I swear I don’t know her She
I swear to the lamp
If I knew that woman, I would
Okay, okay, okay
For someone I don’t know
And I swore a poisonous oath
There’s something wrong with it
My hair is covered in You're in trouble
I'm trying to make you look better
Why are you here
I just want to see you
No The kind of contact that has good connections
Meet directly
Am I a little stupid
You are not stupid at all
You look smart
Let’s go to work
Let me take you to the flower shop
What’s going on with you two?
It’s weird
This
Nothing strange
It’s time to be late for work
Go quickly, go quickly
It’s you. I haven’t made a call
before
Don’t push me
I didn’t push you
Come
Stand still
Keep an eye on it
Come and get in the car
Is there something wrong with you two
Hide it from me
What could have happened between us
hiding it from you
If it weren’t for you
we both would be
Neighbors who have never interacted with each other
Let me tell you something
I’ll just say there’s something wrong
Say
Let’s drive when the light is green
Driving doesn’t affect your speech.
Say quickly
Am I not married?
Park the car
Suddenly my stomach hurts so much
Hold on a little longer
We’ll be there soon
I can’t stand it anymore
I have to go to the bathroom  b>
Really
You should pull over first
Let her get off
Okay
That
Park the car and chat again
If you really don’t want to say anything
Just talk about it another day
You just talked to Shi Ran
The person I saw was my ex-wife
Are you okay
What about the child
Her and her husband’s child
Why is she looking for you?
My dad asked her to bring me some seafood
Why did she come back
She is a single mother now
Is there anything else you want to know
Nope
I’m angry
I don’t know either
She is on her own now
Take a child
Then help your dad
bring you some food
It doesn’t seem to be a problem
Should I be angry
If it were Shi Ran
I would probably be angry
I’ll think about it again
I Went to work
You didn’t tell me before
You were afraid that I
would be angry if I knew you met right
Yes b>
Is this your secret?
Yes
I know
Let’s go
Hand in hand b>
Pull it out
Let’s go
This is the store
Come and treat me here
How about As expected
It’s quite clean
You can also take a look here
It’s pretty clean
Ours house
You know the biggest advantage
What is it
Look across from us
It is the entrance and exit of a community
Get clothes Sending clothes
is very convenient
Business will definitely be fine
As the store grows, we will need to
recruit more employees
You can’t do everything yourself
Do you know these machines?
When did you buy them?
I don’t know much about this yet. Clear
But
about this machine
You can have a chat with the landlord
I think this place is very good
Then hurry up
Prepare the contract
That guy is like this
Can you
follow Let’s talk to this landlord again
Look at it and come up with it
such a sum of money
It’s the same for us
It’s quite stressful
Can you see if the rent of this house can
be lowered
This rent
I You can try your best
to chat with the landlord
But
the location of this store
including its business environment
These previous customer resources
are all very good
So if you two
really like it > I hope I can
make a decision as soon as possible
Make a decision
Do you think there is something wrong with her
What's wrong
This morning Met your sister-in-law
Meeted your ex-sister-in-law
She knows everything
I guess your brother
should have told her
She is here
I think it looks good
It looks particularly good here
Yes, I think so too
It looks good here
Then let’s put this one here too
That’s right
Put this one here right, right, right
Put this one here too It looks good
Everyone in this store is so busy
You two are so free
Aren’t we
busy? Are you arranging flowers?
Waiting for you to get married
I will also arrange flowers like this
Are you happy with it?
That’s fine too
That
How did Zhao Jin tell you
You clearly knew
Why didn’t you tell me
I I don’t know I
saw that woman this morning too
for the first time
Sister Xunuo
I have been with my brother for a long time I told him
Let him tell you earlier But
there is really nothing
between the two of them
It should be me Brother is so nice
She wants to ask my brother for help
But my brother can’t refuse, right?
Yes, yes, yes
This kind of good old man is the most annoying
He has obviously done
unpleasant things
And he still thinks he is justified
But you scold him
You can’t scold him yet, right?
That’s true
But if you think about it carefully
In fact, he didn’t do anything wrong. What
The key is that you don’t
do that Just think wildly, right
Yes
When you persuade others
There are many truths
It’s up to you
You went to find someone else this morning
That’s true
So
When you are unhappy
you have to say it
No matter what happens
We are your strong backing
Yes
I look at you two now
Like two traitors
Stop being idle
Go to the flower market to pick flowers
Let’s do it
What is this?
Doesn’t it look good? I think it’s good
Sister Shi Ran
You said
Sister Xu Nuo and my brother
will not break up
How is that possible
Think about it
The two of them worked so hard
to get together
How could it be because of this?
Just break up
That’s not worth it
Those two people who love each other
How could they separate
I can’t tell you clearly
Maybe it’s because people’s hearts change
How can people's hearts change?
If you fall in love a few more times
you will know
I don't want it
In my life
it is enough to fall in love once
I thought the same way when I was a child
Thinking about
loving only one person for the rest of my life  People
But you find
sometimes in bed
when you wake up
or
on a rainy day When you are walking on the street
Or when the sky is clear
When the weather is particularly good
you will have a voice in your heart
Tell you
You don’t seem to love him anymore
Or maybe he doesn’t seem to love you anymore
This doesn’t seem like something you can do
What you said
It was a line from a movie, right?
I didn’t expect you, Sister Shi Ran,
to speak so poetically and picturesquely
Philosophically, right?
Then I hope you never have to
encounter this day
My brother and sister Xu Nuo are the same
But love is a thing
Who can say for sure
I hope
My brother
Give it to me and I will pick it up
Give b>
Hey sister
It’s me
Where’s Zhao Qin
We both were kicked out
Now we are at the flower market
She is angry
She is angry or not
You don’t know
She is your girlfriend
It’s not my girlfriend
She just
seems to be angry
But she doesn’t seem to be angry at this
Then now I Tell you clearly
She is angry
I think people do wrong things
This is excusable
But you
You can’t hide something from her, right?
You’re trying to trick us now
We’re not human inside or out
I understand.
Then help me keep an eye on it more
If anything happens
You can tell me at any time
Then tell me first I
What else do you have to do
that you are hiding from her
No more
I
I promised to celebrate the child's birthday
You are really hopeless
I can't help you
I won't help you
Hey
If I were your sister Xunuo
I would have broken up with your brother
A hundred times
That would be okay You're not Sister Xunuo
I don't want to be you yet.
You said I'm thinking about it here
Do you want to do this?
Tell Nuonuo again
After all, this money belongs to Yu An
In case she finally
breaks up with Yu An
b>What do you think?
Why do you think so much
Even in the future
They are really not together
It’s not in vain Use other people's money
I've made money
Just pay it back to him
That's what I say
But you said Renyu An
Why did you pay us?
You don’t know clearly
Then go tell your daughter
and ask her to follow The boy broke up
The girl has her own thoughts
I don’t like that boy
But if she is determined
I identified that person
What do you think I should do
Is it possible that I can force her
to marry Yu An
Then She has to listen too
Then I’ll go find the guy named Zhao
Tell that kid to get out
Who do you think you are?
Can you control it?
Why can’t I control it?
We are Nono’s biological parents
We do this for her own good
We can’t just ignore our
parents’ feelings   just
for the sake of a
person we just met
You can also
speak well
Is it possible that you are a daughter
for the sake of your parents
I'm going to sell myself
Aren't you being arrogant?
When did I sell my daughter?
This
We can't just
watch her make the wrong choice
No matter who you tell this to
Xiao Peng Better
Can't look at her
Jump into the fire pit
Emotions
Who can tell clearly b>
Who can persuade others?
It’s useless to tell anyone
But look at you
Aren’t you just a pit of fire
Didn’t I just jump in anyway?
Why am I a fire pit?
It’s not a fire pit for you
You are an alchemy furnace
I was
practicing in your alchemy furnace
I was tortured by you
I still feel that I am full of energy b>
I still want to continue to be tortured
Continue to be tortured
I will give you a golden cudgel, okay?
Give me a cudgel and I will start Smash
your stove
The stick is in your hand
Whatever you want
Kill you, beat you to death b>
I’ll beat you to death to relieve my anger
Okay, keep eating, keep eating
I’ll watch after you finish eating
Okay b>
Drinking
Doctor Zhao
Sister Hong asked you to go to the beauty room
Here you go