Let’s get married
This is too hasty
Marriage should not be taken lightly
At least
there must be one Proposal ceremony
I just thought about it in the bridal shop
You can use this ceremony
to propose to me formally
I think it’s still a bit
Too anxious
Marriage
It still needs to be carefully planned
It needs to be considered in the long term b>
Let’s talk again
Sooner or later the marriage is bound to happen
What do you think?
I’ll go up with you for a while
You have to work overtime again
There is a job that has not been completed
I just forgot about it
Then you go ahead
I'll come see you after I'm done
Tonight
I want to stay here
Do you regard my place as a hotel
You can come and leave as you please
What do you think of me
Why do you say so harshly
When did I do this to you b>
That’s what you just did
What’s wrong with you
Doubt me again
You are the one who resisted me
Yes
I resisted
You are satisfied
You just said you wanted to marry me
If you don’t If you are willing
Just say it
I am not willing
You are happy
Pay attention to safety on the road
What’s wrong with
your clothes
Peng Yuan came to see you
I also saw Dr. Zhao
On the phone at the beach b>
What's the situation
Shi Ran
I can't betray Yu An, right
Then you have to find someone
Must The reason for doing this
The reason why you can only do this
But no matter what
You have to make one thing clear in your heart
That is How
can you make yourself happy
The happiest one
Do you like Dr. Zhao
What’s wrong b>
Why are you crying
I'm fine
I'll hang up first
Then don't embarrass yourself
Yes What do you want to tell me?
This morning
The lawyer sent me
the divorce agreement
You two still go to This is the step
It’s actually nothing
I was very scared when I was a kid
You two are getting divorced
But now that I think about it, it’s a good thing
Both of you are free
We will still be together after divorce
We are still a family
All emotions will last until the end
It will all become a family relationship
I like it to fade in the beginning
And I don’t like it to fade in the beginning
They are two different things
Wait for you later Once you get married
You'll know
Don't you like her yet?
I've been thinking about it recently
What should I do with
What kind of person gets married
You should know it in your heart
I thought I knew it
It can be made as a promise
When you were about to marry me
I was suddenly scared
You never thought for a moment
Breaking up with Xu Nuo
No
That's just
You don't want to be the bad guy
Or
You want to wait for her to bring it up first
It feels like I was dumped
I can’t accept it
That’s your pride
Maybe
Dr. Zhao seems to
something really happened recently
Is he feeling uncomfortable somewhere?
I don’t know No matter
how old you are, Just click
I heard you all
It's okay
How about you do something
You've been here for a long time b>
It’s okay
Why are you all looking at me?
Because Dr. Zhao
You didn’t eat at noon
Yes, I have been in a daze.
I have no appetite.
In addition, I have to think about some
my own things.
Okay. Let’s go after work
Okay
Goodbye Sister Hong
Goodbye Dr. Zhao
Goodbye
It’s because of women
How is that possible
I told you
Your life is also important
Life has many possibilities
If you don’t try, you will give up
Get off work soon, sister
You should get off work early too
Goodbye Have you
gotten off work
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, etc.,
Dr. Zhao, you are here too.
What’s wrong with our family?
I keep vomiting and won’t eat anything lately
I want to come and prescribe some medicine for it
Don’t prescribe it The medicine is over
I'll give it some food
Okay
I seemed to be in the bridal shop yesterday
I saw you
Really?
I'm with Xunuo
Is she okay
Then what?
So you and that Dr. Zhao b>
Is something okay?
Shi Ran
You
must have cried after hanging up the phone last night
Don't Thought I didn’t know
I know you too well
Don’t talk nonsense
That’s it
After he asked you >
Have you anything else to say?
What else do you want him to ask?
But he does want to say something
Finally I didn’t say
Wait a minute
What’s wrong
Hey Shi Ran
Mom, what do you want?
Doctor Zhao
Where are the instant noodles?
Good
Instant noodles
Spicy beef noodles, right?
Why is he there too?
Please keep your voice down
How did I know?
Do I want to inquire about you
I chased you to the convenience store
Come here quickly
That works
That mom
I won’t tell you anymore
Goodbye
Hello
Let’s get together and I’ll see you off
No need for me, I’ll just take a taxi
On your way
I’m going to Xu Nuo’s house
Why don’t you pick up the car
Hello b>
That
I didn’t finish what I just said
Why did you hang up?
Go on,
ask After finishing him
How did he answer you
Buy buy
I just bought instant noodles
I’m not asking this
I, I, I am almost there
At the door soon
Hang up
Thank you, Dr. Zhao
You're welcome
Let's go
Goodbye, goodbye
I'm still not satisfied
How can you follow? He is together
Why didn't you tell me
He sent you back
I can't tell you
He is listening to everything
Then you are dead
Sister
You keep asking me questions
How can I hang up
But I didn’t say anything
It’s still early
Let’s have a supper together
Let’s go and have a drink Let's
Drink some more
Boss, you've had a late night snack recently
You've eaten a little too much
Why
Do you find it troublesome
If so
I will find a new boss for you
No need
I just like to drink with you
Let’s go
Then drink
Zhao Jin
Hurry up, Zhao Jin
Come on, come on Come on, come on
Come on
Okay
How about a drink
Come on Happy weekend everyone
Happy weekend Happy weekend
Is the pet shop still open?
Have a drink after practice
It’s so comfortable
Come on
Open the door
There is something urgent at home
I'll go back first
Are you okay
Nothing
Then please pay attention to safety on the road
Okay
Then let’s drink next time
You can’t park here because of construction work
Why didn’t you finish your drink?
What are you doing
You didn't get off work because you were waiting for me
There were guests just now
Then why didn't you wear a white coat
I'm getting ready to go home
That
Shi Ran is busy
I'm close
I just stopped by to buy some cat food
I was there last night
Didn’t I prepare it for her?
Maybe she doesn’t like eating it
The taste has changed so quickly
I actually
I don’t really like cats
I don’t like raising flowers either
Then you are so unromantic
You definitely don’t either I know how to take care of people
We haven’t seen each other for a few days
I don’t know how to chat anymore
Brothers
Valentine’s Day is coming soon
Who have you been with?
Stop talking about it, I just broke up
Let’s go alone
I’m sorry
I said that among us
Only Yu An’s relationship
is the most stable
Yes
Yu An Brother is getting married soon
I think Brother Yuan
must be the first one among us
to get married
Normally It will be so soon
It’s just a plan
When are you ready?
My girlfriend is very busy recently
I am busy too You also know
You never see each other
So this matter
has to be put aside for the time being
No, brother b>
You have to call your sister-in-law quickly
We brothers will cheer you on
That’s right
Brother’s weekend
Call my sister-in-law now
Ask my sister-in-law to come out together
Yes
Call and call me
Stop well
I’ll call
In fact, there is no frequent construction here
Do you feel it when you sit here
It’s a bit noisy
It’s okay
I’ll be back in a while
Have a fight
Otherwise you should go in Answer it
Hello
Have you slept?
No
What’s wrong
Suddenly with friends Talking about you
So I miss you
I miss you
They asked me to have to call you
Call
Hello sister-in-law
Sister-in-law, we are waiting for you
Did you
drink a lot of wine
Go back early
Not too much
Just happy
Do you want to
come out and have a drink together
Sit down
I won’t go
How about this
I’ll go to your place now
No
Don't come over here
We have to meet each other
I'll go there now
I'm tired
I'm going to sleep
Hello
Are you listening to me
You said I was listening
I see you are tired
Then you should go to sleep first
We will talk on the phone tomorrow
Unfortunately it is too late today
She has already rested
Come, come, I'm sorry
Let's drink
Let's drink, let's drink, let's drink
I'm going back first
I said it Okay
What do you want me to do
I don’t need you to do anything
I can just take a taxi back myself
I’m not talking about this
You know what I want to say
Keep you
Tell you not to leave
Then what do you want me to do
Whether I have a boyfriend or not
I will continue to be with you
Will you continue to get along
Do you want me to be a bad person
In that case
Why do you
come to the bridal shop to find me
Because you want to see you
Me
I
I think
Sorry
You are right
Obviously it was me who came to find you
I broke the
agreement first to be friends
and shirk responsibility
Let you be a bad person
If there is When a friend asks
just say you haven’t done anything
nor do you have any other ideas
It’s all my problem
If that's the case
Me too
Said I want to be friends with you
Make unnecessary phone calls
And just now That way
I found a
random excuse
just to see you
I am even more outrageous
I'm sorry too
There's nothing I can do for you
It's good to know you
You are a good person
I'm not
I have a
very bad idea
I don't expect anything else
I just hope to see you You
will never be discovered
You don’t have to do this
Actually, I understand what you mean
I am Say you
I mean I won’t be discovered by you
I can’t control
my own emotions towards you
I I missed you
I went to find you
So I went to the wedding dress shop
without any plan
But when I saw At
the moment when Peng Yuan
I felt like someone was telling me
it was wrong to do this
I was going to marry him
I mentioned it
You lied again
Just think it was me who lied
I don’t know what else to do
Have you ever thought
Peng Yuan might
be waiting for a
opportunity for you to make a mistake
That is a matter between me and him
I will handle it myself
I thought Zhen Xuaner was there
You seem to be unable to drink
Drink, why don’t you move?
Drink up
Come on, come on, come on
Come on, come on
One more
Good news
Should I stop it?
If this continues
you will lose Many
will also be very painful
I don’t say this to
pretend to be nice
I really think so
If this continues
I will only become more ridiculous
I just like someone
Who is more ridiculous than whom
Catch up Hurry up
Hurry up, hurry up
Hurry up
Get this for me
What else
Okay
I'll get it
the groceries I bought
I'm going to hurry up
Why are you panic
Come on
You haven’t met any acquaintances, haven’t you?
Why are you closing the door?
Let me ask you this
Have you not met any acquaintances, have you?
We are an old married couple
What are you doing
Sneaking like a thief
As for it
What is it for? You
are not my mother now
Do you still have any opinions on you
What about my daughter
Nono, I guess b>
I don’t really want to see you either
Although
our loess is buried
most of it
but There is still
a long way to go
We can’t never see the light
See the light
I’m not saying that It’s up to you
It all depends on your own performance
Just for this performance you can draw so much
In fact, I carry passengers
and pass by often Here
Our mother has lived in the hospital for as long as she has lived
This laundry has been closed for as long as it has
I know in my heart
You actually need me
I don’t want you to be alone anymore
It’s been so many years
I’m not alone
Did you make it through too?
You Don’t worry this time
I will keep my word
I promise never to gamble again
Make our laundry bigger
Live a good life
I am now
I still have some money outside
You still owe money outside
As long as you live in this life Really quit gambling
Live a good life
Let’s pay the money you owe together
How long have
you not washed your dirty clothes  You all
I bought groceries
I will cook for you
No, no, no
I bought groceries
Stop cooking
They will come to you soon
I feel like grandma is a little
unhappy
Did I just
say something wrong
She still can’t accept it
wheelchair and bed
still thinking about going to the laundry Help
I don’t think she will accept it
The days of having a nanny
Once people get used to a life
they are very afraid of being Break
Everyone is like this
Probably
Anyway
Have you changed a little
I will be very nervous
Are you not confident in yourself
Why didn’t you come out last night
Didn’t I say that on the phone
In front of so many friends
You don’t give me any face
What’s wrong with you
Why are you in such a low mood recently
Is it because
your exhibition is about to open
due to high pressure
Are you coming
of course Here you go
Didn’t I agree last time?
Are you showing that you are all
in love for many years
For couples participating
Is there a proposal part?
Just for show
Do you need to wear a wedding dress?
Can you come? Got it
I want to see you in your wedding dress
Get in the car
Let’s go
Don’t worry, hurry up
Let me tell you
Yu An and Xu Nuo are coming soon
Hurry up and leave
Are they getting married b>
It’s almost time
Hurry up It’s okay
Hurry up, hurry up
Okay okay
You
Drive slowly and pay attention to safety
Leave
Slow down
Mom
What are you looking at?
You scared me, you
Look
Look at you, you and me
Didn't you come here
with Yu An
Where is Yu An?
His company has other matters to settle in.
Arrange grandma Okay, let's go
This kid doesn't know either
Come and see me
Yes, come in quickly
I'm waiting for you It’s been a long time
Are you waiting for me
Can’t I wait for you
Don’t you usually
come back from there  b>
Why did you
leave from there today
Whose thing does this belong to
This, this, this thing
The neighbor next door
The neighbor put it here first
Don't worry about it, hurry up, hurry up
Come over, come over here
Tell me what you want It’s really annoying
Obviously the children can
go to elementary school right?
But up to now
I haven’t even received a certificate.
Soon
Really
When will it happen
Okay, okay
Come in and tell me b>
Come on, come on,
come on! Come in first
Come in and talk to me
Come on, come on, come on!
Tell me about it now
What day is it set for?
Don’t ask me if this is okay
every time we meet  b>
Then you two are not in a hurry
I won’t urge you any more
Can this still happen?
Let me tell you
When a woman gets old
she is still the same person
It’s really miserable, look at me
When you got divorced
you didn’t think so
I
This is not
So I regret it now
I’m still thinking about it
Who can I find
to help me take care of this? store
You don’t want to
remarry my dad
It’s not impossible
Think about it b>
After all, I have lived with him
for so many years
We are both so familiar with each other
There is still a tacit understanding
It’s better than marrying an outsider
Mom
Tell me
What kind of person
do you want to marry
You and Peng Yuan
It’s not what you mean
Don’t you have other intentions?
You think Peng Yuan b>
Isn’t it suitable to get married?
What’s the matter with you?
Didn’t you just say it was soon?
I didn’t say I wanted to marry him Break up
Yes
It’s not that easy if you want to break up
I can’t
accord with my own wishes
We're in love
Didn't you
divorce if you want to divorce
Now you want to remarry
You want to remarry again
I
The so-called human heart
Isn’t that what it is?
It’s not under control
Then one moment and the other For a while
Then today will be good and tomorrow will be bad
Then don’t you think the same way?
Who do you think can guarantee
Who likes it? For the rest of my life
Can I help you
Yes
Get married as soon as possible
This is the greatest help to me
Mom
You really want to remarry my dad
When will you
marry Peng Yuan
My Life is hard
My life is hard
My daughter is really unfilial
Ah Quan
Send me a flower
Being in love for ten years
What does it feel like
What does it feel like to be ten years older
What the hell is your answer
Then what do you want me to say
Ten years
Your thoughts on love in the past ten years
There are also lessons learned
What's the use of saying it
Life can't be repeated
What about tomorrow
What are you going to say tomorrow
What do you say? Your
ten-year agreement
with Peng Yuan
I don’t know either
Although I don’t I envy
your love
but as your best friend
I don’t want to see
your ten years of love. Shuidongliu
I have been struggling with you
The human heart is uncontrollable
My mother said
Just stay away Here
Let’s talk a lot
You want to keep it simple
It’s Valentine’s Day tomorrow
Who are you going to spend it with
Who have you been with?
Peng Yuan and Dr. Zhao
You don’t even want to
That Just come and stay with me
I'm going to stay at your house for a few days
The water pipe in my house burst
There is no heating
Real or false
Really why did I lie to you
Promise
Mr. Wang
Sorry
I had an accident here
I originally promised to come here
A few couples
can’t come now
No What's going on?
Why did you suddenly let go?
It's not like letting go.
Break up
As expected
The human heart is uncontrollable
That’s why I’m not coming here
to discuss it with you
Look at you two
They are all so beautiful
The figure is so good
Can you put on our wedding dress
Give me the money
I
No problem
Not just that
I promise
to find all the male guests  for you too
Let your wedding dress
shine here
That would be great
Thank you
Xuan you are so talented
You actually thought of using cherry blossoms
Instead of roses
What a surprise
for us
I will pick out a wedding dress for you
Okay b>
Unexpected you
Unexpected
Not a specific person
I want to say
Love is surprising
The person you thought we would be together
marriage
may still be separated
in the end
What’s wrong, little girl?
I’ve recently started reading
Pretentious literature
Let’s go and have a look
Let's go
Isn't the schedule wrong?
Is there no one on duty tomorrow night?
Dr. Gao asked for temporary leave
I'll come tomorrow night
Don’t you have a date tomorrow night?
Shouldn’t many people date you?
So it’s safer to hide here
Then him
Are you ready?
It’s popular to send cat food for Valentine’s Day
Tomorrow night
Let’s go to the Spring Night Exhibition at the Wedding Dress Shop >
Xu Nuan and Shi Ran are all there
I have plans for tomorrow night
You made an appointment with her
Which one is she?
I said you
How long are you going to hide?
Send you cat food You
are gone
Who did you say you were with? Ah
I don’t know
What are you looking for
An earring fell off
I have something to tell you
Today I am looking for the financial director
To ask for financial statements
He said he needs your approval
I am the same after all
The shareholders of the company
Don’t have this authority?
They just go through the process
Have you found it?
Found it?
I also found this
What is this
Who is this for?
When will you give it to me b>
After breaking up with her
Do you have a schedule?
Didn’t you agree to give me time
I will give you time
It’s not for killing
My feelings for you
You don’t think I’m waiting for you
to give me an exchange, do you?
I don’t know what you are waiting for
Let’s go eat
Old Lin
We haven’t seen you for a long time
Yes
How is it
Do you two work well together
A very good aunt
Guobin b>
What you just said is wrong
Actually, it’s because
they trust me
so when they heard that I would invest
All this money has come to you
Yes, you are the living guarantee
Uncle
I toast you
Okay
Come
Yuan
Me
I also trust you very much
and I didn’t let you go You invest
and let you be a shareholder
I am very satisfied and grateful
Just be grateful
I am not satisfied, dad
I don’t want to be the manager
I think Brother Yu An should do it
Okay
No problem
But things have to go to that point
Only then can there be a place for that step
Yes, yes, yes
Yu An knows this
Yes
Just be clear
Tomorrow night
I booked a private room to sing
Your
first Valentine's Day
Of course you should
Celebrate it properly
Okay, sing well
You don’t know?
Yuan An used to
was the lead singer of the band
Yes
The singing must be very nice
Later, I was afraid that he would delay things
I didn’t let him do it
That’s right
Literary art, thank you
Entertainment is okay
If you want to do it as a serious matter
That would be unreliable
You did the right thing
Come
Did you hear that
Yes
I haven’t heard you say that before
It happened a long time ago
Shanshan
A toast to Uncle Guobin
Uncle Peng
Uncle, let me give you a toast
Okay, okay
Come, come, sit, sit, sit, sit, sit, sit, sit, sit, sit, sit, sit, sit, sit, sit, sit, sit, sit, sit, sit, sit, sit, sit, sit, sit, sit,
sit, sit, sit, sit, sit, sit, sit, sit, sit, sit, sit down
b>Dad
Well call me uncle first
Uncle gives you a drink
Okay