[This trendy drama of romance is only for people aged 12 or older.]
[Once Again]
[Episode 8 Remember to come back to me]
Is it good?
Yes.
Really?
We have two hours before the train departs.
Let's get ready and meet again.
Okay.
Jae-woo, wait.
What is it?
I hope... you can let go of your guilty feelings for me.
Okay.
See you later then.
[Dongsim Hotel for Examinees. Room 308]
[Jae-woo, I know you came here after 15 years to save me. But even so, I will still go save you.]
[Snow cleaner]
Jae-woo.
Jae-woo, I know you came here after 15 years
to save me.
But even so,
I will still go save you.
[Dongsim Hotel for Examinees. Room 308]
Ji-hoon.
Hey.
Where is he?
Where did he go?
He won't answer the phone either.
[I know you came here after 15 years to save me. But even so, I will still go save you.]
Joon.
[11:50, November 29, 2007]
[12:00, November 29, 2007]
[Congrats on Sector 1's rebuilding approval in 2022]
The study room will be closed on January 30. January 30.
Remember.
No.
No!
Open the door!
Sir.
[Congrats on Sector 1's rebuilding approval in 2022]
This is for you trying to be a hero.
Die with him.
Let go! Let go!
Darn it.
I won't let you get away with this.
Sir. Sir.
Wake up! Wake up!
Next news.
The assailant escaping to his residence to hide from the police
has been arrested the next day.
January 30, the police caught the kidnapping suspect...
Are you leaving?
Yes.
Thank you for always taking care of me.
Don't mention it. You worked the hardest.
Anyway, congratulations.
[Dongsim Hotel for Examinees]
What did I say? I told you you'd pass.
Yes, you're right.
[Dongsim Hotel for Examinees]
I'll come back often.
Okay.
I'm leaving then.
Oh, right.
[Dongsim Hotel for Examinees]
I found this while cleaning Room 303.
I'm sure Ji-hoon's desperately looking for this in the heaven.
Give it to him for me.
Yes.
[2022.1.30]
Kang Ji-hoon, how have you been?
[Deceased Kang Ji-hoon]
I haven't visited you in a while. Can't you recognize me?
Are you mad that I came to see you on the anniversary of your death?
Please understand.
I'm really busy.
[Deceased Kang Ji-hoon]
I told you.
Our business is really good.
[Deceased Kang Ji-hoon]
When I first opened a law firm,
I was so tired.
Did you help me in heaven?
[Deceased Kang Ji-hoon]
No matter how tiring it is,
I'm sure it would be fun if you were here.
But today's death anniversary is special. Please understand.
It's today. January 30, 2022, right?
I'll do it for you.
Give it to Jae-woo.
[Deceased Kang Ji-hoon]
I thought you were talking nonsense.
But you're not that kind of person.
I trust you. Bye.
[Deceased Kang Ji-hoon]
This is unbelievable.
You really are here.
What are you doing here?
What happened?
Did you find Ji-hoon?
308, long time no see.
It's been 15 years, right?
15 years.
I'm here to deliver something for someone.
This is Ji-hoon's last will.
You scared me.
Why are you standing here like a ghost?
What's wrong? What happened?
Hyeong-jin, I need your help.
My help?
[Jae-woo, I know you must be sad right now. But you can only come to me when you grow up 15 years later if I go save you now, so that I can meet you again. Just like the wheel of fate. Let's meet again. 15 years later, another 15 years later. For our third reunion, I'm willing to sacrifice 27 years of my life. Jae-woo. So, remember to come back to me.]
Jae-woo.
I know you must be sad right now.
But you can only come to me when you grow up
15 years later if I go save you now,
so that I can meet you again.
Just like the wheel of fate. Let's meet again.
15 years later, another 15 years later.
For our third reunion,
I'm willing to sacrifice 27 years of my life.
Jae-woo. So...
remember to come back to me.
[Congrats on Sector 1's rebuilding approval in 2022]
Where have you been?
You scared me to death.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong with you? You've been acting weird.
Don't worry.
Sir, I'll live well as you say.
Since you saved me again,
I'll try my best to live.
Jae-woo.
[And...]
[Jae-woo who went back to 2007 again.]
[Another 15 years have passed.]
I think it's around here.
Jae-woo. Remember to come back to me.
[Congrats on Sector 1's rebuilding approval in 2022]
Found it.
[Once Again]