Are you jealous of me right now?
Are you out of your mind?
Why would I be jealous of you?
Why not? You can be just a little jealous.
Actually, I was kinda jealous of you.
Especially when I saw you with him.
Why is it not working now!
Gosh.
How can you not buckle up by yourself?
Anyways.
You're still set to be the lead actress.
So you don't have to worry about that.
I didn't mention anything.
I'm not worried about that.
[Notice - One week left to submit
the mentoring assignment]
What should we do now?
Seems like you and I have to go
to the movie together.
Seems like it.
I'm already so out of it these days..
How can we even go for a movie.
Maybe we'll go on your birthday?
It's coming soon.
Well I'm supposed to have dinner
with my friends.
Friends?
Woo Jin's coming too?
Yeah.
[Our Love Triangle]
[EP06. Asking Someone Out Is All About Timing]
I wanted to give you a heads-up,
but it was kind of random to me too, so...
You couldn't even come for classes
because of your schedule.
Aren't you busy these day?
No matter how busy I am,
I've got to make time for it.
It's her birthday.
Hey, come on, chill out.
Actually, he didn't do anything to you.
Anyways,
what brings you here today?
I heard you're going to buy a present
for Hae Rin today.
I'm going to join you.
I'm one of her best friends.
So you'd better count me in.
Then count me out.
You can go without me.
You're not going anywhere!
How can I go without you?
It'd be super awkward!
Well, we're already running out of time.
Shall we head out now?
Isn't that Cha Eun Hwan?
Yeah I think it's him.
He's so handsome.
That's why I didn't want to come together.
Just ignore it.
What's wrong with you today?
By the way, are you looking for something specific?
No, we don't have anything specific in mind.
We're just gonna pick out a gift for her.
You didn't ask her what she wants?
On a meaningful day like this,
givers should thoughtfully pick out gifts.
That's the right attitude as a gift-giver.
So, that's your thoughtfully chosen gift?
Does it have any meaning or something?
You still don't know her taste.
She doesn't like those things.
Things that are flashy or visually appealing,
but lack any real value or substance.
So I suggest you don't waste money,
and ask what she actually needs.
If we ask her directly,
can it even be called a gift?
That's just buying it on her behalf.
That's the way to give someone a gift.
Getting them something they wouldn't get for themselves.
Then, how about we separately pick out gifts
that are actually super useful?
Then what about clothes?
Of course Hae Rin doesn't have clothes. Great idea.
How about this one?
If we order in advance, we can have
customize lettering engraved on it.
Sure, that looks really special.
There are tons of cups everywhere.
That's why we can make it unique,
with some meaningful engraving.
Just stop it!
Let's just buy our gifts
separately...
Please.
[Birthday present ideas for a woman]
[Special gifts]
They're all about the same.
[19.05.04 Ji Woo Jin, High School]
You might end up not being able
to use that one arm forever.
Let's just stop here, Woo Jin.
[Buying a gift for your crush]
I'm leaving school now
together with Eun Hwan Sunbae.
Really? Eun Hwan is going to come too?
Gosh, that photo stand!
Noona!
Why did you come alone?
I had to drop by somewhere.
I see.
By the way,
what is that?
Oh this? It's just trash!
I'm going to throw it away now.
Unni.
Why are you all here?
I have something to throw away.
Go on in first.
What is that?
You don't want to know.
Everything is fine, just go inside!
What are you trying to hide so badly?
It's nothing really.
- It's just a trash.
- Then, lets have a look.
What are you trying to...
♪ Happy birthday, dear Hae Rin. ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you! ♪
Happy birthday, Unni.
Happy birthday, Noona.
Thank you all.
Happy birthday.
Plus,
he wishes you a happy birthday too.
That was just a mistake...
I was about to throw it away anyways.
No one said anything about it.
Hey, come on.
It's such a beautiful day! Stop playing around.
Surprise! Here you go.
It's nothing special.
I just got you a lipstick.
What's this?
I told you not to prepare anything for me.
Thank you, I will use it well!
You didn't bring anything, Eun Hwan?
Well,
you wanted something in particular?
Forget it. Since when did you celebrate my birthday?
You really came empty-handed?
You're so mean.
Then, what about you, Woo Jin?
Well.. I'll... Later in person.
You seemed so confident.
But I don't see any difference between you and me.
Why did you pick a fight for no reason?
It's the thought that counts.
So, never mind.
Yeah, you're right. Presents don't matter.
We all got together. That's what matters.
I should take a picture of this.
Did you change your phone case?
This?
Ah, yes.
These days, I got a lil stressed out,
and didn't know how to manage it.
But this is something I see everyday.
So it's like a self-gift to myself so that I can feel refreshed.
Cute, right?
Hey, what's that for?
Don't you think it's too childish?
Did something happen?
Why are you stressed out?
Well, I'm just a bit worried about the drama,
and something is on my nerves these days.
Personally, I hate using my phone with a case.
It feels heavier.
But you've loved it since high school.
I think you'd better stop drinking.
No way!
You can't tell me to stop.
This is just the beginning.
The beginning of what?
You're already completely trashed.
You are a dumbass.
You are such an asshole.
What? Ass-Asshole?
You...
You really don't give a shit about me. Do you?
She's really drunk.
Unni, wake up!
Are you okay?
Min Joo, I think we'd better
take her home together.
Noona.
You tell me!
Do you think I'm a pushover?
You think so?
Hey, Noona.
You've always been my toughest nut to crack.
Even back in high school,
I liked you so bad.
But you never looked at me the same...
Gosh whatever!
I've had enough.
Now I won't care about you either.
I'm saying it again.
That was just a mistake.
That stupid photo stand.
And what happened on that day.
They were all just mistakes.
Woo Jin.
Can you help me clean up?
Sure.
Hey,
did you know?
That she used to like him?
No.
I saw his face.
Seemed like he also has something for her.
It all adds up now.
That's why there's tension between you and Eun Hwan.
What?
You like Hae Rin too.
You're really sleeping after all that fuss?
That was...
not a mistake.
At least to me.
That day, two years ago...
I haven't forgotten it, not even once.
It was the first time
I wanted something so badly.
But...
At some point, I got scared.
If things went further,
I thought we'd end up like...
Just like what happened with me and my father.
I got scared of losing you.
Happy birthday, Hae Rin.
And...
I like you.
[Our Love Triangle]