LETTER OF RESIGNATION
HWANG DO-HEE
INTRANET NOTIFICATION
LETTER OF DISMISSAL, HWANG DO-HEE
CORPORATE STRATEGY TEAM
What's this? Am I being dismissed?
Well, I don't know
exactly how that happened.
And…
What is it?
You won't get your severance pay.
-We're firing you due to disciplinary--
-Stop parroting company policy and move.
Whether I resign or clear my name,
it's my decision.
On your way to see Ms. Son?
Or do you want to call
an HR committee meeting?
You…
You may leave.
You went too far.
Stiletto heels with glitter.
That's a world you're not ready to enter.
I'd like to think
that I went for something big.
I'll completely remove any traces of you
and rise higher than you.
Keep telling yourself that.
Is this about your severance pay?
Or
your pride?
Maybe you can't accept
being dismissed after ten years here?
Do you think you can
cover everything up by firing me?
Don't tell me
that you consider yourself
a beacon of justice.
You plan to reveal the truth
behind I-seul's death?
This pen
contains the audio recording
of the final meeting
you had with I-seul.
Once made public,
I-seul's mother will learn everything.
Her dead daughter's shameful past,
how you blackmailed her using it,
and how she lied
about being sexually assaulted.
-Guk Ji-yeon!
-That's not all.
The whole world will call I-seul
a gold-digger who deserved to die.
If you want to go that far--
"Attack your target's weakness
to rattle them,
and make them destroy themselves."
Look at me using the method
you've taught me.
That greed will turn you into a snake.
A monstrous beast
that bites off its own tail
to survive.
Return the company car
by the end of the day,
and vacate the company residence
by the end of this week.
FOR A BETTER FUTURE
What happened?
You didn't answer your phone,
so I had to call the next person
on the contact list.
It was an urgent matter.
What's going on?
Why is he being discharged?
Sir.
What are you talking about?
My father's kidney transplant
has been canceled?
The kidney donor has retracted his offer.
Are you sure that's what happened?
Yes, I am.
You have two days to take him home.
He's a gravely ill patient with dementia
and needs daily dialysis.
And you're giving us two days to leave?
We were notified that
he has lost his Eunsung Group VIP status
as of today.
We can no longer offer him
a room at our hospital.
This beef practically melts in my mouth,
but I'm not sure if I should eat it.
I'm afraid I might end up like Sa Jae-gon,
feasting on a meal Ms. Son prepared.
Mr. Kim.
How timid you've grown over the years.
Mr. Sung.
What are we going to do
about the upcoming by-election?
Who to send to the mound?
Leave that to me.
The player I chose has stepped down,
so it's my duty to fill that vacancy.
Ms. Son.
Do you have anyone specific in mind?
I don't think he's half bad.
Ms. Son.
The entire country knows what a great man
your-son-in-law is, but--
And with that,
we're already halfway to victory.
But…
He may lack political experience,
but I'm sure
you supreme members of the party
are more than capable of guiding
and leading him in his endeavors.
Haven't you guys been saying you need
libraries in your electoral districts?
With one for each neighborhood,
you'll have your next election in the bag.
Ms. Son.
Can we trust you this time?
If you change your mind
like you did with Sa Jae-gon--
Don't you worry.
I won't be pulling any tricks
with my own family member.
-Sure.
-Mr. Sung.
You can rest easy.
With Ms. Son's charisma
combined with Mr. Baek's fresh blood,
no one in this country can beat us.
Here!
Cheers!
Are you trying to kill my father too?
He's your father.
He should pay
for raising a beast like you.
Ms. Son.
The reason I tried
to spare your father's life was…
because I trusted you.
I never thought
you'd do something that would offend me.
Ending my father's life…
will make you feel better?
I'll feel somewhat refreshed.
I took in an ungrateful beast like you
and gave you the finest things in life
only to be betrayed.
Don't I deserve some consolation?
Are you trying to turn me
into an actual beast?
Even if you started crawling
on all fours right now,
I wouldn't care.
I shouldn't have…
let you stand on your own two feet
in the first place.
Contact me when your father passes away.
I'll send you a wreath.
Do you have any idea
how many people's blood
have stained my hands
getting your beast-like son-in-law
to walk on two feet?
In order to protect the beasts
that you harbor,
I had to stab, kill,
and bury so many innocent people.
So?
I'll destroy it.
That world of yours,
built on the blood and bones
of the people I've buried.
Everything you love…
I'll grind to dust
before your eyes.
Just like my father,
trapped in his sick body,
I'm going to make you feel…
the pain of being buried alive.
Bring your A-game.
HAN I-SEUL, DECEASED
Watch me.
I'll make that animal beg you
for forgiveness on his knees
like I am now.
Only then…
will I stand on my feet before you.
Residents of Sangah-dong!
You've all been through a lot.
Your sweat and tears
paved the way
for this glorious moment today.
A world where honest
and hardworking people
can reap the just rewards
of their efforts.
Right here where we stand,
that world begins.
My sincerest congratulations
on the redevelopment
of the Sangah District.
-Baek Jae-min!
And
I promise you this.
I, Baek Jae-min,
will serve you,
the citizens of Seoul
who are living in fear
in these uncertain times,
just as I have cried
and laughed alongside you!
Mr. Baek, can we consider that
a formal announcement of your candidacy?
Yes.
I'm running for mayor of Seoul.
-What made you--
-Which party will you represent?
Does the Eunsung Group know?
Everyone!
I first need to take care of myself
to be able to offer
a helping hand to others.
When we have stability and prosperity,
we can work hard
and dream of raising a family.
Wouldn't you like to live
in a world where this is possible?
Seoul is the heart of Korea's economy,
but what use is a rich city
with poor citizens?
I, Baek Jae-min, will make Seoul
a city where its citizens prosper!
-Baek Jae-min!
Look at that.
He's tearing up.
You can tell he used to be a news clown.
That's a master actor right there.
Mr. Ma.
Don't you think we should start preparing?
He already has great brand value,
and his campaign will be loaded
with his in-law's money.
We might end up losing
if we just sit by and watch.
Our candidate's served three terms.
Three terms in a row in the Gangdong area.
She's a pro. In the last 12 years,
she's been through it all.
She's on a different level
to an amateur like him
who puts on a show for sympathy votes.
You think all it takes
to win an election is money?
I'm sorry.
All right. Enough with the serious talk.
Let's plan our campaign.
So, as our policy director,
we want you to keep tabs
on Baek Jae-min's election camp.
Right. Your wife is
in the Eunsung Group's inner circle.
Mr. Kim.
Mr. Ma has been divorced
for some time now.
That's all in the past.
My goodness, you're right.
Mr. Ma, I'm sorry.
It's fine.
But still,
isn't your wife in charge of
Son Young-sim's political donations?
-If you could just get us some intel--
-She quit.
My ex-wife, Hwang Do-hee,
is no longer a part of the Eunsung Group.
ATTORNEY OH KYUNG-SOOK
LABOR LAW SPECIALIST
Ms. Oh, have some coffee.
Oh, I love your hair.
-See you around.
-Ms. Oh, hi!
-Hi.
-Ms. Oh!
Hello, Ms. Oh.
Oh, hi.
-Is everything okay?
-Sure.
-Take care.
-Bye.
What do you want?
It's been a while, Oh Kyung-sook.
I mean,
Attorney Oh Kyung-sook.
Yes, Toilet Hwang.
You're still alive.
I'm pretty hard to kill.
Don't mention the word "kill"
in front of me.
Not when I was almost killed
because you pushed me off that building.
Thanks to you, I've suffered a lot.
I see.
It seems we have quite a few
misunderstandings to resolve.
Misunderstandings, my butt.
Forget it!
I'm here just as Hwang Do-hee.
As a free woman who has
nothing to do with the Eunsung Group.
"A free woman"?
So you were fired.
Have you had breakfast?
I saw a soondae-guk place
at the entrance of the market.
Soondae-guk?
I'm good.
I don't have any business
with Eunsung for now.
Just leave.
If you're that hungry, here.
You can have that.
You're here.
Thank you, all.
-Let's go!
We can do it!
REJUVENATE SEOUL
BAEK JAE-MIN, DREAM MAKER
Thank you for your hard work.
Hello, everyone.
Let's go.
I like the energy.
Thank you.
I need to step up here.
I'm counting on you guys.
Shall we start?
Let us begin the first campaign meeting.
We have exactly 85 days
until the by-election.
Our priority during the campaign
is to have Mr. Baek
rub elbows with the citizens.
We'll finalize the list of mentors
and have them accompany Mr. Baek.
I want the mentors to be people
who regular folks can relate to.
The kind of people
no one has ever seen in a campaign.
Someone like Oh Kyung-sook.
Yes. We're already in contact with her.
Hurry up.
Before some other candidate snatches her.
Above anyone else,
I absolutely need Ms. Oh to work with me.
We'll get it done as soon as possible.
My present…
Is it on its way?
Who the hell is it?
It's me, you idiot!
Hello, Ms. Oh.
Why would you spend the night here?
What did I tell you?
If you get in the habit of sleeping away
from home, it'll ruin your life. Idiot!
Goodness.
Keep living the life of a nomad,
and the life of a bum
will be all to be had.
Ms. Oh.
Don't call me a bum.
I slept here after working all night.
Here are the new cases
we received this week.
All of them?
There's more.
Your popularity is skyrocketing lately,
so you're getting high-profile cases.
Hold on.
This one here.
We're getting clients
all the way from Gangnam.
The client's husband
is a former prosecutor--
Yoon Dong-joo?
Don't get too ahead of yourself.
The workers at the department store
got their jobs back.
So we'll be quiet for a while.
You should
find something to do.
There's lots to do here.
-Ms. Oh!
Come on out! Quick!
-What?
-Everyone's waiting.
Come on out! Hurry!
FUN TIME WITH SANGAH MARKET
AND EUNSUNG
Look at this.
Ms. Oh, this way!
Oh my!
Hi, how are you?
-Kyung-sook!
-Hey!
Ms. Oh! Dong-joo!
Dong-joo!
-On-sil, the uniform suits you.
-Right?
But why would Mr. Baek do
something like this?
It's all thanks to Ms. Oh here.
She joined hands with Mr. Baek
and got on board.
I'm just an old granny in a market,
but I'll get rich soon
with Eunsung's redevelopment.
Auntie, come quick.
What is it?
Ms. Oh!
-Hey, Hwa-soo!
-Dong-joo, come here!
This is our bestseller. Come on.
-On-sil, bring this to them.
-Yes, ma'am.
EUNSUNG DEPARTMENT STORE
EUNSUNG GROUP
Thank you.
Ms. Oh, take this.
What's all this?
Mr. Baek Jae-min ordered yours separately.
Right.
I wanted to treat you to a meal
on a nice day like this.
I can't be there because of my schedule,
but I'll be having the same thing
for lunch, cheering you on from afar.
Give me a call anytime.
Regards, Baek Jae-min.
This looks like a signal
from Baek Jae-min.
What signal?
That he's wooing you
for his campaign?
Dong-joo.
-Yes.
-Hold this.
You're wrong.
It wasn't me who brought
those cheerleaders here.
You really were fired.
Look at you day drinking.
You look like a mutt
abandoned by its master.
Should I call you Mutt Hwang
instead of Toilet Hwang?
-Want one?
-I'm good.
Why did you do that, that day?
What?
On that day, on the rooftop
of Eunsung Department Store…
Why did you come up there at night
and pull that stunt?
I wanted to protect
what little conscience I had left.
Conscience?
I mean it.
I wanted to wash off…
the blood I had on my hands.
What a load of crap. You make me sick.
Get to the point so I can leave.
Why did you come to see me today?
Oh Kyung-sook.
You could be mayor.
What?
The mayor of Seoul.
The Eunsung Group fired you,
so you got pissed off,
and now you want to use me?
You're furious because their son-in-law
is running for mayor,
and now you want your bloody revenge?
Wow. You really are
the nutcase of the century.
I heard this market's being redeveloped.
The good shepherd, Baek Jae-min,
seems to have sent his many sheep.
Yes, he sure did.
If it's a lamb chop you're after,
go ahead and join them.
The redevelopment is a scam.
The people here will lose everything.
Listen here.
By telling me
the redevelopment project is a scam,
did you think I'd go, "Aw, really?
I had no idea. Those bastards!"
Did you think I'd take your side? Huh?
Are you expecting me
to set myself on fire, screaming,
"Be gone, oppressors of the common folk"?
Go peddle your snake oil elsewhere!
Bank workers will come this afternoon.
With seemingly great loan offers
to tempt the merchants.
Sangah Market
will be the most searched term,
and articles about the market
and Baek Jae-min will flood the Internet.
The people here will be ecstatic.
And at that moment,
the press will come.
Sure, whatever.
Get a crystal ball,
and work as a fortune-teller.
Okay. Please come this way.
We'll explain it to you in detail.
SINWOO BANK
LOAN RECEPTION DESK
How many cameras are there?
One, two, three.
Bank workers will come this afternoon.
With seemingly great loan offers
to tempt the merchants.
It was my scenario.
The goal is to dazzle the people
so they'll agree to the redevelopment.
This soondae-guk is amazing.
Have a nice, spicy bowlful,
and come to your senses.
Open it when you're free.
I'll wait here in case you have questions.
Why? What is it?
What's that?
LAYOFF PLAN FOR EUNSUNG
DEPARTMENT STORE WORKERS
"Plan to remove Sa Jae-gon,
Mayor of Seoul, from office"?
DRAFTED BY HWANG DO-HEE
There are rumors about illegal slush funds
that Mayor Sa had been keeping.
He was given cash
totaling 600 million won…
Moon Yong-soon, the wife of Mayor Sa,
was spotted wearing 300 million won
worth of jewelry…
I hereby resign
from the position of mayor.
EXPECTED TO COST TWO BILLION WON
This is how they did it?
Ms. Oh.
Where did you get this?
This is ridiculous--
There were more cameras than I expected.
Is this the Rhino syndrome?
Who do you think you are? How dare you…
Ms. Oh, why is this woman here?
You seem pretty shocked.
What are you trying to do?
Show off?
"I'm the Great Toilet Hwang."
"This is how hard I worked
for Eunsung's owners."
Is that what this is?
No. I wanted to tell you.
How Eunsung's owners manipulate the world.
The merchants have already been taken in.
We'll give you detailed explanations.
Come.
They're hypnotized by Baek Jae-min's show.
Not knowing this redevelopment project
is just a trick to pad Eunsung's pockets.
And you, Oh Kyung-sook…
were the cameo that completed their show.
What are you talking about?
He was able to enter this market
without any resistance
because you took his hand
and shouted hurrah with him.
The people will shed bloody tears,
and you're partially responsible.
GIVE ME A CALL ANYTIME
REGARDS, BAEK JAE-MIN
Shit.
Get out.
Don't spew your nonsense here.
Go to a news channel!
Did you leave your brain at home?
What?
Fine.
Let's say I use the media to expose them.
Then Eunsung would sue me.
For violating my terms of employment
and my NDA.
They'll throw in slander
and libel for spreading falsehoods,
and the lawsuit will last over five years.
The election is less than 100 days away.
While we throw mud at each other in court,
Baek Jae-min will become the mayor
and destroy this market.
It'll already be too late.
Enough.
So, what?
What do you want?
Let's bring it down.
The world of Son Young-sim.
Let's end her for good.
So she can never get back up again.
Why does it have to be me?
With you at that?
Why me?
To bring about the better world
Oh Kyung-sook dreams of.
Just leave, okay?
Pretend to have a conscience all you want,
but I'm not buying it even one bit.
Leave.
Dong-joo.
Let's go home.
Come on.
Yes, ma'am.
A person died.
I killed her.
I, Baek Jae-min,
have a lot to learn.
However, I dared
to jump into this heart first.
To make this city
a place where citizens
are well off and respected,
I started on this path.
But I'm not alone.
I have esteemed friends
who've joined this journey with me.
With them by my side,
I, Baek Jae-min,
vow to be victorious
with every step I take.
Thank you. Thank you for coming.
We've prepared snacks at the back.
The interview will take place later,
so enjoy yourselves. See you later.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you.
Mr. Kim, it's an honor.
-Mr. Baek, you have my support.
-Thank you.
Mr. Jang, I'm a big fan.
I've read all your books.
I drove her to death to hide…
the blood on Baek Jae-min's hands.
Thanks to that,
he managed to keep himself spotless…
rising up higher than ever.
I finally found my favorite mentor.
-Me?
-Yes.
Boy.
You feel awkward being here as well?
Strange is more like it.
The girl's family
must still be wailing at her grave.
But here, the trumpets sound…
Are they so loud because they're meant
to drown out the wails of her family?
What do you mean?
You know I-seul, right?
Ms. Han I-seul
made the choice to end her own life.
I never said anyone killed her.
Oh!
Did some bastard kill her?
I'm telling you this
because Ms. Han and I seem to have
a lot in common.
As you know, I've also fallen from the top
of Eunsung Department Store.
Practically pushed off there.
Ms. Han could have suffered
the same cruelty
I experienced, but you know,
if I'm wrong about this, I sincerely
apologize.
Come on.
We're family now. No need to apologize.
I'll think of it
as concern from a well-fed cat.
What?
Whatever made you jump from the roof,
you survived, and helped
500 people get their jobs back.
Now that you're a hero
and your life has improved,
you can look back
on those who have passed.
It's better to be alive than dead.
I feel bad for I-seul.
Right.
They say that the true hell is here
on earth, not below us.
Do you want to
drive them back to hell, by chance?
Look over here please.
Ms. Oh, smile please. Now both of you.
Thank you.
We're so happy to see you two
on the same team like this.
Mr. Baek, as long as Ms. Oh
is here with you,
we the workers will always support you.
-Here's to Baek Jae-min!
-Let's go!
Go Baek Jae-min!
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Ms. Oh Kyung-sook.
What is your reason behind joining
Mr. Baek's Campaign Mentors?
I don't have one.
I'm not doing it.
I'm withdrawing my decision
to join Baek's campaign.
For what reason?
Are you sure you're not being let go?
Why did you change your mind
all of a sudden?
I don't think he's a suitable candidate
for mayor of Seoul.
Then who do you think is suitable?
Anyone as long as it isn't him.
Are you thinking about running, Ms. Oh?
There's nothing I won't do to stop him.
Sure. Why not? Let's give it a go.
Ms. Oh!
Mr. Baek! Was this discussed before?
Stupid. I must've gone crazy.
What am I going to do now? God!
This damn mouth of mine. What do I do now?
Oh Kyung-sook.
I'm impressed.
TRENDING SEARCHES
OH KYUNG-SOOK
As a PR expert, I'd say
you were born with it.
OH KYUNG-SOOK NEVER DIES
OH KYUNG-SOOK ANNOUNCES CANDIDACY
I'm done for.
You're a natural
at grabbing the public's attention.
You have an instinct
for creating dramatic moments
by spewing things without a filter
and have this defiant look,
perfect for leading a coup.
From a show business standpoint,
you're a desirable talent.
"Show business"? What are you on about?
Do you have any idea
what a fool I made of myself there?
Oh Kyung-sook, get out here!
We know you're in there.
Come out! Quick!
Ms. Oh!
-Ms. Oh!
-Come on out now.
-Come on out!
-Seriously.
Ms. Oh hasn't come to work yet.
She might not come in today.
Where did she run off to, then?
Where did she go after upending
the entire marketplace?
-Sir, what do you mean by "upending"?
-Okay, why don't you tell us Dong-joo?
Baek Jae-min said
he'd redevelop our market.
So, why did she stab him in the back?
Come on, sir. That's not it.
She must've had her reasons.
What reasons?
Ms. Oh!
-This is crazy.
-What are you up to?
Go out and do something.
They seem quite upset.
Do what?
Sit them down,
and explain everything? One by one?
The whole truth?
Reveal everything about I-seul
and the real Baek Jae-min?
You can at least offer them
a sincere apology.
-Just to calm them down a little.
-Calm them down?
Riling them up I can do,
but there's no calming them down.
So many rich people
have sweet-talked them into things
that they won't bat an eye
even if I apologize.
Don't act like you know stuff
when you don't.
Get out here!
This is driving me crazy.
Whatever! What do they want me to do?
I don't care.
There was an unexpected turn of events
at Candidate Baek Jae-min's Campaign
Mentors Inauguration Ceremony yesterday.
Mr. Baek.
I'm incredibly disappointed.
The election hasn't even started,
and you let that woman stir things up.
I thought you would handle
Oh Kyung-sook easily.
Don't worry too much.
We'll publish our press release
through our outlets.
It'll all blow over
after I give them a few interviews.
My loyal supporters--
Elections are about momentum!
Temporary measures won't work.
You have to clip her wings.
Yes. I'll take your advice to heart.
Mr. Baek, don't let this get you down.
I bet our opponent is
much more anxious than we are.
"The People's Servant."
An unexpected incident took place
last night during Candidate Baek's
announcement of his Campaign Mentors.
With about 80 days remaining
until election day,
the Seoul mayoral election
has taken an interesting turn.
We have Assemblywoman Seo Min-jung
of the Reform Party of Korea with us
for a few words today. Ms. Seo.
I hope you are doing well.
I'm the People's Servant, Seo Min-jung.
I believe Ms. Oh's unexpected announcement
could also be considered
as her challenging you
since you're also a mayoral candidate
in the upcoming Seoul by-election.
Me?
You have served three terms already,
and you're the face
of the Reform Party of Korea.
Not only that, you've made your mark
as an irreplaceable female politician
who is much loved by everyone.
But I think she might take
your political position.
You're saying Ms. Oh could replace me?
Yes.
I don't know.
I think I'm the only servant
the Korean people need.
Dear viewers, what do you think?
-Great work.
-Thank you.
-Take care.
-That was wonderful.
-Great job.
Joong-seok, let's go to Mt. Jirisan.
Pardon?
We'll be busy
with your campaign announcement speech--
Should we let Oh Kyung-sook steal
my supporters and replace me?
I need a loud announcement ceremony
to draw attention.
Do I have to provide all the plans?
I'm sorry.
If you're really sorry, get Oh Kyung-sook
and stuff her in a coffin for me.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Don't touch that.
I trusted you.
If I set the board, you said you'd push
king, queen, or bishop out of the way
and rise to the top.
You're ruining everything
because of some woman
who isn't even worth using as a pawn?
Did you drive Do-hee
out of the company for this?
I apologize.
Leave.
You've brought enough shame
to my husband's memorial.
If you have time to bow to him…
go to Do-hee and beg her
on your knees instead.
Ask her to save you.
-Stop Hwang Do-hee this instant.
-Stop her?
How exactly…
You said
you could do better than Hwang Do-hee.
Would she have asked me
something like that?
Guk Ji-yeon!
You said you wanted to rise
higher than her.
If we lose the election
and upset my mother-in-law,
that'll be the end.
You and I
will both be dumped in the gutter.
Get it together.
Jeez.
Whoa.
Stop trying to be so chummy.
And the market people?
Still mad.
Asking how you could do such a thing.
So, what are you going to do?
What do you mean?
You might as well run
now that this has happened.
If you don't after everything you've said,
you'll look so lame.
We could gather your supporters
and run a campaign--
Yoon Dong-joo.
Cut it out.
Yoon Dong-joo, was it?
You seem resourceful.
I could use you as a mid-level manager.
Use me? Who do you think you are?
Chairwoman of Oh Kyung-sook's
Mayoral Campaign Committee.
Seriously?
Too old-fashioned?
All right, then.
Campaign Manager.
That has a nice ring to it.
Call yourself whatever you want.
Let's do this.
It won't be easy to work under me.
Why am I working under you?
I'll lead Ms. Oh's campaign myself.
I will make Ms. Oh the mayor of Seoul
with these two hands.
Come here, you idiot.
Why are you only picking on me?
She started this nonsense.
So unfair.
Unbelievable.
Jeez.
Gosh, when will that punk grow up?
Did you check?
Anyway,
this is as far as I go, yeah. I…
will stop here.
Stop provoking me.
You saw for yourself
what kind of monster Baek Jae-min is.
-That's why you--
-Went off.
I looked so cool doing it.
"Baek Jae-min shouldn't become mayor."
"I won't stand by
if you make someone like him
the mayor of Seoul."
Then why stop now?
If you live your life
only doing what looks cool…
you end up an empty shell.
I've spent all my life fighting
an endless battle
to make the world a better place,
and I ended up becoming a bad wife
and an even worse mother.
Abandoning my family and being a busybody.
Saying I'll make the world better.
I've done enough of that already, okay?
I almost…
died once. That's more than enough for me.
-But--
-Honestly…
I was pushed
from Eunsung Department Store's rooftop.
You know that, right?
That's how I got caught up in this mess
and got this far.
But people call me
the godmother of workers and a hero,
not knowing the truth.
That's too much pressure.
I feel guilty.
Let's end it here.
I'm off.
Quit smoking, you idiot!
Let's go.
Call me.
Hello, Joong-seok.
-Yoon Dong-joo.
-Yes, ma'am.
Let's stop chasing rainbows
and live quietly.
Let's take better care
of our families. Okay?
We'll start.
Hwang Do-hee!
ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS, LOCATIONS,
INSTITUTIONS, AND EVENTS
IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS