Everyone.
Did you know that rhinos
are an endangered species?
It's because the rhino horn
is known as this miraculous cure-all.
However, in reality, a rhino's horn
is made completely out of keratin,
which is nothing but dead skin cells.
In other words, consuming the rhino's horn
is no different than biting
and eating one's own nails.
Disappointing, isn't it?
It seems those who've been enticed
by the rhino's strong appearance
and loud voice
are exaggerating
the value of the rhino's horn.
The crazy rhino…
She seems pretty pissed.
-That's why I provoked her.
-…monikers describing Ms. Oh.
But I found a name that stands out
amongst your campaign staff.
Hwang Do-hee.
Yes, she's our camp's campaign manager.
Exactly. Campaign Manager Hwang Do-hee.
She worked on a conglomerate
corporate strategy team for over a decade
and was their famous problem solver.
Isn't she the polar opposite of you,
the rhino of justice who stands and fights
for the rights of laborers?
That's right.
The path Ms. Hwang was on
was rather different, no,
completely different from mine.
But we happened to face each other
over the issue
of temporary workers one day,
and through that interaction,
Ms. Hwang discovered
the tragic reality of laborers.
She started soul-searching--
Oh, so are you saying
you're willing to embrace anyone
as long as it might win you the election?
That you are willing
to take and use even a rotten tree
that grew in the garden
of a conglomerate family
as long as you can win?
Are you saying
that I should abandon this woman
who devoted her life to me
just because our paths differed
in the past?
"Woman"?
You're making this into a gender issue--
Then, Assemblywoman Seo,
do you think that it's okay for you
to give the cold shoulder
to anyone who didn't support you
in the past?
Is that why you're still ignoring
calls from Hayu-dong residents
to demolish the chemical plant
in the area?
Or are you prioritizing your sympathies
with the corporation that owns this plant
so that you can maintain your power
as a three-time National Assembly member?
Is this your strategy?
Well, now,
you're going off-topic to attack--
Please answer the question.
Why are you refusing to pass the bill
to remove the chemical plant
from Hayu-dong?
Relocating the plant
isn't difficult at all.
But relocating the plant to a rural area
would hurt Seoul by reducing
the number of manufacturing jobs--
This is a chemical plant
we're talking about.
Not a kimchi factory
with chili powder flying about.
It's a chemical plant
that emits sulfurous gases, okay?
Are you willing to ignore
the health and safety of Seoul's citizens
as long as you can bring about
economic growth? Huh?
Does money come before people's lives?
Is that it?
Listen, Attorney Oh. Please calm down.
Of course the health and safety
of citizens comes first.
Yes. I'm glad to hear that.
I definitely agree with you.
Then you must believe
such a dangerous chemical plant
should not be in Hayu-dong,
and it must be removed
for the health and safety of the citizens.
That's what you're saying, right?
Assemblywoman Seo.
The citizens of Seoul
are watching right now.
You should give us your answer.
Yes, of course.
I, too, believe
that we should definitely consider
the removal of the chemical plant.
I knew it!
I wouldn't have expected
any less from the People's Servant.
Thank you.
We'll return after a commercial break.
Call Chairwoman Cheon, and let her know
what I said was just for TV.
Just focus on the debate for now.
The one-on-one debate is over
and the audience questions will begin,
so review the potential questions.
Ms. Oh.
People are going crazy.
They're saying the rhino
body-slammed her opponent.
What about Do-hee? What did she say?
Ms. Hwang. He's here.
Soo-ho, hi.
Am I too late?
No, you're just in time.
This is the Wednesday End-All Debate
that brings about change.
Today, two female mayoral candidates,
Assemblywoman Seo Min-jung
and Attorney Oh Kyung-sook,
are both with us live on air.
Next we'll have a Q&A session
with the audience,
where you'll answer
your supporters' questions.
Now, does anyone have a question
for Assemblywoman Seo?
Oh, yes.
I have a question regarding the video
uploaded before today's debate.
Assemblywoman Seo.
The lifestyle portrayed in the video.
Is it all true?
Okay, let me give you the facts upfront.
It is not.
It seems a certain camp is trying
to brand me as an extravagant spender
and an indiscreet woman.
I think it's a witch hunt.
I think it's an attempt to start a fight
between Ms. Oh and me
by framing this with the cliché
that "Women are women's worst enemies."
I see. Then does anyone have a question
for Attorney Oh Kyung-sook? Yes.
I would like to
ask a question
to Assemblywoman Seo Min-jung.
Oh, it's Attorney Oh's turn
to answer a question--
Assemblywoman Seo.
What do you think
the moral boundaries of a politician are?
Do you think their privacy
should be strictly protected
provided they don't break the law?
I would like to hear
your thoughts on the matter.
Well, yes.
That's quite an interesting question.
OH KYUNG-SOOK
SEOUL, A GOOD PLACE TO LIVE
Assemblywoman Seo?
Well, I would say,
more than anything,
I believe you should listen
to your conscience.
Joong-seok.
Your ex-wife is such an evil bitch.
How could she bring Soo-ho into this?
-I'm sorry.
-Get him out of here!
Get Soo-ho…
out of my sight right now.
We're live on air.
If he disappeared
after asking you a question,
the viewers would think--
You motherfucker. You son of a bitch!
You couldn't control your fucking ex,
and then let this happen?
This is why I advised you
to end things with Soo-ho
before he became a threat to you.
What did you say, you fucker?
We should finish the debate for now.
Clean this mess up.
Or I'll kill that bitch
Hwang Do-hee myself.
Jeez, it's hot.
Hi, Ms. Oh.
I'm soaked!
God, it's so hot.
Guys, have a heart.
-Let me just take this one off.
-No, you can't.
Come on. It'll break all my ribs!
But your waist looks perfect.
-God, I can't breathe.
-Can you hold this?
-Hang in there.
-Okay, the left.
Hey, Do-hee.
Did you see Seo Min-jung?
She seems to have completely lost it.
What's gotten into her?
Forget what happened and keep going.
We're going to ignore the cue sheets
and the questionnaires,
and go off script.
What's this all about?
Just answer the questions
head-on, like a rhino.
Be aggressive and don't dodge questions.
I might end up causing an incident on air.
That's exactly what I want.
Stir things up.
Now, let's take a question
from a female supporter.
Yes, you, over there at the end.
Hello.
I am a great fan of you both
and support you both in the election.
Nice to meet you.
I would really love to see
Seoul gets its first female mayor
in this election,
but I'm worried that this competition
between two remarkable women
might take all your energy
and end up splitting the voters.
So I was wondering
if the two of you were willing
to become one.
What do you mean?
For example,
you could have a primary election
and unify under the winner.
The moderator is on Seo's side.
He took a break
the moment she became flustered.
But only two breaks are allowed
during an hour-long debate.
There's one in the middle,
and he can choose the time
for the second ad.
After that, he can't interfere
with the debate, even if he wants to.
We'll bring up the primary election now.
That's your signal
to start pushing for a primary election
using the power of live TV.
Well, since this isn't
an official campaign period,
bringing up such an issue
might not be appropriate at this moment.
-Excuse me.
-Yes.
Are you cutting off this question?
No, Attorney Oh.
I'm just making a correction--
Sir.
You weren't the one
who asked the question,
so why would you try to correct it?
I thought the goal
of this audience question session was
to create a safe space for the citizens
to freely voice their opinions.
Am I wrong?
You're right. But--
If I'm right,
let's hear what she has to say.
Please, do go on.
In order to win,
are you willing to unify
under a single candidate?
"A single candidate"?
Yes.
I am all for it.
As long as the competition
is fair and square,
I am ready and willing to humbly accept
whatever the outcome may be.
And for Seoul,
I am willing to become one
with Assemblywoman Seo.
We will live and die together as one,
joined by mind
and body too. I'll do whatever it takes.
Oh, I'm afraid that this isn't something
I can decide on my own
without first discussing it with my party.
A primary election is
a family affair between party members--
In that case, I will join
the Reform Party of Korea.
Is the Reform Party of Korea
a supermarket? A convenience store?
There are formalities and procedures
for joining a party.
Come on, is that really important--
We must look into your character to see
if you fit the party's vision
and determine you won't harm
the party's history or its name.
And with the approval
of the other members--
This is so frustrating, seriously.
I can't believe this.
How can you be so stuffy? My God.
Gosh!
Jeez.
Oh my!
I've had enough!
I mean,
formalities, procedures,
and pretending to be pretty and confident.
Let's just stop, okay?
I mean, let's just throw
things like this out the window.
All we need to think about is
what's best for the citizens of Seoul.
I, Oh Kyung-sook,
have taken it all off.
For the city of Seoul,
to protect Seoul
from conglomerate lackeys,
I stand before you as myself,
just as I am, and challenge you
to a primary election, fair and square.
-Oh Kyung-sook!
Ding!
And it seems like that was
the end of the People's Servant.
It seems that Attorney Oh's
on-air corset revolution
has brought Assemblywoman Seo Min-jung
to her knees.
That's right.
And the debate came to an abrupt end
without her really answering
Attorney Oh's request
for a primary election.
Is the rhino already preparing
for the primary election?
Ms. Oh!
You were oozing charisma today.
You were totally and absolutely
awesome today.
I agree.
When you suggested the primary election,
we got goosebumps. Right, guys?
That's right!
Yes. I owe you a big one, guys.
I knew you would back me up,
so I provoked Seo today.
Ms. Oh! She's our hero.
She's the creator of the viral video
that completely shook up
Assemblywoman Seo before the live debate.
I'm Lee Cha-sun.
Ms. Hwang asked me,
so I worked my magic.
Did you like it, Ms. Oh?
Oh, thanks to you,
I had a great start to the debate.
Please keep up the good work.
Raise your drinks. On three,
"Let's win the primary election."
One, two, three.
-Let's win…
-…the primary election!
All right. Let's go!
What's with you?
Why are you here alone,
brooding and looking all cool?
Are you trying to get my attention?
Aren't you the one who tried
to grab my attention with that stunt?
The corset.
It must've startled you.
The Oh Kyung-sook I know
is the last person
who'd use strategies like that.
What strategy?
Who would calculate
and plan a move like that?
Wow. That's why I say you're a natural.
How could you pull
a stunt like that instantly?
You know what?
Can we do
without the corset?
It's suffocating and pretentious.
It oppresses me.
I'd rather wear handcuffs, okay?
Fine.
You win.
You mean it? Keep your word, okay?
Yes!
-Yes, I'm free!
-Wow!
Okay. Here's to my freedom. Cheers.
I thought you'd be drunk out of your mind
after a day like today.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to make Oh the mayor of Seoul.
By doing everything I can
to get dirt on my opponent.
Soo-ho is
just one of the musical prodigies
that Ms. Seo is supporting.
Since he is so gifted--
She started a foundation
with conglomerate money,
bought him a violin worth 300 million won,
got him a house,
and slept with him.
And before she gets caught,
she had you ruthlessly
cut him out of her life.
…and challenge you
to a primary election, fair and square.
It looks like this Hwang Do-hee knows
how to play the game.
Shouldn't we cut them off now?
If Oh Kyung-sook runs wild like this,
it won't be easy for me to draw attention.
This is what makes elections fun.
The dew-christened hero of the morning
makes way for a new hero of tomorrow,
created overnight.
Thrilling, isn't it?
Now, it's about time
we join the game too.
Hello, everyone.
The Greenpeople Foundation is celebrating
its seventh birthday today.
I'd like to express my heartfelt gratitude
to all our supporters
who've volunteered
and shared their time with warm hearts
for all these years.
I am thrilled
that I am able to come to you bearing
a heartwarming gift on this wonderful day.
A shelter for all Korean women,
including single and unmarried mothers.
It's a home for you.
I present to you, Green House.
GREEN HOUSE
We made this plant
so that children can grow
and taste it themselves.
Mr. Baek. Could we have
a nice photo of you two?
Oh, shall we?
Could you two stand a little closer?
This way, please?
Thank you.
-Ms. Eun, is something bothering you?
-Are you two happily married?
No one has asked me that in a while.
Are you aware of the rumor
that your marriage is a sham?
Some say that this event
is also just a show to help you
become mayor.
-Well, that's--
-I was asking Ms. Eun.
I haven't been well recently.
I visited an OBGYN because I had symptoms
similar to when I was pregnant,
and it turns out…
that cancer was spreading in my womb.
I underwent surgery immediately
and am no longer at risk,
but the painful chemo has made me
extremely sensitive to stress.
And…
I was devastated by the fact
that I can no longer have kids.
I know that many of you have noticed
that we've grown apart as a couple.
It felt as if my womanhood
had come to an end…
I couldn't put a smile on my face
when I was with my husband.
He hesitated to run for mayor.
He said he'd drop out and stay by my side
when my condition worsened,
but I urged him to run.
I, who had been living
in the lap of luxury, had to face
such hardship as a woman.
Then how much worse must it be for mothers
in dire situations?
I asked him to lead
the way in helping
those mothers in need.
She's a smooth talker.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
This is the last time
I appear in one of your clown shows.
Wow.
A new hero is born.
You did a great job.
A huge weight has been lifted off my chest
thanks to your stellar performance.
Well, the credit goes
to this loving couple.
The cancer card was really dramatic.
I almost believed it was true myself.
The cancer was Ms. Eun's idea,
and the kiss was improvised by Mr. Baek.
Chae-ryoung, you did well.
You too, Jae-min.
It's nothing.
It was Chae-ryoung
who did all the heavy lifting.
Mom.
Then can I return to the department--
You should be at your husband's side
until the election is over.
Right. You have to support him dutifully
as his wife
for Mom's plan to pan out.
So, you'll have Seo-jin keep running
the department store?
It's also tied to attracting investment
for the duty-free shop.
Enough.
Today is a good day.
Let's enjoy ourselves.
-To Mayor Baek.
Baek Jae-min won over voters
with a spontaneous romantic gesture
during his foundation's anniversary event.
He rose to the top
of the popularity polls.
It's Attorney Oh Kyung-sook,
who has taken the nation by surprise
with her corset revolution,
against Baek Jae-min,
who showcased his loving side
by tending to his wife's broken heart.
It's expected to be a heated race
between the two unique candidates,
the corset Amazon
and the romantic husband…
"A race between the two"?
They're not even mentioning us?
Ms. Seo.
This election is
a total box office flop for us.
That isn't our only issue.
We were counting on her
and didn't prepare a Plan B.
We might end up losing
the public's support
to the Korea Republican Party
as well as the mayoral office.
There's also a rumor going around
between the aides about your private life.
What's going on?
It looks like a bomb
is waiting to explode.
Mr. Yang.
You're crossing the line right now.
Considering how I'm the one feeding you,
you should just use your mouth for eating.
Instead of running it
about my personal life!
Don't you give me that crap!
-Sir, calm down!
-Feeding me?
-Oh, come on, let's go.
-You think you feed me?
Let go of me!
Who do you think you owe it all to?
-Come on.
-Let's step out.
-Who made you win?
-Calm down!
What have I ever done wrong?
Where are you taking me?
Agree to the primary election,
and I won't use Soo-ho
against her anymore.
You'll remove us
through the primary election
and go up against Baek Jae-min?
So cooperate.
Hwang Do-hee.
A primary election isn't that--
The People's Servant
had an affair
with a young artist in his thirties.
Is it desire, neglect of duty,
or a disgrace?
I believe gossip like this
is more than enough to rile up the public.
Should I share it with the reporters?
Agree to the primary election.
That's the only option we have.
They have Soo-ho against us.
Did they promise
that they won't go public with Soo-ho
if we agree to it?
That Hwang Do-hee has done nothing
but stab us in the back.
Ma'am.
Or are you two working together?
Are you using Soo-ho so that you can
put an end to my career for good?
Do you have a better idea?
It's not just your career that's at risk
if we lose this election.
It would mean a death blow
for all the elders of the party,
our representatives,
and the people at the bottom, like me,
who supported you
and the pride of our party.
They only support
whoever emerges as the victor.
Once you defeat Oh Kyung-sook,
the party will keep news about Soo-ho
from harming you at all cost
because that's how we can all survive.
I, Seo Min-jung…
I, Oh Kyung-sook…
swear to fight fairly to become
the Reform Party of Korea's
mayoral candidate.
For the betterment of Seoul,
the burning heart of Korea…
For the happiness
of the beloved citizens of Seoul…
we announce
our full commitment and agreement
to the primary election.
A NEW SEOUL
What about Ms. Cheon?
We've called her numerous times,
but no answer.
Petty hag.
-I'll contact her assistants and--
-Leave it.
She'll call us
when my approval rating goes up.
So it's you.
The infamous
Hwang Do-hee.
An honor to meet you.
Must be your ingrained habit
as a conglomerate lapdog.
You've really dug deep to find dirt on me.
I should teach you a lesson
so that you can survive
in this line of work.
I can't wait
to receive valuable lessons
from a three-time assemblywoman.
How dare you!
Lower your eyes!
Mind your own damn business,
you little shit!
This is the last time
I'll be polite enough to take a blow
from you, three-time assemblywoman.
What?
-Let's go.
-How dare you?
You audacious prick!
Hey, Joong-seok.
Are you going to let him
get away with that?
Right,
Ms. Cheon has offered to throw us
a party to celebrate our candidacy.
Could you tell her that though grateful,
we must decline?
We have no intention
of accepting support from her.
Ma'am! Ms. Cheon!
Wait!
-Ma'am!
-Ma'am, be careful.
Watch your step.
Ma'am!
You grow ever more ill-mannered every day.
How dare you walk over my green
in those heels?
Oh, ma'am.
Ma'am.
Please help me.
You made a public promise
to remove my chemical plant on live TV.
Now you want my help?
It was Oh Kyung-sook.
I fell for her trick.
If I'd said I'd protect
the chemical plant live on TV,
I would've fallen behind in the polls.
And if I fail to become mayor
because of that, you'll also…
Judging from your long-winded excuses,
it must be your time to go.
Ma'am.
It can't be Oh Kyung-sook.
Even if she becomes mayor
with your support,
she will never keep
that chemical plant around.
And?
Just trust and support me one more time,
and I'll swear on my life… No,
I'll swear on my child's life
to protect that chemical plant.
You know how good I am.
I do.
My money is what makes you good.
If it weren't for that, there's no way
you would've served three terms
when you were nothing
but a pretty figurehead
in the political scene, don't you think?
So this time, I intend to see
what you're really capable of.
Win the primary election
without any help from me.
Are you all right?
I have to win, no matter what.
Find dirt on Oh Kyung-sook and her family.
Dig up her ancestors' graves if needed.
The moment I find one tiny fault,
I'll use it to drag her
to the depths of hell
and put an end to her for good.
TRAITOR OH KYUNG-SOOK MUST RESIGN!
SANGAH MARKET MERCHANTS' ASSOCIATION
-That was good.
-Thank you.
-That was delicious.
-Bye.
A bowl of noodles, please.
Hi, yes, welcome--
How have you been?
The kimchi looks good. Is it fresh?
Don't.
Don't touch it.
Please hear me out.
Piss off.
I've got nothing to say,
and I don't want to hear anything, so go.
Get lost!
Stop disturbing my business.
You disgust me!
-Sheesh.
-Auntie.
How dare you sneak in here?
What, are you going to beg for votes now?
What a nerve!
I know that you are upset with me,
and I understand how you feel.
But the only reason
I'm running for mayor of Seoul
is to protect regular people
like the merchants here--
Cut the bullshit!
That's a load of crap!
Hey, Oh Kyung-sook.
Do you think we're idiots?
You bad-mouthed Baek Jae-min,
who wants to redevelop this market,
so you can get votes
from the working class!
We're not falling for your bullshit.
Sir.
Please hear me out--
-Get your dirty hands off me.
-We don't need your help, so get lost!
That's the end
of the ordinary people's hero.
The moment you're branded as tainted,
your own side throws stones at you.
How pitiful.
-Go away!
-My goodness.
Why are you lynching her in the streets?
-Hyun-woo.
-Like mother, like son.
Look at his temper!
That's right. I'm Oh Kyung-sook's son!
So stay away from her
unless you've got a death wish, asshole!
You little brat, what's wrong with you?
Is this how I taught you
to treat your elders?
Apologize, now!
I'm sorry. I apologize.
I'm terribly sorry. Forgive him.
Why aren't you apologizing?
Goodness, would you look at that?
She should teach her son right first.
Hyun-woo!
Kang Hyun-woo!
Look at me, Hyun-woo.
-Hyun-woo.
-Are you a punching bag?
Why do you put up with them?
Why did you let them
beat you up like that?
Hyun-woo.
Please hear me out.
The people at the market are a little--
You said it's for a good cause,
so I should be supportive.
When you missed
my birthdays, graduations ceremonies,
and sports day events,
you said it was to help those in need,
so I should be understanding.
For what?
You took shit from people,
fought for people, and jumped
off a building, only to be beaten up?
Is this what I had to give you up for?
Sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Kang Hyun-woo.
I'm sorry.
If you're sorry,
will you quit?
Hyun-woo.
I can't wait to see
the great world that you'll make.
Hyun-woo.
THE LEAH COMPANY
SANGAH, SOONJUNG DISTRICT
GREEN BELT DEVELOPMENT PERMIT
The fifth investor's conference
for Asia's number-one landmark,
Eunsung's new duty-free shop building,
Heaven, will begin shortly.
We'd appreciate your cooperation
in taking your seats
with our staff's guidance.
"The moment Eunsung's
new duty-free shop building is completed,
Seoul will become Asia's heaven on earth…"
We're ready for you, ma'am.
How many people?
With the guests at the conference
and foreign investors joining us online,
there are 890 in total.
That's twice as many people
as our last conference.
It seems that we're reaping the benefits
of Jae-min's candidacy
in the election.
I hope you like my outfit.
Chae-ryoung's acting as a happily
married wife to keep her share.
So I'll go for it as well.
Friendly competition never hurts.
Let's go.
Heaven of Asia!
The moment Eunsung's new duty-free
shop building, Heaven, is completed,
Seoul will become Asia's heaven on earth.
Over the next ten years,
Heaven is expected
to bring Eunsung a profit of
950 million dollars.
The businesses and the school district
that will be built
around Heaven and the quality of life
for local residents will be top-class.
The infrastructure in the area, including
apartments, shopping malls, and offices,
will be occupied by Eunsung subsidiaries.
The closer your ties to the Eunsung Group,
the more heavenly your life will be.
I welcome you to that noble world
of your dreams
with open arms!
-Baek Jae-min!
SANGAH MARKET
-Impressive.
-Thank you.
But
won't there be trouble from the poor
who cannot enter that world?
Prior to developing the area,
don't you think you should drive out
the poor currently living there?
We need to give them hope.
No one can refuse the sweet promise
that no matter how poor
or weak you are,
you can become rich
and live a life of heavenly pleasures
as long as you join hands with Eunsung.
I, Baek Jae-min, will make sure
that Sangah Market
is redeveloped!
Who does the Sangah Market belong to?
It belongs to you all.
This is your life's accomplishment
that you've poured your blood, sweat,
tears, and youth into.
I, Baek Jae-min, will turn this market
into a place that can provide
for not just you and your children,
but their children too.
I will open
the doors to that heaven on earth!
-Baek Jae-min!
Hi, how old are you?
Thank you!
I will do my best!
-Baek Jae-min!
How sad.
All those naive people
really believe they'll end up rich.
-Baek Jae-min!
He's exploiting that fantasy.
"Trust me, and you'll escape
this wretched life."
-Baek Jae-min!
Anyway,
I know you didn't call me
to watch Baek Jae-min put on a show.
I want you to rain…
on that despicable parade of his.
It was reported The Leah Company,
a multinational corporation
based in the British Virgin Islands,
has obtained the rights
to develop a green belt area in Seoul.
Districts, such as Sangah and Soonjung
that The Leah Company
hold the development rights for,
were originally scheduled to build
five million apartment units
for low-income families.
Why was an area that was supposed to
become a home for the citizens of Seoul
given to a foreign corporation
with no roots in Korea?
Who might be behind The Leah Company?
Oh, thank you.
They say a man's position changes him.
My dear deputy mayor, you look
more like the little president of Korea.
It's all thanks to you, Ms. Son.
I don't deserve the honor.
I know you've had it easy
feasting on the scraps
from Sa Jae-gon's trough,
but I believe that it's time
for you to work for your food.
You must prove your loyalty
by throwing yourself
into harm's way to protect me
if I'm to let you keep feeding
from that trough of yours
and make sure
your family can stay in the States.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
I'll correct everything this instant.
Hold a press conference.
Tell them that Seoul has no relations
with The Leah Company whatsoever
and that you don't intend
to withdraw the permit
given to them or stop them
from their scheduled redevelopment
due to such baseless accusations.
Of course, ma'am.
I'll hold a press conference
tomorrow morning,
and tell them exactly what you told me.
There's a good dog.
As long as you stick
to the food I give you,
you won't ever get sick.
"Seoul city
is in the process of investigating
the fairness of the permit
given to The Leah Company
to redevelop the land in Seoul."
Okay, good.
Got it. Oh, right.
You've included every word
Chairwoman Son relayed to us, right?
You've checked again and again.
Have I?
I've also invited
a few reporters friendly to Eunsung,
so you can relax.
They'll embellish their articles
if we miss anything.
Good. Let's go.
Kim Jeong-do, the acting mayor of Seoul,
will shortly begin
the press conference on the issue
of the supposed favoritism given to…
He won't try any funny business, will he?
In today's press conference,
the acting mayor…
He's incompetent, not stupid.
As long as the press conference
goes over well,
I'll lower the official land value
in Sangah District.
Mom.
But that would reduce the sale price too.
I feel generous.
Once Jae-min becomes mayor,
all the green belt areas of Seoul
will be in the palm of my hand.
It's my present to the common folk
who don't even own a house.
Yes. That's a great idea.
It is in the common folk's nature
to bow their heads
when a ruler they deem harmful
offers them an unexpected kindness.
Yes.
I plan on giving that kindness
little by little
so I can reap the benefits
for a long time.
Until you make Jae-min the new mayor.
Great.
Acting mayor Kim Jeong-do…
I will do my best.
…is entering the press conference.
ACTING MAYOR KIM JEONG-DO
EXPLAINS CONTROVERSY
OVER FOREIGN COMPANY
First of all,
let me apologize
to the citizens of Seoul
about the allegations
that the Seoul metropolitan government
colluded with a foreign corporation.
Yesterday afternoon,
you visited Chairwoman Son of Eunsung
from 1:40 p.m. to 3:30 p.m.
You two seemed quite serious.
Is it related to the press conference
you're holding today?
What are you talking about?
You know reporter Kim Cho-rong from IBC?
Should I send her this photo?
It is strongly suspected
that The Leah Company is owned
by the owners of Eunsung,
and acting Seoul Mayor, Kim Jeong-do,
is at the center of this controversy.
The moment I send this photo,
this will naturally be
the headline of the article.
Why don't you read this instead?
Currently, the Seoul
Metropolitan Government
is investigating the fairness
of the decision to sell
the redevelopment site
to the Leah Company.
Due to the concerns and the interest
of the citizens of Seoul,
we will put a hold
on the redevelopment permit
we have given to The Leah Company
until the new mayor has been elected.
Furthermore,
the 39th mayor of Seoul,
to be elected in the mayoral by-election
in 70 days,
will be given the sole power to decide
whether the redevelopment construction
should continue or not.
Mr. Mayor, what if it's revealed
the city colluded with The Leah Company?
When will it be revealed
whether the land was unfairly sold
for redevelopment?
If the construction doesn't resume…
-Mr. Mayor!
Kim Jeong-do, the acting mayor of Seoul,
has announced
that Seoul city is currently investigating
the fairness
of selling the redevelopment site
to the Leah Company.
In addition, all development
will come to a halt…
How much?
If the redevelopment of Sangah
comes to a halt,
we will suffer a loss
of 2.8 billion won a day.
And the other district?
Things are looking worse
in Soonjung District.
The loans we took out from the national
pension under The Leah Company
were all spent on the construction
of the duty-free shop.
If the investigation starts,
the duty-free shop--
Don't let the investigation start!
Since when do we care
about the complaints of these peasants
when doing business?
The press and public opinion
aren't the issue.
It's our foreign investors
who are getting spooked.
They're withdrawing
their investment in the duty-free shop
because Seoul city
is distancing itself from us.
All right.
Dad, happy birthday!
Thank you, ma'am.
Come on, Dad.
Don't call your daughter "ma'am."
But my daughter got married
to this handsome man you see in the photo.
Come on, Dad.
Hang in there.
I'm doing everything I can
to find a new donor for you.
What's the point of living longer?
I'm only a burden to you and Joong-seok.
Right.
How is my grandson doing?
Oh, I see your daughter is here.
Hello, ma'am.
You're working so hard.
Please. It's the patient
who has it the hardest.
By the way,
why aren't you visiting together?
I'm sorry?
I mean…
Your husband came to visit yesterday.
Right.
-This hand, please.
-Okay.
Ma'am. Please take good care of my father.
Call me anytime if anything happens.
Sure, don't you worry.
What are you doing?
What do you mean?
Where did you go,
and why didn't you answer your phone?
Did something happen?
Yes.
Having you disappear from my eyes is
the worst thing that could happen to me.
If something happened to you,
Ms. Oh would be the one
to suffer the blows.
How could I not care
about your whereabouts?
Are you playing hot and cold
with me or something?
I simply haven't got the energy for that.
I'm too tired.
What about lunch? Have you eaten?
I haven't had a bite because of someone.
Let's eat together if you haven't yet.
What do you want?