I was wondering what you were up to.
You've been living in hell,
where only beasts were born
and live in poverty
because of the sins they committed
in their past lives.
Jacob's wife from the Old Testament.
The woman who prospered her whole life
as her reward for obeying God, Leah.
That's the name Chae-ryoung used
while studying abroad.
It was you, just as I expected.
The de facto owner of Leah Company.
Of course.
You've always been
such a smart girl.
It seems that you take after me
more than the daughter
that I gave birth to.
If you really meant that, you would've
dropped a hint about this earlier.
I spent over ten years
of my life serving you,
but I didn't even know
Leah Company existed.
But, of course,
you wouldn't give the keys
to the safe to a mere guard dog.
-Did that disappoint you?
-Not at all.
I'm glad not to have sunk myself
deeper into the hell
that you've created.
Do-hee.
You should stop now.
You taught me how to run…
but you never taught me how to stop.
Are you sure?
That you can handle
whatever happens to you?
Wasn't it you who told me
that it was my destiny
to handle things beyond my control?
It's gotten chilly.
Take care of yourself.
You've always been
sensitive to cold weather.
Leah Company is a hot topic.
The acting mayor, Kim Jeong-do,
has finally commented on the connection…
Don't you worry.
…between Seoul and Leah Company.
Acting Mayor Kim said the allegations…
This only happened because Hwang Do-hee
knows this family inside out.
You will solve the problem
as the pillar of the family.
I would prefer it if problems didn't occur
in the first place.
Take care of Hwang Do-hee ASAP.
We'll do our best
in the jobs that we each have.
I've prepared a bold color
for you to wear.
Your next stop is
a visit to a digital market.
Don't worry about me.
Focus on supporting Chae-ryoung.
Something's up with them.
That seems a bit overdramatic
for picking out a tie.
Keep your husband in check.
He can't risk messing things up
with another affair.
Is that the best you can come up with
while sitting in the spot
you stole from me?
Your stupidity is the reason
you always lost to me.
Chae-ryoung, grow up.
I didn't lose to you. I walked out myself.
I didn't want to live
as mom's puppet, like you.
Brace yourself.
If Jae-min doesn't become mayor,
Mom will disown you in no time.
You were only my replacement
to begin with.
You must've cared for Hwang Do-hee
more than I thought.
Visiting her in person
at a time like this.
Why haven't you
taken care of Do-hee yet?
I did it for you, ma'am.
I didn't return
just to make
your son-in-law Seoul's mayor.
Then?
Through this election, I intended to make
Baek Jae-min a presidential candidate
so that I can place the whole nation
in the palm of your hand.
Do you think that's possible,
realistically speaking?
It's what the people truly want.
What have they ever gotten
as a result of the squabbles
between the liberals and conservatives?
They'd rather live
in a world ruled by money.
It'd be a lot simpler.
Why do you need
a dangerous beast like Do-hee
in that grand plan?
Elections are the most entertaining shows
in the world.
The show must be a success
for a star to be born.
We need someone interesting
like Oh Kyung-sook to grab attention
and someone cunning like Hwang Do-hee
to play the villain
for our dear candidate Baek's victory
to seem more dramatic.
I understand you are set on this,
but it will all be in vain
if the duty-free shop fails.
And Do-hee knows that better than anyone.
Any other requests?
Do-hee…
Get rid of her.
CREATE A NEW TOMORROW FOR SEOUL TOGETHER
OH KYUNG-SOOK
Approval rating?
Steadily increasing.
We still fall short
against Baek Jae-min head-to-head,
but we have a chance once we bring over
Seo Min-jung's supporters.
Ms. Hwang,
why don't we cut the dead wood already?
Our goal is to win the main election,
not to defeat Seo Min-jung.
You're right. Are the ingredients ready?
Yes.
HYUAN COSMETIC SURGERY
Three times a month,
Seo Min-jung received VVIP care
from Hyuan Cosmetic Surgery
in Cheongdam-dong.
I bribed the manager and asked
about how Seo makes her payments,
and I hit the jackpot.
"KM Management"?
All the artists and actors
that are signed with them
receive care at Hyuan.
KM has been covering the costs
of Seo Min-jung's treatment too.
And what's this?
We looked into who it was
that introduced Seo Min-jung to KM,
and it was a private art tutoring group
in Gangnam.
She's paying 20 million won a month
for her daughter's violin lessons alone.
And how is this tutoring group
connected to KM Management?
The daughter of the parent
who let Seo Min-jung into the group
is an artist signed with KM Management.
The one who was in the news recently
for smuggling ecstasy.
No way.
She brought Seo Min-jung in
to keep her daughter's mishap a secret.
This is huge, like a nuclear bomb,
Ms. Hwang.
Keep KM and the cosmetic surgery
out of this.
Sorry?
But KM is the key here.
It's the education that will rile up
every mother in Korea.
Keep the focus on that issue.
It will be the mothers
of this country
who will bring her down
and not Oh Kyung-sook.
No to expensive private tutoring!
-No!
No to education inequality!
We demand Seo Min-jung resign immediately!
-Resign!
NO SEO MIN-JUNG
Expel Seo Min-jung's daughter!
Expel her!
-We demand Seo Min-jung apologize!
-Apologize!
Seo Min-jung's daughter should be expel…
You!
Is this also that bitch's doing?
Your ex-wife?
Release a statement denying everything,
and sue Hwang Do-hee and Oh Kyung-sook
for defamation and spreading falsehoods.
One wrong move,
and you risk violating election laws.
For today, we should prepare
meticulous countermeasures--
Shut it!
No smear campaign or fabrication.
Not even any legal action!
You son of a bitch. Who are you, a saint?
Oh Kyung-sook is even taking
all the swing voters!
How can you be so laid back,
you meticulous jerk?
Let's bring Jae-i in.
What?
Are you suggesting I sell my daughter
out to the public as a figurehead?
The primary election is
in less than 15 days.
As you just said,
we're even losing our loyal supporters
because of this private tutoring issue
with Jae-i.
If we miss this window,
there's no turning back.
Come on. You're hurting me! It hurts!
-What's with you?
-Han Jae-i!
-Can you listen to me already?
-Why should I help out with your campaign?
What about my rights?
You want to get into Juilliard, right?
And you want a place
on Park Avenue, don't you?
None of that will be possible
if I lose this election, okay?
Shit! This sucks!
Do a good job
if you want to become a New Yorker
and have your fancy
human rights protected!
Jae-i, you have to read
what's written here and--
Read it for me.
You were being bullied in school,
and because of that stress--
Do I look like a loser to you? Do I?
Bullied?
Why are you making me out to be a loser
when I'm not?!
You're shameless, aren't you?
I knew you were stupid, but…
You know your mom changed
the entry regulations to art high schools
and accepts conglomerate money
for your lessons because you lack talent.
You're responsible for at least 80%
of the wrongs your mom committed.
As her accomplice,
this is the least you can do.
SEO, THE ONLY OPTION
FOR COMMON FOLK AND THE ECONOMY
Jeez!
Don't be nervous.
Whatever.
We should get going.
What the hell!
Tidy her up.
Like all she does is study.
And like she's been through hell
with bullying and school violence.
Make her look
as naive and pitiful as possible.
When
I went to middle school in America,
I was badly bullied
and racially discriminated against.
Having suffered from school violence
for so long,
I became emotionally unstable
and depressed.
My days were filled
with thoughts of suicide.
That was when my mom
suggested music therapy,
and I finally started to find hope.
When I played the violin,
I could escape the terrible trauma
imprisoning me.
In order to heal
my daughter's wounded heart,
I had no choice but to get her
expensive music therapy.
I knew that it would end up fatally
jeopardizing my political career.
But I…
I felt this desperate need as a mother
to save my child.
The violin was never an extravagant means
to get into good schools for either of us.
It was a lifeline
we desperately clung to!
Please, find it in your hearts
to forgive my daughter.
As the People's Servant,
I promise to expiate my guilt,
and devote the rest of my life
to serving this country!
Jae-i!
Wow, she's such an amazing actress.
With ten days until the primary election,
the issue of Seo's daughter…
No wonder she served three terms.
She won't go down so easily.
She revealed that she was bullied…
You're right.
We'd better hurry on to the next step.
Ms. Seo.
You're regaining the support you lost.
Your loyal supporters have returned.
Don't get excited.
Oh Kyung-sook isn't dead yet.
Ms. Seo.
Nice to meet you, Ms. Seo.
I was moved
by your passionate motherly love.
Thank you.
Well, now it's time for me
to repay you for your moving speech.
There's a hole in the account that holds
Oh's campaign funds?
Well, it's not an actual hole,
but there's a crack
that could become a hole.
I'm well aware that you are a legend
in the world of politics. That said,
do I look like a joke to you?
Or do you think I'm an easy target?
You seem to think it'd be better for you
if I went to the final round
instead of a nobody like Oh Kyung-sook.
I find it very offensive
and extremely insulting.
The heart of politics is having class.
We had a president
without a university degree,
we impeached a president
with candlelight vigils,
and former political activists
are running amok,
but we must maintain some class.
To have some weed, a nobody
like Oh Kyung-sook, become Seoul's mayor
would be truly offensive.
So, you want to use me
to get rid of that weed
and become
Baek Jae-min's sacrificial lamb?
Not a sacrificial lamb
but a symbol of hope.
When two true leaders with class
compete in good faith,
a healthy tension will return
to this rotten political world.
To the campaign office.
Let's come up with a plan
on Oh's campaign funds.
-We already looked into it, but nothing--
-Hey!
I even had to cut my daughter's hair
to get this chance.
We have to deal Oh Kyung-sook a big blow
and make it into the final round.
That's why I'm telling you.
-If we were to take just any bait they--
-Joong-seok!
When I become mayor,
who do you think I'll give my district to?
Sorry?
Are you going to spend
the rest of your career
cleaning up after me
and going from camp to camp?
You know this.
No matter how smart you are,
you're a nobody if you don't get elected.
Let's go. Trust me.
WOMEN'S ALLIANCE, SOOM
WILL THEY TURN TO ACTIVISM?
SOOM, A WOMEN'S ALLIANCE,
FORMED IN 2019 TO REINSTATE TEMP WORKERS
MAJANG-DONG PREMIUM KOREAN BEEF
"Majang-dong"?
I like that keyword.
All right. Let's start with that.
Oh Kyung-sook, common folk's spokesperson,
uses donations for the Women's Alliance
to feast on expensive Korean beef.
Korean beef dinner.
We should check
if she used the money there personally.
She's been there many times.
-Her employees might--
-What's the total?
A total of 3.6 million won.
With workers' hard-earned money,
she treated herself
to 3.6 million won worth of beef?
She's done for.
-Ms. Seo, you can't do this.
-Why not?
-If we get caught fabricating a story--
-We're not fabricating a story.
We're restoring balance
and making things right.
"Balance"?
In the past, when a child
worthy of being a general
was born to a low class family,
the family would maim that child
to prevent the child's destiny.
Someone with the face of a king
when they are not of royal birth
would break the balance of the world.
If we destroy Oh Kyung-sook,
a better world will come.
OH KYUNG-SOOK FEASTS LIKE AN EMPRESS
DONATION MONEY FOR PERSONAL USE
COMMON FOLK'S FRIEND
IS EXPENSIVE BEEF LOVER?
EAT BEEF WITH DONATION MONEY?
CANDIDATE OH ENJOYS DINNER WITH DONATION
MONEY FROM A WOMEN'S ORGANIZATION
Change the headline to a comment
by a taxi driver or a waiter.
Use the common folk's voice
to rouse their anger.
Publish the exact amount of donations
and the cost of the meal.
3.6 MILLION WON OF BEEF?
And for every article,
add the phrase "Republic of Korea."
Middle-aged people get riled up
by patriotism.
This Carl Yoon is an amazing storyteller.
He is the best there is.
If this gets out,
Oh Kyung-sook won't survive another day.
We should nail her coffin shut.
Violation of Campaign Fund Act,
Local Finances Act,
fraud, embezzlement, minor fraud,
and breach of duty. How many?
Six in total.
Sort them out,
and ask Mr. Yoon to go over them.
Tell him I'll hit her tomorrow
when I get the signal.
Yes, ma'am.
Okay, we've prepared everything.
Why don't we give Oh Kyung-sook
her farewell present?
Allegations that Oh Kyung-sook,
the Reform Party of Korea's
Seoul mayoral primary election candidate,
abused money donated for Soom,
an organization to reinstate
fired female workers, have surfaced.
Oh, who protested for the reinstatement
of female temp workers
fired from Eunsung Department Store,
was found to have used
some of the donations
for personal use,
and the members who worked with her
have either turned a blind eye
or actively hidden this fact,
greatly disappointing the common people.
Ms. Oh!
-She tampered with the books…
-Please step out!
-Ms. Oh! Can you come out…
-Ms. Oh!
There she is.
Do you admit to embezzlement?
Ms. Hwang, what's going on?
Deny all accusations
and put an embargo on the press.
Don't do anything other than that
until I arrive at the office.
What about Seo Min-jung's camp?
Are we letting them get away with it?
Keep a cool head. Let me deal with it.
Be there for Ms. Oh.
You can't let them record anything,
not even her breathing.
Ms. Oh!
-Ms. Oh!
-Is it true?
What did you use the embezzled money for?
Did you use that money
for your primary election?
-I--
-Ms. Oh! You have to go.
Ms. Oh, any comment?
Come on, why won't you
let me say anything?
I did nothing wrong.
Why should I hide like a criminal and run?
You know reporters and their petty tricks.
The moment they provoke a word out of you,
they'll use that to publish fake news.
Fake news?
That's violating the election law.
Election Act, Article 96, Clause 2.
Those who purposely report untrue facts
or report a falsified fact
to aid and abet a particular candidate
to win or lose in the election
will be sentenced to up to seven years
or be fined up to 30 million won.
-Ms. Oh.
-And if Seo is the one behind this?
That makes things even worse.
Article 250 of the Election Act.
Publishing or making others
publish false information.
Up to seven years in jail
or up to 30 million won fine.
If violated in the primary election?
Up to five years in prison,
ten million won fine,
and permanent deprivation of suffrage.
I'll write a bill of indictment.
I'll do it.
Ms. Oh. You should talk this over
with your campaign manager first.
Yes, it seemed like
she had a plan to deal with this.
When will she get here?
Yes, Cho-rong.
Go to the National Police Agency
right now.
Seo is filing a lawsuit against Ms. Oh.
You must have quite the intel.
Stop with your show.
Take another step from here,
and we'll also take legal action.
And I'll also expose
all the dirt I dug up on you.
A villain being bad is one thing,
but a hero being bad is another.
No matter what it is you have on me,
nothing will cover up Ms. Righteous Rhino
stabbing the common folk in the back.
That's how politics works.
What are you up to?
You're the one who started it.
You even dug into her private life.
At least I didn't make things up.
Embezzlement?
It's a campaign tactic, not fabrication.
Ma Joong-seok.
Is this why you entered this election?
To end an innocent person's life
with bullshit from your righteous mind?
That sounds ironic coming from you.
Stop it! Now!
This is not who you are.
Winning an election is being who I am.
And the winner is always righteous.
Today, I'm not here
as the People's Servant,
BILL OF INDICTMENT
but as an ordinary citizen of Seoul
to expose the vile two-faced nature
of a certain woman.
Under the guise of the people's hero,
Oh Kyung-sook's hypocrisy
and selective justice has deceived you.
And I, Seo Min-jung, will expose
her abominable nature at any cost.
Did you trace the source of the money?
What a load of bullshit. Damn.
It's all as I expected,
so don't be too startled.
I'll be there soon.
-We'll prepare to take this to court--
-Let's just face it head-on.
Hold a press conference.
Let's do it my way. Fair and square.
Sir. Have you finished eat--
Huh?
Yes, ma'am.
Do-hee, bad news.
What happened?
Your father's gone!
It's been dealt with.
Right, did they get him a jacket?
He needs to dress warmly
if he wants to play hide and seek
with his daughter in this cold.
Yes.
We'll return him in the evening.
Here's a manual we have prepared
for future countermeasures.
No!
Destroy the report.
There's nothing more
we need to do from now on.
The key to a successful smear campaign
isn't perfect planning.
It's leaving our opponent
no chance to respond.
In its early stages.
Then…
Hwang will fail to make a swift response
while looking for her father.
And without her,
Oh Kyung-sook will be rattled.
And the fake news will continue to spread,
turning mere speculation…
into fact.
PRESS CONFERENCE
Hwang Do-hee! Where on earth are you?
Something happened with my father.
How's Ms. Oh doing?
Ms. Oh's not the problem right now.
There are so many articles
that we can't deal with them all.
Everyone seems to believe
that the embezzlement is true!
Get everything we have on Seo ready,
and help Ms. Oh with the press conference.
I'll be back before the press conference.
This is terrible.
You still haven't found him?
We searched the hospital
and the streets, but no luck.
He couldn't have gotten far
in his condition.
My goodness. How could this have happened?
Ms. Oh, we've sorted things out.
HAPPY SENIORS' HOME
Ms. Oh.
We should get going.
Take that.
-You need to look two moves ahead.
-Darn it!
PRESS CONFERENCE
What?
ALLEGATIONS
REGARDING THE WOMEN'S ALLIANCE, SOOM
Ms. Oh.
-How could this…
-Where are all the reporters?
MS. KIM HWA-SOO REVEALS TRUTH
Today,
I stand here
with Ms. Kim Hwa-soo, who has worked with
Candidate Oh Kyung-sook
in the Women's Alliance, Soom.
Ms. Kim Hwa-soo,
who took care of the group's finances
as a former general manager of Soom,
asked me
to be here with her when she delivers
the truth to the people of Korea.
Are you ready, ma'am?
I stand before you
to clear my conscience today.
Ms. Kim, were you in charge
of the donations that Soom received?
Yes. I'm the general manager, after all.
But according to our investigation,
some money in Soom's donation account
seems to have been used
for illegitimate purposes.
What do you mean?
May 3, 2019, 1.8 million won.
June 8, 2019, 1.7 million won.
July 2, 2020, 1 million won.
A total of 4.5 million won seems
to have been withdrawn in cash.
Did you withdraw this money
for your personal use?
No. I've never done such a thing.
Going around accusing innocent people,
how dare you…
Ms. Kim.
You seem to have done
a great job raising your children.
Your son entered a big company last month
after graduating earlier this year, right?
I wonder how you managed
to pay the 10 million won tuition fee
for a private university
when
you were unemployed?
Ma'am.
My son doesn't know anything.
I am solely in the wrong.
I was going to pay it back
when I returned to work.
Please don't tell my son.
You should focus only on one thing.
Focus on
what your best course of action is
to save your precious son.
At first, I felt nothing but gratitude
towards Candidate Oh.
When someone as smart and brave as her
went up to the department store rooftop
for us poor and uneducated middle-aged
female temp workers, I was so moved.
I was so happy to have her backing us.
It gave me the courage to fight
and the hope
that a better world would come.
But
then, I saw her true face.
The money the good people of Korea donated
for us poor temp workers
who were out of jobs,
a large sum of it, had been used
by Candidate Oh for personal purposes.
I even ended up withdrawing
large amounts of cash
and delivering it to Candidate Oh.
I felt a heavy weight on my heart
seeing the hard-earned money
the people of Korea gave us
being used
not for the women's reinstatement
but for Oh Kyung-sook's own comfort.
But
I believed
that we needed…
that we needed to protect her
for a better world…
so I had no choice
but to turn a blind eye.
You did well. Calm down.
Everyone.
There is no doubt
that she was a victim of gaslighting.
Ms. Kim Hwa-soo is not an accomplice
but a brainwashed victim who suffered
at the hands of Candidate Oh.
I ask that the people bring
Candidate Oh to justice
for how she lied to the people
with her righteous image
and exploited the fired workers.
What exactly did she spend money on
and how much?
Ms. Kim, how much cash
did you withdraw for Ms. Oh?
Ms. Oh, how could Aunt Hwa-soo…
How could she do this to us? Damn it!
That wasn't
Hwa-soo's idea.
Ms. Oh, where are you going?
To talk to Hwa-soo.
Now's not the time.
First, we need to release a statement
denying the accusations--
And drive her to her death?
If we do that, it'd only prove
she committed perjury on that stage.
Hwa-soo is one of my people.
I don't know if Seo Min-jung
bought her off or blackmailed her,
but I'm going to go find out for myself.
Do-hee!
What happened?
Your father… Oh God!
I was just driving by,
and he just appeared out of….
Dad…
No!
Dad!
Thank you for your work.
That being said,
that was completely unexpected.
I only thought about
what would prevent Hwang Do-hee
from responding in that first moment.
It is a pity that what happened was
a lot more cruel
than we intended.
This must be the most traumatic experience
of her whole life.
Her only family member has passed away.
I am deeply regretful.
I didn't intend for this to happen.
Looking at the positive side,
it's part of the process
of everything returning to its place.
Have some flowers sent to the funeral.
And make sure to include…
plenty of hyacinths, her favorite.
-There she is!
-Is it true?
How are you feeling?
Why the sudden change of heart?
You did well.
I'll have them escort you home safely--
Come with us
to the campaign staff's lodging.
I just want to go home.
Hwa-soo!
-Aunt Hwa-soo!
-Hwa-soo!
-Move!
Hwa-soo!
We'll keep you under guard,
for your own protection.
You should rest where it's safe.
-Hwa-soo!
-Step back!
-Come on.
Hwa-soo!
-I said, move!
-Hwa-soo!
Hwa-soo! It's me!
Move aside! Damn it. Aunt Hwa-soo! Aunt!
Hwa-soo!
Let's get going!
-Ms. Seo is leaving.
-Hwa-soo!
A few moments ago,
Seoul mayoral candidate Oh Kyung-sook,
who is under suspicion
of embezzling donations…
Ms. Kim seemed very anxious.
Why don't we send her home?
That's nonsense.
We need to keep her as a hostage
to provoke Oh Kyung-sook.
But something's missing in this picture.
With all of this going on,
how come Hwang Do-hee is
nowhere to be seen near the Rhino?
Huh?
You don't think she ran off, do you?
Did she get scared because she couldn't
see how she could resolve this?
…if she'll announce her resignation.
Next.
She wouldn't be that cowardly.
Joong-seok.
There's no point in holding on
to a woman who left you
or a politician who's lost their power.
-There he is.
-He's here.
Any comment on allegations of misdeeds
regarding your book publication?
Tell us exactly where the money came from.
Where did you use the donations?
How much of the donations did you use?
A comment, please.
Tell us the truth.
Tell us where the money came from.
A comment, please.
PARASITE SUCKING DRY THE PEOPLE'S BLOOD
GET LOST OH
CANDIDATE OH SECRETLY STORED
EMBEZZLED MONEY AT HER IN-LAW'S?
Hey, honey.
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
No, I'm fine.
Okay.
What about Hyun-woo?
Is he back from school?
Yes. He's with me right now.
He's all right.
Honey, could you put him on?
Oh, he's too embarrassed to talk to you.
I'll call you back later.
Stay strong, Kyung-sook!
I mean…
What happened with Do-hee?
Where did she go?
She's at the hospital
with her father right now.
His condition suddenly
worsened this morning.
Oh Kyung-sook, a Seoul mayoral candidate,
is suspected of using
donation money for personal…
Is it serious?
No.
She said she'll be back by tonight,
so don't worry about her, and let's find
a way to get through this first.
The expression, "an ass in a lion's skin"…
This is Hwa-soo's handwriting.
She wrote it herself
when we were doing that protest together,
and as you can see,
it's all colloquial from start to finish.
It's short and simple.
Completely different from the phrasing
she used at the press conference today.
Yeah, they're nothing alike.
I heard that hundreds of times
at the protest site.
We'll be able to use that
to suggest that she made false claims
at the press conference today.
It would be correct to say
that she was forced into false testimony.
Ms. Oh.
We need to meet Aunt Hwa-soo.
We'll be able to turn the tables
once we get the truth out of her.
Turn the tables? Forget it.
The game is already over.
Why should I resign?
I thought you'd be ingenuous
as a human rights activist,
but you're quite shameless.
Can't you see
that you're dragging our party's name
through the mud?
I apologize for having brought the party
in harm's way, however inadvertently.
I'll talk to Ms. Kim Hwa-soo
as soon as I can, check the facts--
Ms. Oh. You know what?
Monkeys start acting like pigs
once you put them in a pigsty.
No matter how capable you are,
there's no way to show it
unless you have control of the situation.
Whatever the truth may be,
the Reform Party of Korea
can no longer assist you in any way,
so resign and leave the party.
I refuse.
Seeing how quick you are
to try to remove me,
yes, I'm now certain…
that Seo Min-jung bribed Ms. Kim,
and the party must have
fabricated this story.
"Fabricated"? How dare you?
One more thing.
I'm not a monkey.
I'm a rhino.
I'm a rhino
who will charge on relentlessly
until the bell of truth rings.
She's not resigning?
No.
Have the reporters on standby
outside the lodgings.
Oh Kyung-sook will rocket herself
into the headlines.
Take them.
Candidate Oh of the Reform Party of Korea,
who has been accused of embezzling money
from the Women's Alliance,
is attempting to enter the accommodation
Ms. Kim Hwa-soo is staying in.
People have been critical of her attempts.
Various activist groups,
who had been her strongest supporters,
were furious and have decided to erase
all traces of Oh.
I am here at the scene
where activist groups are burning
Candidate Oh's effigy.
Many activist groups
and women's rights groups
are withdrawing their support
by declaring a joint statement
that they have officially…
I offer my sincerest condolences.
Thank you.
Oh, um…
I am a distant friend of your father.
I heard he was suffering from dementia.
Yes.
Losing one's memory
can be a good thing in some ways.
One could erase all the times one suffered
and enjoy
the happy moments on repeat
as if for the first time.
I'm sure he left happily
with only the good memories
he had with you.
Do you believe in God?
If you do,
you must feel betrayed
in a situation like this.
You're right.
I'd like to ask why this happened,
if I could.
Why my father
had to be taken away now.
I would have asked the same.
But God is unwavering.
He isn't someone that humans can oppose
or dream of taking vengeance against.
I hope this will be
the turning point in your life
that brings you peace.
Then your father
will be able to truly rest
in peace as well.
OUR CONDOLENCES
They look expensive, don't they?
They smell nice too.
Who are they from?
It was your father's friend,
the one who just left.
I wonder what he does for a living.
Are you sure?
That you can handle
whatever happens to you?
But God is unwavering.
He isn't someone that humans can oppose
or dream of taking vengeance against.