YenYen. The top choice for cooling down
and relieving spiciness.
YUMYUM SOOD-DED Spicy,
Triple Cheese Instant Noodles
Amazing Thailand: Your Stories Never End
Download WeTV
and register to become a member.
Then press "CHUANG ASIA S2" channel page
and click "Vote Now"
to vote for your favorite trainees.
WeTV members
will get the vote eligible every day.
You can vote for seven trainees each day
with the limit of one trainee
per ten votes only.
And purchase WeTV VIP
on CHUANG ASIA S2 page,
you will get 20 votes per trainee daily.
To get more voting privileges,
click "Send gifts"
or purchase CHUANG ASIA S2 VIP gift card
to get extra votes.
This round,
you can also get extra free votes
from various activities on WeTV,
such as continuous daily voting
and watching advertisements.
This round of voting starts
from February 2nd, 2025 at 4:50 PM
until February 28th, 2025 at 10:00 AM.
The first elimination
will be only 35 of 60 trainees.
Come and vote
for your favorite trainees.
Who's going to debut
will be solely determined by your vote.
(PREVIOUSLY)
Welcome to the first public stage
of CHUANG ASIA S2.
BAMBAM: Today we have
a total of ten teams,
BAMBAM: and we gonna split
into five groups
BAMBAM: for head-to-head battle.
BAMBAM: Their destiny will be
decided by you.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): The first public
stage of CHUANG ASIA S2
XU MINGHAO (THE 8):
officially begins now.
TIA RAY: For Team OK, OK, OK,
I think your song choice,
TIA RAY: song arrangement,
and choreography were truly astonishing.
BAMBAM: This performance isn't just for
the fans who came to the first public stage today.
BAMBAM: It will also be
shared with all of our online viewers too.
BAMBAM: After this episode airs online, you will also get
the chance to vote and show support for their favorite performance.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8):
The overall stage presentation
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): and each performer's
expressive talents were outstanding.
BAMBAM: Oh, my God.
XIONG: I feel that they manage
to convey this song
XIONG: in their own unique style,
XIONG: while they fully showcase
their strengths.
XIONG: But I still have
confidence in myself.
BAMBAM: The next team, please welcome
Still Monster.
BAMBAM: Thank you so much.
Now let's switch team.
BAMBAM: Alright, Still Monster,
please introduce yourselves.
XIONG: Hello everyone,
I normally speak slowly,
XIONG: but this time, I'll use
my demonic gaze
XIONG: to conquer your hearts.
SHEN: Hello everyone, I will use
this smile to captivate everyone.
SHEN: It's me, SHEN.
GUANMING: Hello, I'm the one who sang
that heartfelt love song last time.
GUANMING: But this time, we're embracing
a completely different style
GUANMING: that's sure to win
everyone's hearts. It's GUANMING.
WUXUN: Hello, this is my first time
performing as a boy group member.
WUXUN: I want to win your hearts
with beautiful dance moves. I'm WUXUN.
EARTH: Hello, my name is EARTH.
EARTH: Please show some love
to this Shiba too.
SMART: What's that?
SENA: Hello everyone, my name is SENA.
SENA: This charming fluffy arm will
SENA: steal your heart. Thank you.
(CUTE)
BAMBAM: Show us your best.
BAMBAM: Alright, keep going. Fighting!
SHEN: Yes.
YAYA: Keep going.
STAFF: Tell us how your team was formed.
XIONG: Actually, at first
XIONG: I was secretly worried.
XIONG: After the Class B trainees had
already chosen teams, I was still alone.
(The Day of Team Formation)
(B Class: No one chose XIONG)
(STILL ALONE)
XIONG: I thought...
XIONG: the song I chose
might not suit them,
XIONG: or they might not like
this genre.
XIONG: So I was quite anxious.
YAYA: Okay guys, before we're going
to the next for group C,
(C CLASS SELECTION)YAYA: could we have WHYLUCAS,
PEANUT, WUXUN, PRAY, JACKSON?
WUXUN: XIONG.
WUXUN: If I join you, will you teach me?
XIONG: I'll teach you to dance myself.
WUXUN: When I was deciding,
WUXUN: XIONG made me a promise.
WUXUN: Back then, XIONG promised me...
The two of us...
WUXUN: are like
we're from different worlds.
WUXUN: Our called out to each other.
(The Day of Team Formation)
WUXUN: Back then, I stood there calling XIONG.
- WUXUN: Are you really sure?
- XIONG: Absolutely.
- XIONG: Definitely.
XIONG: I don't believe you came here
just to learn to sing.
XIONG: I think you joined this show
mainly to challenge yourself in dancing.
WUXUN: Did I come to this show
for the dance challenge?
PRAY: Let's go!
XIONG: It's okay. It's up to you.
TRAINEES: WUXUN!
WUXUN: I don't want to sing anymore.
XIONG: Yes!
WUXUN: Just a blink of an eye,
WUXUN: I felt confused
like everything's tangled up,
(The Day of Team Formation)
WUXUN: because I promised YUCHEN
WUXUN: that I'd stay
on the same team with him.
(Bro, broke my heart)
YUCHEN: Bro, broke my heart.
WUXUN: Back then, I thought
WUXUN: that I joined this show
because of my courage.
WUXUN: I can't dance.
WUXUN: Right.
WUXUN: And then...
WUXUN: To be honest.
(To Be Honest)
(True Feeling, To Be Honest)
WUXUN: I had this feeling,
WUXUN: confidence...
WUXUN: That's why it motivated me
to join Still Monster.
(BELIEF)
XIONG: I think this song
is really beautiful.
(The Day of Team Formation)
WUXUN: Yes, it's so beautiful.
- WUXUN: I'm scared to dance.
- XIONG: It's okay, don't worry if you can't.
XIONG: You've got me here, okay?
- XIONG: You've got me here, okay?
- WUXUN: Okay.
XIONG: Who else do you think
would choose this song?
(The Day of Team Formation)
XIONG: Still Monster.
XIONG: SENA,
(Original singer: ENHYPEN)
XIONG: ENHYPEN.
XIONG: SENA, K-POP.
XIONG: SENA!
(SENA: Still Monster)
XIONG: Yes!
XIONG: Fighting!
(The Day of Team Formation)
GUANMING: Because XIONG is charming
(GUANMING: Still Monster)
XIONG: Okay.
GUANMING: XIONG is
a very charming team leader.
(CHARISMA)
GUANMING: Because it's also
a Korean song,
GUANMING: I was secretly worried
back then, but XIONG said it's fine.
(XIONG RESPONSIBILITY)
GUANMING: Wow.
GUANMING: I feel safe
because of this word.
EARTH: Since the beginning, it's like...
EARTH: like someone asked
EARTH: who else I want to team up with,
something like this.
EARTH: It seemed like I said XIONG.
EARTH: I feel like...
EARTH: it's quite...
what do they call it?
EARTH: Like destiny.
(DESTINY)
XIONG: Just one more person needed.
XIONG: It's up to you now.
(SHEN: Still Monster)
XIONG: Yes!
SHEN: Actually, this song isn't
my first choice.
(NOT MY CHOICE)
(SELECT XIONG)
SHEN: I'm the chooser; I chose XIONG.
(All Team Members: XIONG WUXUN SENA GUANMING EARTH SHEN)
XIONG: That's great.
- XIONG: That's quite great.
- SHEN: Yes, put two people who can dance
SHEN: together.
- WUXUN: Now I'm the biggest burden.
- SHEN: No, no.
WUXUN: It's really hard to say.
(HARD TO SAY)
WUXUN: I'm not a good dancer like the others.
(TURN?)
XIONG: Step up.
(STEP)
XIONG: Need to step like this.
(That's Why)
(STEP)
(TURN)
(Already Crazy)
WUXUN: Sometimes...
WUXUN: the only thing I worry about is
I'll be the team's burden,
WUXUN: because I feel
I might not dance well enough.
XIONG: Uh... how should I put this.
XIONG: Since he believes in me,
I have to make it happen.
XIONG: Just learned it for one day,
XIONG: he showed me that he
XIONG: is intimate with his own body,
XIONG: is a talented person.
XIONG: He can dance.
XIONG: He just needs more time
and a bit more effort.
XIONG: Hmm...
XIONG: He can't remember anymore...
- XIONG: You can do it.
- WUXUN: I'll practice more.
- WUXUN: Practice more.
- XIONG: You can do it.
WUXUN: Practice more.
XIONG: Actually, he needs to
practice more.
XIONG: It will improve dancing.
(GET)
SHEN: Do this a bit more.
SHEN: Yes, yes, yes.
XIONG: Then, let the body undulate.
SHEN: Yes, exactly like that.
XIONG: In dancing,
there are many such moves.
XIONG: Just need to...
WUXUN: Keep doing it like this.
SHEN: Yes, let's practice.
(TOGETHER)
(Snake Year, Let's Be "Snakes")
WUXUN: It's focusing on back muscles.
WUXUN: I practiced this move all night.
WUXUN: Keep practicing continuously
WUXUN: like a little fish swimming there.
WUXUN: XIONG is attentive
and highly responsible.
WUXUN: As soon as I said
I wanted to practice,
WUXUN: he asked me to practice together,
WUXUN: no matter how late it was.
WUXUN: I remember once we
WUXUN: went to the rooftop
WUXUN: because there were
no practice rooms left.
WUXUN: I wanted to practice,
WUXUN: so he took me to the rooftop,
WUXUN: taught me step by step.
WUXUN: Even if the moves seem simple,
WUXUN: there are countless tiny details,
WUXUN: like hand placement,
WUXUN: making claw-like hand shapes.
WUXUN: He said
because this is the monster's move,
WUXUN: you must exert force
through the fingers.
WUXUN: Before this,
I didn't understand dancing at all.
WUXUN: These didn't even
look like dance moves,
WUXUN: including training
physical strength too.
WUXUN: So, I still have much to practice.
WUXUN: Even before bedtime...
STAFF: Do you know
why XIONG makes you practice?
STAFF: I asked him
during the interview earlier.
WUXUN: Really?
WUXUN: What did he say?
(Q: Why should WUXUN
need to practice basic skills?)
(Q: Why should WUXUN need to practice basic skills?)
XIONG: In my opinion...
XIONG: My opinion is, if WUXUN
XIONG: practices the same moves
repeatedly, he'll master them.
XIONG: But if he practices other moves,
XIONG: he'll have to start over.
XIONG: So, I want him
to practice basics extensively
XIONG: so that he can progress
to subsequent moves.
XIONG: I mean he will memorize
choreography faster,
XIONG: or instantly grasp
weight distribution techniques.
XIONG: It's not that barely
mastering one move,
XIONG: then moving to the next,
XIONG: and repeating the cycle.
WUXUN: Honestly, I'm deeply touched.
WUXUN: I've got goosebumps a bit.
WUXUN: If I join you, will you teach me?
XIONG: I'll teach you to dance myself.
WUXUN: But actually
WUXUN: XIONG has been working
really hard
WUXUN: to keep the promise
we made together,
WUXUN: and make it happen.
(BELIEF)
WUXUN: Could you add
a caption here for me?
WUXUN: WUXUN's mentor
is none other than XIONG.
WUXUN: Words of praise.
WUXUN: My highly respected mentor,
wait no, not 'respected'.
WUXUN: Well, there are no
other words to use.
SHEN: I believe
our team leader is pretty good.
(Pretty Good!)
(Quite a lot)
SHEN: There are many details.
(Quite Strict)
SHEN: Yes, but it's quite strict.
XIONG: Who's dancing slow.
XIONG: Let's do it again.
XIONG: Five, six, seven, eight.
XIONG: Stop.
XIONG: Center position.
(Position Point)
XIONG: Okay?
XIONG: One more.
WUXUN: When taking class with XIONG,
WUXUN: he leads our practice
till the end.
(XIONG is online)
WUXUN: XIONG keeps checking
our dance moves.
XIONG: Wrong side!
(Incorrect Head Movement)
SHEN: GUANMING? Is it GUANMING?
WUXUN: GUANMING, what are you doing?
(Encounter with a Group Attack)
XIONG: Do it like this.
XIONG: Like this.
GUANMING: It's not the monkey jump move.
WUXUN: When teaching,
he looks super serious
WUXUN: unlike his usual self.
WUXUN: In daily life, he's like...
WUXUN: slow like a little sloth.
EARTH: He's genuinely gentle.
EARTH: Talking to him makes me
slightly sleepy.
EARTH: But, I feel that
EARTH: it's his character.
XIONG: Come on, take your positions.
(GET?)
SENA: Mhm!
XIONG: Okay.
XIONG: Good.
WUXUN: How do you understand him?
- WUXUN: How do you get what he means?
- XIONG: Use intuition.
WUXUN: He hasn't even opened his mouth.
WUXUN: Oh, okay.
SENA: Our team
SENA: has a rather bright style.
SENA: I'm very happy
and quite surprised too.
SENA: We're gradually getting closer.
SENA: I think we're doing great.
WUXUN: Yeah.
SENA: Okay.
- WUXUN: Let's go, bro. Yes!
- SENA: Ready to go.
- WUXUN: You're ready?
- SENA: Okay.
WUXUN: Okay, okay. He's a bit shy.
- WUXUN: Startling others.
- XIONG: Startling people completely.
WUXUN: I'm sorry.
SENA: It's like my team
SENA: has many introverts.
SENA: If I were to say,
SENA: their singing voices
tend to be soft.
WUXUN: So small.
(Right on Point)
(MORE POWERFUL)
WUXUN: More powerful.
(LESS TECHNIQUE)
SENA: Yeah.
SENA: Because he sings
better than dances,
SENA: he can project his voice
SENA: at a louder volume.
SENA: When I sang,
he taught me wholeheartedly.
WUXUN: Okay.
WUXUN: The voice...
- EARTH: Should be like...
- WUXUN: Yes, yes.
EARTH: WUXUN gives technical advice.
His approach is like
EARTH: more about voice projection,
EARTH: like someone screaming.
EARTH: I feel that
it's an interesting new technique.
XIONG: Okay, SHEN you enter here.
(My turn?)
WUXUN: Any dance moves here?
- XIONG: When he...
- SHEN: None.
- SHEN: After the verse ends like this.
- XIONG: Once he finishes singing, it's done.
XIONG: Right.
WUXUN: I think most verses
WUXUN: assigned to me up to here
seem slightly more than others.
WUXUN: I don't want it this way.
WUXUN: Actually,
our team's verse distribution
WUXUN: is fairly
WUXUN: equal. Peace.
WUXUN: Actually, I'm slightly concerned.
WUXUN: I feel SHEN
got too few singing parts.
WUXUN: Oh, this is yours.
XIONG: Yes, this is it.
SHEN: Then, he'll get even fewer parts.
WUXUN: No, I'm not complaining.
I already had previous parts.
XIONG: As long as he agrees.
WUXUN: I agree.
XIONG: I agree.
(Team Leader)
XIONG: You follow that.
SHEN: Hmm.
(Humbly Accept)
XIONG: Okay.
XIONG: SHEN is like a younger brother.
XIONG: How to say it?
He's still a tender-aged youth.
XIONG: Five, six, seven, eight.
(Don't do that!)
XIONG: You can't cover
your eyes like this.
SHEN: What should I do?
XIONG: Let me do it.
XIONG: Come here.
XIONG: Then, he had this cute moment.
(PEEPING)
SHEN: I got totally startled.
SHEN: I was assessing
the opponent's strength.
(Know Your Opponents)
XIONG: Tell me how you felt
after seeing it.
SHEN: I think
they're completely unreliable.
(Dares to ask, Dares to answer)
SHEN: Actually, XIONG just wants to win.
SHEN: So, I thought of using
beautiful dance elements
SHEN: to score more points,
SHEN: like the opening
dance move where...
SHEN: Initially, we agreed
to hold this position.
SHEN: Now it requires spinning too.
SHEN: And there's the sound
of pulling iron chains.
SHEN: Then, grab XIONG's hand up,
SHEN: make some movements.
WUXUN: SHEN is very interesting,
WUXUN: and he often comes up with
WUXUN: new ideas
(Dance Training)
WUXUN: that suddenly emerge.
WUXUN: And those are
usually amazing ideas.
XIONG: Okay.
(Dance Training)
XIONG: Perfect.
XIONG: The six of us work well together.
(Dance Training)
XIONG: Everyone values the team.
EARTH: Like genuine friends,
(Dance Training)
EARTH: almost like siblings I'd say.
(To Celebrate SENA's Birthday)
SENA: They came to celebrate my birthday.
SENA: I'm so happy.
SENA: I feel like our teamwork
has strengthened.
(Physical Training: Push-ups)
GUANMING: Fighting!
(Physical Training: Run in Place)
WUXUN: We'll make everyone see
WUXUN: how much we've improved.
WUXUN: And we'll make
all the audience's eyes
WUXUN: focus on Still Monster.
GOU YI: Wow!
THI-O: Still Monster, I think
it's a well-equipped performance
THI-O: in terms of visuals
and performance,
THI-O: as well as singing.
YUCHEN: Honestly, I didn't think
he was that handsome at first.
YUCHEN: It's just...
YUCHEN: Today when he appeared,
I even...
YUCHEN: I even had to look at him
with new eyes.
SUNNY: So, if the MVP, I think XIONG.
BAMBAM: Thank you so much,
Still Monster and Attention.
BAMBAM: You guys did a really great job.
BAMBAM: So, you know, we're gonna vote
for each team's MVP.
BAMBAM: Let's start with Attention.
BAMBAM: Before voting,
anything you wanna say to everyone?
NINJA: Thank you all so much for dedicating
your time to see our shows today.
NINJA: Today
NINJA: no matter who gets
the MVP for the show,
NINJA: you guys here is
the best gift for us. Thank you so much
BIANURA: Yes, yes.
BAMBAM: Next, please.
I wanna hear your voice so bad.
NINJA: Okay.
- NINJA: Okay, okay.
- BAMBAM: Hey, no, no, everybody.
BAMBAM: Can I just be biased
for like a minute?
BAMBAM: Enough.
BAMBAM: You go up, please.
HU YETAO: Okay.
HU YETAO: Hello, my name is HU YETAO.
HU YETAO: Do you like HU YETAO?
AUDIENCE: Yes.
HU YETAO: Thank you
and glad to meet everyone.
WHYLUCAS: My name is WHYLUCAS.
WHYLUCAS: Thank...
WHYLUCAS: Three.
WHYLUCAS: Please remember
to vote for me because...
WHYLUCAS: I don't want to
go back to Singapore. I want to go...
NINJA: Chatuchak.
WHYLUCAS: I wanna go Chatuchak.
Chatuchak, okay?
- AUDIENCE: Okay, okay.
- WHYLUCAS: Okay.
MYST: What's up, guys?
MYST: My name is MYST.
MYST: You can call me MYST.
I am number 4.
MYST: Love you, sisters and brothers.
BIANURA: What's up, friends?
BIANURA: 100% Thai.
BIANURA: It's me, BIANURA number...
BIANURA: Five five five... five
(*Thai's laughing resembles Number Five.)
BIANURA: Whatever you want to vote.
Vote us.
BIANURA: Thank you so much you guys.
BIANURA: I really enjoy it.
BIANURA: Thank you so much.
ALTON ANG: Hello everyone.
ALTON ANG: I'm ALTON ANG,
number five, six... number six.
BAMBAM: Number six, yes.
ALTON ANG: And I love
everyone very much.
BAMBAM: Alright.
BAMBAM: And now it's time for voting.
BAMBAM: Let's see who's gonna become
the MVP of Attention.
BAMBAM: Let's start voting.
BAMBAM: And the voting is ended.
BAMBAM: And... let's go
for the second team.
BAMBAM: Still Monster.
XIONG: Hello, my name is XIONG.
XIONG: XIONG means bear.
SHEN: Hello, my name
is SHEN, number two.
SHEN: Everyone, please vote for me.
SHEN: Love you all.
GUANMING: Hello, I am GUANMING.
GUANMING: Please vote for me.
AUDIENCE: Okay.
WUXUN: Hello everyone.
WUXUN: My name is WUXUN. I'm a rapper.
WUXUN: Please vote for WUXUN.
EARTH: Hello, my name is EARTH.
EARTH: Don't forget to vote for EARTH,
number five. Kenjana!
SENA: Hello.
SENA: Everyone, if you know more
about my charm,
SENA: please vote for me.
SENA: Thank you.
BAMBAM: You guys ready for voting, right?
BAMBAM: Then, if you are ready,
let's go.
BAMBAM: Make your best choice.
Number one, two, three, four, five, six.
BAMBAM: And the time is over.
BAMBAM: So, you know, we gonna see
who's gonna become the MVP.
BAMBAM: But before that,
I need to announce one thing.
BAMBAM: And in case you guys don't know.
BAMBAM: So, the past two winners
were A Class,
BAMBAM: so, if this time,
A Class is winning again.
BAMBAM: then the challenges
of B Class, C Class, and F Class
BAMBAM: is over!
BAMBAM: So, we count it as a lose.
BAMBAM: So, let's see if the center
of the A Class gonna win again or not.
BAMBAM: So, I hope you guys make
your right decision for this round voting,
BAMBAM: and we're gonna vote
as a team from now on.
BAMBAM: So, Still Monster and Attention,
BAMBAM: Let's see who's gonna become
the winner of the round three.
BAMBAM: The last vote for the group,
let's begin.
BAMBAM: Number one is Still Monster
and number two is Attention.
BAMBAM: So, make your right choice.
BAMBAM: Only one team
for the third round.
BAMBAM: And the voting is over.
BAMBAM: Let's go with YAYA.
BAMBAM: How do you feel after watching
these two shows?
YAYA: The Attention team.
YAYA: You guys were such a good team.
YAYA: There was so much charisma
on that stage.
YAYA: So, good job.
YAYA: You guys were really cute!
YAYA: MYST, you're so cute!
BAMBAM: Alright, thank you.
BAMBAM: XU MINGHAO (THE 8),
what do you think?
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): I might speak
a bit long, okay?
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): First of all,
I feel that the Still Monster team
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): should have chosen
a better song than this, and also...
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): To be honest,
earlier when I watched you all,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): I was very impressed
by XIONG and WUXUN.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): And I know that
you all have great talents.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): But,
today's performance made me feel that
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): your singing
and dancing have weakened.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): The only one
that impressed me was
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): SHEN. I feel that
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): in this song,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): what you expressed
was spot-on, very fitting for this song.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): But, I can feel that
you all gave your utmost effort.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Thank you
for this performance.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): As for Attention,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): I don't sense
the teamwork that it should have.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): It's like everyone
has their own strengths,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): but if we combine
everyone's strengths,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): I feel like
you're not a unified team.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): If you genuinely
intend to unite as a team,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): you need to think more
thoroughly and enhance your teamwork.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Keep going.
BAMBAM: And now
the results have arrived.
BAMBAM: The MVP of Attention team is...
BAMBAM: NINJA.
(SUPERB!!)
PLENGTHAI: NINJA.
BAMBAM: You deserve it.
NINJA: Honestly, I never imagined this.
NINJA: I didn't expect it at all,
like I said it could have been anyone.
NINJA: Today, everything has truly
exceeded my imagination.
BAMBAM: You really deserve this.
NINJA: Thank you.
BAMBAM: You catch my attention the most.
BAMBAM: Sorry, I'm biased, HU YETAO.
BAMBAM: But from that show,
I looked at you the most, bro.
BAMBAM: So...
BAMBAM: Do you have anything to say?
AUDIENCE: Well done. Well done.
(So proud of you)
NINJA: MVP shouldn't belong
to just me alone.
NINJA: Teamwork is extremely important.
NINJA: Thank you very much.
BAMBAM: Awesome.
BAMBAM: So, the MVP
of Still Monster is...
BAMBAM: SHEN, congratulations.
SHEN: Let me say something, actually,
SHEN: because truthfully,
I'm a very lazy person.
- TIA RAY: This kid...
- SHEN: It's nothing, I just want to rest.
SHEN: Actually, XIONG is the team leader
who united us all.
SHEN: Moreover, WUXUN has no dance
background at all.
SHEN: XIONG scheduled for us,
with daily self-practice hours.
SHEN: He also led our practices.
We've rehearsed countless times.
SHEN: To me, the most crucial aspect
of being a team is camaraderie.
SHEN: It's great. I want this MVP
to belong to all of us.
BAMBAM: That's a really good one.
Good job.
XIONG: Back then, I just didn't want...
XIONG: Honestly, I didn't want him
to say things like that.
XIONG: I feel that he thinks
he got MVP because of me.
XIONG: I'm genuinely happy for him.
No need for such remarks.
XIONG: So at that time, I...
XIONG: gave him a pat on the back.
XIONG: But he still...
XIONG: "I wanted to say."
XIONG: Just like that.
XIONG: It really moved me deeply
XIONG: that SHEN expressed
such feelings.
BAMBAM: And now let me announce
the winner of the round three.
BAMBAM: Still Monster and Attention.
BAMBAM: The winner...
BAMBAM: After the commercial!
BIANURA: YenYen.
BAMBAM: You're ready?
BAMBAM: The winner...
BAMBAM: Congratulations, Attention!
GOU YI: That's it!
GOU YI: Yes!
WHYLUCAS: Yeah, bro! We won, man!
WHYLUCAS: I'm so happy to say this.
WHYLUCAS: Like, this is like
the best of all.
WHYLUCAS: I danced so hard that
I accidentally did weird moves.
WHYLUCAS: And I felt so happy. Yeah!
NINJA: Thank you very, very much.
SHEN: I feel that our performance
was really good,
SHEN: but still not as good as
it should be.
SHEN: But, I think throughout rehearsals
until now, we've been very happy.
SHEN: I think it's good enough.
BAMBAM: Bye bye, HU YETAO.
NINJA: Thank you so much.
MVP doesn't matter to me.
NINJA: You guys, thank you.
We won today.
SHEN: I also hoped we'd win.
SHEN: But I feel we've gained a lot.
SHEN: We exercised daily.
SHEN: We were happy every day.
SHEN: I think we've achieved our goal.
- WUXUN: Yes.
- SHEN: I think it was worth it.
SHEN: Right? Being happy is enough.
SHEN: I think in our team,
XIONG always helps teammates
SHEN: to improve our performances.
SHEN: Actually, I think we did our best.
SHEN: The MVP belongs to everyone.
TRAINEES: Three, two, one.
TRAINEES: STEAL YOUR HEART!
STILL MONSTER!
BAMBAM: Please welcome Under The Moon Road
and Super to the stage.
TRAINEES: Wow.
BIANURA: SHOYA's face.
WUXUN: Black and white.
GUANMING: One team gives off
the vibe of a deity cult, while
- GUANMING: the other a demon cult.
- SHEN: TAMU.
BAMBAM: Introduce your team, please.
DORN: One, two, three.
- DORN: We are Super Team.
- TRAINEES: We are Super Team.
DORN: Feels like I turned
into SUN WUKONG.
TRAINEES: SUN WUKONG.
(FIGHTING!)
SHOYA: Hello everyone, we are
TRAINEES: The Moon.
PLENGTHAI: I want to say something
to Super team.
PLENGTHAI: Dear friend,
PLENGTHAI: you're just SUN WUKONG.
PLENGTHAI: Do you know
what this thing can do?
PLENGTHAI: One, two, three.
SHOYA: I'll break you into pieces.
DORN: Considering the outfits, we may
represent fire; you represent water.
DORN: But I wonder who will be hotter.
PLENGTHAI: Water puts out fires, buddy.
BAMBAM: You know what, this time
BAMBAM: let's not have them
say some before.
BAMBAM: We are mentors.
We're good enough.
BAMBAM: We trust our guts,
BAMBAM: you know, take a guess right away
from this out of what they have right now.
YAYA: Oh..., man.
It's really, very hard.
YAYA: It's too hard.
YAYA: Can they just decide
by rock-paper-scissors?
BAMBAM: Oh, let's do that then.
BAMBAM: I like it.
BAMBAM: Let's do rock-paper-scissors.
BAMBAM: And who loses, goes first.
BAMBAM: How about that?
BAMBAM: SHOYA, the leader?
BAMBAM: One, two, three.
BAMBAM: Only one time.
HU YETAO: You see it?
- BAMBAM: You know what.
- KOHI: Oh, my God, SHOYA. You can do it.
BAMBAM: Turn back, turn back,
turn back. You, turn back.
BAMBAM: When I say one, two, three,
do this, okay?
BAMBAM: One, two, three.
(We won!!)
TADALEE: Well done, DORN.
BAMBAM: Then, Under The Moon Road,
you guys go first.
BAMBAM: Let me hear from TIA RAY first.
BAMBAM: What do you think about them?
TIA RAY: I love them all.
TIA RAY: But I'll go for
UNDER THE MOON ROAD this time.
BAMBAM: XU MINGHAO (THE 8),
Who do you think...
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): I need to support
my own song, the latter one.
YAYA: What about you guys?
BAMBAM: I'll go with...
BAMBAM: Under The Moon Road
AUDIENCE: GOU YI
BAMBAM: Alright, YAYA.
YAYA: And I have to agree
with TIA RAY on this one.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Alright,
let's introduce yourselves.
KOHI: Hi guys. Our team's concept
is Moon Flower.
KOHI: And we have six characters.
KOHI: And first.
SHOYA: Hello, I am Golden Flower.
SHOYA: Please show
lots of love for SHOYA!
- BAMBAM: Got it.
- SHOYA: Thank you, I love you!
PLENGTHAI: I'm Wood Flower.
GOU YI: And,
GOU YI: I'm a Water Flower.
- AUDIENCE: KOHI!
- KOHI: Hi, guys,
KOHI: I'm...
KOHI: Sky Flower.
TZI XUAN: Hello everyone,
I'm Stone Flower.
WANXIN: I'm the last one, Wind Flower.
BAMBAM: Good luck!
KOHI: One, two, three!
TRAINEES: We are The Moon!
AUDIENCE: SHOYA!
YAO ZIHAO: Fighting!
HIKARU: Let's go, SHOYA!
(Fighting!)
DONGDONG: SHOYA!
SHOYA: I've sung songs
in both English and Japanese before,
SHOYA: so I want to try singing
in Thai, Chinese, or Korean.
(SHOYA Chooses a song)
SHOYA: With fewer options left,
SHOYA: I decided to choose this song.
(SHOYA Chose Under The Moon Road)
SHOYA: Naturally, both the song concept
SHOYA: and each dance move
felt right for me.
PLENGTHAI: Why did I choose this song?
PLENGTHAI: Honestly,
I wanted to choose Super,
PLENGTHAI: I'm usually with SUPER THAI.
PLENGTHAI: We're inseparable.
Basically, we're together all the time.
PLENGTHAI: This round is
a big self-challenge.
(DORN: Super)
(PLENGTHAI: Under The Moon Road)
(Friend = My Dear Enemy)
PLENGTHAI: DORN is my closest friend.
PLENGTHAI: It's tough having to compete
against my best friend.
(Do your best, my friend)
WANXIN: When I first heard this song,
WANXIN: originally, we all
came to this show
(WANXIN Go to Under The Moon Road)
WANXIN: to showcase our talents.
WANXIN: I declare this is my song.
(KOHI Go to Under The Moon Road)
KOHI: For GRAND AUDITION, I did Youngblood.
KOHI: For this stage, I chose this song
to show my sexier side.
(GOU YI Go to Under The Moon Road)
GOU YI: I love this song's mood and tone.
GOU YI: I chose SHOYA
right after I saw him.
GOU YI: I knew that teaming up with him,
1+1 will be better.
TZI XUAN: The same.
(Same reason as everyone else)
(FIRST PRACTICE DAY)
PLENGTHAI: I joined a group of six
who are from five different countries
PLENGTHAI: and I was the only Thai.
(Be not in one's right mind)
PLENGTHAI: I was stressed from the start.
PLENGTHAI: Did I make the right choice?
(You're wrong)
PLENGTHAI: Did we make the right choice?
PLENGTHAI: I've never worked
PLENGTHAI: with these five people.
(PLENGTHAI FIGHT!)
(Am I heavy?)
(No Problem)
(Very Light)
PLENGTHAI: The challenge of this song is
PLENGTHAI: its delicate gracefulness.
PLENGTHAI: If it is just
about the movements,
PLENGTHAI: I think it wouldn't be hard.
(Stiff)
PLENGTHAI: But some moves require flexibility.
PLENGTHAI: It's hard
because my body is so stiff.
PLENGTHAI: I've danced hip-hop
my whole life.
PLENGTHAI: So I've had to adjust a lot.
PLENGTHAI: Everyone has
their own strengths.
PLENGTHAI: Like this one is good at
dancing and visual interpretation.
PLENGTHAI: This one is good
at choreography.
PLENGTHAI: This one is good at singing.
PLENGTHAI: For practicing,
whoever's good at it will be the leader.
PLENGTHAI: That's why it is
a strength of our team.
SHOYA: First of all, since I was
assigned to be the main vocal center,
SHOYA: I'm shouldering
a great responsibility.
SHOYA: I need to be the role model
SHOYA: and also lead everyone.
SHOYA: Yes.
SHOYA: Exactly.
SHOYA: Seven, eight.
SHOYA: One, two. three.
SHOYA: Even everyone thinks
they're not good at dancing.
SHOYA: They still said
they will strictly practice.
SHOYA: There are people
with strong determination
SHOYA: and so enthusiastic
than I imagined.
SHOYA: For the original choreography
of this song,
SHOYA: I do like it.
SHOYA: But if we do that,
we'd just be a cover dance team.
SHOYA: I want to create an impression.
SHOYA: So I tried modifying
some original moves.
SHOYA: Better.
PLENGTHAI: SHOYA is amazing.
PLENGTHAI: I'll call SHOYA teacher.
PLENGTHAI: I feel like everyone
really respects him.
PLENGTHAI: He is admirable.
SHOYA: For dancing,
I collaborated with GOU YI a lot.
GOU YI: And go.
GOU YI: Yes.
GOU YI: You can.
GOU YI: You do this.
GOU YI: We do this.
GOU YI: No.
GOU YI: We might change something a bit
GOU YI: like the flow of the moves
GOU YI: and breathing rhythm.
GOU YI: Like tightening
any loose screws.
- SHOYA: Play the music.
- GOU YI: Okay.
GOU YI: You're a dancer.
KOHI: Dancer...
(Being an idol is not easy.)
(Build Relationships)
(The dance position is for teaching dance)
SHOYA: For dancing positions...
SHOYA: KOHI also stands out
in visual effects.
(KOHI also stands out in visual effects)
SHOYA: He always come up with ideas.
KOHI: Do this.
(Speak Korean)
KOHI: This part... and then...
(I agree)
STAFF: How do you usually discuss ideas?
(Chinese to English)
(Proudly present "A master of Language Translation")
(Korean to English)
TZI XUAN: Thank you.
TZI XUAN: I'm hungry.
(THAI)
PLENGTHAI: TZI XUAN
speaks six languages.
PLENGTHAI: He can translate everything.
(I am a TRANSLATION ROBOT)
TZI XUAN: I would say I take as their translator machine.
KOHI: Because your...
KOHI: I saw everything
during the level test.
(TRANSLATOR)
KOHI: But...
(Speak Korean)
KOHI: It's not about making it powerful,
KOHI: but you need to make it gorgeous.
(Don't stop)
KOHI: So...but the full voice will...
(Stop first,
and wait for the translation)
(TRANSLATOR)
TZI XUAN: He said we should practice
TZI XUAN: like mixed voice.
(MIX VOICE is hard to sing,
need to find a teacher)
(Teacher KOHI)
(That's right my friend)
KOHI: Right. Perfect.
(Perfect)
KOHI: You did it perfectly.
PLENGTHAI: KOHI is the real vocal coach.
KOHI: I've learned singing
KOHI: for seven straight years.
KOHI: During my training,
the most important thing
KOHI: is to have a perfect foundation.
KOHI: Once we have it,
KOHI: then we can go on
to the next level.
GOU YI: It has to be fast,
it's a rapping.
GOU YI: Actually when choosing the song,
I didn't even know how fast it was.
GOU YI: I couldn't catch the lyrics.
GOU YI: Only after seeing the lyrics,
I just realized that
GOU YI: wow, it is a lot and so fast.
GOU YI: It is much harder
than the THEME SONG.
KOHI: This is a mixed voice.
(This is Mix Voice)
KOHI: Perfect.
(Very strict)
KOHI: This feeling.
(Very good)
KOHI: Much better. Really.
SHOYA: For the vocal basic,
SHOYA: everyone is trying
to master mixed voice.
SHOYA: KOHI is the main instructor.
SHOYA: Because it's a Chinese song,
SHOYA: so we need WANXIN's help.
WANXIN: I think I might not dance well.
WANXIN: And the one thing
I might do well
WANXIN: is that this song is in Chinese.
WANXIN: I think
I do speak good Mandarin.
WANXIN: So this is the only thing that
I can help the team.
WANXIN: Help them better
their pronunciations.
WANXIN: Yes.
KOHI: Now I feel it lacks power.
KOHI: More power.
KOHI: But some Chinese pronunciations
doesn't exist in Korean.
KOHI: Like shi, chi, ru.
KOHI: I feel like,
these make it even harder for me.
PLENGTHAI: From the first day
PLENGTHAI: until today,
PLENGTHAI: we genuinely improve
and we can see the differences.
PLENGTHAI: What I've been worried about
PLENGTHAI: has completely
exceeded my expectations.
PLENGTHAI: I'm so lucky
to be part of this team.
SHOYA: Right now...
(1 DAY BEFORE SHOW)
SHOYA: At least, really, I'm so confident.
SHOYA: We finally practice singing
and dancing.
SHOYA: 120%.
(DAY 1)
SHOYA: That team probably
SHOYA: That team probably has
(Second day)
(DAY 2)
SHOYA: a powerful dancing.
(DAY 3)
(DAY 4)
SHOYA: a powerful dancing.
(DAY 5)
(DAY 6)
SHOYA: So with the contrast style,
(DAY 7)
(DAY 8)
SHOYA: So with the contrast style,
SHOYA: we must impress them instantly.
(DAY 9)
(DAY 10)
SHOYA: we must impress them instantly.
SHOYA: I think it would be great
if we can do it.
NINJA: Oh my god.
BAMBAM: I love it.
TIA RAY: Choreography is so good.
BAMBAM: Yeah, it's so good.
(Oh my God)
BAMBAM: Oh my God.
- BAMBAM: Good job.
- TIA RAY: Love it. Love it.
BAMBAM: Love it.
(SUGOI!)
SMART: You nailed it.
B: You nailed it.
PRAY: SHOYA, oh my God.
PRAY: SHOYA...
PRAY: He's truly amazing.
PRAY: His subtle emotional expressions.
PRAY: I need to ask him
PRAY: for a lot of advice about that
PRAY: and will need a lot of practice.
He's truly amazing.
XIN: I think the show is so good.
XIN: The first part
is what GOU YI specialized in,
XIN: relaxed movements.
XIN: Then in the latter half, SHOYA
XIN: gave a fierce
and powerful impression.
(RESPECT!)
XIN: Their show is really great.
BAMBAM: Thank you so much.
- BAMBAM: Under The Moon Road.
- SHOYA: Thank you.
BAMBAM: Yes.
BAMBAM: Alright, I think it's gonna be
a lot of pressure for the SUPER team.
PEANUT: After seeing today's
Under The Moon Road,
PEANUT: I feel quite stressed.
PEANUT: Because I don't want to lose.
TADALEE: At the beginning,
I never felt that
TADALEE: we should compete fiercely
TADALEE: or fight to the death.
TADALEE: After all, as we are
two exceptionally strong teams.
TADALEE: We just want to make it
exciting for AUDIENCE.
DORN: Hello, I'm DORN.
DORN: I'm SUN WUKONG.
YAO ZIHAO: I, SUN WUKONG, have arrived.
DORN: I, SUN WUKONG, have arrived.
YAO ZIHAO: Hello everyone.
I'm from China.
YAO ZIHAO: I'm the little pony
YAO ZIHAO.
YAO ZIHAO: This handsome guy
has arrived to Thailand.
YAO ZIHAO: Hello. My name is YAO ZIHAO.
YAO ZIHAO: Love you, mwah mwah.
YAO ZIHAO: In the SUPER team...
YAO ZIHAO: Actually,
I'm not the Bull Demon King.
YAO ZIHAO: But I'm Nezha.
YAO ZIHAO: My life depends on myself,
not on fate
YAO ZIHAO: Whether I'm a demon
or an immortal, it's up to me.
(So cute!)
TADALEE: Master, don't worry.
Sha Wujing is here.
TADALEE: Hello, I'm TADALEE.
TADALEE: I'm Sha Wujing from SUPER team.
TADALEE: Sha Wujing is kind-hearted
TADALEE: and takes good care of others.
TADALEE: Just like how I'll take
a good care of your heart.
PEANUT: Hello.
PEANUT: Hello everyone, I'm PEANUT.
PEANUT: I'm the third son
of the Dragon God.
PEANUT: No need to make wishes, because
PEANUT: all your wishes
are already here.
JACKSON: Hello everyone,
I'm the real Bull Demon King.
JACKSON: I'm JACKSON from SUPER team.
JACKSON: I am the great one
who brings balance to heaven.
JACKSON: Don't laugh.
JACKSON: Who brings peace to heaven.
RICKY: Hello, I'm RICKY.
RICKY: I'm Xuanzang Monk in SUPER team.
(HELP ME!)
DORN: Master, stop chanting.
HU YETAO: That's very convincing acting.
HU YETAO: Even the voice
matches perfectly.
BAMBAM: Can't wait to see the stage.
So...
BAMBAM: Good luck.
And this stage is yours.
TADALEE: One, two, three.
TRAINEES: SUPER team.
SHOYA: Fighting.
DORN: I feel like
we didn't have much pressure on us.
DORN: This will be the last time
DORN: that we can dance
this song together.
DORN: Just give our all
in this performance,
DORN: making the AUDIENCE
enjoy our show, that's enough.
YAO ZIHAO: At first, I didn't
choose the team because of the song.
YAO ZIHAO: But I chose it
because of DORN.
(Member Grouping)
JEFF: YAO ZIHAO, choose first.
(YAO ZIHAO chooses DORN)
NINJA: What.
NINJA: With who? DORN?
KK: Yeah.
KK: Surprise.
YAO ZIHAO: We are number one.
YAO ZIHAO: Everyone might think
YAO ZIHAO isn't fit to be
YAO ZIHAO: center of dancing.
YAO ZIHAO: They probably think
DORN is more suitable.
YAO ZIHAO: I don't care though.
YAO ZIHAO: On the contrary, I prefer
not being the center.
OMAR: Among all these 10 songs, I think
OMAR: SUPER team
has the most talented skills.
OMAR: With YAO ZIHAO in the team,
OMAR: plus many talented members,
OMAR: it's the show
we've been anticipating.
DORN: TADALEE, PEANUT, JACKSON,
RICKY, YAO ZIHAO.
DORN: I don't know what would happen.
DORN: I don't know.
(How long does the SUPER team
get along?)
(The SUPER THAI Teaching Group)
(DANCE TEACHER teaching RICKY)
(The SUPER THAI team is self-teaching)
(DANCE TEACHER teaching RICKY) (The NI LIU ER SHANG Teaching Group)
DORN: Like everyone is doing
what they're good at.
(Only practicing, but not communicating)
(The SUPER THAI Teaching Group)
DORN: We've got to do something together
DORN: and meet up every day.
DORN: I also have to focus on
what I'm doing.
DORN: YAO ZIHAO also focus on
what he needs to do.
(YAO ZIHAO is practicing alone
with JACKSON)
(Avoid eye contact)
JACKSON: The atmosphere is weird.
JACKSON: Maybe because we are divided
into two subgroups.
JACKSON: They stay in their parts,
and we stay in ours.
JACKSON: We've been practicing like this
for about a week.
JACKSON: But during self-practice day,
JACKSON: YAO ZIHAO went for makeup or interview,
so he didn't come and practice with us.
(Practice dance break)
JACKSON: So we got to practice
the long dance break together.
(Shortness of Breath)
JACKSON: After finishing the dance,
JACKSON: we were so exhausted.
(This move is exhausting)
TADALEE: When it comes to SAY part..
TADALEE: it is not tired.
TADALEE: But when it comes to...
TADALEE: I LOVE... Oh, wow.
JACKSON: Then they suggested
trying to shorten it
JACKSON: like cut out a section.
(Change Dance Break
Day 2)
(Can't keep up with the dance)
(Second attempt)
(Can't keep up with the dance x2)
(PASSIVE)
(Third Attempt)
(Can't keep up with the dance x3)
(OVERWHELMED)
YAO ZIHAO: Can we listen
to the song again?
DORN: Can we listen to the song again?
YAO ZIHAO: Play the latest version,
the second one.
STAFF: This one?
TADALEE: Wait. Okay. I think right now
we're wasting time.
TADALEE: Let's vote.
JACKSON: Let's have a vote.
TADALEE: No dance break.
JACKSON: Keep the dance break or...
YAO ZIHAO: This isn't a dance break.
YAO ZIHAO: It's still a vocal section.
TADALEE: I know, but...
TADALEE: Just the dance break
that we called.
TADALEE: With this part, ENERGY part,
shall we keep it.
TADALEE: Let's vote.
JACKSON: Let's vote.
TADALEE: Because we wasted
like 20 minutes.
JACKSON: Keep or remove the ENERGY part?
DORN: Has RICKY heard it yet?
(RICKY didn't come to training due to MV recording)
TADALEE: RICKY wants that part.
(RICKY agrees with TADALEE's change)
TADALEE: He told me in the car.
TADALEE: He said
(SILENCE)
TADALEE: He prefers the first version
with the ENERGY singing part.
DORN: Yes. RICKY wants that...
TADALEE: RICKY wants to keep it.
TADALEE: Let's vote.
TADALEE: Let's not waste the time.
JACKSON: About this dance break part,
JACKSON: only five people
are here to vote.
JACKSON: RICKY wasn't here.
But his close friend said
JACKSON: RICKY tole him in the car
that he likes this one.
JACKSON: He meant we could count RICKY
as having voted.
JACKSON: RICKY agrees.
JACKSON: Four versus two.
JACKSON: And it ended like that.
They decided to do it that way.
(Change Dance Break: Day 3)
DANCE TEACHER: Now here is the problem.
You've added the dance break.
DANCE TEACHER: In the last part,
do we have
DANCE TEACHER: this move...
DANCE TEACHER: this move?
PEANUT: Should we start over?
DANCE TEACHER: Do we have it?
- DORN: No.
- DANCE TEACHER: You guys... No, right?
DANCE TEACHER: Then here is the problem.
DANCE TEACHER: If we don't have it,
DANCE TEACHER: YAO ZIHAO's parts
might be reduced.
(YAO ZIHAO's parts have been reduced)
DANCE TEACHER: In that case, that position
DANCE TEACHER: that YAO ZIHAO dances...
DANCE TEACHER: Therefore,
you guys need to make a decision.
(Proactive Communication)
DORN: We had discussed about
the dance break for a long time.
DORN: Now five of us
already have our own scene.
DORN: We have our own solo parts,
DORN: but YAO ZIHAO doesn't.
DORN: So I tried to make it fair
for everyone.
DORN: Everyone should have
their own part and be outstanding.
DORN: So I decided to
DORN: let YAO ZIHAO dance this.
I tried to make it look good.
DORN: I never thought that because I'm
the center, everyone should listen to me
DORN: and everyone should follow me.
DORN: I don't have that thought
in my head.
DORN: Being center
is just being selected.
DORN: But whether it's good or not,
it depends on our teamwork.
DORN: As I said, at the end,
we go as a team.
DORN: We need to break down barriers.
DORN: Because we still can't get along,
DORN: we are still not a "team'".
DORN: I feel like we should
bring in a dance break.
DORN: In the "I love my team" part...
DORN: Because first, I'm concerned about
DORN: that RICKY and JACKSON
rarely attend practice
DORN: and about rehearsals.
DORN: It makes...
DORN: The others can't keep up.
DORN: YAO ZIHAO,
what do you think about...
DORN: Hey, this part is funny.
DORN: What do you think about the show
DORN: if we add a dance break
DORN: to replace the "I love my team
I love my partner" part?
YAO ZIHAO: Right,
because this is a survival show.
YAO ZIHAO: When I joined this team,
YAO ZIHAO: I did want to compete.
YAO ZIHAO: It's like there is a wall
separating us.
YAO ZIHAO: So it leads us to think that
the others are not considering the team
YAO ZIHAO: but rather focusing on
personal interests.
DORN: Actually, I really want to show
our standpoint that
DORN: we've never been
prejudiced against you.
DORN: We genuinely
tried to reach out to you.
DORN: But due to language barriers
DORN: and some cultural differences,
DORN: sometime we didn't know
how to approach you
DORN: or how to communicate properly
DORN: to make you feel comfortable.
YAO ZIHAO: Yeah, I know.
YAO ZIHAO: So I apologize
for previous matters
YAO ZIHAO: that made you uncomfortable.
YAO ZIHAO: I'm sorry.
(All misunderstandings
will eventually be resolved)
YAO ZIHAO: At first, maybe because
we spoke different languages.
YAO ZIHAO: So we couldn't
communicate well.
YAO ZIHAO: But now...
YAO ZIHAO: I think I'll work hard on
learning English with DORN.
YAO ZIHAO: So we can communicate.
DORN: I want to talk to you.
DORN: But I don't know...
- DORN: What's the word...
- PEANUT / TADALEE: WORD (word)
(English communication)
DORN: English word.
YAO ZIHAO: I don't know either.
STAFF: Then how do you guys communicate?
YAO ZIHAO: We use gestures.
YAO ZIHAO: This and DORN...
YAO ZIHAO: DORN... back... PEANUT...
TADALEE: I was like, what's that.
TADALEE: Then DORN would be like
"guys, it's this one".
(Blah Blah)
TADALEE: Translating and then...
TADALEE: How did you know?
YAO ZIHAO: Just looking into your eyes,
and I knew it.
(Tacit Agreement)
DORN: After we opened up to each other,
DORN: I started seeing... pink color.
DORN: It's becoming rainbow-colored.
DORN: Because it's starting
to become rainbow-ish,
DORN: I feel like our colors
are starting to change.
(DORN's leg abnormalities)
- YAO ZIHAO: Okay?
- STAFF: Does it hurt?
- DORN: Yes, Yes.
PEANUT: Stretch your legs first.
TADALEE: Are You okay?
(Leg Swelling)
- TADALEE: Tired?
- PEANUT: DORN, are you okay?
PEANUT: Actually, I noticed that
DORN has some injuries
PEANUT: since the Runaway Baby show.
(Backstage of the first stage)
DORN: I don't want to distract anyone.
DORN: I don't want them to see I'm hurt
then it might be like...
DORN: So I just go! If you go, I go.
DORN: But when I finished rehearsal,
DORN: I sat down,
(Iced Drinks)
PEANUT: Oh YenYen.
DORN: Thank you.
(Ice Compress)
YAO ZIHAO: Okay?
(Think)
(You need the best!)
(Heavy) -PEANUT: Just a moment.
-DORN: So quick.
(FOOT)
YAO ZIHAO: Put your foot here.
TADALEE: Wait, wait.
(Yeah Yeah Yeah)
YAO ZIHAO: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
DORN: I was surprised
that foreign friends cared about me.
DORN: Foreign friends suddenly
brought an ice bucket for me.
DORN: They ran to grab it for me.
DORN: Am I happy to see that? Yes.
But I also feel bad for them.
DORN: My sense of obligation
outweighs my happiness.
(Happy Face)
DORN: I'm touched they cared about me.
JACKSON: Don't forget the shoes.
TADALEE: Everyone is getting along.
TADALEE: Teamwork
isn't just practicing together.
TADALEE: We must live our lives together
not just in the practice room.
TADALEE: To develop certain chemistry
that makes us become unity.
JACKSON: Look at this photo.
DORN: I feel that
DORN: after we started practicing
together every day,
DORN: we started to get along.
YAO ZIHAO: When everyone
YAO ZIHAO: became friends,
YAO ZIHAO: I think every moment,
every second is joyful.
DORN: I think when everyone
supports each other...
DORN: Humans can't live alone.
DORN: Everyone lifts each other up.
DORN: I really hope that
DORN: our performance
will make SEVENTEEN fans
DORN: or even XU MINGHAO (THE 8)
DORN: proud of all six of us.
(Rehearsal day)
(FROWN)
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Okay.
YAO ZIHAO: Among all teams,
YAO ZIHAO: our SUPER will definitely
be much-anticipated.
YAO ZIHAO: First from the AUDIENCE.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Make your show
better than this.
(Temporary Adjustment Action)
YAO ZIHAO: Since SUPER has become
YAO ZIHAO: much-anticipated,
YAO ZIHAO: we can't perform poorly.
YAO ZIHAO: Even if we only have one day,
we must give our all.
(What kind of stage
will they be presenting?)
THI-O: Today SUPER showed amazingly.
THI-O: Very powerful and very impact,
for me at least.
THI-O: And very handsome.
JELLY: After a 360-degree somersault,
he continued singing.
JELLY: That was startling.
TIAN QI: Did somersault then singing.
So funny.
TIAN QI: That was so funny.
TIAN QI: Came down and started singing.
BAMBAM: So...
BAMBAM: Original...
BAMBAM: Just a bit, let's start
one, two, three.
(Wow)
BAMBAM: We have to find our MVP
for each team.
BAMBAM: Let's start with SUPER team.
DORN: I'm DORN, number one.
DORN: Please take care of me,
and also support the monkey behind me.
YAO ZIHAO: Hey, yo!
YAO ZIHAO: I'm two.
YAO ZIHAO: Please vote for me,
number two.
TADALEE: Hello everyone, I'm TADALEE.
TADALEE: I hope you choose
whoever you like,
TADALEE: but don't forget
to pick me, okay?
TADALEE: Thank you. Number three.
PEANUT: Hello again, I'm PEANUT.
PEANUT: I hope that my performance
PEANUT: could make you guys
know me better.
PEANUT: And please vote to support me.
PEANUT: Thank you so much.
JACKSON: Hello, I'm JACKSON.
JACKSON: My name is JACKSON.
JACKSON: In Thai, I got a name
called "Jiab".
YAYA: Jiab.
- JACKSON: Number five.
- BAMBAM: Number five
RICKY: Hello, I'm RICKY, number six.
BAMBAM: Alright, this is SUPER team.
BAMBAM: Let's get started. Let's vote.
BAMBAM: Alright, I think that's it.
BAMBAM: Let's move on to
Under The Moon Road.
BAMBAM: SHOYA, start from you.
SHOYA: Hello.
SHOYA: Thank you.
SHOYA: I'm the center and number one,
SHOYA: SHOYA.
PLENGTHAI: Hello everyone,
I'm PLENGTHAI from Thailand.
PLENGTHAI: I am number two.
PLENGTHAI: Number two.
PLENGTHAI: Please support me.
BAMBAM: Really cute.
GOU YI: Hello, I'm GOU YI.
GOU YI: Okay.
GOU YI: Vote for me.
By the way, I'm number three.
KOHI: Hi, everybody.
KOHI: Hello, my name is KOHI.
KOHI: I'm number four.
KOHI: Thank you.
TZI XUAN: Hello, I'm TZI XUAN.
TZI XUAN: Hello everyone,
I'm number five, TZI XUAN.
TZI XUAN: Don't forget to vote for me.
WANXIN: Okay. I'm the last one.
WANXIN: Just like what I said,
WANXIN: my name is WANXIN,
you can also call me XINXIN.
WANXIN: Please vote for me. Thank you.
WANXIN: Love you, mwah mwah.
BAMBAM: Alright. So let's start voting
for Under The Moon Road.
BAMBAM: You guys ready?
BAMBAM: Alright, then let's do it.
BAMBAM: Alright, and we done.
BAMBAM: These are the
strongest two teams so far.
BAMBAM: I think it's gonna be
really hard for you guys.
BAMBAM: I thinks it's really hard
for the mentors too. Right?
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Yes. Both teams
are equally talented.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Their performance
skills are exceptionally strong.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): This team's
performance flows smoothly like water.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Graceful
and powerful, perfectly blended.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Truly impressive.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): While this team
is like a fire.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Fierce and powerful.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): So, I think
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): this depends on
your preferences.
BAMBAM: You're right.
BAMBAM: So SUPER Team
or Under The Moon Road.
BAMBAM: Let's see
who will be the winner.
BAMBAM: The voting begins now.
BAMBAM: SUPER team is number one.
BAMBAM: And Under The Moon Road
is number two.
NINJA: All of the performances...
NINJA: I think Under The Moon Road
is better.
- SUNNY: SUPER.
- THI-O: Alright.
BAMBAM: Alright, so we have to wait
for the result.
BAMBAM: Just a minute.
YAYA: You know. I feel like you guys
came with so much confidence.
YAYA: And that was a good choice of song
for all of you.
YAYA: But I kinda feel like
YAYA: there were some parts where
it was a little bit confusing to watch.
YAYA: Whereas you guys...
YAYA: You were so smooth.
YAYA: Like, literally, you were flowing.
YAYA: And it was much more
than I expected.
BAMBAM: Oh, my God.
BAMBAM: XU MINGHAO (THE 8),
BAMBAM: what do you think?
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): I feel that
the performance
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): was better
than the rehearsal.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): But personally
I still feel that in some parts,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): you putted
too much force.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): So I think
controlling your force
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): is one of the skills
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): you need to
gradually practice.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): It's not that the song
is ferocious so you have to dance harder.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Instead, you should
know how to control your force,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): so your performance
will be more appealing to the AUDIENCE.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Keep going.
BAMBAM: And the MVP of the SUPER team.
BAMBAM: Everybody, turn around
and check yourself.
BAMBAM: The MVP of the SUPER team
BAMBAM: is
- LYU: TADALEE.
- KEVIN: DORN.
NINJA: Too hard.
BAMBAM: DORN.
KEVIN: I love my team.
TADALEE: So awesome.
- YAO ZIHAO: Awesome.
- TADALEE: Awesome.
SUNNY: I see DORN,
he really captured the camera.
SUNNY: And his facial expression
SUNNY: and all of the vibe...
SUNNY: He get it.
So really fire the stage.
DORN: Thank you for voting me as an MVP.
DORN: Many people think
the center must be the leader.
DORN: But actually,
I'm not a good leader.
DORN: I'm more of a good follower.
BAMBAM: And the MVP
for Under The Moon Road.
BAMBAM: Turn around.
BAMBAM: Under The Moon Road MVP
BAMBAM: only got one point
from each other.
HIKARI: First and second place
differ by just one point.
BAMBAM: So it was really hard.
BAMBAM: But let's see
who's gonna be the MVP.
DONGDONG: SHOYA.
KEVIN: SHOYA is good,
but I support WANXIN.
BAMBAM: The MVP is...
(KOHI)
TZI XUAN: Congratulations.
WHYLUCAS: I thought The MVP of Under The Moon Road
should be PLENGTHAI or SHOYA.
WHYLUCAS: I'm a bit surprised
it was KOHI.
WHYLUCAS: But honestly, I also feel that
WHYLUCAS: KOHI's seating part
was really impressive.
KOHI: Actually I'm very lucky
KOHI: to be today's MVP,
but to be completely honest,
KOHI: our team barely slept at all.
KOHI: So many things happened.
KOHI: I think all of us together
earned this MVP.
KOHI: Thank you.
BAMBAM: And the last, for the battle.
TRAINEES: SHOYA.
BAMBAM: You know what.
BAMBAM: This is so hard.
BAMBAM: The point is like
really similar.
BAMBAM: So everyone, turn around.
BAMBAM: Everyone, turn around.
BAMBAM: And
BAMBAM: the winner...
BAMBAM: Please put it up on the screen.
JUNHAN: Oh my god. So hard.
PEAT: It's so hard.
Download WeTV
and register to become a member.
Then press "CHUANG ASIA S2" channel page
and click "Vote Now"
to vote for your favorite trainees.
WeTV members
will get the vote eligible every day.
You can vote for seven trainees each day
with the limit of one trainees
per ten votes only.
And purchase WeTV VIP
on CHUANG ASIA S2 page,
will get 20 votes per trainee daily.
To get more voting privileges,
click "Send Gifts"
or purchase CHUANG ASIA S2 VIP gift card
to get extra votes.
This round,
you can also get extra free votes
from various activities on WeTV,
such as continuous daily voting
and watching advertisements.
This round of voting starts
from February 2nd, 2025 at 4:50 PM
until February 28th, 2025 at 10:00 AM.
The first elimination
will be only 35 of 60 trainees.
Come and vote
for your favorite trainees.
Who's going to debut
will be solely determined by your vote.
Click "Send Love Rankings".
And "Send Love" to your favorite trainees.
Give more benefits for them now.