[YenYen, the top choice for cooling down
and relieving spiciness.]
[YUMYUM SOOD-DED with spicy triple cheese.]
Download WeTV
and register to become a member.
Then press "CHUANG ASIA S2" channel page
and click "Vote Now"
to vote for your favorite trainees.
WeTV members
will get the vote eligible every day.
You can vote for seven trainees each day
with the limit of one trainee
per ten votes only.
And purchase WeTV VIP
on CHUANG ASIA S2 page,
you will get 20 votes per trainee daily.
To get more voting privileges,
click "Send gifts"
or purchase CHUANG ASIA S2 VIP gift card
to get extra votes.
This round,
you can also get extra free votes
from various activities on WeTV,
such as continuous daily voting
and watching advertisements.
This round of voting starts
from February 2nd, 2025 at 4:50 PM
until February 28th, 2025 at 10:00 AM.
The first elimination
will be only 35 of 60 trainees.
Come and vote
for your favorite trainees.
Who's going to debut
will be solely determined by your vote.
BAMBAM: Welcome to CHUANG ASIA S2
BAMBAM: We're looking for
the international boy group.
BAMBAM: That boy group
has to be perfect.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): I have been waiting
XU MINGHAO:
for my ideal A to appear.
TRAINEES: Getting an A is so hard.
TRAINEES: SUPER THAI.
BAMBAM: This is what we're looking for.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Your singing,
dancing, acting,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): all are
really excellent.
BAMBAM: Just come and get it.
THI-O: Oh, my God.
TIA RAY: I can feel the team's spirit.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Finally,
we can see the picture of a boy group.
BAMBAM: OMAR, everyone?
TRAINEES: The one who has
already been controversial.
TIAN QI: Actually, he's not that bad.
TIAN QI: But if we talk about strengths,
TIAN QI: nothing stands out.
BAMBAM: B.
BAMBAM: A.
PLENGTHAI: A?
HIKARI: It's not like he got it
with any special technique.
HIKARI: I believe it's
due to his idol-like quality.
KK: If this is the group
that's going to debut,
KK: I think it's very necessary
KK: to have someone like OMAR.
TIA RAY: Actually, we want to give you
an A, but I think that
TIA RAY: you still have
plenty of time to improve.
TIA RAY: But everyone thinks that
your image
TIA RAY: really fits the boy group.
TIA RAY: Plus, you have charisma.
TIA RAY: I hope you won't waste this.
TIA RAY: I hope that in the days ahead,
TIA RAY: you will make an effort
TIA RAY: more than the others
TIA RAY: to prove that we didn't choose
the wrong person.
TIA RAY: Okay?
- OMAR: Thank you, Mentor.
- TIA RAY: Keep going, keep going.
OMAR: What I want to say is
OMAR: I want to thank my mother.
TIA RAY: Thank your mother, right?
OMAR: Thank you, Mom for giving me
the opportunity to stand here.
OMAR: Really thank my mom and dad
OMAR: for supporting me,
allowing me to do what I want.
OMAR: And really thank my teammates.
OMAR: They are all very good.
OMAR: Being with them makes me feel that
OMAR: just practicing together
makes me happy.
OMAR: And thank you, Mentor...
TIA RAY: Thank you.
Don't forget to thank yourself too.
TIA RAY: Thank yourself
for choosing this path.
TIA RAY: Hope you
won't disappoint yourself.
TIA RAY: Keep going!
- TIA RAY: Okay?
- OMAR: Thank you.
JINGYU: Amazing!
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): All of us Mentors
think that
XU MINGHAO:
your external appearance is
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): quite outstanding.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): For your singing
and dancing,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): there isn't
any part that's bad.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): So, we think that
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): we should
give you an A.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Hope in the future,
you will improve in other areas.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Bring out
your own charm
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): more.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): I believe
that you'll become
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): an excellent idol.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Keep going!
OMAR: I will try my best.
Thank you, Mentor.
TIA RAY: To me,
he really seems like a rising star.
TIA RAY: He possesses the qualities
and conditions of being an idol.
TIA RAY: If I were a young girl
and saw him,
TIA RAY: my heart would race for sure.
Do you understand?
ARIEL LIN: We quite prioritize
the audience.
ARIEL LIN: The audience doesn't judge
based solely on appearance.
ARIEL LIN: He must have a character and
charm that rouses people to learn more,
ARIEL LIN: want to get closer to him,
or even want to continue following him.
OMAR: Honestly speaking,
OMAR: after getting an A,
OMAR: I felt
OMAR: pressured.
OMAR: I need to try harder
OMAR: to be worthy of being in Class A.
GOU YI: OMAR.
TRAINEES: Keep going!
- TRAINEES: Yay, you got an A.
- TRAINEES: Keep going!
TRAINEES: Yay, you got an A.
BAMBAM: Please welcome the next team.
BAMBAM: 4INLOVE
TRAINEES: HU YETAO.
ARIEL LIN: I can't tell at all.
YAYA: Beautiful.
JACKSON: Even without glasses,
I still see that he's beautiful.
BAMBAM: Introduce yourself, please.
HU YETAO: Okay.
HU YETAO: Three, two, one.
TRAINEES: Hello everyone.
TRAINEES: We are 4INLOVE.
LU JUNXI: I'm in Team 4INLOVE
LU JUNXI: as a chef who needs
a lot of nutrients, LU JUNXI.
LU JUNXI: Because now
I'm like plain soup
LU JUNXI: waiting to be seasoned
into various flavors.
GOU YI: Hello everyone.
I'm in Team 4INLOVE
GOU YI: as a choreographer who
has worked with many artists and idols.
GOU YI: I'm GOU YI.
SMART: Hi everyone. Hello.
SMART: I'm SMART.
SMART: If anyone likes spiciness,
SMART: get ready to see us
on this stage.
SMART: SMART is preparing to
SMART: sprinkle some chili
on this stage now.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Spicy Thai boy.
HU YETAO: Hello everyone, I'm HU YETAO.
HU YETAO: I'm a makeup artist
in Team 4INLOVE.
TIA RAY: A makeup artist?
HU YETAO: Last time, the makeup artists
were very busy.
HU YETAO: That day, I did makeup
for 5 trainees.
HU YETAO: This time, let's see how many
trainees I can do makeup for.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Very exciting.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Then let's start
the performance.
YAO ZIHAO: TAO TAO.
TRAINEES: HU YETAO, I'm very excited
about them.
TRAINEES: I feel like their style
must be different.
DAVID: Keep going.
GORDON: I'm going to stand
and listen to this song.
TRAINEES: Very cool.
TRAINEES: TAO!
TADALEE: The other groups
don't really have this style.
TADALEE: It's totally cool.
TADALEE: This is a performance
with a unique style.
BAMBAM: Absolutely beautiful.
BAMBAM: So beautiful.
TIA RAY: Are you okay?
JEFF: BAMBAM, control yourself.
- JEFF: Control yourself.
- TIA RAY: Are you okay?
XU MINGHAO:
The style is very unique.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): I'm curious
what brought the four of you
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): together
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): to create this team?
HU YETAO: I chose them.
HU YETAO: I feel their styles
HU YETAO: are somewhat like mine.
HU YETAO: And their appearance
HU YETAO: is beautiful,
HU YETAO: very good-looking.
ARIEL LIN: That's true.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): But if you
compare with
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): general boy groups,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): how do you present
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): your own style?
HU YETAO: I think being
an international boy group
HU YETAO: shouldn't be limited
to just ordinary boy groups.
HU YETAO: I joined this show in 2021 and
said a boy group has no definition.
HU YETAO: 3 years have passed.
HU YETAO: We've seen boy groups with same styles.
Why should we be stuck in that same box?
MENTOR: Wow.
HU YETAO: So, we shouldn't create
the same old boy group anymore.
- BAMBAM: Good answer.
- YAYA: I love it.
- TRAINEES: HU YETAO!
HU YETAO: From
a traditional perspective,
HU YETAO: I don't even look like
a person who would be an idol.
HU YETAO: The reason I can stand
on this stage with confidence
HU YETAO: is because
HU YETAO: I just want to be on stage.
HU YETAO: After CHUANG 2021 ended...
MENTOR: Goodbye, everyone.
HU YETAO: Actually, the chances
for me to get on stage are very rare.
HU YETAO: If anyone misses out, comment here.
HU YETAO: If you didn't get it, I will...
HU YETAO: Are you ready?
HU YETAO: All viewers,
HU YETAO: move your fingers a bit.
HU YETAO: Whether
it's posting short videos or
HU YETAO: posting dances
on social media,
HU YETAO: sometimes renting
locations for filming.
HU YETAO: Several artists
have filmed videos at this stage.
HU YETAO: We've invested quite a lot.
HU YETAO: But things like that
HU YETAO: can't compare with a stage with lights, costumes,
HU YETAO: the audience and applause.
HU YETAO: For me,
HU YETAO: what I desire the most
is to stand on a real stage.
HU YETAO: I didn't have many performances
back in CHUANG 2021.
HU YETAO: Honestly, I've watched
every performance over a hundred times,
HU YETAO: maybe more than a hundred.
HU YETAO: So, I think
I can't give up yet.
HU YETAO: I think I still have a chance
HU YETAO: to continue standing on stage
HU YETAO: in order to pursue
what I dream of.
HU YETAO: Another thing is the fans.
HU YETAO: All this time,
HU YETAO: for many reasons,
HU YETAO: I haven't given
HU YETAO: what is called
HU YETAO: pride to them.
HU YETAO: So, I feel regretful.
HU YETAO: This time,
HU YETAO: I have quite
some expectations.
HU YETAO: Suddenly, I felt like crying.
HU YETAO: I like it best
HU YETAO: when I see myself
in an attractive image.
HU YETAO: But I think
only being on stage
HU YETAO: will be my best image.
HU YETAO: I want to have
such wonderful moments
HU YETAO: and memories
HU YETAO: for my future self
to come back and watch again and again.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Actually, I really
want to see HU YETAO's solo performance.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): I really
want to watch it.
HU YETAO: I'll go change clothes first.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Sure.
HU YETAO: Thank you.
YUCHEN: We have to go all out.
PRAY: I wonder what kind
of performance it will be.
TRAINEES: So stunning.
TRAINEES: Changed to a limited-edition
skin for Season 2.
BAMBAM: Oh, my God.
TIA RAY: Eh, you're going to be
too beautiful.
TRAINEES: Like an angel.
TIA RAY: What are you going to do?
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): You can start
the performance now.
- TRAINEES: Wow.
- TRAINEES: Look at that pose.
TRAINEES: It's started.
TRAINEES: Truly beautiful.
TRAINEES: It's like watching an anime.
TRAINEES: Like a fox.
TRAINEES: Oh, my God.
TRAINEES: TAO TAO!
WANXIN: I cannot praise the flowers,
nor can I praise you.
BAMBAM: I'm done.
JEFF: Nice.
PRAY: I got goosebumps all over.
WUXUN: Very similar
WUXUN: to the posture of a fox.
JELLY: When he took off the mask,
I thought it was
JELLY: the nine-tailed fox, Daji.
DORN: As soon as it started,
I couldn't take my eyes off.
WHYLUCAS: Seeing HU YETAO over there
makes me like this.
YAYA: You know exactly
what weapons you have,
YAYA: and you know exactly
how to, like bang,
YAYA: like you know how to hit
everyone so well.
YAYA: That's incredible.
ARIEL LIN: I think he was truly
born for the stage.
ARIEL LIN: Even as a woman,
ARIEL LIN: I still feel
fascinated by you.
WUXUN: I don't even want to blink.
WUXUN: I just want to watch it.
ARIEL LIN: I think the greatest thing
you've gained from this stage is that
ARIEL LIN: seeing people
from all over the world
ARIEL LIN: will help you
appreciate the special
ARIEL LIN: and uniquely valuable
qualities you have.
ARIEL LIN: Keep it safe.
ARIEL LIN: This is CHUANG.
ARIEL LIN: CHUANG,
which means creativity.
HU YETAO: Yes, Mentor.
ARIEL LIN: I believe there is
a beauty within him
ARIEL LIN: that is inseparable
from both male and female aspects.
ARIEL LIN: That beauty,
ARIEL LIN: many years ago
ARIEL LIN: or even now in many places,
ARIEL LIN: is still not
understandable or acceptable.
ARIEL LIN: But this world
is becoming more
ARIEL LIN: diverse, and
ARIEL LIN: we can accept diverse beauty.
BAMBAM: One thing I want to say is
BAMBAM: HU YETAO,
BAMBAM: you actually
BAMBAM: are "nothing" to me.
MYST: What?
BAMBAM: Because
BAMBAM: "nothing" lasts forever.
BAMBAM: You get it?
YUCHEN: He's talking sweetly.
JINGYU: Like flirting.
BAMBAM: This is the first time
in my life, I feel like
BAMBAM: man is
BAMBAM: attractive.
YAYA: Nothing wrong in that.
YAYA: Nothing wrong with that.
JEFF: I just wanna say that
JEFF: you belong on the stage.
JEFF: Nowhere else.
BAMBAM: No, you belong to me.
TIA RAY: We belong together.
JEFF: I...
JEFF: Funny.
JEFF: That's it.
JEFF: It's just that BAMBAM...
JEFF: he's really fallen in love.
TRAINEES: Wow, they're so close.
TRAINEES: They're about to meet.
BAMBAM: He looks even prettier
when closer.
TIA RAY: Stop it.
JEFF: HU YETAO.
JEFF: We have to...
BAMBAM: HU YETAO?
JEFF: Okay.
JEFF: What?
JEFF: How?
- JEFF: I'm leaving.
- BAMBAM: Come back. Come back.
BAMBAM: Let's vote.
SHEN: I ship them.
GUANMING: You ship everyone,
you may get hurt.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Okay, we will give
the grading now.
- XU MINGHAO (THE 8): GOU YI.
- BAMBAM: GOU YI.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): B.
BAMBAM: C.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): LU JUNXI.
BAMBAM: F.
BAMBAM: Last one.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): HU YETAO.
BAMBAM: My darling.
TIA RAY: Stop it.
JEFF: Stop it, BAMBAM.
BAMBAM: Stop? Oh, okay.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Okay, HU YETAO.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): The final grading...
YAO ZIHAO: A.
BAMBAM: A.
YAO ZIHAO: Excellent.
ARIEL LIN: Congratulations.
HU YETAO: I thought I would get 3As.
HU YETAO: I'm really happy.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Just now
XU MINGHAO:
the group performance
and your solo performance
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): represented
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): the unique charm
you possess.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): I have emphasized it
from the beginning.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Hope everyone
knows yourselves,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): find yourselves
and improve yourselves.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): You already did it.
TIA RAY: I think you've found yourself.
TIA RAY: But now it's time
for you to see the world.
TIA RAY: Welcome to CHUANG.
HU YETAO: Thank you.
HU YETAO: Thank you, everyone.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Then, HU YETAO,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): please proceed
to the Class A seat.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): HU YETAO,
XU MINGHAO:
he has his own style,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): and the ability
to present that style.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Therefore,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): the ability to convey
his charm to the audience on the stage
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): is very important.
DONGDONG: In reality,
an idol's path nowadays
DONGDONG: is not limited to one style.
DONGDONG: but rather
how you discover yourself
DONGDONG: and showcase your best side
DONGDONG: and let it shine.
DONGDONG: Make everyone like you.
KOHI: A real star
KOHI: must amaze both those
who hate us and like us
KOHI: with our performance.
BAMBAM: I'm done.
KOHI: That is why
KOHI: people call us stars.
BAMBAM: So beautiful.
BAMBAM: Please welcome the next team.
BAMBAM: Here we go.
TRAINEES: Go. Go. Go.
RYAN WINTER: Hello, everyone.
RYAN WINTER: We are from Indonesia.
BIANURA: We are...
RYAN WINTER / BIANURA: APPLE MINT.
RYAN WINTER: My personal charm
RYAN WINTER: is piano
RYAN WINTER: and my singing
RYAN WINTER: is my confident skill
RYAN WINTER: that people can remember me
RYAN WINTER: that a man
who can play the piano.
TRAINEES: Hello everyone,
we are FRIDAY AT.
WANXIN: What I want to give everyone is
WANXIN: relaxation
WANXIN: and happiness.
TRAINEES: Hey, guys.
TRAINEES: We are 5 STARS.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): He struck
a cool pose right away.
HIKARI: My charm is,
HIKARI: among all the trainees,
HIKARI: I'm the only one with red hair.
HIKARI: In Chinese, HIKARI means
HIKARI: light.
HIKARI: Do you believe in light?
TRAINEES: Hello, everyone.
TRAINEES: We are 4EVER.
B: Someone once told me that
B: my smile makes the world brighter.
KAO: And I believe that
my smile can change the world.
JEFF: KAO, did you ever play a role
in the same series with YAYA?
KAO: Yes, I did.
YAYA: Yes, yes, you played
as young Mark, right?
YAYA: Yes, yes.
KAO: Back then,
I was around 13-14 years old.
JEFF: Are you still
13-14 years old now, right?
KAO: Of course, staying young forever.
JEFF: Come on.
BAMBAM: Okay, this stage is yours.
WEIZHI: WANXIN's necklace...
WEIZHI: He danced halfway
and then spun around.
WEIZHI: Then his necklace got tangled
with the headphones.
WEIZHI: And then, he had to
deal with the headphones.
WEIZHI: Only the two of us
were dancing there.
WEIZHI: I felt like he abandoned us.
WANXIN: What I want to give everyone is
WANXIN: relaxation and happiness.
BAMBAM: Alright, thank you.
It's a bit tiring, right?
YAYA: I think you guys
have a good chemistry.
YAYA: It's obvious that
you know each other.
YAYA: But I feel like you don't
really have a clear focus.
YAYA: Like your eyes are doing...
JEFF: If you don't know where to look,
JEFF: look at YAYA.
YAYA: In the future,
maybe find a focus point,
YAYA: so you're not like looking around.
YAYA: That's a little bit distracting.
YAYA: Just being cute alone
YAYA: on a stage with a lot of audience,
YAYA: sometimes it might not be enough.
YAYA: You might need to add
more strength in other areas.
YAYA: Keep going.
BAMBAM: Keep going.
TRAINEES: Handsome.
TRAINEES: Nice.
- TRAINEES: Thank you
- EARTH: Thank you.
BAMBAM: Thank you. Thank you.
BAMBAM: Take your time.
Breathe, alright?
BAMBAM: So, first is
BAMBAM: HIKARI.
BAMBAM: From Japan, 24 years old.
BAMBAM: HIKARI is...
BAMBAM: C.
YAYA: You have some kind of fire in you.
YAYA: And on stage, we could see that
you were trying very hard.
YAYA: But sometimes
when you try too hard,
YAYA: you lose your charm.
BAMBAM: Next is KOSHIN, SUNNY.
BAMBAM: Grade C.
BAMBAM: Next, EARTH.
BAMBAM: SENA.
TRAINEES: Both F.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Lastly,
I want to talk about
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): the overall problem.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): First, I feel that
XU MINGHAO:
you getting lower grades
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): is because
you are each dancing on your own.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): And there are people
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): dancing
a little too fast.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): The move isn't finished,
yet you're already onto another one.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): That makes me feel
a sense of chaos.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Therefore,
with the overall performance,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): even if
you have strengths,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): we still
can't seem to see you.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): I don't know
who to look at.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Also you
seem to not understand well
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): about teamwork.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): It ends up
highlighting your weaknesses,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): completely
overshadowing the strengths.
HIKARI: Teamwork is essential
no matter what.
HIKARI: Our team
HIKARI: is a team that includes
trainees from different countries.
HIKARI: So, the communication
among each other
HIKARI: needs to be reviewed again,
HIKARI: and we need to place
more importance on it.
BAMBAM: See you guys on the next round.
Thank you.
SUNNY: Thank you.
- HIKARI: Thank you.
- EARTH: Thank you.
SUNNY: Thank you.
SUNNY: Thank you to all the mentors.
TRAINEES: Keep going.
BAMBAM: So, let's go to the next group.
BAMBAM: Here we go.
XIAONIAN: Original groups?
HIKARU: To put on a performance,
HIKARU: to appear as
HIKARU: a united team,
HIKARU: I think
HIKARU: it's not that easy.
HIKARU: We have been together for
HIKARU: a couple of years now.
HIKARU: Of course, we have
HIKARU: trust in each other as a team.
RICKY: He's very talented.
Just let him be.
- RICKY: We just do as usual.
- DONGDONG: We are different.
RICKY: Advantage? It's very simple.
RICKY: We have been training
together for two years.
TRAINEES: Hello, we're RACEBACE.
TRAINEES: RACEBACE.
JELLY: Hello everyone.
I am JELLY who joined this show
JELLY: and have to become the senior
JELLY: both in age and skill.
RICKY: Hello, my weight is 65 kilograms,
RICKY: but my stubbornness
is 65.5 kilograms. I'm RICKY.
DONGDONG: Alright, you guys
introduced yourself very briefly.
DONGDONG: Then I will introduce myself
with a short rap.
DONGDONG: I used to weigh 90 kilograms
but changed until now.
DONGDONG: They said I look like
a celebrity. Maybe it's a compliment.
DONGDONG: Shy personality.
DONGDONG: Blushing with shyness.
DONGDONG: Let me show you the difference
DONGDONG: when I am on stage,
vroom vroom.
BAMBAM: Vroom vroom.
PEAT: Vroom vroom.
DONGDONG: Hello everyone, I am DONGDONG.
BAMBAM: DONGDONG.
TRAINEES: DONGDONG.
BAMBAM: From vroom vroom to DONGDONG.
TRAINEES: They're very strong.
LIZI: RICKY and DONGDONG
LIZI: participated in another show.
LIZI: They are experienced seniors.
RICKY: Actually, the three of us...
RICKY: Comparted to those
in the training in China,
RICKY: our training period
is quite long.
RICKY: So...
- RICKY: So...
- DONGDONG: It's hard to have the chance
DONGDONG: to form a group like this.
RICKY: We have been training
together for over two years.
RICKY: We understand each other.
RICKY: Of course, our compatibility
RICKY: is above other groups.
DONGDONG: This time we hope
to make C-POP
DONGDONG: become known,
DONGDONG: because we feel that, in fact,
DONGDONG: in our country,
there's not much space to showcase.
DONGDONG: So, we brought
our debut song to this show.
DONGDONG: It's a chance that allows
everyone to see us more.
WEIZHI: Wow, they are so synchronized.
TRAINEES: DONGDONG is
extremely outstanding.
TRAINEES: DONGDONG.
DAVID: They are holding wireless mics,
DAVID: singing live in such harmony.
DAVID: Not to mention how united
DAVID: their legs are
with that dance move.
DAVID: They are very skilled.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): I can really feel
that they came with genuine sincerity.
TIA RAY: Yes, yes, yes.
XU MINGHAO:
The performed song is
the pre-debut single, right?
JELLY: Yes, yes.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Then may I ask,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): since you are
about to debut in 2025,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): why did you change
the original plan
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): and come here
instead? What is the reason?
JELLY: Because we are about to face
JELLY: a market with hundreds
and thousands of boy bands.
JELLY: If we, who are
among these sixty people,
JELLY: are still unknown,
JELLY: in that case,
JELLY: going outside would probably
make no difference.
JELLY: Therefore, we
JELLY: came here to find
an opportunity to prove ourselves.
JELLY: Came here to test ourselves.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): And what if...
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): You planned
to debut in 2025.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): So what if
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): only one of you
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): makes his debut here,
while the other two are left out.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): What would you do?
JELLY: What should we do?
KEVIN: If two people fell into the water,
who would you save first?
KEVIN: It's like this question.
RICKY: It's fate.
- JELLY: It's...
- DONGDONG: I think
DONGDONG: no matter the outcome,
it's the best.
DONGDONG: If he debuts here
DONGDONG: and has a good future,
DONGDONG: I think we should be
genuinely happy for him.
KEVIN: The success of one person
- KEVIN: is better than the conflict of three people.
- WANXIN: Is better than the conflict of three people.
JELLY: The three of us have
very different personalities.
JELLY: Besides, we have been disbanded
JELLY: and then reunited.
JELLY: Finally, we became RACEBACE.
JELLY: This owes to
our shared determination.
JELLY: Besides being a boy group,
JELLY: we don't want to do anything else.
DONGDONG: We met for the first time
at the boss' studio.
DONGDONG: At that time, they only saw
a rough draft,
DONGDONG: yet still dared to sign
a contract with the company. It's
DONGDONG: kind of trust.
RICKY: Because they made
empty promises very convincingly.
STAFF: What promises?
JELLY: The perfect plan for us
- JELLY: that we would
- DONGDONG: It's our intention
JELLY: be a world-class boy group.
RICKY: They made
a very good presentation.
RICKY: That made me believe.
RICKY: Then, I signed
the contract right away.
RICKY: I didn't even read the contract.
RICKY: After joining the company,
RICKY: we trained privately.
JELLY: We practiced 66 hours a week
JELLY: day after day,
JELLY: year after year.
JELLY: No activities.
JELLY: No opportunity to perform.
JELLY: At that time,
we really had no opportunity.
JELLY: The first opportunity that
came close was probably when
JELLY: we got to participate
JELLY: TONY's birthday live.
JELLY: We had an opportunity
to be the dancers for him.
JELLY: But at that time we wore masks.
JELLY: At that time,
we thought to ourselves that
JELLY: we really wanted
to stand in the center.
JELLY: We wanted to take off the masks
and let others see our faces.
JELLY: That feeling was very strong.
DONGDONG: Because of that,
actually, the past six years,
DONGDONG: the three of us
have dreamed of debuting
DONGDONG: and worked very hard for it.
STAFF: What's the reason for wanting to debut?
DONGDONG: Age.
JELLY: Yes, he expressed
exactly what I feel.
JELLY: It's my age.
JELLY: Nothing to hide.
JELLY: 27.
JELLY: Next year I will be 28.
JELLY: If not debuting now,
should I wait until I'm old?
JELLY: I can't wait anymore.
DONGDONG: My age as well.
Actually, right now,
DONGDONG: I can hardly see
DONGDONG: a 24-year-old
still being a trainee.
DONGDONG: Suppose if someone
debuts in this show,
DONGDONG: it might not be a bad thing.
DONGDONG: Who knows,
DONGDONG: in a few years,
we might reunite
DONGDONG: as RACEBACE,
DONGDONG: and create a new spark
that is different.
JELLY: Hope that the three of us
JELLY: would help each other,
JELLY: walk on a bright path together,
JELLY: be the best RACEBACE.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Do other mentors
want to see any performance?
TIA RAY: I want to see DONGDONG.
DONGDONG: Okay.
TIA RAY: Because I think he
- TIA RAY: seems to have some charm.
- XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Right.
DONGDONG: I want to introduce
the other two members.
DONGDONG: They are just as amazing.
LIZI: Oh, spirit.
LIZI: Spirit, spirit.
ARIEL LIN: I want to see
JELLY's contemporary dance.
- JELLY: Okay.
- TIA RAY: Oh, contemporary dance.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): ZHANG GUODONG,
please go first.
JELLY: Okay.
GORDON: Wow. Very beautiful.
PRAY 杨浦睿: When he stood up,
it was very cool.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): I think just now
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): the way you did
the contemporary dance
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): is much better
than when you sang.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Just now,
when you were on stage,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): I think
the control of your facial expressions
XU MINGHAO:
might need improvement.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): But during the dance,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): you were fully
immersed in it.
XU MINGHAO:
Every movement of yours
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): harmonized with
the music and body.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Great job.
JELLY: Okay. Thank you, Mentor.
JEFF: So, you said that
JEFF: you were forced by your mom
to go on a blind date,
JEFF: and you made a deal with...
JEFF: with your mom to debut
within the year.
JEFF: Is it related?
JELLY: Well,
JELLY: I'm at the age
where I should be getting married.
JELLY: My parents
JELLY: often rush me to get married,
JELLY: find a job, something like that,
and then...
BAMBAM: I want to go on a blind date.
- JEFF: You?
- TIA RAY: You?
- JEFF: Why?
- TIA RAY: Why?
BAMBAM: I'm 27 too. I need to marry.
TIA RAY: Okay.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): So,
if you don't debut,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): do you have
to go back and get married?
JELLY: I don't think so.
JELLY: Because I still want
to pursue my dreams.
TIA RAY: But I don't think
they conflict.
TIA RAY: After getting married,
TIA RAY: you can also perform.
BAMBAM: Yes.
BAMBAM: Be the first idol who
BAMBAM: marry and debut.
BAMBAM: Make a new standard.
JELLY: It's okay. I don't want
- JELLY: to marry that much.
- BAMBAM: Oh, it's okay.
BAMBAM: Alright, DONGDONG,
let's go with your solo stage.
DONGDONG: CHUANG ASIA, let's go.
TIA RAY: Come on.
TRAINEES: Awesome.
TADALEE: Unexpected.
BAMBAM: DONGDONG is the most wanted.
YUCHEN: Very talented.
YUCHEN: I never thought that
someone who looks gentle
YUCHEN: would be so powerful on stage.
YUCHEN: Diverse personalities
at opposite ends.
DONGDONG: What's up?
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Great.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Your experience
and style on stage
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): are both
relaxing and genuine.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): And you interact
well with everyone.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Excellent.
DONGDONG: Thank you.
TIA RAY: I think today you performed
TIA RAY: very naturally.
TIA RAY: Indeed.
DONGDONG: Wow, thank you.
ARIEL LIN: I'm a fan of his now.
DORN: DONGDONG is someone
whose rap is impactful.
DORN: He can make people move.
DORN: And he made me feel that way.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Alright,
we will start scoring.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): DONGDONG.
TRAINEES: A.
BAMBAM: DONGDONG is the most wanted.
DONGDONG: Thank you.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Three,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): two,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): one.
- XU MINGHAO (THE 8): A, A, A.
- TRAINEES: Awesome.
BAMBAM: A, A, A.
TIA RAY: DONGDONG, try your best.
TIA RAY: Keep going.
DONGDONG: Yes, I will make it.
- TIA RAY: Seize this opportunity.
- DONGDONG: Yes.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): RICKY.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): JELLY.
- RICKY: Okay.
- JELLY: Thank you, Mentor.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Hope you
would be able
XU MINGHAO:
to shine in this show.
TRAINEES: Thank you, Mentor.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Welcome DONGDONG
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): to the Class A seat.
TRAINEES: Let's go.
TRAINEES: DONGDONG.
BAMBAM: DONGDONG.
BAMBAM: I think
he's all ready to go out there.
BAMBAM: For my opinion,
BAMBAM: I think now, besides training,
BAMBAM: I feel like
he needs more experience on this stage.
YAYA: He was a very good dancer,
YAYA: also a very good rapper.
YAYA: He has high potential as an actor,
YAYA: because it's very organic.
YAYA: He has dimples too.
YAYA: Every gesture of his
is all charming.
YAYA: It comes like...
YAYA: He can capture people's hearts.
YAYA: And like...
YAYA: Even with eyes closed,
I can still remember his face.
TRAINEES: Very handsome,
very photogenic.
ARIEL LIN: So handsome.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Appearance is
still the most important.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Seeing him
makes you feel happy.
- DAVID: So tall.
- KK: Is he mixed?
HIKARU: Wanna coming?
TRAINEES: MAISON B.
LYU: We are...
SHOYA: Hello.
SHOYA: We are a Japanese
hip-hop boy group.
SHOYA: MAISON B,
please take good care of us.
HIKARU: I would appreciate
your guidance.
WUXUN: I would appreciate your guidance.
LYU: Dragon is LYU.
LYU: LYU is me.
LYU: Support for me.
LYU: LYU from Japan.
LYU: I would appreciate your guidance.
TIA RAY: I would appreciate
your guidance.
SHOYA: Hello.
SHOYA: I am SHOYA.
SHOYA: I am the number one
dance champion in US.
SHOYA: I will do my best,
please take good care of me.
- LIZI: First place in dancing. Oh, my God.
- AGUANG: Expecting a lot.
HIKARU: The diamond of Asia,
born in Asia.
HIKARU: It's HIKARU.
HIKARU: Nice to meet you.
HIKARU: I love GOT7.
BAMBAM: Oh, thank you.
BAMBAM: Really?
HIKARU: Yes.
BAMBAM: Oh, thank you so much.
I appreciate it.
BAMBAM: XU MINGHAO said
you're handsome.
HIKARU: Thank you so much. I know.
BAMBAM: I know.
JEFF: Have you guys
watched FINAL FANTASY?
JEFF: HIKARU, you look like that guy
from FINAL FANTASY.
TIA RAY: Yes.
HIKARU: Thank you so much.
JEFF: See you, Cloud.
PRAY: He is very talented.
TRAINEES: It feels like
a very experienced group.
STAFF: How many years
have you been a trainee?
SHOYA: The first time I
SHOYA: became a trainee
SHOYA: was being a trainee
in a Japanese audition show.
SHOYA: After appearing on that show,
SHOYA: I and the trainees
who were eliminated
SHOYA: made a debut together.
SHOYA: Currently still active in Japan
SHOYA: as part of the MAISON B band.
SHOYA: But as for myself,
SHOYA: I still can't see hope from our continuous group activities.
SHOYA: Therefore,
SHOYA: participating in CHUANG ASIA S2
SHOYA: I strongly feel that
SHOYA: I don't want to do
anything halfway.
SHOYA: Let's go.
HIKARI: Fight on!
SUNNY: Keep going!
TRAINEES: Do your best!
TRAINEES: Fighting!
WHYLUCAS: I'm most looking forward
to their performance.
WHYLUCAS: Japanese.
BAMBAM: Okay.
BAMBAM: Oh, my God.
BAMBAM: Waacking.
TRAINEES: Oh, my God.
TRAINEES: MAISON B.
TRAINEES: Very handsome.
BAMBAM: Oh, my God.
BAMBAM: Who made the dance?
BAMBAM: The choreography is very good.
BAMBAM: I feel like three of you guys
together combine really well.
BAMBAM: So, you know, it's very easy for us
to see each character, all of you guys.
BAMBAM: So, I think that's
a really good sign to source a group.
HIKARU: Thank you so much.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Sister, you laughed
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): ever since
he walked in.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): I wonder...
ARIEL LIN: I'm not just
looking at faces, okay?
ARIEL LIN: Yes, you.
- HIKARU: Yes.
- ARIEL LIN: HIKARU is very eye-catching.
ARIEL LIN: I really want to see
his extra show.
JEFF: Okay.
- HIKARU: I would appreciate your guidance.
- BAMBAM: I would appreciate your guidance.
WHYLUCAS: HIKARU, keep going!
The Spring of the Northern Land
TRAINEES: Why does he use this song?
JACKSON: An old classic song pops up.
JACKSON: I'm surprised too.
JACKSON: Each idol
mostly sings and dances.
JACKSON: He knows
how to use his abilities
JACKSON: to attract more attention.
HIKARU: Thank you for listening.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): He immersed
himself a lot.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): He went all in.
SUNNY: Yeah.
HIKARI: Very cool.
BAMBAM: Well, I like this.
TIA RAY: You know, I feel like
I'm watching INCEPTION.
TIA RAY: You know like a MATRIX.
BAMBAM: Yes, so unexpected.
BAMBAM: First, you don't
really look Japan.
BAMBAM: Second, didn't know you're gonna
sing this kind of style.
BAMBAM: Man, you know
how to play this game.
HIKARU: Japanese, all people love Enka.
HIKARU: I listen to Enka a lot.
HIKARU: In Japan, I worked
at Senior Care Center to four years.
HIKARU: One day, an old lady asked me,
HIKARU: "Can you sing
my favorite Enka before I die?"
HIKARU: I said,
"No, no, no. Don't say that."
HIKARU: "You will live
healthy and long."
HIKARU: So, this is that song.
HIKARU: From there,
HIKARU: I started working
a part-time job
HIKARU: at a nursing home
in the same neighborhood as my house
HIKARU: in my own hometown.
HIKARU: I worked
as a caregiver for seniors.
HIKARU: At that time, I was also
active as an idol
HIKARU: of the MAISON B band.
HIKARU: I was also an idol
at the nursing home.
SHOYA: Regardless of our efforts
and expectations,
SHOYA: results do not appear right away.
SHOYA: So, I want to do a part-time job
SHOYA: and live my own life as well.
LYU: There are times when
LYU: it's hard to do both
at the same time.
LYU: But because of that,
LYU: now the three of us
LYU: can challenge such shows like this.
LYU: I want to try hard.
LYU: I want to ensure that
the efforts made so far
LYU: aren't wasted.
LYU: This includes so many people
who have always been supporting me.
BAMBAM: Oh, I like three of you guys.
BAMBAM: I wanna give everyone an A.
BAMBAM: But I know that's impossible.
BAMBAM: So, let's see.
BAMBAM: Let's go all together. Why not?
BAMBAM: Let's start with HIKARU.
BAMBAM: Go.
BAMBAM: Oh, my God.
BAMBAM: A, A, B.
TIA RAY: I'll teach you a Chinese saying
about what he just did.
TIA RAY: "Out of the blue."
TIA RAY: But, we are looking forward
to more of your performances.
HIKARU: Thank you so much.
YAYA: I feel a little bit bad,
YAYA: because ARIEL LIN
wanted to give you an A.
- TIA RAY: Really?
- YAYA: Yep.
YAYA: But just from my point of view,
YAYA: I just... I think I want
a little bit more like
YAYA: eye contact, you know.
- YAYA: So...
- JEFF: But you can't.
JEFF: You have a fiancé.
YAYA: Eh, he's not here, isn't he?
TIA RAY: I can, I can.
YAYA: I'm kidding.
YAYA: So, like during the performance,
if I can just get a little bit more.
YAYA: Just a little more.
YAYA: Because you're so charming already,
just standing there on your own, you know.
YAYA: Yep.
HIKARU: Thank you so much.
HIKARU: Absolutely,
the mentor is so beautiful
HIKARU: that it excited me.
STAFF: Who are you referring to?
HIKARU: Ms. YAYA.
HIKARU: Ms. YAYA is a wonderful person.
HIKARU: Ms. YAYA is like...
HIKARU: I find it really hard
to look at her.
BAMBAM: Alright, and next is
BAMBAM: SHOYA.
BAMBAM: A A B.
BAMBAM: SHOYA, Congratulations.
BAMBAM: And the last one is LYU.
BAMBAM: Three Bs.
BAMBAM: B, B, B. Alright.
- BAMBAM: So B grade. Congratulations.
- LYU: Thank you.
TIA RAY: You are really good.
BAMBAM: Thank you so much.
BAMBAM: Alright, so...
BAMBAM: Yah, anything?
TRAINEES: Thank you so much.
TIA RAY: I thought you guys
gonna sing a Christmas song.
TIA RAY: It's like...
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): I think this is
the charm of the audition show.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Some people
have trained hard for many years
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): for this opportunity.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Some people
start new dreams
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): because they've got
this chance.
STAFF: Next team, please get ready.
- TZI XUAN: Are you okay?
- XIAONIAN: Okay.
STAFF: Keep going, keep going!
STAFF: Don't be nervous.
- STAFF: Don't give up yet.
- TZI XUAN: Yes, keep going.
AGUANG: I am a professional
esports player of Peacekeeper Elite.
AGUANG: I joined CHUANG
for the first time.
AGUANG: This is the first time I've been
on such a great stage with my team.
AGUANG: I'm hoping to feel accepted.
BAMBAM: Please welcome the next team.
AGUANG: It's finally our turn.
XIAONIAN: We've waited for a long time.
LIZI: World champion right there.
LIZI: I am on the same stage
as the world champion.
TRAINEES: Hello.
TRAINEES: We are WHY NOT.
IVAN: Hello, I'm IVAN
from WHY NOT, dancing.
TZI XUAN: Hello, I'm TZI XUAN
from WHY NOT, Class A.
TZI XUAN: And I'm from Sabah, Malaysia.
XIAONIAN: Hello to all Mentors.
XIAONIAN: I'm XIAONIAN, Nian Hua Doll,
the center of WHY NOT.
AGUANG: Hello, I'm AGUANG
from WHY NOT, debut.
AGUANG: I came from the esports stage.
AGUANG: I switched to the idol stage
AGUANG: as a beginner level trainee.
AGUANG: Thank you.
TRAINEES: AGUANG.
AGUANG: We are called WHY NOT
AGUANG: because all of us don't sing
AGUANG: or dance well.
AGUANG: But we believe that
AGUANG: we will do our best
to reach the top.
BAMBAM: Alright, good luck to you guys.
BAMBAM: This stage is yours.
TRAINEES: Three, two, one.
TRAINEES: Keep going.
AGUANG: We are ready, Mentors.
AGUANG: Hope you are ready
AGUANG: for our amazing
performance as well.
AGUANG: Okay?
HU YETAO: An amazing performance.
BAMBAM: Cute.
TRAINEES: AGUANG.
WUXUN: AGUANG really made it.
WUXUN: When he joined CHUANG,
he really couldn't do anything at all.
WUXUN: But now he has improved a lot.
WUXUN: I'm really stunned.
Is this the right word to use?
BAMBAM: You know,
I think the energy is good.
BAMBAM: I think they're really cute.
XIAONIAN: Thank you, Mentor.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): How long have you
practiced this performance?
AGUANG: Less than 20 days.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): I think
in a span of 20 days,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): from beginner level
XU MINGHAO:
to performing on stage,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): it must take
a lot of efforts.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): I can really feel it.
TRAINEES: Keep going, AGUANG.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): AGUANG, you are
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): the gold medalist
of Peacekeeper Elite,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Esports
Asian Games Hangzhou.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Why did you join
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): CHUANG during
the peak of your career?
AGUANG: The reason I am here,
AGUANG: first of all,
it's because of my love for dancing.
AGUANG: Because when I was 17 years old,
AGUANG: due to an uncontrollable event,
I was unable to attend the audition.
AGUANG: I have loved dancing since then.
AGUANG: But I hadn't studied for long.
AGUANG: Mostly, I was only staying
in the practice room,
AGUANG: learning basic moves.
AGUANG: Besides dancing,
I also played the guitar.
AGUANG: My mom liked it a lot, too.
AGUANG: Like when I played guitar well,
my mom liked to listen.
AGUANG: But there was less than a week.
AGUANG: Then it was time
for practice sessions,
AGUANG: and during the practice sessions
until the time I got the gold medal.
AGUANG: Until now,
I finally got the chance
AGUANG: to learn on this stage.
AGUANG: That's why I want to have
my own growth experience
AGUANG: on this stage.
PD: Deep down, about singing and dancing,
PD: do you like it?
AGUANG: Yes, I think that those
AGUANG: dance moves are really cool.
PD: You think others look cool
when they dance.
PD: So have you tried dancing?
AGUANG: I tried, but everyone said
AGUANG: If you're itchy, take a shower.
AGUANG: But learning to sing and dance
AGUANG: makes me feel accomplished.
STAFF: Go a bit lower.
STAFF: Lower.
STAFF: Don't sing with your throat.
AGUANG: If I don't use my throat to sing,
what else can I use to produce sound?
AGUANG: All this is due to insufficient
practice. No matter how difficult it is,
AGUANG: as long as I practice enough,
AGUANG: everything is possible.
AGUANG: The show is filmed 24 hours
and I'm good at staying late.
AGUANG: If you're tired, take a break.
AGUANG: If you're not tired,
continue practicing
AGUANG: If you're not skilled,
practice a lot.
AGUANG: Because I know
my own ability well,
AGUANG: I am just a beginner
who have learned for less than a month.
AGUANG: Compared to
AGUANG: the seniors who
have learned for many years,
AGUANG: I still probably won't catch up.
AGUANG: Just doing my best is enough.
AGUANG: If an idol becomes
AGUANG: an eSports athlete,
AGUANG: the eSports athlete
AGUANG: can also join the idol shows.
TRAINEES: AGUANG, fly forever.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): AGUANG,
it seems like your team's theme song
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): is especially famous,
so can you sing it for us?
AGUANG: Sure.
TRAINEES: Let's go.
WUXUN: AGUANG.
WUXUN: Let's go.
AGUANG: This song is called
"Break the Limit".
AGUANG: It's our team's theme song.
AGUANG: It represents
AGUANG: an era of Chengdu AG.
AGUANG: I dedicate it
to all the seniors here.
TRAINEES: Go. Go.
AGUANG: I think I gradually
climbed higher step by step
AGUANG: until I won a championship.
AGUANG: Now that I'm here,
AGUANG: and I want to challenge myself,
AGUANG: because I have started
from scratch.
AGUANG: But I'm still confident
in my abilities
AGUANG: I want to write
my own legend again.
AGUANG: Break my own limits.
TRAINEES: Let's go.
AGUANG: Go for it.
YAO ZIHAO: Go for it.
HIKARU: Go for it.
ARIEL LIN: AGUANG, how long have you
spent on eSports?
AGUANG: About...
AGUANG: About five years.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): So, I wonder whether
you want to continue engaging
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): in esports
or aspire to be an idol in the future?
AGUANG: As for being an idol,
AGUANG: I think I had better let it be.
AGUANG: No matter how the outcome is,
I'll continue esports with my abilities.
AGUANG: And I will lead
the team to success.
TRAINEES: AGUANG.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): I think
you have reached the peak
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): of your career,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): and joined us here.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Maybe
the mentors here
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): might not be
as brave as you.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): But now
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): There is no way
to judge you
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): with standards
for a boy group.
BAMBAM: Alright, then I think
we already decide.
BAMBAM: So, AGUANG.
BAMBAM: If you're ready,
then one, two, three.
BAMBAM: Okay, it also F, F, F.
- AGUANG: Thank you, Mentor.
- BAMBAM: Yeah, thank you so much.
- AGUANG: Thank you.
- TRAINEES: Keep going.
WEIZHI: Keep going.
TRAINEES: Keep going.
BAMBAM: And the next one is
BAMBAM: TZI XUAN, XIAONIAN, and IVAN.
BAMBAM: It's a F.
BAMBAM: But you know,
I want you guys to understand.
BAMBAM: You know, you guys
really practiced not too long.
BAMBAM: Everyone needs time.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): We are not denying
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): your dreams.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): It's just that
in today's performance,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): as for the standards
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): for a boy group,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): this is the best
result we can provide.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): If you
truly love this stage,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): I hope
in the future you will
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): gradually develop
step by step,
- XU MINGHAO (THE 8): and keep improving.
- AGUANG: Right.
AGUANG: Thank you, Mentor.
TRAINEES: That's good.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): To be honest,
when I want to play
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Peacekeeper Elite,
don't forget to invite me.
AGUANG: No problem, sure.
AGUANG: I think the ones
in Class F, C, and B
AGUANG: have the opportunity to improve.
AGUANG: The strongest Class F
in the history.
AGUANG: This is the beginning.
BAMBAM: For the GRAND AUDITION,
the last team,
BAMBAM: HEART STEALERS.
TRAINEES: You know, what's up, boys?
NINJA: WHYLUCAS.
TRAINEES: Yo, what's up?
Ladies and gentlemen.
- WHYLUCAS: We are...
- REXY: Thump thump.
PRAY: Thump thump.
WHYLUCAS: Thump thump.
- REXY/PRAY: HEART STEALERS.
- WHYLUCAS: Yes, everyone.
PRAY: Hello, I am PRAY
from HEART STEALERS.
PRAY: And I want to say
PRAY: ♪All I need is love ♪
PRAY: ♪I just wanna run away ♪
PRAY: ♪with you ♪
PRAY: ♪you ♪
YUCHEN: Very smart use.
YUCHEN: Three lines, no copyright.
WUXUN: Excellent.
YUCHEN: Awesome.
REXY: Hello everyone.
REXY: I am REXY HUANG YIXIANG
from HEART STEALERS.
WHYLUCAS: Hello everyone.
I am WHYLUCAS from HEART STEALERS.
WHYLUCAS: Why LUCAS?
BAMBAM: You guys are the ending.
BAMBAM: So, you all have to be
freaking good, okay?
WHYLUCAS: We're gonna kill it.
WHYLUCAS: Let's go.
BAMBAM: Oh, that's perfect for ending.
TRAINEES: WHYLUCAS.
BAMBAM: PRAY,
- PRAY: Yes.
- BAMBAM: REXY,
BAMBAM: and WHYLUCAS.
BAMBAM: Let's see WHYLUCAS's solo.
TRAINEES: WHYLUCAS.
TRAINEES: WHYLUCAS performs the finale.
TRAINEES: Best finale.
BAMBAM: WHYLUCAS, such a weird name,
BAMBAM: but I like it.
WHYLUCAS: Maybe because
I'm the only one from Singapore.
WHYLUCAS: I am from
National University of Singapore,
WHYLUCAS: as a sophomore
in Faculty of Business Administration.
WHYLUCAS: Maybe because
WHYLUCAS: I'm not very good at dancing.
WHYLUCAS: But maybe because
I sing quite well.
WHYLUCAS: Maybe as I play guitar well.
WHYLUCAS: I used to have
some sponsored performances,
WHYLUCAS: and make some pieces of music.
WHYLUCAS: A few years ago, there was
nothing new in my circle at all.
WHYLUCAS: So, I was quite exhausted.
WHYLUCAS: I came to this show
WHYLUCAS: to meet people and learn new things
WHYLUCAS: For instance, I would get
to learn dancing every day.
WHYLUCAS: Dance every day
for 7-10 hours.
WHYLUCAS: I came here to learn
how to be an idol
WHYLUCAS: So I am very excited.
BAMBAM: Oh la.
TRAINEES: WHYLUCAS.
TRAINEES: The guy with the biggest
muscles on the show.
TRAINEES: Big muscles.
WANXIN: Those muscles must be
from push-ups.
GUANMING: Wow, who wouldn't be envious?
SHEN: Do you have them?
GUANMING: If I had them,
why would I wear a shirt like this?
BAMBAM: Oh.
JEFF: He can play.
TIA RAY: Right.
BAMBAM: Sexy.
WHYLUCAS: Let's go.
TRAINEES: WHYLUCAS.
TRAINEES: Wow, Latin music.
TIA RAY: Okay.
WHYLUCAS: Everybody claps.
WHYLUCAS: Thank you.
NINJA: JOHN MAYER of Singapore.
WHYLUCAS: Okay.
YAYA: More.
- YAYA: More. More.
- TIA RAY: More. More.
TIA RAY: I want more.
WHYLUCAS: You more? More originals?
WHYLUCAS: Sorry.
MYST: With that kind of atmosphere
he creates,
MYST: it makes people
want to support him.
WHYLUCAS: Thank you.
TADALEE: Awesome.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Did you compose
the song just now yourself?
WHYLUCAS: Yes, I wrote
both songs myself.
WHYLUCAS: I composed and produced
everything myself.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): I think you're
talented as you can create your own music.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): If you
have to join a group,
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): it might overshadow
some of your shine.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): What do you
think about this?
WHYLUCAS: I think that
it might be a challenge that...
WHYLUCAS: However, I might be
overshadowed a bit,
WHYLUCAS: I feel like the person
who's the center is better than me
WHYLUCAS: in singing,
performing and dancing.
WHYLUCAS: Then, prop them,
but I really got to work.
WHYLUCAS: Because to me, I feel that
I can always achieve something as long as I put endeavor.
WHYLUCAS: That's why I'm here.
WHYLUCAS: Thank you, Mentor,
for even thinking about that for me.
TIA RAY: You know, like he's good
at guitar and then...
BAMBAM: You guys...
BAMBAM: it's hard, huh?
TIA RAY: It's hard.
BAMBAM: Yeah.
TADALEE: Very talented.
TRAINEES: He's starting to blush.
GORDON: WHYLUCAS, where is the toilet?
- TRAINEES: Where is the toilet?
- TRAINEES: Where's the toilet, LUCAS?
BAMBAM: Okay, alright,
I think we have decided.
BAMBAM: PRAY, B B B.
BAMBAM: REXY, triple Cs.
BAMBAM: WHYLUCAS,
BAMBAM: I know why it's WHYLUCAS now.
WHYLUCAS: Why?
BAMBAM: Because, dude, you're good, man.
WHYLUCAS: Thank you. Thank you.
BAMBAM: Sexy.
WHYLUCAS: Thank you.
BAMBAM: You've got all the charm
and charisma. That's good.
BAMBAM: So, WHYLUCAS.
BAMBAM: One, two, three.
BAMBAM: Let's go.
BAMBAM: B A A.
WUXUN: The last card.
- NINJA: Great, WHYLUCAS.
- TRAINEES: WHYLUCAS.
TIA RAY: WHYLUCAS,
TIA RAY: When you do solo
without the instrument,
TIA RAY: I still feel
you're a little weak.
TIA RAY: and you're trying to catch
the audience's attention
- TIA RAY: to cover the weakness.
- WHYLUCAS: I got you.
TIA RAY: So, that's the part I can tell.
TIA RAY: And then practice more singing.
WHYLUCAS: Yes, Mentor.
BAMBAM: You guys are the last team
for the GRAND AUDITION.
BAMBAM: So, we got the last A.
BAMBAM: And Congratulations, guys.
WHYLUCAS: Thank you, everybody.
WHYLUCAS: I've always felt that
WHYLUCAS: I'm like Alex,
the lion in MADAGASCAR.
WHYLUCAS: We all want to perform
on a big stage.
WHYLUCAS: I'm very happy that today
I've taken another step toward that goal.
TRAINEES: WHYLUCAS.
TRAINEES: Nice, bro.
TRAINEES: Awesome.
TRAINEES: WHYLUCAS.
- THI-O: Good job, bro.
- WHYLUCAS: Thanks.
THI-O: Oh, my god.
THI-O: Now you're here,
I look so small now.
THI-O: Very bad, very bad.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): I think today
is just the GRAND AUDITION.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): It's just a scoring
XU MINGHAO:
only the first impression.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Just the beginning.
BAMBAM: A is not the best.
BAMBAM: Actually, the best is S.
BAMBAM: Besides that, I just want
everyone to first enjoy the dance.
BAMBAM: You know,
don't take it too seriously.
BAMBAM: Just enjoy it.
BAMBAM: The GRAND AUDITION stage
BAMBAM: of CHUANG ASIA S2 is officially over.
BAMBAM: You know, it was a long run.
BAMBAM: You know, you show
the legacy of your hard work,
BAMBAM: and the magic
of the collaboration.
BAMBAM: This performance has brought us
BAMBAM: 9 people of A class,
BAMBAM: and 23 people of B class,
BAMBAM: 18 people of C class,
BAMBAM: and 10 people
of F class rankings.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): This is just
a first impression
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): of the mentors
to you.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Class A,
don't underestimate others.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): As for those
not in Class A, don't give up.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): You still have
a lot of opportunities to improve.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Be one of the seven
who can shine.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Join Class A.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Because eventually,
whether you're gonna debut or not
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): depends on
the founders who will have the final say.
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): Now,
you will have your first mission
XU MINGHAO (THE 8): right away.
Welcome Producer BAMBAM.
to perform CHUANG ASIA S2 THEME SONG.
Download WeTV
and register to become a member.
Then press "CHUANG ASIA S2" channel page
and click "Vote Now"
to vote for your favorite trainees.
WeTV members
will get the vote eligible every day.
You can vote for seven trainees each day
with the limit of one trainee
per ten votes only.
And purchase WeTV VIP
on CHUANG ASIA S2 page,
you will get 20 votes per trainee daily.
To get more voting privileges,
click "Send gifts"
or purchase CHUANG ASIA S2 VIP gift card
to get extra votes.
This round,
you can also get extra free votes
from various activities on WeTV,
such as continuous daily voting
and watching advertisements.
This round of voting starts
from February 2nd, 2025 at 4:50 PM
until February 28th, 2025 at 10:00 AM.
The first elimination
will be only 35 of 60 trainees.
Come and vote
for your favorite trainees.
Who's going to debut
will be solely determined by your vote.
Click "Send Love Rankings".
And "Send Love"
to your favorite trainees.
Give more benefits for them now.