=Just Fiancée=
=Episode 11=
(Max Group)
Ms. Gu is here.
Ms. Gu.
We can't stop this project.
It'd make our company
look bad
and we'd not be able to answer
to those villagers.
What do you mean by that?
Don't you know?
Do tell.
You said in the past that
Xiaolin Bay was your hometown.
It is surrounded by rivers
and the villagers are
cut off from the outside world.
It was your suggestion to develop that place
into a tourist attraction.
Ms. Gu,
you agreed to the project in the past.
How come...
Zhong, Zhou!
Enough.
What has already been decided
will not change.
What's with that attitude, Zhong?
Don't cross the line!
Look here, Zhong!
If you behave like this one more time,
I'll...
Enough.
Why did you decide to stop the project?
I don't want to get involved
in Gu Manman's projects.
But
the villagers did nothing wrong.
Gu Manman once
stole company files.
Who knows whether the project
would be a trap?
I'm a businessman.
I have to look at the big picture.
But...
No buts.
I don't change my mind easily.
Hello?
Mom.
What's wrong?
A friend of yours came looking for you.
He asked you to meet him by the beach.
A friend?
I don't think I have any friends.
It's the guy from last time.
Lin Duoduo.
Alright.
I got it.
Erm, Su Yu...
That's enough from you.
Fine.
I'll deal with it on my own.
I'm leaving.
Hey.
Long time no see.
Who are you?
Good one, Gu Manman.
How dare you pretend to not know me?
What's your name?
Gu Manman!
Do you know what happened here by the beach?
Here?
(Lin Duoduo)
(Gu Manman)
Let's play together.
I don't play with childish people.
Got it?
I don't remember.
I, Lin Duoduo, have been trying
to win your heart for years
and you are saying you don't know me?
I looked for you for months
after you went missing,
but now you are saying you don't know me?
Duoduo.
I have some memories of you.
Then do you remember
what happened between us?
My head is killing me.
I can't remember anything.
Manman.
Something traumatic
must have happened
for you to lose your memory.
Don't worry.
I'll help you remember it all.
Do you remember this ring?
A wedding ring?
Did you propose to me?
Yes.
Then did I
say yes?
No.
You took this ring
and proposed to Su Yu.
What?
Marry her!
I'm running out of patience.
Do you want to be with me or not?
Su Yu.
We can never be together.
You are mine.
That is what happened.
That sounds ridiculous.
Then why do you still like her...
I mean me?