=Just Fiancée=
=Episode 7=
Miss Gu, would you like a glass of wine?
No, thanks.
Mr. Su, what do you think?
I'll think about it.
I'm leaving.
No, you can't.
I'm hungry.
Get something to eat.
Miss Gu.
Hello!
Hello?
Qiao Mai, what are you doing here?
Miss Gu!
Do you know the waiter?
We're friends.
We are just friends.
Stop right there!
What is it?
You are not Gu Manman!
Do you have any evidence?
I'm Gu Manman.
Do you need evidence to show
who you are?
The fact that you said that
makes me even more suspicious.
Su Yu brought home a fake Gu Manman.
Others might be fooled,
but not me.
I guess you don't know.
But in the past,
Gu Manman
would not act like this.
Let me see what the waiter
has put in your bag!
They are my belongings!
I'm sorry.
How dare you slap me?
Lin Shaoshao!
You really crossed the line this time.
Let's go.
I crossed the line?
She slapped me!
(Lin Duoduo, young master of the Lin Group)
Brother, someone has slapped me!
I have arrived.
Let me see
who was bold enough
to slap my sister!
How could she slap me!
Gu Manman!
I will get my revenge sooner or later!
Who slapped my sister?
Gu Manman slapped me!
What? Gu...
Manman?
Brother!
Tell me!
Where did Manman go?
You don't care about me at all!
Have I not warned you about her?
Even I got slapped by her numerous times!
Tell me where Manman is?
She left a while ago!
However,
she has been away for such a long time.
Where was she during that time?
Why has she come back all of a sudden?
I find it strange, too.
Manman!
(Lin Duoduo, Gu Manman)
Don't marry Su Yu.
I don't know what you see in him!
You brought me out here
just to talk about this?
This is your marriage we're talking about!
It's none of your business!
Stay away from me!
Su Yu has also changed
his attitude towards her.
I don't care! Even if she's back,
I will take Su Yu
from her!
I think I know where the real Gu Manman is.
Who are you?
I hired a private investigator
and obtained two pictures of Gu Manman here.
Do you know her?
No, we don't.
The two of you are lying!
This is Qiao Mai.
And this is Gu Manman.
Why did Gu Manman
draw freckles on her face
and pretend to be someone else?
Aren't freckles hereditary?
Oh, she is Gu Manman!
How about this?
I can give you a lot of money
if you can get her to meet me somewhere.