- We were here.
You all have different styles.
(The last day of the Madagascar trip
for the four brothers.)
(Surprised)
Oh, it's rising.
It's coming up.
- Oh, the sunrise.
- Oh, my.
(Their last sunrise in Madagascar)
- What a magnificent view.
- How beautiful.
You have to go back to Korea now.
No! Episode ten can't end!
No! We want more!
- Let us go to Korea.
- Don't come back!
- Just stay there!
- Don't come back.
- Don't come up. Go back down.
- Go back down.
- Don't come up, sun.
- Don't come up.
- Don't come up. Go back down.
(So...)
(we put it back down.)
(Adventure by Accident 3)
(Untold Stories)
(Stop the sunrise!)
Can you hear me?
(YouTube Live for Pani Bottle's birthday)
(- Oh, my. It's a live stream.
- Happy birthday, Pani Bottle!)
Oh, thank you.
I'll show you the scenery here.
This is Madagascar.
(- Isn't it Seoul?
- Isn't it Yongsan?)
"Isn't it Yongsan?" It's Madagascar.
(Beware of similar scenery)
Did I do a live stream
for my birthday last year?
(During the South America trip
1 year ago,)
(he also did a birthday live stream
with Kian84 and Si Eon.)
(He does a live stream
every year on his birthday.)
I did do a short one last year
in South America.
"Now that you've started the live stream,
beware of Kian84."
Thankfully, he's still sleeping.
He's still sleeping. The time right now...
What is it... What time is it right now?
Hello.
Kian84 is awake.
So...
(Letting out a laugh)
- We are in Madagascar.
- Why do I feel so anxious?
(- Be careful of spoilers.
- There he goes again.)
- Okay. Next person.
- Yes. Dex...
I think Kian84 must have
a lot he wants to talk about,
but he gave away so many spoilers
during the last live stream.
- Hello. I'm Dex.
- Did you sleep well?
- I slept well.
- How are you feeling?
I'm feeling good,
but my face is very puffy.
You must not know
what a true puffy face is.
This is what you call a puffy face.
(Laughing)
(Okay. Next person.)
Hello.
Your hair looks cool, Si Eon.
(Si Eon's surprise first greeting)
Everyone!
(Greeting the viewers
with too much excitement)
Kian84. Dex.
- Let's say goodbye one last time.
- Okay.
- I have to go now. There's no time.
- Go where?
Oh, the zoo?
(What a nice spoiler...)
Si Eon. Move.
- It wasn't me this time.
- Gosh.
Why did you do that? I just stopped Kian84
from giving away spoilers.
- Oh, I'm sorry. Gosh.
- Anyway, we...
Please give Adventure by Accident 3
lots of love.
This season will be even more fun.
I promise.
How was it for you all?
It'll be a fun season, right?
Can I just give away one thing?
- We kind of...
- No!
This has been Adventure by Accident.
Thank you!
(Since the season is over,)
(we'll give you all...)
(of the unreleased footage.)
(Hard drive)
(Being born...)
(was a surprise?)
I arrived in Madagascar.
Let's get one World Cola.
I wanted to have one.
(Getting local cola as soon as he arrives)
They don't sell Inca Kola here, right?
(A special treat
during the South America trip)
There's no cola.
(A yellow drink catches his eye)
Is this antifreeze?
I'll have one of these.
(He doesn't know what it is,
but he'll get it.)
I don't know what it is.
It says there is vitamin C in here,
so I don't think it's antifreeze.
Oh, my.
Oh, no.
(He spotted another drink
that appealed to him.)
They have Sprite.
(A drink that appears to be Sprite
in the row below)
Yujo.
I wonder how much it is.
(Purchasing 1 drink)
(Handing over money)
(Kian84's first transaction in Africa)
Thank you.
It was 5,000 ariaries. That means...
A bottle of drink is
about 1 dollar and 80 cents.
In terms of beverages, the prices
are the same, whether you're in...
India, Korea, or Peru.
They're all the same.
We will head from Antananarivo,
the capital of Madagascar,
to Moldodava? Moldovada?
Yes. We will go to Moldovada, the beach.
I think...
it might be the Jebudo Island
of Madagascar.
I'll get going.
(Heading to Morondava feeling excited)
Lots of rain. Lots of thunderstorms.
I'm not comfortable
about going through there.
Let's go tomorrow.
They say it's dangerous.
Thank you.
(Kian84's first meal in Antananarivo)
(Ramyeon in lots of broth)
(Glancing over)
(After filling his stomach
with half rain and half soup,)
(Kian84 hurries back
to the lodging they booked.)
What? Is this a bar on the street?
Excuse me.
Whiskey?
Let's see...
Vodka and whiskey?
Do you have?
(Are you not the owner?)
- Over there.
- What? Is the owner someone else?
Are you not the owner?
Oh, there's the owner.
Oh, yes. Whiskey?
(The owner is here.)
What whiskey?
- Whiskey?
- Yes.
A shot?
Shot? Yes.
Oh, this?
(Interested)
How much?
Seven thousand...
Everyone.
I found hard liquor
cheaper than Napoleon V.
This must be about 2.2 dollars.
Okay.
(A clean transaction)
What is this called?
Madagascar rum?
(Yes)
(He's about to leave after paying,)
(but the owner seems to have something
he wants to say?)
Okay.
What did he say?
He asked for 1,000 ariaries more
for the cost of the bottle.
I see.
Okay. This, I'll take. Okay.
Here are 1,000 ariaries. Okay. Understand.
Thank you.
Oh, the bottle costs 1,000 ariaries?
I guess some people bring bowls
and just buy the alcohol.
Anyway, let's go.
(Walking down the dark street
with rum in his hand)
Oh, this feels like the Hongik University
of Madagascar.
How cool.
Some food to have with my drink.
(Spotting a street food stall)
What? Fritters?
(Various Madagascar-style fritters)
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
This. Two.
Two. This. Two.
And...
(Adding an egg he didn't order)
Wait. I asked for this.
Why are they giving me that?
What? Why are they giving me that?
(An error in ordering)
(Oh, not that one...)
Here. This.
That...
Oh, I guess I eat them together.
And this. One.
(Swallowing his saliva)
- And this. Two.
- Two?
(Buying lots of fritters
since he already bought some alcohol)
(Appetizing)
I'm takeout. Takeaway.
To go.
- How much?
- Ariary.
What?
What's going on? From his reaction,
I feel like they're asking for too much.
How much?
(Write it here for me.)
(Whispering)
Hey, they're talking to each other.
Oh, don't rip me off.
(10,000 ariaries)
Three dollars?
(About 3 dollars?)
(Whatever price they asked for,)
(he always said okay.)
(When there's no change,)
(he considers it a tip.)
(Kian84 is a magnanimous customer
with zero negotiation skills.)
Three dollars?
(Will he be different on his third trip?)
(Our friend next to Kian84
is nervous too.)
Okay. Let's just pay for it.
So about 3.3 dollars?
(Another magnanimous purchase)
Okay. Thank you.
(He bought
about 3 dollars' worth of fritters.)
It was 3 dollars and 30 cents.
The prices are lower here.
I do think they kind of ripped me off
for the noodles too,
but it's still cheap.
(Back at his lodging)
(Unexpectedly spending
1 night in Antananarivo)
A two-dollar vodka.
And three dollars of noodles and fritters.
(Opening the rum first)
(How does Madagascar rum taste?)
(Another sip)
Oh, my.
(Madagascar rum gets a pass.)
(Now, it's time to try the fritters.)
(Naturally eating with his hands)
(Sniffing)
This is...
(Naturally eating with his hands)
(On the 1st trip in South America,)
(and also on the 2nd trip to India,)
(he ate with his hands
without hesitation.)
(It feels weird
if he doesn't eat with his hands now.)
The potato one is good.
(Wiping his oily hands on his clothes)
(Stopping to suddenly smell his shoes...)
(Sniffing)
(The intense smell of his feet
stimulates his appetite?)
(Eating)
(Wiping)
(Eating one last bite)
(Putting it away for now)
(Looking around)
(He suddenly takes out a notebook.)
Let's see...
(Okay. I've decided!)
(He's starting to draw something?)
(On his first night in South America,)
(he drew the tough time he had
during his flight.)
(On his first night in India,)
(he drew the young men in Varanasi
that helped him find the hotel.)
(What will he draw today?)
(The object in his drawing is...)
(A rainy sky?)
(As soon as Kian84 arrived in Madagascar,)
(he was greeted by lightning.)
(Lightning strikes)
(Even after he arrived in the city,)
(there was thunder and lightning.)
(His first record of Madagascar
will be...)
Okay.
(The memories he had with the lightning)
(Hoping for good weather
for the remainder of the trip...)
Beautiful.
It's complete.
"Adventure by Accident Season Three."
"Hoping for no rain
every day of the trip."
I'm done drawing.
Now I'll head to bed soon...
since I have to wake up
at 3:30 a.m. tomorrow.
We had a slight change of plans,
but that's what traveling is all about.
I'll eat a bit more, then head to bed.
(Goodnight)
(If our plans hadn't changed,)
(this wouldn't have been drawn either!)
(Adventure by Accident Season 3!
October 18. Hoping for no rain.)
(But his wish didn't come true...)
(Diving into the bed in clothes
that are still wet from the rain)
(Pani Bottle: What are you up to, Kian84?
Is it tough there?)
(Dex: I miss you, Kian84.)
Where is this?
(Where are you guys now?)
(Pani Bottle: We're at Han River.
Dex: Try to guess by the picture, Kian84.)
They're in Madagascar.
Wait. If they were here,
they would've said so.
(Are you in Varanasi?)
(Pani Bottle and Dex
are currently in Varanasi?)
But Varanasi does look like this at night.
The width of the river
is a bit short there too.
- I see.
- And the two sides of the river...
have completely different atmospheres.
(Varanasi is famous for its
beautiful night view of the Ganges River.)
It feels nice to be here.
Right. It always feels nice
to be out here.
(The Seine River in Paris, France)
That place is pretty.
- Oh, what is this?
- What is this?
(Dex and Pani Bottle have a layover
in Paris on their way to Madagascar.)
Parisians really do dress well.
Like the people in coats.
(Observing Parisian fashionistas)
- They dress very gently.
- Right.
(Looking fashionable)
We should start seeing some restaurants.
If you see any restaurant you like,
we can eat there.
You can just stop and tell me
which restaurant you want to eat at.
Okay.
There are a lot of Asian restaurants.
I see Japanese and Vietnamese restaurants.
(They end up in the alley
of Asian restaurants.)
But...
we're in Paris.
Isn't eating Asian food kind of lame?
(Even before arriving in Paris,)
(Pani Bottle and Dex looked forward
to food in Paris.)
(I want to have an authentic pasta dish
from France.)
This must be that alley.
The alley with a lot of Asian restaurants.
What is this?
(He stops at a Korean restaurant.)
Pick the restaurant you want.
I'm good with anything.
(Then let's go inside.)
Hello.
(They enter a Korean restaurant.)
We walked around,
but we ended up at a Korean restaurant.
(They're Korean to the bones.)
This is crazy.
One order of the fried dumplings,
one order of kimchi jeon,
one order of tteokbokki,
one order of spicy stir-fried pork,
one order of kimchi stew,
and one bowl of jjajangmyeon. Perfect.
And we need more food.
One beer.
And one bottle of makgeolli.
- Can we finish everything?
- Four cans of Zero Coke.
- Zero Coke? Four?
- Yes. Four.
(Ordering a feast of Korean food)
Gosh. You would've been so disappointed
if we didn't come to a Korean restaurant.
I'm going to satisfy my last cravings...
for Korean food here tonight.
(Their last supper begins in earnest.)
(Having a heap of rice)
(Slurping)
(Crunchy)
(Steaming hot)
This is crazy. It's so tasty.
(This is what I'm talking about.)
(Cheers)
(They have a Korean feast in France.)
(Happily shaking his head)
Check out what Kian84 is doing now.
I bet this is what he's doing now.
(Hitting the spot)
Is he having a glass of whisky
at a bar or something?
(That's correct.)
I bet he bought some food and liquor
and ate them in a hotel room.
I bet he bought a bottle of hard liquor.
And here's the important part.
The room probably has
a table or side table.
He won't sit on the chairs.
- He would sit on the floor.
- He'd sit on the floor.
That's Kian84 for you.
(They have become three brothers
who know everything about each other.)
Now that we're drinking,
let's have a heart-to-heart conversation.
Have you been busy lately in Korea?
- Before the trip?
- Yes.
- Because...
- You want me to be honest? I was so busy.
I was extremely busy.
Because you were so busy,
did you experience any signs of burnout?
I'm already experiencing a burnout.
- Already?
- Yes.
But I think it has to do
with my personality too.
- I didn't star on a lot of shows.
- Right.
So I never felt burned out
from starring on TV shows.
But I got burned out from traveling.
- From traveling.
- Yes.
That's the thing. Traveling...
became work now.
I thought I would never experience this.
I loved traveling so much that
I wouldn't get burned out from it.
But the type of trip I want...
and the type of trip people want to watch
didn't align.
So I got burned out.
What's the type of trip you want to go on?
- Me? Just doing whatever I want.
- Yes.
Let's say I'm in Paris.
I feel lazy,
so I don't want to do anything.
- Instead of going out?
- I would stay at the hotel.
- To me, that's also traveling.
- Yes.
As for the time
I have left in Korea in 2023,
it's fewer than two weeks.
- Really?
- Yes.
I'll have to keep traveling after this.
I'm already booked out for the year.
- As for this year,
- You don't have any free days.
all of my days are booked.
- You know, we should be grateful.
- Totally. I'm so grateful.
People want to work with us.
But it's hard not to feel burned out
despite knowing that.
(They are grateful to be loved
despite their busy schedules.)
We ought to overcome it.
As for the members of our show,
you, Kian84, and me,
we weren't popular in the beginning.
Yes. You're right.
It's not like we started our careers
as an elite group.
When Kian84 wasn't doing well
as a webtoon artist...
I know the kind of life he had.
- I knew you were on "Toy Soldiers."
- Right.
You weren't as famous as now.
- I know how it had been for you then.
- You do.
You know how it had been.
Of course, I wasn't famous at all.
I think that might be why
the viewers love...
the combination of the cast.
That crossed my mind.
People who had a hard time
in the beginning are on this show.
You're right.
Seriously. We destroyed this meal.
(The food is gone.)
Seriously. I'm so full.
What do you say?
We should go to the Louvre.
Forget about the Louvre.
(They had a productive day in Paris.)
(The Seine)
(The strong man)
(The next day)
(The airport lounge while making
a transfer to go to Madagascar)
(Dex is spotted
playing a game against a kid.)
(The kid, Dex)
(Ruthlessly kicking the kid's character)
(Chuckling)
This is the bitter taste of life.
(The kid's character is knocked out.)
(I'm leaving.)
(Laughing)
(Glancing)
(A triumph mixed with shame)
I won.
(The kid leisurely leaves.)
The kid went to his parents
the moment he lost.
I think I need to walk away
from the scene.
Let's go.
(Making a stop in Paris was fun!)
(Hello, My Friends from Madagascar)
(In the meantime,
Kian84 met some Vezo people.)
(After struggling with spearfishing,)
(he revealed a wild side of himself
he had never shown before.)
(The local guy was shocked.)
(They come back to the land side
of Belo sur Mer.)
(They're going to the market
to buy ingredients for dinner.)
(His local friend, Florant)
(Hello)
- What? Your friend?
- Yes.
- Your friend?
(See you later.)
(Greeting)
Hello.
(Like the zoomer,
he says hi to his friend from the area.)
(We're here.)
Gosh, this is a market.
(Welcome to the market.)
This is a market.
(A small market is set up
on the sandy beach.)
(There's an abundance
of freshly caught fish...)
(and fruits.)
(Belo sur Mer Market)
(Fascinated)
What's going on?
The ladies are angry.
They're talking, but they sound so angry.
(Surprised)
What's this?
(Mangos and grilled fish)
Fish.
(Rice)
(Charisma)
(Oh, right.)
Where can I buy a toothbrush,
toothpaste, and a razor?
(The night before)
Oh, the toothpaste.
I forgot to bring
a toothbrush and toothpaste.
(He nonchalantly rinses his mouth
with water.)
(Feeling refreshed)
Are you looking for a brush?
(Right here.)
No, not that kind of a brush.
(A huge brush)
Does he only sell one?
(Luckily, he also sells small brushes.)
(He buys a toothbrush.)
(He also gets the toothpaste.)
A toothbrush and toothpaste cost a dollar.
(A toothbrush and toothpaste,
equivalent to 1 dollar)
Thank you.
Let's go.
Will this be enough fish
for our dinner later?
One bunch of fish.
Should we buy these too just in case?
(Well...)
Do you not like them?
No?
You don't like them?
What do you like?
Then what about these? Good?
What do you say? Good?
Okay. I'll buy them.
That many fish cost 10,000 ariaries.
(They cost about 3 dollars.)
They're cheap.
Okay?
(Spotting something)
Why are these sweet potatoes so big?
Check them out. They're sweet potatoes?
(Huge sweet potatoes from Madagascar)
This too. Yes.
(2 of the huge sweet potatoes
cost about 60 cents.)
The sweet potatoes...
(It's on the house.)
Okay.
They are the biggest sweet potatoes
I've seen in my life.
(Her generosity is befitting
of the huge sweet potatoes.)
(They're really done shopping
for groceries.)
(Oh, right!)
I almost forgot the most important one.
Well, where can I buy some liquor?
(It's that way.)
Let's go.
It could've been awful if I forgot.
We're having a party tonight.
We could have ended up having
only fish and sweet potatoes.
Okay. What's the total?
(They also buy liquor.)
I got them. Okay.
(They're finally done shopping.)
Let's go.
(They head over to Florant's house
for the dinner party.)
(Hello)
A photo.
Hey. Why are you...
(Is this the kid version of Yerpe?)
A photo.
(He twirls away.)
(They arrive at Florant's house.)
(The dinner is being prepared.)
Do you wear hats?
This is really rare.
It's a limited-edition hat
of a fashion brand...
a famous Korean rapper launched.
Do you want to put this on?
(Impressed)
You look like a rapper from Madagascar.
Do you like it? Do you want to keep it?
Thank you.
That's a really precious hat.
(Smiling)
Do you wear socks?
(Barefoot)
Okay.
I have a canoe. Do you want to go see it?
I want to show it to him.
- Your boat?
- Yes.
Okay. Let's go.
Did you make it?
- Yes.
- Gosh. Good.
He's got skills.
(How will the canoe he built look?)
(It's over there.)
That's the boat.
(Impressed)
Did you build this on your own?
(Florant built it solely on his own.)
(The craftsmanship is good enough that
he can even take it out to the water now.)
(He just has to paint it now.)
Did you name your boat?
Titiabasua?
Titiabasua? What does it mean?
It means "love for my family."
Then will you fish
and make a lot of money?
Yes.
(Let's see.)
Then...
why don't I...
You know, I'm an artist...
in Korea.
So...
I would like to draw something
on the boat for you.
I would like to wish you safety
on the water and bountiful catch of fish.
Can I draw you something?
- Yes.
- Are you cool with that?
I'll draw something cool tomorrow morning.
If you don't like it, you can cover it up.
(Laughing)
Then should I go and buy some paint?
Yes. Okay. Let's go.
Gosh. This place is so cool at night.
Do you have any design in mind?
A big whale.
- A big whale?
- Yes.
That's romantic.
(As they walk in the village...)
Hello.
Hello. Any paint?
- Paint?
- Paint.
I see. Are there any colors you want?
Green. What else?
(Yellow, green, white, and red)
Green, white, and red.
And black?
- Yes.
- That's black? You already picked it.
You're milking this chance.
Nice. I like your attitude.
That's 180,000 ariaries.
Hold on. How much is that in dollars?
That's about 50 dollars.
Okay.
(He purchases the paint
without bargaining the price.)
Loha, catch a lot of fish.
- Thank you.
No freebies?
Come on.
Give me one more brush as a freebie.
I'll give it to you next time
as a present.
Gosh. She's a good businesswoman.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you.
Let's go.
- Thank you.
(That's how they drew
the whale together on the boat.)
(Although they couldn't communicate
in the same language,)
(being with each other became
more natural than being alone.)
(As he rooted for Florant's future,)
(Kian84 drew a whale on the boat.)
That looks cute.
(Florant will be smiling
just like the whale on the boat.)
(After saying goodbye to Florant,)
(he came back to Morondava.)
(He united with the two brothers
he had missed.)
Why am I so happy to see you guys?
Nice.
(They are lifting
random items they see to work out.)
Two.
(Panting84)
(Feeling proud)
(After their intense workout
at the beach...)
Gosh. Look at him.
- Right.
- He elbowed the other kid.
(He approaches a kid.)
One.
Two. Okay.
No. That's one.
One.
(An enthusiastic student shows up.)
One. Hey.
One, two.
(The second student catches up fast.)
(Giggling)
Well done.
(The first student shows up again.)
(He's showing off his flexibility.)
How to...
(Let me join you.)
(They dive backward together.)
(Trying hard)
(They're loving it.)
Good.
(Sweet Dex is popular among kids.)
Gosh. The kids have well-defined abs.
- Good.
- Okay. Ready.
(It's time to go and see
the baobab trees.)
Gosh. This is nice.
Let's go.
(They will finally get to see
the long-awaitedbaobab trees in person.)
I'm really curious about the baobab trees.
I'm looking forward to them.
Should we guess the height?
Let's guess the height
of the longest tree.
- The longest tree...
- Then I'll go with 20m.
- I say 40m.
- I say 50m.
- Fifty? Gosh. That means...
- Well...
I bet they rarely die. They can live
for thousands of years and on.
Right.
(Should I have picked
a higher number then?)
Gosh.
(The mecca of baobab trees...)
(finally came into view.)
(The history for the thousands of years
is evident...)
(in the biggest habitat of baobab trees
in the world.)
(Every moment is accompanied
by a different view of Mother Nature.)
(And such beauty unfolds here.)
(Baobab Avenue)
- A photo. Yes.
- Should the three of us take a photo...
- before we go?
- Let's take a picture before we go.
- Excuse me. A picture, please.
- Can you take a picture of us?
- You should be in the middle.
- Okay.
Right here. The light is...
- I see. This way?
- Yes.
- Okay. This way.
- I see. This way.
(The three baobab-tree-loving brothers
are painted by the sunset.)
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- What?
- Sorry?
Are you actors?
- Well...
- Yes. He's like an actor.
- Yes.
- A Korean actor.
- Okay.
- Thank you. Where are you from?
I'm from Morondava. From here.
- Really? Okay.
- Morondava.
Are you a guide or just visiting here?
We work here.
Are you a movie actor?
No. He's a YouTuber. And then...
- YouTuber.
- A famous YouTuber.
We keep telling them
about each other's fame.
- He's famous.
- He's...
- He's famous in Korea.
- Yes.
- And he's famous on a streaming website.
- Really?
- No.
Yes. Really.
- You can find him on the website.
- Yes.
Is he famous? Your friend?
- He's so handsome.
- Very handsome.
- Is he an actor?
- He's a Spanish actor.
- A Spanish actor? Really?
- Spanish?
- A Spanish actor.
- Hello.
I work in Spain and Madagascar.
Are you from Spain?
Yes. My mother is from Spain,
and my father is from here.
- I see.
- I see. He's in his hometown.
Are you a famous man?
- I'm not famous. But I'm trying.
- When did it get turned off?
You're trying. I see. That's right.
How about this? Maybe,
after this video gets uploaded,
you'll be famous in Korea.
- Yes.
- Okay?
- Hello.
- Gosh. He knows Korean.
- Yes.
Correct.
So you do YouTube videos?
- Yes.
- He's a YouTuber.
A famous YouTuber.
- I want to see it.
- I'll show you. Okay.
- Yes. Show them.
- Yes.
I should make business cards
with the address for my channel.
I'm starting to make videos now.
- Really?
- Here in Madagascar.
What is... Could you type here?
- Okay.
(He shares his channel address
with the aspiring YouTuber.)
Pani Bottle is popular abroad.
And I. There's a space,
and then type "Bottle."
- "Bottle."
- Pani Bottle.
- On YouTube?
- Yes.
I see. People all over the world
love meeting celebrities.
- I think you are...
- Let's see.
- doing well on YouTube. Yes.
- Yes.
- Very handsome.
- Thank you.
- Do you have an Instagram page?
- Yes. I think so.
Okay. I'll follow you.
(I'm envious.)
Can we take a selfie?
- Yes. Sure.
- Sure. Yes.
(Recording a moment
with new friends on Baobab Avenue)
- Thank you.
Can you take another picture of us?
- The three of us together?
- One last picture.
(They take one more picture
before the sun goes down.)
Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
- Yes.
(They enjoyed the sunset on Baobab Avenue
with new friends.)
The sky looks beautiful.
- I think this is the view.
- Yes.
Gosh. This is nice.
(They're feeling sentimental.)
Gosh. The backlight and the trees...
Anyway, I think I won the bet.
- What bet?
- I said it was 20m.
- It's 30m tall.
- Gosh. It's only 20m tall.
- Just 20m?
- No.
- Kian84.
- We said it had to be the tallest one.
I said it had to be the tallest one.
My guess was 30m.
- The tallest one among here?
- It has to be over 30m.
But your guess was 40m. My guess was 50m.
(The three of them had a bet
on the height of the tallest tree.)
(He gave a moderate number.)
(Kian84 made a bold guess.)
(Dex made a reckless guess.)
- I think Pani Bottle won this bet.
- But...
- Let me win one bet.
- Pani Bottle.
It will be over 30m.
If it goes over 30m,
I'll accept my defeat.
Well, you don't have to.
But the fact is, it goes over 30m.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Who won and lost?
- Right.
- That's important.
I'm curious about the victor of this bet.
Then my guess was the closest
to the correct answer.
- Gosh. He's so stubborn. I'm out.
- Listen.
Then should we get going?
(They put an end to this meaningless
battle of knowledge.)
Gosh. This is nice.
(The three of them had to the campsite.)
Gosh, this place is nice.
We can go in that way.
(Pani Bottle guides them to the campsite.)
Wait. Do they sell the seeds
of baobab trees here?
It's 15,000 ariaries.
- It's 15,000 ariaries. That's cheap.
- That's cheap.
Actually...
Is this a baobab tree?
- Yes. It's a baobab tree.
- Really?
(He's the groundskeeper.)
(The seedlings for baobab trees)
How old are these baobab trees?
- Sir.
- "How old are these baobab trees?"
- They're three months old.
- Two?
(He kindly tells his answer
with his fingers.)
Then they must be 2,000 years old.
(What?)
(No. They're about 3 months old.)
Gosh. They are that old?
- If they're 2,000 years old,
- They are way too old.
- are they 100 million years old?
- I think there was a misunderstanding.
- Right.
- Let's get going.
- Hey, then...
how many generations of my family
must be around to see those trees?
(They are 2,000 years old by accident.)
(The night has come.)
(They're pitching the tents
to camp out for the night.)
Gosh.
Should I ask them to give me some water?
(Dex walks around the village
to get some water.)
Thank you.
(Thank you.)
(He was going to ask them
for some hot water.)
(But the family is already eating.)
Enjoy your food.
(Have a nice dinner.)
Gosh. They're having dinner.
I should go somewhere else.
Gosh. It's dinnertime.
Everyone is having food.
(He goes to a different house.)
- Hello.
You're the driver from earlier.
(Giddy-up!)
(It was the house of the ox cart's driver
from the afternoon.)
It's nice to see you here.
What's that?
(Rice)
(They haven't had dinner yet.)
I need hot water.
(Hot water)
(For this!)
Three.
(Please give me some water.)
(Okay.)
(Thanks to the water
that was as warm as his heart,)
(the three of them
got to have a warm meal.)
If you don't mind,
can I look around the house?
I'm just curious.
Can I take a look?
(This is Dex's first time
at a local family's house.)
I'm curious.
I need to take off my shoes here.
(It unexpectedly turns into
a Korean housewarming party.)
Thank you.
(He politely enters the house.)
(The trees and soil from Morondava
were used...)
(to make up the cozy house.)
This is nice.
I have a question.
I would like to know
how you start the fire.
Can you teach me how to start the fire?
Can I try it?
(Is there a traditional method
that shows the wisdom of their ancestors?)
(I got it.)
(Anticipating)
I see. You use a lighter.
(Civilization trumps
the wisdom of their ancestors.)
Well, I thought... A lighter.
- A lighter?
- Yes.
(- I also have that.
- A lighter is the best.)
That was a silly question.
I'm good then.
Yes. We now have smartphones.
I'm the fool for thinking
they would use a traditional method.
(The morning after camping
on Baobab Avenue)
Gosh. They're fighting.
- The cows are fighting.
- The cows?
(The two zebu cows are butting heads.)
Gosh, they're fighting.
- It sounded like a gourd breaking.
- The sound...
(Cracking)
- It sounds like something is cracking.
- Gosh.
The goats are watching them fight.
(The flock of goats came out to watch.)
- The goats.
- The goats too.
(It's fun to watch them in the front row.)
They look like cartoon characters.
(They're actively watching the fight.)
They're cheering for the cows.
(Let just any cow win.)
It's fun to watch fights.
Back in the day, people said that...
no one could stop angry oxen.
Gosh, look at their eyes.
(Those are definitely angry eyes.)
- Gosh. This is getting serious.
- Things are getting heated. Wait.
(Focused on the fight)
They're so strong.
Even if the victor
will end up with wounds.
Why are they fighting
this early in the morning?
"You teased me and called me a pig first."
Gosh. Come on.
- You guys are close. What are you doing?
- You're friends. Don't fight. Hey.
- Talk this out. Hey.
- Hey.
Our teacher will come soon.
Stop it already.
Hey, get the teacher.
Gosh. What are you doing?
(As the black cow stirs up the dust,)
(the black cow wins.)
It's over.
When he knew he lost,
he quickly accepted his defeat.
He's alone now.
All right. The black one won.
(The winning zebu cow hangs out
with the others.)
(They're done watching the fight
that stirred up the dust.)
- Let's clean up and get going.
- Yes.
- Let's hurry back.
- Okay.
(Baobab Avenue was filled
with intense memories.)
- Let's go.
All right.
(After returning
to the capital city, Antananarivo,)
(the exercisers of the pull-up bars
welcomed them.)
(They headed to the mecca
of muscular men, the gym.)
(They enter the gym.)
Are you a bodybuilder?
- A bodybuilder?
- This place is packed.
- This is so impressive.
- Are the muscles natural?
- This is firmly fixed.
Are they natural?
- Natural muscles?
- Those are natural muscles indeed.
- His muscles look great.
(It's indeed the country of muscles.)
(Staring)
Should I climb up to that point?
(What does he want to do?)
Is this safe?
(Will he climb the ladder?)
(The ladder goes up all the way
to the 2nd floor of the building.)
If you do that, you'll get hurt.
I'll only climb up to that point.
Just a little bit.
I can't go all the way up.
Be careful.
(Charismatic Pani
bravely goes to the ladder.)
(Staring)
Gosh, hey. Be careful. Watch his legs.
(Pulling back)
(Laughing)
(He's trying to lift his body
with his soft arms.)
(Shaking)
(Soft Tofu Bottle falls down
without any resistance.)
That was really tough.
(Watch this.)
(The local training helper demonstrates.)
(Climbing up)
This is crazy.
This is the world of monsters.
(Just passing the entrance
is tough in Madagascar.)
I'll only watch them.
I won't get cheeky here.
What's the weight?
Each one weighs 10kg.
So the total is 60kg.
Maybe, it's about 70kg.
- It's 70kg.
- It's 70kg. Okay.
- Kian84.
- The fight of men has begun.
- Darn it. Hey.
- We can't lose to them.
- Are you sure?
We must show it to them.
(They can't lose this battle
of muscular strength.)
- This weighs 70kg?
- It weighs 70kg.
(Let's go.)
(Gosh, Kian84.)
(Surprised)
This weighs 70kg?
(Clenching his teeth)
(Screaming)
- It's too heavy.
- Hey, this isn't 70kg!
(Laughing)
(Chuckling)
- Let me try it.
- Okay.
(Suit yourself.)
Will he show us?
(The eldest brother tries it out
since he's at the gym.)
Great.
(Can he lift weights?)
- One.
- Are you ready?
(Lifting)
Hey, he can do it.
(Impressed)
(The old guy
is doing better than expected.)
Five, six, seven.
(He's pretty good.)
(Surprised)
- He's gotten stronger as he got older.
- Six, seven...
(Lifting with all his might)
(Si Eon grew tougher as he got older.)
(Clapping)
You still got it.
(Feeling proud)
(Jealous84 is motivated
to work out harder thanks to him.)
Let's go over there.
- Should we stay out?
- Gosh, my back.
- We're not going to work out.
- Let's sit down.
I went at it too hard.
(Republic of Korea in Madagascar?)
So this is the airport terminal.
Gosh. This airport terminal reminds me...
of the terminal I went
in order to visit my relatives in Yeoju.
It reminds me of the bus terminal
in Icheon, Gyeonggi Province.
- You're bringing up Yeoju again.
- There he goes again with Yeoju.
He mentioned
his relatives' house early this time.
There were traces of Yeoju
all over the world.
(Even when he came to Antananarivo
for the first time...)
This place is just like Yeoju.
(he saw the vast rice paddies of Yeoju.)
When my relatives had a block party,
everyone in the village
came over like this.
We cooked a whole pig.
The elders came together and had a meal.
(You guys did this too?)
This culture was around
when I was in elementary school.
- In Yeoju?
- In the countryside. Yes, in Yeoju.
(He was walking along the path
with the others in the countryside.)
No way.
There was Yeoju...
in Madagascar.
(He mentions Yeoju again.)
(The atmospheres of Korea
were hidden all over Madagascar.)
"Youn's Restaurant?"
(He spotted a Korean restaurant
with a familiar name in Antananarivo.)
What? There must be
a Korea-related building here.
What is this?
"Trinity."
(Why is there a Korean flag?)
"Dreaming Library."
I see. Someone from Korea
must have built a library here.
- How old is this car?
- But this is cool.
Isn't this such a classic car?
(Even when they were going
to the University of Antananarivo...)
There's a Korean car
with "beginner driver" sign.
(A familiar "beginner driver" sign)
Gosh, isn't that Mashimaro?
That's Korean. It must have been
imported from Korea.
(They followed traces of Korea...)
(to University of Antananarivo's...)
(library of books
about the Korean language.)
I've never seen this before.
- A workbook for proficiency in Korean.
- What's that?
"Listen to the following
and choose the appropriate response."
- Okay.
- "Is the apple good?"
Number one, "There's no apple."
Number two, "The apple is good."
Number three, "The apple is expensive."
Number four, "I like apples."
"Is the apple good?
Yes, the apple is good." Number two.
- Number two.
- I see.
(He's proud of his fluent Korean.)
(He is now in Teacher Dex mode.)
(Look who we have here.)
(He approaches a student
who is studying hard.)
What year are you in?
- What year of university are you in?
- I'm in...
First year? Second year?
Third year? Fourth year?
- Year?
- Yes.
- Of university.
- University?
- I'm in my 2nd year.
- Your 2nd year?
- Yes.
- I see.
Your Korean is great.
- A little. It's not great.
- How...
How many years
have you been studying Korean?
- Two years.
- Really?
But you're very good.
You should visit Korea sometime.
Yes, I want to visit in the future.
- You do?
- Yes.
Can I take a look at
what you've been studying?
- Sure. I study...
- Yes.
Studying Korean...
What's difficult about studying Korean?
- It's easy at first. Yes.
- I see.
But there is so much grammar.
- There's so much grammar?
- Yes.
Well, I'm Korean,
so I'll help you out with
the things you find difficult.
- Okay.
- Show me.
- Okay. This is my book.
- Right.
This one is a bit tricky.
- It's "eunikka" and "haeseo."
- I see.
How are they different?
So, "eunikka" means...
(He's expectant.)
"Eunikka" means...
"myself." "Eunikka."
- "Eunikka."
- Yes. But...
with "haeseo," it's more...
(Brain freeze)
like you're talking about something
that's very close, a bit far.
You say to a friend,
"Because I had lunch,"
or "Since I had lunch..."
- "I feel sleepy."
- Did that help you understand?
- Yes, thank you.
No problem.
So which part are you studying right now?
(He's flustered.)
Right here. I think that's it.
- Thank you.
- Good.
(The two arrived in Antsirabe first,
and they are having dinner.)
What's this?
It's called romazava, and it has spinach,
- and they used chicken here.
- I see.
To compare it with Korean food,
it's like...
doenjang jjigae or kimchi jjigae.
(He tastes a spoonful of it.)
This is just like siraegi gukbap.
It's as if I'm eating Korean food
all of a sudden.
(Let's talk about Madagascan food.)
This is just like sungnyung.
- That's interesting.
- It was exactly Korean food.
(Even the food they eat
on special occasions...)
(was like the Madagascan version
of the meat stew we eat in Korea.)
(It's fun running into Madagascan versions
of Korean food.)
This tastes totally the same as gukbap.
(He digs into the Madagascan gukbap.)
(Slurping)
Gosh, I...
can't help but mix in rice.
(He can't help but mix in rice.)
(The rice makes it taste
even more like Korean food.)
I'm so satisfied with this.
It's so satisfying for me too.
(He's even holding the bowl up
and gathering all the remaining food...)
(to finish it off.)
That was good. I'm full.
This was exactly like Korean food.
(All together rather than alone)
(At Morondava beach,)
(the three Madagascar brothers
had an epic swimming match.)
(They're taking a minute to freshen up.)
(Pani Bottle is freshening up
his stomach with a coconut.)
(Dex is freshening up
by readjusting his swim trunks.)
Pani Bottle, this is insane.
Take a look at this.
What's up?
What's this?
(A fist full of sand came out
of his swim trunks.)
- You're not pooping, are you?
- No.
Wait, there's a whole lot of it in here.
A whole bunch... It keeps coming out.
(Stay tuned while we find something more
aesthetically pleasing for you to watch.)
(He's enjoying some spare time against
an aesthetically pleasing backdrop.)
(He's not day-drinking.)
(Taking a sip)
I think this will taste good.
Gosh, that's a great idea.
(He's a true eating show content creator.)
This is so refreshing.
The ice makes the orange juice
taste completely different.
I didn't realize how precious ice was.
(Gosh, that's cold.)
I'm drinking way too much
liquid fructose today.
(He's worried about his health.)
(But he's still pouring down
so much liquid fructose.)
Want some?
No, you have it.
- Gosh, let's go.
- All right.
What is this?
What's wrong?
- What's that?
- Goodness.
Oh, my gosh.
What on earth did you eat, Kian84?
It's like seeing llamas poop.
Llamas just drop poop, you know.
- Goodness.
- This is what he meant.
You only had a little, though.
I thought I was a pooping elephant.
(Dex was almost like an elephant.)
Shall we go?
Let's go.
Do you want to look around
and see what they have?
Hey, I need cola.
I needed a comb.
(He found a store that sells
traditional combs.)
I should get one in black.
Gosh, this is nice.
- Capri?
- This?
(The two older brothers
stopped by a snack bar...)
(to buy drinks and snacks.)
This is...
the Morondava airport lounge.
Are these chocolate wafers?
These are barbecue-flavored.
These are the chips
Pani Bottle kept talking about.
I'll give it a taste.
- Do you like chips, Pani Bottle?
- Yes.
- Salty ones, not sweet ones.
- Why is my face like this?
What's wrong with it?
Don't you think
something's wrong with my face?
You look handsome to me.
What? My face? Or your face?
You're so mean.
Isn't he being really mean?
I wasn't...
You're mean.
What are you going to do
when we get to Antananarivo?
They say it's election season
in Madagascar.
Do you want to go see
the election campaigns of Madagascar?
- Like go and campaign with them?
- Yes.
You?
(Laughing)
(Since their trip to South America,)
(Kian84 has had a strange bucket list.)
(I want to come with you.)
- I want to come with you.
- You want to come?
I should come with you.
(Pani Bottle always tags along,
for some strange reason.)
(They threw Kian84 a birthday party
at a restaurant in Antananarivo.)
(The three got drunk on excitement
and lost themselves in the songs.)
Gosh, singing is fun.
- One more?
- One more.
- This is going to be the last one.
- The way I see it...
- "Running in the Sky," is the last one.
- It's really the last song.
("Running in the Sky" by Lee Juck)
I'll only sing the first verse.
(Expectant)
Yeah.
(My heart pounded)
Park Jae Hwan!
(Pani Bottle's real name is Park Jae Han.)
(Someone was chasing after me)
(At the edge of the black cliff)
(He's serious.)
(There was nowhere else
to put my foot down)
(I kept getting choked up)
(So I desperately repeated your name)
(In my ears rang)
(Your voice full of warmth)
(That was my salvation)
(They're cheering him on
with their chopsticks.)
(I'm running in the dry sky)
(He's humming along.)
(If that means you will hug me
in your arms)
(I don't care my body might break)
(Even if I fly too close to the sun)
(He's humming along.)
(And both my legs melt away)
(My heart will run toward your heart)
(I'll keep running to you forever)
- I thought you were Lee Juck.
- I'm only going to sing the first verse.
(They quickly end the song.)
- That was great.
- You're Pa Juck.
- Pa Juck.
- That was great.
Pa juck.
(Si Eon and Pani Bottle are
exploring the streets of Antananarivo.)
Gosh, this is amazing.
Let's check out the food.
I did want to try this one.
I'll try it for you.
Okay.
- Hello.
(He's ordering the food with the excuse
of trying it out for Si Eon.)
- It's 2,000 ariaries.
- It's 2 dollars?
- No, it's 50 cents.
- What?
- It's 50 cents.
(She's preparing
the food for him to taste.)
It looks so delicious, though,
don't you think?
(Sure)
I'm supposed to
mix everything together, right?
What?
It tastes just like a salad.
Do you know those crab salads?
- It tastes like that.
- I feel like I'm watching his YouTube.
(He starts to taste it earnestly.)
(Eating)
(He eats very well.)
(He's exercising
through masticatory movement.)
Okay.
(He finishes one bowl alone.)
(They returned to
the accommodation briefly to refresh.)
(Dex is showering.)
(His target)
It looks tasty.
(Pani Baguette eats a baguette first.)
You eat very well.
The food here is delicious.
You're born to travel.
(A travel YouTuber calmly
prepares for an eating show.)
Is the ice cream tasty?
- Have one. It's delicious.
- It's not sherbet, right?
No, it isn't.
- That's a shame.
- It's made of milk fat.
I don't need to eat it. Help yourself.
(He resumes eating the baguette
after refusing an ice cream.)
(Chewing vigorously)
There's Pringles.
Oh, it isn't. It's a different brand.
(He eats his baguette first.)
(Stands up)
(He approaches the others quietly...)
(and naturally steals their snack.)
(Having a bite of a salty snack)
(Having a bite of carbohydrates)
(Amazing collaboration
of carbohydrates and salt)
What is this? Is this a soda?
(A soda?)
- What?
- It's a coconut yogurt.
- Oh, my.
- I'll eat it.
(Drinking)
(After drinking,)
(he continues to fuel himself
with carbohydrates.)
(He finished showering.)
- Dex.
- Yes.
- Have one ice cream.
- Okay.
(Moisturizing)
(I'm having water too.)
(Rummaging)
I'm in trouble. It's so delicious.
(His appetite is speeding up very fast.)
(Licking)
(He starts his 2nd round
with an ice cream.)
(He even consumes dessert heartily.)
(10 minutes ago)
What time shall we depart?
After ten minutes.
- Ten?
- Yes.
I have ten minutes more.
(I still have 10 minutes to eat.)
You're having your lunch here.
(Clean plate)
Right?
(His lunch is over.)
(Maybe it's good to be alone sometimes?)
(Before meeting at Antsirabe...)
(Pani Bottle suggested traveling solo.)
I agree.
(The next morning)
(They're asleep
in their separate bedrooms.)
(Dex woke up the earliest.)
I slept so well in the hotel.
I'm going to eat the hotel breakfast.
It's my first time
in Adventure by Accident.
(The first hotel breakfast footage
in Madagascar.)
The hotel breakfast looks like this.
One omelet, please.
- Omelet.
I was greedy so I asked for 4 eggs.
They're all in.
(Morning protein)
This looks tasty.
Isn't this a chocolate-flavored cereal?
Dex.
(Pani Bottle came down to eat breakfast
as soon as he woke up.)
Did you have a good sleep?
I fainted.
Would...
I be able to eat anything?
I'm still full.
- You don't need to eat.
- Yes.
- I'll have a cup of coffee.
- I see.
My breakfast is simple.
(A simple big bowl of coffee)
(Since a big bowl of coffee is
too simple...)
The weather is very good.
(He has one bite
with an excuse for good weather.)
(Looking around)
(Let's see.)
(He has a yogurt too.)
(He's a typical Korean.)
(He eats a simple yogurt too.)
(Dex eats his omelet too.)
(This is Pani Bottle's minimalist meal.)
- Hello.
- Good morning.
(Kian84 joins after getting ready.)
Hello. Gosh, it looks delicious.
You can choose how many eggs you want.
- Did they cook the omelet for you?
- Yes.
I need to take a shower and leave.
Help yourself. I'll get going.
- What?
- I don't have much time.
You don't want to be with me
even a little?
- There're only two seats.
- What?
- Okay. Let's go.
- See you later.
- Okay.
I'll have a cup of coffee.
(Kian84 chooses
to have a morning coffee too.)
- Did you sleep well?
- I slept too well.
I had a great meal.
(Stands up)
- Hey.
- See you at Antsirabe.
Everyone is leaving after I sat down.
(It's so fun to tease him.)
Come safely.
- Okay.
- Come faster.
(He's somewhat lonely.)
See you at the hotel alive.
- I'll call you.
- Okay.
(They start traveling solo.)
What's up?
Hey.
Do you know any traditional shops?
What?
I need a knife.
- What?
- A knife.
Do you know? A knife.
(Slicing)
I want to buy a knife.
(He's confused by a foreigner
searching for a knife.)
- I think he's looking for a bag.
- A bag?
Is it over there?
- A knife shop.
- Yes.
- You can...
- Ammonite.
(He has an ammonite.)
No, ammonite. Sorry.
(He tries a new tactic
to make sales by rhyming.)
- Sorry.
- It's a good price.
- No.
- It's metal iron.
- I don't need it.
- Lucca stone.
- I want a knife.
- Yes.
(It's there.)
- Over there?
- Yes.
(Buy this first.)
I'm so sorry.
But good price or no money to buy.
- But I love you. It's all lies.
- No.
This isn't easy.
Can you come together?
(He asks the boy for guidance.)
How old are you?
I'm 29.
(Instead of telling his age,
the boy guides him to somewhere.)
Here?
Oh, this way?
Okay. Let's go.
(Dex follows him.)
A knife.
This is a hotel.
No, a knife.
(He asked for a knife,
but the boy guided him to a hotel.)
(It's inside.)
They're not the right people.
- No.
- No?
Okay. Thank you.
Bye.
We were looking for...
different things,
so we said goodbye.
I'll travel alone.
(He searches alone after accepting
that they can't communicate.)
Hello.
(Is he the first Korean to meet
in Madagascar?)
(Perhaps?)
Hello.
Are you Korean?
No. I'm Chinese.
Oh, no. It's okay.
I just have a question.
So I want to buy...
a knife from Madagascar.
Where is the shop for it? Do you know?
(I don't know.)
He doesn't know. Okay. Bye.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
Gosh. It's not easy.
I think today will be difficult.
(While he was struggling
to buy Pani Bottle's present...)
It's a bummer.
(Pani Bottle starts traveling solo too.)
(Oh, my goodness)
When the market opens, it's spectacular.
An observatory is not needed here.
I can just watch it here.
The whole hillside road is a market.
(Beach umbrellas lined up
along the slope.)
The market is so huge.
I'm not sure where to find it.
They're opening up now.
There's a slipper.
(Pani Bottle is here to buy new slippers.)
Hello.
This looks nice.
(He likes this pair of slippers.)
Thirty thousand?
It's 9 dollars. Quite expensive.
(He tries to haggle.)
No? Okay.
(He gets declined.)
Sorry.
(He turns his back.)
(Hey, wait.)
Twenty.
(He succeeds in bargaining
to 20,000 ariaries.)
Okay.
(Bargaining looks the same
in every country.)
(It's cute.)
Okay.
(He buys a pair of slippers
for 6 dollars.)
- Thank you.
- Yes.
Okay. Bye.
(With his new slippers,)
(he walks to a sunglass stall.)
(Trying to choose one)
(He carefully selects items
at the market.)
There's no mirror.
(She finds it fascinating
to see foreigners shopping.)
This is nice.
(This pair of sunglasses he chose here...)
(Depending on the viewer,)
His glasses make him look like a fly.
(it becomes a fly costume,)
Hello, Robin?
He looks like a successful
businessman in Africa.
(or it becomes an item
of a successful businessman.)
It's like "Casino."
(How much is it?)
(It's 15,000 Ariary.)
It's reasonable.
(Searching)
(A pair of fly sunglasses
of a successful businessman: 5 dollars)
Thank you.
I don't need to haggle
if it's 15,000 ariaries.
So how much is it?
About 3 to 4 dollars?
Antananarivo never disappoints.
They don't overprice to foreigners.
(Pani Bottle heads to Antsirabe.)
(The taxi stops at a rest area.)
Is it a rest area?
It's quite different
from what I had imagined.
Can we eat here?
- Yes.
- Eat.
(Can we eat something here?)
(I can't miss this chance.)
(Hello)
(He gets off making a groan.)
I'm hungry.
(Give me this one.)
(He chooses one cheese ball.)
- Five thousand ariaries.
- Oh, 5,000 ariaries.
- It's 5,000 ariaries.
(Together with the cheese ball,)
Yes, one.
- One?
- Yes, one.
(he adds another snack.)
Okay.
(He pays 4,000 ariaries
which is around 1.3 dollars.)
Chicken.
(This one?)
There's its head too. My goodness.
Wait.
My goodness. I thought it was the feet.
(Laughing)
I'll take this one.
(Chicken without a head)
(A piece of chicken is 2,000 ariaries.)
Okay.
Bye.
(He buys a few snacks.)
I'm starving.
(He goes to eat.)
A sausage?
(It's a restaurant that sells
hand-made sausages.)
How much is it?
(5,000 ariaries)
I think she means 5,000 ariaries.
(He enters after checking the price.)
(What is this?)
- Lasage?
- Lasa Rianada.
(If you don't know, try it.)
It's okay.
Give me this and this
together with the sausage.
I'll take a seat.
(For a heavy-eating customer,)
(she prepares the food quickly.)
It's a convenient...
amount to eat on the go.
The sausage...
(He starts his simple meal.)
looks primitive.
It's super tasty.
It's grilled very well.
(The local food suits his taste again.)
They won't leave me, right?
(Reading the room)
(Being a meerkat)
I can't focus on the meal as I'm worried
if they'll leave without me.
(But his mouth is straightforward.)
(Sausage over rice:
6,000 ariaries which is around 2 dollars)
- Thank you.
- Thank you. Bye.
(He returns after filling
his stomach full.)
My goodness.
Is it okay to eat the chicken here?
(I'll have my dessert now.)
(Taking it out)
(He takes a bite.)
It's delicious. It's grilled well.
It tastes somewhat like a fried yakgwa.
My favorite chicken breast part.
(Chicken breast: tastes like yakgwa)
I was shocked to see the chicken head.
(Even though the chicken
tastes like yakgwa,)
(it's delicious.)
Oh, protein.
(Is he local?)
(Taking out something)
Holy cheese ball.
(Would you like some?)
(He doesn't refuse.)
(Eating)
(It's tasty.)
It's stimulating.
(He eats the cheese balls
as if someone's chasing him.)
(Licking his fingers)
(He wraps it up by licking his fingers.)
(The professional traveler has finished
his satisfying meal.)
(Zoning out)
I want a baguette.
With a slice of cheese on top.
(His favorite food of all is
always baguette.)
(At Antananarivo, after two days)
(After finishing the university tour,)
(Pani Bottle was heading
to the animal sanctuary.)
My goodness.
(He found a hair salon.)
Shall I cut my hair?
It's time for me to trim.
Hello.
(Can you cut my hair?)
(The hair salon only has
children customers.)
Maybe it's only for kids.
We'll find another one on the way, right?
(Adult Pani Bottle is
looking for a hair salon for adults.)
The sausage looks delicious.
They fry it.
(They look tasty.)
(He doesn't get distracted
by the sausages.)
(He looks for a hair salon.)
Wait!
Missy Umban.
(Can I cut my hair here?)
(Yes, you can.)
How much is it?
(It's written there.)
(How much is it to have a haircut
in Madagascar?)
It's cheap.
(It's 2,000 Ariary
which is around 60 cents.)
- Hello.
- Welcome.
It should be fine, right?
(Beeping)
Why can I hear chicks?
(He enters the hair salon
with welcoming beeping.)
I need to trim my hair.
Will it be okay?
Is this price correct?
Yes. If it's 2,000 ariaries,
it's around 60 cents.
It's a haircut worth 60 cents.
There are many people behind me.
They're here to see me have a haircut.
(Are you going to cut your hair?)
Yes, in Madagascar style.
- Please cut.
- Yes?
Cut his hair like mine.
I'm going for the Madagascar style.
(Go away.)
(The hairstylist chases them away.)
(I'll do it my way.)
I have no idea,
but I think it's going well.
(He starts cutting in Madagascar style.)
I feel good. He's bold.
(- Is it good?
- It's good!)
(His hair is getting trimmed boldly.)
The more shorter my side hair is,
the more convenient.
(His back hair gets shorter too.)
(The top of his hair gets shorter too.)
(He's changing into Madagascar style.)
Why are they looking at me?
I'm just here to have a haircut.
But everyone's watching.
All passers-by are looking at me now.
(What's going on?)
Why are they laughing? I'm very curious.
(His back of his head is charming.)
I don't think I look that funny.
(Is it weird?)
I think it's fine. He's doing a good job.
Shabby places have good skills.
(The hairdresser's skill
looks professional.)
It looks clean. It's cooling.
It's cooling.
(Make him feel cool!)
(He takes out a new tool.)
(No way. This is...)
(A barbershop razor?)
(Excited)
Foreign hair salons shave your beard
when you cut your hair. It's nice.
(He gets excited to get his beard shaved
which is unexpected.)
(He makes his sideburns sharp.)
It's a full service.
(He makes his back hair clean too.)
His razor...
(Sharpening the lines)
It's so good.
(It's very nice.)
- Do you like it?
- Yes.
(Front hair)
(Side hair)
(His haircut and his shaving are done.)
Thank you.
He cut very well.
This is the price, right?
- Yes.
- Okay.
(Sixty cents)
Oh, my gosh. It's 60 cents.
(Amazing)
(Clapping)
(Congratulations!)
(He just had a haircut, but everyone is
congratulating and supporting him.)
My goodness.
It was a good deal.
Thank you.
(Bangs his head)
(He shakes hands with his fans too.)
Why?
I just had a haircut.
Honestly,
I thought my hair would look funny.
But it looks good and clean.
(And...)
(he expresses how satisfied he is again.)
I'm good.
(Showering with bottled water)
(A manly man from Korea?)
(Their hearts are fluttering.)
It's refreshing.
(It's thrilling!)
(With all eyes on him,)
(the cost-effective superstar
is leaving unhurriedly.)
(Welcome, My Brother)
By the way,
aren't you guys expecting a guest?
- I...
- I think there will be a guest.
- If you go to a baobab tree,
- Yes.
you'll see Si Eon.
- Hanging on the tree?
- Yes.
- I think there will be something.
- Isn't he doing a drama?
- It's over.
- Is it?
It's perfect.
Is Dex here?
(The next day,
under the baobab tree where they'll camp)
He's not here yet.
There might be someone inside the tent.
(He suddenly has a weird feeling.)
(Approaching)
(Swinging)
Is it perhaps...
Si Eon?
(He carefully checks if he's there.)
Si Eon.
(Empty)
(His guess is wrong.)
He wouldn't come here.
"He wouldn't come here."
(That's true.)
(That's how Kian84 forgot about Si Eon.)
(But several days later,)
(he arrived in Madagascar.)
(He's still in full combat gear.)
Finally, I'm in Madagascar.
The country of penguins.
- The home of hip-hop.
- Right.
(There's nothing right
about his knowledge.)
Welcome to Madagascar.
Madagascar.
(He was given money for a trip.)
Do I get less because I arrived late?
(He got 100 dollars per day,
which is 400 dollars in total.)
Four hundred won?
It's only 400 won?
(Again, it's 400 dollars.)
I...
came almost at the end.
So I think this will be enough.
Let me exchange the money first.
Hi.
Four hundred.
(This is 400 dollars. Please exchange it.)
I got 1,688,000 Korean won.
(He got a roll of bills.)
(He feels pressured for no reason.)
(He's feeling the Madagascan air
outside the airport.)
It's much better than I thought.
(The first impression is good.)
(Looking around)
(He's going
to the center of Antananarivo.)
Gosh, it's Tiburon.
I think it's Tiburon Turbulence.
(An old Korean sports car
he found in another country)
Santa Fe and Grace.
(You can commonly see
Korean second-hand cars in Madagascar.)
I see many Korean cars.
It kind of feels like Korea.
Korea used to look like this.
(It looks familiar,
including the cars and the paddies.)
Now, I came...
to a market in Madagascar.
(He came to a market
with an interesting sense of familiarity.)
It's my cup of tea.
Hi.
(He was a city man with his guard on.)
I feel more comfortable as I've been to
other countries a few times.
(He's back as a traveler
who can enjoy the journey.)
(This one)
(He happily greets the helicopter guy
on the street as well.)
There's something
I really wanted to do in Africa.
I'm looking for it.
(Si Eon's Africa bucket list)
I really wanted to try cornrows.
(Cornrow hairstyle)
- Hi.
It's a baby.
Cute.
I'm hair.
(I'm hair.)
(He wants to experience
the local culture.)
How much is it?
Cornrows.
Same hair with you.
Yes.
(Okay)
(He sits down after making a request.)
I'm finally doing it.
(She's prepping his hair carefully.)
I'm worried I might lose hair.
(Don't worry, mister.)
(She starts braiding it.)
(Thrilled)
Oh, my gosh.
No hair.
(She's making ridges without hesitation.)
A mirror?
(An interim check)
(Is he laughing because he's satisfied?)
Oh, my gosh.
(What do you think
of the Madagascan hairstyle, Korean?)
This is not what I imagined.
I thought I would look so cool.
Like those hip-hop artists in Hollywood.
(He can't get close to his dream.)
(It's almost finished.)
No hair.
(Laughing)
(Half nervous, half excited)
(The local swag look is completed.)
(After transforming like that,)
(he sneaked into the accommodation
where the younger ones are staying.)
I think it's going to be hot and dusty.
What's this?
(Without being suspected by anyone,)
- What's this?
- My gosh!
(he surprised them successfully.)
(Even his best friend of 10 years...)
(and his travel buddy in Latin America
are shocked.)
- What's this?
- My gosh!
(Si Eon's surprise appearance)
I knew it.
- I made it.
- But...
I made it.
He's a good actor.
(All brothers are finally here.)
(The 4 Madagascar Brothers...)
(had a college tour with Generation MZ,)
(had a tear-jerking birthday party,)
(and went through many hardships.)
(And they got to Nosy Be.)
(They went to a grocery store
before taking a ship.)
- So this is it.
- Yes.
Okay. Here, we'll buy things
before going to the port.
Okay.
A supermarket in Nosy Be. A big bazaar.
It's a grocery store.
It has everything.
Should I get this?
I'll carry it.
(They got a cart.)
(I can't believe it.)
I can't believe it.
There are many things that look delicious.
Finally, it's our last shopping.
Brush every day.
- Brush.
(Are you guys doing well?)
Hey, how about this one?
- You guys like it.
- Nice.
(I got something you like.)
Okay. Corn.
And the pasta sauce you like.
- Let's get pasta sauce.
- Here.
Should I get something
that looks like French?
- Yes. Let's get the French one.
- "Tomato."
Si Eon, let me quiz you.
What are the essential items to survive?
- Pani Bottle, you can answer too.
- Water.
- Water. Fire.
- Fire.
How about tools?
- A knife.
- The tool you need the most to survive.
- Is this difficult?
- As expected, you're a soldier teacher.
Is this hard to guess?
(He feels good anyway.)
When you sleep
in the same room with someone,
I guess it makes the bond stronger
even between guys.
I think we have a firm friendship.
And there's a very strong bond between us.
They have pork belly here.
This is pork belly.
Pig.
(They got a big chunk of pork belly
they will eat on the island.)
(Is it pork?)
(Yes)
- Is this...
- Chocolate rolls.
It's what Dex eats all the time.
There are many things to eat.
Jam.
"Madagascan number one."
We're going to spend
all the money we got here.
- Snacks.
- Okay.
We still have some money left.
Pick a snack you want.
It's cheap.
What's this?
Why did you get two toothpastes?
- Why did you get two?
- I'll use them.
I use a lot of toothpaste.
I use so much toothpaste
that I can get two.
- Get them.
- Okay.
- I just pour it in my mouth.
Let's go then.
(The cart is full.)
- Let's go.
- We don't have time.
- Go.
(They got a lot of items.)
We might not have enough money.
Roughly,
- it's going to be 170 dollars.
- About 170 dollars?
It's going up.
I should take out the money.
(Let me see. How much is this?)
How much is it already?
It's 48,000 ariaries?
- Is it pork belly?
- Yes, it's pork belly.
That's 60,000 ariaries.
Now it's 70,000 ariaries
and 90,000 ariaries.
It's become 100,000 ariaries.
No, that's...
(Stop. Are you trying to sneak that out?)
(He almost shoplifted.)
- I'm sorry.
- She caught you sneaking that out.
- That's 100,000 ariaries.
- It's 120,000 ariaries.
It's 130,000 ariaries.
It's 160,000 ariaries.
Two, four, six...
- Twenty thousand.
- That's 210,000 ariaries.
Thirty thousand.
- Goodness.
- Ninety thousand.
That's about 70 dollars.
- Let's bag them.
- This bread is still warm.
- Where are the croissants?
- I got them.
(Tzuyang Bottle makes sure
they've got the bread.)
- Thank you.
- Let's go.
- Yes.
- Bye.
We don't get a watermelon? Do we just go?
- Watermelons?
- Yes.
Let's get some if we see them on the way.
Okay.
(Getting on the tuk-tuks
that were waiting for them)
- We have a little more to go.
- Okay.
(Off to the harbor)
The fruits here look fresh.
Mangoes.
- Buy some.
- I'll buy some with the change.
- Mangoes, please.
- Mangoes?
(They can't miss mangoes.)
It's sad that I can't take them to Korea.
Is that a coconut?
- Is that a papaya?
- How much are they?
Shall we try that?
I was wondering what you were doing.
You were buying fruit.
(They buy large fruit
without knowing what it is.)
- What is that?
- We don't know.
- Let's go.
- We've got a lot of food now.
We have enough now.
We bought too much. Gosh.
How long will it take from here?
(Now they're off to the harbor
to take a boat for real!)
We'll be there soon. We're close.
It's so cool.
It looks cooler
because it's a wooden boat.
- I know. I like how quiet it is.
- Yes.
I think I like wooden boats
more than steel ones.
So here we've got food.
There's some bread for you too.
- Breakfast?
- It's free.
- Thank you.
- Help yourself.
- Okay. Thank you.
- I've been so hungry.
- I see.
- Shall we try some?
- Let's eat.
This looks good.
Is it bread?
It's good.
- The jam is good.
- I knew they'd have a jam.
It's a little spicy.
It's a little weird that bread is spicy.
(The bread they bought at the supermarket)
(Brewing coffee)
- That's coffee.
- Is that so?
Is that coffee?
- My goodness.
- He's brewing coffee himself.
(That's the way to go.)
- That's drip coffee.
- That's amazing.
He's using a filter like that.
- Is that a filter?
- Yes.
It smells so good.
- Ethiopia is famous for its coffee.
- Yes.
Malagasy coffee must be good food.
- That is...
- That coffee...
(Can we try it?)
Can I have a cup of coffee?
Thank you.
(Have some coffee.)
Thank you so much.
(Slurping)
It's so delicious.
- Delicious? Okay. Cheers.
- Cheers.
(Do you like it? Then, cheers.)
(On a boat with a sea breeze blowing)
Si Eon, the coffee is so good.
The coffee is good.
- The coffee?
- It's so tasty.
Are these coffee beans from Madagascar?
- Yes.
- From Madagascar?
It's good coffee.
You're drinking a local coffee
from Madagascar.
They used coffee beans from Madagascar.
- It's delicious.
- It's good.
The coffee is amazing.
It's even better than the coffee
from a global coffee chain.
This is what delicious coffee tastes like.
(After drinking a dreamy coffee)
Shall we open the papaya?
(The questionable fruit was a papaya.)
Si Eon, let's open it and make chocolate.
Make chocolate?
- Chocolate?
- How do you do that?
Papaya is the main ingredient
in chocolate.
Isn't that coconuts?
It's papaya.
Papaya is the main ingredient.
Chocolate is not made from papaya.
Is that so?
Dex.
- What happened to you, Dex?
- What is made of papaya?
- I think he got struck by lightning.
- He sure did yesterday.
- It must have struck him slightly.
- Yes.
- It must have gone past him.
- It went past him.
Gosh.
(Suddenly wiping his face
with a wet tissue)
How refreshing.
(Let me help you.)
Look how Dex is wiping my face.
- What?
- Has he done it for you?
He won't text you
once we go back to Korea.
(Does he feel guilty?)
- Here we go again.
- Jealous84.
Blow your nose.
(Blow your nose, Si Eon.)
He's being nice to you for the last time.
He's nice before saying goodbye.
(I'm jealous.)
Let me see.
How come nothing sticks to your skin
whatever you apply?
Apply some of it to your neck.
Wait. Your philtrum.
- It's not sticking here.
- He's getting so much love.
- It looks like you're teasing him.
- What is this?
- Should I clean your sunglasses?
- Okay.
Dex, do you like me or Si Eon?
What are you talking about?
Give me your sunglasses.
What?
Give me yours.
Si Eon, me or Dex?
Dex.
Oh, dear.
(The boat is filled with dreams
and a hint of jealousy.)
- It's so nice.
- I'm full.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Oh, dear.
(The travelers arrived on Nosy Iranja.)
This is crazy.
Oh, my.
(The emerald sea greets them.)
This is insane.
(In a paradise surrounded
by the primordial sea,)
(the Madagascar Brothers reached
the end of their journey.)
I hope all of you stay healthy
and safe and be happy!
The trip...
ended so quickly for me.
What?
It will be truly beautiful memories
that I can't return to...
when I look back on it in 5 to 6 years.
I don't think I can ever come back
to this time again.
Once I felt like we were just traveling,
- I feel good!
- it made me relax.
I'd been exhausted in Korea,
but my mind was at ease...
during the trip.
It didn't matter
if they were traveling with me again.
Here's what I thought my role was.
Obviously,
Kian84 and Si Eon were the main cast.
And I should help them
with what they don't know.
I thought my role was to assist them.
But as I went, it became my trip too.
(But as I went, it became my trip too.)
(And the man who was both the beginning
and the end of the trip)
(How the trip started)
Nothing is fun, and I've done everything.
(He'd been feeling like
he was stuck in a rut.)
I didn't know if I was alive or not.
I felt like a farmed flatfish.
It eats what it's fed,
and it's just perfect for living.
But it doesn't feel alive.
(That's how he ran away...)
(or dreamed of a new beginning in life.)
(He started traveling with no plans.)
(Can I get this to go?)
(How come you don't have
side-view mirrors?)
(The beginner traveler was clumsy
at everything.)
(But he experienced the local culture
in his own way without prejudice...)
(Gluping)
(and fully immersed himself in it.)
(Then he adapted
to the new environment...)
(and embraced the local culture
like a local.)
(A raw traveler)
(Even though he was a stranger,)
(the people he met on the other side
of the world opened their hearts to him.)
(They shared deep affection
like family...)
(and cherished their encounters.)
I'm so grateful...
that I met people from the other side
of the world and communicated with them.
(The traveler embraced
the unfamiliar world with open arms.)
I was a farmed flatfish,
but while filming Adventure by Accident,
I felt like a wild flatfish.
I've become a wild flatfish.
I feel alive now.
(And he's grateful to have had his friends
along on the journey with him.)
(He was alone at the start.)
(They became two,)
(three,)
(and four.)
(Kian84's world expanded further.)
(The past days are more precious
as they can't come back again.)
(Birth itself is a journey.)
I hope all of us...
eat good food,
visit nice places,
and live with no regrets...
until we depart this world.
I wish that for everyone.
(I wish everyone a journey
with no regrets!)
Let's go.
Good work, everyone.
Traveling is about seeing
completely unfamiliar things,
embracing challenges,
and facing unpredictable situations.
(The third journey
of Adventure by Accident has ended.)