Auntie,
This dish is An Jin's favorite.
It's scrambled eggs with Chinese toon.
Auntie,
please try it.
Alright.
It's really not that good.
Why are you all just standing there?
Let's eat together.
Auntie,
I
actually care about you very much.
Yes, Auntie,
An Jin usually never goes into the kitchen.
You mean
this dish was made by An Jin?
She made it especially for you.
An Jin,
you still like eating this even now?
Yes, Auntie,
An Jin feels uncomfortable if she doesn't eat it for three days.
She says it's a habit from childhood.
Yes,
I used to make this for her often when she was little.
So many years have passed,
I didn't expect you still haven't had enough of it.
Let me tell you all,
actually, from any perspective,
the chemical plant
has more investment value than your business.
It's just that An Jin can't understand it for now.
Auntie,
we all understand.
through our unremitting efforts,
our occupancy rate
has already exceeded 80 percent,
and it has become Nanling Village's...
That's enough.
No need to keep acting.
I've already investigated.
The business of your guesthouse
is actually quite average.
Alright,
let's eat first.
We'll talk after the meal.
Let's eat.
Today,
we are honored to have invited our local renowned celadon master,
Master Zhou.
These two teacups
are also crafted by Master Zhou.
Now, we will
ask Master Zhou to explain to everyone.
Alright.
This one,
the design inspiration
is the sun.
Yue kiln is the most famous ancient celadon kiln system in our country.
Our Yucheng
is
the birthplace of Yue kiln celadon.
If you're interested,
you can follow me to the Banshan Hillside Homestay later
to DIY by yourselves.
There's more over here.
I'll take you there.
Mom,
this is a homestay, not a rural guesthouse.
Come, come, come.
Keep up!
We're almost there.
Watch your step.
Auntie,
Your village is so beautifully built.
We thought the videos were enhanced.
Didn't expect it to be exactly the same.
Right?
As for our village,
since some young people came to open guesthouses,
things have been getting better and better here.
Come, come,
take a look.
Look around.
It's really nice.
You're welcome to visit often.
Okay, definitely, definitely.
Come on,
look over here.
Zhi Yi.
I've been cooking all day.
and I still have to clean up the cups.
Hello?
Yes, alright, alright.
Please wait a moment.
There's a tour group at the front desk.
About twenty or so people.
I'll go attend to them now.
Then hurry and go.
Should we go check how the kitchen is doing with the food preparation?
Oh, right.
Food prep.
I'll go check on it.
Those in the back, please move forward.
Your room number is 0125.
Let's check in first.
Hurry up, hurry up.
There are so many people.
I'm dying of thirst.
My throat feels like it's on fire from all the talking.
You should drink more water.
I'll go attend to them.
Those in the back.
Please line up here.
Please don't push.
Everyone, please don't panic.
Form an orderly line, please.
We still have rooms available.
Everyone, please don't worry.
Don't push.
We'll make sure to accommodate all of you.
Right.
Don't worry.
Boss.
Boss, we're out of rooms.
Shh.
Oh.
Go check if other places have any vacancies.
See if there are any available guesthouses.
Wait for me.
An Jin.
We did it.
I didn't expect it either.
This Celadon and Hanfu Cultural Arts Festival
is unexpectedly popular.
The entire Nanling Village
is filled with tourists from outside.
Indeed.
You must work diligently,
and never be negligent.
Make sure to receive every guest with sincerity.
Do you understand?
Don't worry,
I've got this.
Let me tell you,
President Zheng from the Yucheng Youth Palace will be coming
to sign a contract with us later.
What kind of contract?
He said next month
he will bring the children
here to do that
study tour and investigation.
He wants us to help with the event planning.
That's great!
Please come in.
Chairman Zheng.
You're here.
Hello.
Hello, hello.
Please have a seat.
Here.
Please take a look at this contract.
Here's some tea for you.
Thank you.
This time, you...
This art festival has been organized quite well.
Secretary Ma has been full of praise for you all.
Even Old Zhou...
you've managed to invite him here.
And who is this?
This is Master Zhou's apprentice.
You're the only apprentice...
Old Zhou has taken in all these years.
Young man,
you must work hard, alright?
It's going alright.
I'll do my best.
Oh, by the way,
Xiao Lin,
I wonder if you're interested in setting up a creative base?
Creative base?
Yes.
I have a friend
who's looking for a nice place these days
to set up a creative base.
I think your place here would be great.
If there's a chance,
I'll find time for you to discuss it.
That sounds good.
That's great.
Thank you.
Nowadays, young people like you
who are willing to return to the countryside are rare.
Not to mention,
you've provided us with such good conditions.
Alright,
then let's...
Here's to a pleasant cooperation.
Pleasant cooperation.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
I apologize to you.
I shouldn't have lost my temper with you.
I've thought it through.
I want to stay here.
Auntie,
Although An Jin initially
joined us as an investor,
after spending so much time together,
she has become one of us.
So,
even if you want to withdraw your investment,
please allow An Jin
to continue staying here
and start this business with us.
You mean
even if she can't bring you investment,
you're still willing?
Of course.
To us, An Jin
is like family.
Yes, auntie.
Please, I beg you,
let An Jin stay.
An Jin is already part of our family.
An Jin.
Are you really sure about this?
I've really thought it through.
Ever since I was young,
I've always lost interest in things quickly.
But this time,
I've really made up my mind.
Alright.
An Jin,
go and do what you like.
Mom won't force you anymore.
Thank you, auntie.
Send me a message when you get home.
When you go back, please tell Dad
that I'm doing well here.
Don't keep urging me to come home.
Right now,
I just want to start my own business.
This place
is my home now.
Our daughter has grown up.
She needs to make her own decisions now.
An Jin,
based on your mother's years of professional experience,
this investment of yours
may not necessarily be the best choice.
But with the efforts of you and your guesthouse partners
and your passion,
the success or failure of this investment
might be difficult to measure with data for now.
From now on,
do what you want to do.
Mom will always support you.
No matter what happens,
Dad and Mom
will always be your strong support.
Why am I feeling a bit nervous?
Don't be nervous, don't be nervous.
if we don't make a profit this time,
our guesthouse
will it really have to close down?
I can't bear the thought of it.
Trust Zhi Yi.
Our event this time has been so well organized,
we're sure to make a profit.
I've calculated it.
Did we make a profit?
I'm afraid to hear it.
After deducting the initial losses
and labor costs,
in three months, we've made a total profit of
291,500.
We finally made a profit.
That's great!
Now we finally have something to show for our efforts.