Zhi Yi.
You're finally awake.
There was a big fire in the rehearsal room last night.
you and Jiang Cheng almost
didn't make it.
This...
I changed your clothes for you.
How did I get back?
Jiang Cheng brought you back.
Jiang Cheng.
Zhi Yi.
Are you feeling better?
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
I'm okay.
Zhi Yi, take it easy.
I'm really fine now.
The door to the rehearsal room
must have been locked by the old security guard.
He didn't know you were inside.
No wonder.
I thought someone had locked it on purpose.
I thought Jiaojiao had locked it.
I didn't lock the door.
I don't have the key either.
This rehearsal room,
how could it just catch fire out of nowhere?
I think I saw a ghost.
it just floated by,
in a line.
Don't you dare scare me.
It's true.
Someone must be playing tricks.
They even dare to set fires so brazenly.
That fire...
I set it.
Ah!
You set it?
No, it's not like that.
Zhiyi said she saw a ghost.
I've never encountered this kind of situation before.
I panicked...
...and threw my lighter over there.
Who knew the clothes would catch fire?
I'm sorry.
I've caused trouble for everyone.
I'm sorry, Secretary Ma.
the village's losses...
We will compensate for them.
Well, this is just great.
We didn't make any money,
and now we have to pay compensation.
It's okay.
As long as everyone is safe, that's what matters.
We can always earn more money.
Fortunately, the firefighters arrived in time.
There wasn't any major damage.
I won't dare to play with fire next time.
My name is Wang Meili.
I'm from our village,
the sister in charge of the information station.
Everyone also calls me
Universe.
The top gossip girl.
That's right.
I'm the one who knows the juiciest gossip.
And I'm the most sincere person you'll ever meet.
Gossip Girl, Gossip Girl,
oh yeah!
Does everyone understand now?
Quick, quick, quick!
What's going on?
Come on.
Have you heard?
Last night, right here,
there was a fire.
What?
You didn't know?
There were so many fire trucks here last night.
It was a huge fire!
I saw it with my own eyes.
That Shen Zhiyi
was carried out of the rehearsal room by a man.
Tell me, tell me.
A single man and woman, late at night,
together,
what could they be doing?
Right?
I guess they were rehearsing Yue Opera.
Yue Opera?
How is that possible?
What Yue Opera?
Think about it.
At their age,
still unmarried,
a single man and woman,
always together.
But I reckon
they must be a couple.
They're definitely married.
Right?
Mm, yes, yes, yes.
Hey, quick, quick!
Let's go see what's happening.
Come on, let's go!
You must be Zhiyi's husband, right?
No, I'm not.
Don't misunderstand.
I... we haven't reached that stage yet.
Wang Dama told me everything.
Please don't listen to her nonsense.
It's not true.
He's just my schoolmate.
You see,
Zhiyi is so beautiful,
and so capable.
You better cherish her well.
How did it get spread like this?
Aunt Li,
we have something to do, so we'll be going now.
Please, don't let us keep you.
Auntie Li,
spread the word, spread the word.
Young man,
remember to cherish her, okay?
Oh, okay.
Bye-bye.
Grandma,
we have a Yue Opera performance tomorrow.
Remember to come and watch, okay?
Oh, okay.
Opera.
I heard there's a Yue Opera performance.
Yes, uncle,
we have a Yue Opera performance tonight.
It's 'The Butterfly Lovers.'
It's especially stunning.
You must come.
It's been many years since I've seen a play.
Indeed,
so don't miss it if you're passing by.
You must come, we'll be waiting for you.
Young lady,
there will be peanuts and sunflower seeds to share in the evening.
Tonight, we'll have more than just peanuts and sunflower seeds.
There will be various snacks as well.
You must come.
Ah, that's wonderful!
Okay.
Get me one too, please.
I want to go too.
Sure.
I'll definitely wait for you.
Brother Liang,
If Yingtai were a lady in red,
Ninth Sister would resemble you.
Reluctant to part at farewell.
How did you forget again?
Oh my, our Zhiyi is amazing!
you learned it so quickly,
and you sing so well too.
Why don't you compliment me as well?
You have the nerve to say that after forgetting the lyrics?
Hurry up and practice, the performance is tonight.
You're not bad either.
Really?
Yes, yes, yes.
Alright.
Let's go prepare the stage.
Good luck.
Let's go.
Brother Liang,
There's a well right in front of us.
I wonder how deep the water is.
Look at those two shadows at the bottom of the well.
I am clearly
Hurry up, brother.
a man,
why do you compare me to a woman?
Okay.
Thank you, everyone.
okay.
Thank you.
Zhiyi.