[Unexpected Falling]
[K💖I💖S💖S💖K💖H]
[Episode 8]
Sir.
One soda drink, please.
Alright.
Five yuan. Here you go.
Scan the QR code here.
This is such a remote place.
Is your business doing well?
I don't require a big budget here.
I can easily earn money
by selling whatever product.
Your job is stable,
unlike mine.
I've been visiting a few factories,
yet I haven't made any deal.
It's a tough time for business now.
Are you a salesperson?
I sell oxygen tanks.
May I ask
how is
the business of the factory across the street?
I've been here for a while,
yet their gates are closed.
There's no one to be seen.
Let alone you.
Ever since the factory is built,
I've never seen anyone around.
How so?
Why?
Empty shell.
Li.
Here you go.
Okay.
Hello.
Su Wen told me
that you're back in Beiling today, aren't you?
Thanks.
I'm there already.
I have a case
that will come to trial this afternoon.
Is there anything?
I have a question.
Go ahead.
If I manage to find Xia Xinliang,
do I have the rights
to ask him to provide me
with the supply contract?
Find Xia Xinliang?
That's right.
[Nanzhou Xinliang Food Processing Manufacturer]
If he insists
that Xu Youning owes him money for the goods
and the money credited into his bank account
is the payment for the goods,
can I ask him to provide me with the contract?
First, Xia Xinliang wouldn't see you.
It's pointless
to find Xia Xinliang.
Even if you'd want to find him,
wait till I'm back.
Let's discuss it first.
Do you understand?
Ruan Zhenzhen.
Okay, I get it.
Thank you.
Ruan Zhenzhen.
Sit down and have a drink.
Come on.
[Nanzhou Xinliang Food Processing Manufacturer]
What do you want?
Hello, I'm here to look for someone.
Who are you looking for?
Mr. Xia. I'm looking for Mr. Xia.
Who are you? Why do you want to meet Mr. Xia?
Someone entrusted me to gift Mr. Xia
something.
Is he around?
Mr. Xia isn't around.
You may leave the thing here.
When will he be back?
I don't know.
Where is he then?
Do you know?
No.
What is the gift?
Where is it?
It's over there.
In my car.
I'm not sure
what it is exactly.
He said it's rather valuable
and it's a token of gratitude for Mr. Xia.
Bring the gift
and leave it here.
Well, I'm not doubting you,
but I don't think it's a good idea.
My friend specifically told me
that I must give it to Mr. Xia in person.
If I left it here,
how could I
explain this to my friend?
Take the gift back then.
What do you want exactly?
Is Mr. Xia really not around?
He's not around. Leave immediately.
How about this?
I'll get the gift
and leave it with you.
You can give a call to Mr. Xia
and let me talk to him for a moment.
It's just like doing a handover.
Or else it wouldn't sound good
if I just left it with you.
I'm just being entrusted by my friend.
Is that okay?
Fine.
Bring that thing over.
I'll give Mr. Xia a call.
Okay.
Thank you so much.
Is this the one?
Please kindly give a call
to Mr. Xia
and let me talk to him.
I'll hold it for you.
[Boss]
Stop barking.
Mr. Xia.
Someone send you a box.
She said that it's a token of gratitude
that her friend entrusted her to pass it to you.
It's a paper box.
I'm not sure what's inside the box.
Okay. What is your name?
He asks for your name.
Zhang Lili.
She said her name is Zhang Lili.
She's around thirty years old, medium-sized.
Slim and fair-skinned.
She has big eyes.
Her upper lip is curved upwards.
Alright, Mr. Xia.
Okay.
Please help me ask Mr. Xia
about his whereabouts.
I can pass the gift to him
in person.
Mr. Xia said
that he would come and pick up the gift later.
You can leave this here.
Tell Mr. Xia
to hurry then.
This gift cannot last long.
Are there any other models?
Take a look at this phone model.
It's on promotion now.
1,200 yuan.
Where's your integrity?
Well?
Is a verbal agreement
not an agreement?
I was going to pay,
yet you changed it to full payment.
How could you do this?
It fits you so well.
Let me have a look.
Alright.
I'm getting this then.
Can you
talk to the landlord again?
This is too urgent.
How could I get such a big amount of money?
(WeChat payment received, 1,200 yuan.)
Have a nice day.
Okay.
Alright.
We'll see how it goes.
What's the matter?
We agreed that I can take out a loan.
Now they changed their mind.
I have to make the full payment
and they're rushing us with the payment.
Sir.
Good day.
How can I help you?
Is there a new model?
This is our latest model.
And this too.
This is our flagship model.
It's our top-selling model.
I'll have a look.
Have a look.
Ma.
Do you have any cash?
Lend me some.
I work for you.
How could you borrow money from me?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
This phone model is good too.
You can check it out.
Well, look at the damage
that Anhe's shares have done.
Our net asset value
is experiencing a drastic decline.
Clients are asking for redemption.
What can I do?
Even if I were to persuade them,
they would not listen to me.
It's more than
just the redemption issue.
The net worth of a few of our products
has dropped to liquidation price.
If we don't take drastic measures,
the floating loss will be realized.
If this goes big,
our company's image aside,
when the China Securities Regulatory
Commission issues a warning letter,
the damage caused to the company
will be irreparable.
Stop complaining
and find a solution.
Our immediate concern
is to solve the liquidity.
We must stabilize our clients' confidence.
Otherwise, if China Securities Regulatory
Commission takes a denunciation
and orders us
to take measures and correct the situation,
that would be brutal.
What about
using the company fund
to subscribe to our own products temporarily?
It's just temporary. We need market liquidity.
That's not doable.
Without the consent from the board of directors,
no one is allowed to use
the company fund.
We'll be doomed then.
Are you nuts?
Stop it.
Is this the time to have a squabble?
Let's think of a solution.
How should we explain this
to Mr. Fang?
Who will do the reporting?
Mr. Shen.
I'm working in the administration department,
it's inappropriate for me to do the reporting.
Mr. Qiu.
I have something to do later.
Well, I shall...
Liu.
Mr. Qiu.
Fine.
All of you refuse to go, don't you?
I shall go myself.
Please go with me, Mr. Shen.
If the chairman
gets furious
or upset...
Alright, I'll go.
Due to Anhe's shares,
our company's liquidity
is experiencing a major issue.
The redemption pressure is massive.
According to the statistics
from all sources...
the redemption amount
that the clients submitted
takes up more than 20 percent
of our equity quota.
And the numbers are still increasing rapidly.
Some products
are facing the risk of liquidation price.
Please calm down, sir.
All departments
are trying to find a solution
to solve the issue.
That's right.
Someone suggested
using our company fund
to maintain the liquidity
to cope with the redemption.
I see.
Well.
Clear some of
the open interest shares
to deal with the redemption pressure.
We must not breach the contract.
We must ensure our clients' benefits
and our company's
credibility.
Our clients buy our products
as they trust and support us.
We mustn't fail them.
If there's a need
to use our company fund,
I'll handle that.
Okay?
That's all for now.
Noted, sir.
Let's go.
Is that all?
Was I not clear enough?
Or did Mr. Fang not hear me clearly?
This is such a major issue.
Why do I think
that Mr. Fang doesn't really care about it?
I'm not sure about the business.
However,
our chairman looks at the big picture.
We can't possibly understand him, can we?
Am I right?
Hello.
He hasn't come out yet.
It's pointless getting nervous here.
Even if we get
to use the company fund
to fill up the hole
and elevate the share price,
we'd need to wait till the resumption.
I know.
Okay.
Are you in Nanzhou?
Are you free for a meeting?
Okay.
I'll wait for your call.
I'll refill the water.
Greetings, Mr. Qiu.
That girl named Su Wen
looks familiar.
Is she related
to Xu Youning?
I think
she went to the same high school
as Xu Youning's wife.
The same high school?
Are they close?
I think they're good friends.
She was there
throughout the funeral.
Listen.
Keep an eye
on Su Wen for these few days.
Report to me at once
if the inspection team is
asking for any information.
You must get my permission
before giving her any information.
Noted.
Any updates
on Xu Youning's family?
No.
Mr. Qiu.
Is the company seriously
affected by Anhe?
I heard
that the company
is going to use the company fund.
This is none of your business.
Check on
Xu Youning's family
and see how is everything.
But...
how?
What should I check?
What else?
Hello, Mr. Attorney.
What's the matter?
Come and drive my car now.
I can't.
I'm occupied.
Can you wait a little longer?
I want you here now.
Come and drive my car away.
Okay.
I'll come right away.
I'll be there in a jiffy.
Are you here yet? Where are you now?
I'm so sorry.
There's a jam.
Please be patient.
Hurry up.
[Nanzhou Xinliang Food Processing Manufacturer]
[Lemeijia Residence]
Hello?
Hello, Mrs. Xu.
This is Lu Yang.
I've packed Xu Youning's items
in the office.
I was rather occupied with work,
hence I didn't get to give it to you.
I happen to be free tonight,
so I'm here to pass it on to you.
Are you at home?
I can bring the things upstairs.
Thank you so much.
But
I'm settling some matters outside
and won't be home soon.
There's no one at home.
How about this?
You can put the things in your car first.
I'll get them from you
when I'm free. Is that okay?
Well, that'd be such a hassle for you.
I have nothing to do tonight anyway.
I can wait for you.
When will you be back?
You don't have to wait for me.
I'm not sure
when I will be back.
I see.
Alright, I won't wait for you then.
The things are in my car.
I'll give it to you another day then.
Okay, thanks.
Goodbye.
Hello, Mr. Gao.
Are you at home, Ruan Zhenzhen?
Open the door.
Are you outside?
Yes.
I'm settling something outside.
What's the matter?
Can you come back for a while?
Why? Is there anything wrong?
I...
I just came back from Beiling
and I brought you something.
I'm at your doorstep now.
Hurry up and come back.
I'll wait for you.
I'm here.
How come you're stuck here
because of Ruan Zhenzhen?
Didn't you know that she was coming in advance?
Seems like your plan is not ready yet.
Hurry up and drive the car.
You're right.
Xia Xinliang's factory
is an empty shell.
How did you know?
Ruan Zhenzhen.
Did you go to his factory?
You're so stubborn.
How dare you go there on your own?
Xia Xinliang is such an evil person.
How could you go alone?
What if you get into trouble?
I'm almost home.
Stop lecturing me.
Let's talk about Xia Xinliang, can we?
This company
has four shareholders.
[Xia Xinliang]
Aside from Xia Xinliang,
the rest
have not
appeared in the Loan Agreement.
I've investigated
the related companies.
To date, I haven't found any
relevant information.
We should
find Xia Xinliang first.
Gao Jun.
Hello?
Where are you?
I don't see you.
I need to leave due to some urgent matters.
Why? Are you at home now?
I just arrived home.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Ruan Zhenzhen.
Hello? What's wrong?
Someone broke into my house.
You're at Block 11, right?
Don't be afraid.
I'll send someone over immediately.
Be careful.
Put on your shoes.
What's wrong? Did someone break into your house?
We met
the owner who called.
Don't be scared.
What does he look like?
♪I opened my eyes, but I'm unwilling to wake up♪
♪The dream you appeared in
was like a shooting star♪
♪Out of reach, your ephemeral silhouette♪
♪I knew it was a trap♪
♪But I let the cold lie harden my heart♪
♪Believing it to be your selfless warning♪
♪I try so hard to prove♪
♪Holding your hand is my response♪
♪Only realizing after suffering♪
♪Happiness is in the past♪
♪The outcome is covered in mud♪
♪Forgive my stubbornness♪
♪The tears will never pretend to be calm♪
♪The familiar past scenario♪
♪The plot you weaved repeats itself again♪
♪Destroying my unattainable yearning♪
♪Whirling incessantly in my head♪
♪Giving up what is fair for you♪
♪To piece together the fragmented conviction♪
♪I listen with my heart♪
♪The night breeze strokes the wind chimes♪
♪Swaying, struggling to fly♪
♪Like a dragonfly with broken wings♪
♪Only then realizing, love is not a movie♪
♪You won't win by taking it too seriously♪
♪I will remember the promise I made to myself♪
♪My promise♪