[Unexpected Falling]
[Episode 32]
Happy now?
Tell the company
to stop pulling such dirty tricks.
No problem.
One more thing.
Leave Jiu to us.
Sure.
Get him up.
Those despicable men.
How can you be so vicious
toward your own colleague?
What's wrong with your leg?
Boss, my leg is fine.
I sprained my ankle
when I was fighting
with them.
Boss.
Believe me.
I didn't betray you.
Let me explain.
I'm going to explain it to our boss.
Why are the two of you here?
Go ahead and explain it to him then.
You don't have to tell me twice.
Why are you pointing at me?
Enough.
Boss, listen to me.
I really didn't betray you.
They forced me to lure you here.
But I adamantly refused.
So they beat me up
and kidnapped me.
Then, they used my phone
to contact you.
I know.
If you were their accomplice,
you could've just called me.
You didn't have to send me a message on WeChat.
You know that?
It's good that you know.
Can you walk?
Yes.
Let's go.
Boss.
Boss, I can walk.
Put me down.
Boss.
What about Ruan Zhenzhen?
Put an end to it.
You should've done that earlier.
You should just cut her off.
That's the smart choice.
I'm talking about us.
Although you didn't lie to me this time,
you had betrayed me quite often before this.
You were colluding with your company,
right?
For me,
I just think
that since I'm going to investigate,
I shouldn't waste the opportunity.
I just want to earn more money.
But I don't have any ill intentions.
I never thought that those people
from our company
would be so cruel.
I didn't expose you
because I wanted to see
how far you would go with this.
You didn't betray me today
and I saved your life.
We don't owe each other anything now.
Let's put an end to it now.
Boss.
We've known each other for so long.
Do you have to do this?
Do I have to do this?
You should've thought about that
when you sold our information
to your company.
It's too late now!
You'll have to find yourself
a new place to settle down.
I'll be out of your life.
No.
Forgive me, Boss.
By the way,
I didn't tell the company
that your identity was exposed.
But those people already know.
There is something fishy going on.
You have to be careful.
Use my phone
to call Ruan Zhenzhen.
[Ruan Zhenzhen]
[Speaker]
Tan Shen, I'm being followed by a car.
It's a grey van.
Its registration plate is covered.
Don't panic. Where are you now?
I'm on my way back through the small road.
Two of them are coming for me.
-Call the police now.
-Stop right there!
You can't run away.
Let's go.
Zhenzhen.
Zhenzhen!
Don't panic.
Wu and the others departed first.
I think they'll be there soon.
Stop right there!
Let's go!
Are you okay?
-Here.
-Be careful.
Are you okay?
What's wrong with your head?
Did you hit the back of your head?
Do you still feel dizzy?
I feel much better now.
Who are those three people downstairs?
They are my men.
All of you can go back first.
Be safe.
I told you that I'll be honest with you.
I won't lie to you again.
You are feeling unwell today.
And it's so late now.
Tomorrow,
I'll introduce them to you.
What?
You can't even get something so simple done?
Useless beings.
You are so punctual.
Hello.
I'm raising the money now.
Give me a few more days.
Give you a few more days
to run away?
Mr. Fang.
Don't treat me like a fool.
You know
that I'm just working for someone.
Cut the crap.
You have until midnight tomorrow.
If I don't see the money,
you can wait for that list
to go online.
[Payphone]
I've just sent you
a phone number from a landline phone.
Check its location.
Yes. At once.
Why is Mr. Xu suddenly back in Guangzhou?
Something came up at the firm.
So Mr. Xu had to go back.
There's only
one meeting left between us.
Our firm has sent me to take charge of it.
So,
you'll have to deal with me.
Sure.
Great.
Let's start now.
[Nanzhou Humanity Hospital]
[Building Complex]
Yangyang.
Think carefully.
How did you get hurt?
Yangyang.
Here. Eat a piece of apple.
Mr. Qiu.
Ms. Shen.
What brings you here?
My friend fell sick.
So I'm here to visit him.
What are you doing here?
One of our employees
has been hospitalized.
So I'm here to pay him a visit
on behalf of our company.
Okay. I'll leave you to it.
We can talk later.
Sure.
Mr. Qiu.
You are here to visit Yangyang, right?
He's awake.
Yangyang.
Your superior is here to see you again.
Please go in, Mr. Qiu.
-Okay.
-I'll get some water.
[Buchuo Antique]
Let's check it out.
What is it? Do you like it?
I wouldn't say that I like it.
But it looks
interesting.
Have you been here before?
I passed by twice.
But I didn't enter the shop.
Come.
Fu.
How did the house hunt go?
I found a house.
But it's a little bit small.
You can't live in it.
I'm still hunting
for a bigger house for you.
-Understood.
-Mister.
You have a parcel.
Take a seat.
Let me check it out.
I prefer standing.
Do you want some water?
No.
Are you looking for a place to rent?
The place that we were staying in is not safe now.
I need to find a new place for Jiu and the others.
Jiu?
Your underlings?
Xu Youning was in debt with their company.
Their company asked them
to investigate this matter together with me.
Where are they?
Didn't you say
that you would introduce them to me?
Jiu injured his leg.
Wu and Qi are keeping an eye on Shen Nanqiu.
Shen Nanqiu?
The person who pretended to be Xia Xinliang
told me that it was a woman who hired him.
Based on what we know right now,
the only woman
who's related to Xu Youning
is Shen Nanqiu.
And Shen Nanqiu
has a complicated background.
If we keep an eye on her,
we may be able to find something useful.
Hello.
Boss.
I saw Qiu Zhijian
at the hospital.
Qiu Zhijian?
Yes.
Qiu Zhijian went to the hospital to visit Lu Yang.
What about Shen Nanqiu?
What is Shen Nanqiu
doing at the hospital?
Shen Nanqiu greeted Qiu Zhijian
when she saw him.
Then, I felt like Qiu Zhijian
was acting very suspiciously.
So I followed him instead.
Enough.
Come back with Wu now.
We'll meet at the usual place.
Wu.
Did I do something wrong again?
You are so stupid.
Where are we going?
As I said,
I'll introduce them to you.
Thank you for your support, Mr. Fang.
You are all welcome
to come back to guide us.
Goodbye.
Mr. Shen.
Please see Ms. Zhang out for me.
Yes, Mr. Fang.
Have a safe journey.
Mr. Fang.
I have something
to report to you.
Mr. Fang, go ahead and do what you need to do.
We'll go over there first.
Okay.
Xu Weidong went to Guangzhou
last night.
I need to check
if something has happened.
Okay.
What is it? Tell me.
I've located where he made the call.
It's from a payphone
under Nanzhou Humanity Hospital
that Lu Yang is staying in.
And I went to Lu Yang's ward
to visit him.
I think Lu Yang is acting strange.
They say that he has gone out of his mind.
But it doesn't seem believable.
It looks like
he's faking it.
I think
that either
Lu Yang is colluding with Xu Youning,
or
he is...
He is
Xu Youning himself,
right?
But how can we confirm that?
We have to confirm it with his wife.
We've
failed the first time.
We can't do it the second time.
No one is willing to do it.
Pay more money then.
If the pay is high enough,
someone will do it.
Okay.
I'll get it done.
When I was at the hospital,
I also saw...
Wait a second.
Hello?
Can you talk now?
Go ahead.
I went to visit a friend at the hospital today.
Do you know who I saw?
Who?
Mr. Qiu from Jinshang.
He was standing in front of a ward
without going in. He seemed suspicious.
I didn't know what he was up to.
Okay.
I have to hang up now.
Qiu.
Where were we just now?
I wanted to say
that I saw
Shen Nanqiu at the hospital.
Okay.
How's my service, Jiu?
Do you want to eat it?
Don't be shy.
Okay now. Just serve the food.
Come here now.
Okay.
-Come.
-Let's go.
Serve these skewers first.
Let me do it.
I'll take these.
Here you are.
Eat them while they are hot.
He's the one who followed me
when I was in my hometown.
That's me.
I'm Jiu.
He's the one who changed the lock.
That was me. I'm Qi.
Nice to meet you.
Wu.
I'm different from them.
I'm a decent lawyer.
I don't do anything that's against the law.
Wu, Qi, Jiu.
(*five, seven, nine)
What about Liu, Ba, and Shi?
(*six, eight, ten)
Who are Yi, Er, San, and Si?
(*one, two, three, four)
Well,
our boss has the character of four in his name.
So, we start with Wu, five,
to show him respect.
It's easier for the operation too.
He has the character of four in his name?
So Tan Shen is your fake name?
His name is Tan Sitiao.
What?
What is his name?
What is it?
Tan Sitiao.
(*"Si" means "four")
Just take a look at it.
[Tan Sitiao]
Tan Sitiao.
It's a good name.
As I said,
I'll be honest with you.
Come on.
Let me open a bottle of beer for you.
She doesn't drink.
You are so inattentive.
Zhen.
Come on.
Jiu.
How's your leg?
It's painful. More painful than yesterday.
Since your leg is in pain,
you shouldn't drink.
Okay? You have to drive.
I'll drink for you.
You brat.
Where's your compassion?
Are you going to ask a cripple to drive?
You are on a probation period now.
You have to show us your worth.
I almost forgot if you didn't mention this.
The two of you
didn't even defend me
yesterday.
I had treated you so well
for nothing.
To me,
you are like my own kids.
♪The traces left by you♪
Let me tell you.
The incident yesterday
was obviously
a trick to lure us away.
They didn't want me
to go back to our boss at all.
They just wanted to capture Ruan.
I'm sure that was their plan.
Think about it.
There's no reason for the company
to catch Zhenzhen.
Kidnapping someone on the street
is a serious offense.
No matter how bold your company is,
they wouldn't dare to do that.
They also kidnapped me last time.
It's different.
You are their employee.
They have something on you.
They know that you won't call the police.
♪Picking up the broken promise♪
♪And refusing the possibility
of losing myself♪
Hello?
Okay. Thank you.
I'll be there now.
Okay.
Sir, madam.
Mrs. Xu will be here soon.
Please wait for a moment.
When all of you are here,
we'll talk about financial aid,
okay?
Okay.
Okay. I have things to do.
Please pardon me for a moment.
Later,
don't talk too much. Let me do the talk.
We need to keep the money
for Youning.
In case Ruan Zhenzhen loses her conscience
and abandons Youning.
Youning is not a registered citizen.
He's not protected by the law.
Got it?
I'll go with you.
Why?
I'm not there to pick a fight.
Don't worry, I'll be fine.
There are so many people in the company.
Just wait here.
According to the company's rules,
the three of you
need to go to the Notary Public
to be notarized as the inheritors.
After that, bring us the document
and we'll sign an agreement.
Then,
we can transfer the money
into the bank account
of your choice.
Is there a requirement for a bank account?
The bank account
needs to belong to the inheritor.
Can you pay us in cash?
I'm afraid
I can't do that.
We can only do a bank transfer.
If we pay you in cash,
we can't tally up the numbers.
Zhenzhen's account
is suspended by the court.
She can't use it.
You can transfer the money to my account.
Zhenzhen,
you can trust us.
When they wire the money to me,
I can give it to you in cash.
Don't worry.
You'll get everything you deserve.
We should get the notarization done first.
We'll discuss other things later.
Okay.
You can
discuss it with each other then.
Ms. Ruan.
Please wait.
I need to talk to you.
Let's go.
But...
Ma'am,
please wait here.
Okay?
Okay.
Let's go.
This way, please.
Do you think
they will do something
behind our backs?
Drink some water.
(I'm close with Mr. Yan)
from Anhe Travel.
He told me that you are looking for a job.
Coincidentally,
Jinshang Capital
is hiring now.
If you are interested,
you can send me your resume.
What kind of position is it?
It's a position
in the administrative department.
You'll be working in my department.
But
there's something
that I need to tell you.
You are under a lawsuit right now.
So I can't
officially hire you.
You don't have to worry about your salary.
You'll be paid the same.
Considering your current situation,
I'll come up with a way
to pay you in cash.
As for your work hour,
you can have a flexible one.
If you need to do anything, go ahead.
Just give me a notice.
Don't worry.
It's just a temporary collaboration between us.
He'll look for the money
while I'll look for the list.
Yes.
He says that it's a list of clients.
For the time being,
I don't know anything about the list.
Don't worry. I'll be careful.
Keep in touch. Bye.
What took you so long?
Jinshang has offered me a job.
What did you say?
Jinshang has offered me a job
in the administrative department.
Why?
On the surface,
the company is trying to take care
of the employee's family.
But I don't know what their real intention is.
What did you say then?
I accepted their offer.
Can't you tell
that they are trying to keep you
under their watch?
So what?
I can find more information by working with them.
You can't work here.
Because
we don't know
who your kidnappers from last night are.
What if they were sent by Jinshang?
If you work for them,
you'll be entering the tiger's lair.
We can't get anything if we don't take the risk.
What if
you are chewed up by the tiger?
I'm even dancing with the wolves now.
I'm not afraid of a tiger's lair.
I'm not a bad person.
And I used to think
that you are a good person.
Who were you calling just now?
A friend.
Who?
You are too controlling.
I thought that we were supposed
to be honest with each other.
Being honest with each other
doesn't mean that you can
invade my privacy.
Ruan Zhenzhen, I hope you'll understand
that the friend you trust
may not be a true friend.
Just be frank.
Who were you talking to on the phone just now?
As I said, a friend.
Do you mean Gao Jun?
Why do you suddenly mention him?
That day, you said that you went back
to clean Xu Youning's grave.
But you actually
went to look for Gao Jun at the law firm
to verify my identity, right?
You unplugged
the dashcam
in your car
because you wanted to hide
where you went.
That day, I really thought
that you just wanted to change my tire for me.
That's not the point.
Really?
What's the point, then?
The point is
that you can't simply
trust anyone.
Including Gao Jun.
When it comes to this matter,
he's not more trustworthy than me.
Thank you for the warning.
Can we end this conversation now?
About the financial aid,
have you thought about how to split it?
The company doesn't care about that.
They'll just transfer the money to an account.
Then, we'll split it ourselves.
I can't use my account now.
So they can only
transfer the money
into the account of Xu Youning's parents.
I think I won't get anything in the end.
But there's a solution to that.
What solution is that?
The court is only suspending
your account temporarily.
You can go to the bank
to open another account.
Xu Youning's parents
won't agree
for them to transfer the money into my account.
What can you do then?
You have to discuss it with them.
They can have all the money.
You are what they call
the generous poor, right?
Keep your eyes on the road.
(Do you call collecting debt, drinking, fighting)
(a job?)
(You're a perfectly healthy person.)
(Why can't you find a decent job?)
Why did you have to do
something indecent like this?
Xiucai.
I respect you.
I've been meaning
to tell you this,
and I will tell you today.
♪Glancing up♪
♪The night sky seemed to bloom like a flower♪
♪Subzero temperature♪
♪Flying alone, wandering♪
♪Without a direction♪
♪You look at me♪
♪As if I were an injured lamb♪
♪I peer at you♪
♪Like fireworks, burning bright♪
♪You describe how heaven is with your silence♪
♪I pretend to be captivated,
the corners of my lips upturned♪
♪You walk towards me♪
♪Like the moonlight peeking through the tears♪
♪I hold onto you♪
♪Like a wish fulfilled amongst the despair♪
♪Although the moth is drawn to the flame♪
♪Since the smoke is still warm
and the night is still young♪
♪Let it burn♪
♪You look at me♪
♪As if I were an injured lamb♪
♪I peer at you♪
♪Like fireworks, burning bright♪
♪You describe how heaven is with your silence♪
♪I pretend to be captivated,
the corners of my lips upturned♪
♪You walk towards me♪
♪Like the moonlight peeking through the tears♪
♪I hold onto you♪
♪Like a wish fulfilled amongst the despair♪
♪Although the moth is drawn to the flame♪
♪Since the smoke is still warm
and the night is still young♪
♪Let it burn♪