The oil lamp burns through the Yin-Yang Divide
The Lamp Keeper stands at the Gates of Hell
You two kids
Remember this well
We must never let the Eternal Lamp
of the Bone-Keeping Temple go out
What if the wind blows it out?
If the lamp dies
I die
Little lady
Out here in the dead of night
Widowhood must be so lonely
How about
you keep us brothers company?
Come on
Come here
Lay her down
Hold her down!
Pin her down
No!
Stop!
Haven't had a piece like this in ages
Let me go!
Feels good
Feels great!
Lord Beile
I'm begging you
Please let my father go in
Sure
But if your father goes in
where do we go?
The rain's too heavy
I'm begging you
Lord Beile
Please, I beg you
Here
Hold an umbrella for your father
Wouldn't want him getting soaked
This is outrageous
Exactly
Bullying
us living folk is one thing
But now he's bullying the dead too
That man
will get what he deserves sooner or later
Keep your voice down
His brother-in-law is the Mayor
Cross him and you'll...
Move
You all
Father!
Lord Beile
You just don't know what's good for you, huh?
Smash the coffin open!
No!
I'm begging you
Lord Beile, I beg you
Smash it!
It's alive!
Little brother
Don't eat me
Master
A Daoist Priest is here to see you
Daoist Priest
How did it go?
Child's play
He's awake
It's a Jiangshi
A Jiangshi!
Serves you right
You turned the Bone-Keeping Temple
into a chaotic mess
You're getting what you deserve
The Mayor is mistaken
A Jiangshi
forms when Resentful Energy gathers
in the corpse's throat
festering and refusing to disperse
To become a Jiangshi
the corpse must be buried in
the Land of Converging Nine Yins
for fifty years
Becoming a Jiangshi
is no easy feat
Why would I lie to you?
Everyone saw it
In that case
Tonight
I'll confront him myself
Daoist Priest
He's right inside that room
You
Get over here
Tie him up
Brother-in-law is calling you
Hurry up
He's calling you
Why does it have to be me?
You caused this trouble
You expect me to go?
I refuse to believe it
Even immortals fear a puff of smoke
Today, I'll see your
body and soul obliterated!
Men!
Lady Fox Immortal is here
Who dares be insolent?
Hurry, hurry!
Don't let him escape
Catch him
Hurry, catch him!
Lady Fox Immortal
You fools!
Hurry and catch him!
Lady Fox Immortal
Daoist Priest
He got away
Good thing he got away
Thank you
Your name is Ruling, right?
Why did you save me?
Then why did you save me?
The dying lamp won't go out
Boundary between Yin and Yang
The Lamp Keeper remains
The vow of the living
Such heavy yin energy
Is this sung for the dead to hear?
Or sung by the dead for the living?
Five Thunders, Five Thunders
Heavenly thunder follows
Thunder in my palm
Strike ghosts and banish evil