What's going on?
That bastard Sun!
Didn't we agree on a truce tonight?
It's the Ghost Soldiers!
Ghost Soldiers?
Marshal.
Take a look.
Here they come.
They're fighting!
What's your name?
His name is...
Lao Jiugui.
Good.
Lao Jiugui,
I hereby appoint you
Major, Regimental Commander.
Quick, thank the Marshal!
Plus ten gold bars.
Marshal.
You may go clean up the battlefield.
Move out!
The Eternal Lamp burns even by day.
That's a lot of oil money over a year.
How many times have I told you?
If this lamp ever goes out,
the departed spirits get no guidance,
can't enter Reincarnation,
and become...
wandering ghosts.
I've followed you for over ten years,
and never seen a single ghost.
What do you mean, "followed me for ten years"?
Don't you go disturbing my Daoist heart.
Back then, it was the Mayor
who, to shut me up,
handed the Bone-Keeping Temple over to me.
And I, seeing you all alone with no one,
young and strong,
called you over to look after the two kids.
Isn't that right?
Thank you, Lao Jiugui.
What is it?
I suddenly...
felt a trace of happiness.
My Daoist heart is shaken.
I feel something bad...
is about to happen.
What are you talking about?
Where is he?
Get out here!
Who the hell are you people?
Why are you beating him?
Out of respect for Lao Jiugui,
we only beat him up.
Otherwise, he'd be at the station already.
Why would you send him to the station?
He cheated.
Any other time,
we'd have chopped off his hands and feet.
Since he owes me gambling debts,
we'll let him off today.
How much does he owe you?
One hundred silver dollars.
What?
You're lying!
I only owe you twenty silver dollars.
What kind of interest is that high?
Think it's too much?
Then don't fucking borrow!
Pay up, now.
Paying debts is only right.
But let me tell you,
inside the Bone-Keeping Temple,
only the dead are kept here.
If you keep yelling like this,
you'll disturb the departed spirits,
and have bad luck for life.
Hand over the money.
Ruling.
Get the money.
I was wrong, Master.
Idling about every day,
your sister is off at university,
and look at you.
Now you've picked up a gambling habit too.
Master.
I truly know I was wrong.
I'm sorry.
Back in the day,
I never should have taken you in.
I'm sorry.
The boy is still young.
Still young?
And what'll he do when he's older?
Tear a hole right through the sky?
Give them back their money.
It's not enough.
There's only eighty silver dollars.
Not a cent less.
Inside the Bone-Keeping Temple,
besides that Eternal Lamp,
what else do you think is valuable?
Take it.
That's Lao Jiugui for you.
Always a straight shooter.
Forget it.
Let it go.
Dongsheng.
Get up and apologize to Master.
Apologize to Master.
Sit down and eat.
Eat what?!
Get out!
From this day on,
don't set foot in the Bone-Keeping Temple again.
I can leave,
but...
can you tell me,
who killed my mother?
Get out!
Dongsheng.
Lao Jiugui, what's wrong with you?
Say one more word,
and you can get out too.
Out!
Get out!
Well, if it isn't...
the young master of the Bone-Keeping Temple.
What?
Back to play a few hands?
Play?
Even a dog wouldn't play with you.
Wake up!
What is it?
You wanna sleep?
You'll have to sleep somewhere else.
We're recruiting soldiers here.
Lend a hand.
With a build like yours,
it'd be a waste not to enlist.
You mean me?
I'd rather starve to death
than become a soldier.
Why?
These days,
anyone with a couple of guns
dares to call himself a Marshal.
You're talking about the old warlords.
Our Brigade Commander is different.
Same wine, different bottle.
My Master said it himself.
Today,
either Warlord Zhang fights Warlord Wang,
or Warlord Wang fights Warlord Li.
Your Master was a soldier too?
A mere soldier? Please.
My Master was a
Colonel, Regiment Commander.
Steamed buns!
Hot steamed buns!
Do soldiers get fed?
Have a bite first.
Flatbread!
Slow down.
No one's gonna fight you for it.
Eat slowly.
By the way,
What's your name?
Shuisheng.
Shuisheng?
Born in the water.
That's the Mayor's car.
Looks like over these years,
the Mayor's been pocketing plenty.
Qiuying!
Somebody!
Quick, put her on the bed.
Brother.
Who are you?
Director Sun.
A busy man like you forgets easily.
I'm Brigade Commander Li Chuanzhong's
Orderly.
Last time the Mayor came with you
to our Commander's residence,
we met.
Look at me.
So busy I forgot.
Lord Beile.
The young lady's illness...
I...
I can't treat it.
You damn useless fool!
Lord Beile, I really can't treat it.
This isn't an illness at all.
No clinic will be of any use.
You two.
Who are you, then?
Well,
Lord Beile,
Let me
introduce them to you.
These two
are famous Spirit Mediums from Manchuria.
And today they
happened to wander by my place.
Since the great masters have spoken,
then the young lady
can definitely be saved.
You say it's not an illness.
Then what is it?
This...
She's Possessed!
Impossible.
Your young lady...
recently, did she
encounter Something unclean?
Impossible.
She's the Mayor's daughter.
She's never lifted a finger.
The servants do all the dirty work.
What they mean is,
has the young lady
encountered any Demons and monsters?
How would I know that?
But,
this morning,
my sister and brother-in-law
did go to the temple to burn incense.