Stop staring.
Move along, move along.
Captain Ma.
Should we call the police?
Are you stupid?
We're the military.
Why call the police?
If word of this gets out,
we'll be the laughingstock.
If the Brigade Commander finds out,
he'll have me shot.
Then what about...
This...
those bodies in here?
You go
find some reliable brothers,
bury them on the back hill at midnight.
Go on.
Yes, sir.
Wait.
Remember,
find ones who can keep their mouths shut.
Yes, sir.
Alright.
That's enough.
This money
is from the Captain.
Keep your mouths shut.
Yes, sir.
Alright.
You all head out first.
Aren't we leaving?
I think this whole thing
seems a bit fishy.
I think so too.
This was definitely done by a person.
But who could it be?
If only Master were here.
He'd know for sure.
You miss your Master.
Master has flaws
as numerous as the stars.
His virtues
are as scarce as the sun.
But whenever the sun rises,
all the stars
fade into nothing.
What kind of person
is your Master, really?
Want to hear about him?
Yes.
I remember when I was sixteen...
Where'd you get that gun?
It's mine.
Give it to me.
Hand it over.
Give it to me!
It's a fake.
What're you so nervous about?
Listen to me,
you can't carry even a fake gun.
You hear me?
I'll carry it anyway.
And I'll get a real gun too,
to kill the man who killed my mother.
Brother.
Why are you bringing this up again?
Master said never to mention it.
Why shouldn't I?
It wasn't your mother who died.
It's "for my own good" again, huh?
Don't you glare at me!
Get down on your knees!
Auntie Xiaoling.
Kneel down!
Didn't I tell you?
Never bring this up, ever.
What are you two doing?
Fighting and shouting over this little thing.
Don't practice anymore.
I train to build my strength,
you know?
Look how skinny he is.
He couldn't even haul manure now.
You Lao Jiugui.
Had too much to drink again?
We're eating now.
Manure this, manure that.
Come eat.
It's all your favorites.
Auntie Xiaoling.
I'll go grab you a bowl.
Such a good boy.
Get up, Dongsheng.
Go fetch some wine for your Master.
I'll discipline the kid from now on.
Could you stop interrupting?
I'm afraid I'll hurt you by accident.
The kid's all grown up now.
You think it's like before?
Get five doses with this prescription.
Then the illness will be cured.
No need.
Just have...
the doctor take a look.
No need to pay.
No need.
We don't...
We have no money for medicine.
Um...
Ruling!
Coming!
Come here, come here.
It's all right, it's all right.
That, um...
Uncle Li needs to buy medicine.
He's got no money.
Here, look.
This should be enough.
It's enough, it's enough.
This is plenty.
Thank you, Lao Jiugui.
Get up, get up, get up.
Take the money and get the medicine.
It's fine, it's fine.
All right, all right.
Dao ke dao...
Dao...
Dao ke...
Dao what Dao?
You're holding the book upside down.
What are you looking at me for?
Got peanuts on my face?
Even with all the peanuts in the world,
they're useless.
Listen, listen, listen.
It's empty.
If it's empty, then stop drinking.
At your age,
have some water.
You...
Water?
This...
Water...
has no alcohol in it!
My savior,
um...
Have a heart,
go fetch me some wine, won't you?
Just for tonight.
Okay?
Please?
It's not that I won't go.
This temple...
really has no money left.
Don't try to fool this old man.
You think I don't know?
The Mayor gives us...
ten silver dollars every month.
The Mayor gives that to you?
Yes, it's given to me.
He only gives it...
out of respect for Marshal Sun.
Even so,
it's given to me.
Marshal Sun was killed two years ago...
by his Adjutant.
The ten silver dollars stopped long ago.
My ill-fated Marshal Sun!
And the last silver dollar...
you just gave away too.
No way.
I'm going to take it back.
Go.
Go quickly.
Go on.
This...
Then how have we...
gotten by these past two years?
These two years,
it's all been Auntie Xiaoling
earning it through mending clothes.
That's been hard on you.
Ruling.
This hard...
What are you doing?
There are kids around!
You really ruin the mood.
No wonder Master doesn't like you.
Lao Jiugui!
Coming!
I'm begging you, please save me!
What are you doing?
You're kneeling to the wrong one.
Lao Jiugui!
Save me!
I beg you, please save my life!
Lao Jiugui!
Aren't you from Hanging Gourd Hall,
Shopkeeper Li?
Who died in your family?
Bring them over.
Lao Jiugui!
Nobody's dead yet!
Lao Jiugui, at a time like this,
could you stop joking around?
I'm not joking either.
Get up, get up.
Take it slow.
What's going on?
Lao Jiugui,
please come to my place
and take a look.
My house
is haunted!
Well, well...
For ghosts, you need a Taoist priest.
I'm a Lamp Keeper.
I can't catch ghosts.
This is...
I really...
There's nothing I can do.
Well...
I understand.
Lao Jiugui, look,
I get it.
Lao Jiugui,
as long as you
fix this for me,
afterwards,
I'll show my appreciation.
I'll also give you...
But I really...
Master,
just agree to help him.
I've never seen a ghost before.
I want to go see one.
See what?
Just read your books.
You look like a ghost to me.
Master,
just agree to help him.
You don't want Auntie Xiaoling
to work so hard, do you?
Well...
I guess it's not impossible.
Shopkeeper Li,
do you have wine at home?
Yes!
I have premium Tiger Bone Wine.
The finest quality.
Right.
Tiger bone—
that's so nourishing.
For you, it's not just a tonic.
For you, it's simply...
it's...
prepared just for you.
Alright.
Let's go, let's go.
Master,
we want to go too.
Go where?
Stay home and read.
Master,
take the kids with you.
I'll watch the house.
Let's go.
Come on, come on.
Let's go, let's go.
Hurry up, hurry up.
Tiger Bone Wine—
finally, we're saved.
Lao Jiugui,
we've been waiting for you!
This is our shopkeeper's home.
Please, come inside.
This is it.
Yeah.
What are you giving
this to me for?
Shopkeeper Li said
to give me Tiger Bone Wine later.
Where's your shopkeeper?
He went to fetch the wine.
He's scared, isn't he?
Aren't you scared?
Not scared.
Then why is your lantern shaking?
Just keeping up appearances.
It's fine, scared is scared.
Your shopkeeper
dropped to his knees at our place.
I'm scared too.
This residence,
even if it's not an Auspicious Land,
it's perfectly proper.
So tell me,
what's been going on here?
Every time it gets past midnight,
we hear knocking at the door.
But the moment we open it,
there's not a soul in sight.
Could it be a prank?
When my brother and I were kids,
when we got mischievous,
we used to do that too.
The shopkeeper and I
thought the same thing at first.
But once it got past midnight,
well...
it wasn't just knocking,
there was also...
Here we go.
Go on, tell me more.
What else was there?
There was also...
a female ghost's
crying.
Here it comes.
You two wait here.
Cowards.