I'm back.
Master.
Look what I brought you.
Tianjin fried dough twists.
And cat's ear snacks.
So you're back.
I'm not eating any of that.
That's what you say,
but you always end up eating a lot.
Auntie Xiaoling.
I brought this perfume for you.
It came all the way
from England,
shipped over on a big steamer.
Smells nice, huh?
It does smell like the ocean.
Let me spray some on you too.
Go on, spray it.
You're spraying it everywhere.
You just sprayed it into my wine!
At least you won't smell like an old man.
Now you're complaining I smell like an old man?
Weren't you the one cuddling me to sleep last night?
Hold on.
Last night, cuddling...
to sleep?
What part of that
did you not understand?
That's great!
Auntie Xiaoling,
you know what?
I've waited ten years for this day.
Come on, Master.
Let's go to a restaurant.
What are you so excited about?
It slipped out.
Just keep it to yourself.
Don't go telling everyone.
You'll make it
the talk of the town.
I'm embarrassed.
What's there to be embarrassed about?
At your age,
you still get embarrassed?
Does embarrassment depend on age?
Fine.
I'll just
go fix you two a couple of dishes.
You two chat.
Master,
tell me.
How did you destroy the vengeful spirit?
As soon as I entered the town,
I heard people talking about it.
Come on.
Pour the wine.
Dongsheng,
like I've always said,
in this world,
there are no ghosts.
That was Liu Kanshui's doing.
Liu Kanshui?
That's right.
The Sorceress, your Brigade Commander's favorite.
Back in the day,
I killed her brother.
She came back to get revenge on me this time.
That damn witch.
I'm going to shoot her right now.
All right, all right.
Change that temper of yours, will you?
Don't jump to conclusions.
Besides, you can't shoot her now.
She's your Brigade Commander's favorite.
Master,
tell me what happened.
I have no idea how Liu Kanshui
slipped the Illusion Grass Worm to Old Zhang.
The Illusion Grass Worm is actually
a poisonous grass that causes hallucinations.
It looks just like a maggot.
This poisonous grass
has three nasty traits.
First,
it sucks blood.
Second,
this grass is harmless during the day,
but wreaks havoc at night.
Third,
it can cloud a person's mind.
So Old Zhang
lay here in the Bone-Keeping Temple by day,
and went out from here at night
to hurt people.
Then, Master,
why would this worm
be afraid of the Brigade Commander's Talisman?
That's all nonsense.
It isn't afraid of his Talisman.
That Talisman,
pasted on the door,
let Liu Kanshui know
who paid up and who didn't.
For those who hadn't paid,
Liu Kanshui
smeared something on their doors.
What was it?
Shoe polish.
Shoe polish?
Because Old Zhang
shined shoes his whole life at Yin-Yang Crossing.
As soon as he smelled
shoe polish on a door,
he'd think he was
home.
Dongsheng,
peel some garlic for me.
Sure thing.
Then what was the Talisman you gave me about?
I drew it with sulfur.
Sulfur has a strong smell.
It can cover the shoe polish smell.
Lao Jiugui,
you really are a sly devil.
I'm just a fake one.
Master,
I heard that night,
he stood when you told him to,
and sat when you told him to.
That's because
I smeared shoe polish on the ground too.
And that...
the spell you used to set him on fire,
what kind of spell was it?
Teach me, would you?
I put white phosphorus
inside that lantern.
You know what white phosphorus is?
The moment it hits the air,
it bursts into flames.
Old Zhang
was cursed with the worm.
Blades and bullets couldn't harm him.
Burning him was the only way.
Actually, Old Zhang
was also a poor soul.
All right.
Anyway,
that's all in the past now.
Dongsheng,
why did you go to Tianjin?
Well, our Brigade Commander
made a fortune,
so he took me to Tianjin
to do a deal with the foreigners.
We ordered a shipment of German arms.
They said it will arrive next month.
Why are you acting so shocked?
What is it, Master?
They're buying those arms to attack Xiaolian.
How could I have missed that?
You have to think of something.
Xiaolian is your sister.
Don't worry.
Auntie Xiaoling,
even if it weren't for Xiaolian,
I wouldn't let those arms harm the people.
Good boy.
For saying that,
your Master here
will toast you.
Master,
this is the first time you've toasted me.
What?
You don't want to drink it?
Bottoms up.
The Communist Party guerrillas
will surely set an ambush on the main road.
Load all the arms onto the wagons,
and take the back trail through Wild Fox Ridge.
This is what we call
a diversionary tactic.
What are you eavesdropping on?
Eavesdropping?
I'm the Brigade Commander's Senior Adjutant.
Do I really need to eavesdrop?
You really want to know?
I can tell you right now.
Those German devils' arms are really something.
Yeah.
The ambush turned into a defensive battle.
It's Shuisheng!
Shuisheng!
Brothers, open fire!
Hurry, haul the arms over there.
Shuisheng.
Is hugging really the only way
you know how to show affection?
Even if you aren't sick of it, I am.
I heard that under Brigade Commander Li Chuanzhong,
you're already a Battalion Commander.
Then what's
all this?
Even if I were the Generalissimo,
I'd still take my sister's side.
What's going on with you two?
We...
There's nothing to be embarrassed about.
We've become outlaws.
Clear Wind Stronghold is our home now.
We heard the Communist Party was fighting here,
so we came to lend a hand.
But I didn't expect we'd reunite so soon.
This isn't the place to talk.
Let's evacuate first.
Right.
Okay.
Xiaolian's right.
We'll head out then.
All right, brother.
Take care.
If you need anything, come find us at Clear Wind Stronghold.
Hope you have a little chieftain soon.
All right, sis.
I should get going too.
Before the Brigade Commander gets suspicious.
Okay.
Brother.
Send my regards to Master and Auntie Xiaoling.
Will do.
Maybe by the time you come back next,
you'll have little junior disciples.
What do you mean?
Nothing.
Oh, right.
Here, take this.
For you.
I don't need it.
Take it.
I've got it all up here anyway.
Thank you, Comrade Dongsheng.
You're welcome,
Comrade Xiaolian.
What?
It's all gone?
Who did it?
We're investigating.
Useless fools!
Good-for-nothings!
Why so furious, Brigade Commander?
That shipment of German arms I ordered
was completely hijacked.
Do you know who did it?
If I knew who did it,
wouldn't I have gone and taken it back already?
Would I need to be sitting here fuming?
I do have some leads.
What lead?
I suspect you have a mole by your side.
Who?
Your Guard Battalion Commander,
Dongsheng.
Impossible.
Absolutely impossible.
I was afraid of leaks too,
so
for this transport,
I didn't use any of my own men.
The escort team
were all hired by the seller.
Since you put it that way, Brigade Commander,
I must've overthought it.
Sorceress,
military matters
are not your concern.
Hurry up and think of a way
to make up for my loss this time.
Alright.
That made me jump!
Brother-in-law.
Come, hand these out to everyone.
Everyone, take a look at this flyer.
Let me just say a few words.
A philanthropist from England,
an educator,
Ms. Maria Amari,
is planning to open a girls' school
in our provincial capital.
For ages roughly
between ten and sixteen.
Everyone, have a look.
I was wondering what the good news was.
Just this?
Yeah.
I thought it was something good.
Forget it, let's go.
Let's go.
Did you guys read it carefully?
We can't even afford to send our boys to school.
How could we send our girls?
Exactly.
Not to mention it's a school founded by foreign devils.
This...
We can't afford to attend this.
Ignorant.
Foolish.
Did I say it costs money?
It's free!
Everyone, listen to me.
We aren't charging money.
Moreover, when every girl comes,
we can reimburse
travel fees,
uniform fees,
boarding fees,
and food expenses.
Moreover, I promise you all,
if a girl comes to our school to study,
each household will receive
one silver dollar
as a family subsidy.
Is there really such a good deal?
I tell you,
I'd dare dream of being the emperor before
I'd dare dream of a deal this good.
Am I right, folks?
Exactly.
Everyone, listen to me.
You might not believe me,
but
surely you believe our mayor?
Fellow townsfolk,
even if
you don't trust me either,
come,
take a look here.