Master, Master!
Wake up, get up!
What's the fuss so early in the morning?
We found the murder weapon while dredging the dry well.
Look.
Let me see.
It's an ordinary watermelon knife.
but it's worth noting that
when we found it, it was wrapped in a raincoat.
Raincoat?
Gong Sun He, what do you think?
I'll go and do a wound comparison first.
Chief,
there's a man outside trying to force his way in.
Who's so bold?
Let's go take a look.
Sir,
this is a crime scene, you can't go in.
I've said this several times already.
I'm a lawyer.
A lawyer?
A lawyer, huh?
Even lawyers can't barge into a crime scene.
You're the lawyer in charge of the will
for the owner of this house, Mr. Lu Tianyang, right?
Yes, my name is Lin Tian.
I'm here to work today.
I'm here to announce Mr. Lu Tianyang's will.
Alright then, let him in.
What do you mean the will's publication needs to be postponed?
Because the killer hasn't been caught yet.
Our investigation here isn't over either.
Ah.
What right do you have to interfere in our family affairs?
Right?
By virtue of my position as the police chief.
Is that enough authority?
You greedy descendants.
arguing about the inheritance again.
What are you saying here, you old geezer?
Our family matters
are none of your business.
I'm warning you.
I don't care if you're a real uncle or a fake one,
don't meddle in our family affairs.
Young man,
you're asking for trouble.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Alright, let's do this.
There's no need for you to argue over something like this.
When the will is announced later,
I'll watch from the side.
Why didn't you say so earlier?
This uncle's skills
are impressive.
His skills
are indeed those of an expert.
If that's the case,
uncle's bodyguard,
Anderson's skills must be even better than his.
I'd really like to test them out.
Qingtian,
I didn't know you had this hobby.
Martial artists always want to test themselves against stronger opponents.
they always want to give it a try.
Alright.
But I'm still wondering,
if this uncle's skills are so good,
is it necessary for him
to hire bodyguards to protect himself?
Maybe he feels safer with an extra person for protection.
Hmm.
Let's go inside.
Okay.
Now then,
I will announce Mr. Lu Tianyang's
last will and testament.
Please listen carefully.
Where's the will?
I remember putting it in my bag.
Where did that arrow come from?
It's a delayed device.
Once the time is up and the alarm goes off,
it will automatically break out and shoot the hidden weapon.
Who set this up?
Who on earth
would set up something like this?
This is attempted murder!
Who on earth
set up this trap?
I think
it must be that uncle you mentioned yesterday.
It has to be him.
He's also the one who was peeping at the back door yesterday.
He must have sneaked into our house.
He's planning to kill one of us
to show up here and inherit the estate.
Damn, just for a larger share of the inheritance,
is it necessary to do such a thing?
No.
He didn't do it.
How do you know it wasn't him?
Follow me inside and take a look.
This should be the killer.
Repeated experiments to determine the direction of attack.
The purpose was to shoot and kill
the person who would always sit there.
If I'm not mistaken,
the matter of reading the will
must have been decided to be in the conference room long ago, right?
Then,
how did the killer know who would sit where?
Of course he knew.
The Lu family is a big clan.
Big families always like to follow the rules.
As the current head of the Lu family, Lu Jingtai
would certainly sit at the head of the table.
And the seat to the left of the head
is reserved for the person
with the highest seniority in the family after the head.
So the person the killer wanted to kill was
your uncle,
Mr. Lu Tianci.
I knew it.
Those black-hearted people want my old life.
Saying the threatening letter was a prank.
I think
it must be that man who was peeping at the back door yesterday.
It seems your uncle really hates our family to death.
It's very possible.
Maybe the killer is sitting in some corner right now,
watching us with a cold sneer.
We found
an unfinished cigarette in the backyard warehouse.
May I ask if anyone here smokes?
No,
no one in the family smokes except my father.
That's strange then.
Because that cigarette was still warm.
Song Si, take me to see it.
The man with sunglasses must still be nearby.
Go search quickly.
Not only that,
when I examined the murder weapon,
I only found the victim Xu Yazhi's blood and fingerprints.
Moreover, from the fingerprint marks,
it appears the victim held the knife handle in a natural grip.
Natural grip?
That's impossible.
If she was being stabbed,
she would instinctively grab the knife,
but it should be a reverse grip,
not a forward grip.
Could the killer be trying to make it look like suicide?
I don't think that's possible.
The killer couldn't be that stupid.
I'm back.
How did it go?
I went to the Pingkang Hotel.
According to the hotel manager and Xu Yazhi's friend,
Xu Yazhi did go to the hotel last night.
But they don't know when she left.
I also checked the call records at the switchboard.
Indeed, at 9 o'clock at the hotel,
there was a call made from the Pingkang Hotel
to the Lu family mansion.
Tian Shan,
you said yesterday that your second aunt called at 9 p.m.
and said she wouldn't be home until after 11, right?
That's right.
At first, I couldn't hear clearly what she was saying.
The last sentence was the clearest.
But why did she come back around 10 o'clock
when she clearly said she'd be back after 11:30?
You all come back first.
The lawyer has found the will.
It will be announced soon.
Let's go.
Xiao Fu,
show me their statements again.
Here you go.
Who is this Gu Wanting?
She said she seemed to have seen
Xu Yazhi making a phone call at 9 o'clock.
She's a waitress at the Pingkang Hotel.
But she said she couldn't really remember.
She's not sure if anyone made a phone call.
That's not right.
If she can't remember
whether a call was made or not, that's possible.
But not remembering who made the call,
that's a bit stupid.
You think
this waitress is suspicious?
That's right.
Okay, I'll go investigate.
Mm-hmm.
Wait a moment.
What's wrong, A He?
I already know.
who the culprit behind these two cases really is.
Who is it?