Raise red, raise white,
don't lower red, lower white.
Lower red, raise red,
raise white, lower white.
Hey, wait!
Wasn't that weird just now?
Funny face, right?
Again?
Funny face festival!
- Fine, here we go. Ready?
- Funny face festival.
Thanks to my routine, a brief peace had
settled over the Yanagida household,
but I still hadn't told Chika
about my great idea.
Funny face!
We're gonna make you pull a funny face!
Do you think you can go, Taro?
Don't force it. It's totally fine
if you can't go.
Come on! They picked the flag-raising game,
and we practiced a ton.
Don't force him to go.
I'm not forcing him, but if he goes,
it'll boost his confidence.
Taro, you decide. Either way is fine.
You've worked so hard already.
Even Mama's terrified of performing.
No go, huh.
Okay. I'll go.
Wait, you will? Are you sure?
If I don't go, there's no one
to call out the flag commands.
That's right! Good boy, Taro.
You'll feel great once you do it.
But don't come watch, okay?
What? Why not? I wanna see!
- I don't want it.
- It's fine, we won't go.
We're just happy
you're going to school at all.
It's at the morning assembly, right?
It's time. Should I take you by bike?
No, I'm fine. I'll walk.
Okay. See you later!
Wait, we're really not going?
Oh please. Of course we're going.
He's embarrassed to be watched by you.
We'll sneak in and watch secretly.
Then let's hurry! Are we taking the bike?
Are you stupid? If we leave now,
we'll catch up to him!
Oh, right, right.
So let's go inside for now...
Inside? No, hold on,
we just wait a bit, then go!
How many minutes?
Three, four, five minutes.
- Three, four, five minutes?
- Five minutes!
- Okay.
- Let's go in five.
Hey, calm down. Close it, close it.
Alright!
Ta-da!
Yay!
Thank you!
Here we go!
- Shall we have some action tonight?
- I'm so glad to be alive!
I Still Want to Do It with My Wife
Episode 10: Married Manzai Duo
I'm sorry you came all this way,
especially before work.
Well, I had a feeling this would happen.
But I really thought he could pull it off.
It can't be helped. But I think
he's probably feeling pretty down.
About running away at the last minute.
Please, look after him for us.
Of course. I think it's wonderful
he made it as far as he did.
Thank you. We'll be going now.
Thank you.
Hey, stop making that face. The teacher said
he did great just getting this far.
You're expecting too much.
I know, but I thought this was
a small step, you know...
A chance for him to build some confidence.
It
was
a small step. More than enough.
Worry about yourself, alright?
You'd better show some results.
Also, hang out the futons to air.
And vacuum the bedroom.
Wait a sec!
What? I'm running late here.
No, um, well...
What?
So, about those results you mentioned...
Wait, do we have to talk about this now?
I have to get to work, unlike you.
Fine, I'll say it in five seconds.
- Make it two.
- Okay.
Um...
Will you form a manzai comedy duo with me?
Huh? What? Who?
Me and you, Chika.
What are you saying?
Are you stupid? Seriously.
Wait, wait. Just hear me out.
I'll explain calmly.
You know I've always been into comedy, right?
Like I said before, we used to go
to comedy shows all the time.
And you even said I was funnier
than Summers, remember?
I never said that. And clinging
to past glories like that? It's pathetic.
I'm not clinging to past glories or anything.
Yes, you are! I complimented you. It's one
of the few things you can be proud of.
Fine, let's leave it at that then.
So what if I make it big as a comedian first,
then break into film and TV from there?
You know, like Takeshi.
With manzai comedy, we only need two people.
People from other fields make movies
all the time with zero talent.
You have zero talent, too!
Why do I have to be your manzai partner?
I just feel like it would
definitely work out with you, Chika.
Plus, while helping Taro practice,
I realized something.
Showing Taro that his parents take on
a manzai challenge could be
a really wonderful thing for him.
You know that live venue
by the station? Marquee?
They do comedy shows there sometimes.
We went to one when we moved here, remember?
That totally unfunny show.
Remember, they had
an amateur segment? Do you recall that?
What if we performed there a bunch
and built up a reputation?
What do you think?
Just hang out the futons to air.
Forget it, and you're dead.
A married couple in their 40s debuting
in manzai might even go viral online.
These half-baked little delusions were
already creeping into my mind.
I'm home!
Welcome back.
Hi.
How'd it go? Your school presentation.
Hmm? Fine, I guess.
Did they laugh?
Yeah, sort of.
Which part got laughs?
Huh?
Did they really like it?
It's okay if they didn't.
Hey, did you really do it?
I'll watch this elsewhere.
Taro, wanna go grocery shopping
for dinner with me?
No thanks.
I'm home!
I'm back.
Welcome back.
Huh? Where's Taro?
Probably in the bedroom
or workroom, watching his iPad.
You didn't say something stupid again,
did you? Like about his presentation.
I didn't say anything.
You're always so pushy.
Hey, the futons are still out.
Bring them in already.
Oh, sorry, sorry.
Seriously, do what you're supposed to.
Taro! Taro, I'm home.
Broccoli?
Broccoli. Not cauliflower.
Not cauliflower?
It's growing out of his head!
Could it be...
You were totally grilling Taro
about his comedy role, weren't you?
He says you're too pushy,
so he's staying over there.
I just asked him casually.
Seriously, stop it.
You're always so relentless.
Also, about those results
you mentioned this morning.
Huh?
Don't "huh" me.
You're serious about this, right?
Oh, this morning's topic.
That's what I said! God, you're annoying.
I'm serious.
You better be. Then actually commit to it.
Don't you dare bail.
I won't bail.
Say it again. Louder.
I won't bail...
Then fine, I'll do it.
But you better come up
with a damn good routine.
If it's something lame
like the flag-raising game, count me out.
Honestly, I was getting a little scared.
This willingness to commit is
what makes Chika amazing,
and also incredibly reckless.
When Chika makes up her mind,
her resolve is something else.
Was forming a comedy duo really
the right path for us as a couple?
The more I thought about it, the more
an indescribable fear welled up inside me.
Here.
Huh? Wait, what's this?
Got it from a live venue.
I already signed us up.
Huh?
November 10th? That's so soon!
You're serious about this, right?
Then sooner's better.
All right!
And if you write something boring,
I'll kill you.
I had no choice
but to start writing material for that show.
We got married and formed a duo
as husband and wife,
but we divorced four years ago,
so now we're a duo of total strangers.
Nice to meet you all!
Wow, Dad, you've really gotten
into stand-up comedy, huh?
Well, Dad ended up forming
a comedy duo with Mom.
With Mom?
Any ideas what we should do?
Huh? Why not just do the flag-raising game?
That's a no-go, apparently.
Mom's so mean, right?
She said to write
something funnier than that.
Then Mom's funny face! Make a funny face
and sing like Doburock. That'll be great!
Yeah, but Daddy's a terrible singer.
You're so picky.
Then dirty stuff.
Dirty jokes always get laughs.
Dirty stuff? Like what?
You'd know, Dad.
Well, yeah.
Hey, if it flops,
can we join Doburock's fan club?
The Doburock fan club
and this are two separate things.
But you're the one who asked me!
I just asked what kind of stuff is good.
That's not the same thing.
Dad, why are you smirking?
I just thought of a funny routine.
What? Tell me!
No way.
It's dirty, isn't it?
Yep.
Huh? What?
I'm sorry.
Dad just came up with a funny routine.
Ugh, it's gonna be lame again.
Just like the flag-raising game.
That was fun, though.
Yeah, it was fun.
How was that fun? It's just a game.
- Like the funny faces.
- Yeah, the funny faces.
That's not a routine.
Funny face.
Huh?
Why?
Why do I have to do it?
- Funny face.
C'mon, do it for real.
Why would I do that for real
while we're eating? No way.
- When you get the call, you gotta!
- Like this?
The rule is you have to go all out.
No exceptions.
Um, got a minute?
You'd barge in even if I said no.
You never wait for consent.
Sorry.
So, I wrote some material.
And?
I want you to look at it later.
After Taro is asleep.
If it's boring, I'm seriously not doing this.
I'm not too confident either.
Please.
What is this?
What's supposed to be funny?
No, it's probably funny.
You were laughing too, Chika.
I was laughing at how stupid it is.
This whole thing's riding on my funny face.
Your funny faces make it good.
You don't see stuff like this, you know!
How would I know? Unlike you,
I'm busy. No time to watch comedy.
Wait, just a little.
Just a bit.
Hm?
Wanna try running through it?
- Right now?
- Yeah. Just to try it.
Hey there, everyone! I'm Tsumi!
Hey there, everyone! I'm Batsu.
Together, we're Dostoevsky!
This is kinda embarrassing.
You can't be the one getting shy!
So, we're a husband-and-wife manzai duo
on the verge of breaking up...
Let's make it married manzai.
- Married manzai duo?
- Yeah.
- Don't tell me what to say.
- It'll be better.
We're a married manzai duo.
You came up with a funny bit today, right?
Yep, nailed it.
If it's boring, we're divorcing.
Well, I'm confident this time. We are
actually suffering from a loss of libido.
That's right. We don't just have
less of it, we lost it.
Wait, is this necessary?
- It's corny.
- No, a bit of corny stuff works, trust me.
It's all corny, though.
No, no.
That's exactly why we, a couple
without libido, should do this routine.
Go on, let's hear it.
We each pick a celebrity we would sleep with
and act out the faces and sounds
we'd make at the climax.
Wait, what?
You like Koichi Sato, right?
You would act out the face and voice
right before you finish with Koichi Sato.
Huh? What? Like this?
I just did it with Koichi!
Oh no, I'm coming! Squeeze.
Hey, will this really gonna get laughs?
Well, today's just our first read-through,
so we can refine it from here.
I put a lot of thought into this, you know.
Like, maybe use his full name
instead of just "Koichi."
Sorry, I don't get it at all.
You're more into the Kin-chan types,
so maybe this isn't your thing.
Okay, Koichi Sato is fine,
but what's up with Bekako Katsura?
I want Hugh or Ken Takakura.
"Hugh?" Oh, you mean Hugh Grant?
Yeah. And when will you stop
having a crush on Mitsu Dan?
Hey, it's fine. It works better
if we pick people we actually like.
Wait, didn't you have a thing for Bekako?
I like him, but not like that.
Plus, he goes by Master Nanko now.
Anyway, I'm going to bed.
I've got a bad feeling about all this.
Can't you write something else?
Something like Yasu & Kiyo?
- Good night.
- Yeah, good night.
Still, after Taro went to sleep,
Chika and I rehearsed night after night.
I just did it with Hugh Grant!
Oh no, I'm coming! Squeeze.
You gotta do the funny face
on the "squeeze" part, or it won't land.
Come on, I've only done it a few times,
there's no way I can pull it off.
No, I think that's a mindset thing.
It's fine, we're just practicing.
No, you're holding back right now.
I don't need comments from you.
You try it yourself.
- No, it's your bit now.
- You should do it, too.
I just did it with Jennifer Lawrence!
Oh no...
Why are you embarrassed?
That was weak. So lame.
I just did it with Shohei Hino...
Wait, it was Shohei Uno.
I just did it with Shohei Uno.
So cute, I can't even...
What's this?
This makes no sense. "So cute, I can't even!'
I was just writing from your perspective.
You so don't get it.
Oh my God, I just did it with Koichi Sato!
Oh no, I'm coming! Squeeze.
But yeah, Koichi Sato really gets me going.
It does feel different when you say his name.
Love matters, huh.
I just did it with Brad Pitt!
Oh no, I'm coming! Bang!
I just did it with Ryoko Yonekura!
Oh!
I never fail.
I told you, stop saying that stuff to me!
Say it to the audience!
If we're talking about that,
you've been looking down the whole time.
I'm reading the script, okay?
- They'll be there, you know.
- I don't know it yet!
I was getting scared all over again.
I had a feeling that performing this would
lead to something truly terrible.
I just did it with Kate Winslet, too.
When I say "Titanic pose," you do this...
Shohei Uno?
No, no, no! This part!
Next Episode Preview
I'm nervous too, you know!
Wait. Hold me.
Is this some kind of punishment game?
Is my whole life a punishment game?
I don't think that's true.
It's all my fault. It's all my fault
for not living my own life!