Hey there, everyone!
I'm Tsumi.
Hi, I'm Batsu.
We're a married manzai duo
on the verge of breaking up.
- You came up with a funny bit today, right?
- Yep, nailed it.
We'll show you the faces and voices
we'd make right before we come.
I just did it with Koichi Sato.
Oh no, I'm coming! Squeeze.
Hey there, everyone!
- I'm Tsumi.
- Hi, I'm Batsu.
Together, we're called Dostoevsky!
I just did it with Jennifer Lawrence.
Ahhh, ngh.
Oh no... I'm coming, ohhh!
I just did it with Cameron Diaz.
Ahhh, guh!
And finally,
the day of the audition arrived.
I felt like Rocky
before his fight with Apollo.
Rocky stepped into the ring,
certain he could never beat Apollo.
I, too, had a meaningless certainty
that our act would absolutely bomb.
But there was one big difference
between me and Rocky.
Oh, you're up.
This is bad. I'm crazy nervous.
Me, too.
Don't you dare get nervous.
Rocky fought a battle he knew he'd lose
to prove he wasn't just a lowlife.
But by dragging Chika into this fight,
I felt like I was only proving
that I really am just a lowlife.
Alright, I'm gonna go
get a little more sleep.
Okay.
Alright!
Ta-da!
Yay!
Thank you!
Here we go!
- Shall we have some action tonight?
- I'm so glad to be alive!
I Still Want to Do It with My Wife
Taro, hold the fort, okay?
Mommy and Daddy will do their best.
Episode 11: Am I stupid?
I wanna come watch, too.
Sorry, Taro. But it'd be embarrassing
if you saw Mommy and Daddy perform.
We didn’t go watch you either, did we?
In exchange, you can use the iPad all day.
- Really?
- Yep.
Okay, good luck!
All right, we're off!
- Bye-bye!
- See ya later!
Right, let's go.
What is it? Get moving, come on.
Maybe we should've let Taro
come watch us do comedy.
Are you crazy? Not with that routine. No way.
But he watches Doburock all the time.
He's probably immune to dirty jokes.
Our act is way cruder than Doburock.
You think so?
Wait, is that a compliment?
Hell no! Why would you even think that?
Are you stupid?
- Hello.
- Hello, ma'am.
Yes.
- D-Dost...
- Dos-to-ev... Just a sec. It's Dostoevsky.
- So, you're Dostoevsky?
- Dostoevsky, yes.
- Yes.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Please come back here at least
30 minutes before the audition.
Got it.
- We'll go in sign-up order.
- Okay, thank you.
Good luck.
Move it, you're in the way!
- Good morning.
So... I just did it with Ken Takakura!
Oh no, I'm coming! Squeeze.
Um, I just did it with Ken Takakura!
Hey, your line's up next!
Oh, sorry... who was the next one?
Huh? Mitsu Dan, obviously.
Are you okay?
You've had no energy this whole time.
I'm just nervous, so I feel a bit sick.
Get it together.
This whole thing was your idea.
Seriously.
I'm gonna buy another one.
- You want to drink more?
- I'm nervous too, you know!
Ow, damn it.
Come on, hurry up.
Alright.
Stop making that face.
Pull yourself together.
Okay, okay, settle down, please.
Thank you all for coming here today.
We'll now be starting the audition.
We're hoping to select two
or maybe three acts from you all.
Those selected will perform
in the live show starting at 6 pm.
Some people have gone professional from here,
so if that's your goal, give it your all.
Our judges will be
these distinguished comedy writers here.
- That's enough of that.
- They worked on
The God Tongue
.
No, that was Gogoro.
He's tall, too.
Same thing, really.
Well then, let's go in sign-up order.
Let me see...
- The Water Flees?
- Yes!
- Water Flees!
Go ahead, please.
- Good luck.
- Thank you, sir!
Here we go!
- Hi everyone!
- Hi!
- Hi, we're the Water Flees!
- Thanks for having us!
Um, I really love baseball clinics,
so I'm gonna do one.
What's your 50-meter dash time?
50-meter dash time, huh?
15 seconds!
- Well, kids are usually—
- That's slow!
Don't be so blunt! It's mean!
- What's Isao Harimoto's dash time?
- A pro's dash time, huh.
- 14.9 seconds.
- That's barely any different!
This blond guy's been stalking me.
Huh?
- Toshi!
- You were a stalker?!
Can't believe you're going to Tokyo, but—
C'mon, get pumped! Get pumped!
Let's go! Here we go!
Come at me! Low and hard, come on!
What kinda throw was that?
Try to knock me out!
Come on, gather here!
And next up...
The Knock on the Knee duo!
Knock-knock, knock-knock,
knock on the knee!
Thanks, we were Knock on the Knee!
One more time for Knock on the Knee!
Please exit the stage.
Thank you!
And next up is...
D-D-Dostoevsky!
- Yes! Here!
- Dostoevsky, please.
That's us, Dostoevsky. Yes.
Come, we're on.
Get it together. You wanted results, right?
Hey!
Yeah... okay.
- Whenever you're ready.
- Right. Let's go.
Wait.
Huh?
Embrace me.
What are you saying?!
I'm nervous too, you know. Let's do this.
Hey there, everyone!
I'm Tsumi!
Hi, I am... Batsu.
-Together we are...
-We are...
Dostoevsky!
You were totally late, idiot!
Uh, how did it go again?
Don't give me that.
So believe it or not, we're actually
suffering from a loss of libido.
- We don't just have less of it. We lost it.
- Yeah, yeah, loss... Los Lobos.
What are you even saying?
So we decided to each pick our favorite
celebrity and imagine doing it with them.
Yeah. Doing it. Doing it.
Speak up! That's supposed
to be your line anyway!
Like, you're into Mitsu Dan, right?
So you'll show everyone the face
you'd make after doing it with Mitsu Dan.
No, I can't...
Don't give me that!
Fine, I'll go first then.
So, I absolutely love Koichi Sato.
I just did it with Koichi Sato!
Oh no, I'm coming! Squeeze!
What are you doing? It's your turn!
Da-Dan... Dan...
I just did it with Mitsu Dan... Squeeze.
I just did it with Hugh Jackman!
Oh no, I'm coming! Hew-hew, baby!
It's your turn!
I just did it with Brad Pitt!
Oh no, I'm coming! Pew pew!
I just did it with DiCaprio!
Oh no, I'm coming! Titanic!
I just did it with Ken Takakura!
Oh no, I'm coming! He's so clumsy!
I just did it with Shohei Uno!
Oh no! Too cute! Blegh!
I thought I'd be better off dead.
I just did it with Hugh Jackman again!
Oh no, I'm coming! Squeeze!
Thank you very much!
Oh, um... thank you!
- Well then, please exit the stage.
- Okay.
All right, next up, um...
- I'm thinking of taking up judo at my age.
- Judo at your age? That's unusual.
- And I think the very first move is crucial.
- Yeah, it is everything.
What's wrong?
What am I doing?
What is this?
Am I stupid?
This...
This isn't my life.
It's not like I had big goals or anything.
So what the hell is this?
Why?
I work to cover for you.
And for what? Is this some punishment?
Is my whole life some sort of punishment?
That's not true.
But...
This happened because I didn't
live my life right.
I don't think that's true.
I know it, deep down.
I've been looking the other way,
from my own life.
Nobody knows that better than me!
But...
Why the hell did I end up with you?
Seriously, what are you?
Who even are you? Get it together!
You said you'd get results.
And what was that?
How did we end up like this?
You should try harder. Harder!
I...
I'm so frustrated.
So damn frustrated.
'Cause I thought you were
the greatest, you know?
Aren't I so damn pathetic?
But I didn't have the guts.
I was just whining
about my life all the time.
I'm pathetic.
This is your fault.
Or actually...
I'm the pathetic one
blaming you for everything.
Actually, it's all my fault.
It's all my fault for not living my own life.
But you know what?
You pull yourself together, too!
Just do it!
Don't make me tell you that! I don't wanna.
God, I'm so pathetic.
A hundred times more pathetic than you.
Fifteen years and ten months ago
Welcome back. How'd it go?
It...
didn't work out again.
I see.
Yeah.
I thought it was funny, though.
What could have gone wrong?
I'm so frustrated.
So frustrated.
But you must feel it even more, Gota.
Taro, we're home.
Welcome back. How'd it go?
Yeah. It was fun.
Got any laughs?
Not really.
That's why I told you, you should've
done the flag-raising game.
Yeah, you're right.
I'm hungry.
I'll make something.
Mama's tired, so she's gonna
take a bath first, okay?
Okay.
Oh, right! You said if it bombed,
I could join Doburock's fan club, right?
I decided to try writing
a screenplay for the first time in a while.
I wanted to write about Chika.
I wanted to write a story
about how she is the best,
yet also the worst person at the same time.
Next Episode Preview
I'm gonna live however I want.
If you keep putting on airs,
it won't resonate with anyone.
I figured maybe we just
have to do it.
I don't care what happens to you.
I love you.
Well, I don't love you.