ALL DEPICTED EVENTS ARE FICTIONAL
From now on,
I'll devote even more of my love to you.
I'll also love you more and more.
At least we became
boyfriends at your house.
On top of that,
we also created new memories there.
What I wanted was
a hug from my parents.
It's time to stop holding
your younger self's hand and hold mine.
I'll be everything for you.
Walk with me, Qin.
Here you go.
Drink so you can feel refreshed.
Look at you drinking Ichitan.
You're adorable!
You're also adorable, Duang.
Adorable, my ass.
What are you looking at?
You're wearing my outfit today.
Let's do a fit check.
It's too early for this.
What's with that look?
I don't want you to overthink.
Overthink?
About last night?
Yes.
I'm done overthinking. There is
something else I need to think about.
Whoa…
You're right! The jazz showcase is today!
Are you nervous?
No.
Eat your food.
I'm not eating!
Okay, let's go.
Whoa! What?
I can walk.
- Hey.
- Huh?
Let's head out.
- It's looking pretty good.
- Yeah, it's a big event.
Whoa… What's the matter?
- Huh?
- In a hurry?
I'm buying roti for Qin. Want anything?
Absolutely. I'll have one with egg
and a lot of condensed milk.
A lot of condensed milk?
Jamie! I'd love to set
your messy system straight.
I'm dying to see what kind of person
you're falling in love with.
Stay out of it.
- Hey, I know…
- Whoa!
You're hiding something from me!
I'm sulking now.
Damn you!
Yes, baby?
I don't think I'll have time to eat.
I have to be on standby.
Okay, I'll be right with you.
I'm going to see Qin.
Find seats in front and call me.
What? Wait!
What about my roti with egg?
Jeez, what's with that dude?
He's out here selling my roti dreams.
I've never seen anyone so madly in love.
I'm mad.
Good luck.
You can do it, my baby.
What? Why did you take off your shirt?
I got hot.
Let's meet halfway then.
Were you trying to concentrate?
Are you nervous?
Now that you're here,
I don't feel nervous anymore.
Then…
Can you give me a smile?
Why here? It's a waste of film.
It's never a waste when it comes to you.
Let's take one together.
How about a selfie?
Three, two, one.
Wow.
Come on, Qin.
Let's get ready by the stage.
I won't say good luck
because you don't need it.
But I will say, "You can do it!"
Hold these for me.
Come on.
Right, Daung.
About what I said before,
I'm sorry I meddled.
It's fine.
I understand that
you wanted the event to go smoothly,
but…
I made Qin overthink that day.
But you did great earlier.
He might seem reserved,
but his heart was warmed by your support.
I'll be cheering.
- Hello?
- I'm by the stage, on the right side.
Alright, I'm coming.
TRUST GANGNAM CLINIC FOR HAIR REMOVAL
What a charming voice.
Shit!
The jazz students are on fire!
They're really going all out
with this year's event.
- Do you see that?
- What?
The art was done
by the Decorative Art students.
It looks awesome!
Well, it's the art students.
- How could it not be?
- Right on.
It's amazing. Sheesh!
Did you hear that?
More than clear.
They said that our artwork looks awesome.
- "Our," my ass!
- What?
You disappeared for days.
Well, I was the leader.
I was the leader!
- You were?
- Jeez!
If you were the leader,
I was your right hand man. Case closed.
- Shit…
- How fussy.
- Shit!
- What?!
Qin is up!
The stage looks awesome.
What's wrong?
He's so handsome it hurts.
How could someone
be so handsome,
talented,
and cool?
I already told you he's a ten!
Girl,
doesn't he look stressed out?
Maybe he's so serious
that he can't feel it.
Qin, you're gonna get in trouble.
Qin, baby!
Qin!
Qin, you're totally my type!
Damn, you're always so extra.
It's embarrassing.
Do you think… What the fuck is with you?
If you look up at the sky one day
When the rain's coming
The clouds dress in gray
But you know, the clouds won't last…
Damn,
that's some good music!
Leave me right here
'cause I just can't.
Even if today
Your dream's long to bloom
Be kind to yourself tonight
As long as you believe
That your hope stays close to you
Beautiful days come with time
Just smiling back at yourself once again
Smile through the storm and falling rain
Better days are waiting
Happiness will find you
It wasn't meant to be
Can't you see?
And I just had to leave
Now, I'm free
How could I think to myself
That you were the one for me?
I think we all agree
You're not my cup of tea
How could I think to myself
That you were the one for me?
I think we all agree
You're not my cup of tea
You're my cup of tea
Whoa…
- Whoa…
- Got it?
Hello, Mr. Prachai.
Jettana here, live from the scene.
We're encountering a situation
where a student's heart skipped a beat.
Hey!
Hey…
I'd like to know something.
What makes your heart skip a beat?
It's my boyfriend.
"Boyfriend"!
I wish I could be all over him now.
From what you've heard,
how does it make you feel?
All the feels!
- But I won't ship them anymore.
- What?
They are an item now!
May I ask where you are?
There's a flower delivery for you.
Hi.
Alright.
Here are the flowers.
May I take a photo?
Okay, thank you.
GOOD JOB, QIN
FROM DAD AND MOM
INCOMING CALL FROM MOM
Qin!
Let's head back.
Let me carry those.
Aw, this was really nice of your parents.
They never miss an event, huh?
They're busy.
Only their flowers can make it.
You must be so tired, my Qin.
Do you want to eat something?
I'll order it for you.
You did an amazing job today.
When you sang,
the audience was really into it.
You really felt the song.
I couldn't take my eyes off you.
You seemed like
an entirely different person onstage
with how you held yourself.
I was clenching my fists so tightly.
How dramatic.
How was I even holding myself?
It's true.
Everyone was so impressed.
I'm getting kinda possessive.
But I do want everyone
to respect your skills.
When did you become so rational?
When I fell in love with you.
Here.
This is my gift for you.
I love you.
Thank you, Duang,
for always sticking by my side.
Are you sad?
Just tired.
You're tired?
Duang.
Sing for me.
You want me to sing for you?
Are you serious?
Come on.
I want you by my side
Only you by my side
Nothing more
Nothing else I wish to adore
I want only you and me
Only us in my mind
Just us two
It's better than
Everything I've ever known
That's beautiful.
Did you receive the flowers we sent?
Sunflowers really suit you,
our smart cookie.
Is everything okay?
Ever since I let go
of my younger self's hand to hold yours,
I've become more sensitive.
It's not a bad thing.
It's just new.
So…
what do you feel?
Lonely.
I mean,
all this time,
I've been so lonely.
You…
Don't.
Don't feel bad for me.
I just wanna say that
before I met you…
I was so lonely.
I was always lonely.
It was like I had no one.
I'm okay now.
I am…
Hey…
Can I ask you for one thing?
Can you try telling your mom and dad
how you feel?
No.
I don't wanna talk to them.
Are you mad at them?
Yes.
And I'm scared…
that they won't listen.
All this time, they never listened to you?
Then…
Wanna play a game with me?
Send them a text.
Tell them you want them to come here,
and if they tell you that they're coming…
we'll talk to them.
I'm out.
You'll never know until you try.
You don't have to play the game with me.
But I do want you to ask yourself,
from the bottom of your heart,
what you want…
like how you trusted yourself earlier.
Papa, Mama…
I want you and Dad to be here with me.
Can you come here?
How are you feeling?
Can you tell me?
Scared.
Qin,
your Mom and Dad love you.
Or they wouldn't have
come back so quickly.
Come on.
- Hello, Mom, Dad.
- Hello there.
- Hi, Duang.
- Hello.
Look, I brought you lots of gifts.
Here are some snacks.
Let me take these.
- Here.
- Thank you.
- Thanks, Duang.
- You're welcome.
Qin.
Wow…
Look,
your place is crisp and clean.
That's my son.
Goodness, honey.
What are you worried about?
Qin is doing great living alone.
Right, Qin.
The jazz showcase is over, right?
I asked my secretary to send you flowers.
You said
you wanted us to come over.
Is everything okay?
Do you need something?
I'll buy it for you.
It's not like that.
- It's--
- I know.
You're mad at us for not attending
your jazz showcase, aren't you?
No.
Well, that's part of it.
But…
I do have something to tell you.
Sure.
What is it?
I've never felt
like you were truly there for me.
Why…
Why would you say that?
I've never forgotten
the memories of being abused.
I don't know if you know that,
or if you are pretending to be clueless,
or are actually clueless.
Qin,
about that…
Mom and I talked about it.
- Right.
- It was over,
so we decided not to bring it up again.
What did you talk about?
What did you two talk about?
Please.
Can I, for once, be a part of this family?
Well…
Mom and I
were worried that
you'd struggle
with what happened back then.
As time went on, we…
- always watched over you.
- Yes.
We saw that
you overcame it with grace.
Yes.
You're always such a good boy.
I thought that…
if you ever wanted anything,
like this condo,
we would buy it for you.
Whatever you wished for.
When you wanted a tutor
or wanted to go to university,
we always supported you.
Okay.
I understand.
Qin.
- We--
- Yeah…
Everything you gave me,
including this condo
and my education…
- Well, Dad--
- Yeah…
- Mom and I--
- He and I…
- We tried.
- We really did.
What about me?
What about what I actually want?
I…
The reason we did all this
is because we love you.
Mom, you don't get it at all.
You never even tried to.
Qin…
What's happening, Son?
You've never been like this.
You were always a good boy. You…
You were always so capable, I…
We barely ever needed to worry about you.
Being good at everything
is the reason you're never there, huh?
Then I don't want to be good.
I'd rather not be good.
Qin…
what you're saying,
I think you're being unreasonable.
- Mom, I'm not being unreasonable.
- Qin, stop.
Listen to your mother.
We've done our best raising you.
We've put our heart and soul
into caring for you.
Are you really
gonna pay us back by being snarky?
If you're upset about us
not going to your showcase,
just say it.
Right, just tell us.
That's why you're upset, isn't it?
- Even when I'm gone…
- Say it, Qin.
…you won't get to be with your parents!
- Say it out loud!
- Stop!
Don't you realize
why I turned out like this?
It's because of you guys!
Qin,
I won't accept you
talking to us like this.
- Apologize to us.
- No.
Qin!
You're making me feel bad,
do you know that?
I don't!
Because you've never told me anything.
- All you do is leave me alone!
- Qin!
What?
Are you angry?
Am I not a good kid anymore?
All this time, I followed the path
you said was nothing but great.
I just wanted you to ask if I'm tired.
You know?
Even now, what happened when I was a child
still haunts me.
When I was abused,
I cried out for you guys,
but no one answered.
Why didn't you say anything?
Do you ever listen when I do?
You're not even listening to me now!
Do you know how uncomfortable it is
to be in this family?
Okay.
Qin,
it's my fault.
Alright? It's all my fault.
If this is what you want, fine.
I'll take all the blame.
It's my fault. Are you satisfied? Are you?
Duang, I can't take it…
It's fine.
I'm right here with you.
I'm right here.
This is all it takes, Mom.
This is all it takes to fix everything.
Just hug him.
That's all it takes.
You're not going to stop? Stop!
Papa, Mama…
- Cry all you want!
- Qin…
Cry here, outside the house.
Qin…
Are you going to stop?!
You're not going to stop?
- Dad, Mom.
- Are you going to stop?!
I'm so sorry, Son.
I'm hurt.
Please stay with me.
I don't want to eat mud anymore.
I don't want to.
I'm sorry.
- Please don't leave me.
- Sure, Son.
- Can you please not leave me?
- Alright, Son.
We're right here.
I'm sorry.
Are you going to stay?
- We are.
- We're not leaving you, Qin.
I'm sorry.
Then…
from now on,
just focus on becoming our boy again.
Alright?
Let's be a not-so-capable family together.
We'll talk about everything.
If there's a problem,
we'll work on it together.
You too, Duang.
Alright.
How does this sound?
It's adorable.
I'm heading out now, Qin.
Okay.
Take care, Son.
You guys too.
Bye-bye.
- See you, Duang.
- Bye.
Bye-bye.
- Let's go, honey.
- Let's go.
Get home safe.
Yay!
Your parents were right.
You really are an amazing boy.
You finally got through it,
my Qin.
Come on…
What's your deal? Why so clingy?
You're at ease now, aren't you?
Seeing you happy with your mom and dad
makes me happy too.
Not yet.
That feeling is still lingering.
Things like this take time.
But it's a good start.
At least I got to hug them.
This time around,
I really felt like Mom and Dad were there.
Duang.
Thank you.
No need for that.
I'm happy to help.
Wanna go to Siam after exams?
I wanna get the film developed.
After that, we'll go home.
I…
will do whatever you say.
Sweet dreams, Duang.
Sweet dreams.
Duang?
Thank you for today.
Thank you for today too.
Go on.
Hi, I'm here to develop this film.
It'll take about 30 minutes.
Okay.
Here's the receipt.
Thank you.
Buying a new camera?
I'm not.
Just browsing.
Do you think the photos will be beautiful?
Of course, we're pros.
But you,
you are the most beautiful.
Wanna go for a walk?
We can come back later.
Qin.
Let's change our outfits.
I'll go with this.
That won't do!
Then, can you wear a tank top inside?
I've changed my mind. Not this one.
Don't rush to say I'm not a hottie.
Give me a chance to dress up first.
If you see me when I'm not mewing,
I'm gonna look skibidi.
Speak properly.
What?
Why though?
I think I look fine in this.
Plus, it's not expensive.
- It is.
- Whoa…
Said the boy
who wears shoes worth 30,000 baht.
A bit rich coming from you.
Said the boy
who bought a camera worth 55,000 baht
and ended up having no money to eat?
A bit rich, no?
Then…
give me a reason.
If it sounds reasonable, I won't buy it.
Why?
I look good in darker colors, don't I?
Just buy it, then.
Just say you're possessive.
How about
you try this one?
How is it? Does it look okay?
There's one word I want to say,
but you won't like it.
Don't say it then.
Do you think people outside will know
I'm teasing you?
Bastard.
Your heart is beating out of your chest.
Now you're the one
being teased.
Enough.
It's hot.
I wanna take you home right now.
In your dreams.
Go pay.
I got everything I need.
What?
I want to invite you over for a meal.
Do you wanna come?
Where is this coming from?
Well, when I was shopping earlier,
I realized
I haven't introduced you to my parents.
What are you introducing me as?
I'll tell them that
you're my boyfriend.
Is that a good idea?
My parents are really nice.
My mom is also good at making desserts.
Please come.
I don't mind.
- I'll go.
- Then…
Let's go see your mom and dad today,
and we'll visit my house later.
Let's go.
Hey, let's take a photo.
You're so cute. What do you want, baby?
Duang.
Here you go.
- Here's yours, sweetie.
- Thanks.
- For you two.
- Popcorn!
- Thank you, Mom.
- Thank you.
- Where were we?
- Oh, right.
How about we start it over
so Mom can catch up too?
Sure.
Of course.
Actually, I got lost with the subtitles.
Alright, let's start over.
Okay! It's so nice
to watch a movie with Qin.
Dad, Mom,
I have… something to tell you.
What is it, Son?
Duang and I…
are boyfriends.
Dad and I…
Dad and I already knew.
I'm so happy.
Duang, come give Mom a hug.
So…
I need to get serious.
Welcome to the family, Duang.
Yay!
- Yay!
Okay, I think
we'll need to start over again.
That's right.
I'll try keep up with the subtitles.
Get 'em, Duang.
- Sure thing.
- Ready?
Let's go.
Baby, come sit on my lap.
Are you tired today?
When you told your parents,
I was flabbergasted.
You really went all out.
It gave me peace of mind. How about you?
I'm happy. I wanna eat you up!
You're so annoying.
I want to thank you a million times more
for choosing me.
Stop.
Didn't you see something?
See what?
When you were lifting stuff,
did you see anything?
What?
Is it… the ghost in your room?
I see dead people!
Is it the ghost in your room?
Why are you scared? Here.
Whoa, you!
Whoa…
My heart almost stopped.
I'm so happy.
I put a lot of thought into this.
Thank you.
You did this for me?
Let me see.
Wow…
Whoa, Qin!
These are nice.
I love them.
But you shouldn't have.
They're really expensive.
Are you sure about this?
You fussed about the camera.
That's why I debated giving them to you.
But after some pondering,
since I genuinely wanted to,
I decided to buy them.
Plus, I'm not struggling.
I know they're expensive…
but they suit you.
I love you, Qin.
I love you too, Duang.
Here you go.
I'M IN A GOOD MOOD TODAY
MY BOYFRIEND PICKED MY OUTFIT
Is this a makeover or a renovation?
Jettana, just say you're jelly.
Who'd be jealous
of a lover boy showing off his love?
When will it be your turn?
Is hooking up
all you'll ever look for in life?
Are you making your own clothes?
It's for you.
Try it on for me.
What made you want to do that?
We've spent so much time together
that I know the size you wear.
Get up.
Here.
Hold up.
Go change properly, not here.
What?
Why not?
It's nothing you haven't seen.
Alright. I'll go change in the bathroom.
Here I am.
That looks sharp. It really suits you.
Try this one on for me.
Overalls?
Please?
Will they look good on me?
Of course. You have a nice body.
Everything looks good on you.
I really like your eyes
when you get serious.
Then…
Would you be a model for my final project?
If I agree to being your model,
what do I get?
Well, what do you want?
You know too well what I want.
Are you sure this is all you want?
I'm not falling in love.
Marvis…
Huh?
I'm not good with words.
I know.
Will it be okay?
It'll be completely fine.
If you don't want to talk, I will.
Everyone in my family is talkative.
My parents are
even more talkative than I am.
Don't you worry.
I'll never leave your side.
Besides, you're good
at having conversations with me.
Thank you.
What for?
Thank you
for making me a better version of myself.
I also thank you
for making me
a better version of myself.
Come on.
I'll hold your hand through all of it!
Hey, I can't get out that way.
Did you transfer him the money?
Darling! Duang is home!
Jeez, like no one can tell
you miss your son.
You… Duang!
Duang!
I'm home!
Hello, Dad. Hello, Mom.
Hi, there. Come here, Duang.
Give Mom a hug. I've missed you!
Funan, hi.
Hey.
Look at your brother for once,
not just your phone!
Bro, look over there.
Look at Dad and Mom.
They miss you like crazy.
It wouldn't feel right
if these two didn't fight.
Stop right here, guys.
I've brought someone special home.
This is Qin!
Too soon!
I'm just so excited!
He's my boyfriend.
- He is… my boyfriend.
- So cute.
He's adorable.
Qin…
- Hello, Mom.
- Hi, sweetie.
Hello, Dad.
- Hello, Funan.
- Hi.
Dad,
Duang really did it!
Right? I thought this day
would never come.
Hey, don't make fun of your son!
Duang is my son. Of course he did it.
Mom, you're buttering me up.
But let me tell you guys that
Qin isn't good with words.
Please be patient with him.
That's fine. Make yourself at home, Qin.
Every animal here has been vaccinated,
so make yourself comfortable.
We're not animals.
Alright.
Qin! My… you're so cute.
What a cute one.
You're really handsome too.
Exactly as Duang described.
True, Mom.
He's the CEO of being adorable!
Right. Hey, Qin.
Have you ever tried Betong chicken?
- Jeez, Dad.
- Not now.
Is this how you're treating him?
Right? I'm confused.
Come on now.
I haven't, but I have seen pictures.
Right, it's okay if you haven't.
But is there something else you like?
Duang said you have many favorites,
like desserts and all that.
- Yes, I like everything.
- Right.
Would you like to come
to the kitchen with me,
or would you prefer waiting out here?
I'll…
Mom, you're luring him with food.
I'm not. I've just prepared a lot of food,
so I want him
to check it out in the kitchen.
- Wanna come with?
- Sure. I'll go with you.
Qin, are the dining room
and kitchen the same?
Mom's confused.
But I do think they might be.
Qin, walk with me.
- Duang.
- Yes?
Come help me set the table.
What about Funan?
Whoa, don't point your finger at me.
Shoo, go help Dad.
Stop it. Both of you, come on.
Let's help each other.
Come on, I'm hungry.
Whoa!
- Qin?
- Yes?
What specific desserts do you like?
Nothing specific.
I love every dessert out there.
Nice, you're not picky.
This family doesn't care for desserts.
I even took some cooking classes
and never got to show off my skills, Qin.
What level of sweetness do you like?
- Just normal sweetness.
- That's right.
That's exactly how it should be. Here.
I'll teach you how to make jelly.
How does that sound? It's not hard.
It'll only take a sec,
and maybe three or four stories.
- Okay.
- We'll start by turning on the stove.
Then you place the pot on it.
It's so simple.
See?
But you can relax
because if it's edible, we'll eat it.
If not, we'll throw it away.
I know who Duang takes after.
Is it me? I need to tell you this then.
Wanna listen?
I do, Mom.
Right! Let's sit down.
It's story time. When Duang was little,
when I took him places,
everyone said we were like two peas--
Eavesdropping, I see.
Everyone said we were the same.
- Right.
- I was so confused.
Eavesdropping to see
if he gets along well with Mom?
Aw, you puppy!
I'm so happy
that Qin gets along with our family.
- Funan, I have a question.
- What?
Do you think…
Dad and Mom are okay with Qin?
Look at them.
They're besties already.
Qin, you sing so beautifully!
Did you take singing classes?
Mom is kind.
As for Dad,
even though he's a poser, he's also nice.
- I'm telling Dad.
- Whoa!
Why did you ask?
I'm scared Qin will feel uncomfortable.
Our family isn't like his.
Before you overthink,
have you asked him if he's uncomfortable?
Exactly.
So don't think for him.
When you're in a relationship,
you can't think for each other.
You need to talk.
I'm scared he won't like us.
Jeez.
If he doesn't,
he should tell you
because that means
you have to adapt to each other.
Even family members
can't think for each other.
So… you need to talk to each other
so you know what the other is thinking.
Especially in a relationship
where you grew up
in different environments.
Do you really know what he's thinking?
See? No freaking way you do.
Listen and think. What comes after that?
Think, think, think.
Think and execute!
What about savory dishes?
What do you like?
I eat garlic shrimp a lot.
Do you know that Duang
asked me to teach him how to make that?
Dad and Funan had to eat shrimp
for a week before he got it right.
So, did you get to taste it?
Was it any good?
I did. It was pretty good.
That's nice to hear.
But do you know that
Duang isn't very talented?
I sent him to every class out there.
Whatever he wanted to attend, I sent him.
Like when Duang
asked to take guitar classes,
I allowed him to.
But after a while,
he said it hurt his hands.
What did he do?
He quit since it hurt, right?
After that, he was picked on,
so he wanted to do taekwondo.
I bought him the uniform
and got him geared up.
I got him all the belts out there.
Then he got hurt,
so there goes another class.
But I didn't give up.
After a while, he asked me
to take drawing classes.
That's when I felt uneasy
since it required him
to concentrate and stay still.
I thought, "Gosh, he's not gonna last."
But in the end, he did!
I was over the moon, Qin.
This is what's right for him.
And I think you are too.
He really tried,
whether it was the show or the cooking.
I'm his mom, after all.
But I thank you
for being in his life.
There's no need to thank me, Mom.
You've raised him well.
That's why he turned out to be so lovable.
Besides…
I didn't choose him.
He chose me.
I understand why he chose you, Qin.
Jeez, my voice is starting to get shaky.
Let's turn on the stove
and make jelly, Qin.
Here.
This is yours.
Betong chicken.
- Qin.
- Yes?
Eat as much as you can.
Mom's Betong chicken
is the best in the entire world.
That's right. I worked so hard on it.
The meat is gonna be so tender.
Okay.
Quiet down. It's embarrassing!
Qin.
Want to spend the night?
Spend the night?
Since you drove a long way,
just spend the night here, alright?
- True.
- Honey!
That's right.
Tonight,
stay over, would you?
Just stay the night.
I have so much to gossip about.
Also, I checked the weather.
It's going to rain cats and dogs.
I'll be worried if you're on the road.
- Whoa.
- Whoa, really?!
- That's dangerous.
- Couldn't be more dangerous, Mom!
No, that's dangerous.
Seriously!
I don't agree.
- Or spend half the night.
- Let's eat first.
Please stay over.
- Alright, thank you.
- Yes.
It's too dangerous on the road.
What if there's an accident?
Yeah, it's better this way.
So we don't have to worry.
- Exactly.
- So…
Do you have class tomorrow?
I do.
In the afternoon.
Me too.
So you can go back tomorrow morning.
Yes, tomorrow morning.
So, Qin will stay in Duang's room then.
What?!
Of course he will!
Huh? Why are you screaming at me?
Obviously, Qin will stay in your room.
He can't sleep in my room.
Why would he stay in your room?
He won't!
He will be in your room!
Do you have to keep raising your voice?
He will be in your room.
I've already cleaned it!
Alright. It's settled then.
Qin,
- you'll sleep in Duang's room.
- End of story.
- Yeah, that's it.
- Alright.
It's way cleaner than your condo.
Definitely.
Mom is a clean freak.
I can tell. Your house is very tidy.
This was from
when I took taekwondo classes.
I lasted three days before I quit.
Your mom already told me.
Whoa,
she gossiped about me?
But I want to know more. Tell me.
When I was small,
Mom had me do a lot of things,
but I was never good at anything.
Luckily, she told me to tell her
if I didn't come to like it.
Mom said,
"Don't be afraid to fail
if you're eager to get back on your feet."
She's such an angel.
I really like your family.
That's how I found out
I like drawing the most.
But now,
I like you even more!
Stop it.
Duang!
That's a cute picture.
Jeez… Let's take a shower
if you're gonna compliment me this much.
Too dangerous.
Are you crazy? I won't do anything
unless you allow me to.
Is that so?
You always go for it.
That's nuts!
Here. These pajamas are for you.
No need for underwear.
I'll wash your clothes.
Your dirty mind again.
You brought it up.
I was just mentioning it.
Let's take a shower together.
Save the planet.
Are you giving in?
Or do I need to do more?
If I shower with you,
then we're going straight to sleep.
No more touchy feely.
You got it.
Get me a towel. I don't have one.
You're all mine.
Duang…
Don't bite.
Just a little taste.
I can't stand it anymore.
You're just…
Please?
Roar.
Go get 'em.
Duang.
Be gentle.
Do you like it?
Are you ready?
Yes.
I am.
It's confusing
that we had to come to Japan,
- but I think the timing is just perfect.
- What do you mean?
Perfect for our honeymoon of course.
Today is our monthiversary again.
I want this trip to be a gift for you.
What's the difference between
being into someone and liking them?
Excuse me.
I wanna sing the song I wrote for Duang.
Duang,
I wrote this song for you.