ALL DEPICTED EVENTS ARE FICTIONAL
I just ran into this guy,
and he's so damn cute.
His name is Qin.
From the College of Music.
If you rush in now, you're screwed.
Do your homework on him first.
Help me.
Someone's following me.
The fortune teller was right.
She said Qin would ask for help.
The prediction will come true.
Gotta have each other's backs.
I've got a plan
for your confession, buddy.
Hey! I'm going to win your heart.
I'm not asking for permission.
Just letting you know.
I feel like I've been enchanted
all because of your voice.
Good luck with that then.
Yay!
- Hey!
You're such an easy target.
I love kicking your ass!
Stop! Leave me alone.
- Pae!
- Stop it.
- Help me!
- I'm in a team fight!
Don't gang up on me.
Gosh! I died. Damn it!
I'm nothing but a ghost.
Enjoy chasing me, huh?
- Hope you like my ult.
- You knew they were after you?
They've been doing it often.
- Man!
- Come on!
It's over.
Blown to pieces.
- You suck.
- Because of you.
I've got it!
These are my plans to make Qin mine.
HOW TO WIN QIN'S HEART
Plan A is to buy snacks.
From the latest info I got,
Qin loves eating snacks.
How did you know?
Back at the festival,
he had a ton of snacks.
What's next?
I will win him over with snacks.
If he likes the snacks I give him,
that means he likes me.
How much will you give?
As much as I can afford.
You're going all in?
What if you fail?
Plan B, of course!
Scare him into loving me.
I'll scare him with a ghost.
Once he's scared, I'll comfort him.
This way, he'll fall for me.
That's weird.
Yeah.
How do you know
he's scared of this kind of ghost?
You need to dress up and play your part,
so I can do my part.
Hell no!
What if I get punched?
You be the ghost!
Who's going to help me?
I need to comfort him.
Jamie, are you--
Hey, stop it.
You have to do something
he will remember for the rest of his life.
Win him over by dressing up as a ghost.
It's so unique.
It's as unique as your stupidity.
Hey, but this one's not stupid. I'm sold.
I want him to remember every moment.
I'm blushing.
You two are crazy. It won't work.
I don't think
Qin will recognize you in disguise.
You'll terrify him.
Then we'll go with Plan C.
Bug him all the time.
I'm going to be around him
at every given moment.
What if he punches you?
I have to make sure this is safe,
so he doesn't clobber me when he sees me.
I acknowledge your determination
even though all of your plans are stupid.
I'll help.
Me too. You can count on me.
I want to witness your stupidity up close.
You're so unique.
You are. Do you get it?
See? This is why we're friends.
- Right.
- Yeah.
What should I get?
How about this one?
That's not a snack!
How many should I get?
As many as you can.
Gosh, you're the real lover boy.
I'll win his heart.
Write him some notes too.
Sure!
Done! Let's go!
We're done! Go!
Qin is on his way to class!
Pae, help us attach the notes!
He'll be too full to read.
- Help me with the notes!
- I'm working on them!
Arrange them properly, please!
Stop arguing!
Why are there two here?
- Just fix it then!
- The ice cream!
Hurry up!
This one?
Shove it in!
Go!
I'm going now!
Shouldn't I be the one
giving him the snacks? Hey!
Hey!
Hey, that's Qin.
Come on.
Not interested in
your so-called lover boy?
My lover boy? No.
If he's not yours, then whose is he?
I need to focus on school.
I'll deal with that later.
I feel so sorry for him.
Qin!
I got you some snacks.
Wait up. At least talk to him.
What do you want me to say?
"What brings you here, Duang?"
How would you like me to answer?
Enough.
I'd say it's the wind of love.
Go ahead and talk.
I need to submit my assignment.
It's too hot.
Qin.
Will you accept these?
They're your favorites.
How do you know?
I saw you buying these
at the Loy Krathong Festival.
Don't want them.
I'll come find you later.
It's too early for me to give up.
Prepare to be mine!
The wind of love will find you.
Not it.
Or maybe Krahang?
What about Ramphueng?
No, Master would exorcise me.
Maybe a zombie?
Are you all right?
Care to see a doctor?
What? Why not help me then?
I need to spook him tomorrow.
I'm still not in the mood.
Eat that somewhere else then.
What? Just tell me what you need.
What ghost should I dress up as?
You're really doing it?
I'll help.
Any ideas?
A madman?
I'm going to smack you.
Kuman Thong then?
Qin will address you nicely.
It's perfect.
Brother Duang, can you offer me red soda?
Brother, my ass!
Be serious.
How about a vampire? Pretty cool, huh?
It is cool, but does it suit me?
You don't like any of my ideas.
Can you just make up your mind?
I want a ghost that's scary but cute.
Only one option left.
Chucky.
Hey.
Hey, stop it!
That's hilarious.
- Oh, shit!
- Shit!
You scared me.
You nailed the costume.
I had to.
I'm not doing this for nothing.
Damn, this is cool.
How are you going to
confess your love wearing that?
I've got it all planned out. Wait.
What's the plan?
Do we have to do anything?
You do. Now listen.
Jamie, you follow Qin.
I think he'll take his usual exit.
I'm going to
jump out scare him over there.
Keep me posted.
Pae, stay with me and scout ahead.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Group chant.
Hey! Come on!
Damn you!
Get on with it.
Come on, let's go.
I have to go. I'm busy.
Yeah, I have to go too.
- Bye, Qin.
- See you.
QIN IS ALL ALONE NOW
Shit. What do I do?
Hey!
Why are you scared?
It should be me.
- Hey!
- What?
The plan isn't working.
Qin is coming this way.
Get ready.
Get ready?
- Do I still look cute?
- No.
Enough. Duang, just abort.
No, you can do it. Go.
Wait, Duang!
Your knives.
Shit! These look real!
Go.
Hey, it's me, Duang.
You? Stop fucking clowning around!
- Hey!
- Shit.
I should abort the plan.
If I scare him,
I'll probably get knocked out.
- What?
- I don't want to do this.
I don't want Qin to hate me.
You said you wanted
to be a bad boy, right?
What's the plan, Duang?
- Qin is coming!
- I want to stop.
Man up, come on.
- He's gonna hate me.
- Come on!
See? Told you. This plan is terrible!
- He's so fucking weird.
- Let's go already.
I'm not a ghost! This is a costume!
It's not real! I'm a student!
I'm not a ghost.
What? He's my friend!
- Don't scream!
- So cute!
That's my friend!
- No! I'm sorry!
- That's my buddy!
Hey, everyone is looking at us!
Wrong way!
Where are we going? Duang!
Guys, I'm not a ghost!
Calm down!
Duang! Everyone is looking at us!
Since Plan B didn't work,
we need to go to Plan C.
Still at it?
None of this sounds like
it came from a sane mind.
No complaining.
And cut that properly.
What? Pae.
Pae!
What the heck?
You're unbelievable, Duang.
One complains and the other sleeps.
It's fine. We're besties after all.
I'm a catch, yeah?
Man!
I'll revolve around you.
Qin.
Jeez. You didn't even look at me.
I went all out with these stickers.
- Do you serve Americanos?
- No.
But I'll make one.
Please wait a sec.
That'll be 60 baht.
I'll scan to pay.
Sure.
Here you go.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
It's hard to peel.
Shit, someone's coming!
Hurry.
I know you're around here somewhere.
Come on out.
Come here.
Do you know that
you're causing people trouble?
Yes.
Look, I…
I'm sorry.
Peel them off properly.
And tell your little friends to help you.
Jamie, Pae, you masterminds.
I told you not to do it.
Come out from behind the piano!
- Bastard.
Peel them off properly.
And the ones in the other building too.
Get rid of all of them.
That was close.
Duang, you're nothing but trouble.
The fact is
I'm spending all my time helping you,
and you blamed me.
Yeah.
What?
Why did you leave this part out?
Why not layer them up properly?
What?
It wasn't me. It was you.
What? It wasn't me.
You're wrong.
No, I'm Pae, and that wasn't me.
- It was.
- What?
- It wasn't me.
- You're wrong.
I'm Pae. And it wasn't me.
- It was you.
It was you.
Jeez, just peel them off!
Yeah.
Jeez.
- You're wrong.
- No, I'm Pae.
Qin's taking forever.
Here he comes.
They're all over campus.
I told him to remove them.
When?
- Just now.
- Right.
So that's why you were late?
So, how did it go?
With how he's pursuing you,
be honest, are you uncomfortable?
No.
You think he's acting weird?
I do.
I think that this lover boy
might just have a chance.
Why is it so hard with Qin?
That makes one of us.
It's never this hard for me.
Jamie.
You don't win people's hearts.
You just have flings.
Get it straight.
How should I pursue a music student?
All three of my plans have failed.
I got it, Duang.
Sing for him.
You're not bad looking.
We're the Gigachads
of the century, anyway.
- Just serenade him.
- No, stop.
Not to be a buzzkill,
but I'm pretty sure Duang can't sing.
Do you play music?
That's Funan's guitar.
You play?
One more time.
Enough, Duang.
It's crystal clear.
Skip the guitar,
or else Qin won't ever
want to talk to you.
What do I do then?
All I've ever been good at is drawing.
Wait! There's another thing.
Not just drawing.
What else?
Liking Qin, of course.
I'm second to none.
What?
It's the truth.
I know that, sweetie.
So what next?
I don't know what to do about Qin.
Even though I really like him, it's like…
Do you feel me?
I don't.
Me neither.
I understand that people fall in love,
but why are you so madly in love with him?
I think…
he's totally my type.
When I said I wanted to win his heart,
he said…
Good luck with that then.
Guys…
he's giving me a chance.
I've gotta do my best.
So, you're not just trying to win?
Like, maybe he dared you or something.
No, that's not it.
I've never thought about winning.
I just know that I'm really into him,
and I want to follow my heart.
How so?
It's like this.
Typically, a dog barks at a plane, right?
But suddenly…
the plane opens its doors for the dog.
You really made us get the picture.
What if you can't win him over?
I'll just cry.
- You'll cry and move on.
- I'm not moving on.
What?
Once I'm done crying, I'll start over.
Shit. What would it take
to make you quit?
Maybe if Qin told me to stop
and chased me out of his plane.
Or maybe,
if someone better came into his life.
Man, that's so sick.
But I'm the best.
That's what makes you unique.
Then how about you do you?
Follow your heart.
But there's a fine line
between pursuing and stalking.
You gotta be genuine.
If he's uncomfortable
with the way you're doing it,
then you'll be a stalker in his eyes.
I think being a straight shooter
is always best.
For me, that's all it takes.
That's good advice.
If he likes you back…
maybe he'll take you
on a first-class flight.
Think about it, if you two work out,
you might just be the first puppy
who gets to fly a plane!
You copying me?
What?
Copying, my ass.
Totally unrelated.
You guys are good at this.
Of course. We're the best.
- Not when it's you though.
- What?
Is that an insult?
- It's a compliment.
- All right.
Coaches don't play, you know?
Because the coach is pathetic.
Right?
Who is?
I've already washed my hands.
Hello,
this is chocolate.
Add some enchantment.
I am Little Duang.
Put it here.
Or can this suck it up?
Trust the process.
It opens.
You're such a dummy, Duang.
That's the last one.
Let's taste it.
Gross.
No problem. I'll start over!
Let me see.
Sheesh!
- You made those?
- That's right. Did I do good?
- They suck.
- What?
Just kidding. Hey, let me see.
All that effort for this?
Yeah, but I messed up a lot of them.
But my feelings for Qin
are a million times more than this!
Don't make that face.
You guys told me
to do something Qin likes.
He loves snacks,
so I made these for him.
Right. Why not make them into boxes?
What boxes?
Blind boxes. Ever heard of them?
How many flavors?
Two: dark and white.
Hey, that's perfect.
Make blind boxes and give them to Qin.
It'll be a total ice breaker.
Wow, that's smart.
This way, Duang won't be a sad pup
if Qin rejects his gifts.
And how do I make them?
Give those back.
Why'd you take them?
Aren't there any for us?
What should we eat?
May I have a few minutes of your time?
I'd like to ask you for a favor.
Is this a direct sale? I'm busy.
Your Christmas gift.
I made it myself.
I wanted to give you a gift
and play a game with you.
I said I'm busy.
Tell me when you're free.
I'll wait right here.
Lover boy isn't giving up, huh?
Duang, let me tell you something.
Approaching his friends may help.
If you have extra,
maybe give them to us.
Sure. Next time, consider it done.
Don't forget about me.
Copy that.
If I agree to play, will you leave?
Yes. I'll leave if you play with me.
Go ahead. I'll catch up later.
Here.
You gonna play?
What do I do?
Here, let me explain the rules.
If you get dark chocolate,
you can request one thing from me.
But if it's white,
I can request one thing from you.
Go ahead.
White. What's your request?
I want…
This won't end well, will it?
Can I walk you home?
I like walking.
That means more time together.
I also like walking.
I can even walk to Bangkok.
Then you wait. I need to practice first.
Yes, I can wait.
- Please let me carry your stuff.
- I can do it myself.
But I want to help.
Then leave it to me.
Right, you look so cute
when you practice.
I'm happy to be walking with you.
Can you do so quietly?
Of course!
We should take cover from the rain.
I'll count to three,
and we'll run over there.
One,
two, three!
Qin, hurry.
Come on, Qin.
You and me, standing way too close
Feels like everything is moving slow
Something inside
Is getting hard to hold
That feeling I gotta keep low
I forgot how long it has been
I lost track of time so much
That I almost forgot to breathe
We still have time
If you're not in a hurry
Please let time slip by
Just take our time
And let it slowly flow
Stay a little longer
Don't leave me here alone
Just want to be with you
Even if we're stuck in the rain
I just want to be here
'Cause you make me feel at home
I can feel your heartbeat
Every time you breathe
I don't know if we'll ever
Get to have this moment again
So please, don't leave this place
There you go. Satisfied?
Of course.
Leave then.
Hey!
Can you follow me back on IG?
You said only one request.
Can we play again then?
No, I don't want to.
Please play!
I have so many chocolates at my place.
Are you sure?
We can play way more.
No.
You like chocolate, don't you?
I have tons I can bring for you.
Please play with me!
Don't push it.
New information acquired:
this is Qin's condo.
My boyfriend's place!
My future boyfriend…
If you get dark chocolate,
you can request one thing from me.
But if it's white,
I can request one thing from you.
Hey, everyone.
- Hello, Coach.
- Hi.
Hey, what about PK?
I'm here, Coach.
You're late again.
All right, let's practice.
Start warming up.
Sprint and touch the line.
All right, let's take ten. Go.
Right, Qin.
How was it with Duang?
Why did he walk you home?
I'm confused.
That's all it was.
- You took the same route?
- No.
So you're warming up to him?
What?
No, it's just,
if you are,
I'll give him your class schedule.
He asks for it every day.
We'll see.
You're gonna be friends for now?
Not friends.
I don't let friends pursue me.
Friends are friends.
If someone doesn't want friendship,
they shouldn't approach me that way.
Okay. That's not sus at all.
Qin knows what he wants.
Come on, let's practice.
When he said, "We'll see." Does that mean
I should give Duang his schedule?
Maybe he'll do it. Just stay out of it.
You're right.
This isn't right, Jamie.
Do you think they're exploiting us?
Why did you stop?
Just keep going. It's heavy!
That's why I stopped.
It's too heavy.
Hey, Duang!
Hey, what is it?
These are heavy.
Hold this.
Guys, sorry for troubling you.
What's your deal?
Yeah.
- Come on!
- Are you all right?
Pae, stop playing dumb.
You're gonna wear out the word "cute."
Duang!
My name is Alice.
Our university is having an open house.
This means
there will be a ton of visitors.
I'm sorry?
Well… I'd like you to dance
at the opening for the open house.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
Duang.
I expected to hear a "yes" from you.
You're my only option, Duang.
I can't sing, you see.
My friends say I'm tone-deaf.
I can't dance either.
So how would I be of any help?
Please, Duang. I need your help.
I'm out of options.
I do have a friend
who is really good-looking.
His name's Jamie, and he can sing.
He's a better option.
He's probably around there.
What? Jamie? I know him.
He does whatever he wants.
He's not reliable.
There's only you,
my adorable little Duang.
I'm not adorable. I'm handsome.
Yes, you're right!
You're extremely handsome.
You're the most handsome guy there is.
Since I was born,
I've never met anyone so perfect.
Trust me. I'm right about this.
Anyway, please get back to me.
Don't keep me waiting.
But--
If you don't want to do it for me,
then do it for our university.
I really can't do this.
I could ruin everything.
You won't be alone.
I knew you'd be lonely.
That's why I got you a partner.
I really can't do this.
It's that guy.
Hey! How did you get in here?
Get out! We're practicing!
I can do it!
What? For real?
Let's get started.
Let me call my professor.
Don't bail on me.
Promise?
Yes. Let's do this. Let's go.
Wait, you two know each other?
- We don't.
- We do.
What's going on?
That's okay.
Now you two know each other, right?
And soon, you'll be
rehearsing together a lot.
I'M PREPARED TO LOVE YOU
WITH EVERYTHING I HAVE!
This is Duang and Qin.
They'll join us on stage.
I won't let you down.
I totally forgot.
I won't get to see Qin during break.
If you want to see him,
come up with an excuse then.
Should we grab some food?
The ship isn't sinking anymore.
That's 100,000 points for our lover boy.
Stop with that tone.
I can't do that.
I'm just so into you.