♪I get anxious when love is around♪
♪The little devil in me
turns into a nagger♪
♪Quick, show me your smiling dimples♪
♪I have a secret to tell you♪
♪That is, I fancy you♪
♪Your fragrance and smiling eyes♪
♪I bump into you
in the corridor on purpose♪
♪I even dream about
what to wear for our date♪
♪It's okay
if you know nothing about all this♪
♪I get anxious when love is around♪
♪The little devil in me
turns into a nagger♪
♪Quick, show me your smiling dimples♪
♪I have a secret to tell you♪
♪That is, I fancy you♪
=Time and Him are Just Right=
=Episode 3=
(Ji Luchi,)
(don't ever ask me
to wear cartoon panty)
(with you again.)
Why is it at Ji Luchi's balcony?
What are you doing?
Are you alright?
I sprained my ankle not my chest.
Haven't you peeked enough?
Why are you here?
There's no need to feel embarrassed.
Actually, I like Pikachu,
Crayon Shinchan, and Doraemon too.
Can you stop talking?
Can I ask you one more question?
Do you want to go to hospital?
Who is it that's got an issue?
It's him.
I sprained my right ankle.
It might be a fracture, doctor.
He fell on his face just now.
It looked painful.
You'd better check on him.
The best is to do a...
Can you leave first?
Sure.
Come, take off your shoe.
Let me take a look.
Has Crayon Shinchan had
a grudge against me?
Miss.
Do you like Crayon Shinchan?
I don't like it.
I like it.
I can even talk like him.
That's impressive.
Let me show you.
The alien who shows his butt.
Shake it, shake it.
Shake it.
Don't overthink it.
He performs for me
on his own free will.
Right?
I... I... Anyway,
I'm not trying to tease you.
I mean it.
Shake it.
Shinchan,
let's go home.
Go back to your dad.
Okay, Dad, coming.
Dad, how's your leg?
I'm fine. Let's go home.
This kid happens
to be called Shinchan.
I have nothing to do with this.
I know.
You didn't do it on purpose.
This must be an accident again.
Do you really mean it
or you're just being sarcastic?
It's like the umpteenth times
of accidents back then.
You pulled my shirt.
I was punished and forced
to read an apology because of you.
All this must be your careless mistakes.
You don't think so.
You're clearly accusing me
of being heartless.
I share the blame for today's incident.
Just today?
It's not only today.
What happened back then was
my fault, okay?
So what did the doctor say?
Besides the leg,
how about the other parts?
Do you wish to see me
get hurt all over my body?
I'd like to take responsibility for you.
From now on, I'm your
personal nanny for 24 hours,
a smart butler at your beck and call.
Just think of me as a leg.
Use it whenever you want.
It's not necessary.
I swear.
I won't bring
troubles to you again.
From today onward,
I'll be at your disposal.
I'll do whatever you ask.
(Your ankle is fine.)
(Go back and get some rest.)
Are you for real?
Really and truly.
There's no doubt
about my sincere heart.
So what did the doctor say?
The doctor said my ligament is torn,
and the cartilage in my ankle is
torn and fractured.
It'll take a while to heal.
That serious?
Well,
it must be taken care of.
Let me help you.
Easy, easy.
Be careful.
Slow down, slow down.
I'll go get the prescription for you.
Easy, easy.
Go that way.
Turn right, turn right.
Hold my arm.
Keep the weight off.
Lean against me.
Lean against my body.
We're almost there.
There's one meter away.
Hang in there.
Be careful.
Be careful. We're here.
Come, lean against it.
It'll feel more comfortable.
Let me help you take off your shoes.
I'll put them on the bed.
Another one.
Sir,
do you need anything else?
Can you prop my leg up?
Got it.
The pillow.
I'll be gentle.
Easy. Slow down.
I'm sorry.
Do you want me to tuck you in?
No need.
I'll call you if I need it.
Okay, rest in peace.
That was a slip of the tongue.
Rest, rest well.
Close the door when you leave.
Yes.
Will do.
That feels great.
It's a blessing in disguise.
I can finally have some privacy.
It's really hard to be an errand girl.
It nearly killed me.
Water.
I need some water.
Lin Xi!
Sorry,
I'm a bit thirsty.
Coming!
On my way.
Junxing, come hand out
the test papers.
Miss, I'll help him do it.
I'm leaving, Xing.
Don't forget that you're on duty today.
Let's go.
You leave first.
I'll do it for you.
(Realistic Progressive Erudite Humble)
What are you doing?
I dropped my pen.
Don't move.
Let me do it.
Do you know
the phrase, "Butterfly effect"?
As you bend down
and hold your hand out,
what if it affects your leg?
Geez.
You're right.
(Unremitting self-improvement,
the unity of knowing and doing)
Wait, guys.
We'll have a compulsory labor
in the community tomorrow.
I'll assign tasks
to each team.
Okay, work brings glory.
Team one and team three are
to sweep the floor.
Team two and team four are
to remove the advertisement.
Team five and team seven are
to wipe the glass.
Team six and team eight are
to remove the weeds.
Well, when we reach there,
the teacher will assign
the responsible areas
to each team. That's all for now.
Xie Ang,
come out for a minute.
What's wrong?
You're acting all mysterious.
Well,
during the compulsory labor,
can I be on Ji Junxing's team?
You want to transfer to his team?
I knew you got evil intentions
towards Xing.
It's not what you think.
His leg is injured.
I just want to share his burden.
Are you going to help me or not?
Yes, of course I'll help you.
As the saying goes, everything could be
damaged except...
I'm not done yet.
What were you two talking about?
Xing,
I'm really envious of you.
Can you teach me your skill?
How did you make
Lin Xi so obedient?
It's very easy.
Break one of your legs first.
It's you.
Long time no see.
I went out for a game
two days ago.
And I won three gold medals.
You can have them.
The champion of men's 110-meter hurdles
at High School Athletics Championships.
The winner of the regional, municipal
and provincial games.
Impressive.
Of course.
When one gets a gold medal,
they'll first bite it
and see if it's a pure gold.
Why didn't you do that?
I'm afraid it'll break my teeth.
Besides, the Olympics gold medals
are all gold plated.
They contain
less than one percent pure gold.
The rest are silver.
Then, my dream of making
a fast buck by selling
gold medals is over.
You don't know that?
Yes.
I saw you lying here,
looking quite upset.
Tell me
who upset you.
I'm fine.
I broke someone's leg.
That's brutal.
I'm impressed.
That was a careless mistake.
But the consequence is
that I've got to be
the victim's slave.
During the weekend community labor,
I have to remove the advertisement.
What is the location, then?
Happy Square.
Happy Square?
Accreditation and mortgage.
Infertility.
Professional lock-picking.
Unblocking the drains.
Pay dear for a son.
There are so many careers.
They put up flyers everywhere.
This is spectacular.
I'll leave them
to you and Lin Xi.
Jiang Yimian and I will be there
to remove the bubblegum.
Let's have lunch
at the gazebo this noon.
Since it's a heavy task,
let's work together.
Sure.
Well, let's distribute the work
by three and seven.
No.
Nine and one.
I do this because you're a girl.
Don't push it.
No, no.
You've got the wrong idea.
I'm the nine, and you're the one.
What are you doing?
You'll take care of the area
below this line.
I'll be in charge
of the area above it.
How is it? Are you satisfied?
Okay, let's work well together.
Okay.
No.
It'll take forever for you to remove
all the advertisements in this street.
You're definitely quick
as there are only two to remove.
What are you doing?
Watch me.
That's amazing.
Got that?
Actually, I didn't get
a clear look at it.
Can you do it again?
Should I remove all of them
on this wall for you?
I'll do it.
You go and take a break.
Xing,
(Recycle without wasting)
you're such a philanthropist.
This Kentucky Chicken has
perfectly cured the weary me.
I think you're possessed
by a hungry ghost.
No one will steal it
from you. Slow down.
Here, eat a drumstick
to boost your energy.
This is not what I need.
What I need is
that 1000 hands
of the thousand-armed bodhisattva.
You look down
on this drumstick, don't you?
Forget it.
I should fill my stomach.
Eat more.
We can do work well
only when we're full.
Mianmian,
do you know how many posters
in total I've removed today?
245 pieces.
That many?
You've worked hard.
Five more pieces to make it
a round number, 250.
It fits a simpleton like you.
How dare you laugh?
Those two pieces
you used to demonstrate
and the three pieces you removed.
Who do you think it's the simpleton?
Come out for a moment, Lin Xi.
What do you want?
Can't you tell he does it on purpose?
You just let him bully you like this?
He broke his leg because of me.
Besides,
I really want to make friends with him.
Your leg is broken for real?
You guess.
Xing,
you're really cold-hearted.
It's not right to treat
a girl like this.
I didn't treat everyone like this.
Fine, she has pushed your button.
You must know who started it at first.
It was her who started it.
Look at your hands.
Just let him do it this afternoon.
Your hands are all red.
It's alright.
Come on. Let's go eat the drumstick.
Look at this.
It's a missing cat notice.
(Notice for missing a cat)
Both of you, come over here.
I've got no kids.
And this cat and I have lived
together for years.
I found it since it was a kitten.
It's been over ten years by now.
We're deeply bonded.
It's like a family to me.
It seems like the owner is
a granny.
Didn't you see it just now?
No.
Mimi.
Kids,
have you seen my Mimi?
Granny, is this your cat?
Yes, it is.
It's already ten-odd years old.
It can find its way home
when it was little.
But this time, it hasn't returned yet.
What if it's hungry?
Don't worry, Granny.
I'm sure we can find Mimi.
Well, if you find it,
can you bring it back for me?
Sure.
My phone number is on it.
Look.
Okay.
I'm counting on you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Mimi?
What should we do now?
Should we continue our task?
Of course.
Let's find the cat first.
Mimi?
- Mimi.
Mimi, let's eat canned food.
Mimi.
- Mimi.
Will it be on a tree?
Do you find anything there?
No.
I see one over there.
Mimi.
This is too skinny.
And its color is different.
All of these are not Mimi.
It's getting dark.
Did it go far?
A ten-odd-year-old cat should
be moving slow.
She just lost it today.
It won't go far.
Look, is that it?
I can't do it. It's too high.
I'm afraid of heights.
An eighty-year-old granny is
more daring than you do.
You're such a coward.
I seriously can't do it.
Why don't you do it?
Let me do it.
You?
How are you going
to do it with one leg?
Let me do it.
I actually...
Actually, I'm good at climbing trees.
I've climbed a taller tree than this.
Are you serious?
Just forget about it.
Just use a ham sausage
to lure it down here.
It'll only take a while.
I'll surely get
both of us down safely.
Be careful.
Don't get yourself hurt.
Rest assured.
I'll still take care of you
even if I'm hurt.
Hold on tight, Lin Xi.
I'm alright.
Mimi.
She's there.
I caught it.
She's way stronger than you.
That's impressive, Lin Xi.
You really got it down.
It's high. Aren't you afraid at all?
As long as you caught it.
Mimi.
It's so cute.
Wonderful.
Granny is on her way here.
Mimi.
Thank you.
Thank you, kids.
Don't mention it.
Mimi.
You must listen to Granny.
Mimi, where have you been?
You went up the tree, didn't you?
And you couldn't get down here.
I can't do square dancing anymore.
Both of us are old.
Let's just stay with each other.
Thank you.
Let's go home.
Go home and eat prawns.
One set for each of us.
Let's eat prawns.
This is so touching.
Even a cat has a better meal than I do.
Nonsense.
Are you as lovely as the cat?
I'm envious.
It still can be found
when it got lost.
Let's call it a day. Dismiss.
Let's go.
That's a wrap.
Go!
We'll come back tomorrow.
That cat is very cute.
Isn't it?
Come, get me the bag behind me.
This?
Wipe it yourself.
Or my mom would think
that I've treated you badly.
Thanks.
Sit over there. Move over.
Let me do it.
Hey,
we could've just lured it down
by using the canned food.
But you insisted on climbing the tree.
You even wasted a box
of alcohol wipes of mine.
That cat is old.
It can't get down by itself.
What if it fell off?
It can as it was able to climb up there.
What if it didn't want to get down?
Can you read the cat's mind?
You don't understand.
A cat will run away from home
when it gets old.
It's a final goodbye to its owner.
A final goodbye?
You've got a vivid imagination.
This is true.
A cat can predict its death.
It knows that it's dying.
So it'll find an empty space
and return to its own planet.
It fears that its body will attract
its nemesis
and bring troubles to its owner.
So it'll choose to disappear.
This is the last thing
they could do for their owners.
Where did you hear
this touching story?
It's not a story. It's true.
This is not scientific.
From what you said,
a cat has nine lives.
Well, it still has eight lives
after losing one.
Can you not joke about life and death?
A cat only has one life like the human.
It dies when it loses its life.
Is she mad?
Ridiculous.
Brother,
I miss you so much.
(There are four reasons for cats to leave home:
when cats get old...)
(Cats' spirituality will never dissipate
until their getting old)
(When cats get old,
they know their limit and choose...)
Such a claim does exist.
Did I misjudge her?
I was wrong just now.
I shouldn't have made
a joke out of it.
Sorry.
Are you asleep?
(Rules of Living Together)
(Points to note when getting along
with Ji Junxing)
Don't interfere with his freedom.
Leave it. I'll do it.
Is it too clean?
Done.
How is it?
Have you finished eating?
Yes.
(Xiao Longdu Hawker Stalls)
I'm so full.
- Thank you, Kai.
(Xiao Longdu Hawker Stalls)
It's not good to overeat in the evening.
Come, let me help you digest the food.
No, Bro.
Are you asking us
to jog with you now?
It's no fun to jog.
Let's do a big project.
Come on.
What's going on?
Kai,
this is the big project you mentioned?
I didn't expect Lin Xi to be so fast.
Since we're already here,
let's do something meaningful.
Let's go.
Am I dreaming?
Come here.
What are you doing? It hurts.
Is it?
You're not dreaming since it hurts.
So there really is a snail girl.
Maybe it's a snail boy.
So we've got nothing to do today.
That we can happily enjoy
the good weekend time.
Who did this?
That's immoral.
I just put up the poster
last night
and it was removed right after that.
Who did this?
It's you.
What are you going to do?
Are you trying to show
how reckless you are?
Rest assured.
I'll outsmart him this time.
Reliable small investment brings
you a fortune for sure.
You just have to invest RMB 198,000.
You'll get RMB 396,000
in return at year-end.
The return on investment is
up to 200 percent.
What is this about?
Why are you reading it?
Go away.
Mister,
I want to remind you
that you've miscalculated
the return on investment.
What is wrong with it?
198,000 times two.
Two times eight is 16.
Write six and carry one.
Two times nine is 18.
19, it's 396,000.
Invest RMB 198,000
and net RMB 396,000 in profit,
that's how you get
a rate of return of 200 percent.
If you get RMB 396,000 in return,
that's a rate of return of 100 percent.
Is that so?
Mister,
this is elementary mathematics.
You never passed
your math exams, didn't you?
I'm bad at math.
But you're in no position to teach me.
Go away.
Stop messing around here.
It's illegal to put up
false advertisement.
I'm here just to remind you this.
Stop putting up the posters.
This is my job.
You're out of your depth.
Move aside.
You put up the posters
and I'll remove them.
I'm in this.
So it was you who removed
the posters I put up.
It wasn't me who did it yesterday.
But those posters you put up today,
I'll be sure to remove them.
Are you asking for a beating?
You...
How dare you avoid me?
You're trying to beat me.
I'd be a fool if I didn't avoid it.
What are you waiting for? Run!
Stop right there!
Stop!
Xie Ang.
Go get him.
Troublemaker, stop right there!
Mister, calm down.
Don't move.
Xie Ang.
We're finally safe.
Would you stop acting so recklessly?
What if you really get beaten up?
I still have you.
Besides, that kick was really...
Your... Where's your wheelchair?
I lost it.
You lost it?
With a torn ligament,
a bruised cartilage of ankle
and a fractured cartilage,
how did you run so fast?
I was eager to rescue you just now.
Luckily, I have a strong body.
It's starting to hurt again.
It's that leg which's injured.
Yes, this hurts more.
So you've been lying to me
in the past few days, right?
I did sprain my ankle.
But it wasn't that serious.
If so, why did you boss me around,
ask me to run errands
and serve you like a slave?
Wasn't it your suggestion?
I just went with it.
Ji Junxing,
do you think it's fun
to toy with me and take advantage
of my concern for you?
It's not that fun.
Actually, when you climbed
the tree yesterday,
I was going to tell you the truth but...
I thought you only had a long face
and a bad temper.
I didn't approach you in the right way.
That's why you kept ignoring me.
This is my wishful thinking.
I shouldn't have approached you,
cared for you
and had the idea
of making friends with you.
Because people who make fun
of their health
don't deserve others' concern.
What has my health condition
got to do with you?
Besides,
I took a joke on my own leg.
Why are you so mad about it?
Why am I so mad?
What are you doing?
Does it hurt?
It does.
Anyway, it's not my leg.
It has nothing to do with me.
The guest shuts the owner out.
You occupy my place.
What an ungrateful person.
I sincerely treated you.
But you didn't appreciate it.
How dare you get mad at me?
What have I done wrong?
I've only made you
my sidekick for several days.
I got punished, read an apology
and had nightmares because of you.
You made a mess of my life.
Yes.
I did bring you some troubles.
But at least, I was sincere.
Unlike you, you're a trickster.
What kind of a person is this?
You're black-hearted
like the black sesame rice ball.
I'm a bad person.
Then, just ignore me.
If it wasn't for my brother,
I wouldn't have run errands for you.
I'm not going to do it again.
Suit yourself.
Perfect.
It's less troublesome for me.
This is hard.
What do you think I should do?
Come in.
What do you want?
It's for you.
A fox.
Why isn't it a bunny?
A bunny is more lovely.
The fox suits you more
as you're full of tricks.
Who told you that?
I'm kind and lovely.
How could I look like a fox?
Both of you have
a common characteristic.
You'll fight if you can.
If you can't, you'll stay and watch.
When the opponent is not aware,
you'll continue to fight.
Anyway, you won't suffer losses.
When the opponent is not aware?
You're the opponent.
I give you a present but you beat me.
It's not my favorite thing.
Yes.
Who am I?
How could I let others bully me?
♪Your gentleness
is like the afternoon breeze♪
♪Amongst the crowd♪
♪My gaze remains on you♪
♪As if I were watching the starry sky♪
♪I can't help blushing♪
♪She's got such a gentle demeanour♪
♪I'm not myself when talking to her♪
♪Can I feel his heartbeat
at this very moment♪
♪And play the most romantic love song?♪
♪Can I reach his heart♪
♪With just one look?♪
♪Should I tell her
that I'm noticing her too♪
♪When she tries to
steal a glance at me again?♪
♪Catch the most gentle wind♪
♪And never let it go♪
♪Many of our love whispers♪
♪Are hidden in this city♪
♪Let the wind hear them♪
♪No matter how far
we are from one another♪
♪The cheeks are always blushing♪
♪That beating heart♪
♪Is like the rainbow
that appears after rain♪
♪Listen to it closely♪
♪I'm about to fall in love♪
♪Yes, I'm sure it is you♪