♪I get anxious when love is around♪
♪The little devil in me
turns into a nagger♪
♪Quick, show me your smiling dimples♪
♪I have a secret to tell you♪
♪That is, I fancy you♪
♪Your fragrance and smiling eyes♪
♪I bump into you
in the corridor on purpose♪
♪I even dream about
what to wear for our date♪
♪It's okay
if you know nothing about all this♪
♪I get anxious when love is around♪
♪The little devil in me
turns into a nagger♪
♪Quick, show me your smiling dimples♪
♪I have a secret to tell you♪
♪That is, I fancy you♪
=Time and Him are Just Right=
=Episode 4=
Are you looking for Lin Xi?
She left for school.
She left?
Yes.
She said that she had to
go to school early these few days.
She couldn't have breakfast with us too.
Look. I even bought three servings.
It's all right. I can take two servings.
Come here.
You have quite a good appetite.
I didn't know
you liked steamed buns so much.
Mom.
This is the taste of freedom.
What's going on between
you and Ji Junxing?
I was sitting in the front row,
but I could feel
the awkwardness in the air.
That's right.
I need to stop talking to him
for a few days
and give him a taste of loss.
Don't you want to be his friend anymore?
I want.
Then, why are you not talking to him?
It seems like
you're losing more than he is.
Our relationship has hit rock bottom.
I have nothing to lose.
If the results are what matter the most,
all I want is to be his friend.
I can't be acting servilely
the whole time.
So I've decided to lift my chin up
and stick my chest out
as I march on this path of friendship.
Nice.
I like how domineering you are.
But
what's your plan?
Have you ever heard
of the story about a fox
that's chasing a rabbit?
I haven't.
If the fox keeps on chasing,
and the rabbit keeps on running,
then it'll never catch the rabbit.
So after a few days of chasing,
the fox will disappear.
When the rabbit lets its guard down,
the fox will catch it by surprise
and take it down.
Wait a minute.
Who's the rabbit?
Ji Junxing.
Are you saying that he's the rabbit
and you're the fox
that's trying to catch him?
Do you really think
you're capable of catching him?
Just wait and see.
(Lin Xi's bathroom time)
Go! Pass the ball!
Pass it!
Pass!
Defend!
Come back and defend the goal!
Good morning, Xing.
Good morning.
Morning.
Isn't it a bit too early
for carbonated drinks?
Don't worry. Mianmian won't mind.
Thank you.
You are really something.
It turned out
Ji Junxing really is a little rabbit.
I've got to go.
(Water Dispenser)
You forgot your coke.
No.
Do you think you're in a commercial?
You looked as if
you wanted to drink it rather badly.
What's the matter?
I'm not trying to give you a lecture,
but it's a little too much
to pretend to be injured.
Lin Xi did everything she could
in the hope of being your friend.
Aren't you moved by her sincerity?
You are too cold-hearted.
If she finds it difficult,
the best thing she can do
is to give up now.
Everything is great now, isn't it?
We will just stay away
from each other's business.
She's doing well,
and I'm doing well too.
In fact,
I don't think she's doing well.
I don't think you're doing well too.
It's actually very easy
to mollify a girl after you upset her.
I'm very experienced in this.
I can share
some of my experiences with you.
Thank you,
but it's fine.
I'm just giving you
a small tip as a friend.
Arrogance might feel good now,
but it'll eventually lead you
to a dead end.
Lin Xi is going to give up on you soon.
I'm only doing all of this
to keep her away from me.
I can finally be at peace now
and I feel great about it.
I'm very happy too.
Are you sure?
Of course.
Smile, then.
Looking at you from the back,
I can't help
but want to sing you a song.
♪You are not truly happy♪
♪Your smile is only a facade you put on♪
In order to promote the construction
of spiritual civilization in our school,
diversify our school's culture,
build a harmonized
and civilized environment,
and train our students to be stronger,
so that they can keep striving
to achieve better results,
we are going to organize
the 15th Chunhui Basketball Tournament.
Please join us.
Our school is holding
a basketball tournament.
When is it?
Did our class participate
in the tournament last year?
You're interested
in the basketball tournament?
Of course.
It's the basketball tournament.
I can be a manager,
or a cheerleader,
or even handle the logistics.
Why don't you find out more
about it first before...
There's no need for that.
You can do whatever you want.
You can also have the honor
of doing a very difficult task too
and handle the registration too.
I will definitely complete the task
assigned by the organization.
I'll never let the organization down.
Both the organization
and I have faith in you.
All the best.
Xie Ang, why...
I don't want to see you disappointed.
(Progressive Erudite Humble)
It's not making sense.
Why isn't anyone here
to register for the basketball game?
You fell into Xie Ang's trap.
This is a difficult task.
What's going on?
You haven't heard about this.
There is a hierarchy
for the Chunhui Basketball Tournament.
The Art Class
despises the Science Class.
The Science Class looks down
on the Literature Class.
And we're stuck in the middle.
I'm not done yet.
The Art Class despises Class One.
No way.
I need to figure something out.
Have you considered
joining the basketball tournament?
Sign up now to get a sachet
of instant coffee for free.
Refer a friend
and you'll get a chocolate bar for free.
If two persons sign up together,
you'll get both freebies.
The more contestants we get,
the more gifts we'll be giving out.
Here's a free gift
for our first meeting.
Hello.
Please help us promote the game.
Thank you.
Hello.
Please promote the basketball tournament
to your friends.
How trivial.
Xie Ang.
Think about it.
Lin Xi.
These deals are very attractive.
I'm sold.
So will you be joining us?
No.
I'll talk to you again
when you decide to join us.
But I can refer a friend.
Who's it?
Your deskmate.
That guy?
Can he play basketball?
I'll think about it
if you are sincere enough.
I don't think you're a good candidate.
Why not?
You just don't look like one.
You look nothing
like someone who plays basketball.
Hello.
Please help us share this
with your friends. Thank you.
Hello. Please share it
with your friends.
We're counting on you.
Come on, Qin Kai!
On your marks!
Ready!
Come on, Qin Kai!
Qin Kai, you did great!
Have some water. You've worked hard.
Thank you.
Have some water.
What? Who's this?
What brings you here?
It's my first time seeing you hurdling.
You were amazing.
I was just doing it casually.
I'll show you what I can do
for a real competition one day.
Are you looking for me?
I happened to pass by,
so I thought I would just deliver
some drinks to you.
I don't receive drinks
from every Tom, Dick, and Harry.
Precisely.
I don't deliver drinks
to every Tom, Dick, and Harry too.
Drink it.
Drinking it
means you've agreed to do me a favor.
What?
What have I agreed to?
You'll be an aid
to our class's basketball team.
Hello.
Hi.
Can I have a cup of milk tea?
Sure.
Normal sugar level, add on pearl,
Nata de coco, and grass jelly.
I want all the add-ons.
Wait a minute.
That's it.
I spent the whole day running around
but I still fail
to form a basketball team.
Just join us.
We'll be a great team
if you can join us.
I'll be dead if I join you.
My classmates will send me
to an early grave
if they find out that
I'm joining your team.
Moreover, if I join your team,
what about my classmates?
What about my friends?
I didn't expect
a free man like you
to care about collective honor.
This is what we call sportsmanship.
We've failed
before we even managed to do anything.
It seems impossible
for our basketball team
to turn things around.
I think
even if you manage to form a team,
your class will be eliminated
at the preliminary round.
It's the participation that matters.
It's about sportsmanship.
Other girls don't even know
how many members are there
in a basketball team.
But why are you so interested
in basketball?
It's mainly
because of my brother.
(My brother was a fan of Kobe.)
I used to play basketball with him
when we were little.
We watched basketball games
together too.
As time went by,
I started to get interested
in basketball games too.
That's great.
Let's play together.
What about you?
Why do you like sports?
I like the idea
that you won't know who the winner is
unless you fight until the final second.
That's why we are friends.
Exactly.
Wait.
How many basketball players
do you have in your class?
Everyone in our class
can play basketball.
Let's make a deal.
You'll come and watch me play next time.
I was
Chunhui's most valuable player
last year.
Sure. I want to see
how good your three-pointer is.
Just swish it.
Everyone can do it.
All right. You can go now.
She has quite a number of friends.
Where did everyone go?
Lin Xi.
You're amazing.
There's finally a dream basketball team
from our class.
Are you kidding me?
It's true.
They went out early in the morning
for the basketball practice.
Come with me if you don't believe me.
Let's go.
It's true.
Ji Junxing is here too.
He's the captain.
Can he play basketball?
Why not?
If there's only one guy in our class
who can play basketball,
it has to be him.
Others might not know about this.
But we came
from the same middle school.
They called him Little Kobe.
It's either he doesn't play,
or he'll win the game.
You were in middle school.
Things might be different now.
He's still doing pretty well now too.
Do you find anything unusual
when he's playing basketball?
I do.
He's unusually steady.
With his help,
we'll surely win the tournament.
Xie Ang.
Has he recovered?
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
Who are the others?
The boy with the brightest smile
is Gao Yunlang.
He's nicknamed Cheerful Gao
and is a very good athlete.
(Gao Yunlang, Cheerful,
Takes Chen Mo as his best friend.)
The prettiest boy among the bunch
is called Chen Mo.
(Chen Mo. Studious, quiet, and gentle)
As his name suggests,
(Gao Yunlang's best childhood friend)
he's quiet, gentle, and a laconic person.
However, he is really good at math.
He won the first place
in last year's Olympiad.
That's Kai.
He's very good at chemistry.
And Xie Ang...
I'll be very grateful as long as
he doesn't jeopardize the whole team.
Anyway, all our class's top students
are here.
It sounds more
like a mathematics competition
than a basketball tournament.
You can leave now.
Why are you playing basketball
early in the morning?
Don't you need to study?
Whether we need to study or not,
it has nothing to do with you.
Don't you know that the basketball court
belongs to the Art Class in the morning?
Did the school set the rule
or did you come up with it yourselves?
It doesn't matter who set the rule.
We can have a match
if you're not happy with it.
The winner gets to stay.
What do you say, Kai?
Sure.
The skills will speak for themselves
on the court.
We'll play one-on-one and
the first to score five points will win.
Who's going to do it?
You?
Come at me.
I'll do it.
Sure.
I'll play with you, then.
Nice shot.
What do we do now?
Miss.
He scored five points in a row.
They're now Class 12's rivals.
He's just asking for trouble.
It's not too late to admit defeat now.
Give me the ball.
Nice shot.
Did you see it?
We scored five clean shots.
You barely scored the last shot.
You only scored four and a half shots.
Whatever. You can have the court.
Let's go.
Lin Xi.
Drop by and watch me play next time.
It's fine.
Let me inform you
that I'm now the manager
of Class One, Grade Two's
basketball team.
I also handle their logistics
and am their cheerleader.
From now on, we're rivals.
Sure.
Good luck.
I hope you'll do better than last year.
I hope you can
get into the quarterfinals.
We might even make it to the final.
Do your best
and win second place too.
Kai.
What are you looking at?
Our opponent.
Xing, well done.
You scored five consecutive shots.
You're quite a good basketball player.
But are you feeling all right?
Why? Do you think I'm weak?
That's not what I meant,
but
let me know if you need help.
Remember.
(Realistic Progressive Erudite Humble)
With Ji Junxing on our team,
I'm very hopeful
that our class will win the tournament.
Come on. We're counting on you
to break Class One's curse.
Come on.
Wait a minute.
Now that we have formed
a basketball team,
it's time to sign our cheerleaders up.
Wait a minute.
I need to jot you down one by one.
Go back to your seat.
What are you doing?
How long has the bell been ringing?
This is outrageous.
People are racing against time
to work on worksheets
and memorize vocabulary,
only hoping to score a better result
in the college entrance exam.
But look at you.
Basketball?
You think you'll do
very well in the exam, right?
In the previous monthly test,
only six out of the top 20
are from our class.
Are you still proud
of being a Science Class student?
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
Aren't six a lot?
Keep laughing.
You'll start crying
during the college entrance exam.
We're not joining
the basketball tournament this time.
Why not, Miss?
Why not?
Because you're not students
from the Art Class.
Your priority is to secure
a place in the college.
Let's start our class now!
Kai.
That was a very handsome shot.
It's just something I always do.
You're all here.
What are you doing?
Can't you see the water is mine?
The water here is for everyone.
Let's go, Xie Ang.
Wait.
You can have it.
Since you can't play basketball,
you can play with the water.
What did you say?
Don't talk rubbish.
I'm not as good a talker as you.
You're the best academically,
but you're the worst
when it comes to basketball.
I dare you to repeat it.
You're the worst.
Initially, I wasn't hopeful.
Then, I saw hope.
And now,
the hope was taken away from me again.
It was really a dream team.
It was just like a dream.
I got it now.
Basketball isn't Class One's curse.
It's Miss Sun.
Luckily, Ji Junxing no longer
has to participate in the tournament.
Why do you dislike Ji Junxing?
Oh, no.
Our classmates have gotten into a fight
with the Art Class.
What's going on?
Let's go. Hurry up!
What's the matter?
Miss.
Look.
What happened? Why is there blood?
It looks pretty bad.
Where are they?
It must be the doing of your students.
Where are you going?
I'm going to look for Mr. Xie.
Listen. Calm down first.
Say something.
Dad.
I'm not your dad.
Come here.
Does it hurt?
You deserve it.
You should've put your effort into
something else rather than fighting.
Mr. Xie.
We weren't fighting.
You weren't fighting?
Then, what happened
to the wound on his face and his shirt?
Dad, this...
You're the best academically,
but you're the worst
when it comes to basketball.
I dare you to repeat it.
You're the worst.
My nose...
Blood.
My nose is bleeding.
Mr. Xie.
They only shared a hug.
Fine.
I'll not press on
this matter.
But
you'll need to share a hug now.
Then, I'll let this matter rest.
Another hug?
What's wrong?
Don't you want to settle this here?
Do you want to get punished?
Go back now.
Get back to class now.
This...
Mr... Mr. Xie.
It's fine.
You're here right on time.
Bring them back to their classes.
They weren't fighting.
It was just an accident.
All right, Mr. Xie.
Get back to your classes now.
Go back now!
Miss Sun.
There's something else
I want to tell you.
What is it?
This incident
might appear like an accident,
but actually, it's not.
You disqualified Class One
from the basketball tournament,
and we were really upset.
Miss.
It's not fair.
We want to take part in the tournament.
Enough.
I won't allow that.
Miss.
You said
that the basketball tournament
will affect our learning.
But have you ever thought it through?
If you don't allow us
to take part in the tournament,
our low morale
will affect our studies even worse.
Is the basketball game so important?
Will it help your college entrance exam?
Can it be one of your specialties?
Will it help you
get a place in a reputable university?
Yes, Miss.
We need to
secure a place in the university.
But college is not
the final stage of our life.
If we miss the good experience in life
because of this,
life would be meaningless.
Even if I allow you
to take part in the tournament,
you would be eliminated
in the preliminary rounds.
What's sportsmanship about?
Higher, faster, and stronger.
Can you beat
those kids from the Art Class?
Michael Jordan once said,
"I can accept failure,
but I can't accept not trying."
Even if we lose the competition,
it's still better than
giving up before trying.
Miss Sun.
Just give us a chance.
We shouldn't be wasting our time
being indecisive,
regretful, and anxious.
We should make good use of the time
and play a good match.
That's right, Miss.
Sakuragi Hanamichi said
that if you give up,
the game is already over.
Miss Sun, please let us do it.
We promise that
we'll never neglect our studies.
Let them do it.
Don't make it look
like we're abusing them.
If you wish to participate
in the tournament,
you must do your best.
Don't let the other students think
that studying is the only thing
students of Class One know.
That's great!
I'll see you at the basketball court.
Don't be happy just yet.
Our goal
is to beat you.
All right.
Stop standing here.
Meet me at my office.
Go back to class.
We can play basketball now.
Wait a minute, Xie Ang.
That quote was not from
Sakuragi Hanamichi.
It was from Anzai-sensei.
Miss Sun watched this series too?
You watched it too.
We can play basketball now.
Ji Junxing.
You were so cool just now.
I agree.
Wasn't I cool?
Of course, you were.
It was the first time
I thought you looked handsome.
Good boy.
Lin Xi.
What are you looking at?
Is there someone behind me?
This time,
I'm really impressed by what you did.
You confronted Miss Sun alone
to secure Class One's honor.
I'm not that selfless.
All I want is to play in
the basketball tournament.
Do you want to play the game so badly?
What if you get hurt?
What... What if you hurt your arms,
legs, or...
Or if anything happens
to your heart or your other organs?
Are you worried about me?
I'm worried about our class's performance
in the basketball tournament.
I want to win.
It's rare to see us
sharing the same goal.
You can be my friend
if I win.
Don't you want to keep
your social circle exclusive?
We need
some low-quality friends in life too.
Your words, not mine.
Don't break your promise later.
Say it again.
I want to keep a record of it.
Golden words are not meant
to be repeated.
You should go now.
I need to practice.
I wasn't expecting this.
The fox really outsmarted the rabbit.
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
I mean, good job, my friend.
Give me a high five, my friend.
Didn't you say that we're friends?
Come on!
Class One, Grade Two
has advanced into the next round!
Class 12, Grade Two
has advanced into the next round.
(Final. Class 12, Grade Two
versus Class One, Grade Two)
(Final. Class 12, Grade Two versus Class One, Grade Two)
Come on!
Hey.
Luck is on your side, huh?
You actually managed
to get into the final.
But now that
you're playing against us,
you'll soon run out of luck.
Don't get ahead of yourself.
You might embarrass yourself soon.
Class One. Class One. We are number one.
Class One is the best.
Defy us and you shall be dead.
See?
This is what a winner looks like.
We have
a very strong cheerleading team too.
We're leading. We're going to win this.
Isn't it nice?
It is nice indeed.
But we'll find out
who's the winner on the court.
We are number one.
Class One is the best.
Let's go.
Defy us and you shall be dead.
(15th Chunhui Basketball Tournament)
Class One is the best.
Defy us and you shall be dead.
(Final. Class 12, Grade Two, 21,
versus Class One, Grade Two, 17.)
Come on!
(Final. Class 12, Grade Two, 42,
versus Class One, Grade Two, 41.)
Okay.
(Final. Class 12, Grade Two 75,
versus Class One, Grade Two, 72.)
Are you all right?
What's going on?
I sprained my ankle.
I'm fine.
No. You won't be able to keep playing.
Go to the infirmary now.
Careful.
It looks pretty serious.
Ziyang.
Bring him to the infirmary.
Now.
What do we do now?
There are only five people in our class
who can play.
We don't even have a substitute.
Less than a minute left.
Why don't you surrender now?
(Final. Class 12, Grade Two,
versus Class One, Grade Two.)
(Final. Class 12, 84, versus Class One, 81.)
You won't win anyway.
That's right.
Stop wasting our time.
Just resign to your fate.
Moreover,
you have already done
a pretty good job.
You don't have any substitute, right?
Who told you that
we don't have a substitute?
Mianmian?
There are no other substitutes, right?
I'll do it.
You?
You're a girl. Can you really do it?
Can't girls play?
It's the Chunhui Basketball Tournament.
There are no rules saying
that it's for boys only.
Are you sure you can play basketball?
Don't get ahead of yourself.
Sir.
Can I join the tournament?
There are no rules in
the Chunhui Basketball Tournament
saying that girls aren't allowed
to participate in the tournament.
You're right.
56 seconds left. The game will resume.
Class One will have possession.
Come on!
Let me show you
what Black Mamba is made of.
Use a feint
to make the defender
lose his center of gravity.
When the defender loses
his center of gravity,
he will lose
his advantage of height too.
♪Your gentleness
is like the afternoon breeze♪
♪Amongst the crowd♪
♪My gaze remains on you♪
♪As if I were watching the starry sky♪
♪I can't help blushing♪
♪She's got such a gentle demeanour♪
♪I'm not myself when talking to her♪
♪Can I feel his heartbeat
at this very moment♪
♪And play the most romantic love song?♪
♪Can I reach his heart♪
♪With just one look?♪
♪Should I tell her
that I'm noticing her too♪
♪When she tries to
steal a glance at me again?♪
♪Catch the most gentle wind♪
♪And never let it go♪
♪Many of our love whispers♪
♪Are hidden in this city♪
♪Let the wind hear them♪
♪No matter how far
we are from one another♪
♪The cheeks are always blushing♪
♪That beating heart♪
♪Is like the rainbow
that appears after rain♪
♪Listen to it closely♪
♪I'm about to fall in love♪
♪Yes, I'm sure it is you♪