♪I get anxious when love is around♪
♪The little devil in me
turns into a nagger♪
♪Quick, show me your smiling dimples♪
♪I have a secret to tell you♪
♪That is, I fancy you♪
♪Your fragrance and smiling eyes♪
♪I bump into you
in the corridor on purpose♪
♪I even dream about
what to wear for our date♪
♪It's okay
if you know nothing about all this♪
♪I get anxious when love is around♪
♪The little devil in me
turns into a nagger♪
♪Quick, show me your smiling dimples♪
♪I have a secret to tell you♪
♪That is, I fancy you♪
=Time and Him are Just Right=
=Episode 11=
I should just turn around
and let you look at my back.
It's not necessary.
I was too excited.
We finally met each other in real life.
You look more lovely
than you were in the video.
Do not use the word "lovely"
to describe me.
After all,
my age is in double digits.
So is mine.
Then, we're about the same age.
Besides,
we're
roommates who used the same room.
Right.
Nice to meet you.
It's for you.
Thank you.
The latest RC formula car!
You got to be kidding me!
How did you know I like this?
Because we're connected.
Open it.
Is this your favorite color?
I like red the most.
Try it.
Guys, come down and eat.
You need to twist it.
Isn't this the latest
RC formula car?
What now?
With the new racing car,
you don't have to eat anymore?
I don't want to eat.
Sister Lin Xi,
let's race.
See who's faster.
Okay, drive forward.
Both of you should have a race.
But it's an eating race.
I was wrong. I was wrong!
My slippers.
I dropped my slippers.
Get his slippers over.
Don't catch a cold.
Here, have some prawns.
Thank you, Aunt.
Here's the soup.
Lin Xi,
we don't have to eat takeout anymore.
Because the chef is back.
I'm not the chef.
It's a light meal.
You guys go on and eat.
Eat up.
Thank you, Aunt.
Lin Xi,
how does it taste?
It's delicious.
It tastes like home.
Then, you should eat more.
Eat more if it tastes good.
You have no idea.
Since you and Junxing moved out,
I was quite unaccustomed to it.
I've troubled you for the last semester.
Our school happened
to have unoccupied beds.
It's also good
to live on campus.
If you lived here,
it'd take you an hour to go there.
It'd be over 300 hours in a year.
The time cost is quite high.
Yes, Sir.
If I live on campus,
I can attend night classes.
If there's time,
I can do another half set of papers.
You should keep this spirit
to prepare
for the college entrance exam.
Do you have any plan for your future?
Future? I don't really know.
But I want to go to Jinghua University.
Jinghua University is not bad.
Its international ranking
has been rising lately.
That's enough.
You just got back
but you kept asking questions
as if this was an interview.
How is Lin Xi going to enjoy the meal?
It was my negligence.
Ji Junxing,
get Lin Xi a bowl of soup.
Never mind. I can do it.
When have you become so sensible?
I've become sensible long ago.
That's enough.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You're good at taking care of others.
Of course.
I'm a gentleman.
Then, get me a bowl too.
Do it yourself.
You're well-fed.
Geez,
the food can't even shut your mouth.
Sister Lin Xi,
time went so fast.
I was going to play
a little longer with you.
Will you come
and eat with us next weekend?
I will.
We can go out and have fun.
Wonderful.
There's a car race next weekend.
Sister Lin Xi, are you coming?
Sure.
I'll come too.
Didn't you just say you're not
interested in the activity
for primary students?
I'm interested now, okay?
What is the location?
Wang Dong and I agreed
to meet up at the park.
Who is Wang Dong?
My tablemate.
Wang Dong is scarier than Voldemort,
and more horrifying than Godzilla.
Did Wang Dong bully you?
Who's that kid?
Lin Xi!
Qin Kai,
why are you here?
It's a coincidence.
I just left the cybercafe.
What an odd coincidence.
You came all the way here
to surf the internet?
Won't the scooter run out of battery?
Thanks for your concern.
It has enough battery
to get me back to school.
Lin Xi, let's go.
It's not necessary.
We'll send her back to school.
It's the middle of the night.
You even have to take care of the kid.
It's troublesome.
It's quite late now.
Ji Luchi has to go home and sleep.
I'll get going.
Bye bye.
See you at the race.
Slow down.
The helmet is quite nice.
Junxing,
don't you think it's better
to get a scooter?
Is the scooter the problem?
I got it.
It's your problem.
That dude is more handsome than you.
You little brat!
You favor an outsider over me.
Let's go home.
You're hurting me!
Do you concede?
I was wrong. Help!
Come, let's go home.
I was wrong. I was wrong.
So now, you know that.
Stop there!
Who's the kid?
Ji Junxing's baby brother.
Biological?
Yes.
He had been abroad with Mr. Ji
to convalesce.
He just returned recently.
They've reunited with each other.
It's amazing.
It's not as amazing as I am.
I was born to be wild
and free.
We never interrupted each other.
There's no connection
between you and your family?
Not quite.
I still have my grandpa.
Let's go. I'll take you to him.
Now?
That's so sudden.
He should be sleeping as it's late now.
Rest assured. He's wide awake.
Sit tight.
Slow down.
Isn't this the direction
to our school's boiler room?
Does your grandpa live
in the boiler room?
Technically, he lives
above the boiler room.
Let's go.
That's impressive.
You even found this shortcut.
It's all
for this momentary freedom.
Come, this way.
It really is a boiler room.
Yes.
Hold it for me.
Does your grandpa really live in here?
Why would I lie to you?
Come, this way.
Welcome to my secret base.
Please.
Hello, sorry to interrupt.
Where is he?
He's here.
This is my grandpa.
Isn't this a grass?
Watch your words.
It's called Li Bai.
Your grandpa?
Li Bai?
Then, mine would be Du Fu.
It's not the Li.
It's the inside "Li".
It's a fern
which exists earlier than the dinosaurs.
We can absolutely call it
Great Grandfather.
So,
you kept your precious
Great Grandfather in this boiler room.
Don't underestimate
this boiler room of mine.
It's small but fully equipped.
We can eat, drink and have fun here.
Next, let me introduce this
to you.
Monilaria moniliformis seeds.
It looks nothing like a bunny.
It's only a brain now.
But over time,
it'll grow bunny ears.
Is that so?
Tell me when it grows out.
I want to check it out.
Then, I've got to protect it.
Or else it'll die before the bunny ears
grow out.
Touch wood.
Don't listen to him.
I didn't expect a person like you
would grow plants.
It's a long story.
Come. Sit down.
I'll tell you about it.
Actually, I like plants
by happenstance.
When I was a kid, my dad went
to Australia to do business.
So he brought me with him.
But he didn't have time to care for me.
What about your mom?
My mom.
She didn't go.
Let me finish.
That time, I always looked
at those succulent plants
at the door
which were taller than me.
When I was bored,
I would talk to them,
and chat with them.
One day, I suddenly found
that they grew better every day.
That time, I thought
plants were actually quite righteous.
If you treat it well,
it'll also be nice to you.
It's more reliable than human.
It feels like
your relationship with them
is like the little prince
and his roses.
You tame it
and it accompanies you.
You can tame me.
I'll keep you company.
I'm not a trainer.
We're done here.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
I'm not leaving.
Staying here to watch movie is
better than going back to the dorm.
What if the security finds out?
So you've got
to keep it a secret for me.
Okay.
This is just between me and you
and Grandpa.
I'm leaving.
Do you remember the way out?
I remember it.
Who am I? I'm Lin Xi.
Stay safe.
Okay.
Yangtze River. Great Wall.
Mount Huangshan. Yellow River.
Weight thousand pounds in my mind.
Whensoever,
and wheresoever,
my heart's always...
Why is the water so cold?
Who is it?
Who turned the heater off?
(Gas Boiler No Smoking)
Qin Kai.
It's you again.
This is the car I gave Ji Luchi.
Why is it here with you?
Does he not like it?
He likes it so much
that he'll use it to race
with Wang Dong.
So he asks me to remodel it.
Keep it up.
Now, I'll announce a punishment.
Last night, Qin Kai
from Class 12, Grade Two
broke into the boiler room
and closed the heater valve,
causing hot water outages
in the bathroom.
This is a bad behaviour.
This is a serious violation
of the school rules.
He's now given a reprimand.
Fellow students,
please take warning from it.
Did he really get caught?
You went to the boiler room last night?
Hmm.
Why did you go there
instead of returning to the dorm?
Were you in on this?
No.
It's hard to explain.
A home theater. A projector?
A speaker.
A blanket.
And cup noodles.
Look.
You've prepared all kinds of stuff.
Do you take the boiler room
as a home theater?
So-so.
It's warm in Winter
and refreshing in Summer.
But it has poor soundproofing.
It's too bad
that I can't use
this 360-degree Surround Sound Speaker.
Wipe that smirk off your face.
I asked to see your parents last time.
Where are they?
Didn't I already tell you
that I don't have parents?
Then, did you pop out from a stone?
You can interpret it that way.
I'm like a dandelion now.
I don't have a fixed place to go.
Do you think I'm joking with you?
Let me tell you this.
The school principal
has known about this matter.
He's going to take this
as a bad example
and seriously deal with it.
Mr. Xie, let me off just this once.
I won't go there again.
Let you off?
I've let you off
too many times.
I must see your parents this time.
Mr. Xie,
I can do everything you say.
Just don't make me ask them to come.
Do you think this is a market?
That you can bargain with me?
I tell you what.
Next Monday,
your parents must come.
If not,
pack your stuff and leave.
Didn't you say you're a dandelion?
Just go anywhere you like.
There's no other way?
This is the only way.
How much longer will
the international meeting take?
I've waited for a day.
Sorry.
I guess it'll be quite late.
Is this something urgent?
What about tomorrow...
It's not necessary.
I can't afford a delay
in his billion worth of business.
You tell him
that I'm on my way to the crematorium
to commit suicide.
I won't trouble him.
Qin Kai.
Are you alright?
I heard this is quite serious
that they want to meet your parents.
It's alright.
This is just a small matter.
Are you sure?
Yes.
It's just asking my parents to come.
I've got work to do.
Go back to your classroom.
Class is about to begin.
Kai.
Are you alright?
Black Bull!
Is Qin Kai really okay?
Don't go there.
He's been
distressed all day
because of his parents.
What's wrong?
His parents are not coming?
His dad is as busy as a superman.
He almost detaches
from the gravity.
Even if he contacted his dad,
his dad would yell at him
and get his secretary
to handle it.
What about his mom?
His mom would like to come.
But she can't.
His mom is not at home too?
His mom
passed away when he was five.
He didn't tell me this.
This is how Kai is.
He doesn't like being worried about.
He's like an orphan.
What do you think he should do?
So you want to borrow
a mother?
That's new.
I've only heard
of borrowing books, money
and meal card.
It's my first time seeing
someone borrow a mother.
If you want to borrow money,
our commissary can make
a little contribution.
Just don't forget about the interest.
I don't want money or card.
I just want a mother.
I beg of you guys.
If Qin Kai couldn't get a mother,
he would be expelled from school.
You can get someone under a bridge
with only RMB 100 a day.
So no one will be troubled.
There's no time for it.
And we have to find
someone who's about our parents' ages.
So she won't get caught.
Count me out.
There's no way
my dad can't recognize my mom.
I don't think my mom can do it either.
She's bad at acting.
She can't even hide her emotion
when she gets a hit in a card game.
If she came
and spilled the beans,
Qin Kai and I would get expelled.
Sorry.
My parents are always away from home.
It has always been
my aunt who attends
my parent-teacher meeting.
Don't look at me.
You haven't met my mother.
It's unfulfilling to handle
the family affairs.
She'll often come to school
and look into my situation.
She could talk to Mr. Xie
all afternoon
in the parent-teacher meeting.
Every teacher knows her.
Xing,
you're the only hope
in our team.
My mom is quite good at acting
and she's open-minded.
Besides, she doesn't have
much contact with Mr. Xie.
The point is
why I should help him.
It's no use acting cute.
Ji Junxing.
Qin Kai is your roommate.
Are you going
to watch him teeter
on the verge of despair?
Don't you have a heart?
Why would he want
to borrow a mother?
Doesn't he have one?
His mom can't make it here.
You knew
Qin Kai is a lonely person.
Lonely?
I'm lonely too.
Everyone was born to be on their own.
His mom passed away.
You want to borrow a mother, right?
How did you know that?
Everyone knows about it.
I'll go home and talk with my mom.
I'll keep you posted.
That would be great.
But can she handle it?
Don't get your hopes up.
If you have a plan B,
execute it now.
But it is
when plan A fails.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Get off.
Since we've recognized
each other as relatives,
let's go all the way.
Let's go home.
Mom.
Why are you suddenly back?
That's enough.
Mom, I've got something to tell you.
So this is how it is.
So you're asking me
to be his mom for a day?
One day. That's all.
Help us, Mom.
You're Ji Junxing's baby brother,
aren't you?
Yes, I am.
You are
the guy who abducted
Sister Lin Xi, aren't you?
You've got a good eyesight.
You're right.
Besides, I'll soon become your brother.
This is all I can do for you.
You're on your own for the rest.
It's alright.
I'll find a way to make it work.
Here.
Aunt, these dumplings you made
have thin wraps and lots of stuffing.
They're fresh and tender.
It's like a three Michelin-starred dish.
They are frozen dumplings.
It's from the supermarket.
And you haven't tried it.
How did you know it's fresh?
As she does well
in choosing frozen dumplings,
what does it mean?
It means your mom has
good taste in things.
Enough, stop cozying up to me.
Junxing has told me
about what happened to you.
I don't think it's a big deal.
I can help you.
Really?
Do you really understand my situation?
It was just a mistake.
Everyone makes mistakes.
Unless this person
has never tried new things.
It wasn't a general mistake I made.
I'm numero uno
on the Dean of Student's blacklist.
Making a mistake
doesn't mean anything.
As long as you change it.
Aunt, you're so open-minded.
I'll see you at school
tomorrow afternoon.
Sure.
I'll meet you at the school gate.
Aunt, promise me you'll go.
If not,
I'll have to rove all over the world.
Don't worry.
Tomorrow,
I'll be your mother.
Eat up.
Mom.
Let's say
if I made
a grave mistake,
can I borrow a mother as well?
Well, you have to ask your dad
if he agrees or not.
Forget it.
I think he'll break my bones.
I'm glad you know that.
Eat up.
Here, eat more.
Thanks, Aunt.
Here, eat the dumplings.
I've already got a lot.
Just eat it.
He must've eaten a lot.
You eat it.
Mrs. Qin,
it's so hard
to see you in person.
Sorry.
I was too busy.
Yes.
Even so,
you should take time
to discipline your kid.
Are you aware of Qin Kai's situation
at school?
What's the matter?
Did he cause trouble again?
About his academic result,
I won't talk much.
He's always in the last place.
The total scores
of all subjects
are less than 200.
It's worse this time.
He broke into the boiler room,
causing hot water outages in the school.
The school is looking at ways
to see
if we should expel him.
Perfect.
I'm here today
to withdraw him from school.
What does Aunt mean?
What's going on?
Just trust my mom.
I'm sure she has a mind of her own.
What do you mean?
Frankly speaking,
I wasn't going
to let him go to school
this semester.
I'm too busy.
I don't have time
to handle some crap like this.
Leaving him at school
will only bring troubles
to you and the school.
Mom, give me one more chance.
Mr. Xie, help me convince my mom.
I want to go to school.
Yes, right.
Actually,
things are not that serious.
We can find a solution together.
Forget it.
He's not good at studies.
I think
it's better to let him enter society
to gain work experiences.
Mom, I'm still a kid.
I haven't graduated from high school.
How can I compete
with the people in society?
Mr. Xie.
Yes, right.
Qin Kai is right.
Besides,
he's in his second year
of high school now.
There's still hope if he works harder
in the cultural classes.
So you're not going to expel him?
Our school won't easily give up
on any one of our students.
Especially at a time like this,
parents must not be discouraged.
I asked you over
just to wish
that you could work with us.
Parents can't just leave the kids
at school without caring for them.
You should care more
about his physical and mental health.
Well, then.
If you say so,
I'll go home and talk to him.
Yes.
This is my phone number.
If he makes troubles again,
feel free to call me.
Okay, sure.
Thank you.
This is my job.
Mr. Xie,
you're not going to expel me?
Cut the nonsense.
Go write an apology.
Okay.
Bye bye.
Aunt, you're really good at acting.
You retreated in order to advance.
That was really convincing.
No matter how good my acting is,
I can only help you once.
I can't help you all your lives.
Rest assured.
This is the first time
and also the last time.
I won't bother you anymore.
It's no big deal to trouble me.
But this is your life.
You have to be responsible for it.
Didn't you say so yourself?
What can people
of your age do in society?
Actually, I just realized
that I was quite afraid
of being expelled.
Go back and study hard.
I'll get going.
Well, Aunt,
if I have time,
can I go to your place
and eat dumplings?
Of course you can.
You're always welcome.
Thank you, Aunt.
I should go.
Goodbye, Aunt.
Goodbye.
Thank you.
You should thank my mom.
Oh, no.
What's wrong?
We forgot
about Wang Dong and Ji Luchi.
Let's go.
Ji Luchi!
What took you so long?
How is it? We're not late, are we?
You're not late.
Is Wang Dong here yet?
Not yet.
What's the rush, then?
You don't understand.
Tactically,
it's more imposing to come early.
Ji Luchi!
You must be Wang Dong.
I am Wang Dong.
So this is
the tablemate who bullies you?
Yes.
She's scarier than Voldemort,
and more horrifying than Godzilla?
Yes, it's her.
Didn't you always have an attitude?
How could you
be bullied by a little girl?
Everything is
afraid of something.
Are you going to compete with me or not?
Are you afraid?
You should be.
I've brought a secret weapon over.
I'm sure I can defeat you.
Ready.
Start.
- Wang Dong, you can do it!
Ji Luchi, you can do it!
It feels like Ji Luchi will win
this time.
The race has just begun.
The winner is still undefined.
Are you really Ji Luchi's brother?
I just think
the victory doesn't do him any good.
Being happy is better than being upset.
As he pays so much effort,
if he loses,
will he be able to take it?
He's not that vulnerable.
Look, if Ji Luchi wins,
Wang Dong will be upset
and continue to bully him.
It's a vicious cycle.
If Ji Luchi loses,
he'll keep asking
to race with her.
Over time,
they might be friends by then.
- Wang Dong, you can do it!
Oh no.
Wang Dong's car fell into the fountain.
What should I do? It fell
into the middle of the fountain.
The water is running too fast.
Junxing,
help her.
How to get in there?
Hmm.
What are you doing?
One, two, three.
The fountain will stop for three seconds
after going off in every 30 seconds.
The next time when it stops,
I'll rush in there.
Let's endure hardships together.
I'll go with you.
Okay, sure.
♪Your fragrance and smiling eyes♪
♪I bump into you
in the corridor on purpose♪
♪I even dream about
what to wear for our date♪
♪It's okay♪
♪If you know nothing about all this♪
♪I get anxious when love is around♪
♪The little devil in me
turns into a nagger♪
♪Quick, show me your smiling dimples♪
♪I have a secret to tell you♪
♪That is, I fancy you♪
Thank you,
Brother Junxing and Sister Lin Xi.
I thought I can't get it back.
- You're welcome.
But I wonder if it still works.
Let me see.
It's a minor problem.
It's drenched.
I'll repair it for you.
Sure.
I'll buy you fried chickens.
Sure, it's a deal.
Come.
Let's make
a pinky swear.
Okay, I'll repair it for you later.
Okay.
The friendship between kids is
very simple.
With a model car,
and a bottle of milk,
it can bring them together.
You'll be satisfied
with just a cup of milk tea as well.
As I get to drink the milk tea,
it's nothing to be upset about.
By the way, I didn't know
what your favourite drink is.
Take a guess.
I guess it's Cola.
At our previous gathering,
I saw you drank it.
That was because you only ordered Cola.
Green tea?
You seemed to know a lot
about tea leaves
as I heard you talking about them.
That's my dad's favourite drink.
Then, what's your favourite drink?
Don't tell me you like
to drink milk too.
Actually, I like to drink mineral water.
It's a simple
and refreshing thirst-quencher.
It's no fun.
But now,
I think
a cup of milk tea is quite nice.
♪Your gentleness
is like the afternoon breeze♪
♪Amongst the crowd♪
♪My gaze remains on you♪
♪As if I were watching the starry sky♪
♪I can't help blushing♪
♪She's got such a gentle demeanour♪
♪I'm not myself when talking to her♪
Hello?
(What are you doing?)
(Do you want to eat with me?)
Never mind.
I've already eaten.
(Did everything go well today?)
(Did Mr. Xie punish you?)
Everything went well.
Mr. Xie looks smart
but he's actually gullible.
I was wondering
how he became the Dean of Student.
(Just keep it down.)
(Don't get caught by him again.)
I'm a free man
when I'm not at school.
I'm not afraid of getting caught by him.
I'd like to have this.
Sure.
And this.
Okay.
And a plate of peanuts.
Sure.
Then, give me two bottles of white wine.
Okay.
That's all.
Thank you.
No problem.
Beers will do for me.
What are you thinking?
It's not for you.
Dude, give him a bottle of herbal tea.
Sure.
It's boring.
My mom has already come.
What do you want from me?
I just want to eat and chat with you.
Can't I do that?
I think this is a trap.
Let me ask you one thing.
Where do you normally go after school?
This is entrapment.
This is out of your jurisdiction.
I'll give you a free pass.
At this moment,
I'm not Mr. Xie.
Are you for real?
Do I look like I'm joking?
Well, I'll tell you about it.
After school, I'll go over the wall
and go to the cybercafe,
to binge-watch American Drama,
read internet novel,
and stay up all night playing games.
Stay up all night?
You're out all night?
Free pass, free pass,
Mr. Xie.
Do you go home on the weekends?
No.
Then, where do you go during holiday?
I go anywhere I like.
I'm the universe orphan.
Just wander around the earth.
Then, what do you eat
when you're hungry?
Cup noodles, Malatang,
and self-heating pot.
If I'm lazy,
I'll get by for a day with hard tack
and mineral water.
That's what you eat?
Do you have enough living allowances?
Don't you worry about this.
Over years,
I've been lacking everything
except money.
Look.
(Payout RMB 65
Balance RMB 125,296.92)
(Chunhui High School Student's Profile)
(Mother Deceased)
Qin Kai is quite pathetic.
His mother passed away
when he was five.
What about his father?
I heard
that his father has remarried.
He's always abroad.
It's the secretary who attends
the parent-teacher meeting.
You're quite rich.
Are you going to confiscate my phone?
You can't do that.
I need to make a phone call.
Who are you calling?
Me.
Okay.
If your family is busy, I'll attend
your parent-teacher meeting.
You're taking advantage of me.
You brat.
What are you thinking?
Just spare my concerns.
Quickly finish it.
And go back to the dorm.
Don't always wander around out here.
I tell you what.
You'll be closely monitored.
If you don't pick up my call,
I'll kick your ass.
I got it.
Here, Mr. Xie.
Are your clothes dry?
Do you want to come
to my house and get changed?
They're almost dry.
I won't make it to school
if I go to your house.
Sister Lin Xi,
you can sleep in my room.
Weren't you asleep?
I was.
Didn't you hear me snoring?
Geez.
I think you just don't want to walk.
I can't walk anymore.
Sister Lin Xi,
let's go home.
Let's do it next time.
Next time, we'll play
with the RC car together.
We can also play with the RC airplane,
RC tractor,
and RC excavator.
And many more.
Junxing, I'm sleepy.
Hurry back.
I'll get going.
Stay safe on your way back to dorm.
Bye bye.
Don't forget this.
♪Your gentleness
is like the afternoon breeze♪
♪Amongst the crowd♪
♪My gaze remains on you♪
♪As if I were watching the starry sky♪
♪I can't help blushing♪
♪She's got such a gentle demeanour♪
♪I'm not myself when talking to her♪
♪Can I feel his heartbeat
at this very moment♪
♪And play the most romantic love song?♪
♪Can I reach his heart♪
♪With just one look?♪
♪Should I tell her
that I'm noticing her too♪
♪When she tries to
steal a glance at me again?♪
♪Catch the most gentle wind♪
♪And never let it go♪
♪Many of our love whispers♪
♪Are hidden in this city♪
♪Let the wind hear them♪
♪No matter how far
we are from one another♪
♪The cheeks are always blushing♪
♪That beating heart♪
♪Is like the rainbow
that appears after rain♪
♪Listen to it closely♪
♪I'm about to fall in love♪
♪Yes, I'm sure it is you♪