♪I get anxious when love is around♪
♪The little devil in me
turns into a nagger♪
♪Quick, show me your smiling dimples♪
♪I have a secret to tell you♪
♪That is, I fancy you♪
♪Your fragrance and smiling eyes♪
♪I bump into you
in the corridor on purpose♪
♪I even dream about
what to wear for our date♪
♪It's okay
if you know nothing about all this♪
♪I get anxious when love is around♪
♪The little devil in me
turns into a nagger♪
♪Quick, show me your smiling dimples♪
♪I have a secret to tell you♪
♪That is, I fancy you♪
=Time and Him are Just Right=
=Episode 2=
Don't you know how to knock?
So...Sorry.
I'm... I'm used to
not knocking back at home.
I didn't see anything.
What's the matter?
You wore your shirt wrongly.
This is how it's designed.
Am I that bad at fashion?
Ji Junxing.
Let's be friends.
I love you.
(That can't be true.)
What are you doing?
I was having a hard time falling asleep,
so I wanted to drink some water.
I only took the first sip
when I heard you coming down the stairs.
Then, I was reminded of your advice,
telling me to watch my behavior
when I'm living at your place.
I agreed with what you said,
so I found myself a hiding place.
Great.
It makes perfect sense.
I can't refute whatever you said too.
I guess so.
My main concern
is not wanting to scare you.
But I think you're trying to scare me.
What else do you want?
You're holding the tomato sauce.
Tomato sauce is exactly what I want.
Lin Xi.
You're done for.
It's only the first day,
and because of you,
he was late to class, got punished,
and had to write a reflection letter.
You scared him big time too.
How are you going to be his friend?
Good morning, Madam Wen.
Good morning. You're up.
Did you sleep well?
Did you hear any weird noises at night?
Weird noises?
I didn't hear anything.
I'm well-rested.
By the way,
I saw this
in the property owners' chat group.
Our neighbors said
that their dog
was barking hysterically
at midnight yesterday.
Did it wake you up?
No.
I was sleeping rather soundly.
That's good.
I was worried that
you wouldn't be able to get a good rest.
I'm fine.
Have an egg.
Thank you.
(Facial Cleansing Foam)
It's going to be a brand new day.
Ji Junxing.
Are you done washing up?
Come and have breakfast.
You can eat all you want.
Why are you so grumpy
early in the morning?
Junxing.
Make sure
you send Lin Xi to school in one piece.
Did you hear me?
Mom.
If you're worried about her,
you can risk being late for work
and send her to school personally.
Little rascal.
I do have
some confidence in you.
Lin Xi.
I've got to go.
Bye.
See you tonight, Madam.
What are you doing?
Madam told you
to send me to school, right?
Come here.
Never let anyone find out
that we're living together.
Bear in mind.
I'll keep it to myself.
How do I go to school from here?
Turn right after you exit this area.
Take Bus Number 14.
(Yuezhou City Chunhui High School)
Ji Junxing.
There was something
I couldn't understand
from yesterday's English class.
Can you explain it to me?
Which part do you not understand?
The question about passive voice.
Let's discuss it on our way to school.
Sure.
For this question...
It's quite difficult.
What are you staring at?
You're scaring me.
Is Ji Junxing always this popular?
Of course.
What are the two types
of popular guys in school?
The first type is guys
who're gentle and good at studies.
And the other type is boys
who are good-looking and sporty.
And Ji Junxing
is a combination of both.
You'll find out more
when you spend more time with him.
Let's go.
It's quite convenient for you
to travel to school.
We agreed to keep it a secret, right?
Sorry.
Is she rolling her eyes at me?
She has rolled her eyes at you
for several times.
We'll start the class now.
I have an announcement to make
before we commence the class.
The school authority
will be here next week
and join
one of our public English classes.
I need six students
to present a sketch.
Ji Junxing,
you are the class representative.
Make some arrangements for the sketch.
Take the script.
Sure.
Any of you wants to join the sketch?
It's a good chance to skip classes.
Me. I'm joining!
You're right.
I want to join too.
Me too!
Miss.
I volunteer
to help Ji Junxing with the sketch.
Sure.
There will be five of us including me.
Anyone else wants to join us?
I want to join the sketch.
Working Cell.
It's a relatively simple story.
Simply put.
Streptococcus pneumonia
invaded the human lungs.
The red and white blood cells
then work together to chase it out.
You have read the script.
Pick a character you're interested in.
I'll be the villain.
The villain is usually the strongest.
Sure.
What about the white blood cell?
Anybody wants
to be the white blood cell?
These vocabularies are too advanced.
I can't remember the lines.
It's a difficult task
and it's also the main hero.
Junxing, you should do it.
Sure.
I'll be the white blood cell then.
Then, I will act as the red blood cell.
I speak very decent English.
Besides, I am deeply moved
by the hug shared between
the red blood cell
and the white blood cell
at the end of the story.
I'm sure
I can give my best performance.
Anyone else wants this character?
Of course.
You want to play the character, huh?
Can you speak fluently?
No.
He will play the character.
Me?
Yes.
You will do it.
Yes. I'll do it.
It's the perfect role for me.
And if the play
ends with a hug,
of course, it has to be me.
But you're a boy.
The red blood cell is the heroine.
It'd be really fun
to see him cross-dress.
Yes. Cross-dressing.
It's a very interesting idea.
I agree.
But Xie Ang...
Let's vote.
If you agree that
Xie Ang should be the red blood cell,
raise your hand.
Four and two.
It's decided.
Junxing wants us
to go to the east of the field.
We'll do a rehearsal under the lamp post
right before the third tree.
Do we really have to
act so secretive for a rehearsal?
They never turn off
the street light there.
No one will notice us.
Will they
be there too?
Of course.
Do you think Ji Junxing
will want to meet you there alone?
In your dreams.
One. Two. Three.
I'm at the right place.
Why is no one here yet?
How dare you bite me?
Despite the difficult circumstances,
we continue
with our rehearsal late at night.
We deserve an Academy Award
for all the hard work we put in,
or our cast and crew
will be very disappointed.
I'm a bad cell.
I am dying.
Have you taken your dinner?
I bought some supper.
Tell Lin Xi to join us.
She's not home yet.
She's not home yet?
But it's late now.
Where did she go?
Why is she not home yet?
I have no idea.
Then, why are you still here
watching the TV show?
I told you
to go to school and come home together.
How can you not know where she went?
She has her own social life.
I'm not her minion.
I can't follow her
everywhere, right?
(Madam Wen)
Her phone is not with her.
She didn't take her phone with her?
She's a young girl.
And it's late now.
Why is she not home yet?
She has already missed
the last bus of the day.
How will she come home later?
Enough, Mom.
I'll go and find her now.
What if she runs into a bad guy?
It's late.
And she's not home yet.
I got it.
I'm a bad cell.
I am dying.
Are they having dinner?
I don't think so.
I'm a bad cell.
I am dying.
My goodness.
I'm hallucinating now.
I've been reciting this for an hour.
Why aren't they here yet?
You're still alive.
Who's there?
Take it easy.
Where did he go? Let's search that area.
I saw him going this way.
Where did he go?
Where is he?
I saw him just now.
Let's split up.
Sure.
Where did he go?
Who are you?
We are schoolmates. I'm not a bad guy.
Did I scare you?
You scared me big time.
I almost passed out.
Come here.
You're quite interesting.
Are you new here?
What tells you I'm a newbie?
Everyone in this school
thinks I'm a bad student.
You're the only one
who's not afraid of me.
You even bit me.
That's because
I'm different.
Hi.
My name is Qin Kai.
I'm from Grade Two's Art Class.
What about you?
My name is Lin Xi.
I'm a new student in
Class One, Grade Two.
Nice to meet you.
Keep looking.
Come here.
Why are they looking for you?
I sneaked out to the internet cafe.
I just got back here
by climbing over the wall.
You're quite unlucky today.
I don't think I'm unlucky.
I got to know you.
That's a very pleasant surprise.
You would know what a real surprise is
after you leave this bush.
This is more like an accident.
Why are you here?
I...
I guess
my classmate pulled a prank on me.
Search that area.
Hurry up!
What will happen if we get caught?
According to the rules
of Chunhui High School,
those who break the curfew
will either be asked to write
a reflection letter or get expelled.
I can't write another reflection letter.
Where did he go?
I saw him going this way.
Are you a runner?
I guess so.
You'll go that way and I'll go this way.
Are you ready?
Run!
Stop running. Stand there!
Stop running!
Hurry up!
Stop right there!
Stop running!
Careful.
Stop right there!
Let me catch my breath.
What an exciting day.
You look like an obedient student.
I didn't expect you to be so cool.
Why not?
Are you looking down on good students?
That's not true.
Search the tunnel.
They're here again. Let's go!
Why are they still on our heels?
There he is!
There! Hurry up!
Stop running! Stop!
Stop!
Here. Hurry up!
This...
Be careful.
Stop right there!
Where did they go? Stop right there!
We lost them.
Where did they go? Let's look around.
We're finally safe.
We've finally regained our freedom.
Fate brought us together.
Let's be friends.
I thought we're already friends.
Fine.
I'll listen to you.
It's getting late.
I've got to go.
I don't want to worry my family.
Sure.
I'll meet you at your class next time.
You should go home now.
Bye.
What brings you here?
Let's go.
Are you here to look for me
because you didn't see me at home?
Do you know what time is it now?
You should be more conscious
when living under someone else's roof.
You'll worry others
when you stay out late.
It was all because of Liu Yin.
She lied to me, saying that
you were going to have a rehearsal here.
Otherwise,
I wouldn't have stayed
in the field for such a long time.
Why did you believe everything she said?
I thought you had a clear head.
Why didn't you verify
her words?
I didn't want to upset you.
You are unpredictable.
All I want to do now
is to become a harmless animal
and stay very quietly by your side
every day.
I'm afraid that I might make a mistake
and accidentally push your buttons.
Then, not only will we
fail to be friends,
we will also become enemies.
Enough.
Shut up.
Why are you so talkative?
Let me share
an interesting story with you.
We did a physical examination
in school today,
and I removed
my tablemate's height insoles.
He got his height measured,
and he is
three centimeters shorter than before.
- Also...
- Why are you so talkative? Shut up.
What did you say?
Why are you so talkative?
The previous sentence.
Shut up.
Can you connect them?
I'll shut up after you repeat it.
Are you mad?
It doesn't matter.
Say it again, please.
I won't.
Just once.
It won't hurt you.
Just repeat the sentence
you said just now.
Please. Just once.
Good morning, Sir.
Good morning.
Good morning, Mr. Xie.
Morning.
Mr. Xie.
Hello.
Do you have a hidden agenda?
No, I don't.
You're quite good at fighting back.
I only want to tell her
that I'm not one to be trifled with.
What are you laughing at?
What's so funny?
We'll now do a rehearsal
for the public English class now.
Don't make any mistakes tomorrow.
Did you hear me?
Yes.
I'm a red blood cell, now...
I will fight.
Why can't I memorize it?
White Blood Cell.
Thanks for saving us.
The lines are in English.
Miss Sun won't show you any mercy
if you fail to memorize your lines.
And of course,
I won't let you go too.
What do I do now?
I'll just eat.
Let's welcome Class One, Grade Two.
They will present a sketch named
"Working Cell".
Working Cell.
(Working Cell)
I'm a white blood cell.
I'm responsible for removing
bacteria and virus
that invade the body from the outside.
I am Streptococcus pneumonia.
My destructive power is very strong.
What's the matter?
I get an upset stomach
whenever I'm nervous.
Are you all right?
(It's neck and neck.)
What do we do now?
(Let the white blood cell's partner)
(show up!)
Where is Xie Ang?
Why isn't he here yet?
Keep fighting.
We're done for.
What if the audience gets bored of us?
Xie Ang, can you
just hold on a little longer?
I don't think so.
I can't move at all.
What do we do now?
Set him free!
Who are you?
I'm the red blood cell
you're looking for.
Now, I'll fight with you.
Finally, the red blood cell is here.
They will resume the battle.
Watch out!
Thank you for saving me.
It was really close.
My voice was trembling
when I was on the stage.
Fortunately, we managed to complete it.
How come you know Xie Ang's lines?
I saw you
worrying about Xie Ang yesterday.
So I thought
I should memorize his lines too.
I only wanted to remind him
behind the stage.
Little did I know
it would actually come in handy.
Thank you so much.
What did you say?
You heard it.
I'm not hallucinating, am I?
It's your first time
saying "thank you" to me.
Does it mean
that I was actually helpful?
that we're one step closer
to being real friends?
That's not what I meant.
Since we aren't friends,
a simple "thank you"
won't be enough.
What do you want?
Buy me milk tea.
Hello. Your drink is ready.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Here.
The milk tea you asked for.
Two cups?
Thank you.
Oolong without sugar.
Pure milk.
Tea and milk.
That's the milk tea you were asking for.
Ji Junxing.
Are you doing this on purpose?
Milk tea has a high content
of trans fat,
caffeine and fat.
Too much milk tea
will increase the risk
for cardiovascular diseases.
It'll also make you gain weight.
It will do you no good at all.
I suggest you reduce
your milk tea intake.
You're talking
as if you're the expert
we see on the TV show.
Thanks for your concern.
But
I want my milk tea now.
Normal sugar,
with pearl and Nata de coco.
I want grass jelly too.
I want every other add-on as well.
My brother and I like it.
Up to you.
Ji Junxing.
Wait.
Do you like Crayon Shinchan too?
Go away.
♪Your gentleness
is like the afternoon breeze♪
♪Amongst the crowd♪
♪My gaze remains on you♪
♪As if I were watching the starry sky♪
♪I can't help blushing♪
♪She's got such a gentle demeanour♪
♪I'm not myself when talking to her♪
♪Can I feel his heartbeat
at this very moment♪
♪And play the most romantic love song?♪
♪Can I reach his heart♪
♪With just one look?♪
♪Should I tell her
that I'm noticing her too♪
♪When she tries to
steal a glance at me again?♪
♪Catch the most gentle wind♪
♪And never let it go♪
♪Many of our love whispers♪
♪Are hidden in this city♪
♪Let the wind hear them♪
♪No matter how far
we are from one another♪
♪The cheeks are always blushing♪
♪That beating heart♪
♪Is like the rainbow
that appears after rain♪
♪Listen to it closely♪
♪I'm about to fall in love♪
♪Yes, I'm sure it is you♪