♪I get anxious when love is around♪
♪The little devil in me
turns into a nagger♪
♪Quick, show me your smiling dimples♪
♪I have a secret to tell you♪
♪That is, I fancy you♪
♪Your fragrance and smiling eyes♪
♪I bump into you
in the corridor on purpose♪
♪I even dream about
what to wear for our date♪
♪It's okay
if you know nothing about all this♪
♪I get anxious when love is around♪
♪The little devil in me
turns into a nagger♪
♪Quick, show me your smiling dimples♪
♪I have a secret to tell you♪
♪That is, I fancy you♪
=Time and Him are Just Right=
=Episode 6=
Thank you for all
the excellent performance.
(Celebration of Chunhui High School
75th Anniversary)
Marching forward against tempest
(Warmly Celebrate the 75th Anniversary
of Yuezhou City Chunhui High School)
over the past seventy-five years,
those fervent times
would adorn our school with glory.
How is it? Is everything ready?
We have rehearsed it many times.
We guarantee that you...
No, we guarantee that she
will be the brightest one.
You better not ruin it like last time.
No worries, Kai.
- We're off.
- Go.
Chunhui's 75th Anniversary Gala Night
will end here.
- Wish you a good night.
- A good night.
Tonight's performance was good.
Right, the last performance
was quite creative.
Don't you think Ji Junxing
did a great job as the emcee?
I was moved by what he said just now.
Well.
I haven't started
the English review given by Miss Sun.
I'm going to burn the midnight oil
tonight.
Jiang Yimian, let's do it together.
I won't despise you
even though you are bad at English.
But I despise you as a person.
Xie Ang.
It's fine.
Look at his face.
Is it a blackout?
Would it be the surprise event
of the gala night?
It's too good to be true.
Why not?
What's going on?
What?
Right. Look for Lin Xi.
Good.
What's going on now?
Lin Xi.
It seems that the light is for you.
You look pretty
under the limelight.
Is it you?
Yes.
Didn't you say
Ji Junxing and Song Linxue look gorgeous
under the limelight?
So, I cut the power
and asked Black Bull and the rest
to be the light-chasers.
You can experience
how it feels standing
under the limelight.
How do you feel now?
It is good, right?
I was just saying.
Why make a big deal out of it?
Aren't you afraid of being caught
by Mr. Xie?
Yes, I do.
Before he comes,
I must tell you everything.
What is it?
Actually, I didn't prepare
a beautiful speech.
Also, this idea came out on a whim.
It was because
I noticed you were upset
at backstage just now.
I couldn't guess
what made you feel upset.
But,
I'm willing to try my very best
to make you happy.
Ostentatious.
Lin Xi.
I want you to stand under the limelight.
However, to me,
regardless of whether you standing
in a bright place or not,
you are always glowing
in my eyes.
Because
I...
Why gather over there?
Qin Kai. It is you, again.
I'm going to punish you.
Mr. Xie is here.
Run.
Lin Xi.
Run. Faster.
Let's leave.
Lin Xi.
Come with me.
Let's leave.
(Next, I'm going to make an announcement.)
Yesterday night, Qin Kai
from Class Twelve of Grade Two
shut off the electricity in the school
for the light show performance.
This is bad conduct
and has violated the school disciple.
(Therefore, I render him reprimand.)
(This is also a warning for all students.)
Qin Kai.
I came here...
To comfort me.
How do you know?
I can tell from your face.
Don't be nervous.
We can get on well
like we used to previously.
Do you mean it?
You have moved on already?
But,
if you regret your decision
and want to develop
a deeper relationship with me,
I agree with you too.
You can crack jokes now.
I'm relieved then.
I couldn't sleep well yesterday
as I worried that you might be upset.
I was confusing how to reject you.
How considerate of you.
Come on.
Share with me.
No.
Please.
Tell me.
Wait for me.
Just tell me.
Hey, tell me.
I was wondering
what would happen
between you and Qin Kai.
Yet, you have nipped the possibility
between you.
That's regret.
Nothing to regret.
This is like different arrangements
of carbon elements
forming different isoforms.
If the arrangement forms
in the right mode,
it will be a diamond.
If not,
it will be graphite.
May I ask
if you both are still on good terms?
Can you talk as usual?
We are still good friends.
I'm relieved to hear that.
This is the interview plan.
The school wants to launch
the booklet for promoting
the school anniversary.
(School Anniversary Promotion)
The names in the table
are excellent representatives
in their fields.
I have to do the photoshoot
and interview with them
for the sake of the booklet.
Song Linxue, Ji Junxing,
(Song Linxue; Ji Junxing,
Top Student of the Grade)
and Qin Kai?
He is the gold medalist
in the municipal competition.
He represents the athlete student.
Do you want me
to interview all of them?
Not all.
Song Linxue and the others
will be handled by me.
As for the remaining two,
(Ji Junxing, Qin Kai)
one is your good friend,
while the other one sits beside you.
You have the best convenience
to interview them.
You are the best choice.
May I say no?
Lin Xi.
Can you bear to see me shouldering
such a heavy task on my thin back
without helping me?
Can you bear to...
Fine.
I will do it.
I know
you will help me for sure.
When do you need this?
Tonight.
Seriously?
If it wasn't this urgent,
I wouldn't torture my best friend.
Anyway, I have faith in you.
With your smart brain
you will definitely accomplish it.
You can do this.
Oh gosh, she indeed tortures me.
Let's use this room.
Sit anywhere you want.
You can start now.
We have to wait for a while.
Who is coming?
Qin...
I'm sorry.
I was having a training just now.
I'm not late, am I?
You got here just on time.
Isn't this the star emcee
in the gala night?
You are here too.
Why didn't you tell me
someone is coming too?
Please hear me out.
I was given this task at short notice.
Both of your interview outlines
are the same,
so I call you two here
due to time concerns.
Help me, please.
Thank you so much.
Let's do it now.
This is the outline of the interview.
Let's start with the first question.
What does Chunhui High School
mean to you?
Surprise and joy.
Care to elaborate?
For example,
the night when I first met you
and we were running in the night
to avoid security.
It was a surprise and a joy for me.
What about you?
Chunhui is where we spend
our youth together
and a place where our dreams begin.
These words ring a bell.
Lin Xi wrote this for me.
The hosting script.
Lin Xi wrote these lines
for Chunhui's 75th anniversary.
Next question.
Out of the school's motto,
freedom, perseverance and erudition,
please define your understanding
of freedom.
Speaking of freedom,
this is simple.
Freedom means to be our real selves.
Laugh when you are happy
and cry when you are not.
Not bound to any restriction.
Be bold to confess
when you admire someone.
Freedom
doesn't mean one can do anything
he wants without restriction.
Instead, despite under conditions,
one possesses liberal thoughts
and a free spirit.
Freedom that comes with restriction
is like an eagle on a leash.
Eagles should soar in the sky freely.
Wings are not ornaments.
Flying has to be their mission.
Speaking of the sky,
in a manner of fact,
it should be the troposphere.
No eagle can fly in the stratosphere.
For one to soar freely,
it should be within the limits set.
Or else, one will turn wildly arrogant
and out of order.
You're coming after me.
I just hope that you
could behave when you possess freedom
but not to display some kind
of light show
before the public.
You made others feel awkward.
Did I make you awkward?
Not really.
Didn't his behaviour bother you?
Yes, a little bit.
Wait.
We are talking about freedom.
How is this about me?
Who's the one
getting interviewed?
This is not effective though.
I will answer the questions myself.
Good idea.
Submit it to me by today.
Do you want to answer the questions
by yourself?
No.
It's better if you interview me.
During high school time,
have you met a friend
with whom you were honoured to know
and want to continue the friendship?
Honoured to know? No, there is none.
But one I feel ill-fated to meet.
How is it?
I'm done.
Take it.
Thank you.
I go to bed now.
It is only eight now.
(A friend you wish to continue
your friendship with in high school)
All students?
What a big heart he has.
Mission completed.
(Jiang Yimian)
Hello.
Hello, Lin Xi.
You've done perfectly
with their interviews.
Amazing.
You're more resourceful
than the Monkey King
and more compassionate than
the Goddess of Mercy.
There are no challenges
too difficult for you.
Stop it.
Stop singing praises of me.
When you start praising me,
you must have something to ask of me.
You are indeed smart.
Good guess.
What is it?
My mum said
I screwed my exam this time.
She forced me to study at the library
this weekend.
And I can't do the photoshoot
for both Ji Junxing and Song Linxue.
Therefore, I would like to task you
with this important job
at the last minute.
How would I, a day worker
be able to shoulder
such an important task?
There is a new escape room
around the photo shooting venue.
You can go there after the task.
Are you sure to turn my request down?
Fine, I will think about it.
I take that as a yes.
Bye-bye, dear.
She got me again.
Good morning.
Are you going out?
Where to?
Same as you. I'm going
to the bookstore too.
You slept in early yesterday.
I forgot to tell you
that Jiang Yimian
has a sudden plan today.
She asked me to do the photoshoot
for you and Song Linxue.
Oh, you wear two hats.
Yeah, life is tough.
Aperture, focal length,
ios icon.
Hey.
Do you know where the shutter button is?
I do have some knowledge about cameras.
It is just that I'm not sure
about the parameters.
Come, let me show you.
Do you know about cameras?
Look at this.
This button adjusts
the size of the aperture.
Large aperture size
gives a shallow depth of field.
It helps to focus the object
and the background becomes blurry.
The picture portrays as hazy
and soft.
This is suitable for portraits.
How does the picture look?
See it yourself.
Right.
Good.
Excuse me.
I think
you can squat.
My legs seem longer from that view.
Got it.
Lin Xi.
You are a bit too low.
Just bend your knees a little.
No worries.
I will get you the best picture.
Nice.
One more.
Ji Junxing. Smile, please.
Try to be friendly.
That's good.
Maintain it.
Maintain the smile.
The light is good.
Yes.
Ji Junxing.
Relax your body.
Don't strain yourself.
Perhaps you can lean against the wall.
Like this?
Your leg.
My goodness.
Stretch your right leg out.
Bend your left leg a little.
Relax your upper body.
Right. Relax your body.
Show your neck and strong jawline.
Act like you enjoy the sun.
Are you an old man?
What's with your stiff neck?
Look over there.
Relax.
Adjust your gaze.
Look over there.
Ji Junxing.
What's wrong with you?
Hurry up.
Got it?
Yes, got it.
Stay still.
Stand there.
Yes.
Look over there, not me.
Hello.
What?
Escape room?
Today?
Give me ten minutes.
Did you rest?
Yes, we are done.
Come on. Get ready for high knees.
Qin Kai. This is the finish line.
My finish line is over there.
Just four of you?
Two teams?
Yes.
I prefer the package
if we are split from the start
of the game
and meet up at the end.
Why? Don't you have a package like this?
Yes. Of course, we have.
Here, take a look.
Iris.
This name sounds elegant.
What do you think?
Yes.
Let's go.
This way.
Sir.
Is this game suitable for weak hearts?
For two of them.
They can't play horror themes?
Leave the horror theme to us.
Got it.
They play the theme that needs thinking.
All right. Come with me.
I can't see anything.
I'm not shivering. I'm not afraid.
How much further do we have to walk?
How much longer?
Who is it?
Someone holds on to me.
(The most popular escape them.)
(Aside from testing your intelligence
and collaboration,)
(trust and luck are crucial too.)
(Only a few accomplished the challenges.)
(There will be two routes.
Please enjoy the game.)
(There is a surprise awaiting you.)
(Take off the blindfold now.)
You are here.
(Driver.)
(You have three minutes)
(to look for the raincoats in the van)
(and take the passenger to leave)
(for the next level.)
(Otherwise, you will be swallowed
by darkness.)
When can we remove the blindfold?
I'm afraid.
Don't be afraid.
I'm here.
(Take off the blindfold now.)
Hello.
(Welcome to my resource room.)
(This place keeps)
(the information of four people.)
(Please find them out)
(Beiyang Times)
(and put their name cards in order.)
(Zhang Yueru, You Lian)
(And you will get the clue)
(Castle Peak Hospital)
(to open the safe behind you.)
(You can enter the next level)
(only by accomplishing their last wishes.)
The numbers of car light flashing
corresponds to the passcode.
You are smart.
Six.
One.
Two.
Three.
Six, one, two, three.
Qin Kai, we got the raincoats.
You are awesome.
These are the documents
of the four people.
Participants, please
put the name cards in the correct order.
I think we should put it here.
What is the sequence of the name cards?
Could it be
the year when they got admitted?
Give it a try.
Let's try it.
The first person is
Xu Guoqiang.
Then, Zhou Lihua.
Jie Lu.
The fourth one is Yue Bing.
This one.
It is a tape.
A tape.
Let's find if there is a tape player.
Something is in this box.
There is really a tape player.
This is kind of boring.
Why don't we...
(This is so fun.)
(The character is cool.)
(Mister, don't run.)
They seem to be enjoying this game
very much.
Forget about them.
Zero.
Five.
One.
Zero, five, one, one.
The passcode is zero five one one.
(Congratulations.
The passcode is correct.)
(Castle Peak Hospital)
Go to the chemistry laboratory
and find the passcode to the next level.
The game
is challenging our intelligence.
Here comes another riddle.
Let's go
to the chemistry lab.
Yes.
It is a dead end.
There is a button behind you.
Why are you here?
Why did the door bring you here?
Ji Junxing.
Press the red button.
I did. Nothing happens.
Press it again.
It doesn't work.
I can't go back.
So do you.
Stupid door.
What do we do now?
Do you want to continue?
No, let's leave.
Don't go.
Try the passcode.
Don't give up.
Quit pressing it.
Let's try again.
Don't leave.
Quit pressing the button.
It won't do any difference.
Probably this is the surprise mentioned
just now.
What the heck?
I thought we could play the game
separately.
The boss lied.
Boss.
We want to quit.
We quit.
Boss.
I'm sorry
for disturbing you and Qin Kai.
You were indeed having fun just now.
This is so fun.
I'm so happy.
Why did it sound weird
when you said that out?
Because I'm imitating your tone.
If you think I'm loud,
go back now.
I can't.
Come with me.
I don't want to. Why should I?
Don't drag me.
I'm not playing. I want to go out.
Don't force me.
Here.
Boss.
Boss, I quit.
Boss, I give up.
Hey, boss.
Didn't you pester me
even though I ignored you
when you wanted to befriend me?
How come
you want to step down now?
Are you afraid your shallow
intelligence will be exposed?
I don't think this game
can be difficult though.
Good for you.
The reverse psychology works.
Today, I will continue the game
till I pass.
I would love to.
Well.
According to my understanding of them,
there will be something showing up
from the window
to scare us out later.
You can hide behind me.
Don't be shy.
Your health matters more.
Hurry up and find the clue.
There is a chest.
It seems we have to open it together.
Unlock it.
We are nearing the victory
and I'm free then.
One eight two seven.
The passcode can't be this easy.
(The passcode for this level
is five words.)
(It is something common)
(in the kong fu novel.)
She said the passcode is five words.
These numbers aren't the passcode.
There are many chemical solutions here.
If I'm not wrong,
one eight two seven
is the sequence
in the periodic table.
I thought so.
Based on the periodic table,
oxygen is the eighth
and nitrogen is the seventh.
Therefore, one eight two seven should be
nitrous oxide.
[*Note:1 oxygen atom and 2 nitrogen atoms]
But it is strange for nitrous oxide
to be found in the kong fu novel though.
Nitrous oxide
is found in the laughing gas.
Laughing gas.
Laugh in half step epilepsy.
Exactly.
The answer is
'laugh in half step epilepsy'.
Don't look.
Is the answer wrong?
It shouldn't be.
Nitrous oxide.
Ten spices of nerve numbness.
Stop guessing.
Do you still remember
what the boss said?
Aside from intelligence
and collaboration,
trust and luck are crucial too.
Right.
He must be
hinting at us.
Besides,
Iris brings the meaning
of love and trust.
What if the boss
is testing our trust in each other
at the final level?
What do you mean?
We came up with this answer together.
I don't think it is wrong.
What if it is wrong?
At least I'm here with you.
We don't change the answer.
- Laugh in half step epilepsy.
♪Your fragrance♪
♪And smiling eyes♪
♪I bump into you♪
♪In the corridor on purpose♪
Congratulations, players.
Iris that symbolises love and trust
will give you its best blessing.
♪It's okay♪
♪I get anxious♪
We got it.
♪When love is around♪
♪The little devil in me♪
♪Turns into a nagger♪
♪Quick, show me♪
We made it.
Let's leave.
♪I have a secret to tell you♪
♪That is, I fancy you♪
Didn't he say he was bad
at taking photos?
They did well together.
It has been one hour.
Why hasn't he come back yet?
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I'm watching the drama.
Didn't you go to the bookstore
with Song Linxue
after leaving the escape room?
Why are you back early?
We've bought the books.
It seems Qin Kai and you
are out of strength too.
Didn't he take you to savour
all delicious food in the city?
We did savour all kinds of food.
The street stalls downstairs
serve delicious from all around
the globe.
Here, the Korean fried chicken.
Qin Kai bought this.
Taste it.
Just so-so.
Just so-so?
Give it back to me.
♪Your gentleness
is like the afternoon breeze♪
♪Amongst the crowd♪
♪My gaze remains on you♪
♪As if I were watching the starry sky♪
♪I can't help blushing♪
♪She's got such a gentle demeanour♪
♪I'm not myself when talking to her♪
♪Can I feel his heartbeat
at this very moment♪
♪And play the most romantic love song?♪
♪Can I reach his heart♪
♪With just one look?♪
♪Should I tell her
that I'm noticing her too♪
♪When she tries to
steal a glance at me again?♪
♪Catch the most gentle wind♪
♪And never let it go♪
♪Many of our love whispers♪
♪Are hidden in this city♪
♪Let the wind hear them♪
♪No matter how far
we are from one another♪
♪The cheeks are always blushing♪
♪That beating heart♪
♪Is like the rainbow
that appears after rain♪
♪Listen to it closely♪
♪I'm about to fall in love♪
♪Yes, I'm sure it is you♪