=What If=
=Episode 18=
(A Farewell Without A Goodbye)
(Xue Yuming: Xia Guo, are you busy?
Reply to me when you're free.)
(Xue Yuming: Move to my house.)
(I'm still renting it.)
(Xia Guo: Thank you. No need.)
(Xue Yuming: Have you eaten?)
(Xue Yuming: Are you up?
Xia Guo: Yeah.)
(Xue Yuming: Are you asleep? Goodnight.)
(Xue Yuming: Guo, take some time off.)
(You haven't used your annual leave
over the years.)
(Are you okay?)
Alright.
This is the modified proposal.
See if you have any comments.
- I look forward to working with you.
- Thank you.
That's great.
Implement these as soon as possible.
Especially the end of the year.
Ms. Xia, do you want to check that out?
I'm fine.
Everyone must focus.
Don't ever lose focus.
Get motivated. Got it?
Got it.
Ms. Xia!
The doctor recommends
that you get hospitalized.
Take the doctor's advice.
Your stomach problem, bronchitis,
and high blood pressure
are too serious.
No. I have a lot of work on my hands.
Alright.
Come in.
Mr. Wu.
Ms. Xia, can I help you?
I just finished a meeting this morning.
I want to report some things to you.
What happened to your voice?
I just have a cold and a little cough.
I'm fine.
Well...
Ms. Xia.
You don't have to work so hard.
We know
all about your mom.
You can use this time
to take a long holiday.
Get some rest and refresh yourself.
I'm fine, Mr. Wu.
Thank you for your concern.
But the marketing department
hasn't met your expectations.
How can I rest?
You're too stubborn.
You're not the only one
in the marketing department.
Sorry.
I know
you're trying to become official.
This puts a lot of pressure on yourself.
Of course, this is coupled with
my high expectations for you
and the marketing department.
It's beyond your abilities.
I understand.
You've worked very hard.
I can see that.
So take some time to relax.
Release your tension.
Pay attention to work-life balance.
Okay, I got it, Mr. Wu.
I'll think about your suggestion.
I'll tell you about work
another time.
Take your time. Take your time.
Take good care of yourself.
Okay.
(Chen Nan: We haven't talked
for a long time.)
(Do you have time to meet tonight?)
(No. 18, Bund, Huangpu District.)
What's wrong?
You're so pale.
Are you sick?
I'm fine. I just have a little cold.
I'll be fine after resting for a few days.
Alright. Stop pretending.
Didn't Wu just satirize you?
You found out?
I don't think I can stay
in Haowei any longer.
Don't stay if you can't stay.
I came here today to poach you.
I joined a jewelry company
and want you to come with me.
This...
This is so sudden.
Can I do it?
There's no doubt
that you can't do it
in your current state.
Xia Guo, do you know
what I like most about you?
It's your relentlessness.
Whoever it is,
you don't care.
Now great.
When I saw you today,
you became a total coward,
You let reality beat you.
You were defeated by Wu.
You lost your aggressiveness.
Maybe?
I'm just a little scared.
You were right.
This job is more important
than fairness.
The more you're scared of others
bullying you,
the more they will bully you.
The more you fear losing,
the more you'll lose.
But I think I've worked very hard.
That means
you're not working hard enough.
Actually, everyone wants results.
Only you should know the process.
Do you have to explain to others?
Do you want people to pity you
and comfort you?
Fine.
Come to me when you
can't make a living for yourself.
I'll make sure you can make a living
wherever I can make a living.
If you don't have a place to live,
come to my house.
The couch is yours.
Will you come?
Ms. Nan, how can you
make something so sweet
sound so bad?
I just want to vent to someone.
I can't tell others.
Tell others? Who are you gonna tell?
Do you want me to introduce you
to some elites?
You're still single yourself,
and you want to introduce me?
I'm happy to be single.
I'm comfortable on my own, okay?
Comfortable, comfortable.
I'm not trapped by love like you.
Are you still thinking about Xue Yuming?
No.
But honestly, I suggest you
to forget about him.
Really. Because I know him too well.
He's your standard
refined egoist.
Do you think someone like him
is worth your energy and time?
You'd better pull yourself together
and fight with me, okay?
Okay.
I'll pull myself together.
Hurry and eat. The food's getting cold.
Who are you looking for?
I'm here for Allen.
Who?
Get Allen for me.
Allen, Allen, someone's here for you.
Coming.
Why are you here?
I was about to find you.
What are you doing? It's so noisy.
I'm having a party on the weekend,
of course.
You're not sleeping so early, are you?
I can't sleep even if I want to.
Since you can't sleep, come in.
This is the dress code
for our party today.
Pajamas.
Do people really hold such parties?
Don't you guys sleep?
We've been going to bed
before dawn for a month.
So we need to celebrate it, of course.
Is that worth celebrating?
Of course.
Aren't you going to
break your streak today?
Who cares? It's fun.
Are these all your friends?
Yeah, these are my best friends.
How energetic.
These are all people I met at the bar.
Zhang Sen.
His ancestors made Nv Er Hong
in Shaoxing.
He's amazing.
When he was 16,
he came to Shanghai alone
to learn mixology.
Pretty lady.
This is my neighbor.
This is my neighbor, Xia Guo.
Who?
It doesn't matter. Let's dance!
Okay.
- Cheers.
Here's to Xia Guo!
Cheers!
Did you get your heart broken?
Look at you.
I know what's going on
without you telling me.
Long-distance relationships
are sad, nerve-racking and don't work.
No, we're just contacting lesser.
So I think it's pointless.
So become a career woman
and work on your career.
It's not that easy to be a career woman.
They're very lonely.
It sounds like your love life and career
aren't doing well.
How do you know?
I just want to say
you don't have to be
so hard on yourself.
You know that?
Your bullies
are enjoying themselves.
Why are you so hard
on yourself?
You'll have to make a choice, right?
You can't just
go with the flow.
Let me tell you a solution.
You can use it later
when you have to make a choice.
Do you want it? Here.
What?
Look.
You see that guy down there?
Once he finishes his call,
you'll choose option A
if he goes to the left.
If he goes to the right, it's option B.
What do you think?
Is that just going with the flow?
Don't get discouraged. Try it.
Figure out the option you want
and close your eyes.
Close them.
When you open your eyes
and find the option
to be what you want,
you'll be happy.
But if the result
is different from what you want,
you may be disappointed
and even frustrated.
But that frustration
will also remind you
what you really want.
And you'll also know what to do.
(Each of us makes a choice)
(about A or B every day.)
(Just like what Allen said,)
(no matter what you choose,)
(it's probably not too bad.)
(But it's not that great either.)
- (Everything's possible.)
- Three.
- (Will life allow us)
- Two.
- (to play games once in a while?)
- One.
(Resignation Application)
What's going on?
Why are you resigning all of a sudden?
Mr. Wu.
I think the only way
to give myself a good rest is to resign.
I believe
you can find
someone more qualified
to be the director.
Xia Guo, do you
have some misunderstanding?
What I said to you earlier
was out of concern for you.
I don't intend for you to leave.
I understand.
But I think you have a point.
I really need to make some adjustments
in my life and work
and think about my future.
You're so determined.
It seems there's no way
I can change your mind.
Thank you for helping me
make this decision.
Okay, I respect your decision.
All the best.
(Xue Yuming)
(I don't want to go on like this.
Let's break up.)
(When we figure out what to do next,)
(we can say goodbye to the past.)
(I've decided for now.)
(Where's my next choice?)
(I don't want to go on like this.)
(Thinking about it this way,)
(life is full of)
(new opportunities and challenges.)
(I don't want to go on like this.)
(Let's break up.)
(Block)
(Crossroads Bar)
Try this glass of Midsummer Fruit.
I modified it a little.
It's not to your taste again?
I'm just thinking
it's a shame this drink
isn't the bar's signature.
Forget about it.
This
may be the last drink
I make you in this bar.
The owner
is selling the bar.
I heard about it. What about you?
What is your next step?
My next step...
is to freeload meals
off you for a while.
Are you scared?
Sure, you can freeload meals off me.
And I'll pay you a salary.
Are you drunk after taking a few sips?
I'm thinking of taking over this place.
The man downstairs walked in
exactly the direction I wanted.
So I quit my job
and broke up with my boyfriend.
I want to say goodbye
and take on new opportunities.
Let's partner up.
I'll invest, while you do the work.
You're not trying to make me
your sugar baby, are you?
I don't do such things.
Get lost.
No, didn't I just give you
a few free drinks?
You're not really
interested in me, are you?
I'm serious.
Forget it if you don't want it.
You won't have another chance like this.
I want it.
I can work for you.
But
I want to officially become
a shareholder when we make money.
You're farsighted.
Okay, you can do whatever you want.
Okay.
Let's celebrate.
Resignation and breakup.
Two happy occasions.
Happy?
Fight fire with fire.
Two wrongs make one right.
Okay. Happy.
(Crossroads)
Let's start
by welcoming our new employees.
I'm really glad
to have you join our team.
I hope you can learn more
from our old staff in the next few days.
Whether it's the delivery speed
or the service quality,
I hope you'll all learn something.
But we're not the only ones
learning from you.
You're also learning from us.
We're gonna learn from you too, right?
So I hope we can progress together
and make our bar better.
An extra portion would be good enough.
You've been coughing for days.
You should check it out at the hospital.
It's okay. It just keeps recurring.
No need to go to the hospital.
Take a break. Take a sip of water.
Thank you.
You're burning.
It's your hand that's cold.
Have you sent the invitations?
What invitations? I'll send them
after you go to the hospital.
No, we're about to open up for business.
- I still have...
- Go to the hospital.
What are you doing? Put me down.
What are you doing?
It's still not finished.
What time is it?
Stop asking. Continue sleeping.
I feel much better already.
Your fever is almost 40 degrees.
Can you heal so fast?
Look at you.
You'll make money
but you won't be able to enjoy it.
You don't have to challenge me.
Since I decide to do something,
I must do it well.
I support you in doing it well.
I support you to do it tomorrow.
But tonight...
Just tonight.
I beg you to get some rest, okay?
Fine.
Go to sleep.
How about you and I be together?
We can eat together,
drink together, club together,
and do all the things we've never done.
Okay?
Xia Guo.
I'm talking to you.
Don't pretend to sleep.
You're pretending to sleep.
Xia Guo's exclusive red packet
has arrived.
I wish you all the best.
Good luck.
You didn't show up
for the opening the other day.
Since you gave me
a red packet,
I'll forgive you.
I really couldn't come back.
I wanted to come.
What's wrong? You can't act freely
after marrying into a rich family?
Don't talk about it. It's a long story.
Here. Please enjoy.
- Thank you.
- Here. Try it.
What do you think?
The drink's good.
The bartender's better.
- Allen.
- Coming.
I'll head over first.
Have fun.
Watch your words. You scared him.
He's a kid.
Kid?
He's already an adult, okay?
And can't you tell he likes you?
Don't you want to give it a try?
Try?
He's my business partner.
So what if he's your business partner?
Guo, look how good
you are now.
What happened to you and Mr. Xue?
He went to Singapore.
Are you sure you're not going with him?
I wanted to go,
but he...
He won't let you go?
He was hesitant.
He just can't give me
a clear answer.
All I really wanted was a word from him,
but he won't give it to me.
Guo, why don't you start
by dating long distance?
No.
I can't stand the uncertainty anymore.
When I came to Shanghai,
I didn't think
I'll split up with Yu Jian.
But it still happened.
I don't want to repeat the same mistake.
It doesn't matter, Guo.
I figured it out anyway.
The most important thing
is to depend on yourself.
And you must find
someone who really likes you.
Look how many wrinkles I've got
since I got married.
I even have eyebags now.
Thank you for your support.
I'll drink first.
You can do whatever you want, okay?
Okay, okay.
Come on.
Thank you.
Guo, he's a good guy.
He's motivated, hardworking,
funny and handsome.
Most importantly,
he only has eyes for you.
His eyes light up whenever he sees you.
I'm so jealous.
How can you get excited about anything?
Of course.
You just have to remember
the most important thing for a woman
is to find someone
who only love her and make her happy.
Guo, I really hope
you can be happy.
So whatever choice you make,
I'll support you.
You have to be brave.
Okay, be brave.
Here. Cheers.
Cheers.
Are you being a free driver again?
It's called additional service.
Come on.
♪Our eyes met♪
♪The bridge to happiness♪
♪The world is too small♪
♪It's all your smiles♪
♪Beating pulse♪
♪You're the light in my eyes♪
♪Warm poetic sun♪
♪The past hidden in my heart♪
♪Open in full bloom♪
♪You're the light in my eyes♪
♪My sunshine♪
Thank you.
Settling accounts again?
I had a look.
Our revenue this month
is about what I expected.
Isn't it New Year's and Christmas soon?
We need to increase our budget.
Everything is about
vibes and sense of occasion these days.
We can't lose.
And we can make more money.
I'm not that interested in making money.
What are you interested in then?
You.
Didn't you hear everything
I said in the hospital?
I...
You're pretending you can't remember,
aren't you?
Let me say it again.
No, no, no.
Don't scare me.
Don't joke like that with me.
Joke?
You're a woman, and I'm a man.
We're over 18 and single.
Why can't we be together?
Yes, you're over 18, but...
You're too young.
I'm young, but you've never given it a try.
How do you know it won't work?
I...
Let me put it this way.
I don't think
I'm at my best right now.
I'm still working on a lot of things.
I can't take action
without thinking about the consequences.
I can't make decisions
as easily as you do.
Do you understand?
Decision-making again.
Is it that hard?
I don't know how to explain it.
It's just that...
Look at them.
Look. Look at the couple over there.
No matter what happened to them
yesterday or tomorrow,
they're happy today.
Right?
Let's make another bet.
Are you addicted?
Another bet?
You're the one
who's afraid to make a decision.
That's why we're leaving it to fate.
Look over there. Look.
If the guy raises his glass first,
you'll become my girlfriend today.
If the girl raises her glass first,
you're still my boss tomorrow, okay?
Allen, this is...
Don't interrupt. Look, look.
Look.
Waiter, get me the bill.
Here's your bill.
It's destined.
Enough. Is making money a bad thing?
Don't overthink it.
Happy New Year!
Aren't you taking
today's high-speed train home?
It was canceled.
I can't go home now.
I'm here to freeload
a New Year's dinner from my boss.
I brought things.
I brought some food.
Come in.
You're making dumplings.
We have to eat dumplings
during the New Year.
Look at your dumplings.
Stop. Let me make the dumplings.
Have you washed your hands?
Wash them and disinfect them.
Hurry.
Disinfect and wash my hands.
Wait for me. Stop making dumplings.
Alright, no more drinks after this.
No, I...
Here's to you.
I hope you won't
stress yourself out so much
this year, okay?
Alright, no more drinks.
Let me send you home. Come on.
Guo, I like you.
You're drunk.
Do you like me?
Allen, we're not right for each other.
How about this?
I was very clear with you.
We can only be friends.
Nothing else.
I'll just assume you're drunk today.
Make way.
I can't accept it.
If you do that again, go home.
Don't ever find me again.
I'm sorry.
Allen.
I'm being serious with you.
I really, really want you to be happy.
But I'm not the one
who can make you happy.
Got it?
I hope
this new year goes well for you.
I also hope I can make you happier
in this new year.
(Allen, thank you for appearing)
(in these troubled times)
(and stagnant life.)
(Your appearance)
(brings me to peace)
(and let me)
(know myself better.)
(I hope my presence)
(gives you strength too.)
(I hope we can)
(get better in this new year.)
(Crossroads)
(Notice of Opening Delay)
I'm so sorry.
I know you didn't go home
for Chinese New Year
just so the bar could open for business.
But with the way things are going,
I don't know when we're gonna reopen.
So I'm gonna pay everyone
another month's salary and...
You don't have to
come to work anymore tomorrow.
Boss.
Look. We didn't even go home
for Chinese New Year,
waiting to open for business.
We've been eating and using
everything here.
We even took a month's pay for nothing.
If we take this severance now,
we'll feel bad about it.
- Yes.
- Yeah.
Besides,
everything outside is closed now.
Where can we find new jobs?
Yes.
We might as well stay here, right?
Yeah, Boss. Don't make us leave.
Let us stay.
Don't make us leave.
But I can't afford
to pay your salaries anymore.
I can't let everyone work for free.
It's fine, Boss.
I saved up some money. Don't worry.
I'm willing to wait without a salary.
Yes, we don't want you to pay us.
We're all willing to wait.
We're willing to wait.
- Don't worry, Boss.
- The pandemic will pass, Boss.
(Fisher: Boss, do you make
simple meals for food delivery?)
(I'll send you the address if you do.)
Thank you.
I think we're saved.
We're saved.
Calm down first.
Go back to your posts and get ready.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Let's go. We're saved. Hurry.
(Xia Guo: We can make and deliver them.
What would you like to order?)
I'm a hit.
I'm telling you.
Why didn't I find
live streaming so fun before?
You're having fun.
But can your fans
patronize our shop?
Can they give us business?
They can't, right?
This is a message from a customer.
Why didn't I think of
doing food delivery before?
Yeah, people can only order takeout now.
Wouldn't we make money
by making simple meals?
Yeah.
(Fisher: Fried chicken,
salad, and fries.)
Someone ordered.
There is always a way out.
As long as a customer needs us,
we can keep this place open.
Here. I'll contact
the food delivery platform
to start a takeout business.
Any business counts.
I'll handle the recipe.
Leave the menu to me.
Here. 53 and 54 are ready.
This is a cocktail
that I'm going to recommend you.
I'm recommending this one
because the liquor it uses
is common in the market.
Tequila, rum, vodka and whiskey
are easy to find.
You can easily make them at home.
I'm going to talk a little more
about the amount of each liquor.
(Mr. Fisher:
7th order. Shenghua Apartment.)
(Allen)
(Watch my live stream.)
Do you remember
the name of this cocktail?
Yes. It's called Xia Guo.
I saw someone ask
why it's called Xia Guo.
(The color's pretty.)
Good question.
(It looks good.)
Because Xia Guo is my only goddess.
Today is my goddess' birthday.
I hope my friends, fans, and buddies
watching the live stream
will comment
"Happy birthday, Xia Guo." Okay?
Here. Three, two, one.
(That's a nice name.)
Xia Guo, happy birthday!
(Looks good.)
I hope you're happy today, tomorrow
and the day after tomorrow.
(I'd like to have a glass.)
I hope you're happy every day.
I hope every day is like your birthday.
I hope I could always be there for you
and be your bartender.
No more worries on making money,
or on anything else.
I hope we can live happily together.
Okay?
(It must be good.)
Xia Guo, happy birthday!
(Xia Guo, happy birthday.)
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
You have such a flair
for food and drinks.
Have you ever thought
about opening a restaurant?
Not everyone can enjoy
my cooking.
You have to learn to serve the people.
Look.
The restaurants are reopening.
But bars are off-limits yet.
Making simple meals alone
is too monotonous.
It's not a long-term solution.
Do you think we should
get a bigger place?
One that's suitable for a restaurant.
Let's open a restaurant.
Look at all these
office buildings around us.
Lunch is in high demand
among white-collar staff
returning to work.
Besides, rents and tax points are low
during the pandemic.
We can make it work.
But no one goes to restaurants now.
Who's going?
If no one comes,
we can do food deliveries.
How did our bar survive?
Isn't it by doing food deliveries?
We can do some good advertising.
It will work.
Haven't you ever heard of a saying?
Live fish swim upstream.
Are you swimming upstream or impulsive?
There's no way to cover
the cost of food deliveries.
You know that.
Allen.
There is no shortage of clever people.
What's missing are people
who work hard and take risks.
All success doesn't fall from the sky.
I won't listen to those principles.
Seriously, I think you should check out
the stores without
regular opening hours.
They open
whenever they want.
Aren't they doing well?
I think that's the life
we should be pursuing.
Let me ask you.
Do you have a plan for the future?
Why should I think of the future?
I think the most important thing
is not to trap yourself in this place.
We should do something awesome
and meaningful.
Why don't we drive to Xizang?
And then what?
And then?
Why think so far ahead?
Can't you think about it
when the time comes?
Allen.
Since we chose to start a business,
we need to have a sense of crisis.
We have to think big and look far.
We can't miss any chances.
But it's not a good time
to start a business.
Why are you so hard on yourself?
Guo, did you say these
because you don't want to be with me?
Why are you mixing relationships
with work?
Don't come to work tomorrow
if you keep talking like that.
Fine.
You're right.
There's a big difference
on our values.
Ms. Xia, this is your pub.
You can do whatever you want.
It has nothing to do with me.
I'm officially requesting for leave.
(One day,)
(when you can calmly face
life's sudden changes,)
(it means)
(you know what you really want.)
(Does that count as growth?)
(My heart is as calm as water.)
(as if it can no longer feel excited.)
(I even miss the excitement.)
(Dear other me,)
(how's your life?)
(Is it still exciting?)
(Is it still passionate?)
♪The laid-back lights in the city♪
♪Warming the exhausted hearts♪
♪The familiar back I remember♪
♪Let's embrace now♪
♪There's no need to make a choice♪
♪I just wanna spend my life with you♪
♪A wonderful life is a simple song♪
♪In my heart♪
♪I wanna be with you♪
♪Are you also thinking of me♪
♪When you're elsewhere?♪
♪I wanna be with you♪
♪I yearn to tell you♪
♪How lonely this city is♪
♪I wanna be with you♪
♪Are you also thinking of me♪
♪When you're elsewhere?♪
♪I wanna be with you♪
♪I yearn to tell you♪
♪How lonely this city is♪
♪There's no need to make a choice♪
♪I just wanna spend my life with you♪
♪A wonderful life is a simple song♪
♪In my heart♪
♪I wanna be with you♪
♪Are you also thinking of me♪
♪When you're elsewhere?♪