=What If=
=Episode 16=
(Three Meals &amp; Four Seasons)
(The coldest moment of the year)
(is passing gradually.)
(I'm starting to feel
the warm embrace of spring.)
Here, give me a smile.
(Once you've been through
the worst moments,)
(everything will get better
in the future.)
(That's what I believe.)
♪I just want to spend my life with you♪
♪A wonderful life is a simple song♪
Raise your feet.
♪I wanna be with you♪
♪Are you also thinking of me♪
♪When you're elsewhere?♪
♪I wanna be with you♪
♪I yearn to tell you♪
♪How lonely this city is♪
♪There's no need to make a choice♪
♪I just want to spend my life with you♪
♪A wonderful life is a simple song♪
♪In my heart♪
♪I wanna be with you♪
Yan, what are you doing here?
Guo, is it convenient
for us to meet now?
Yeah, please come inside.
♪When you're elsewhere?♪
Guo,
I'm truly sorry.
It all happened
because of my willfulness.
That's why you had to...
Enough already.
Yan, don't bring it up.
It's all in the past now.
I don't blame you for it.
I'll be honest with you.
I feel terrible when I see the situation
between you and Jian.
Now that I think about it,
I know you felt desperate back then.
After all, two lives were at stake.
But Jian saw blood
all over the floor in my room.
I'm sure he panicked.
That's why he couldn't tend to you.
I know that.
Chen.
Look at who's here. It's your aunt.
Say hi to your aunt.
Say hello to her.
He's tiny.
Do you want to carry him?
You can give it a try.
You must be happy
that your aunt is carrying you.
Chen is such a good boy.
He's smiling.
Are you happy?
He's a good boy.
He can already sleep soundly now.
And, he doesn't cause trouble
late at night either.
That's great. He's so cute.
Your aunt is praising you. Look at her.
Here, Chen.
Here's a gift from your aunt.
In the future, I'll spend
all my money on you, okay?
You're thanking her, huh?
I'll get you a gold chain in the future.
Yan,
you'll have a child too.
Wait for me to finish
the divorce case in the U.S.
After that, I'll finish
my postgraduate studies.
I can lead a good life
even when I'm alone.
Okay.
Everything will get better.
Look, he's staring at you.
Why the rush?
Your blood pressure will rise
due to this, you know?
The child will come back eventually.
He's back.
I'll heat your meal.
I already had dinner with my colleagues.
I thought Guo allowed you
to go back to her house.
You're triggering him again.
You're something else.
You should've told us
that you weren't having dinner
with us tonight.
My phone's battery was flat.
No wonder.
Yan called us and told us
that his phone was switched off.
Your sister wanted me to tell you
that the divorce case was over.
She found a unit
together with her coursemate
near the academy.
She said it was a safe place.
That's great.
Her troubles are finally over.
What about you?
My first grandson will celebrate
his one-month birthday tomorrow.
Do you expect Guo to live there
together with Chen forever?
I can't just abduct them, right?
Why did I give birth
to a useless son like you?
Didn't you watch videos of him?
That's different.
We want to see the real deal.
We want the real baby!
The real baby.
I'm talking to you. Did you hear me?
In-law, long time no see.
We're here to visit them.
Mom, we're here to visit Guo and Chen.
Let me see. You're making
this sweater for Chen, right?
It's cute. It's white and clean.
I know how to do this too. Let me do it.
It's fine, Mom. You don't need to.
It's no trouble.
Mom, aren't you here
to visit Guo and Chen?
Why are you knitting a sweater?
You see,
I'm not just here to visit Chen.
I'm here to visit Guo too.
You can have Chen's sweater.
Guo, let me take a good look at you.
You look healthy.
You look like your body
has recovered considerably.
Your recovery is going well.
Mom,
Chen is sleeping. The maternity nurse
is taking care of him.
That's good.
It's good for him to sleep more.
Mom, Guo,
my mother and I are here
to discuss something with you two.
We hope that you and Chen could
go back and live with us for a few days.
The confinement period is finally over.
That's why we're here to visit Guo
and my eldest grandson.
Don't you think it's time for you
to leave after seeing the child?
In-law, why the rush?
It's rare for us to visit you.
I brought Yu Jian here
so that he could
apologize to Guo in person.
Mom, Yu Jian already apologized to me.
But you haven't forgiven him.
If you don't forgive him,
I'll kick him out of the house, then.
Enough.
Stop trying to push everything to Guo.
To be honest with you,
we made Guo spend
her confinement period here
because you had
to take care of your daughter.
How could you tend to
a wife who just gave birth
and a new baby at the same time?
You're right.
Miss, the baby is awake.
He's awake. Let me carry him.
Mom is here.
Chen.
You're awake.
He's awake.
Did you sleep well?
Guo,
can you let Mom carry him?
Chen.
I finally saw you in real life.
Am I right?
Did you see Grandma? I'm over here.
You saw me, right?
Grandma is over here.
You don't know who I am, right?
Guo,
his eyes and nose resemble yours.
Look. He has big and beautiful eyes.
He'll be gorgeous in the future.
You'll be a handsome guy
in the future, right?
Yeah. Grandma does miss you.
You still don't know me, huh?
Guo,
may we speak in private?
Come inside.
Look at my precious baby.
I'm your grandmother.
Why are you still standing there?
Pack these things up.
Guo,
have you stopped blaming me for it?
Blame you? For what?
Should I blame you for
carrying Yan to the hospital?
Or should I blame you for abandoning me?
I'm not blaming anyone for it.
Yan was in danger back then.
I'm sure you had to save her.
But I...
Dear, I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
It hurts so much.
Dear, it hurt so much back then.
I was terrified.
I know.
You don't.
The doctor said
we had to do a C-section
because the fetus lacked oxygen.
The fetus lacks oxygen.
The fetus is at risk of asphyxia.
We need to perform surgery
on you immediately.
Where's your family?
I came here alone.
But none of you were by my side.
I had no choice but to
sign the agreement myself.
I was afraid that
I might've died back then.
(Individual or Representative: Xia Guo)
Dear, it's all my fault.
Why don't you hit me, then?
You can inflict the pain
you felt to me, okay?
Come.
Does this hurt?
It was 10,000 times
more painful back then!
If so, you can pinch me 10,000 times.
This time, I promise
I won't make a sound. I swear.
You still have 9,996 times to go.
Does it hurt?
It doesn't.
Dear, you're finally smiling.
I truly know my fault now.
Dear, can we go home?
I can't live without you and Chen.
I haven't agreed to it yet.
I know you're not willing
to come to my house.
If so, can you let me stay?
Let me take care of you two, okay?
I don't agree.
Why do you object
to all of my decisions?
It's not that easy to raise a child.
The maternity nurse has left.
Yu Jian has to work every day.
What can he do to help you out?
He's just duping you.
At most, I can raise him myself.
What about your work?
Do you intend
to raise him all your life?
Chen will grow up, you know?
If it doesn't work out,
I can hire a nanny.
I already told you before.
Although Zhang Xiaoqin
isn't a great person,
she should be able to take care
of her grandson without any issues.
Just return
to your mother-in-law's house.
This way, you can spare yourself
from all the trouble.
You're just reluctant to
part with that rental income of yours.
I'll pay you the rent.
Just like before.
I'll rent it from you, okay?
I don't want your money.
I just want you to move into her house.
Mom, it's not like
you didn't see for yourself
when I was giving birth.
She has so many people to take care of.
She won't be able to cope with it.
Instead of relying on other people,
I would rather rely on myself.
Isn't that what you always advocated?
Now, I have decided to rely on myself.
Fine.
Anyway, it's your choice.
I'll stay out of your life
in the future.
Mom, we're just worried
that you might be too tired.
We want you to focus on Dad.
You do make it sound nice.
Guo is just blaming me for the incident.
No. I came up with the suggestion.
I'm sure she and her mother
forced you to relay the message.
If I must say,
she's a terrible mother-in-law.
She even wants you to pay her rent.
She's a grandmother now.
She wouldn't think about
something like that.
Besides,
even if it's paying her,
I'm willing to do so.
Right now, Guo's comfort is my priority.
Once Guo lives comfortably,
you can visit Chen from time to time,
am I right?
We can
also bring Chen back home
from time to time.
I understand now.
You're just saying that I'm not
good enough to raise my grandson.
How is that possible?
If I must say,
you see, in the end,
if both Guo and I have to work,
you'll have a valid reason
to help us take care of our child,
am I right?
You're taking things for granted,
aren't you?
We just want you and Dad
to enjoy your lives.
Fine. I'll stay at home
and enjoy my life.
Now,
your wife is making the call anyway.
Now that you have a wife,
you forget about your mother.
That's not true! Mom, that hurts!
I dare not forget about you.
- Happy New Year.
(Osmanthus Tower
Community Fitness Center)
Dad, Mom.
Our eldest grandson is back!
Call Grandpa and Grandma.
Come, Chen.
My baby grandson is back.
Look at Guo.
She did a great job
in raising our grandson.
Turn around and let me take a look!
Your mother has done
a great job here, am I right?
Dad, how's your recovery going?
I'm doing great.
I can throw these crutches away
in just a few more days.
You can carry him.
Forget it. He might
slip out of my hands.
Pass Chen to Guo.
Let's enjoy our reunion dinner.
Okay.
Did he poop?
It's time.
The diaper is here. Come.
Prepare some warm water for me.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- Let me change into the slippers.
He's upset now.
That's why he pooped.
We'll be done soon.
Look.
(This tiny and precious living being)
(brought two generations
of people together.)
(It showed me
the definition of a family.)
(There's food on the table,)
(flowers by the wall,)
(whispers of advice in my ears,
and warmth in one's embrace.)
(I started to hope)
(that the sunlight can turn warmer)
(and that our days can pass slower.)
Say, why did the main characters
have to play
this game of dare?
It's because they're cowards.
They don't dare
to confess to each other.
But doesn't that mean
they'll hurt each other?
Look at them.
In the end, they didn't get married.
Marriage might not necessarily
be the endpoint of a relationship.
You see, hurting people
might sometimes be
an expression of love too.
But they'll miss out on each other.
If so, they should
just leave it to time.
It's just like the message
behind the movie.
Time can prove everything.
Of course, time can decipher
the meaning of love too.
I don't think so.
I think
both parties should cherish each other
and hold on to every opportunity
when love is at its peak.
We shouldn't escape or be afraid.
It's because you have no way
of predicting what will happen next.
Isn't that the meaning of life?
You'll never know
what will happen tomorrow.
There'll be many surprises.
For example, you.
How could I have possibly
celebrate New Year's Eve with you
had you not come here from Leshan?
That's why I'm very happy.
New Year in Shanghai is pretty quiet.
There are no firecrackers at all.
Yeah.
It's very quiet.
Are you homesick now?
Not really. I just think
that I would be lonely
if I had to celebrate New Year
by myself here.
There's no ifs.
We were destined to meet each other.
Do you believe in destiny that much?
I do.
Even so, you can't just
believe in destiny for everything.
You at least need to have a goal.
After that, you need
to work hard to achieve it.
We need to do our best,
and leave it to God for the rest.
I'm talking about love.
You're talking about work.
One year passed by
in the blink of an eye.
I have to plan out my future somehow.
You're already very hardworking.
If you keep this up,
you'll suffer a breakdown.
Let's not talk about work, okay?
Staying in the same spot
is the same as deteriorating.
Who said so?
Me.
The Marketing Department
doesn't have a HOD yet.
I wish to give it a try.
You'll definitely be fine
with the job scope.
However, your qualifications
are a bit lacking.
You just need to
let things happen naturally
and wait for your opportunity.
Work isn't the only thing
that matters in life.
You have to enjoy your life too.
Just like me.
I enjoy the days I spend with you.
That's right.
If so, I wonder who's the person
who said the headhunters
would flood his phone with calls
after he resigned?
How many days has it been?
- Are you despising me now?
- That's not true.
- No, you're despising me.
- That's not it.
I can feel it.
A man like me was despised
by you right after losing my job.
I'm so pitiful.
You're a little pitiful.
If so, I have to work harder.
If not, I can't afford to support you.
And, I'll feel guilty if you just
let your career go downhill from this.
Alright now.
You don't need to feel guilty.
Charles already gave me
plenty of chances.
It's just that they didn't
meet my expectations.
We'll have plenty of opportunities
in the new year ahead.
Come. It's New Year's Eve.
May we have a lucky year.
That'll definitely come true.
♪The moon shines bright♪
Happy New Year.
♪Leading us♪
♪In this gentle night♪
♪And when we walk together♪
♪In this dreamy atmosphere♪
♪Like a mesmerizing spell♪
♪We can pull through♪
♪The night is ours♪
♪Just do as we please♪
Hurry!
♪I know you won't♪
♪Make me wait tonight♪
♪Cause I know♪
♪I know you won't make me♪
♪Wait for too long♪
♪Our hearts, beating fast♪
♪As we dance away♪
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Remember to prepare a red packet for me.
And, it must be a huge one.
Of course.
Have you booked the hotel
in Maldives, then?
Don't bring it up.
This Tim is putting me
in charge of everything.
I'm so tired.
Isn't it good for your husband
to listen to you in everything?
That's great.
If I must say,
we two do have an affinity
with each other.
Look. Our secret relationships
were discovered.
And, both turned out pretty well.
That's why you have to hurry too.
Guo, I have something to ask you.
Will you be terrified if Mr. Xue
doesn't want to marry you?
What's with the question?
Actually,
me and my colleagues
have discussed this before.
We think that Mr. Xue
should be a non-marriage advocate.
Think about it. He's an outstanding man.
Even so, he's unmarried at this age.
I can't think of a valid reason
except for the fact
that he fears marriage.
Just look at them.
In the end, they didn't
marry each other.
Marriage might not necessarily
be the endpoint of a relationship.
Actually,
sometimes, you need to force men to act.
Look at me. I succeeded, right?
Yeah, yeah. You're the smartest.
(Tim)
Hello? I'm outside.
I'm with Xia Guo.
What's there to worry about
when I'm with Guo?
Fine. I'll go back.
I'll go back right now, okay?
Guo, sorry about this. I have to go.
Go now.
Goodbye.
- Goodbye. Go now.
- Goodbye.
Let's keep in touch.
Goodbye.
What's wrong?
Did her words reach your heart?
Are you trying to use this
as a springboard again?
You see,
that bosom friend of yours
does have a point.
However, you don't need
to heed her words.
What kind of logic is that?
Your bosom friend's husband
is a good-for-nothing, right?
He's even putting your bosom friend
in charge of their wedding.
Even when she's out for a drink,
he called her back in a hurry.
He's irresponsible
yet has a strong sense of control.
In my opinion,
their marriage won't last long.
They'll get married soon, you know?
Don't jinx them.
I'm not jinxing them.
I just want to tell you
that you shouldn't heed
your bosom friend's advice
and force that bossy CEO
to make a stand.
Your bosom friend truly
wanted to help you out and support you.
However, she had no confidence
in her own marriage as well.
And, I realize women like you all
always have an inexplicable fear of men.
You guys also pay great attention
to your marriages.
If I must say,
when you're strong enough,
it doesn't matter if he fears marriage
or advocates non-marriage.
You're a kid, you know?
Where did you learn
all this nonsense from?
You're making me confused here.
You're confused, huh?
If so, I'll help you to sober up
with a drink.
Wait, you should stop hesitating.
Your conditions are literally impossible
to fulfill in a place like Shanghai.
Besides, the market
isn't doing well now.
It's hard for me to find
a great position like this
with a high salary.
And, it's one of
the top 500 companies in the world.
It's already good enough.
But the workplace is based in Singapore.
What's wrong with Singapore?
Isn't it good for you
to gather some experience overseas
at this stage?
You have leadership experience in
prominent domestic private enterprises
and is coupled with a background
in international corporate environments.
Brandon.
I think you shouldn't miss out
on this opportunity.
My girlfriend is in Shanghai.
I need to consider her feelings.
Wait, Xue Yuming.
Since when were you
tied to your relationship?
Are you worried that a long-distance
relationship between you and her
might make her upset?
It's more than just a long distance.
We're in different countries.
So what?
Are you sure you can maintain
this relationship
without a good job or wage?
How many women do you think
are able to truly share
wealth and woe with their men now?
If you say that out loud,
women will bash your head in.
I'm being realistic here.
It's already spring.
The number of staff for this position is
recruited from the Asia-Pacific region.
If you don't fight for it,
someone else might take it.
Once you miss out on it,
you might have to wait one year for it.
Do you truly wish to keep waiting?
What is this?
It's Lucy's wedding invitation.
She asked us when
we would book our flight tickets.
Oh, her wedding
will be held in Maldives.
Maldives, huh?
I was just going to tell you
that I might not be able to make it.
- You might not be able to make it?
- It's because I need to go to Singapore.
But why?
There's a summit over there.
They wish to invite
veterans of the industry
to be their guest speakers.
Charles knew that I was free lately.
He registered it for me.
I'll be paid for it.
I'm sorry. I can't
attend the wedding with you.
If you're not attending it,
I won't attend it either.
Come. Follow me.
Don't be angry, okay?
Let's give it a try first, okay?
Try it on.
You look gorgeous.
You do look gorgeous in it.
What should we do?
You're attending your friend's wedding,
but you'll steal the limelight from her.
Stop it.
Don't think that I won't be angry at you
just because you bought this for me.
You look gorgeous
even when you're angry.
Let's go and buy a wedding present
for your friend later, okay?
Thank you.
It's my pleasure to serve you.
Ms. Ping, you crossed the line.
You didn't tell me that you were coming.
I wanted to give you a surprise.
It's my fault. I rarely contact you.
Both of us are busy.
I can understand your feelings.
HQ is different indeed.
It's fast-paced,
and the pressure is tremendous.
I only finished an afternoon's lesson,
yet I'm all giddy.
Here, Ms. Ping.
May you become
the manager of our branch soon.
Hopefully that'll come true.
Didn't your husband say anything
about your trip here?
My family was in a messy state
for the past six months.
When you came back,
my husband's company went bankrupt.
He did nothing at home for two months.
My children are either busy with school
or busy crying their hearts out.
He finally understood
how tough it was for me back then.
Yeah. You complained about him
every day back then.
During crucial moments, your husband
is the most thoughtful person around.
You call that thoughtful?
It's just a change of role.
Now, he has empathy for me.
But to be honest,
I've readjusted
my state.
My husband found a new job.
He didn't need to go on business trips.
He could share
the family chores with me.
Now, I can be a workaholic again.
That's great.
If I must say, men and women
should share their burdens
with each other.
When technology advances further,
men might be able
to give birth to children too.
Society will be harmonious by then.
It's nice when
you think about it, right?
I was just joking.
Ms. Ping,
I'm truly happy for you.
Now that you're doing great in Shanghai,
I'm happy for you too.
Who said I'm doing great?
I'm sure you'll do a better job than me
if you came to Shanghai instead of me.
Shanghai's environment
is very stressful.
I don't think I can persevere.
Don't you think you have
to tell me something?
What is it?
Your legendary tales with Mr. Xue
were spread to Leshan long ago.
How is it?
When will you guys hold the wedding?
It's too early to say.
Yu Jian is going to have a child soon.
You should work harder.
You can do it.
I can do it.
Hello. What can I do for you?
We want to buy
a wedding present for our friend.
Okay. Over here, please.
This is our latest series.
What about this necklace?
It looks good.
You know her better than me.
May I take a look?
Of course.
It's pretty good.
It's white.
She has a fair complexion too.
I think this will do.
Really? We'll take it, then.
Okay. The latest series is over there.
Do you wish to take a look?
- I'll go and take a look.
- Okay.
Over here, please.
Over here is the Tiffany Classic Series.
These are our classic
Tiffany Wedding Ring Series.
So, this is the ring area?
Yeah. Miss, do you wish
to check out our diamond rings?
We've recently acquired
a batch of diamonds
with exceptional color and clarity.
The designs are classic too.
These are the best presents
for weddings and engagements.
I can show them to you guys.
It's fine. We're here to buy
a present for our friend.
Okay, mister.
Get me the bill.
This light is portable.
You can move it anywhere. Look.
The thing is, there's an app for it.
Once you connect it to your phone,
you can turn it on
even when you're not home yet.
Let me demonstrate.
I'll turn it on first.
Like this.
Now, I'll use the phone.
Let's get married.
Give me a second.
Oh no.
The bulb is fused.
They didn't even prepare a spare bulb.
I'll go and buy a new one.
Sorry. What did you say just now?
It's nothing.
(Li Qiuman is
inviting you to a voice call)
Hello, Migao?
Hi, Dad. Where are you?
I'm at Ms. Xia Guo's house.
Is Paris cold?
Yeah. Mom got me
some thicker clothing.
Is today your first day of school?
(I'm not trying to scare you here.
Mr. Xue has a child.)
(What if, I'm saying what if,)
he needs a lover
instead of a wife?
What will you do by then?
But I might be working.
You can come back.
I'll go and pick you up
when you're back, okay?
You're back.
Is Chen asleep?
What did you have for dinner?
I had dinner with my colleagues.
How was your interview today?
I didn't go. My mother was too busy.
[Take care of child,
send child to and pick up from school]
You're looking for a nanny already?
We have to hire one eventually.
That's why I'm checking it in advance.
Didn't we agree that we would hire a nanny
based on your expected salary
after you found a job?
A good nanny is hard to find.
If you don't search for them in advance,
you won't be able to hire one by then.
I heard that nannies are very costly.
Maybe your monthly salary
isn't as high as theirs.
What do you mean by that?
Are you telling me to stay at home
instead of working?
You see, it's tiring to work nowadays.
You have to stay outside. And...
So?
I've been home for too long.
I'll be detached from society
if I don't go out and work now.
Take your time, okay?
When I'm free, I'll do the interview
together with you.
I'll go and take a bath first.
Tang,
what's with the low dividend
this time around?
Yu Jian,
the company hasn't
been doing well lately.
I'm sure you know that too.
And, you were tending to your family
more often in the past year.
The company shared your burden with you.
I can't just let them work for nothing,
don't you agree?
What about this?
You should assign
all the required jobs to me next time.
I'll complete them no matter what.
I need to make a living here.
I understand.
You need a lot of money since
you just had a child.
Your wife isn't working
and you're the sole breadwinner now.
But you need time to take care
of your wife and child.
I don't want to tie you up
with our projects every day.
My child is growing. It'll be fine.
You don't need to work so hard.
This studio is yours, too.
We have plenty of time.
I'll make sure you receive
every single cent of the dividend once
you resume the normal work schedule.
But now, you need to help Guo
take care of your son.
That's your priority.
You can complete your projects
at home too, you know?
Are you short on cash?
If so, you must tell me.
Don't worry.
I'll seek your help if it's necessary.
Alright.
Mr. Han.
That's right.
What do you think about
the proposal I sent to you?
What do you mean?
Understood. That can be amended.
Yu Jian, long time no see.
I'll hold a housewarming party
for my new shop tomorrow.
You must attend it, okay?
Dear, have you turned into
a full-time housewife?
Hello.
Who are you?
I'm Nanny Qian.
Nanny?
Nanny.
- Coming.
- I think Chen peed himself.
Be careful.
Be careful. Support his head.
Okay.
Chen, let's change your diaper.
Guo.
Why did you hire a nanny this soon?
I have a lot of job interviews lately.
I went out often too.
You can't just apply for leave
every day, right?
Chen is still very young.
Can you rest at ease
if you entrust him to a stranger?
Besides, since he's our child,
we have to be responsible for him.
How am I being irresponsible?
Do you think I'm being responsible
by taking care of him
as a free nanny every day?
There you go again.
Who said you were a free nanny?
Just tell me directly
if you don't want me to go and work.
Stop beating around the bush.
Who said I was beating around the bush?
I'm doing this for
you and Chen's sake, you know?
Fine. Since you already hired a nanny,
I'll go to work now.
It's pretty lively in there.
Tang, I'll stay here for an hour, okay?
There are potential clients in there.
Wen Ya held this party
on purpose, you know?
We should stay here longer
when we have the chance.
- I need to look after my son.
- I know that.
Seniors.
Go inside.
Here, this is for you.
- Thank you.
- It's a present for you.
Go inside.
We're enjoying some games now.
Come on.
- Let's go inside.
- Okay.
- Come on.
I'll only stay here for a while.
Yeah, I know that.
Hurry up.
Let me introduce them to you.
These two
are the heroes behind my shop.
Tang Yiming and Yu Jian,
they're designers, quite famous.
Welcome.
She flatters us too much.
It was an group effort.
They are my seniors
from the same course.
You guys may look for them
if you require help
in designing or renovations.
You'll get the best service
with the most affordable price.
- Okay.
Yu Jian is my junior
and my studio partner.
He received a huge award
on the year he graduated.
He's amazing.
This is my name card.
Our company can handle
indoor decoration, outdoor design,
landscaping, even old house renovation.
Please take care of us.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Alright.
Please take care of us.
Yes. They're young and talented.
Let's resume the game.
- Okay.
- Alright.
The name of this game is "I Have Never."
Each of us will raise five fingers.
After that, we'll talk about the things
we never did before.
Those who did it before
will subtract one finger.
The person with
all five fingers subtracted
has to drink.
I know that game.
- I played it before.
- Come on, then.
Raise your hand.
I'll start first.
I have never gotten married before.
Me too.
We have no chance now.
Yu Jian,
since you're married,
you need to subtract one finger.
Like this?
He's married at such a young age?
What a shame.
It's fine. I'm still here.
Okay. Don't move now.
Give me a kick.
Okay.
It stinks.
I'm sure you feel better now.
I'll be done soon.
I'll drink on his behalf.
Wait.
I was the one who raised the issue.
Yu Jian, what are you doing here?
I drank too much.
I'm here to take a breather.
You can't hold your liquor well, right?
Why did you drink so much?
Everyone was in a happy mood.
I didn't want to spoil their mood.
It's been so long since we met as well.
How have you been?
Is your family doing okay?
They're doing fine.
I heard you've taken some
impressive design projects again.
They were even on the cover
of Home Living Magazine.
I knew I was right about you.
Since I took their money,
I have to provide them
with the best service.
You're a sincere person indeed.
Not beating around the bush at all.
Very nice indeed.
You're amazing yourself.
You already own two shops at this age.
You have a successful career.
It's because I found myself.
I'm trying to realize
the life I dream about.
Wen Ya, I want to know something.
What does it mean for a woman
to find herself and realize her dream?
Does it mean that you have to work?
I understand now.
Is Guo trying to work?
How do I put it?
Initially, I thought
that working for other people is tough
and that men should handle that.
Women can tend to their affairs at home.
It's important for her
to raise her child too.
You reap what you sow.
And, she can watch over
her children as they grow up.
Isn't it great?
In the end? She doesn't want that.
She insists in joining society
to suffer with the rest of us.
I didn't want her to suffer.
Do you know what she said? She said
I'm playing make-believe with her.
Let me ask you this, then.
How long has it been since
someone addressed Guo by her name?
I mean her full name.
I...
I never addressed her
by her full name before.
I guess I had when we argued.
If so, let me explain
what it means to be oneself.
It's when people address her,
she's not the daughter of someone,
someone's wife,
or someone's mother.
She's not an accessory.
It's herself.
With a complete name.
That's what we mean by being oneself.
People often address you
by your name directly at workplaces.
Therefore, getting a job
is the quickest way
to find oneself.
Wait.
Is it that important for people
to address you by your name?
Let me put it this way.
It's just like how
you chose your major back then.
Wasn't it because
you were passionate about
coming up with the greatest designs?
And, your designs
are connected to your name, right?
Isn't it like realizing one's dream?
That's right.
Just like how opening
a florist is my dream.
I'm very happy with it.
It doesn't feel tiring to me at all.
I'll be even happier
if I can make money with it.
I guess that's what Guo is thinking.
If that's the case,
that means it was my negligence.
Guo has her own dreams too.
Yu Jian, in my heart,
you're 100% a good husband.
(I've been home for too long.)
I'll be detached from society
if I don't go out and work now.
Just tell me directly
if you don't want me to go and work.
Stop beating around the bush.
That's not true.
I always make her angry.
Wen Ya, thank you.
I think
I sorted my issues out
after chatting with you.
You can come to me
if you need any help in the future.
Even if I can't help you out,
you can still confide in me.
♪The laid-back lights in the city♪
♪Warming the exhausted hearts♪
♪The familiar back I remember♪
♪Let's embrace now♪
♪There's no need to make a choice♪
♪I just wanna spend my life with you♪
♪A wonderful life is a simple song♪
♪In my heart♪
♪I wanna be with you♪
♪Are you also thinking of me♪
♪When you're elsewhere?♪
♪I wanna be with you♪
♪I yearn to tell you♪
♪How lonely this city is♪
♪I wanna be with you♪
♪Are you also thinking of me♪
♪When you're elsewhere?♪
♪I wanna be with you♪
♪I yearn to tell you♪
♪How lonely this city is♪
♪There's no need to make a choice♪
♪I just wanna spend my life with you♪
♪A wonderful life is a simple song♪
♪In my heart♪
♪I wanna be with you♪
♪Are you also thinking of me♪
♪When you're elsewhere?♪