(Sumiharu) 《Delicate and luxurious petals➡
Elegant gradation and confident appearance》
(Sumiharu) 《Peony invites the viewer to a dreamy feeling》
(Sumiharu) 《It's a moment of escapism》➡
"yes . Just a moment...》
(Sumiharu) 《Reality always slaps me on the cheek mercilessly》
(Sumiharu) 《Wake up》
Sweet scent... (Sumiharu) Huh?
♬～
Ah... Excuse me a little. ➡
Ah. (Sumiharu) Wait.
(Sumiharu) 《Reality》
That.
Could you please exchange contact information?
Huh?
I wish we could communicate directly instead of using an app.
Huh... Look, we both know our real names ➡
Don't you feel more intimate that way?
(Sumiharu) 《Yes. This person might just be 》➡
《It doesn't matter whether you cry or laugh》
But after all... (Sumiharu) Please enter your number.
Are you wary of me?
That's not the case though...
(Sumiharu) 《Standard sentences are enough for conversation》
(tap sound)
yes .
(mobile phone)
thank you . I'll contact you again.
Well then.
(Sumiharu) 《Rubbish》➡
《Hopelessly barren and worthless》➡
《My reality》
(Sumiharu) Huh... (Sound of pressing a switch)
Sumiharu Welcome back.
Have you been waiting for this long? (Lina) Yeah.
(Sound of putting down smartphone)
Sumiharu: Something smells good. ➡
perfume?
Flowers?
Hey, why?
It's work.
Really?
Fufufu…. Was it annoying? joke .
Haven't you eaten yet? I'll make something.
There's no need to worry.
Sumiharu...
(Sumiharu) 《Is this also a fixed phrase? I don't know my true feelings》➡
《Already... forever》
I'll make it right away.
(Sumiharu) 《Maybe... from that day》
♬～
(sniffing sound)
I won't.
(mobile phone)
Ha... Ah!
(Aoi) Yuko: I'm really sorry. (Yuko) It's totally fine.
Let's have a toast. (Aoi) Yeah. thank you .
Good.
But I can't believe I forgot my birthday promise➡
what happened? Did something happen?
Ah... .
Aoi?
Actually... I met that person.
That person...
Today, I suddenly received a call saying that they wanted to meet again.
(Yuko) Huh! ?
So... (Yuko) That's it! ?
After all, just like Yuko says➡
I think it's best not to pursue it too deeply.
Huh? (Aoi) Something➡
My name and phone number were revealed.
Well, we're mutual, though. that's why… .
Mutual-sama! ? (Aoi) Yeah.
Aoi: Did you hear his real name?
Yeah . Ah, that's my last name... Ah, I just happened to know it.
Well, um... .
(tap sound)
"Subaru"... ➡
Subaru... Subaru...
I wonder what kind of character it is...
here we go .
(Yuko) It's frustrating...
Yuko?
I don't know anything about him.
I can't believe I fell in love with him without even knowing his real name...
Aoi. I just can't give up like this.
Huh?
Could you please continue a little longer?
No, but... (Yuko) Please!
Know the truth and accept it➡
So I want to move forward.
Aoi!
Got it. (Yuko) Really?
Only once. I'll see you just one more time. ➡
So, let's get the evidence and call it a day!
Fufufu…. thank you .
Aoi Thank you so much! (Aoi) Yeah.
(Ryuta) Doesn't it have a weak taste? I like it dark though.
That's why I can't have a girlfriend.
dressing? mayonnaise? ➡
Yeah .
Huh...
Sumiharu: How was it?
(Sumiharu) Huh? (Ryuta) The customer.
You met today, right? Is it likely to be taken?
Ah... .
(Ryuta) Huh? Was it weird?
It's rare for you to be so difficult. Are you okay?
I never thought I'd feel feelings for the old lady...
(Sumiharu) That can't be true. It's the same as other customers.
Are you okay . I'll drop it next time.
(Aoi) I'm really sorry. I'll make up for today soon.
(Yuko) Yeah. I'm looking forward to it. (Aoi) Yeah.
But it might not be possible for a while. (Aoi) Why?
Actually, I decided to work at night as well.
Huh? (Yuko) Only a part-time job at a cleaning shop➡
Honestly, money is tight. (Aoi) Night?
Snack. (Aoi) Snack! ?
No, it's okay! Because it was an introduction from a part-time friend.
It seems like a shop with a homely feel.
(Aoi) Yeah.
See you then. (Aoi) Yeah.
Ah...! already!
(Sumiharu) 《Maybe it's just the same as the others》➡
《Nevertheless》
It's like a person.
You always look sad though.
(Sumiharu) Huh...
(Doctor) Well, the last time you came was eight years ago? ➡
It's been quite a while.
(Aoi) Sorry. (Doctor) That➡
What was the situation when you felt the scent of flowers for a moment?
(Aoi) Someone gave me a flower called a peony.
(Doctor) I see. ➡
In cases of psychogenic olfactory dysfunction like Mr. Ichinose➡
Connected with memories and emotions➡
Sometimes smells remind me.
Memories and emotions?
But, sir, I just met that person➡
I don't know him well, though.
(Doctor) In that case➡
Maybe you didn't actually smell it.
Does that mean it's my imagination?
If only once. ➡
Depending on whether the same thing happens repeatedly➡
Judgment will change.
(Sound of door opening) (Nurse) Please take care of yourself.
Ah, thank you very much.
(sound of door closing)
(Sumiharu) 《Damage of property...? 》 (Police Officer) 《The other party is➡
I'm willing to settle the matter...] (Shintani) "How much do you need? 》
(Sumiharu) 《1 million yen…》 (Shintani) 《Within two weeks➡
Please sell me 3 million. If you can't do it, it's your neck.
《Please try to live as hard as you can》
《Ah! 》 《Don't let anyone who has nothing to do with it say anything》
(sound of trampling on a bouquet)
⚟ (Shintani) It's noisy.
Huh?
(Shintani) It's inside Higuchi's head.
It's full of noise.
(Shintani) Being lost means ➡
That's what people with a choice do.
Hey.
(Ryuta) Hey, Sumiharu.
(Sumiharu) Huh? (Ryuta) He's coming.
that… . (Masumi) Oh?
ah . Ha. I got a new job. ➡
I was really asked to do it.
That's why I'm busy too. What? Speak briefly.
⚟ (Lina) What are you doing? You.
(Ryuta) You shouldn't just come in without permission.
Is someone coming? (Ryuta) He's Sumiharu's father.
(Rina) Huh! ? (Ryuta) Shhh! ➡
Whoa...
(Masumi) I forgive you. (Sumiharu) Huh?
I can't say it's a very wise choice, but I can't help it.
I'll forgive you just this time.
You can just pay the settlement fee or whatever.
If that makes you feel good, do whatever you like.
That's why I don't pay the monthly fee➡
That's different. I won't allow it. Pay as usual.
This month's child support is still due.
I don't have that kind of money... (Masumi) No good. ➡
Once you allow something like this, it becomes a habit.
Pay it.
How much do you think it cost to raise him?
Huh...
This is all I have now.
Is it true?
Pathetic.
Even though I had worked so hard to raise her, why was she like this?
This is not the time to buy flowers for a woman!
(Sumiharu) Woman? (Masumi) It's that woman. ➡
We ran away holding hands. Tsk.
Who is it? What kind of relationship is that?
It's a customer.
Just a customer.
(cough)
I'm suffocating because of you.
(Masumi) Anyway, do it quickly and properly. ➡
Get out of this shabby house!
You can't stay with these guys forever!
(Lina) Ha! ? (Ryuta) Rina.
Tsk.
(Sound of door opening) (Lina) Huh...
(sound of door closing)
(Rina) Hey, what's that? Is that really Sumiharu's father?
(Ryuta) Hey. (Rina) Why are you giving me money? ➡
I wish I could cut off my father like that!
(Ryuta) Stop it.
(Sumiharu) It's my fault.
(Sound of refrigerator door closing) (Lina) Huh?
No... (Lina) What do you mean?
(Ryuta) Huh... (Rina) Hey, Ryuta.
It's tough for even Sumiharu to see a dad like that.
Huh? (Ryuta) It's like that now➡
I used to run a pretty big company➡
He was a cool, cool guy. ➡
There were times when it was really tough to make Sumiharu the heir.➡
Are you passionate about education? ➡
That mom passed away too early➡
I feel like my uncle is doing his best. ➡
But when I was in high school, I think we had some trouble about my career path...
⚟ (Sound of bicycle bell) (Male) You're in the way!
(Ryuta) From then on, things got more and more strange...
(Masumi) Noisy idiot. Tsk.
(Ryuta) In the end, the company went bankrupt.
(Rina) Is that because of Sumiharu?
(Ryuta) Hmm... no... I don't really understand either➡
That's what he seems to think. ➡
Huh…. (Rina) Huh...
♬～
(Sumiharu) 《Because I had a dream》
(Sumiharu) I will not inherit the company.
I won't live like my father.
(Sumiharu) What are you doing! (falling sound)
Look at the reality!
(Sumiharu) 《So my father...》➡
《The reality I invited》
(Sumiharu)《This is not the time to be lost》➡
《This is the only way I can live》
♬～
(mobile phone)
(Sound of putting dishes down)
(Doctor) 《It depends on whether the same thing happens repeatedly➡
Judgment will change》
(Mobile phone) (Vibrator sound)
(Yuko) “First time at work tonight” ➡
"I'm going!" (Aoi) Huh...
Are you going to work tonight? (Aoi) Wow!
No, I was already surprised! Don't be surprised.
what? Yuko-chan, are you starting your night job?
Do you have free time? (Okuda) I have some free time.
I came here to look for materials. (Aoi) Oh yeah.
Then, hurry up and look for it. (Okuda) I'll look for it.
Yes, please look for it.
Are you worried? About Yuko-chan.
(Aoi) Does it look like that?
Is it different?
I'm the worst.
Even though you say you're doing it for Yuko, you're thinking about yourself.
《Sweet scent...》
Maybe.
(Okuda) Huh? What do you mean?
Ah, sorry. That's fine. It's nothing.
(Okuda) Does that mean hurting someone?
Huh? (Okuda) That's your criteria for judgment.
As far as I know.
(Okuda) Huh? (Aoi) Isn't there something different about the character?
(Okuda) Huh?
Huh...
♬～
(Aoi) "I'll meet you now."
⚟ (Mom) Yuko-chan. Please join me at the table.
Ah... yes.
(Yuko) Good evening. Nice to meet you. I'm Yuko. ➡
Today is my first time.
Um... (Iwamura) Yuko Sagawa?
Huh? (Iwamura) That's right... ➡
It's Yuko Sagawa! Oh, right! ?
that…? (Iwamura) Oh, good. That's it➡
Sit, sit, sit. Fufufufufu….
Excuse me. (Iwamura) Ah, me➡
Kengo Iwamura, who I went to junior high school with. Hmm... the brass band!
Ah! Hahaha... Iwamura-kun... Fufufufufu….
Ah... don't you remember?
That's right.
I was a secret girl, and Yuko was the idol of my school year.
That kind of thing... (Iwamura) No, really!
All the boys said they liked Yuko-chan. ➡
Yuko is in the school trip photos➡
It was a competitive battle.
No! Stop it too! Such a long time ago.
It's embarrassing.
Now she's just a tired old lady.
Huh? Eh, where! ? (Yuko) Huh?
It hasn't changed at all from back then!
With Yuko-chan, who I admired. Fufufufu….
Ah... thank you .
Hehehe. (Iwamura) Hehe.
⚟ (Aoi) Subaru-kun.
Thank you .
Ah... Thank you .
(Sumiharu) 《I will definitely drop this person today》
Ah... Um...
(Sumiharu) You gave me a key chain.
(Aoi) Yeah. Because it's cute.
surely . Cute.
(Sumiharu) 《Even with such flimsy words➡
Apparently it sounds true to the people who want it.
Subaru-kun... (Sumiharu) Huh?
She's cute when she smiles.
Let's go.
That➡
There's a place I'd like to visit, is that okay?
Huh?
do not… .
Aoi-san!
♬～
(Shopkeeper) Oh no! sorry!
Ah, a towel! towel towel.
Ah... I'm sorry.
Ah... Are you okay? (Sumiharu) Ah...
(Sound of dryer operating) (Shopkeeper) It's going to dry soon.
Oh no, it's really okay. (Dryer operating sound)
Huh? Ah, it's okay, it's okay! It's going to dry soon. Hehe.
Sorry...
Oh no, I'm sorry.
Due to my carelessness.
Flowers... (Aoi) Huh?
Did you want it?
Oh no, um... just a little.
Ah, that's right.
Can I ask you a question? (Sumiharu) Huh?
(Aoi) Look, I don't know much about Subaru-kun yet➡
I want to know.
(Sumiharu) 《Stop it》
No?
home . I also want to know about Aoi-san.
(Sumiharu) 《There's nothing about you I don't want to know》
What kind of thing?
Ah, what is that?
Huh?
This is the silver one I found.
Ah ah... Hehe.
this? (Sumiharu) That's it.
An atomizer is a container used to carry perfume.
perfume.
(Aoi) It's an important thing that my best friend gave me.
Hey.
Next it's my turn.
How do you write Subaru?
Huh?
Kanji name.
Oh...don't you want to answer?
Oh no.
The kanji ``sumiru'' in sanzui means ``sunny'' in weather.
vinegar… . Oh, wait a minute.
(Aoi) ``Clear'' and ``Hare''... ➡
this? (Sumiharu) That's right.
(Aoi) That's a beautiful name.
(Sumiharu) 《Why are you talking like this?》
Who put it on?
He's my father though...
There are no obstacles, and I feel like there's a bright future ahead. ➡
I guess that's what your father thought as well.
(Sumiharu) 《If that's the case, it's too ironic》
Huh.
Ah... So what about Aoi? (Aoi) Huh?
What kind of characters does Aoi-san write?
I am the summer flower ``Aoi''
flower? (Aoi) Yeah.
Characters like this.
(Sumiharu) Hey...
What kind of flower is it?
Huh? Ah, that's right...
Isn't it here?
Well, there are 5 petals➡
They spread out softly and overlap.
It feels round.
lend me . (Aoi) Huh?
after that?
after that… .
Ah.
Roughly speaking, this is it. It looks like morning glory.
Many blooms grow vertically on a single stem.
♬～
Like this?
Wow...
Was it wrong?
can't believe it . Why are you so good?
(Sumiharu) No, I just drew it randomly.
So nice...
(Sumiharu) 《What sounds true➡
Because those are the words I wanted? 》
(Mobile phone) (Vibrator sound)
(Mobile phone) (Ring tone)
(Mobile phone) (Vibrator sound) (Sumiharu) 《Reality》
If you don't go soon, you'll be late.
Ah yes. (Sumiharu) Sorry.
No?
Huh.
(Aoi) Is this a gallery or something?
(Sumiharu) Yes. I actually work in the art field.
I see. That's right .
I thought Aoi would definitely like it➡
I wanted to come with you. (Aoi) Ah... yeah.
I'll bring that. ➡
I have a picture that I prepared for Aoi-san.
Ah yes. (Sumiharu) Please wait a moment.
(footsteps)
(Ryuta) Um... (Aoi) Ah...
(Ryuta) Huh? (Sumiharu) Sorry to have kept you waiting.
♬～
(Sumiharu) Just a little bit.
(Speaker) (Operation sound) (Speaker) (Aoi) Subaru-kun. Thank you .
(Speaker) (Sumiharu) So you gave me a key chain.
(Speaker) (Aoi) Yeah. Because it's cute.
What is this? What do you mean?
What do you mean by that?
Huh? What are you talking about?
Who are you?
Yuko Sagawa. (Sumiharu) Huh?
Yuko Sagawa's friend that you deceived.
You cheated, right?
Tsk. Huh….
(speaker) (operation sound)
Go home.
(Aoi) I can't go home.
Give me my money back.
It was money that Yuko's father had left for her.
Yuko worked desperately to take care of her father➡
Important...
And yet you took advantage of Yuko...
Do you go out of your way to express such resentment?
It was a relief.
Your words, "I'm doing my best."
It became Yuko's hope.
A future with you.
My dream has finally come true... (Sumiharu) It's pathetic.
I can't affirm my life unless I cling to someone 20 years younger than me➡
What have you been doing up until now?
You've never lived desperately!
Desperate, desperate, what do you mean?
I'm living desperately, so what?
After all, if it's empty, there's no point in it, right?
Please tell your friends.
Look at the reality.
♬～
There's no point in remembering you.
Don't get involved in my life again.
(Ryuta) Hey! The customer from earlier...
(Shintani) Higucchi-kun.
(Sumiharu) Sorry. ➡
The customer started begging, saying he didn't have any money.
It was a hassle so I cut it.
I'll bring another customer.
There's no time.
(Sumiharu) 《Reality》
Huh... (Sumiharu) 《What is this reality?》
Huh... Hehe.
It's like a person.
(Sumiharu) 《The expressions she shows from time to time➡
Somehow I felt the same smell》
(Sumiharu) 《Nevertheless》
(slapping sound)
♬～
(mobile phone)
(Yuko) “How was it?”
Huh...
(Aoi) Yuko wants it back.
I was reflecting on it.
Sumiharu-kun? (Aoi) Yeah.
Really? (Aoi) Yeah.
Did you admit it? He said he was cheating on me.
He said he was sorry.
Huh... It seems like there's something wrong with that kid.
Organizing your feelings... It may be difficult right away ➡
But can we move forward now?
(Yuko) Yeah.
Proceed... ahead.
thank you .
Huh.
I'm home.
It's me.
My plans were suddenly canceled.
What about Sumiharu? (Ryuta) At work.
That guy is desperate.
♬～
⚟ (Female) Are you all able to draw good pictures?
(Children) Yes! (Female) Well, let me show you. ➡
Oh, that's amazing. The purple flowers are so beautiful. ➡
What about this one?
(Sumiharu) 《I will not inherit the company》
"I won't live like my father"
(Masumi) 《Wait. Sunny weather! 》
There's a place I want to go with Noriko-san.
(Noriko) Eh, where is it?
(Sumiharu) I think you'll definitely like it.
(Noriko) That's... for someone like me.
I like it. (Noriko) Huh?
An adult woman working hard.
I understand. Living desperately...
《Please try to live as hard as you can》
(Noriko) Huh? Mr. Suzuki?
(Sumiharu) 《Why do you talk about that woman...》
♬～
(Aoi) I guess it's no good after all. (Sound of placing a vase)
(Okuda) Eh, what are you doing? (Aoi) Wow. Have you come again?
No, you smell like flowers right now... you're an idol, after all.
It's noisy. (Okuda) Huh? What happened? What happened?
What are you imitating? (Aoi) It smelled.
Huh? (Aoi) Just for a moment the other day.
(Okuda) Does that mean you're probably getting better?
No, I don't know. There's no way to be sure.
No, is there something I can get away with without knowing?
Huh? (Okuda) Something➡
I don't know what the circumstances are ➡
How important is the scent of flowers to you?
I know. ➡
Is that so?
If there's even the slightest chance, hang on.
♬～
(Aoi) 《I like that picture》
《Lively➡
I can almost smell it➡
Because it reminds me of happy feelings》
(Aoi) 《No matter how hard it is》
♬～
(mobile phone)
Huh?
♬～
⚟Sumiharu-kun.
Long time no see, Sumiharu-kun.
Hehe...
Hehe.
(Sumiharu) 《Reality》
♬～
⚟Hello!
Hello the other day.
Um... what is that?
No, what are you?
Huh? (Masumi) With my son➡
What kind of relationship do you have?
son? (Masumi) I won't forgive you.
I won't forgive you.
(Sumiharu) 《Reality always slaps me on the cheek》
(Sumiharu) 《Wake up》
(Sumiharu) 《But➡
I can't forget that dreamy feeling.
[“Last Note” is…]
[and…]