Why is she coming here?
Darn it.
HANJU HOTEL
There's more.
Hand all of them over to the police.
INAUGURATION FOR CHAIRMAN HAN SUNG-HYE
I'll keep it short.
This is the beginning of the new Hanju
that I've always dreamed of.
Why was Seung-wook in there?
I couldn't find any excuse
to kick him out.
What about the others?
The two trespassers
have been taken by the police.
But Cho Yeon-ju wasn't caught in the act,
and the prosecutor
from Seopyung was here too.
You can go ahead.
Since when do you have to be guilty
to be arrested?
Why don't you let her off for today?
The prosecutor is being demoted.
All this will be over in a few days.
All this will be over in a few days?
In a few days,
will Cho Yeon-ju not exist in the world?
What was Mr. No doing in that car?
He planned this with us
from the beginning.
Why is he doing this?
Was this his plan all along?
Has he been fooling us all?
I don't know. I'm sure he had a reason.
A reason?
Like what? In this situation?
We only have Jung Do-woo left now.
He won't open his mouth.
He claims that he acted on his own.
Since your uncles have been taken away,
I'll go and check on Mi-na
in the hospital.
-What about you?
-Don't ask.
I don't trust anyone right now.
One of us may be a traitor too.
It must have been traumatic.
I guess.
I'm Kim Kyung-sin.
You know who I am, right?
Yes, ma'am.
May I see Jung Do-woo's resume
from when he first started?
Is there no hope for her to recover?
There isn't much we can do now.
However, we found something unusual.
What…
The person you have reached…
-Hello?
-Awesome. He picked up.
Stop calling, will you?
How can I answer your call right away
in this situation?
I was too frustrated. So? What's going on?
Tell Seung-wook that I'm sorry.
Whatever. Let's meet.
No. I can't meet you right now.
I don't trust you.
But it's not like I can not meet you.
I had my reasons.
I'll tell you the details in person.
Is it really safe for me to meet you?
You won't do anything funny?
I'm not a villain.
If I were going to be a spy,
I wouldn't have been openly
by Han Sung-hye's side.
Must we meet somewhere so loud?
Don't you watch the movies?
If you go somewhere quiet
to discuss important matters,
someone always listens in.
You need to go somewhere loud
and look like you're just chatting.
Then no one will care
about our conversation.
And even if they bug us here,
they won't be able to hear well.
Plus, I don't trust you enough
to meet alone in a remote place.
Seriously.
So? What's going on?
The thing is…
When Seung-wook's father passed away,
I already knew about that ledger.
If I had told President Han,
he may not have gone to the factory.
Oh, my gosh.
How could you keep that from us
all this time?
People can never talk about
their deepest, darkest sins.
That's human nature.
Even still. You were so close.
Show some loyalty.
Loyalty? Sure, loyalty's good.
But would being loyal
get me one million won a month?
My father has been in the hospital
for over 20 years now.
Loyalty is a luxury
for people like me who can't afford it.
Regardless, I guess
there are no secrets in this world.
Han Sung-hye used that to threaten me.
That was why I had no choice.
Seriously.
So? What will you do now?
What do you want me to do?
Come on. Even still, this is wrong.
Do you plan to be a conglomerate's gofer?
You can just start your own law practice.
You are so clueless.
It's not like I was a minister.
I won't go to a large law firm.
Do you know how much money
I have to send my family?
You still don't get it.
What?
What's wrong with being
a conglomerate's gofer?
I told you. I have to find a way
to survive over there
if I get ousted here.
You know how gangsters are.
Even a minion from a gang
will take the leader's head
when he betrays them.
I can't go by myself without a gift.
What…
What?
Did you…
drug me?
That jerk. How strong a drug did he use?
Right?
I said I wanted to kill you myself,
and he drugged you just enough
so you wouldn't die.
Look here, Chairman Han Sung-hye.
My biggest strength
is one-on-one interrogations
while we're alone.
Whether I made deals, lied, or screamed,
I always got
the suspects to say what I wanted.
So? Are you saying you'll interrogate me?
No. Today, I'll just make a request.
Turn yourself in.
I heard the recording of you
from when you killed Han Kang-sik
and hit my grandmother
with your car.
It was an accident.
You must think you're still a prosecutor.
So what if I turn myself in?
The law sides with the powerful anyway.
No one knew back then either
that I killed them.
If Ryu Seung-duk
hadn't looked the other way
in exchange for promotions,
you wouldn't have ended up like this.
Turn yourself in.
For trying to run over and kill
the real Kang Mi-na,
for killing Lee Bong-sik,
whom I risked everything to catch,
and for killing Jang and his wife
in the reservoir too.
Just admit it all and turn yourself in.
Why should I?
Do you have proof?
Of course not.
All I did was give the orders.
That is why you're begging me
to turn myself in.
All of them
passed on nicely
without me getting blood on my hands.
So will you and the real Mi-na
very soon.
How many people
are you admitting to killing
by murder-for-hire?
What?
If you use wealth or power
to induce or consent to murder,
you get the death penalty, life,
or at least five years in jail.
I told you. I always get my answer.
Did you think
I was just a pawn on your chessboard?
Do you know
how to attack such conglomerates?
Their weakness is something
people who think they succeeded
all on their own have.
Faith that they are always right.
That's what you have to attack.
Are you telling me to do
as Han Sung-hye said and betray you?
This is great. He's totally a perfect fit.
I know that was how I've lived
because I was desperate,
but don't treat me like a louse
who flips back and forth like a pancake.
Come on. Okay.
You're as pure as a lotus
that bloomed in the mud. Happy?
Darn it.
I can't force you if you refuse.
I told you before, right?
You should use a pawn to capture the king.
No one puts their guard up
against a powerless pawn.
So it's easy to flip sides
whenever you want.
So, you'll do it?
Why do you always throw a tantrum
when you know you'll do it?
Try working at a company for 30 years.
It's not easy to say yes right away.
Seriously.
Once Han Sung-hye gets Mr. No
in the palm of her hand, I'll be next.
She'll think I'll keep annoying her
as I did during her inauguration.
She'll try to get rid of me at all costs.
Do you think she'll trust me?
You have to give her something big.
Give her the originals
of all the evidence that we have.
And if she says she'll kill me,
make it happen.
No.
We can't use you as collateral
to take such a gamble.
Don't worry.
As long as we get her to sit
at that gambling table,
I can get her to confess.
Even if we get her to confess,
how will we have her locked up?
When you find bugs in rice,
you have to dry the rice in the sun.
Then the bugs that were hiding
inside the dark, damp rice jar
will crawl out.
My gosh.
So you mean we should publicly
humiliate her in broad daylight.
You made it sound very graceful.
Public humiliation?
Like you said,
the law in this country
usually sides with those with power.
But once in a blue moon,
it sides with the powerless.
It happens when the issue is publicized.
Are you going crazy?
What is this gibberish?
This is what I always say to those
who have suffered such injustice.
"If you think someone with power
is going to hit you,
make sure
there is a security camera around."
If they barely manage to fight back
after getting beaten up
with no one around,
they'll have no way to prove it
when those with power
also decide to press charges.
I didn't do anything today.
You brought this upon yourself
by acting recklessly.
That thing up there encourages bad people
to let their guard down and be reckless.
-My gosh.
-Unbelievable!
-Han Sung-hye!
-I can't believe this.
-This is crazy.
-How could she do this?
-Did you see it?
-No way.
Han Sung-hye acted like
she was kind and generous,
but she was human trash after all.
This man, Ryu Seung-duk,
is the chief prosecutor
of the Central Prosecutors' Office.
We, "Mr. Law Teacher,"
checked the statute of limitations
as quickly as we could.
And it doesn't look like
Ryu Seung-duk can be charged
as the statute of limitations has expired.
MR. LAW TEACHER, LIVE
Does this make sense to you?
-It's insane!
-I can't believe this.
-How could he be let off?
-Seriously.
-This is wrong!
-The corruption…
This world is so unfair!
-Unbelievable.
-This is so wrong.
How could this happen?
Everything you just said.
It was all live-streamed,
from the very beginning.
MR. LAW TEACHER
LIVE, MR. LAW TEACHER
HAN SUNG-HYE IS SO TWO-FACED
ARE THE RICH ABOVE THE LAW?
My gosh. How strong a drug did he use?
I told you
that I wouldn't let you
get away with it twice.
Are you all right?
There are cameras here,
so let's get out of here first.
-My gosh!
-What are they doing?
We should change our channel's name.
-Justice prevails!
-"Ms. Love Teacher."
They look so cute together.
Can someone give me a hug?
-Hug me!
-This is what I'm talking about!
-I want to be in love too!
-This is it!
ARREST THE CHIEF PROSECUTOR!
LOCK THEM ALL UP!
DID YOU HAVE FUN WITH HANJU'S MONEY?
CHIEF RYU SEUNG-DUK
It's me, honey.
I won't be home for a few days.
And they might conduct
a search and seizure of our house,
so take all the valuables
and go somewhere safe.
Go stay with your family or friends!
You've been showing off our money
to lots of people!
Hey.
If Internal Affairs investigates me now,
they'll see all my transactions
and call logs. I'll be dead meat then.
Hey. When they wanted to investigate you,
I stopped them, you know.
So you need to save me this time.
Hey, please…
Hello? Hey!
Darn it.
What have the prosecution
and this country
ever done for me?
I want to go back!
You know, when you're so angry,
you say things that aren't even true.
That woman kept talking complete nonsense.
What are you all doing?
Must I keep blabbering on?
The conversation was live-streamed
without your consent,
so they'll certainly have trouble
using it as evidence in court.
We can also say it's a deepfake,
saying it was manipulated
and that it's fake news.
All the live stream videos
have been taken down.
It's not like it was on the news,
so please don't worry.
And you're in possession
of all the evidence now.
Here's the Lee Bong-sik list.
I brought back the wiretapping device too.
And the files on the corruption.
I brought them all back.
You two are too much.
I'm the oldest here,
but you two keep bossing me around.
Do you know how much I struggled
to install those webcams
or whatever they're called
on the basement ceiling?
It's not like I've been doing nothing.
First off,
I was the one who brought
all the streamers.
And I had to go to the hospitals…
Same here.
It's not like I've been doing nothing.
How strong a drug did you use?
My head still hurts.
Exactly. You didn't have to actually
drug her water, you know.
My point exactly.
She is the one who said
it had to look real.
I only said that because
I thought you'd put nothing in the water
because you care about me so much.
Did it really have to be that realistic?
Gosh, you looked at me
with that evil smirk on your face.
When I think about that,
I still get chills.
You told me that I had to be a good actor
because someone would be listening in.
And did you really have to
say things like that?
"A conglomerate's gofer?"
"Gofer?"
Also, why did you call me 100 times?
And then you got
all angry when I answered.
At the inauguration ceremony,
were you supposed to get out of her car?
No, right?
So of course, I was surprised
when I saw you get out of that car.
You let all your emotions show
on your face.
So how was I supposed
to trust your acting?
I needed you to be really surprised
for Han Sung-hye to believe it.
I told you that he must have
had his reasons.
My goodness.
What reason?
The man who turned himself in
for the incident 14 years ago.
Why don't we dump it all on him?
When I was told to "go get some rest,"
that was my cue.
Kang Mi-na, Lee Bong-sik,
Jang Seok-ho and his wife,
and the director of Haebyeol Gallery.
Do you admit to killing
or attempting to kill them
and that Chairman Han Sung-hye
ordered you to do it?
That's correct.
And the incident 14 years ago.
That was also her.
Yes.
Why are you suddenly
changing your statement?
Your sister
has been in the hospital
for a long time, right?
I heard she underwent surgery
when she was young
with the help of Chairman Han Sung-hye.
That's correct.
What would you have done
had there been a way for her
to be fully cured?
I would've made it happen, at all costs.
It's the resume of Jung Do-woo,
a former employee of Hanju Security.
He lost his parents at a young age
and has a younger sister,
who had acute kidney failure
and underwent surgery
as soon as he joined the company.
Which was paid for by Han Sung-hye.
Han Sung-hye? Why?
She took over Hanju Fashion
at a young age.
And she must have wanted
to be seen as responsible.
She supposedly hired him for that reason.
So she's been helping his sister
financially all these years?
Something's strange.
What is it?
She could have cured
her kidney condition if she wanted.
She's had many chances
to get a kidney transplant.
But the guardian said no.
Did Mr. Jung say no?
We were told to contact Ms. Han
about those things.
And she's the one who said no.
That's why the patient's condition
continued to deteriorate.
Since you knew her weaknesses,
she kept you working for her
by taking your sister's life hostage.
I asked why you were changing
your statement all of a sudden.
Because I feel
this is unfair.
Here. We have breaking news.
You get to deliver
such interesting news on your last day.
I heard Han Sung-hye spread rumors
about you and his brother
to get rid of you
and you're being fired because of that.
So what?
Are you here to see how I'm doing?
No.
Even though
you've brought this upon yourself,
you must've worked hard so far.
I thought you might want to
fulfill your duties
as a news anchor for once
before you leave.
Let's get started.
Hold on.
Yes, I understand.
We won't report any news about Hanju.
They're threatening
to withdraw all their ads.
All right, here we go.
Three, two, one.
Cue.
Here's today's first story.
Breaking news.
This evening,
Chairman Han Sung-hye's misdeeds
were broadcast live and created an uproar.
-What is she saying?
-What?
-Why is she doing that?
-What's wrong with her?
Hey! Are you out of your mind?
Hey!
For those of you
who missed the live broadcast,
SBC had prepared an in-depth report,
but Hanju Group forced us to cancel it,
threatening to withdraw
their advertisements.
As a news anchor whose duty
is to report the truth, I apologize.
There must be a reason
why they stopped us.
-Is she drunk?
-Moving on.
The government recently…
Is Sung-hye out of her mind?
Does she want the company so badly?
She's just insane.
We didn't know anything.
-Mom.
-If we get involved with her now,
it'll be the end of us.
Do you want us all to go down together?
Don't answer her calls.
Will you be attending
the pre-arrest questioning?
I won't.
These days, if you don't,
it can be interpreted
that you have no objection
to being arrested.
Don't make me repeat myself.
I'm not attending it.
Yes, ma'am.
Sir, this is Chairman Han Sung-hye.
I see. When should I call you then?
Okay.
Minister, this is Chairman Han Sung-hye…
It's that obnoxious woman.
Hello, Chairman Han.
Mr. Ryu.
Regarding the recent matter…
I'm glad you called.
Can you help me?
I'm sure you have connections
in the Assembly and the administration.
I can't be the only person
having your back.
You hire those people's children
and offer them
huge severance payments, don't you?
Recently…
What an obnoxious woman.
-He's coming out!
-Here he comes!
-He's here!
-He's coming out!
You prosecuted almost everyone
in Hanju Group
for their crimes and corruption.
Are you ready to go all the way?
You also prosecuted gangsters
who have worked for Hanju Group.
What's the reason you declared war
against both sides?
I'm not sure
if I understand your question.
Do you have any personal goals
as a prosecutor?
I didn't prosecute them
to achieve my personal goals.
I prosecuted them
because they committed crimes.
Isn't that what
a prosecutor is supposed to do?
-Sir!
-Wait!
-Is it true…
-How do you feel?
-Sir!
You and I
seem to be in the same situation.
Oh, my. Are you crying?
Look at those eyebags.
Didn't you get any sleep last night?
Don't be ridiculous.
I slept well.
I heard you announced
your resignation yesterday
but it wasn't accepted
because of the public rage.
I'm being investigated by my subordinates,
and I know more about the law
than you all do.
That would only make you more scared.
Is this really necessary?
Must you put me behind bars?
It's not like
I killed a person or anything.
I just…
I just turned a blind eye, that's all.
I've never seen anyone
who passed the bar exam
admit their wrongdoing
without me having to go this far.
That's an overgeneralization.
See? You're not admitting it.
Cho Yeon-ju!
Do you think I can't climb back up?
You'll see me again someday.
I don't care.
I'm not interested
in the end of the wicked.
Goodbye.
Hello? What's up?
Mi-na woke up.
Thanks to
my stellar deduction skills and memory,
I passed the bar, became a prosecutor
and overcame all the obstacles
that were laid before me.
I can't possibly pretend to be Kang Mi-na
in my sleep too.
Was Kang Mi-na graceful even in her sleep?
Well…
You're two years older than her, right?
I unlocked it by entering today's date.
Your birthday.
Mi-na!
He'll be fine.
Seung-wook is tougher than he looks.
But at this very moment,
I resent my stellar memory
and deduction skills.
Why are you being a loser
and remembering all of that?
Stop deducing what happened, will you?
Seriously.
Darn it.
Let's go in.
She really wants to meet you.
Okay. But…
Maybe you should go in first.
Just me?
Why? What about you?
Well…
It's been a while
since you've seen each other.
I'm sure you have things to talk about
and things must seem very complicated.
People are very simple.
When you truly like someone,
it's never complicated.
Let's go in.
Come on.
It's nice to meet you, Yeon-ju.
Let me formally introduce myself.
I'm Kang Mi-na.
Yes. It's nice to meet you.
You too. It's been a while.
What happened?
I don't know.
When I woke up,
everything was back in its place.
How do we
look so alike?
Tell me about it.
I asked my dad over and over again
and he kept saying
he wished I were the daughter
of a conglomerate owner.
So my mom really must have had me.
I heard my aunt
went into the delivery room
and watched my mom give birth to me.
She took me immediately after I was born
to run a paternity test.
Gosh. That aunt, seriously.
But anyway…
I'm sorry for pretending to be you.
It wasn't intentional at first.
I'm the one who owes you an apology.
That happened to you
because Sung-hye was trying to kill me.
I thought she'd just frame me
for being a drug addict
and send me to a mental hospital.
I was naive.
It wasn't your fault. You didn't know.
Had you known the plane would crash,
you wouldn't have fled.
Had I not fled back then,
I would've been killed
right after the plane crash.
I'm alive right now
thanks to the both of you.
Why didn't you take the tablet with you?
At first, I wanted to meet Seung-wook
somewhere abroad
and give it to you.
All I could do was flee,
but I wanted someone,
anyone, to destroy Hanju.
But I changed my mind
just before I ran away.
Why?
When your life has hit rock bottom,
you end up thinking about
other people's lives.
I didn't want to use his life
for myself any longer.
I want to apologize
to him more than anyone.
When I returned to Korea
and saw you living as me with my face,
I realized I had been a coward
all those years.
That was why
I decided to find Sung-hye's weaknesses.
Although most of my life has been painful,
there were nice gifts now and then.
I had you two, for instance.
I'm very sorry and grateful
for you both.
Anyway, what were you saying
we don't know yet about Sung-hye?
Well…
Every member of Hanju
is being judged by the law
for their respective deeds.
Except for my mother-in-law.
That's right.
She may have harassed her daughter-in-law,
but she didn't break any laws.
What I mentioned about Sung-hye
will hurt my mother-in-law
more than anything,
so I want to tell her personally.
Since I need to
take revenge for myself too.
I heard you were in a coma.
You just never die, do you?
How could you show your face here?
Are you here to taunt me
and see how I'm doing here alone?
You haven't changed.
Your daughter almost killed me
several times,
but you won't even apologize.
So? Did you die?
No, you didn't.
Now, you can live however you want.
Stop being arrogant.
Do you think the world is yours now?
Didn't you plan to hide
behind that new face
because you were afraid of us?
Do you think I'm hiding
just because I changed my face?
So what?
What do you want?
I came here to tell you something,
so I'll leave as soon as I'm done.
Like you said,
I was blessed with a long life,
so I have survived
a number of life-threatening incidents.
But why did your eldest son
die like that?
Just when Father was about to
promote him to vice chairman
instead of Han Sung-hye.
What are you trying to say?
Gosh, I'm exhausted.
What did you put in my water?
Did my sister put you up to this?
You see,
I'm not like Sung-chan.
I won't let my guard down.
I won't let her get to me.
Never.
Sung-chan went to volunteer
at an animal shelter with Sung-hye
and died of an asthma attack.
You don't even want to set foot
in an animal shelter
ever since that happened,
so I always went there alone.
I found out that the dog shampoo
she had donated that day
contained an ingredient
that was lethal to asthma patients.
If he'd had his inhaler,
which he always carried around with him,
he could have lived.
But it just happened to
disappear that day.
Ask your younger son where it was.
He knew all along,
but he's been keeping it to himself
because he was afraid of his sister.
I just want to live quietly.
I don't want to end up like Sung-chan.
I wanted to get a confession
out of Sung-hye.
But given the situation,
it'd be pointless to get her convicted
of one more crime,
so I figured
I should just tell you personally.
Shut your mouth.
Get out at once!
You won't go to jail
for being a toxic mother-in-law.
However,
your daughter killed your eldest son,
who was your most beloved child,
and your younger son
has kept his mouth shut
even though he knew all about it.
Just remember that
and spend the rest of your life
in the jail you've built for yourself.
HANJU HOTEL
HANJU GROUP
EMERGENCY MEETING OF SHAREHOLDERS
We are here to discuss
the dismissal of the owner family.
I will now announce the voting results.
HANJU GROUP
EMERGENCY MEETING OF SHAREHOLDERS
Here. Am I too late?
We need the approval of
at least two-thirds of the shareholders.
But as you can see,
it didn't reach that number.
Hence, this proposal has been rejected.
What? Those of you who are against it.
Are you crazy?
How could we trust them
to run the company properly?
Does one have to be ethical
to run a company successfully?
They're unrelated.
I apologize.
I'm sorry I'm late. May we have a revote?
-Who is she?
-Who's that woman?
Who are you?
Ms. Kim has that much power?
She got the director title for a reason.
My grandfather gave her
only valuable stocks,
so I'm sure she can exercise
a lot of influence.
It's true that late bloomers
are more enthusiastic.
She used to say
she wanted to always remain neutral.
Must she make it so obvious
which side she's on?
Hanju's shareholders' meeting
took place earlier today.
After a revoting process,
which took hours,
the company has announced
that 67.1 percent voted in agreement
of the dismissal
and 32.9 percent voted against it
and that Chairman Han Young-sik's
family have been dismissed.
CONGLOMERATE OUSTED BY SHAREHOLDERS
This makes Chairman Han Young-sik and
his family the first conglomerate family
to be ousted by shareholders.
The arrest warrant for Han Sung-hye
has finally been issued,
and the police plan to arrest her soon.
The Seoul Central District Court
issued the arrest warrant
based on sufficient evidence against her
and a reasonable flight risk.
CHAIRMAN HAN SUNG-HYE
Early this morning, Chairman Han Sung-hye,
who had been missing
since the announcement of her arrest,
was found dead by a reservoir
in Gyeonggi Province.
The body had already been decomposed
when it was found,
but the clothes and accessories
Chairman Han was wearing
when she went missing
were all found on the body.
Hanju Group held a board meeting
and appointed Han Seung-wook,
the son of Han Kang-sik,
as the group's new leader.
The late CEO Han Kang-sik
is now the group's honorary chairman.
Hanju has released a statement
expressing condolences
on the passing of Chairman Han Sung-hye,
and has canceled the inauguration
and all other events.
My gosh. I guess you're going to Vietnam.
Do you want to learn a Vietnamese idiom?
In Korean,
"A long tail is bound to be seen."
How did you know…
I know people like you very well.
True cowards
can't take their own lives. Why?
Because death terrifies them.
I examined the corpse very carefully.
The clothes, shoes, watch
and rings were all yours,
but the underwear.
I could tell it wasn't yours
because I used to hand-wash
all your underwear for you.
How dare you try to fake a suicide
and get away with it?
How many times must I tell you?
Just turn yourself in.
Darn it.
I was going to kindly let you
keep that elegant front.
Too bad.
Darn it.
HAN KANG-SIK
Han Sung-hye must have believed
that everyone is afraid of
admitting and apologizing for
their past wrongdoings.
She doesn't understand that
not everyone is like her.
She must have thought
you were keeping everything from me.
It wasn't easy for me to tell you.
But everyone makes mistakes.
You just have to try
not to repeat the same mistakes.
I feel like I've finally paid off my debt.
I feel relieved.
Hey, Seung-wook.
Yes?
Since I've quit my job
and paid off my debt,
just think of me as your friend.
I want to take it easy now.
And stop asking me for rides.
I'll get going. You have company, right?
Yes.
Goodness.
CHOI SEUNG-OK
How do you feel?
I feel like I've just finished a sprint
and now I have to run a marathon.
In which direction should I run?
Where do I belong?
I ask myself those questions.
You wonder where you belong?
You once said to me
that you didn't want to
sit there wondering
how your stock price would crash
whenever something happened.
So I thought about it too.
About what kind of life I wanted to live.
But I couldn't figure it out.
For a long time,
I only lived to achieve my goals
and take revenge.
Now that everything's over,
I really don't know
what to do with my life.
Let me know when you figure it out.
You must have found
what you want to do.
I'll be waiting for you.
TAMNA FISH MARKET
-Look at this.
-Who sent it?
The owner?
Oh, my.
I did hear your sashimi
was extremely fresh.
And you opened your second restaurant.
Stop being angry with me already.
How could you still be so upset
about being taken by the police?
Hey!
Do you think that's what this is about?
You didn't tell us you were pretending.
-Please…
-Stop talking to me.
We're busy answering
franchising inquiries.
What?
Don't be like that.
Right, Pil-kyu?
I knew you'd be on my side.
Where's my dad?
I'm not going to tell you.
Never ever!
CONGRATULATIONS ON OPENING
YOUR SECOND RESTAURANT!
-Hey, you're here.
-Yes.
If you opened a new restaurant,
you should hand out flyers or something.
The flowers aren't enough
to attract customers.
How can you be more behind than me
when I've been in prison for ten years?
Who attracts customers
with flyers these days?
What you have to do is
give away coupons on apps
and advertise on social media.
We're already fully booked for today.
Why did you open a restaurant
right after being released?
You could have rested more.
Pil-kyu says you can get wrist pain
from working with knives.
Take it regularly.
You should have asked
what my role here is
before buying this.
I never used knives
even when I was in a gang.
So why would I now?
I hired someone to do that.
Then I'll take it back.
Well, it doesn't mean
I want you to take it back.
Maybe I'll get joint pain
from counting all the money.
Drink slowly.
I guess I don't have to worry about you.
Are you leaving now?
Yes.
All right.
Yeon-ju.
If you're going to say
something cheesy, don't.
Just don't say anything.
I was going to ask for a napkin.
It got all over my hands.
I see.
I'll be going.
Take care.
I will.
Goodbye for real.
Gosh, I'm stressed out.
I keep being told to step down.
Can you explain why you pick on me
at every shareholders' meeting?
Have I ever pocketed any money?
Why do you insist on
hiring a professional manager?
That's because you've been establishing
an excessive amount of funds.
That's why the shareholders
suspect you of money laundering.
Gosh, I wish I could
smack her in the head.
Nothing gets past her.
How does she know about money laundering?
Just when I barely managed
to get rid of the fake one,
the real one showed up.
And she's just as difficult to deal with.
But is she really her?
I'm doomed.
Gosh!
BRIQUETTE DONATION
TO SHARE LOVE AND WARMTH
I just don't understand.
Isn't all this just for show?
We should just pay more taxes.
What difference does it make
if we deliver these briquettes?
What's even more difficult
to understand is you.
Why did you come back to us?
Even at my parents' house,
no one welcomed me.
The final straw was them
looking down on Sun-woo
just because he was a daughter's child.
We know the real reason.
You thought Seung-wook
would swallow Hanju up whole,
but since he hired
a management specialist,
you figured Sun-woo
may get a chance after all.
If you're so smart,
stop being lazy and work hard.
Father says convictions
for financial crimes aren't a flaw
and plans to make a comeback
when he gets out,
and is gnashing his teeth.
We should help him.
He's being way too excessive.
Anyway,
why did Mother change so drastically?
My gosh. She has no energy at all.
Ninety-one.
Ninety-two.
Ninety-three.
Ninety-four.
Ninety-five.
Ninety-six.
Ninety-seven.
Ninety-eight.
Ninety-nine.
One hundred.
I will not fall.
How dare you punks…
How dare you?
How many times must I tell you?
I'm not interested at all
in the end of the wicked.
Who cares if they do squats
or take body profile pictures?
Don't tell me about things like that.
I know you started your own practice,
but did you have to
spread rumors everywhere?
Word-of-mouth advertising
is the most effective.
Anyway, now that your father
is out and established,
you must feel relieved.
I am.
So actually, I came to say bye.
Are you finally going?
Yes.
I tried doing this and that
to find my place in this world,
but it doesn't matter
where I am or what I do.
If I'm with the person I love,
that is where I belong.
Are you really okay
with someone else living here?
That's right, I am.
Or why don't you move in? You punk.
What? You're being demoted?
You went straight to Central District.
I'm very proud of you.
Anyway, I got to live for cheap in Seoul,
which is notorious for high rent
thanks to you.
Thank you for never raising my rent.
Well… Thank you for everything too.
What's wrong with you?
I didn't do anything for you.
You always came late or not at all
because you forgot
I was waiting.
So…
I studied all the time
while waiting for you.
That was why I did well at the institute.
And…
I was grateful
that you never felt bad toward me.
I was able to act normally with you
thanks to that.
I feel like
it's really goodbye now.
Yes. Someone once said
that even if your life is tough,
you meet someone
who is like a gift once in a blue moon.
I think you were my gift, Yu-jun.
Take care of yourself.
LOS ANGELES, USA
My life had been filled with endless days
of dreaming of being somewhere else.
But when I looked back,
I realized that what I truly missed
were the moments that had passed.
Although I wanted to be
very different from who I was,
I was able to do everything because I was
the most like myself.
When we don't lose ourselves,
regardless of whom we're living as,
we are capable of doing anything.
EPILOGUE
This is the first thing you wanted to do
after passing the bar in the US?
They don't have jokbaengi there.
We can fly back right after we eat, okay?
There were so many jerks in the US
who tested my patience.
They're dead now. Just you wait.
CONGRATULATIONS CHO YEON-JU
BECOMES LICENCED US ATTORNEY
Did you call Mr. No?
He asked when we were coming
every single day.
So that was why he asked.
Ms. Cho.
Where are you going?
Seriously.
What is this?
It's jokbaengi.
You brought this stinky food
all the way here?
I know.
I brought this stinky food
and timed it with your arrival…
Stop ordering me around.
I don't know anyone else in Korea.
-Let me see.
-Get it yourself next time.
Shall we just eat it here?
Where do you want to eat?
MOTORCYCLE GUITAR RIDE
Let's ride a motorcycle on a guitar
Let's ride a guitar on a motorcycle
Let's ride
Let's ride a snail
On a watermelon
Let's ride the light
On a quail
With a balloon
Let's give it a hug
Let's hug a wardrobe
With a pine caterpillar
Just as you imagine
Cyber
One, two.
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING ONE THE WOMAN