She slapped my back with such conviction.
My gosh.
You always have pork bone soup
once every three days,
so I was wondering what was going on.
According to her, I love pork bone soup
and run a huge tab.
Prosecutor! Over here!
Someone called me something similar once.
Hello there, Prosecutor.
Funny seeing you here.
Wasn't that a great tip?
Did you hit the jackpot with it?
Yes, that con artist.
So he really meant…
I am a prosecutor?
Wait a second. I'm extremely smart,
quick-witted,
and familiar with the law.
I know someone in the Prosecutors' Office,
and someone even called me "Prosecutor."
Does that mean…
Since the article about Hanju Group
helping us came out,
people seem to think I hit the jackpot.
Why did he even go there
in the first place?
Maybe he was meeting someone.
By any chance,
did you check his phone?
It was smashed to pieces in the accident.
Then could I at least
have his phone number?
Did his condition worsen lately?
No.
It started to worsen
around 14 or 15 years ago.
After the factory he worked at had a fire.
Come to think of it,
the factory he worked at
belonged to Hanju Group.
Hanju Fashion.
Hanju Fashion?
HAN KANG-SIK
HANJU GROUP'S FIRST SON DIES IN A FIRE
When the fire started,
my husband was asleep in the quarters.
Luckily, one person went around the rooms
and woke everyone up,
so he was able to avoid injury.
Still, it took a while
before he was rescued,
and it must've traumatized him.
His seizures got worse after that.
Wait a second. I'm extremely smart,
quick-witted,
and familiar with the law.
I know someone in the Prosecutors' Office,
and someone even called me "Prosecutor."
Does that mean…
I was impersonating a prosecutor?
Gosh.
Was I both a gangster and a con artist?
I knew it.
Honey.
Why did Seung-wook give you a ride?
Well, why do you think?
See?
I always know what to say
to throw the other person off.
That's a characteristic of a con artist.
What?
Of course, it was Mr. No
who came to pick me up.
But then he got a stomachache
and had to rush home.
Turns out, Seung-wook had followed me
to make sure
the new chairman he supported
as a major shareholder was safe.
And I figured this was my chance
to get to know him better.
That's why I asked him to give me a ride.
See how smooth that was?
I'm definitely a con artist.
I see. You should've called me.
Honey.
Maybe I'm too used to being
in the shadow of my big sister.
I don't feel inferior to my wife at all.
I sincerely hope you'll become successful.
You're the new chairman of Yumin Group,
and I never got
to congratulate you properly.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
By the way, honey…
What is it?
I can't seem to remember.
Did I have any close friends
I often hung out with?
I can't figure it out
because my phone broke into pieces.
Well, I'm not sure
if you should think about your friends
at a time like this.
You have a lot on your plate
right now, don't you?
You don't know, do you?
Did you ever even ask?
-Get out.
-What?
Get out.
Why did I even ask you?
Okay.
Good night.
How much longer do I have to lie?
Once Mi-na is found,
I'll make sure you can go back
to your normal life.
My normal life?
The life of a gangster and con artist?
Everyone wants to know
where Kang Mi-na is.
But no one is interested
in who I really am.
Even if I were a thug and crook,
I must have a family, right?
Is there really no one looking for me?
What is it, sir?
Inmate 3452. You have a visitor.
It was you guys?
Who else would come here?
You come at most once a year.
Don't talk like you come often.
Boss.
We have something to tell you.
There's a gang
called Samgeori Gang in Seopyung.
Those guys totally humiliated us recently.
-What happened was--
-I told you
not to come here to talk about your gang.
That's not it.
If you can't find a job,
say you're from Nammoon Gang
and start a YouTube channel.
I'll allow that.
No one will post nasty comments
on your videos.
Yeon-ju is a prosecutor,
a public official.
She is doing great things.
I refuse to taint her name any further.
She's doing well, right?
She cut ties with our world
and is a great prosecutor, right?
-I need to tell you--
-Hey!
Of course, she's doing well.
She's eating well and working hard.
Of course.
She's doing very well.
Darn it.
Why wouldn't you let me talk
after coming all the way here?
You saw his eyes sparkle
when he talked about his daughter.
How could we tell him
that his daughter had been
taking bribes and using violence
and is being hunted by Samgeori Gang
and that she's hiding from us as well?
I wasn't thinking straight.
He cut ties with her anyway.
What use is it if he knows in there?
What if he gets out on parole?
He'll be disappointed.
He's serving a life sentence.
He needs to serve at least 20 years first.
He has a long way to go.
Good morning.
What are you doing here?
I said I'd take care
of everything, didn't I?
Rather than have you meet
a bunch of people,
it's better to have the one person
who signed the oath deal with everything.
It's more cost-effective.
Rich people are worse.
Anyway, I look forward to working
with you, Mr. Double Agent.
Why are they doing this? It's too much.
It's to show respect for the new chairman.
Your father, Chairman Kang Jang-soo,
refused to give his children
their inheritance in advance
even if they had to pay taxes later.
That is why you,
his daughter, received everything he had,
including his wealth and power.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
CEO KANG MI-NA
I turned down the inauguration
and everything else,
but it would've seemed strange
if you passed on the briefings
regarding new businesses
of our core subsidiaries,
so you'll have to attend to those matters.
Will they talk to me and stuff?
What do I say?
Don't say too much.
Just say okay to everything for now.
You're just a fill-in anyway.
We should maintain the situation.
Let the real chairman decide
whether or not to keep it going.
But this is kind of…
Is there a problem?
Your aggressive marketing plan
is to just spend lots of money.
Buy one get one free promo,
giving out coupons,
giving kickbacks to dealers
for selling our products…
They're methods of sales as well.
Exactly.
I'm saying I don't like that method.
Don't try to use tricks
to start a new business.
Cut down on marketing costs
and invest in product development.
Bluetooth earphones?
Even a local business shuts down
if it can't recoup its capital
in five years.
This business keeps failing
year after year.
What is the point of changing the name
and doing the same thing?
Mobile healthcare platform business?
What about the legal aspects?
You must not know,
but the law was passed recently.
What passed recently
was Section Three of the Data Law.
This will have many issues
under the Health Law.
It falls under several regulations too.
Do you know what a pain it is
if we get cited for violations?
Revise it, including contingency plans.
I turned down everything else,
but furniture
is the core business this year.
The new chairman should come
and encourage them.
How is a higher-up
looking around encouraging?
I'll sit here for a bit and go.
Give the employees a small bonus.
That's how you encourage them.
You may go.
I won't check every corner of the store
or anything like that,
so go back to work comfortably.
What's this?
I turned down everything else,
but Yumin Group's motto this year
is global management,
so you should attend the video conference
with the Australia branch.
All you have to do is show your face.
What exactly did you turn down?
That's nice and comfy.
Your position is a bit…
What? It's perfect.
People don't buy sofas to sit on them.
They buy them to lie on.
What's wrong with this?
Hello?
These punks.
Are they doing this intentionally?
To make the decisions themselves
after I show my face?
They must look down on me
because I'm a young woman.
Tell them I'll reschedule the meeting
and attend properly from my office.
What?
I don't know what you did
in your previous life,
but I guess the board didn't
pass you for nothing.
I feel like I was worried
for nothing this morning.
Do you understand English too?
I think so.
I was at the Prosecutors' Office
all day yesterday.
Isn't this too much work
for the morning after?
No one made you do it.
You're the one who chose to work hard.
It'll be lunchtime soon, so wait.
I can eat comfortably, right?
Father, if you wanted to talk to me,
you could've talked to me
when you saw me at home
instead of outside at a restaurant.
Does this look like we're just eating?
Joining Yumin's new leader
during her first lunch
symbolizes a lot.
I see.
About the hotel
that you're launching in Jeju…
It opened without any fanfare.
You can't just leave it like that.
The entire family died
on the day of the grand opening.
That is a terrible image for a hotel.
Since it's already happened,
why don't you merge it
with our hotel business
and make a fresh start?
-Dad canceled the lunch with me?
-Yes, ma'am.
A lunch meeting was suddenly scheduled
with the new chairman of Yumin.
The new chairman of Yumin?
Do you want to become a politician?
Me? No.
Then you're being awfully gutsy.
You barged in
to arrest the head of a conglomerate
because of a mere tip-off?
It was a credible tip-off,
and we were afraid she'd flee
or try to destroy evidence.
And that's what happened.
She was released
because the test came back negative.
Stop talking nonsense.
Besides, the prosecution
takes hierarchy very seriously.
You can't just raid the office
without even reporting
to your higher-ups first.
Because it is illegal.
As a prosecutor, isn't it my job to
investigate and indict every unlawful act?
Since when did the prosecution
have to investigate every unlawful act?
I do not understand what you've just said.
Goodness. What am I going to do with you?
Have you given up on a promotion?
No. I was never interested to begin with.
Sure. Being in a small town like Seopyung
can make you feel that way.
Then I suggest
you start taking an interest in it.
What do you mean, sir?
You know…
about the Hanju lobbying case
that was assigned to Division Two, right?
I've reassigned it to your office.
You reassigned
a previously reassigned case?
I'm sure you're surprised.
Just think about all the hard work
I must've had to put in to pull this off.
According to my colleague at your office
who played a huge role in it,
the office is so tiny
that you are unfortunately the only one
who can take on
a case that huge.
With that said…
Just bury it.
I wanted to find out more about you today.
Clearly you don't want
to launch a career in politics later on.
You're not very interested
in becoming successful.
I guess you just work hard
without a plan for your future.
If you cover this up,
I can make you interested in success.
You're close to Cho Yeon-ju.
Then you must know.
Look at her. She got her act together
and managed to return to
the Central District Prosecutors' Office.
What about you though?
Will you work in the boondocks
for the rest of your life?
Do you have bad lungs?
Do you have to live in a place
with clean air?
Don't waste your time
on useless cases
like the Lee Bong-sik one.
This is fate,
and it'll be a great opportunity for you.
Do a good job with the investigation.
Make sure you refer to the precedents
for the lobbying cases
involving conglomerates.
Precedents are just precedents.
The law is different.
I'll take care of it.
So you'll follow the law?
Father, your charisma is incredible.
I couldn't even pick up my spoon
while you were talking.
-What?
-But you see,
at your first lunch meeting
with the new chairman of Yumin,
you're referring to the accident that
killed my entire family as a mere mishap.
And you expect me to agree to the merger?
As you know,
my family treated me like dirt,
but fortunately for me,
I completely lost all those memories.
So let me be blunt
without any hard feelings against them.
Don't you dare
take over our hotel like that.
Yumin Hotel is clearly greater
than Hanju Hotel.
No one can ever completely hide
their true colors.
Why did I never see this side of you?
Well, I should get going
before you see something else.
Enjoy the food.
They say every prosecutor
can make his own decisions,
but they won't let you do
whatever you want.
If Ms. Cho was around,
I wouldn't even be asking you.
We've even filed a missing person report.
Where is she?
The police don't even want to
investigate the case yet.
You've reported her missing?
Yes. She's nowhere to be found.
We can't just sit back and wait.
Anyway, I got your point.
If you're done talking, I'll get going.
-Enjoy your lunch.
-Hey.
Wait!
What is his deal, seriously?
You didn't have to storm out like that.
I couldn't really think
because I was so hungry.
We should leave now to pick up some gimbap
before the lunch hour is over.
Thanks for lunch.
What? He didn't finish the food.
-Mr. No, let's go back.
-Go back where?
They must've ordered expensive dishes
for the chairman.
We should eat the food.
Come on. Hurry. I'm starving.
Hurry!
Hey! Wait!
Mr. Chairman.
I didn't know I'd see you here.
Are you here for lunch?
We had to put a project on hold
because of the summons,
but look at you lunching at a restaurant.
I guess you have
a lot of time on your hands.
Well…
Please don't worry, sir.
This is done very often,
but I reassigned the case
to another office
where many of my colleagues work.
Well, I'm sure you'll take care of it.
Wait, sir.
Wait.
Darn it.
How come you still haven't had lunch?
I had a lunch meeting,
but something unappetizing happened,
so I left.
My gosh, the soup is delicious.
Where's the female colleague
you're fond of?
I thought she'd be here because I saw her
while delivering some orders last night.
-Who? Cho Yeon-ju?
-Yes.
Nonsense. I'm sure it was someone else.
No way. I've known her
since her rookie days.
I've developed a keen eye
through doing this for 30 years.
Don't be absurd. My goodness.
I saw Ms. Cho yesterday too.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
What? Where?
In the hallway at
the Central District Prosecutors' Office.
She was with a man.
Are you sure you weren't mistaken?
I'm sure of it. I saw her snapping at him.
Didn't you hear I had to cancel our lunch?
Why are you waiting here?
Why didn't you call me
if you were having lunch with Mi-na?
It was about the hotel,
so I had to speak with her privately.
Are you already planning
a merger with Yumin?
If it's about the hotel,
shouldn't I know too?
I'm not trying to help you
with your business.
This is about expanding my business.
I received a summons
from the Seopyung District Office.
Goodness. Bribing the National Tax Service
is still bogging me down.
Without the list that has your name
from three years ago,
they had to summon Sung-woon's wife
because she's in charge
of artwork dealing now.
If there's any possible issue,
get it sorted out
with the gallery in advance.
Okay.
Let's see how Mi-na
handles things this time.
Whether I want to help you
with your business
or just focus on expanding my own
is a conversation to be had
after we sort that out.
I'm totally drained after that talk
with my father-in-law.
Can I go to the hospital
and get an IV or something?
Do you not want to work?
What do you take me for?
I'm really exhausted right now.
As the head of the group,
you can only be treated
by your personal physician.
And your doctor is attending a conference
in Singapore right now.
Sing, Sing, Singapore
I'll go to the pharmacy
and pick up some energy drinks.
Drink those and try to hang in there.
I'm the chairman of a group.
I can't go to the hospital
when my personal physician is away?
This is ridiculous.
The stock price is plummeting as is. If
rumors spread about your hospital visit,
the stock price is done for.
Why are you here?
Go look for the real Kang Mi-na--
Go find her.
I can't find her
if don't give me any info.
I couldn't even reach you.
I had no time to call you.
Do you know how busy I am?
Did you look into her daily routine,
her friends, and if anything else happened
the day she went missing?
No.
You said it'd be no problem.
What have you been doing?
It's not like I didn't even try.
No one seems to know
about her personal life.
Friends?
You never told me about your friends.
You didn't go out except to visit
the gallery or do volunteer work.
Whatever you did outside
had to be reported to the family.
No wonder you were stuck at home
all the time.
She was a speck of dust to her family,
her husband had zero interest in her,
and all her friends were closely watched.
It seems like she was never able
to open up to anyone.
You're one emotional man.
Your face tells how you're feeling.
What are you talking about?
Come to think of it,
I'm the chairman of Yumin Group now.
Yes, you are.
Then I'll postpone all projects.
They'll all be rejected anyway.
What?
It's not that I don't want to work.
Just look at your face.
I must find Kang Mi-na first.
Let's go to the gallery first.
The last person who saw Kang Mi-na
that day was the director there.
Will you be okay by yourself?
If I'm not, are you coming with me?
We don't know who was behind
the hotel and the drugs incidents.
You can't be too careful.
Why are you looking at me like that?
You don't have to thank me.
It's no problem for me
to deal with a few men by myself.
He's only going to get in my way.
Okay. I won't thank you.
I seem to keep thinking of you as Mi-na.
I'll try not to attract attention.
By the way,
will you really be okay at the gallery?
You may have to lie to people
you don't even recognize.
It's fine.
Because I'm a professional liar.
Gosh.
How can she be so confident?
-She wasn't here yesterday?
-No.
The phone is turned off.
But I heard she was.
Please leave a message…
Her phone is still turned off.
Nothing's changed.
Just what is she thinking?
Usually, radio silence is a bad sign.
Will she show up with Lee Bong-sik
out of nowhere or something?
Hey, are you sure you can't reach Yeon-ju?
Didn't I say I'd let you know
when I hear from her?
I heard that she came to work yesterday,
but she's out of reach again.
What's going on?
Is she trying to make me look for her?
If she was there yesterday,
she should come back soon.
I'm busy. I have to go.
Hello? Hey!
Why did she have to take so many bribes
that I had to rush over
before the police got here?
But what is she up to really?
SOONDAE SOUP
There's a weird rumor
going around about you.
-What is it?
-They call you Seopyung's vacuum cleaner.
They think you're a troublemaker
who sucks in chump change.
-So I succeeded.
-What do you mean?
Hey. After years of slaving away in Seoul,
I realized something
when I was transferred here.
I'm an ordinary prosecutor
with no money or connections.
Which do you think will be easier for me,
going to see the higher-ups
or making them come to see me?
Surprisingly, it's the latter.
Is that right?
For a nobody like me
to get the upper hand,
I must try my best to stand out.
That's why I try my best
to be a troublemaker.
You should stop coming to see me.
We should stop eating together too.
If people find out we're friends,
they'll think you're a troublemaker too.
What kind of mischief is she up to now?
WE WELCOME OUR NEW CHAIRMAN, KANG MI-NA
Who are you?
I'm not a bad person.
I just want to talk to the chairman.
Then…
what is this?
They're Bluetooth earphones.
Bluetooth earphones?
This business keeps failing
year after year.
What is the point of changing the name
and doing the same thing?
I was informed this morning
that the business plan was scrapped
and we didn't have to supply
our products anymore.
We're forced to discard everything
that we already produced.
That's why I came.
These have completely different features
from our old version.
I just wanted to show them to you.
Still, you can't barge in like this.
You should take proper steps--
While he does that,
his contract would be terminated.
Don't worry.
Which do you think is easier,
a supplier seeing the chairman
or the chairman coming to see a supplier?
Surprisingly, it's the latter.
When you have nothing
but want to get the upper hand,
this is often the only way.
Sir, I'll make sure
to pay you a visit soon.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Still, protocol is protocol.
Please follow me to the security team.
Are you okay?
You seem to faint
every time you get shocked.
I suddenly felt dizzy. But I'm fine now.
Seeing how these things keep happening,
I wonder if that was really
the first accident Mi-na had.
Let's say these things
were happening all the time.
Even though I'm looking for her
using all the resources I have,
I still haven't found her.
Maybe it means she's actually abducted
or something even worse happened, but…
But?
What if Kang Mi-na is hiding on purpose?
What are you talking about?
Father.
Is someone hiding?
Who? Where?
Father, this has been a very eventful day.
After careful consideration,
I rejected a proposal.
Apparently it upset the supplier,
and he just attacked me.
Luckily, I was able to escape danger,
but I was concerned about the image
of both Yumin Group and Hanju Group.
So I was trying to come up with a way
to calm down the supplier.
That's when I remembered
our major shareholder, Alex Chang,
who is devoted
to building social enterprises.
But the supplier must be
a for-profit organization.
What does it have to do
with social enterprises?
Exactly. I realized that
after talking to him for a moment.
Since I injured my head,
he's worried
that I've been preoccupied with work
unlike the old Kang Mi-na.
"Look for the kind-hearted Mi-na
hiding within you."
That was his thoughtful suggestion.
People are complaining
that you sent back reports
that were just waiting
for Chairman Kang to sign off on.
Word spreads so quickly.
I don't have to do everything
exactly the way my father did.
Just because the chairman
has the final say doesn't mean
the chairman should dictate everything.
I know you hurt your head,
but you're out of control.
Why do you think
that rumor is circulating?
Do you know how much people are talking
about how strange you've become?
How well do you know me?
Human beings are complicated
with many sides to them.
People say something's changed
when it doesn't feel familiar anymore.
Can't you just see me for me,
for who I am now?
Do you come running whenever Mi-na calls?
Let's finish talking about this upstairs.
Upstairs?
-But…
-The stock price will fall again
since people say
the new chairman is crazy.
Stop it. Don't scare me like that.
I don't know what it's about,
but you should go.
You always make me go alone
in times like this.
You said earlier I reminded you of Mi-na
and you'd go with me.
No. You're different from Mi-na.
What now?
What are you trying to say this time?
You're cooler than Mi-na.
Although you wouldn't know.
Seriously.
Gosh. He thinks I'm cool?
What does he want to say to me?
You know I was investigated for lobbying
the National Tax Service, right?
I do.
I tried to stop it,
but annoying things keep happening.
Anyway,
you received a summons
from the Seopyung Prosecutors' Office.
You were in charge
of our family's artwork deals,
so you'll need to go.
Father.
It's been ten minutes since you said
I was out of control
after hurting my head.
Now you want me to go
to the prosecutors' office?
I don't know anything.
You'll say you don't know
and that you don't remember anyway.
Even if they use a lie detector,
it may go in your favor
since you really don't remember.
But…
Darn it.
This is the assailant's call log.
Am I the head of the legal department
or an employee
at a private detective's office?
Why did you go there alone?
It's unbecoming to just tell others
what to do but do nothing myself.
You knew that?
Is how I dress also unbecoming?
Why? Did someone say something?
Well…
Did that person also say it was unbecoming
to just tell others what to do?
Yes.
Whoever it is,
you should become close to them.
I think that person
will be of great help to you
both externally and internally.
Did you meet
that prosecutor you mentioned?
Actually,
I can't reach Cho Yeon-ju at all,
so I'm looking around.
It makes me uneasy.
I feel like she went into hiding.
Are you sure we can trust her?
I heard a lot about her
from junior prosecutors in Seoul
when she was appointed.
She was the top trainee
at the Institute and is infamous
for her hot temper.
But she has a poor background
and has no connections.
They say she's good at trials.
Do you think Hanju did something to her?
No, right?
I doubt they'd go that far.
Anyway, we'll have to find
a new prosecutor.
What about that prosecutor
who barged into Yumin's chairman's office?
Someone that bullheaded
wouldn't care what others think.
It may be the opposite.
Do you mean he may be with people
who are after Mi-na?
I'll look into him a little first.
Why don't I meet him instead?
-Mi-na took the paintings?
-Yes.
She asked us to bring them into the room.
I don't think she had them
when she was hit by the car,
so I thought someone else picked them up.
Didn't you know?
Why are you only telling me that now?
-Have you always been this sloppy?
-No.
I reported everything about Ms. Kang Mi-na
up until now.
This time was because of the accident…
I apologize.
The Seopyung Prosecutors' Office
will summon her soon
to question her about the paintings.
It'll probably become a pain
for you again.
Gosh. I was dragged here and there
a few years ago because of Lee Bong-sik.
What choice do I have?
I have to do a good job
so that you can win points
with the chairman.
Don't worry about me.
Even if I'm talking to a prosecutor,
my lips will be sealed again
as they were for you last time.
Ms. Kang Mi-na…
No, it's Chairman Kang Mi-na now.
Chairman Kang is another one
you need to be wary of now.
I won't tell Chairman Kang
that you had her watched
and things like that.
That wasn't my point.
Pardon?
You've worked hard for our family
all these years.
Why don't you take a trip somewhere,
given the circumstances?
Before the prosecutors start bugging you.
I'll clean things up here.
Was that what you meant?
Actually, it isn't that easy
being dragged here and there.
Then do that. You're due a break.
Get some air…
while you're away.
Thank you.
I'm not even well.
How could he send me to Seopyung?
Even if I am a tiger cub,
he shouldn't kick me
off of a cliff like this.
Did Mi-na really make deals
with paintings?
Ms. Han Sung-hye was in charge of that
until three years ago
to build up their slush fund.
But ever since
she was conned by Lee Bong-sik,
Mi-na made the deliveries.
Darn it.
What if I say something wrong
and end up behind bars?
Why do I have to clean up
after Kang Mi-na every time?
She may not have done it…
on her own volition.
Look at him still taking her side.
Forget this. Look.
If you can't find Mi-na,
at least find out who I am.
You're a rich American.
Call the FBI and have them
run my fingerprints
and find out who I am.
FBI? Are you joking?
Why would they have
a Korean citizen's fingerprints?
If you're so curious,
go to a police station and ask them.
Police station?
We're almost there. Pull over here.
Stay hidden.
Seopyung?
Do you think it's the prosecutor
I said I'd meet?
It's a small town, so it's very likely.
We need to find her quickly
before she goes in for questioning.
What if she says something wrong?
She'll be in danger.
Whom are you worried about?
Mi-na or…
What are you doing here?
Did Father tell you
about the summons?
Yes. That too.
What a shame. You're too late.
I came to see if I could help you,
but the director must have gotten a whiff.
She left for the US this morning
on business.
She did?
Anyway,
I heard something strange.
On the day of your accident,
you had bought paintings at the auction.
The five billion-won painting
our family was supposed to buy
and the 300 million-won painting
you bought personally.
You bought two paintings.
But I heard you took them.
What?
You didn't have them on you
when you got hit
and you didn't give them to anyone either.
Apparently, you told the director
to bring the paintings to you.
What?
What could you have done with them…
before you lost your memory?
What were you trying to do
before the accident?
I want to find that out
more than anyone else.
You need to get your memory back soon.
Either there was a mistake
or you put them somewhere safe.
I made up an excuse.
There's no need for you to go in.
Bye.
CALL LOG
WIFE, CLIENT, PARK
SEPTEMBER 12, OUTGOING CALL
Yes.
Hello?
When he left the Hanju factory,
he received huge severance pay.
On the morning of the accident,
he said he was expecting a big sum
and told me not to worry.
Hello?
What happened?
Did they answer?
We've got a problem.
Apparently, I ran off with paintings
that are worth 5 billion
and 300 million won.
Kang Mi-na said someone was coming
to pick them up that day.
What was she up to?
What do I do now?
That's not the problem now.
What is a bigger problem than this now?
We don't have time for this now.
Then what should we talk about?
She ran off with 5.3 billion won.
It's just 5.3 billion.
Pay it back with Mi-na's money,
or I can give you the money.
My gosh.
Talk about culture shock.
Right,
it's nothing in the world of the rich.
No wonder Han Sung-hye said nothing
about paying back the 5.3 billion.
I think Han Sung-hye had something to do
with the accident.
-What?
-Looks like the driver
has a connection with Hanju.
The call log shows that he was in touch
with Han Sung-hye.
Kang Mi-na was the target.
But why?
She wasn't a chairman or anything.
She did nothing but stayed home all day.
Hold on.
So I have to go to the house of the one
who tried to kill me
and eat and sleep as if I know nothing?
No way. I'm just going to run away.
Where will you go?
What?
They don't know that the real Mi-na
is gone, so they're not looking.
But if you disappear, the Hanju family
will find you no matter what.
Let's be careful and see
how the situation unfolds.
Darn it.
I believe that Ms. Kang overheard
some inmates' conversations
while volunteering at the penitentiary.
Since then,
she's been doing a little digging
into the arson case
that took place at Hanju Fashion
14 years ago.
-Since when exactly?
-I think it's been a while.
Then how come she's been quiet
all this time?
To use it against us down the road?
Maybe she was planning
to hand it over to her family
and demand a divorce in return.
I suppose she doesn't really know
how to win a game like this.
In some games,
you lose if you hold on to a joker.
She was afraid things wouldn't go
according to her plan,
so she tried to run off
with the paintings?
Then who has the paintings now?
-Ma'am, about dinner--
-I have no appetite.
I knew you'd say that,
so I bought some pastries for you.
I'm difficult, right?
No, ma'am.
But this is how I am.
I'm naturally fussy.
You can change your ways,
but not how you naturally are.
Right?
What do you mean, ma'am?
There was this person
I just couldn't stand.
I could never tell what she was thinking.
But…
-Mi-na.
-Don't mind me.
I can say that much. What's wrong with it?
Who am I?
I can't believe how much she has changed.
You said you checked
the drug test results again.
Yes, ma'am.
I've confirmed that they found nothing.
Ms. Kim. It's me, Sung-hye.
What's for dinner?
Should I really be here when I know
that this is the tiger's den?
I think this is a bad idea.
I should go talk to them again.
You're home.
Did you hear what I just said?
Hear what? I came out just now.
The walls in these rich families' mansions
aren't that thin.
Did you have dinner?
It's okay. I'm good.
Whether I had dinner or not,
you shouldn't have to fix dinner
more than once a day.
I've done it, so I know how annoying it is
to fix a meal
every time someone comes home--
-Come in.
-Yes, ma'am!
This must be hard for Jae-hee.
She's not used to doing housework.
Does it taste okay?
Why? Did she spit in this?
I made it, and I didn't spit in it.
It's good. You're the best, Ms. Kim.
Ms. Heo
took cooking classes
before she got married,
so she knows her way around the kitchen.
Of course, she took cooking lessons.
She's from a rich family.
I'm sure I did too.
Because of my amnesia,
I even forgot
all about the cooking lessons.
It was hard to get up
at 4 a.m. to do housework,
but approving stuff at work
isn't exactly easy either.
I guess nothing's easy in life.
Just do as you're told.
Sorry?
Just eat when someone fixes you a meal.
It's stressful because you insist
on doing the dishes too.
Just leave everything in the sink
when you're done.
My gosh!
What are you doing, hiding here?
I wasn't hiding. I just walked in.
I figured you'd be tired
because it was your first day.
I brought some tarts from the hotel.
I don't want them!
Don't worry.
They're cheese tarts, not walnut tarts.
I don't like baked goods.
Really?
You used to love them.
I no longer like them.
Then what do you like now?
What do you mean?
Well…
I'll make sure to get them
for you next time.
-Hey.
-"Honey".
What are you playing at here?
Why are you suddenly nice to me?
Come on. We were business partners
to begin with.
I must change now
that our contractual terms have changed.
Don't be like that.
Sweet dreams, honey.
Go away!
Enjoy the tarts.
My gosh.
Every eye in this house
is like a surveillance camera.
Why is he being so clingy all of a sudden?
Gosh.
Hold on.
Don't worry.
They're cheese tarts, not walnut tarts.
Get it together. How could you eat this?
Could it be…
Hello?
It's me. Was Mi-na allergic to nuts?
Yes. She couldn't even stand
the smell of them.
But Ms. Kim gave me kongguksu.
She must know I'm allergic.
Pretend you're sick tomorrow.
Avoid contact with family members
for the time being.
-Bye.
-Okay.
You used to show up like Superman
even when I didn't call you.
How could you hang up on me like that?
Answer me.
That's what I would normally say.
So why did I say,
"Okay," and just hang up?
You're different from Mi-na.
You're cooler than Mi-na.
Although you wouldn't know.
Stop. What are you thinking about?
She was a speck of dust to her family,
her husband had zero interest in her,
and all her friends were closely watched.
It seems like she was never able
to open up to anyone.
Oh, no.
If I think he's cool,
a slap in the face can wake me up.
But if I start to feel sorry for him,
it means it's over.
What is this?
Could it be that I'm innocent,
although I'm a crook?
My gosh!
What are you doing, hiding here?
See?
I totally acted like
I'd never dated anyone.
If the crook turns out
to be an innocent virgin,
what on earth
was the conglomerate's
daughter-in-law like?
Too bad we couldn't meet outside.
Prosecutors don't have time to go out.
We have to read all the records,
investigate, report, write up drafts
and gather statistics.
I only made time for you
because you told me
you had intel about Hanju Group.
So what is this about?
You received a tip about
the second daughter-in-law
of Hanju Group using drugs, right?
That's right.
Can you tell me who gave you the tip?
That case was transferred
to Seoul Central.
So you're not here to give me a tip
but to receive a tip?
I assume there aren't many prosecutors
who could barge in there like that
just because they received a tip.
In addition, you sent a summons
to the same person again.
I'm wondering if you have any plans
regarding Hanju Group.
It seems like you got the wrong idea.
I only went there because I received a tip
about her drug use.
And the summons was sent to a witness
in the National Tax Service bribery case.
I'm just an ordinary prosecutor.
Ordinary prosecutors are quite rare
these days, aren't they?
And an ordinary prosecutor is
just what I'm looking for.
I don't know what you imagine
an ordinary prosecutor to be like,
but prosecutors are just as
performance-driven as salespeople.
That's why ordinary prosecutors spend
all their time chasing petty offenders.
Then why don't you make time
for bringing down a big shot?
Wouldn't that help your career?
You might even be able
to put him behind bars.
I brought this
thinking you might want to know more
about Hanju Group.
You seem busy, so I'll get going now.
Right.
By the way, have we met before?
I ran a check on you,
but you and I don't seem to have
anything in common at all.
Bye then.
When we went to arrest Kang Mi-na,
he barged into the chairman's office
and complained it was an illegal arrest.
He did?
PROSECUTOR AN YU-JUN
What's that?
This is a pretty old case.
The Hanju Factory arson case.
Didn't the first son of Hanju Group
die in that fire?
-He's that guy's father.
-Really?
If I remember correctly,
the fire was started
by a worker who had been fired.
Anyway, he's a member
of the Hanju family himself.
Why did he bring that to you
and say those things?
Is he a Schrödinger's person?
A what?
You've heard of Schrödinger's cat, right?
You don't know what Schrodinger's cat is?
There's a cat in a box.
Until you open the box,
you don't know whether the cat
is alive or dead.
You can say
it's the world's most famous cat.
I'm like that.
A Schrödinger's person, if you will.
Does that answer my question?
Do you really have to become successful
by doing exactly what someone did
to your grandma?
Yes, it answers your question.
Until everything's over,
you can't say someone is good or bad.
On her deathbed,
do you know what my grandma told me
when I was blaming myself for her death?
CHOI SEUNG-OK
What did she tell you?
"No one is 100 percent responsible
for anything that happens."
She didn't want me to spend
the rest of my life
tormented by guilt, doing nothing.
There's nothing that my memories
of Grandma can stop me from doing.
So until the box is open,
you shouldn't conclude
whether I'm good or bad.
Yes. I'll be abroad for a while.
You might not be able to reach me.
Sure. I'd like to get some good rest.
Okay, bye.
What's going on?
That scared me.
My goodness.
The scene has been taken care of.
The gallery will be sold to someone
appropriate soon.
People are so foolish.
Unless you express your anger,
they don't know you're angry
and keep crossing the line.
But I couldn't get angry with someone
way below me, could I?
Assistants can always be replaced
without any problem.
Don't you agree?
When you're getting
too big for your boots,
when you think you're somebody,
that's a sign…
that you must think long and hard.
Otherwise, those thoughts
will eat you alive.
Oh, dear.
My gosh.
Oh, my. If it isn't Ms. Kang Mi-na.
I almost forgot what you look like.
It sounds like your memory
is getting pretty bad.
Should I hang a picture of me
on the wall or something?
Do you think I'm out of my mind like you?
What I mean is,
why have you been stuck
in your room all morning?
I had kongguksu yesterday,
and I've been feeling unwell since.
Oh, gosh.
Have you lost your mind?
Why did you give that to her?
Mother!
Are you okay?
I've seen her splashing coffee
on you countless times,
so I saw this coming.
What will you do
if she gets sick but doesn't die,
causing our stock prices to fall?
You got in my son's way and made him die.
Your family copies everything we do
and gets in the whole family's way.
Goodness. You frustrate me.
Mother.
I know you're taking it out on Jae-hee,
but I think you're out of line.
Hey, I didn't say anything to you.
Stay out of it.
Seeing how you're picking on me,
were you lying
when you said you were unwell?
Was I lying?
You get so aggressive
every time I say something.
Are you a thug or what?
A thug?
Why are you so quiet?
I'm sorry.
It wasn't Ms. Heo who gave her kongguksu.
I gave it to her last night.
I must be getting forgetful in my old age.
Ms. Kim.
At your age, if you make such a mistake,
people will think you have Alzheimer's.
-Be more careful.
-I will be.
Ms. Kang, I don't think
you should eat anything today.
-Go upstairs now.
-What?
She's right.
You're being questioned
by the prosecutors later.
You're usually way too aggressive.
You should at least look sick.
It worked out well.
Ms. Kim.
Sorry for asking you
to do that last night.
It's my job.
How's Mi-na?
This was from a while ago.
Yes?
Just as you did,
Madam instructed us
to feed Ms. Kang food with peanuts in it.
I wasn't home at the time,
so someone else served it to her.
She wanted to know
how serious her nut allergy was
and whether or not
she'd actually die from it.
I think that was what she wanted to know.
Since Ms. Kang
had not lost her memory back then,
she could've stopped eating
if she felt something strange.
But now, since she has no memory,
she'd keep eating
even if she feels something wrong.
Did it not matter what happened to her?
Make your point.
That was why
when you told me
to make Ms. Kang kongguksu,
I made it with all soybeans
and no nut powder.
I don't care what you do
outside for the company.
But don't drag that into the home.
However,
Ms. Kang said she got sick
because of the kongguksu.
How strange.
Darn it. That witch yells at me
and tells me to starve,
but I can't talk back
because I'm a crook and a gangster.
-This is so annoying.
-Mi-na.
Yes?
I didn't know you cared so much about me.
I don't exactly.
It was more because of my temper.
Regardless.
I suddenly became
a third-class citizen in this house.
You were the only person
to openly take my side.
Sun-woo caught on and checks
his grandma's facial expression.
-Jae-hee.
-What?
To be honest, you're not my type,
but you have the tenacity
to survive in this family
and have financial means.
Why do you stay here like this?
Your parents are loaded.
You could ask them
to give you a subsidiary.
You heard Mother earlier.
My parents' company and Hanju
overlap in types of business
and company size,
so even they treat me like a spy.
I have my reasons too.
I see.
Which gets me thinking…
To be honest,
I've been closely watching
your every move.
-And?
-This is the best time to ask.
A few years ago,
I decided I had to take care of myself
and found a hedge fund.
Private Equity Fund for chaebols.
Only people who qualify
can invest with them.
The more funds the better.
Can you invest in me?
-Jae-hee.
-What?
When you hear
an explanation about something,
if you think it sounds
too good to be true,
it's always a con.
What are you talking about?
It's like if I want to
take out money I put in,
I need to put in more money
so that I can get paid sooner.
Those cons are popping into my head.
That's not true.
It's a small fund
with people who know one another.
Deals involving money
between people who know one another.
That's like in-laws.
What does that mean?
It may be okay.
But that's rare.
Pull out as soon as possible.
It's not like you've pulled cons before.
How do you know that?
Right?
If you don't want to give me the money,
fine. But don't be insulting.
What if I do?
What will you do for me then?
Well, I won't just
sit back and do nothing.
In that case,
tell them I'll invest
and use that as bait
to get yourself paid first.
Then pull out.
Pull out?
I'm telling you, it's a con.
If it really is a moneymaker,
you do it alone.
That's how the world works.
What do you have to do
to avoid Mother lashing out at you?
You have to get angrier.
If you don't want to get conned,
you have to pull a bigger con.
Okay.
You know, right?
This stays between us.
Why do I know those things so well?
Did I pull cheap cons like that too?
Darn it.
EPILOGUE
HANJU FACTORY FIRE IN SEOPYUNG
HANJU FACTORY ARSONIST FINALLY CONFESSES
SUSPECT
Please tell us.
Why did you do it?
-Happy birthday!
I can't believe
I had a meal with people on my birthday.
You should get going, right?
Why are you trying to kick me out?
She must've been hanging out
with her cousin-in-law so often
for such disgusting rumors to have spread.
Who's on Chairman Kang Mi-na?
-What are you doing here?
-Do I know you?
You're the one
who used that to bog me down.
I'm trying to be understanding,
but you've changed too much.
I call this "Magic Powder."
Who told you it's called "Magic Powder?"
The tablet you used to carry around
all the time.
You activated the fingerprint lock.
Unlock it right now.