Episode 16
Look at the chest.
The ancient insect has started to eat the heart vein.
If we don't do something about it,
I'm afraid
it will be more dangerous.
Reversal?
How could it be?
Before,
I fell into the fire.
Let's get better.
We can start to
collect the primordial fruit
if they stay in this temple.
God is so stupid.
Is it wrong to choose another life for survival?
It's a different life.
Whatever you're struggling for now,
it's all for nothing.
Why?
Do you think
why he tried to approach you?
Why did he choose you as his wife?
Is it because he likes you?
Stupid.
Of course it's because your heart
can cure his bone poison.
All of this
is our game for you.
You don't know yet,
the man in front of you
is the real master of Wuming Pavilion.
Wu Feng.
Xie Zi Yuan.
If you want to live,
you must die.
Voracious והn
Dashes, long sleeves and short sleeves.
Dad, you should take it off.
How can you wear it?
It's Cheryl.
My daughter made it
for me for the first time.
She didn't even change anything.
Shi An.
Have an YJ.
I bought it from the mountains.
I want to try the sweet and sour for you.
Hurry up and try it.
How is it? Is it sweet?
Tian Dong?
It really is Tian Dong.
It's been a long time since it was born.
I must take it back today.
Oh no!
Turn out
I'm a pupa.
We've found out
that the man beside Mu Wan
is Prince Xuanping, Xie Ci Yuan.
But the strange thing is
according to the news from Ping City,
Xie Ci Yuan was imprisoned in the mansion
because of the illness of the Sky Flower.
Why did he appear in the city?
Prince?
How could Xiao An be involved
with the court officials?
There's something more strange.
I sent someone to find out
where Mu Wan was when she disappeared.
That place was actually related to the Wu Ming Pavilion.
It's not related.
You mean
Xiao Wan has been in the killer group
for these days?
It's possible.
After all, she can't remember anything.
It's really strange.
Since Xiao Wan has become a killer,
how could she be involved with the mansion?
I'm afraid her fate is not that simple.
The most important thing now
is to take her back to the Flower Valley.
If it's the mansion of Prince Xuanping
or the Wu Ming Pavilion,
it's very dangerous for her.
Master, bad news.
Young Master is in trouble.
How dare you hurt her?
Let Master take the blood.
Okay, I'll try to save her.
You can't be poor.
Trying to hurt her,
I'll get her out.
You borrowed the Heart understood this man's actions.
She must die today.
Take the Chief away first.
You've suffered.
I'll get justice for you.
Mu Wan...
How is it?
That bastard.
How dare he
take my blood?
I won't let him off.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Xie Ci Yuan was poisoned with the Purple-Blood Bone.
Mu Wan's blood was the only solution.
I've been eating
Longjie Grass since I was a child.
His blood can cure all kinds of bones.
Xie,
must have been deceived by me
by my memory loss.
He was so confused
that he became a princess.
His purpose was
to find the blood
that was on his body.
This time,
he was so anxious.
It's really bad.
One more thing.
Yesterday, I heard that girl from Wu Ming Pavilion
call her Chief.
You mean
Xie Ci Yuan
is the Chief of Wu Ming Pavilion?
Wu Feng?
No wonder I found out
that Xiao Wan
is the killer of Wu Ming Pavilion.
She went to the same place
with Lord Xuanping.
If Lord Xuanping is Wu Feng,
then everything is clear.
If Xie Zi Zhou knows
that he is a useless brother,
he is so scheming.
I wonder what he will do.
I will make him
know the true face of this chief.
Yes.
Well,
you keep an eye on Xiao Wan.
I'll go make the medicine.
I'll be in the next room.
If anything goes wrong with Xiao Wan,
report to me immediately.
Yes.
You're fine.
Don't worry.
When you come back to me,
I won't let you get hurt again.
You really want to leave with him?
Why can't I leave?
Because your bones haven't been removed.
What?
I was right?
You're asking me?
I'm not.
Let me explain.
Explain what?
You came to me
not for the result.
You wanted me to stay
because you really love me.
If I say...
Stop telling these ridiculous lies.
If one day,
you want to take my blood
and my life for the result,
do you want me to believe
you have your reasons?
Xie Zi Yuan,
we were wrong at the beginning.
Let me go.
Impossible.
Don't touch me.
You're my wife.
Why can't I touch you?
Zi Yao, don't forget.
You're my wife,
the Princess Consort of Xuanping.
You're crazy.
I'm not Zi Yao.
I'm Fang Mu Wu.
I'm not from the Wu Ming Pavilion.
I belong to the Flower Valley.
You're wrong.
You belong to me from the beginning.
No.
I'm not.
Let her go.
Xie Zi Yuan,
I'm going to kill you.