Unaccom injuries
The set free surface
Episode 16
Good.
Gentlemen,
I'd like to ask
where you are selling horses
in the city.
You want to buy horses too?
Yes.
Please give us a tour
and give us a guide.
I wonder
what kind of horses you like.
In my opinion,
you need a
large-sized horse.
Yes.
Is it funny?
Try again.
You're talking nonsense.
Miss Chongzhuang,
please forgive me.
I'll go now.
Yes.
White stone hairpin.
I heard Lu Cheng is a good painter.
He likes to collect
the paintings of this antique shop.
You're a painter too.
If you don't collect them,
it's a pity.
They said they were here to buy horses.
But there are no horses in this place.
Besides, when they talk about buying horses,
they are rude and rude.
They are different from ordinary people.
I'm afraid
they are not horses.
Yes.
In my opinion,
they are not horses.
They are human slaves.
They are bad people.
Let's go.
We are familiar with Lu Cheng.
Let's see if we can see
the so-called big figure
in the mouth of the mute.
I heard that
Xie Zizhou sent Li Yan to Lu Cheng.
The show in Lu Cheng
is getting longer.
I wonder who will be the next one to come on stage.
This is Hao.
He is 14 years old.
He is young and slim.
I think you should like him.
I think you should like him...
I think it's hard for me to like him.
I think it's easier for you to love him.
If the Golden Lottery were here,
it would be hard to like you.
This is not the tim eine theta downstairs.
There is lots of gold and silver.
But this gold standard should be higher.
I don't know if we should do it.
The best Dig out Army of China
How dare you kidnap me?
You don't want to live anymore?
You're still stubborn even though you're dead.
Please spare me, Heroine.
I was being rude.
Please don't blame me.
If you want money,
I have some money with me.
Just take it.
If you don't have enough money,
I have a jade pendant with gold in it.
It's worth a lot of money.
I don't care about the money.
I'm here to ask you a question.
Heroine, please.
I heard that you keep two
most beautiful girls
for an adult.
Who is this adult?
Chief, don't be surprised.
I've known the things
you and the Li family did.
The girls were all caught.
Now, you just tell me
who this adult is.
I can give you a chance.
Who is he?
Wu Mingge?
Wu Mingge killed the traitor.
You're not the first.
You're not the last.
You're a girl with no family.
You're innocent.
But if you tell me
who this adult is,
I can break up with you.
You deserve to be punished.
You have a right to live.
What?
You want someone to save you?
I'm afraid you'll be disappointed.
After we parted ways,
I went to the gate of the city
to watch Li Yan.
The first thing Li Yan did
was to go to the Chief.
I didn't see this idiot.
So I took my horse
to save Qinglong.
It seems that Li Yan came to the city
to kill the girls
who were kidnapped.
It's a pity that he came late.
They were rescued
and sent to Ping City.
No.
What if they do something to those girls
on their way back to Ping City?
Don't worry.
I've sent people
to ensure the safety of those girls.
That's good.
It's a pity that
we still can't find Cui.
That's not easy.
I only give you one chance.
You can decide
whether to tell or not.
I really don't know anything.
Tell me.
Don't kill me.
I'll tell you.
The Chief promised me
that he would take the girls
who were kidnapped
to the city to entertain the nobility of Yunzhou
to win people's hearts.
But I don't know why
the Ping City thing
was stopped by your Wu Mingge
and the carriage to get out of the city.
The Li family is very cautious.
They asked me to find people
in the local city.
No wonder
the girls in the city
are also missing.
You haven't answered me yet.
Those girls who were not given
to the nobility
were sent away.
By the order of the Grand Tutor,
I'll leave each group of girls
who are the most talented
to the City Leader first.
Xie Zizhou is a man of great talent.
Why does he want these girls?
I really don't know.
I beg you not to kill me.
I don't want to die.
I really don't want to die.
You've betrayed Xie Zizhou.
If it's in his hands,
it's even worse than death.
Why don't you let me send you off?
Xie Zizhou,
Zi Yuan has been manipulated by you for so many years.
He has suffered so much for you.
Now,
you want to trap him
and let him die in my mansion.
Xie Zizhou,
you're not a human being.
Didn't you say
everyone knows my temper?
I even killed my biological father.
I'm not a human being.
I killed him.
Besides,
I'm the younger brother of the same mother.
Mrs. Jin,
don't be too sad.
I was just joking.
His Majesty has a infectious disease.
It's a good time to get a blessing.
Besides,
he's my other life.
How can I watch him die?
I've ordered
to send him medicine and tonics every seven days
to comfort His Majesty.
But if His Majesty can't get through this,
and Mrs. Jin sends the black-haired man,
I'll definitely arrange a grand funeral for him.
I won't humiliate the Xie family.
Xie Zizhou, you...
I fell and cut my knee.
You're looking at me like this.
It's so ironic
what happened in the world.
Although I knew
I didn't have a source for myofascia,
I'm still playing with the ball of consciousness.
Even though I'm not the defect of a person,
I'm still a human being.
Even though huge included
I have a physical body.
I want to..
I'm worried about Xiao Cui.
I think Xiao Cui's parents
are so anxious about this.
They must love him very much.
This kind of feeling
really makes people envy.
I want to help them reunite as a family.
But right now,
there's something else more important.
I want to help them reunite as a family.
You're making me worried.
You know a secret trick called Flower-Frozen Sand.
Flower-Frozen Sand?
That's right.
It's a very evil trick.
It can make a cook who's under 16
drop a chain of elixir.
Rumor has it that it can make people
live forever.
If Xiao Cui and those girls
are really given Xie Ci Zheng,
will they...
How could she do such a stupid thing?
Yunzhou is in a turmoil.
If at this time,
a missing girl appears,
it will only make her more popular.
No.
I was too hasty.
She doesn't care about the popularity.
You're right.
Since the person who sent Li Yan
to kill Lu Cheng is Xie Ci Zhou,
it means that she must know about this.
Xie Ci Zhou is arrogant and arrogant.
She wants to be satisfied with everything.
She wants to have
all the glory and status.
And she must have it.
That's why
she wants to marry a girl
to write the elixir.
Lu Cheng is dead.
This place will be in a mess.
Since we've got
the clues we want,
we should leave
and return to Ping City.
Find out the truth.
In case there's another girl
who's innocent.
Where's the sachet?
It's here.
Are you all right?
I'm okay.
I'm fine.
Wait for me here.
I'll go to the car shop to look for a carriage.
We'll return to Ping City tonight.
If Xie Ci Zhou
really sent the elixir
to the girl,
then she's more dangerous
than I thought.
She's more inhuman.
We must save her
and leave the City Hall.
Memories come back and forth like tide and waves.
Our story is no longer here.
The sweetness of the past is empty.
Now all that's left is the pain in my heart.
Tears flood my eyes.
I can't see your back.
This love can no longer be returned.
Only sorrow remains.
My happiness is leaving and I wander on the include deaf.
For whom should I
long for?
Time flies so quickly.
The Long Ballad