Unreleased hands
After letting go, the sky is wavering
As long as fate is fated, it can no longer be kept
The love that has been lost is the most sorrowful
Episode 16
I heard from the servants that you went to Qifeng House today.
The prince has been losing sleep recently.
I am very worried.
I heard that Sister Xiaoyu has a secret Anxi incense.
It is the most favorite scent of the prince who used to stay in Qifeng House.
So...
So you went to find her for incense?
I did something wrong.
The prince is angry.
There are not so many rules in the Xueping Palace.
You can do whatever you want.
Report to the master.
In the sachet, in addition to the usual medicine,
there is also a very rare dragon knot.
Since the princess cares so much about me,
I should also escape from violence.
Take you to a good place.
Qinglin is not monitoring me all day long.
It's monitoring Xie Ci Yuan.
It's not a way to go on like this.
I have to find a chance to get him away.
Go.
Your Highness, where are you going?
I'm going to take the princess out and have a date.
Don't tell me you will follow me even if you don't know the way?
Boss, have you seen this girl?
No.
Sell buns.
Freshly made buns.
Come and have a look.
I can't say anything, so I hide my feelings.
My feelings are still strong.
How should I say it?
Let each other go.
When the yearning is still moving.
I'm sorry. I got the wrong person.
Let go of my hand.
Let go of the hand and the sky is clear.
Only fate can't keep it.
Losing love is the most painful.
How did you find this place?
It's too hidden.
This is the secret place my mother gave me when I was a child.
I've never brought anyone here.
So no one knows this place.
You are the first one.
Why are you so nice to me?
Because you are different from others.
You are so talkative.
Maybe the entrance to Flower Valley is in Longji Mountain.
I don't know if I can remember anything when I get back to the familiar place.
What are you looking at?
Look, my lord.
There's a table of herbs.
It's called Tian Dou.
Normally, the growth is at the peak of the cliff.
It needs to be under the tree.
The growth conditions are very high.
It's not easy to find the right one.
Since it's so rare,
I'll help you pick it back.
No.
It blooms in autumn and flowers in spring.
When it blooms, it's the real Tian Dou.
You know so much about herbs.
Have you learned medicine?
I've learned medicine?
I've learned medicine.
Learned medicine?
Yes.
I heard that there's a mysterious place in Longji Mountain.
It's called Flower Valley.
The people in the valley are all so rare.
It's rare to see them all.
I wonder if you've heard of it?
Flower Valley?
Do you remember anything?
Should I remember anything?
For example, your past, or your past.
My past?
Your Highness.
I don't remember. I don't remember anything.
I don't remember anything.
Okay. If you can't remember, don't think about it anymore.
I'll take you back now.
Your Highness, the carriage was tied up with several women a few days ago.
We have to find them as soon as possible.
I know. The head of the hall has sent someone to investigate.
I guess that the carriage will follow the road.
Which road?
The road?
It's one of the most prosperous and convenient cities in Yunzhou.
If those women were abducted,
the road would be a perfect place to transport them to other places.
According to the news of Wu Ming Pavilion,
the head of the road seems to be someone from Li Rui.
Li Rui is a man of great power.
If this is related to him,
we should investigate it thoroughly.
I'm warning you.
Don't think about going out again when you come in.
If anyone runs away, I'll beat him to death.
I've been very good to you.
That girl cried and tried to kill herself this morning.
So what?
You still have to be good to me.
I'll be a good hostess to you.
So I suggest that you all should behave.
You can make it easier for the poor.
Who are you?
It's the head of the royal family.
Don't worry. I will send someone to escort you home.
Thank you, young master.
Young Master.
Thank you.
Thank you, Young Master.
Today,
I've searched several women
who were kidnapped from Ping City
and sent to Lu City.
I didn't find Young Master.
I'm incompetent.
Please punish me.
It's not your problem.
No one wants Xiao Wan to be in trouble.
For the past year,
we've been inquiring about her everywhere.
As long as we don't see her body,
it means Xiao Wan is still alive.
I'll find Young Master.
Well,
send the kidnapped girls
back to Ping City safely.
Anyway,
it's a great merit
that my daughter is still alive
and can save others' daughters.
Madam, don't be afraid.
Oh no.
A man
is here every day to listen to the walls.
He's really not a coward.
For Xie Cizhou,
let alone listening to the walls,
even if he jumps the tower,
he won't have any complaints.
He's gone.
What else do you want to do?
What do you think I want to do?
Your Highness,
you look a little disappointed.
Have a good rest.
I'll go out for a while.
You...
Where are you going?
He's always in the mansion
and is meddling in our affairs.
It's not a way out.
I have to get thisbelomax
out of my eyes.
What's the matter?
It's nothing.
It's because the City Leader
myself provoked me
and made me lose consciousness.
Don't be a bad boy.
Our story is gone.
The sweetness of the past is empty.
Now only the heartache is left.
Tears blur my eyes.
Can't see your back.
This separation can't be returned.
Only sorrow remains.
My heart is like a mountain.
Lost in the wild world.
No longer care about anyone.
Maybe it's a kind of fog.
The youth is like a flash.
Gradually being crushed by the years.
Who still remembers the love words in the breeze.
My heart is like a flash.
Lost in the wild world.
No longer care about anyone.
Maybe it's a kind of fog.
The youth is like a flash.
Gradually being crushed by the years.
Who still remembers the love words in the breeze.