♪Wandering alone♪
♪Walking far by dusk-lit streets♪
♪Your eyes are as cold as clouds♪
♪Faintly coming into view♪
♪The city lights♪
♪Lit up that single moment♪
♪I can't hide or stop missing you♪
♪I can't forget those moments♪
♪Losing you♪
♪Like the seasons in my memory♪
♪Without winter♪
♪Walking down the long, dark street♪
♪Snow will never fall again♪
♪Our old story was torn♪
♪Into scattered pieces♪
♪Replaying every single scene♪
♪After you left♪
♪As if our documentary♪
♪Lost winter♪
♪The breeze speaks of good times♪
♪Pure white devotion♪
♪Send out a letter♪
♪Carrying my longing♪
=The Double Game=
=Episode 18=
(Lu Tingxiao's uncle, Fang Wenyuan)
Uncle, don't worry.
It's safe here.
Can you tell me
why Lu Jianchuan locked you up
for so many years?
Why?
He feared I'd expose his secrets
and ruin everything he had.
I...
once saw
a certification document.
It had my mom's signature on it.
He must've used that document
to get the project approved.
It was approved by my grandpa.
What exactly happened?
Your mom was too innocent back then.
Meeting Lu Jianchuan
was the start of her tragedy.
At the time,
your grandpa was still in office.
Your mom
was fooled
by Lu Jianchuan's fake kindness
and care.
She insisted on marrying him.
Later,
she even used our family's resources
with his startup.
Until Lu Jianchuan
used the Lianxin Island project
to completely destroy our family.
Lu Jianchuan used those dirty tricks
to get the development permit.
After that, he got even bolder.
He used the signatures and approval
to force your mother
to keep taking money from our family.
After your grandpa found out,
he had a heart attack
and died suddenly.
Your mom was already torn up inside.
When Lu saw she'd lost support,
he actually got back together
with his old flame.
Later, he even brought her home.
Your mom couldn't take
that many blows anymore.
In the end...
I couldn't let it go
and went to settle things with Lu.
I said I'd expose all his dirty secrets.
I never thought he'd be so low
as to lock me up.
That ordeal
lasted more than ten years.
How's your uncle doing?
Is he asleep?
You don't look well.
Did you find any leads?
Nothing important.
It's okay if you don't want to say.
Wen Yan,
if the price of the truth
is the person you love most
losing everything,
would you still keep going?
I understand your struggle
and why you want to protect your uncle.
The truth matters,
but people
matter too.
It's not my uncle.
It's my mom.
She was used by Lu Jianchuan.
Without even knowing it,
she signed forged documents.
Also, my grandpa
was fooled
by Lu Jianchuan's schemes.
It left a stain on his career.
Once the truth
about Lianxin Island comes out,
they'll lose everything.
No matter what you choose,
I'll support you.
You need to know
you're not alone.
I'll stay with you.
Where is he?
Who let him go?
Tell me.
You...
You betrayed me too.
You betrayed me first.
You wanted to climb higher,
so you threw our love away.
When you joined the Fang family,
why not stay loyal?
I had my reasons back then.
I was thinking about our future.
Do you really
want a hard life in the countryside?
If I hadn't endured all that,
would we live this well now?
Then what about Lin Yuqing now?
What humiliation
are you enduring?
I don't want to argue about this.
Don't think
letting them out can scare me.
I'm telling you.
I only
kept them locked up for a while.
I didn't kill anyone.
Even if they get out,
what can they do to me?
Those young punks alone
can't shake things up.
(Put myself in his shoes.)
(If my mom were mixed up in this,)
(I'd probably be hurting like he is.)
(But where is my mom?)
(Is she doing okay?)
Her name is Wen Hui.
Her household registration record
is active.
(Wen Hui)
I'll cook for you.
Here, have some fruit.
(Wen Hui)
(I've searched and wondered)
(for so long.)
(Mom,)
(you've been by my side all along.)
(Love Is Timeless like Pearls.
Pearl Bay)
Let's go inside first.
In the depths of the sea,
there was a beautiful Pearl Bay,
where a kind Mermaid Princess lived.
One day,
the Mermaid Princess
saved a merchant from a wreck.
The merchant was charming and witty.
He told the Mermaid Princess
of the vast, vibrant world above.
She soon fell in love with him
and brought him back to Pearl Bay.
The merchant told the Merfolk King
he could take the pearls of Pearl Bay
to the land above
so more people could see their beauty
and, in turn, bring Pearl Bay
endless wealth and honor.
Blinded by love and his lies,
the Princess
persuaded her loving father.
However,
once the merchant got the pearls,
he showed his true colors at once.
He was never a stranded traveler.
He was a hunter all along.
He teamed up with a greedy lord.
They stole Pearl Bay's pearls in bulk
and cast aside
the pregnant Mermaid Princess.
As it turned out,
the merchant already had
a family on the land.
When the old King learned the truth,
he was crushed by rage
and fell sick.
Pearl Bay lost its pearls
and all its former joy,
and slowly faded away.
As for that greedy lord and hunter,
they feared the merfolk's revenge,
so they sent their men
to snatch away
the newborn little mermaid,
but what they didn't know was
that Mermaid Princess had two daughters.
To keep her younger girl safe,
Mermaid Princess
tearfully sent her away to be raised.
From afar, Mermaid Princess
quietly watched both girls grow up.
She thought
once her older daughter
married the lord's son,
she'd live in peace.
But unexpectedly,
she still suffered so much hurt.
Her younger daughter suffered too.
Mermaid Princess's biggest regret
was failing to protect them
and stay by their side as they grew.
Mom.
Yan.
My daughter.
Mom.
Zhi'er.
My precious daughter.
Mom.
(Our story began with Pearl Bay's tide)
Congratulations.
You finally found your family.
You're not
the lonely little elephant anymore.
Tingxiao,
you're not alone anymore either.
I'm your family too.
♪This door♪
♪Lets in the sky outside♪
♪With a voice even lighter♪
♪Than how you just greeted me♪
♪I know now♪
♪What the chill in my body means♪
♪The moment salt hits the wound♪
♪My heart still beats so naively♪
♪To complete♪
♪A joy that needs no brave pretense♪
♪How cruel sincerity can be♪
♪Like a door with no key♪
♪Maybe you just passed by♪
♪The tears in my eyes♪
♪You looked like you had nothing to say♪
♪Then got so good at being cold♪
♪That's why a smile feels so precious♪
♪Maybe you just passed by♪
♪The tears burned into my heart♪
♪Let's say silence was just for show♪
♪Even if I've grown another year♪