[English subtitles are available]
[Love Never Fails]
[EP13]
Master!
Master, hurry!
Well,
I didn't mean to bother you.
I saw a block of ice in the forest,
knew it was Bailing,
so I nudged it
to tease him.
But,
Bailing turned human form, and just...
stopped breathing...
I...
That's...
Ow, ow, ow...
Ouch!
That hurts!
Wait, Bailing,
why prank me?
I never messed with you.
I...
Sorry, Tian Nanxing.
If I hadn't,
Master wouldn't show up.
Master, look.
Those saplings you told me to plant
are now a whole forest.
Will you finally say
why you made me do it?
Wenxin.
Yes.
Master must have his reasons.
Tian Nanxing.
He has his fate in it?
Bailing.
Am I
being tested?
It's to show you that
every tree and blade of grass is hard-won.
Learn to cherish them.
Forget it.
You've re-forested for years.
That counts.
From today,
join your mates
and hunt demons down the mountain.
Thank you, Master!
I'll go now.
Avoid...
Wang's Village.
Don't wander far.
Be home for supper.
Dad,
I'm heading up the mountain for herbs.
Fine.
Oh, and steer clear
of Mt. Cangwu.
Got it.
Bye!
Take care.
Hongning chatted
to our radishes again the other day.
Yesterday
I saw her talking
to a rock by the wall.
That girl...
Oh, stone, dear stone,
some people
just love
to gossip.
Always talking behind others' backs,
no filter at all.
But our Hongning's
quick-witted.
She'll talk to anyone she likes,
and nobody can stop her.
Today the creek
feels colder than usual.
Look at this chunk of ice!
I'll haul it back.
Give my drink stand a fancy twist.
Hurry up!
Wait for me!
Ningmeng.
Wake up!
I told you,
don't call me "Ningmeng" in the street.
Forgot you're not human, sorry.
Never mind,
you wouldn't listen anyway.
See what I've got?
Where'd you nab such a monster block?
Dredged it from the river.
Froze my tail off.
Hongning,
I literally shaved bits of myself
for your herb-lemon mix.
Cheers.
Why are you even sourer than yesterday?
Means I'm riper than yesterday.
Stop ripening
or I'll be out of business.
Those customers have no palate.
They can't appreciate my bathwater.
Bathwater?
You drink it.
Hongning & Ningmeng's herbal jelly.
Tangy, sweet,
and ice-fresh!
Lujiu,
sorry if I woke you.
I'll be on my way.
Slipping down the mountain again?
No,
hardly slipping.
Look,
I openly took a pixie-hunt decree
and came down the mountain.
It's my master's test.
Once I catch enough pixies,
he'll duel me himself.
Did you
steal that decree?
Seriously?
You think
I'm some petty thief?
You're right.
I...
I'm really here to catch demons!
Do what you like,
just not here.
Find another trail.
Why?
Why guard Wang's Village all year?
What treasure's tucked away?
None of your business.
Move, or I won't be so nice.
Want to duel?
If I fight you,
I get punished.
So, no thanks.
Leave now
or I'll have Master
revoke your decree.
Fine, I'm gone.
Your Samadhi Fire's nasty.
I'd rather dodge than roast.
I told you, quit running off.
What?
This is my newest herbal jelly drink.
Want a taste?
It's good.
You're easy on the eyes.
It's on the house.
For free?
Then I'll cool off.
Thanks.
Say,
any strange
happenings in your village?
Strange?
Like what?
Like...
Missing folk,
shady strangers...
Wang's Village
is the safest place around.
You're the oddest face we've seen.
Me?
I'm a cultivator from Mt. Cangwu,
here to wipe out
demons for you.
Demons can cultivate now?
Absolutely.
My master judges no one.
Drink.
How'd you know I'm a demon?
I've spotted demons since I was little,
though
I can't tell what kind you are.
Ice pixie.
Listen,
while resting
in my true form
in the stream,
someone
smashed it,
costing me
200 years of power.
He can't be far.
Well...
I...
This is outrageous!
We'll catch them!
Why's there a block of ice in here?
Fished it out of the river.
Wait...
is this your body?
Confidence, please.
Yes, that's me!
-Help!
-Stop right there!
-You're coming back to Mt. Cangwu.
-Help!
Hongning, run! Go!
Never seen a demon arrest?
Lemon!
So sour!
Hongning, this way.
Careful.
Here.
Easy.
Hongning,
you okay?
I'm fine.
He's right behind.
You go!
What are you talking about?
I'm not leaving you.
I'll draw him off.
I'm just a pixie. It's not worth it.
Rubbish.
You're my best friend.
I'll handle him. Go!
Hongning...
I feel your pixie aura.
No escape!
Hongning,
same as ever.
A friend like you
is all I need.
Trying to flee?
Ningmeng...
Master!
The blazing-fire curse flares up again?
It's nothing.
I quelled a rogue immortal in Ganzhou.
Spent some of my power.
A short rest will fix it.
So the fire wound
truly can't be cured?
I once made a grave mistake.
This is my destined trial.
No medicine can help.
Master,
then please stay in seclusion and heal.
I'll manage
the academy.
Very well.
Hongning...
Don't worry.
From today, we're friends.
From today,
you're my best friend,
and my only friend.
Hongning...
Come to think of it,
fate loves irony.
In your half-dead,
death-seeking state,
you'll never
see her again.
No,
I will see her.
I must.
Elder White Camellia?
Eat him.
Prove your loyalty.
Show me you've truly submitted.
Serve me,
body and soul.
I can't.
I...
I just can't.
Devour your own kind or perish.
No!
I can't do that!
Then
forget about
meeting her.
Hongning...
Living can hurt worse than dying,
yet you cling to life for her.
Hongning,
I'll break out and find you.
You need me.
Wait for me.
Please
wait for me.
Useless!
All this time
and you still can't locate the Matriarch?
Forgive us, General.
Double the troops.
Search every Matriarch Temple
in the NCR.
Flip the Three Realms
if you must.
Bring her back!
General,
both Emperor Stars of Midheaven
are undergoing mortal trials.
It's our
best chance
to rest and rebuild,
not chase the Matriarch.
Fool!
The Matriarch comes from the Fox Sanctum.
To Midheaven,
we're still beasts.
Without her and the Golden Lotus Dew,
Western Sea and Midheaven
would've crushed us
long ago.
Your point is sound.
Typical scholar.
Spread word:
the useless king dies soon.
Beef up patrols.
Find the Matriarch.
At once.
Father faces execution.
How can I keep hiding?
You mean the Sky Fox
released that news on purpose?
In normal days,
he acts reckless,
but he's shrewd.
He won't dare
kill Father outright.
Still,
the NCR dungeon is damp
and cold.
How long can Father last?
I'm wounded
and on the run.
When can I...
Search everywhere!
Where is she?
Rice is up!
Here.
Let me help.
Give it to me.
That girl.
It's getting late
and she still hasn't come back.
Don't worry,
Hongning'll be fine.
Dad,
Mom.
Why so late?
Come.
-Where have you been?
-Sit.
Sit and eat.
Lovely evening.
Let's eat outside.
Good idea.
Your face is a mess.
Dig in.
Here.
Dad, quit fussing
and eat.
You too.
Sweetheart,
why aren't you eating?
Mom, is it odd
I've seen demons
since I was little?
What's odd about that?
I glimpsed a god
giving birth to you.
Ask your dad.
True.
What if I befriend a pixie?
Nothing strange.
Pixies, like people,
come good and bad.
Make friends
with the good ones, right?
Exactly.
And
if my friend's in danger,
should I help?
Who's in danger?
No one.
Just asking.
Eat up.
Dad, have some more.
Mom, you too.
Eat.
[Dad,]
[Mom,]
[my friend's in trouble because of me.]
[He's a good soul]
[and I must save him.]
[Don't worry.]
[I'll stay safe.]
[Take care till I'm back.]
[Love,]
[Hongning.]
I have to help Hongning.
Fox, hey Fox!
I need some help!
I'm stuck here!
Fox!
I'm stuck!
My magic won't budge this!
I can't get out.
Please help me.
Master said: unite,
help,
and keep your word.
Why are you so heavy?
Move!
Okay.
Quite dashing, right?
Matriarch, it's late.
We'll lodge here tonight.
Please excuse me.
[Kunlun?]
Middle-of-nowhere dump.
There's nothing here.
Though the Matriarch
looks somewhat familiar.
[You jinx!]
[Running into you here...]
Decent features.
If mortal girls looked like her,
I'd fall hard.
You're a pixie. She's the Matriarch.
Stop daydreaming.
Why not?
We're both shaped like humans.
But then again...
If she met me,
she'd probably fall for me too.
I can't listen to this anymore.
Who's there?
Evil creature, show yourself!
You're the evil one yourself.
Who are you calling evil?
Good for you.
As a demon,
your transformation skills are quite impressive.
Your fox tail is showing.
And you still claim you aren't a demon?
[The Emperor Star has descended to undergo trials.]
[He has lost his memories,]
yet still acting like a jerk.
So you know me?
Seems I'm quiet famous
in the demon world.
How ridiculous.
You're infamous.
And you are a feisty little fox.
Interesting.
How about I take you as my pet?
How rude!
I'll teach you a lesson!
Anything else to say?
You jerk! Let me out!
Go on, keep talking.
Be good.
Daddy will take you home soon.
Pervert! Let me out!
Let me out right now!
Shut up.
Have you seen a woman
accompanied by a man in black?
Woman?
Man?
Or a nine-tailed fox?
Fox?
What if
I've seen the fox?
What if I haven't?
Answer me.
Fine.
Is it someone
who looks similar to the Celestial Matriarch?
Yes.
I saw her.
She went south.
Let's go.
-Yes.
Trying to run?
Where am I supposed to find Ningmeng?
Excuse me, is that Mt. Cangwu ahead?
It is.
Thanks.
Miss, please wait.
It's Mt. Cangwu ahead.
I know.
You just said it.
I'm afraid you came to the wrong place.
I didn't.
I'm heading to Mt. Cangwu.
You might not know,
but Cangwu Academy forbids female disciples.
If you seek immortality,
you should go to Xuyun Temple instead.
No, I'm not here to cultivate.
I'm looking for someone.
Still not allowed.
Historical records show
Xuyun Temple bars men,
while Cangwu Academy forbids women,
a long-standing rule.
Alright, I get it.
Fellow immortals, thank you for waiting.
Today is Cangwu's sword selection day.
We appreciate your journey here.
Now, please follow me up the mountain.
Great! Let's go!
Let's go.
After you.
[That person looks familiar.]
Whatever.
It has to be me...
Behave yourself.
I only let you out for air
in case you are suffocated.
If you keep acting,
I'll put you back in.
Jerk!
The humiliation I suffer today
will be repaid a hundredfold!
Why do you
keep blabbering
nonstop?
Keep it up, and I'll sell you for money!
Say,
would you fetch a good price?
For a cultivator,
you're so vulgar and money-obsessed.
You'll never achieve immortality.
Seems I must teach you a lesson
to shut you up.
Fine.
What are you doing?
Bro,
it's not as plump
as you said it'd be.
How is this not plump?
I think it's only worth...
How much?
Worth about...
That's it?
That's plenty, bro.
Who'd want fox fur
in this scorching heat, right?
Fox fur?
What do you do for a living?
Me?
I make fur coats.
I skin foxes
and turn them into coats.
There's actually someone like you
in the Northern Celestial Realm?
D-Demon!
Demon!
Don't run!
Listen up,
this is a lesson for you.
Will you skin little animals again?
No, never again!
Now, piss off.
Go.
-My money.
-Get lost.
As a cultivator,
you actually aid the evil!
How am I aiding...
And you called me plump!
I...
Alright, fine.
I am aiding the evil.
I'm utterly wicked.
I'm Bailing the devil,
Mt. Cangwu's top villain.
Good you know it.
So what?
What can you do?
If you don't behave,
I'll silence you with a curse
and sell you back to that skinner!
See how tough you are then!
You...
Move!
Mt. Cangwu is breathtaking.
Really nice.
This place is exceptional.
Better than home.
Perfect for my cultivation.
Know what? My martial arts
are ideal for absorbing the world's spiritual energy.
The guy from earlier...
From earlier?
You've seen me?
I've seen you,
but you've never seen me.
Down the mountain...
Don't remember.
But who'd have thought someone so young
could be so remarkable,
making it this far.
Here?
What do you mean?
That mountain path
was to test immortal affinity,
called "Immortal's Guidance."
Mortals would get lost in the mist
or fail to reach here
for various reasons.
Only those with immortal destiny
can make it here.
You mean I have immortal affinity?
Of course.
I thought I'd be the only one.
Never expected
you'd join me.
Master Wenxin said
those who pass Immortal's Guidance
can proceed to sword selection.
He let us wait here for now.
This is the famed Cangwu Academy.
Upon entering,
you can feel Cangwu's aura.
That mystical?
Absolutely.
All cultivators yearn for Cangwu.
Aside from its supreme immortal arts,
Cangwu people
bear Cangwu soul,
that
indomitable, righteous spirit of the brave,
making its energy purer.
So, like me,
you also prepared
for years before coming, right?
Yes.
I prepared for many years.
Then
what magic power do you have?
I don't.
Do you?
I've mastered such basic spells as demon-slaying
and shapeshifting.
You came with no magic power at all?
I...
Peony, thank you!
Keep my secret.
It's huge.
Where can I find him?
Finally figured it out,
the world's deadliest poison.
Can't let Master find out.
Who is it?
Stop right there!
Stop! Stop!
What is this place?
Why does it feel so familiar?
I-I'm sorry!
I didn't mean to come here...
Are you okay?
Why are you vomiting blood?
How did you get here?
How come you show up?
You...
You know me?
Forgive my rudeness.
Sorry if I offended you.
Who are you?
[She's human in this life.]
[Of course she doesn't remember me.]
[Perhaps it's for the best.]
Why are you dressed like this?
Dressed?
Is it strange?
All men in my village dress this way.
Men?
Can't you tell?
I'm male.
Stop! Don't move!
If I catch you, you'll be sorry.
Master. Master.
Sorry to disturb you.
I just saw this person
trespassing in your secluded area.
You're the Master?
Where did you come from?
Master, let me apprehend him.
Don't! It's a misunderstanding!
Wait.
Why have you come to Cangwu?
I came to seek apprenticeship.
Apprenticeship?
I've loved cultivation since childhood.
Hearing Cangwu is sacred ground,
I journeyed here.
So I came to find you, Master.
You are lying.
Those seeking apprenticeship
all gather outside.
You're clearly
a lying thief.
I'm not lying.
I was just there too!
But everything on Mt. Cangwu
has spiritual energy,
as you know.
I simply followed that energy,
and it guided me here.
You are still lying.
Without dark arts,
how could you reach this place?
You...
If she used forbidden magic,
the sacred flora
would have barred her path.
But...
See?
Master is much more reasonable.
You know what?
When I entered,
the peony flowers
even showed me the way.
That's why I found you so quickly.
It's so meant to be.
Truly an honor.
Now that you see me,
you may leave.
Tiannan, escort her down.
Master, this person is suspicious.
We should interrogate her.
Escort her down.
She is forbidden from ever setting foot here.
Wait.
It took me three whole days
to climb up here.
Those without immortal affinity
are still stranded below.
If I have no immortal affinity,
how could I have reached this far?
Since I have it,
why do you drive me away
for no reason?
Is this how you deal
with things on Mt. Cangwu?
I have my reasons
to send you away.
Then enlighten me.
If you can't explain,
we'll settle it in a fair way.
What do you mean?
Doesn't Mt. Cangwu
have entrance exams?
I demand to take them.
If I pass,
I stay.
If I fail,
I leave on my own.
You...
Master,
it sounds a good point.
Fine.
You may participate in the exam.
If unchosen,
you descend immediately.
Deal.
You must honor your word.
Agreed.
Tiannan, escort her down.
Yes.
Let's go.
Master, I failed you.
Your seclusion is interrupted.
Never mind.
The sword selection will start soon.
Go ahead first.
I'll be there shortly.
Yes.
[Do you know how hard I've tried]
[restraining myself]
[to avoid seeking you?]
[Yet here you appear.]
Aren't you hungry?
How do you have energy for this?
Is it really that delicious?
Watch your tone.
If not for my brilliant memory
of your pitiful
temple state,
I'd think you were
some pampered
palace princess.
With your "brilliant" memory,
even if I admitted it,
you wouldn't comprehend.
Fine.
Then I'll believe you
you are an immortal.
Then you need not
eat the noodles.
Since you are an immortal,
wind and dew should suffice.
Leave
the noodles to an exceptional demon
like me.
Stuff yourself.
Honestly?
You should eat now while you can.
Once locked in the dungeon
of Mt. Cangwu,
no more noodles for you.
You're taking me to Mt. Cangwu?
Or what?
I'm not going.
My fox princess,
can't you tell who's in charge?
Let me clarify.
You're my captured demon.
Where I go,
you follow.
Understood?
This, are we clear?
What's wrong?
I didn't hurt you, did I?
Like you were able to.
What's wrong with you?
Why didn't you tell me?
Let's go.
Where?
Come with me.
Waiter, money's on the table.
Alright.
Collect it.
Give me your hand.
Come on.
No need.
Mortal herbs can't heal my wound.
Better treated than neglected.
So stubborn.
Weren't you taking me to the dungeon?
Why pretend concern now?
Who's concerned?
With your sickly state,
my fellow senior brothers would accuse me
of bullying the weak.
You are
such an ungrateful person.
[The sword selection approaches.]
[Return promptly.]
Sword selection...
Little fox,
prepare to be amazed.
Fool.
Let's go.
I'm to be your consort
to cultivate alongside you.
This time
in the illusion,
though our life was simple,
it brought me true joy
and happiness.
Only then did I realize
the greatest bliss
in this world
is staying with one you love.
So,
will you marry me?
[You loved that red camellia,]
[yet she perished]
[for your sake.]
[You indulged]
[fleeting passions,]
[but what good came of it?]
[Reflect on what you've done.]
[Still my heart, and cultivate in solitude.]