[English subtitles are available]
[Love Never Fails]
[EP08]
Well cared for?
My Empress,
thank you
for the birth of two children.
Two?
Yes.
Jinxiu
and Kunlun.
Stop!
Fairy?
Which fairy?
You are the exalted Celestial Empress.
Don't forget your station.
My station?
Had you remembered yours,
you wouldn't have sired children
with some unknown fairy!
As daughter of the Western Sea,
I'll never acknowledge it.
Stop!
When we wed,
we swore before the Ancestral Gods
to uphold Heaven's Will
and protect natural order.
Jinxiu
bears the Emperor Star's destiny.
Harming him
would defy Heaven's Will!
You really think
you outweigh the Emperor Star?
Defy Heaven's Will,
and I won't spare you.
Heaven's Will?
Sure.
You married me for that,
fathered children for that.
Everything you do now
is for that!
My love for you
means nothing compared to it.
Then why would I care?
Well, I'll sever
all mortal attachments,
devoting eternity to that!
How could I rest easy
if it's not well cared for?
Sir Jinxiu,
take good care.
Ningmeng.
Jiaobo.
Where are you?
Ningmeng.
Hongning!
Jiaobo, Ningmeng!
- Hongning!
You're finally back!
Where have you been?
I searched everywhere.
Hongning, were you captured?
It's a long story.
I went to the Celestial Realm.
- The Celestial Realm?
And got banished back.
What?
Come, I'll explain.
Let's go.
You are telling me
my leaves
are brewed into fine wine
in the Floralia Palace?
Floral Deity loved it.
That makes me shy.
How pathetic.
Hongning,
are there many
celestial fairies above?
Pretty?
Gorgeous!
Really?
But none match my beauty.
I believe so.
By the way,
you mentioned an ascended
white camellia immortal on Mt. Baizhou,
remember?
You mean Baicha? He just came back
Where is he? I'll go find him.
You'd better not.
Why?
It has nothing to do with him.
It's just that place has grown perilous.
Immortals and demons who ventured there
never returned.
That dangerous?
Then I must find him!
Come on.
Since Baicha ascended,
his cultivation
must be far beyond ours.
Maybe
instead of helping, you'd just
get in the way.
No,
I must find him.
Father,
the envoys from East Sea and NCR
have all departed.
They watch
our affairs far too closely.
This is your fault
giving them cause for gossip.
Don't let it happen again.
My apologies.
Report!
What is it?
Strange occurrences
have been frequent at Mt. Baizhou.
Many demons are missing.
Even fairies
who passed through the garden there
never returned.
Likely the white camellia clan
is causing trouble.
Petty demons
can't pose real threat.
Investigate further.
Yes, Sir!
Anyone here?
Don't tell me my fears came true.
Demon?
Demons don't torment their similar kind.
Baicha!
Hongning.
Baicha...
What are you doing here?
What happened?
Why do you look so battered?
Never mind me.
Why are you down here?
Did I put you in trouble?
No, no!
The Floral Deity
sent me to cultivate here.
You haven't told me
why you became like this.
Perhaps this world
has no place for me.
The sunlight and rain denied in heaven
remain out of reach here too.
What are you talking about?
Don't think that way.
You have me
and many friends.
Besides,
the Lantern Festival approaches.
We should be happy.
By the way,
have you heard any strange rumors?
This place has become dangerous.
Many demons and immortals are missing.
No, I haven't.
Really?
Hongning, I have to go now.
See you at the festival.
Then...
be careful!
She's my best friend.
You can't hurt her.
Hurt?
I merely want all female
to experience my suffering.
Shuixian!
Hongning.
Exercising again?
We've been waiting.
Don't tell me
you pulled an all-nighter?
I just woke two hours earlier.
Who knew you'd keep this up?
The laziest girl on Mt. Baizhou reformed.
I'm not lazy.
That one is,
still asleep.
But you...
Sorry,
I drank too much last night.
You know what?
The early worm gets eaten.
Avoid their vigor, strike when they're weary.
Avoid their vigor?
Still get eaten.
Anyway, I've decided
to cultivate hard,
no more slacking.
First time I've heard
of pixies cultivating through jogging.
Hongning.
What exactly did you do up there?
Did you go to the wrong place?
Anyway, I've made detailed plans.
Strengthen my body before cultivation.
Who knew a trip to Celestial Realm
could transform her completely?
It's all because
of the power given by the Floral Deity.
He'll grant me strength.
[I wonder]
[how her cultivation progresses?]
These books should suffice,
enough to study for days.
He promised to supervise me.
But where is he?
[Why do I keep worrying about her?]
[Let's see what the books say.]
Records of Immortal-Demon Romance.
Records of Immortal-Mortal Romance.
Official Chrysanthemum...
What nonsense
does he write all day?
[Chapter one,]
[since the Great Emperor's reign,]
[the hierarchy between immortals and others]
[grew more distinct.]
[Yet love governs all creation,]
[even immortals feel affection.]
[The anecdotes are countless.]
[Fellow immortals,]
[if you've reached this page,]
[you must]
[have romantic quandaries.]
[Should these signs appear,]
[you've likely]
[fallen in love.]
[First,]
[a day apart feels like years.]
[Second,]
[restless, on edge all the time.]
[Third,]
[unpredictable, prone to wild mood swings.]
[Fourth,]
[overthinking, irrational suspicions.]
[Fifth,]
[Blinded by love, unaware of your feelings.]
Not a single symptom matches. Good!
[Jinxiu.]
[Try this wine I brought you.]
What's wrong?
Why do you look so agitated?
Do I?
Your cup doesn't even have tea.
What are you drinking?
I just
couldn't find you anywhere,
figured you were upset,
so came to drink with you.
Celestial Realm Rule 82,
"No stealing."
Return this to Sir Taiyi.
Jinxiu...
My...
My eyes!
Jinxiu.
Where are you going? Jinxiu?
Sir Jinxiu.
[Sir Jinxiu.]
What are you doing?
[What are you doing?]
Do you miss me?
[Do you miss me?]
I miss you so much.
[I miss you so much.]
Focus on cultivation.
No distractions.
[Focus on cultivation. No distractions.]
[My magic art can barely contain]
[this power within him anymore.]
[Must find a solution quickly.]
It's not for kids.
Here, fill the cup.
Hongning is here!
This is my homemade wine.
Very delicious! Try it!
Hi, everyone!
- Hongning!
Over here!
Fill.
Hongning.
Remember me?
I'm Green Tea,
your distant cousin.
Green Tea?
C'mon, what distant cousin?
Impossible!
Same species?
Just trying to cozy up!
Let me tell you all a story!
See
that beautiful cloud eastward?
Though
you can't discern it,
that's Floralia Palace
up there.
At its gates
stands a dun-robed guard,
and he is
Official Chrysanthemum.
Don't underestimate him.
He records countless matters.
Nice! Go on!
And he writes, too!
He can write!
Hongning, tell us more!
More stories, please!
C'mon!
Baicha's been there, too.
Let's have him share his experience!
Baicha, come here!
Don't be shy. Tell us.
Baicha? No way.
Please tell us!
Tell us, please!
Go on, tell them.
I...
Hongning.
Are celestial fruits
all big and sweet?
Yes, they are!
Each one huge and sweet,
every variety tastes amazing.
Hongning.
Do celestial immortals only eat fruits?
No food like ours?
It's not that they don't
eat food...
Baicha...
Better to say the food there is bland.
The popular wine up there Hongning mentioned
is created by me.
Very tasty.
Do immortals eat children?
Just rumors.
Wanna try?
I made flower cakes there,
and I gave all to the Floral Deity.
Oh, yes,
there are so many fairies up there.
They are all beautiful!
Leaving.
See you.
- See you.
- See ya.
Bye.
Goodbye.
Let's go, kids.
How impressive!
Hongning.
Your stories really highlighted
our Lantern Festival!
All thanks to you!
Don't worry.
I'll come help every day
after cultivation.
Baicha.
Baicha,
they invited us
to tell stories
at the festival.
I'll pass.
I only wish
to spend the festival with you.
Sure.
Then it's a deal.
Hongning,
No slacking. Come help.
Coming.
I'll get to work now.
Okay.
Scrub this.
And here.
Alright.
Greeting, Sir Jinxiu.
What brings you here?
I accompanied my father here
for the Celestial Banquet.
I know
you're preparing the banquet,
so came
to offer my help.
You are our guest.
No need to trouble yourself.
It's my pleasure to help.
Sir Jinxiu,
may I ask you something?
Go ahead.
Rumors say you've shown
particular attention to a camellia pixie,
even repeatedly protecting her.
[Jinxiu.]
Why are you here again?
You come here every day.
So do you, Sir Kunlun.
Haven't you been recalled?
Why do you come by here every day?
It's my right to come see my brother.
But you?
I...
What brings you here?
Nothing.
Sir Jinxiu,
Sir Kunlun,
My Lady,
His Majesty summons you three.
- Greetings, Father, Mother.
Greetings, Your Majesties.
Girl,
you've come a long way.
We really appreciate it.
You're so kind.
Since you've trusted us with this task,
we'll definitely take care of it.
Jinxiu,
take good care of her.
Understood.
You're called here
for a joint plan
for the Celestial Banquet.
This grand event is
a celebration for all immortals to
display the splendor of the Celestial Realm.
Previous banquets were our responsibility.
Since we entrust it to you,
make sure to prepare thoroughly.
We obey your decree.
With your wisdom,
I'm confident in the outcome.
I'm flattered.
Father, Mother,
I have a request.
Speak.
I suggest that Kunlun and the Matriarch
collaborate to prepare.
Why?
I must fulfill my duties as the Punisher
and managed the affairs at Floralia Palace.
I can't fully dedicate myself
to the preparation.
Kunlun has proven responsible
overseeing the Wine Garden.
This task suits him well.
Responsible?
He'd probably set
the banquet on fire!
This task will
refine his character.
With the Matriarch's guidance,
success is guaranteed.
Let it be as you say.
Thank you.
[What's wrong with that?]
Being the Matriarch
doesn't make you right!
Shelve your outdated notions!
The Celestial Banquet is sacred.
Adding combat arenas?
What possessed you?
Even if I tolerated this absurdity,
His Majesty wouldn't approve!
Discussions mean
proposing various ideas!
Don't dismiss everything outright!
Discussions require meaningful ideas.
Not nonsense!
Kunlun,
do you truly understand what
the Celestial Banquet represents?
What does it represent?
Should we prepare it
exactly as I dictate?
"Yes, I'll do what you dictate."
Did you think I'd say that?
You tricked me!
Casting a charm spell on me?
You really underestimate me!
You!
The banquet is
your shared responsibility.
Persuade each other and
settle the plans yourselves.
I'll take my leave now.
Persuade?
Why bother?
Force works better!
Hongning,
look!
Hongning.
You cultivate all day,
yet still help with invitations.
I really appreciate it!
Don't mention it.
You organized previous
Lantern Festivals alone.
I should've helped sooner.
Pixies from all over
Mt. Baizhou heard about
your story and
planned to visit you!
You're the pride
of Mt. Baizhou!
We're all basking in your glory!
Really?
I wish the Floral Deity
could attend the festival.
How's that possible?
He's the Punisher
who hunts down demons!
Even if you're close to him,
he'd never come to Mt. Baizhou!
If he showed up here,
we'd all flee in terror!
Besides,
when we celebrate the festival,
the Celestial Realm
holds their own Celestial Banquet!
Celestial Banquet?
Banquet,
and festival.
No conflicts!
Hongning,
I'm off to deliver these invitations!
Deliver a letter to Sir Jinxiu?
He created you himself.
You must know his whereabouts.
But I'm a pixie now.
Trespass into the Celestial Realm…
You're not.
You don't even have a core.
Then what am I?
At most, you're a piece of paper
that can fly to the Celestial Realm.
Alright, I'll try.
This is the supreme art of wind control.
Tomorrow, not a ripple will
mar the water at the banquet.
Let's hope you don't blunder.
Let's check over there.
Just wait!
Sir.
Snowflake nectar?
Sir,
Matriarch just ordered us to
remind you that tomorrow's event
permits no errors.
You must stay sober.
She ordered you to monitor me?
All attendants received
her order.
Sir,
His Majesty commands us
to descend to Mt. Baizhou at once
to investigate the missing demons
before the banquet.
Any further orders?
I'll handle this personally.
Understood!
Excuse me,
have you seen Baicha?
The white camellia pixie?
[You've come at last!]
[camellia pixie... ]
[No,]
[soon you'll become Shuixian.]
Who are you? What do you want?
[This is an illusionary realm.]
[Oh no!]
[Hongning!]
Sir, it's been too long.
Shuixian,
you're demoted to pixie for breaking rules.
Yet you create illusions
trapping innocents in your past!
Release them now!
Those who enter my realm
must live out their fates
by my rules.
Save them yourself
within my illusionary realm!
[A millennium ago,]
[Envoy Narcissus of Floralia Palace]
[fell to the mortal realm]
[during an immortal tribulation.]
[She vanished without trace.]
[Where am I?]
Last one.
Uproot this, and we're finished!
[Don't uproot me! Please!]
Wait.
Leave this narcissus.
Young Master,
leaving it will
hinder the garden's replanting.
Delay the replanting.
You can enjoy your wine in the backyard.
Your pay remains unchanged.
Thank you so much!
We'll take our leave.
[That was close!]
[Who is this man?]
[Why save me?]
Such perfect blooms.
It'll be a shame to uproot you.
[He's actually handsome.]
Did you
sense my intentions?
Young Master!
Young Master,
the Chu family proposes marriage again.
Decline it.
But…
That's weird.
These flowers sway without wind.
I'll fetch temple monks to
look into this tomorrow.
Why fear?
A pixie guest might
liven things up.
What cursed realm
lacks even water?
Stop!
There you are.
You weren't sleeping.
You tricked me.
A little pixie after all, huh?
I'm not!
I'm Shuixian, Envoy Narcissus.
More like a trickster.
I didn't lie.
I stranded here after a failed tribulation.
Just need temporary shelter.
I trust you.
You trust so easily?
What if I'm truly some evil demon?
Wouldn't you fear me?
Immortals, demons...
what difference does it make to me?
Stay if you wish,
but agree to my terms,
Little Narcissus.
What terms?
Indenture contract?
Press your fingerprint here.
After that,
you can stay freely.
I'm only staying a few days!
Why shackle me with this?
You immortals live millennia.
I'll be dust in a century.
This scrap of paper costs you nothing
unless you refuse.
What happens then?
You will die.
When your revert to your true form,
I'll have the cook make you into a dish.
You can also flee.
Just so you know,
only my place
in the whole town
has water source for your cultivation.
Seek other towns?
You'll wither first
before you find water resources.
You…
Done.
I don't even know your name yet.
Duan Fei.
Duan Fei?
You've signed the contract.
From now on,
you'll serve me tea,
attend to my every need,
bloom daily for me,
and keep me company.
Your body and soul
belong to me.
So, you still plan to eat me?
That's wrong.
I want you to think of me every day.
Every day?
We immortals live for millennia.
What of it?
I'll only burden you for mere decades.
A fair trade.
You mean I must
remember you until
your mortal death?
Precisely.
Fine.
I'm going to sleep.
Hold on.
Lull me to sleep first.
How?
Sing a song.
I can't.
Share a drink, then.
I'm not allowed.
Tell a story, at least.
Just leave.
I'll tell a story.
Proceed.
I was once Envoy Narcissus
of Floralia Palace,
a place that
governs all blossoms' fates
with strict rules.
I never descended nor
met mortals before.
You're the first mortal I've met.
In Floralia Palace…
Jinxiu isn't here?
Then where did he go?
You've guarded
this gate for centuries
yet know nothing!
Absurd!
Open up.
Fine.
Jinxiu!
Consider yourself lucky!
[This is so boring!]
[No entertainment!]
Sir...
Greetings, Sir.
What brings you here?
State your purpose.
The NCR Matriarch requests audience
with Sir Jinxiu.
I'll decline her request.
Wait!
Let her in.
Yes, Sir.
Don't mention my presence here.
Understood.
Greetings, Sir.
If no urgent matter,
best depart.
Sir,
are you unwell?
Emm...
Tea scalded my throat.
Nothing serious.
Last time you praised
our snowflake nectar.
I brought some
for you this time.
How devoted you are—
always bearing gifts for me.
This nectar soothes throats.
How about drinking some now?
Don't bother.
I brewed this personally.
If you refuse to drink,
I will stay here forever.
Then...
I'll drink.
You tricked me!
This cheap trick
reeks of desperation!
Your own tricks stink worse!
Neglecting the Celestial Banquet
to laze about!
Any problem?
The whole celestial realm knows
every palace of Jinxiu's
has a seat for me!
Resting at my place isn't lazing!
You however,
intruding on this place uninvited
like you're already
his consort!
None of your concern!
Mind your business!
Your "heroic" act of
saving a pixie is widely known.
I can't help feeling embarrassed for you!
So what?
I did save that pixie!
I should do that!
Besides,
you're not my consort...
Stop meddling!
Cease such speech against celestial rules!
[Sir, urgent news!]
[Sir Jinxiu is trapped in Mt. Baizhou!]
Jinxiu's trapped!
[Wait! Where are you going?]
Jinxiu!
[Stop!]
Luyao, this place is dangerous!
Return at once!
Duan Fei...
You're under narcissus' spell!
Why didn't you wait for me?
Why should I wait?
I'm here to save Jinxiu!
Don't fall under the spell!
You shouldn't forget me!
How could you?
[I've sealed your five senses.]
[The spell can't influence you now.]
[This place is strange.]
[I shall scout carefully.]