[English subtitles are available]
[Love Never Fails]
[EP07]
Hongning?
Sir,
you really came.
Stop right there.
This is dripping wet.
Did something
threaten you?
No.
I was trying to chat
with the Lilybell,
but it ignored me.
I regret ever giving you that plant.
It climbed out by itself!
Why talking with your back?
Think about it.
Why do I
always find you in bath?
You like bathing that much?
Can you imagine if...
Bathing?
You mean soaking?
Back on Mt. Baizhou,
I loved hot springs with the pixies.
So comfy.
So you bathe
with others down here?
Before my human form,
they'd dunk me in springs
and rain pools.
Next time I'll take you.
By Floralia Palace law,
Hongning may
bathe only at midnight,
alone, and must never
mind-link me while doing it.
Break it again
and I'll seize your Lilybell.
Since when is that a rule?
Just now.
You're being mean.
Wait!
What now?
The herbal mix I made for you
is ready.
I can walk by myself.
Let's go.
Hongning, how dare you!
Well...
Covering my eyes is such a pain.
See no evil.
It's etiquette.
Why so many rules?
Mortal or immortal,
desire breeds want,
want breeds chaos.
The Northern Celestial Realm
set codes to curb it.
Shared rules for all.
Cultivation starts by
restraining desire.
Even gods must.
Chaos turns gods
into demons,
and Heaven strikes them down.
How did you
get hurt so badly?
It...
It must hurt terribly.
No one
has ever wept for me.
Have you ever cried for anyone?
Human,
demon,
or god?
Sir,
those wounds are backlash
from the Oceanic Codex.
These herbs
can't heal you.
They'll inflame the cut,
especially the Baihe nectar.
It's all right.
All right?
You refuse my
celestial remedies
yet prefer this?
Well,
she put her heart into it.
Romance makes poison
of any draught.
What...
Wait.
That is good medicine.
Good medicine indeed.
Still, the backlash
grows worse. How strange.
Don't be scared.
This is dew.
Drink it now.
Slow down.
Easy.
You've been dry so long.
Drink slowly.
Here's fresh soil too.
You can have it.
You're a red camellia?
We are from the same clan.
I'm a camellia pixie.
Pixie?
You passed the trial?
No,
I broke Heaven's rules
and got caught.
A pixie here
in Floralia Palace.
So,
where did you come from?
Mt. Baizhou.
I'm from Mt. Baizhou too.
The Baicha
who ascended next door,
that was you?
Yes.
But you're already a flower immortal.
Why treat you like this?
I reached Heaven
to claim my immortal register...
Thank you.
Where are you from?
I'm Baicha,
from Mt. Baizhou.
Mt. Baizhou,
dens of demons?
Yes.
Wait there.
Move.
My turn.
Thank you.
I...
Please,
my register...
Cousin!
You're Ziteng?
I am.
Kept me waiting forever.
Forgive me.
Tribulation was hard.
I'm late.
Thank you, Envoy Apricot.
From this day
you're fairy Ziteng.
Come, into Floralia Palace.
Envoy Apricot,
well,
what about my register?
Still here?
The last register is taken.
Nothing left for you.
Off you go.
Why?
Passing the trial
should earn a register.
Who said so?
Heaven's decree.
The decree also says
pixies can't become gods.
Passing the trial
means nothing
if fate says no.
It said no to you.
Run along.
So I lack that fate
yet...
this pixie gets hers?
That "pixie"
is now fairy Ziteng.
One more word
and I'll throw you out.
Come on.
That Apricot Envoy was cruel.
She had no right.
I wouldn't leave,
so I hid in the Withered Garden.
No dew, no rain.
I withered
until you revived me.
Don't worry,
with me around
no one will bully you anymore.
They look down on me
for being a pixie.
I thought ascension
would shed that label.
Turns out,
nothing changed.
Why are we lesser?
You're not wrong.
It's them.
We have hands
and feet like they do,
only our
homes differ.
Why are they deemed superior?
I thought
you stayed
because you
revered the gods.
I'm staying,
but not to worship.
I owe a debt.
What debt?
The Floral Deity once saved me.
I must repay him.
Don't worry.
He'll see
justice done for you.
No,
I broke Heaven's rules
by hiding here.
He won't spare me.
Then what?
You can't live here forever.
If you're scared,
I'll sneak you
back to Mt. Baizhou.
But...
I still want to be immortal.
You feel it's wrong too,
don't you?
If that's your choice,
follow your heart.
Every flower
should bloom
where it wishes.
I don't know how to help yet,
but whenever you need me,
I'll be here.
No one
has ever cared for me
this way.
To think we would meet here.
Don't worry.
From now on,
we're friends.
you're my best friend,
and my only friend.
Sir.
What is he looking for?
He's been circling an hour.
Wonder what he's after.
Greetings, Sir.
What are you looking for?
One blossom on this magnolia is missing.
Forgive me.
Magnolia Fairy is still away,
so I'm tending it.
It's all right.
Magnolias are fussy.
Still, in Flora Grove
a gap spoils the view.
Sir,
please,
don't trouble yourself...
It's okay.
A true Floral Deity handles every pot.
No.
Let go.
You are Floral Deity.
Leave it to me.
Then...
let's go together.
Very well.
Hongning,
look who's here.
Shaoyao.
Sir,
you've come to watch me train?
No,
just delivering this pot.
Not to watch me cultivate?
Oh, just this one pot?
Shaoyao, what about you?
I'm also here to drop one off.
Two people
for a single plant?
Does any law say
only one courier per pot?
Guess not.
All right, I'll place it inside.
It bloomed fine.
Why banish it to the Withered Garden?
One blossom short.
It looked odd among thousands.
True.
The Flora Grove is vast.
I'll take my leave.
Sir!
Yes?
Well,
take care.
A white camellia pixie!
Leave Hongning out of this.
She has nothing to do with this.
I rescued him.
No,
I found him in the Withered Garden.
I restored his energy.
White camellia pixie,
this palace is tightly guarded.
How did you slip inside?
I admit my crime.
Sir,
he ascended by passing trial.
The truth is...
Apricot Envoy stole his register!
That's a lie!
Sir,
that wasn't true.
I never met him!
Sir,
Hongning speaks the truth.
I once braved lightning at Mt. Baizhou,
seeking to change my fate,
to join the immortals.
But sadly,
though I passed the heavenly trial,
in the end,
the Envoy, for selfish gain,
blocked me outside Floralia Palace.
I swear, I speak the truth.
White camellia pixie,
you did pass the trial,
but without a register
you're still a pixie,
now hiding in the Withered Garden.
By Heaven's law
you should be expelled from Heaven.
Sir.
Envoy Apricot,
any explanations?
He comes from Mt. Baizhou,
a place swarming with demons.
And now he's skulking in the Garden.
His intention is unknown.
I only meant to protect the Court.
To stop future disasters.
Consideration ends by the third violation
You've abused
Heaven's code
and misused registers.
Such arrogance
cannot be tolerated!
As of now
you're stripped of rank,
demoted to junior immortal,
and assigned to guard Flora Grove.
Mercy, Sir!
A pixie hidden in Floralia Palace
shames us all.
From this moment,
no one is to gossip outside these walls.
Break the rule and face punishment.
Understood.
Envoy Plum,
escort Kunlun and Hongning.
They're not
to take a single step out.
Yes, Sir, your highness.
Envoy Apricot.
Envoy Plum.
Envoy Plum,
wrong title.
I'm just a junior immortal now.
Sir Jinxiu is furious.
That's why he punished you so harshly.
Lay low for now.
Reflect and stay out of trouble.
Don't stir up more mess.
So you came to laugh at me?
Unlike you,
I was born low, and had to
fight for every ounce of respect.
Excuse me?
I was born a pixie,
clawed my way up here.
In this Floralia Palace,
everyone calls me "Envoy",
yet snickers
at my bloodline.
You're overthinking.
Envoy Plum,
you grew up in this palace.
You have no idea
how hard the climb is
for us groundlings.
Since I took this post
I've been strict and fair,
exactly what the
his Highness preached.
He's the one bending rules now,
not me.
You're too stubborn.
Yes,
stubborn, not slippery.
Gods are gods,
pixies are pixies.
Reward and punishment must stay clear.
Yet he
took that red camellia pixie to Heaven
and tolerated a white camellia bloom up here.
I won't let it slide.
Baicha.
Hongning?
How bold!
How dare you block the way?
Seize her!
I...
-Stop!
-I...
Greetings, Sir Kunlun.
Leave Baicha with me.
He's due at the Demotion Pool.
A short wait won't hurt.
Heaven's penalty can't stall.
Baicha isn't on the pool list.
His Highness added him off-record.
If Sir Taiyi hears this,
Baicha would be dead.
Difficult old man.
Tell me,
would delaying
the penalty be worse,
or defying me?
Uh...
Baicha,
I'm sorry.
I failed to protect you.
No at all.
I'm the one who got you into trouble.
If it weren't for you,
I'd be dead in the Withered Garden already.
But you're denied access to immortal.
It's so unfair.
They're immortals, and I'm just a pixie.
That's my fate.
Hongning.
Thank you for saving my life.
I'll remember your kindness
for the rest of my life.
What are you going to do now?
What will happen to him down in Demotion Pool?
Demotion Pool
is the place to punish wrongdoing immortals.
They will be no longer immortals after demotion.
But he's not even an immortal yet.
Then he will be demoted to be a pixie
that can never upgrade again.
Hongning.
Trust my brother's decision.
Thanks to you, I'm lucky enough to
still be a pixie.
I'm not obsessed with becoming immortal anymore.
You have immortal roots
and the bond with
Floral Deity.
Work hard on your cultivation.
You will be the first immortal from Mt. Baizhou.
After that,
I'll be proud that I have an immortal friend.
Baicha.
Sir Kunlun.
It's the time now.
Alright, alright.
Take him now.
Hongning!
I'll pray for you
whenever I can.
Baicha!
Take care of yourself!
Sir Taiyi.
The sentence has been carried out today.
Seven immortals have been deprived of power
by Demotion Pool.
And twelve evil spirits were
sent to the Kylin Lair
waiting for Sir Jinxiu to punish.
Give me the list of these seven immortals.
Yes, sir.
That's all?
How dare you
harbor evil spirits
and obstruct the execution?
Mercy, Sir Taiyi!
I didn't!
Guards!
Take him to the Demotion Pool!
Mercy! Sir Taiyi!
I was just following orders!
Mercy!
Mercy! Sir Taiyi!
Envoy Apricot was right.
These camellias
are really something.
Sir Jinxiu.
Baicha was taken?
Yes.
Did Hongning go with him?
Don't worry.
She was taken
back to the Withered Garden
and locked up.
There's no way she can
sneak out again.
But...
but no one could
stop Sir Kunlun
from getting in.
Sir Jinxiu.
Speak.
Hongning and Sir Kunlun
were arrested by Celestial Military.
No lies and excuses!
NCR and the East Sea
complained
that you harbor
that white camellia pixie.
The prohibition of pixies in Celestial Realm
is not to be violated.
Who gave you the nerve to do that?
What's done is done
and he was taken to Demotion Pool.
I know those seniors
have hated me for long
and gave me hard time by this excuse.
What more do you want?
You've really grown up, haven't you?
Since your release,
I thought you had learned your lesson.
Before long,
you've made such a big mistake again!
You think you can
get away with everything?
Of course not!
Since I was born,
you have been keen
on punishing me.
I know you've
looked down on me,
thinking I'm an eyesore.
Why don't you
send me to the Demotion Pool
or Kylin Lair? That will
end all your troubles!
Enough!
Father, Mother.
Jinxiu.
You've come just in time.
Your brother befriended
evil pixies
and messing up Floralia Palace.
You're in charge of the Palace.
Tell me what happened
and punish him harshly
without mercy!
Please rest assured.
I will punish him severely.
However, he has got nothing to do
with the harboring.
It's my responsibility.
What do you mean?
Father.
Baicha was qualified for becoming immortal,
yet he missed the time to register
and was stranded in Withered Garden.
Now he's been expelled.
In that case,
that's the end of the ruckus.
Baicha might be pardoned for being stranded,
but rules are rules.
His clan will be banned from
blooming for a hundred years.
Your Majesty.
There's another pixie
in the Floralia Palace.
What?
There's another?
Bring her up!
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, Baicha was...
Silence!
Before you're
spoken to.
Jinxiu.
It's you who brought
this camellia to Celestial Realm?
Yes.
Celestial Realm forbids pixies.
As the Punisher,
how dare you violate the law?
I have seen the error of my ways.
I got carried away.
But this camellia pixie
is innocent.
May Your Majesty...
Enough!
I'm tired of excuses.
I'll punish you for breaking rules.
It's just that I never expected you
to be so ridiculous!
It seems that Kunlun's
disruptive behaviors come from his brother!
Tell me.
Does she have anything to do with
that previous camellia?
You indulge her so much.
Does that also mean
that you like her?
Father.
She was brought here as a warning
and to take punishment for her
violation beneath.
Nothing personal.
I didn't expect her to
make such a big mistake
instead of reflecting on herself.
It's all my fault.
As the Punisher,
it's my duty to take the blame.
I'll punish her to the mortal world
immediately
Jinxiu.
[Go and get your own 81 Celestial Punishments]
[according to the rules.]
[Yes, Sir.]
[You are the Punisher of Celestial Realm,]
[an example to the immortals]
[and the embodiment of rules.]
[You can't afford]
[to make a single mistake.]
[Do you understand?]
I apologize for my error.
Didn't Sir Taiyi know
that you got such serious injuries?
He hits you badly every time.
It's alright.
Sir.
Hongning should leave now.
Official Chrysanthemum.
Out.
I'll take my leave.
Hongning.
Shaoyao.
Give me some more time.
Be quick.
Hongning.
If you get
bullied beneath,
turn to any peony of my clan,
and they will help you.
Thank you, Shaoyao.
These are
nectar and wine from cotton rose,
hibiscus blossom and sunflower.
These are
the farewell letters
from the Morning glories.
They should've seen you off, but they're taken to
rebuild Flora Grove now.
I can't take these.
They're too valuable.
They took you too much efforts.
I can't.
You must take it.
If you don't,
they'll blame me.
Take it.
Okay.
Thank you, Shaoyao.
Hongning.
You've helped me so much,
but I'm not able to do the same for you.
I'm so sorry.
That's not true!
I came here, got to know you
and become friends with you.
It's the best thing that happened to me.
Really?
I'll try to make some mistakes
to be demoted to see you.
Don't!
You should keep cultivating.
Think about it.
Maybe we have chance to
reunite at the Floralia Palace in the future.
You're right.
Then I'll stay here
and wait for you.
It's about time.
I'll leave now.
Look after yourself.
Take care.
Stay well.
You can go back.
I can take care of the rest.
Yes.
Come on.
Don't be so upset.
Pity that you haven't finished your punishment,
but don't worry,
I'll be up here
to punish you
after you go back.
I'll be watching you.
Official Chrysanthemum.
Can I see Sir Jinxiu
one more time before I go?
I'm begging you.
Can't you behave?
Do you know how much trouble
you've caused him this time?
But I couldn't just stand
and watch Baicha suffering.
You're just a pixie.
Why do you always have to
challenge the conventions
of the immortals?
You know?
The immortals rule the Celestial Realm.
Their rules are above all.
You're a just an insignificant pixie.
Why do you have to go against the authority?
Listen.
Don't
blame Sir Jinxiu this time.
He's doing this
for you.
Under that circumstance,
if he hadn't done so,
you
might have been put into Kylin Lair
and been annihilated.
I understand.
I just want to see him one more time.
If I don't, the next time we meet
will be a long, long,
long time from now.
You understand?
You don't!
I don't think
you've ever understood!
You don't.
Sir Jinxiu is the Emperor Star!
Once passing trial,
he will be back to Midheaven.
Even though you could come back,
you couldn't see him.
What are you doing?
You're going to summon him by this?
That's a high-level spell.
Unless it's authorized by Sir Jinxiu himself,
even Emperor and Empress
can't summon him at random.
Don't you understand? I tell you...
Sir Jinxiu.
My apologies, Sir Jinxiu.
Why waste your chance to summon?
Sir Jinxiu,
I have something cooking on stove.
Could you take her to the Gate for me?
The Lilybell is for you
to call for help in times of trouble.
I'll come wherever I am.
Don't use it for no reason.
Sir Jinxiu.
Why do you look so bad?
Are you being punished again?
I'm okay.
Sorry.
I didn't realize the consequences.
It's my bad.
You did nothing wrong.
The celestial rule isn't wrong, either.
You wanted justice for Baicha.
But the celestial rule
is for keeping order
for the Realms.
Will you miss me
after I'm gone?
Leaving
is for your own good.
But I'm going to miss you.
Hongning.
If I say
you have chance to become a junior immortal
if you keep cultivating yourself,
will you do it?
Will that enable
me to see you?
You could stay in the Floralia Palace.
Really?
Then I will do that!
No matter how hard it is,
as long as I can see you again
and stay at Floralia Palace,
I'm afraid of nothing!
Sir Jinxiu.
I'm leaving now.
Can you give me a hug?
Work hard on your cultivation.
Then let's say goodbye.
Wait.
I'm not sure I can protect you every time
when you in mortal world.
This Camellia Hairpin
can transform into a sword
and protect you in danger.
Sir Jinxiu.
Why are you so nice to me?
It's time to go.
Sir Jinxiu.
Wait for me!
Hongning.
You will become immortal.
Be quick!
What are you thinking?
Alright, alright.
Just be quick.
Look!
It's... it's...
Where?
it's Baicha, the immortal!
No way.
He's home by now.
It must be him.
It's him!
Yes, it's him!
Sir Baicha.
What an attitude
as an aristocrat!
Sir Baicha, where are you going?
Back on cards.
Come on.
Your Majesty.
The servant in Nebula Pavilion said that
Emperor Stars are still in the mysterious clouds.
There's no other change yet.
Alright. Leave.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Come out.
Your Majesty.
How's Envoy Apricot doing?
Your Majesty,
she's been punished in Flora Grove.
Sir Jinxiu was really irritated this time.
I'm afraid
she won't be able to
greet you for a while.
I knew her bossiness
would get her in trouble one day.
She is reckless.
I will remind her.
I'll do my best
to serve Your Majesty these days.
You're a clever girl.
What about Kunlun?
Sir Kunlun is very powerful.
He disappeared right after returning to the Palace.
I was unable to detect him.
Fine.
If he's up to something,
he'll make it known.
You'd better concentrate
on Jinxiu.
The princes are your care.
I'll come to report as frequent as possible.
Okay, you can leave.
Yes, Your Majesty.
"My care".
If I don't,
how can I rest assured?