[English subtitles are available]
[Love Never Fails]
[EP21]
Master,
no clue why, but the pixies
in the dungeon
are getting hyped lately.
I'm worried
there's some strange
energy at play.
No need to worry.
I'll set up a barrier.
Tell the disciples to
go grab their protection charms.
Yes.
Any word from Lujiu?
He sent a communication talisman,
said not to worry about him,
he's already on his way back,
we'll see him soon.
Good.
Ningmeng,
where'd you find all these pretty flowers?
Pretty, right?
Got them down the hill.
Once I finish this,
I'll give it to you
on my wedding day.
Never seen anyone make this.
What's it even for?
To pass on some joy, of course!
Guess you just don't get it.
Ningmeng…
thanks for sticking with me
through two lifetimes.
That means a lot to me.
Alright then.
So just tell me,
who's better,
me, or Jiaobo?
You're both great.
You say that while holding my flowers?
Alright,
you win, you're better, happy?
That's more like it.
Lately,
a lot's been coming back to me.
I even remembered that
bedtime story you used to tell me!
Which one?
A crane pays debt?
I remember every single word!
Nope, I can't cry!
I'm just really happy!
I've gotta go tell Jiaobo, our dear
Hongning finally got her memories back!
She has to come to your wedding!
Don't run too fast!
[Where's Hongning?]
[She'll be here soon!]
Mom, Dad.
Hongning!
She's here!
-Hongning!
-Auntie!
Auntie, what brings you here?
Came to find my lost daughter-in-law!
Master of Cangwu Academy invited us over.
He said he's marrying you!
Hongning,
on the way here, your auntie said
she's covering the whole wedding,
proposal, betrothal, and all!
That's right!
Mom, Dad…
You're not mad I
didn't tell you such big news
sooner, are you?
Silly girl,
all your Mom cares about
is whether
you're doing okay,
if your future husband really loves you.
Nothing else matters!
Exactly!
Just look at this lovely family!
Hongning,
your situation's a bit special.
Normally I'd just grab your birth charts
and pick a date.
But,
none of the fortune-tellers
dared read your Master's birth chart,
three of them turned it down!
How am I supposed to pick a date?
Didn't dare read it?
Yeah!
They said reading it would be
prying into heaven's secrets,
and it'd cost them their lives!
What's your Master's deal?
Hongning.
Jinxiu,
come, sit!
No need to be formal!
Uncle, Auntie,
I brought the wedding dress.
See?
That's my son-in-law!
It's…
all silk!
Mom, it's gorgeous!
Must've cost a lot!
Let's not go overboard!
What do you know?
It's our son-in-law's heartfelt gesture!
Besides,
Hongning's worth it!
Still, no need to splurge!
Hongning,
do you like it?
It's beautiful.
If it's from you,
I love it.
Glad you do,
I worked hard on it.
By the way, Master,
your birth chart's unreadable.
So…
when should we set the date?
How about
the seventh of July?
That's a lucky day!
Let's go with that!
Good pick!
Lucky day!
Perfect!
Great!
[Here we go!]
[A bit to the left.]
[Alright.]
Tie it tight.
One more loop.
Okay!
Let's set it down over there.
Shouhou.
What a name.
[Little Fox,]
[wish you were here.]
No!
It…it lit itself!
[Don't!]
I was wrong!
Enough!
It's a big day,
no fighting!
Yes, Master.
-Let's go!
-Master, look at him!
No respect
-at all!
-You guys…
Honey,
can't you stop pacing
and help me out here?
What can I do?
My girl's getting married,
can't say I'm thrilled.
Don't be like that!
What do you want me to say?
Even if he's a deity,
I still don't want to let her go!
Look at you!
You really are Ningmeng!
Don't touch me!
I'm just curious.
Hey,
you've been
circling me for ages!
You're gonna wear a hole in my fur!
Don't move!
You're giving me goosebumps!
Hongning,
you really do
talk to fruit
and animals!
I do!
I said it when we were kids,
you guys just never believed me.
Wait…
they're all pixies?
So our whole village
is crawling with pixies?
Yep.
Even my big black dog
talked to you?
Your dog's not a pixie,
it's just a spirit.
Then…
Hongning,
before I leave,
can I get a few
pixie-banishing charms?
Sure!
I'll give you a few to stay safe.
But don't mess with them,
they're good pixies,
they won't hurt you.
Still thinking about Black Serpent?
He didn't even
say bye after
all that care I gave him!
He should've said something, right?
Living alone at the bottom of cliffs
for years left him a bit twitchy,
don't take him seriously.
Ningmeng,
Jiaobo…
still won't come to my wedding?
I never knew she was so stubborn!
I told her to come early and help out,
she called here some kind of
sacred no-go zone, shouldn't stick around.
She just kept dragging her feet!
Took me forever to talk her into it!
She…
should be on her way now.
Master.
Where are you going?
Hongning's trying on…
her wedding dress,
I'm bringing her some jewelry.
Jewelry?
You can't go in!
Why not?
You're a guy, how could you go in there?
Do Lemon Pixies even have gender?
Fair point.
Give it to me.
Nope,
I… I'm going.
I'm her bestie!
Give it!
Then…
Go.
Back to sleep.
Go on!
Is it a bit tight?
Maybe I've gained weight lately?
Do I look okay in this?
Try it and see.
Sir!
Are you still
that same camellia pixie
I met?
Why so shy now?
I'll go try it on then.
[Do I look good?]
[Can I be your Empress?]
[When you like someone,]
[you wanna see them all the time.]
[Just seeing you makes me happy.]
[I wanna stay with you forever.]
[Sir, I'm not just]
[grateful to you,]
[I've fallen for you too.]
[You said at the Celestial Floralia]
[if I become an immortal,]
[you'd make me as your Empress.]
[Don't go back on that.]
Is it bad looking?
Yeah, I guess
it's not quite me.
You look
really amazing!
Sir,
are you sure about this?
I'm just a mortal,
if we marry,
what about the Celestial Monarch and Celestial Empress?
Don't worry,
I'll figure it out.
Really?
I promise
I'll convince them.
What's wrong?
It just feels…
everything's so unreal.
In the past life,
I tried so hard
to be your Empress.
Could it really be so easy now?
Not in this life.
I'll always be here, protecting you.
I'll never break my word again.
Lujiu?
Lujiu,
when did you get back?
You…
How's it going with Little Fox?
When did you start caring about me?
I just wanted to ask
how's Little Fox doing?
She should be doing well.
After all, she's home now.
She has her family,
and her friends there.
True.
She probably doesn't need us.
Is this it?
Even though he's a deity,
he's really broke!
Can't even get a proper
sheep or cow!
Right!
When I married you,
at least I brought two ducks!
Yeah!
Well,
the Cangwu Academy
looks quite impressive!
Stop the ducks!
Is this really our Master?
I'm not so sure anymore.
See,
when someone's in love,
[their brain really does turn to mush!]
[That's scary!]
I really wanna know
what ridiculous things
our Master will do for Hongning!
[Seems like he's done all he can.]
What's Master doing now?
Who knows?
[Hongning,]
do you mortals not give silk when you marry,
but ducks instead?
[The ducks are coming your way!]
Master, I'll help you!
Another fool!
I wish my Little Fox were here.
Then I could
catch ducks with her.
The third one!
Lujiu doesn't want to return with me.
In the vast NCR,
you're the only friend I have left.
[Search over there!]
Where are you going?
No!
You can't go alone,
it's too dangerous!
They have the Deity-slaying Talisman!
Where is the sinner, Luyao?
[Speak!]
Stay alive…
[Matriarch shouldn't have gotten too far.]
[Chase!]
[Boring.]
[Why are they locking me up here,]
[learning dance and embroidery?]
[Why are they]
[keep telling me about responsibilities]
[and duties I don't understand?]
[Are you playing with me?]
[My name is Luyao,]
[you're my shadow]
[and my first friend.]
[What's your name?]
[You can't speak?]
[You look like a mirror to me.]
[You're a magical mirror.]
[Could I call you Qijing?]
[Great!]
[I have a friend now!]
Don't worry.
I'll make sure to take you home.
You're my first friend,
my only…
and best friend.
Are you really marrying him tomorrow?
Why do you still believe that
he's coming back to marry you
and keep his promise?
Are you out of your mind, Hongning?
You're a pixie,
he's spent decades finding you,
he must have some other agenda!
If he wanted to catch me,
he would've done it already.
Do you know
you might be the Demon King?
Demon King?
The black snake you met in the Dragon's Abyss
is an ancient divine beast.
It was the mount of the Demon King
Fuzhu from ten thousand years ago.
But it called you its master.
So,
it's very possible you're the Demon King's bloodline.
Impossible.
How is that impossible?
Do you know how quickly you cultivated
in Floralia Palace?
You crossed immortal tribulation
easier than ordinary immortals too!
I noticed then that
your power is extraordinary.
And with the black snake calling you master,
I'm even more convinced!
But I've never heard of
the Demon King!
And Master never mentioned it!
There are so many hidden secrets!
Just because we don't know them
doesn't mean they don't exist!
The power of the Demon King can
command all pixies in the Three Realms.
He wants to use you
to gather all the pixies
and then wipe them out!
You're talking nonsense!
If Master was like that, why
would all the pixies in Cangwu Academy
have a chance to cultivate?
Those are pixies
blessed with divine fate!
Typical of them,
ranking pixies like some celestial caste system!
Blessed pixies get divine perks,
while the rest get purged!
Your Master
acts all noble,
but he's really just a bloody executioner!
The gap between immortals and pixies
has existed for a long time.
Master can't bear all of this alone!
Are you deliberately this oblivious?
I risked my life
to return to your side from the Kylin Lair
because I want to lead all the pixies
to fight against the Celestial Realm!
The Dragon's Abyss is bottomless.
I risked death
to bring you Memory Spring,
just want you to remember
you used to be a camellia pixie!
You were killed by those immortals,
don't you get it?
You're blinded by hate!
You've got it out for all immortals,
you know that?
You're the one who's been blinded,
not me.
Don't you get it?
I really like you.
That's not me,
it's your headcanon.
So…
you're really choosing to
side with the immortals?
I'm not siding with the immortals,
I'm following my heart!
I'm getting married.
If you wish me well,
stay for a drink.
If not…
then go.
Fine.
Alright.
Hongning,
you'll pay for
what you chose today.
Baicha!
It's really you!
It's been a while!
How have you been?
You came for…
Hongning's wedding, right?
I was just leaving.
What's wrong?
You don't look happy.
Hongning and Jinxiu
shouldn't be together.
Why not?
What's wrong with them?
I think
they're perfect for each other!
The groom is a
Floral Deity from the Celestial Realm,
future Celestial Monarch!
And the bride is
our Mt. Baizhou's pride!
They make a great match!
Immortals and pixies can't be together!
Why not?
Love can
break any rule!
[Besides, they've been]
[through so much,]
and finally made it!
We should be happy for them!
And,
Sir Jinxiu's amazing!
[There's nothing he can't handle!]
[With his power,]
how could pixies like us…
who can't even cultivate
stand a chance?
What's going on with you?
Master,
I found it while patrolling.
No sign of life when I got there.
Don't let word get out.
Yes.
Master.
Hongning!
They say it's bad luck to see the bride before the wedding!
Go back, quick!
But I need to ask you something.
What is it?
Do you know anything about the Demon King?
Why would you ask that?
Am I… the Demon King?
Of course not.
Really?
Really.
Good, that's a relief!
I'm fine, Master.
See you tomorrow!
Greetings, Master!
Master,
all the disciples have gathered.
Good.
Today's my wedding day.
Lots of guests are coming.
Even some from Mt. Baizhou.
Remember,
don't be rude.
Me?
Master,
don't worry, I've got this!
When they arrive,
I'll wine and dine them!
To avoid trouble,
check every invite carefully.
Only those with the Cangwu Academy's seal
can enter.
[Block off]
all the main paths too.
Got it!
Come,
everyone head up!
[Mom,]
[this place is amazing!]
[I wanna learn magic too!]
[I bet I've got talent!]
Look, I'll show you!
How was that?
You wish!
Why not shoot for the moon!
Get back to
hitting the books!
You never focus,
always daydreaming!
Move aside!
Head up!
Mom!
Maybe I really can reach the moon one day!
Okay, thanks.
This one's mine.
Here you go.
Senior,
what are you writing?
It's Hongning's wedding,
I wanted to give her a gift.
Thought long and hard,
I recalled that
she's flunked a bunch of tests.
So,
I made her
a study guide!
That's great!
Wait,
that's your wedding gift?
What?
Got a problem?
No!
I mean it's thoughtful!
Of course!
Hongning was my first friend
on Mt. Cangwu!
Didn't expect
she's a girl
and now she's marrying our Master!
So that means…
Master is
my brother-in-law!
Too much on the plate!
Pick it up!
Come on!
[Look at Master!]
[He's a real catch!]
[This way, please.]
[Come!]
[He looks so different today!]
[Yeah!]
[He's got that special aura!]
Never seen Master
look this festive!
Exactly!
[Seriously!]
[What a charmer!]
Master, turn around!
Master,
I got too excited!
Such a rascal.
Master,
I want a hug too!
Back to business,
what about the others? All set?
Is the dungeon guarded?
Lujiu kept an eye
on everything himself.
[Also, Baibuqu and the little bros]
[are guarding the dungeon.]
Good.
Hand out the charms now.
Yes, Master.
Bailing,
how are Father and Mother?
Who?
Hongning's Mom and Dad.
My in-laws!
How are they doing?
That's right!
Your Dad-in law,
he's gone to the bathroom over ten times today!
Hasn't stopped at all!
Look, there he goes again!
Must be too nervous.
And Mom-in law, still with Hongning.
And Hongning…
Master,
why so many questions today?
Not like you at all!
You're nervous too?
Alright.
Trust me.
I'm here,
so you'll
get your bride safe and sound.
Where are you sticking it?
[I…]
[Master, it's time.]
[Bailing, time to fetch the bride!]
Blush.
That's lip balm, the other one!
Hey buddy,
why are you still here?
The bride
can't be seen by any guy now!
Out you go!
It's fine.
Just pretend I'm one of the girls.
[Come on, smile!]
Auntie,
is the blush too bright?
Not bright enough!
[The brighter, the more festive!]
Hongning's Mom,
why the tears now?
[Come help her with her hair!]
Hurry!
First stroke to the end,
a lifetime without worries.
Second stroke to the end,
safe and carefree.
Third stroke to the end,
plenty of kids and long life.
Last stroke to the end,
hearts forever tied.
Mom,
this was such a big decision
and I didn't talk to you in advance.
You're really not mad at me?
My girl,
as long as you're happy,
I'm okay with anything.
All I want is for you to be happy.
With you and Dad,
I'm already super happy.
Alright.
Stop or your makeup's gonna run.
And you, Ningmeng,
thanks for growing up with me
in this life.
What now, Hongning?
You getting married
or going to war?
Listen,
even after you're married,
I'm still one of the most important people
in your life!
Bride ready?
It's almost time!
Yes, we're ready!
This is a happy day,
no crying now.
Everyone smile!
Where's Dad?
Your Dad?
He went off to cry somewhere.
[Didn't want you to see him like that.]
[He's not mad at you.]
Alright.
Time for the bride to head out.
Exactly!
Let's go.
Go.
Come on.
Wait, no veil yet!
Veil…
Dad.
How would you head out
without the most important thing?
Alright, sweetheart.
Let's go.
If that guy ever bullies you,
just come home.
Dad will take care of you forever!
[I don't care if he's a deity or whatever,]
I'm not scared!
And neither should you be.
Beauty shines like the moon,
but a red camellia blooms from within.
Time to veil the bride.
Let me
kneel and thank Mom and Dad.
Get up, quick!
Up.
Get up, Hongning.
Let's go.
Green leaves, red cherries.
[No more clinging to the balustrade.]
[No more peeking through the curtain.]
Here comes the bride!