[English subtitles are available]
[Love Never Fails]
[EP35]
Why aren't you off
handling the divine punishment?
Father!
Father,
I grew up in Celestial Realm,
repeating your lessons,
watching every step of mine.
Until this trial
I never truly grasped
what you,
Mother,
and Kunlun
mean to me.
Muxian
is the woman I love.
I beg you,
please approve
our marriage.
In ten‑thousand years as Monarch
I've never held a family feast.
Know why?
It softens the will.
Now,
I allowed one
this time from pity,
not indulgence.
You've been back long enough,
yet you are still
narrow‑sighted.
Blind to the bigger picture.
Do you think
the Emperor Star's trial
is to teach you
worldly romance?
No.
It shows you
the world's chaos,
and that order
and fairness
are the only constants.
Father,
all I want
is to stand beside the one I love,
never to slack off.
You are not qualified.
Sir.
I'm sorry.
Perhaps,
in His Majesty's eyes,
I'm still unfit
to be your Empress.
I'm just
the punisher now;
even so,
eyes follow you.
If I took the throne,
you would become the target of many.
If some battles can't be dodged,
let's face them together.
Will you truly stay?
Would I
be here otherwise?
Come here.
The Celestial Floralia's over.
You're the new Floral Deity.
Train harder.
Strengthen your powers.
I'll be your help.
Focus.
Only then can I
pass power into you.
But you're wounded.
I don't want you to strain.
Listen.
I cultivate faster,
and dual practice
boosts us both.
Dual practice?
They say it accelerates cultivation.
Let's do it.
Do you know...
It's born of love.
I owe you
my life,
and now I love you too.
[Why does his energy]
[feel blocked,]
[as if sealed?]
[Could this be the Soul‑Binding Litany]
[the Sage spoke of?]
[And how is it linked to that bracelet...]
Greetings, Your Majesty.
You've kept
the Withered Garden in fine order.
Just doing my job.
Do you know,
in Celestial Realm,
everything must
be flawless?
So why leave
a Withered Garden?
Trials are harsh,
ascension harsher.
I thought
it spared broken flowers
a last breath.
Broken is broken.
No life left to save.
I kept this garden
as a warning.
A reminder to myself.
Show mercy,
and all becomes ruin.
I
never knew
this garden's story.
Of course you didn't.
No one does.
Ten thousand
years ago,
it became like this.
It was once a fairy's home,
a remarkable one.
Now
even her name
is forgotten.
[Could this]
[link to Jinxiu?]
If I may,
where is
she now?
Dead.
Sacrificed for the three realms
to end
an unforgivable mistake.
Your Majesty,
what's this?
Well,
I chose once ten millenniums ago;
I won't let
that error return.
I don't understand.
Camellia pixie!
So you knew it all along.
He prizes you
above life.
Of course I knew.
I forged Jinxiu for ages,
yet
he's still soft.
He's a total disappointment.
Today proves you can't stay.
Let this garden
be your grave.
Consider it my mercy
to you both.
You want to kill me.
What mercy is that?
You preach order
and justice.
This life,
I rose by merit.
Why kill me?
You shattered Celestial Realm's order.
That's
reason enough.
It was you!
You cast Soul‑Binding Litany on Jinxiu,
and Soul-locking Bracelet on me, through him.
You hurt your own son!
He is not my son!
If he weren't the Emperor Star,
he'd be ash
in Kylin Lair!
Jinxiu,
Stay away from him!
Jinxiu!
Don't go.
He's lying.
He's hurting you.
Everything he does
is an act.
Father!
Why stand by?
Seize her!
Kunlun!
Kunlun, move!
Hongning!
This is the woman
you long to marry?
All of this
began with you!
Kill me, then.
It all
started with me.
Silence.
She snuck in and attacked the Monarch.
Her sin is unforgivable.
By my decree,
hand this camellia pixie
to the Punisher:
rip out her core,
smash her soul.
Mother,
let's take Father back
for treatment first.
No.
I'll watch the Celestial Commander
punish this fiend myself.
What are you waiting for?
If you won't kill her,
I'll bury Floralia Palace
with her!
Sir,
can't swing the blade?
I
slayed your father.
Do it.
Why?
Why did you do it?
If you hate me,
kill me.
Sir,
from now on,
we owe each other nothing.
Are you deaf?
Kill her!
Now!
[Sir,]
[farewell.]
Brother,
do you even grasp
the price of letting her go?
This isn't
just a lightning sentence.
Keep shielding her
and you'll lose
your own life.
If I don't protect her,
no one
will.
She locked her own heart
for her evil purpose.
How can you still not see it?
She'd never
put on a Heart Seal by choice.
She must have a reason.
Reason?
What reason could she have?
She's a camellia pixie
with nerves of steel.
What can't she do?
You saw it.
She hurt Father with demonic energy.
What else is she hiding?
Without the forbidden spell you cast
to descend her,
you wouldn't even see that seal.
Brother,
she's not the Hongning we knew.
She's using you.
That's not who she is.
Fine.
Then tell me this:
how the seal
pierced her heart
if it wasn't her doing?
If she truly loves you,
why not stand
beside you openly?
Why use
a seal to get close to you?
Don't tell me
you felt nothing.
I know exactly
who Hongning is,
and so do you.
Sir Kunlun,
His Majesty was already
drained from seclusion.
Demon King's power tore his core.
We're patching his spirit,
but that's only a stopgap.
How bad?
Let me have a look.
No need to see, Mother.
You're shaken enough.
No need for more shock.
Hongning's strike
shattered Father's core.
Only his millennium body
keeps him alive.
The healers
flooded him with power.
He's stable for now.
How could that wretch
wield such force?
She absorbed vast demon energy
back in State Wuzhang.
So you knew she was Hongning all along?
Your brother's
bewitched,
and you let it happen!
What were you thinking?
What should we do now?
I've frozen
Father's body,
but her power
keeps gnawing
at his spirit.
If it breaks through...
he'll be gone.
You're saying
he could vanish at any moment?
Yes.
He would never imagine,
all his pride,
and his obsession with divine law,
were ended up
by a camellia pixie.
Where is Jinxiu?
My brother
knelt for punishment the moment
you and Father came back.
You still call him brother?
Think a
half‑hearted scolding
fixes his sin?
Ridiculous!
Is Father holding on?
For now, the healer's holding his spirit.
But her power
keeps attacking
his spirit.
If his spirit gives way,
I'm afraid...
I've let everyone down, haven't I?
Brother,
you've always been our pride.
To me,
you'll always be.
Whatever trouble I stir,
you carry me through.
If I hadn't
dragged Hongning up here,
none of this
would have happened.
Brother,
do you remember
when we were kids
and I
nearly died?
How could I not remember?
The Demotion Pool. I took you there.
You recall taking me,
forget I
begged for days
before you agreed.
Kunlun.
You promised,
no mischief.
Relax!
Live a little.
Isn't that exhausting?
You said just to look,
not to go in.
It's too dangerous.
Come back!
Father's off at Kylin Lair.
He won't be back soon.
So why not have a little fun?
How about this:
catch me
if you want me home.
Kunlun!
It's too dangerous!
Scare tactics again?
It's just a pool.
Do you know, that pool
strips all power.
Fall in
and you're dust.
Brother,
what would you do
if I had fallen?
What could I do?
I'd have jumped in after you.
And if you fell too,
I'll dive after you.
Think of how sad
Father and Mother would be
if we both vanished.
Brother.
Listen, Kunlun,
we both should stay safe...
[You're always]
[ready to]
[risk your life]
for others,
yet now you shut
everyone out
when it's you in danger.
Celestial Realm's duty rests on me.
That's how it must be.
And that
lone‑wolf act
is what landed us here.
Everything Hongning did
were her own choices.
This was
all set in motion,
a trap
from the start.
She drew close to you,
won your trust,
and returned to Celestial Realm with you.
It was all her scheme.
Brother,
it's never your fault.
If you erred at all,
it was
your love to her
blinded you.
Her hate
began with me.
If I'd noticed sooner,
explained to her
and begged forgiveness...
Please,
don't flog yourself.
If that's true,
I'm guilty too.
I knew she was Hongning
and kept quiet.
None of this
is on you.
Brother.
Kunlun,
Mother always
favored you.
That's why
you acted
carefree and uninhibited,
but really,
you did it for me.
So I could be the heir.
In truth, your skills
and your power
are no less than mine.
I know it.
You'd make
a better Monarch.
Do you
hear yourself?
Promise me
you'll look after Father
and Mother.
Celestial Realm's future
is yours now.
Sir.
Sir!
Mother.
You've got some nerve.
Mother,
Father's life hangs by a thread.
I'm worried about him.
I know
it's all because of me.
It's too late now
and I'm ready to trade my divine bones
for his safety.
What did you say?
Father's spirit
is corrupted
by demonic force.
This method may not work
but it will save his life.
Trade away your divine bones,
and you'll be no different from a mortal.
Do that,
and you'll lose your god power,
even the right to inherit the throne.
My sins
stripped me of that right already.
I know
this all began
because of me.
But as his son,
I owe him my duty.
I can't think of
any other way.
Afterward
I'll exile
myself below.
Please let me.
Mother,
another peony bloom
opened on my true form.
Would you like to see?
Celestial Commander's true form
naturally has
81 golden blooms.
This one bloomed so soon after the last.
We just admired the last one.
I'll pass this time.
Okay.
Rest well, Mother.
Your Majesty,
Sir Kunlun
has mastered puppet magic.
Truly?
Take me to him.
Mother.
Wait here.
When I return,
we'll view the new bloom together.
Yes, Mother.
Right now,
giving Father my divine bones
is the only cure.
Mother, you know me.
So please indulge me this time,
just this once.
Mother,
you're back.
Why are you still here?
You said
you'd see Kunlun first,
then my new peony bloom,
so I waited.
You're from the Flora Clan.
Blooming is normal.
Must I come
every time one of your
81 petals opens?
Mother,
this gold petal
is different.
It's just 81 petals.
Different how?
Mother,
it opened
while I pictured
your face.
A peony is a peony.
What's it to me?
Rise.
Not unless
you agree.
In ten thousand years
I've asked you for nothing else.
Please, Mother.
Get up.
You said
you never asked me for anything.
But you're wrong.
At 500,
when your first golden bloom appeared,
you begged me.
Yes,
yet
you never came.
Jinxiu,
I always favored Kunlun
and was strict with you.
I tried to control it,
but it wasn't hidden.
Have you ever
wondered why?
Because I'm the elder son,
I bear expectations.
So Mother disciplined me strictly.
Do you really
believe that?
I
have to.
If you're displeased,
I must try harder.
So, since I was little,
I've always
worked harder
than Kunlun.
I thought
if I excelled at everything...
perhaps
you'd love me just a bit more.
You've never fallen short.
You did better than Father,
Kunlun,
any god
of your age.
But it changes nothing.
No matter how hard
you try,
it won't lessen
my hatred for you.
Jinxiu,
you know,
I hate you.
The more you try,
the more I'm torn.
You are so innocent,
yet I despise you.
You bear
this coldness
because...
you're not
my flesh and blood.
You've sensed it,
haven't you?
Whatever my birth,
I owe you ten millennia of care.
I
cannot forget that.
Today,
I proved your
thousand-year doubt.
I should've known.
Your refusal to fight
wasn't virtue.
It was fear of the truth.
Fine,
I consent your request.
Thank you, Mother.
No thanks needed.
I agreed
for one reason:
to dispel you from Celestial Realm.
Mother,
I have one more favor to ask.
Speak.
Please,
spare Hongning's life.
You heard all that?
You don't look surprised.
Though I'm unremarkable,
but we're close.
I sensed it.
You're good at hiding it.
Mother,
we may not share the same blood,
but we've been brothers for so long.
That bond is real.
Please, don't do this to him.
What,
you think
I'm cruel to him?
If I said no,
you'd know I'm lying.
Everything you did was for me.
Mother, you may well ask me:
in all three realms,
who has least right to call you cruel?
The answer, of course, is me.
Yet, Mother,
have you ever considered my feelings?
Did you ever ask me
whether any of this is what I wanted?
Well,
too late for that.
If you hadn't feigned ignorance,
and taken
responsibility sooner,
none of this
would've happened.
Now,
words are useless.
Since everything is beyond saving,
as the Celestial Realm's Punisher,
carve out Jinxiu's divine bones.
What?
Afterall,
you're his brother.
Ease the pain
if you can.
It may be
all you have left to give.
The decision is yours.