[English subtitles are available]
[Love Never Fails]
[EP37]
Your Divine Highness,
are you alright?
I'm fine.
She still refuses to leave.
Would you like me
to drive her away?
Leave her be.
Everyone in all realms
wants her dead.
Are you not worried?
Today,
had the troops not lost their way in the
twisted passages of Dragon's Tomb,
her fate would
have been sealed.
She's come a long way from
being that camellia pixie.
Her powers as the Demon Queen have awakened.
She no longer needs anyone's protection.
Perhaps she'll be
better off without me.
You still
harbor feelings for her.
What difference does it make?
Our paths
must part here.
Your Divine Highness,
this place is no longer secure.
What's your next move?
Baiyu and Mokui have exhausted
their powers to save me.
It's time
we part ways.
Your Divine Highness,
please don't send me away.
This isn't banishment.
I want you to
experience life's fullness for yourself.
When I saved you,
I never expected anything in return.
Your loyalty
has gone far beyond
any favor I showed you.
But I've never
seen it as a burden.
Lujiu,
you've followed me through countless lives,
living solely for my sake.
What's wrong with
dedicating my life to you?
That's because you've never known
what it feels to live for yourself.
I've walked a path
of many mistakes.
It took lifetimes of pain
to learn this simple truth.
I will seek
my own path,
but until then,
I will not leave your side.
Remember these words.
Seek out
your own destiny.
Greetings, Sir Kunlun.
Where is mother?
She is in conference with the officials.
She just left.
I'll inform her of your arrival.
Don't bother.
I'm here to see father.
You may all leave.
Yes.
Come on, old man,
wake up.
Mother's so angry with Jinxiu
that she banished him to the mortal realm.
I knew
you've always favored him.
The throne was
meant to be his.
That's why I played along since childhood,
acting as the troublemaker.
I thought it would
keep our family in harmony.
Who could have guessed
things would turn out like this?
With Jinxiu in the mortal realm,
mother expects me
to take the throne.
I understand that
now is the time
to answer duty's call
and fulfill
my role
as a royal son.
But I just can't
make peace with myself over this.
You once said that
of the two Emperor Stars,
only Jinxiu's shone bright.
Only the one whose
Emperor Star gleams
has the right to inherit the throne.
How can I seize
what rightfully belongs to him?
I cannot claim the throne
without true legitimacy.
By the way,
who was
Jinxiu's mother?
The divine maiden who gave birth to him
must have been
a stunning beauty.
What else could explain
Jinxiu's ethereal beauty?
Perhaps if he'd been born less handsome,
mother wouldn't have been so consumed by jealousy.
Father,
allow me more time.
When my Emperor Star finally glows,
perhaps I too can
become a worthy son in your eyes,
just like Jinxiu.
I have to leave now.
These days, the affairs are demanding,
and mother's wearing herself out.
She needs my assistance.
You've rested long enough.
It's time to wake up,
old man.
Take a look, my lady.
Our rouge is quite famous.
Have you found one you like?
[Quick,]
[which one do you prefer?]
[Can't decide?]
[I'll purchase the entire collection.]
[I'll take this one.]
Sir Jinxiu,
I've searched far and wide for you.
Are you alright?
My lady,
we are strangers to each other.
Please keep your distance.
Don't you remember me?
It's the injury, isn't it?
Baicha told me
your divine bone was extracted.
How are you holding up?
I fail to comprehend your meaning, lady.
It's alright if you don't understand.
Just know that
I won't harm you.
Let me check
if you have other injuries.
This is absurd.
Sir Jinxiu,
I've spent a millennium searching for you.
I know I've committed
many wrongs against you,
caused you pain.
But I can explain it all.
My lady,
I don't know whose heart you've broken,
but I'm sure he wouldn't be pleased
to see you grabbing
another man's hand in public.
There is no other man.
It has always been you.
If you have no other business,
I shall be on my way.
I was gone for just a moment,
and you're here harassing him again.
He said he doesn't wish to see you.
Sir Jinxiu.
Sir Jinxiu...
Sir Jinxiu!
why do you lie?
Are you still angry?
If it would ease your hatred,
you can take my life.
Why are you so convinced I wish you dead?
I'll accept whatever you choose to do.
There are torments beyond death.
If you're afraid,
leave now.
I won't leave.
You killed my father.
I paid for your crime with my divine bone,
asking only that we never meet again.
There's nothing more between us.
You know my powers are weak.
He could have ended my life with ease.
I still don't understand
how I managed to wound him.
How did I possess
such strength...
But I clearly remember
his words.
he had placed a Soul-binding Litany in you.
He admitted
that you were not his son.
[He is not my son!]
[If he weren't the Emperor Star,]
[he would have been cast into Kylin Lair]
[and obliterated into nothingness!]
Why didn't you tell me then?
Why did you ask me to kill you?
Why did you speak such harsh words?
Because I couldn't bear to see
your Floralia Palace fall with me.
I wanted to keep you safe,
but things didn't go as planned.
These consequences,
they're my fault...
You killed him claiming to keep me safe.
You'd rather die at my hands
rather than reveal the truth,
again saying it was for my protection.
What about the Heart Seal?
What's your explanation for that?
Another act of protection?
All along,
your approach to me
held hidden intentions.
You're wrong.
Destiny played its cruel game.
I was unwilling to accept it.
I believed
I was bound by vengeance,
but once I found you,
I understood that
my search for you
was never driven by hate.
Yet you'd rather endure the Heart Seal
than admit your love for me.
So many died because of you.
Their cries kept me awake at night.
But when I
learned of Lujiu's story,
I finally realized,
I was the one at fault all along.
You trusted me, loved me,
while I kept deceiving you.
I feared that once you knew the truth,
you'd doubt the sincerity of my love.
I...
I couldn't bear to hear you say,
"we shall never meet again."
So
that's why your heart
was aching all that time?
Yes...
it hurts...
my heart aches whenever I think of you.
What is my true identity?
Celestial Commander,
Floral Deity,
Sir Jinxiu...
Before I descended to the mortal realm,
mother revealed that
I wasn't her true-born child.
Regardless of your identity,
to me, you are simply my Jinxiu.
My initial plan was simple:
descend to the mortal world,
find a place I like,
live a life I enjoy,
and silently pass away there.
The life of an immortal is endless.
I spent ten millennia in heaven,
yet now I realize
those decades of mortal trials
left deeper marks on my soul.
I was like
a misplaced stone,
just sitting there
while people passed by,
calling out "Your Divine Highness"
to me, a mere stone.
But only I knew
that inside,
this stone was shattered.
Looking back now,
perhaps everything had its reason.
Maybe
I was never meant to be there.
Perhaps...
you were meant to wait for me.
When the emperor tried to kill me,
he planned to cast you into the Kylin Lair.
So,
you want me to go to the Kylin Lair.
I am going to accompany you.
Whether through hell or high water,
I would remain at your side.
After all this time...
why does His Majesty remain unresponsive?
Mother, please ease your worries.
Father will surely be fine.
Your Divine Majesty!
Father...
Father!
Hurry!
Announce to all realms!
His Divine Majesty has awakened!
Yes!
My beloved...
It's me.
You?
Why did you tap me?
Hey, little fox,
have you lost your mind?
Don't you know they're hunting demons?
Yet here you are, hanging around.
Aren't you afraid they'll catch you?
Those meatballs?
Well, they're welcome to try.
Aren't you a demon too?
What's your business here?
You think I want to be here?
I'm on the run with these two.
Here I am, trying to do you a favor,
and you're giving me attitude?
On the run?
Where are you heading?
To Mt. Baizhou.
It's become a sanctuary for demons
who have nowhere else to turn.
Halt! You won't get far!
Oh no,
It's the divine troops.
They must have detected our presence.
I swear, they can
sniff us out like bloodhounds.
Let's get out of here,
hurry!
Hurry!
Why run?
Let me handle this.
General Manwu,
where are you off to?
aren't you going to greet His Majesty?
As the Punisher,
I've seen countless demons thrown into the lair.
I never thought
it might hold answers about my past.
I feel such pain for
those demons cast into the lair.
They suffered terribly,
burned by the heavenly fire.
This place is meant for demons
of the gravest sins.
If
the emperor wished to confine me in here,
perhaps
my origins are connected to demons.
I think it's wonderful this way.
You're finally like me now.
They can no longer preach about
the divide between immortals and demons.
You take this rather lightly.
I've always been this way.
The heavenly fire is perilous.
This journey...
might be one of no return.
When I chose to come,
I had already abandoned hope of survival.
Shall we?
[This is...]
[My king's aura...]
Who are you?
I'm half of Yanwei, the twin-headed serpent,
steed of Demon King Fuzhu.
How curious...
You?
It is you...
My master,
the sovereign of all demons,
he is the Demon King.
Your master is the Demon King?
My master ruled over all demonkind.
I've been waiting for my master
for so long...so very long...
until I
nearly lost all memory...
You,
saved by his finger bone...
you are my rightful master!
Finally, after all this time...
Master...
All that you wish to know
lies within this eye.
You need to recall it all...
and you shall remember everything.
So,
you not only
condemned Jinxiu to the mortal realm,
but also took the liberty of
passing the Emperor's Seal to Kunlun?
Jinxiu brought a demon here
and plotted your assassination.
His crimes deserve no mercy!
I only did what was necessary.
Such insolence!
Father,
circumstances were critical.
Had I not assumed temporary authority,
chaos would have ensued.
Mother acted only out of necessity.
Your Majesty,
Jinxiu was aware that Muxian
was the camellia pixie,
yet still brought her here.
He purposely enabled
her gradual approach to you,
leading to your grave injury.
Such betrayal and defiance
of divine order,
are you still defending him?
And that camellia pixie as well?
The pixie means nothing.
That very pixie
left you in this state!
How can you still turn a blind eye?
So what?
A hundred camellia pixies
would mean nothing to me.
Jinxiu is all that matters!
Father,
Brother's descended to live as a mortal.
Please let him be,
allow him to live out his days
as a mortal!
Ignorant boy!
Such foolish mercy...
You know nothing!
I fear you'll find this disappointing.
Jinxiu's whereabouts among the mortals
are currently unknown.
It seems no one will be able to
succeed your divine throne!
Bring him back to me,
dead or alive!
I don't care whether
he's mortal or immortal.
Every demon in existence
may die,
but only Jinxiu can complete
this grand design
I've crafted for millennia.
Yet you all,
with your selfish whims
and foolishness,
have destroyed my careful planning!
Father,
I don't understand...
You don't understand?
None of you could possibly understand!
Issue my decree!
Yes, Your Majesty!
Search every corner of all realms
if necessary,
but bring Jinxiu to me!
As you command!
This must be what the serpent
meant by the dream of the eye.
But this Mt. Baizhou
looks different from the one I know.
Did you hear anything
before arriving here?
I heard a woman
calling your name.
Good sir,
is this Mt. Baizhou?
He can't see us.
What are you up to?
So that's what
dream of the eye meant...
Lady Cixin said
she loves red camellias.
If I make them all bloom,
she'll surely be happy.
With immortals and demons
on the brink of war,
you're still focused on
romance with a fairy?
Mind your tongue!
Don't tarnish
how she sees me.
I say we should
just storm heaven with the Black Serpent,
defeat her brother Yaotian.
Wouldn't that solve everything?
Scram!
She's almost here.
Little troublemaker,
what do you want from me now?
Have you been causing trouble again?
My lady,
behold...
It's quite lovely.
So Lady Cixin
is the emperor's sister.
Why has father never
mentioned her to me?
At the Withered Garden,
I heard he mention
that millennia ago,
it was home
to a fairy.
Though no one
remembers her name.
Perhaps...
she was my mother...
Haven't seen a trace of her,
why so impatient?
This isn't right.
I've been sick for a day and night.
What if something's happened to her?
Surely not...
She's coming!
Quickly, lie down!
The agony!
Oh, the agony!
You little troublemaker,
what's wrong with you this time?
I fear I'm lovesick,
afflicted with
the illness of longing...
My lady,
where are you going?
Stop these
childish games.
I shall not visit you anymore.
But why?
I am the Punisher,
and you are a demon.
Our union
violates the divine order.
So what?
Surely it wouldn't deny
our child a father?
These laws you hold so dear,
weren't they made by yourselves??
That's not what I...
All things are possible.
Stop
worrying so much.
Do you know what
matters most right now?
What?
Naming our child!
Haven't...
haven't you thought about it?
Have you?
Absolutely!
I've long decided.
Our child will surely
become like me,
supreme ruler of the world,
king of the demon realm.
So
I plan to name him
"Megatron!"
Do you have other ideas?
Not to your liking?
I did think of another one.
Come...
"Overlord."
My wish is that
this era of peace and prosperity endures.
With beautiful landscapes...
Shall we name them Jinxiu (splendor)?
Jinxiu?
Jinxiu...
Jinxiu is perfect!
From now on, you'll be Jinxiu.
You'll be Jinxiu.
Easy there!
Jinxiu...
Merely a scratch...
Cixin!
I know
you won't spare us.
All I ask is that
you spare this child.
Grant him a chance to live,
and we'll surrender our lives now!
Cixin,
as the Punisher,
how could you be so stubborn?
Cixin,
I won't let you die!
I want you to
live on with Jinxiu.
How can I live on
if you perish?
Master...
Do you truly believe you alone
can destroy the entire demon race?
You've already lost.
After your annihilation,
no one
in this world will remember
the existence of you, the Demon King!
You heaven-born fool,
how ridiculous you are!
You may take my life,
but you can't eliminate all demons.
As long as someone remembers,
the Demon King will exist.
And as long as the Demon King exists,
the demons will never submit
to the Celestial Realm!
Sooner or later,
a new Demon King will rise,
succeed me,
and end your life!
My love!
No...
My love...
My love!
Jinxiu,
though we cannot watch you grow,
may your days
be blessed with happiness.
Mother!
My father, the Demon King...
my mother, Cixin...
were slain by the emperor
I once respected...
Jinxiu...
Master,
now you know everything!
You must avenge your father!
You are the rightful ruler
of demonkind,
the true Sovereign of all demons!
Jinxiu!
All kings have been allied with Kylin.
Kylin protects our kind,
and their blood was sealed here,
waiting for master's return!
Master,
under its protection,
with eternal heavenly fire
and the return of Kylin blood,
the world shall flourish in splendor!
Jinxiu!