[English subtitles are available]
[Love Never Fails]
[EP32]
Luyao,
you should know the way you are
is holding you back.
Mention your father's alive, and boom—
you jumped right on it.
I'll kill you
sooner or later.
I'll avenge my father.
You aren't my match at all.
Why bother?
Just marry me.
I can help you restore the NCR,
far stronger than that under your father.
You murdered the king
and usurped the throne.
We don't need someone
as greedy as you
to rule the realm!
A mere woman.
The masses hail you as an auspicious omen.
But when I become the king,
you are only auspicious
when I say so.
If I deny it,
you'll be nothing.
My Lord,
an envoy from the Celestial Realm is here.
Who?
He claims to bring you a gift.
Think carefully.
You're getting bolder.
How dare you sneak into Floralia Palace?
Don't worry.
Only here can we
reminisce properly,
don't you think?
Absurd.
You should leave.
With my current power,
I can hide myself well.
I won't put you in trouble.
He went to the NCR without you,
left you alone
in the palace.
It's for their own matter.
Unsettled, don't you?
'Cause you lack the authority or status
to be a part of it.
As immortals,
they can cross borders effortlessly.
But you can't do anything
without a proper status.
Even ascended to heaven,
you're just
a minor flower deity
tending withered blossoms.
Don't project your
insecurities onto me.
I won't force you to admit it anymore.
Muxian,
I know exactly
what you truly are.
I believe
you know it too.
Ask yourself,
when will your
demon king's power finally awaken?
It's been suppressed too long.
Once unleashed,
you can claim
everything you desire.
The time has come
to make those hypocritical immortals
feel our demonic might.
Listen,
not all in heaven
are hypocrites.
But they excel
at wearing virtuous masks
while
stabbing you repeatedly in the back!
I'm curious
how he'd feel
if he knew
you're approaching him
with ulterior motives?
I could tell him the truth,
and even leave the Palace.
From what I know of him,
Jinxiu might abandon
his throne for you.
But what of his parents?
Would they allow it?
Moreover,
there's the heart seal...
I never asked.
You may fool me,
but not him.
I know what I'm doing.
You should go now.
Long time no see.
General Sky Fox.
You're delivering the gift in person.
I'm truly
honored.
A millennium ago,
my brother failed Luyao
at the wedding.
Hearing she's found an ideal match,
he felt relieved
and sent me to bring you a gift on behalf
of the Celestial Realm.
Does he think
I've forgotten
what happened
on that day?
He deeply regrets his actions
and has prepared a grand gift.
Golden Lotus Dew.
You deserve it.
Golden Lotus Dew?
Didn't Sir Jinxiu
give it
to his lover?
This
one-drop-in-every-ten-millennia dew
was divided upon delivery
to the Celestial Realm.
Half to Jinxiu,
half to me.
It possesses
immense power.
We're always prudent.
We never
pin all hopes
on Jinxiu himself.
That does sound like your way.
You'll never jeopardize your future
for a mere woman.
Then I'll
accept it.
May I see the Matriarch?
I wish to personally return it
as a token of apology and blessing.
She's been in exile for years,
running on fumes.
She needs rest.
It's not convenient
for you to see her now.
If you wish
to see her in person,
I invite you
to attend my coronation
ceremony.
My brother asked me
to hand-deliver this
to her.
If she refuses to meet,
I'd
take my leave.
You are toying with me.
More than that.
I'll also take your life for her sake!
How arrogant!
Jinxiu.
Why are you here?
I told you about the wedding invitation.
How could I not save you?
But...
Enough talk.
Go save Luyao.
Leave it to me.
Alright.
One more step,
I'll kill her.
What are you doing here?
I promised to protect you.
I don't need that!
Just leave!
Stop there!
I swear I'll kill her!
You bastard!
Shameless!
As a general,
you're resorting to such threats.
How do you live up to your reputation?
Kunlun!
Insolent fool!
Alright then,
I won't marry you.
Tomorrow,
I'll ascend
the throne alone!
Got it now?
That's what we call
fighting fire with fire.
Kunlun.
Luyao.
Shall I do it, or will you?
I'll do it.
You're self-righteous
and insatiably greedy.
Everything you ever despised
has become
the weapon that kills you.
Thank you, Sir Jinxiu,
Kunlun,
for helping me slay my enemy
to reclaim my place.
Don't mention it.
This is what I owe you.
The debt had to be repaid.
Uh... I'm leaving now.
Kunlun,
stay to help
sort out the rest.
I will.
Take care.
See you.
Are you still mad at me?
I wouldn't dare.
Then why did you save me?
Don't you know how dangerous it's?
If...
I was afraid you'd leave,
marry another,
and I'd never see you again.
In the Three Realms,
I am the only one
who can
marry you.
Don't act so childish.
I didn't.
Listen carefully,
through every high and low,
I'm yours
to lean on.
True love
is based on mutual trust
and companionship.
I'll protect you,
walk you through the dark,
but
forge
your own sword along the way.
Besides,
I'll also grow stronger
to become your sturdiest shield.
That way, you can feel free
to do what you love
and be yourself.
Kunlun,
before
I spoke in anger.
Truth is
I don't care
about being a queen
or a king.
What I told you
has nothing to do with our status.
I still see you as
that little feisty fox I found.
No matter what,
you belong to me.
You once called me your demon pet.
So, as it turned out,
I'm the patronizing one.
Jinxiu, you are back.
You've been waiting?
I heard you came back today,
so I waited here for you.
[Report!]
Sir,
about the divine punishment thing
in the mortal realm,
we've found some leads.
I see.
Don't do anything yet.
Understood.
Go back and wait for me.
I'm coming with you.
Last time you left,
I didn't accompany you.
I wish
to go with you now.
Fine.
Mr Han is the owner of this Langhuan House.
He loves collecting rare
and priceless artifacts.
Any treasure
you can imagine in this world,
you can find it here.
Since it's so renowned,
why so few visitors?
Mortals have an unwritten rule.
Rare treasures
belong only to a select few.
Mr Han
capitalizes on that desire.
His Langhuan House
isn't open to the public,
only receiving nobility from Ganzhou.
Entry is permitted only with his
invitation.
Invitation?
Yes.
Let's go.
Young Master Jinxiu,
what an honor
to have you grace
my house.
Thank you for inviting me.
My pleasure.
I wonder
what rare treasure has prompted
such a grand auction.
Countless legends
speak of it.
Yet almost none have laid eyes upon it.
Sir, even you
will be astonished.
Please, come inside.
Attention,
this is Young Master Jinxiu.
- Mr Han.
- Mr Jinxiu.
Mr Jinxiu.
Mr Han.
After you.
Have a seat.
Gentlemen.
Gentlemen,
I wish
to express my deepest gratitude
for your presence today.
The treasures I've brought this time
will surely not disappoint.
Stop teasing us.
Just bring it out.
[C'mon.]
[My apologies...]
Sir, why came disguised as Jinxiu?
Do you have concerns?
I can't act
in the name of Punisher.
There are more urgent matters.
[What is it?]
Here's the clue.
Has legs yet seems legless.
Like a man, yet not a man.
Often found in tales and lore.
But never shows its true form.
How mysterious.
I've no idea.
Demon.
[Tell us.]
[Spill it already.]
[Alright,]
[I'll tell you.]
This treasure
is actually present
among us now.
Where?
Right here!
[This old man?]
[He's just some old man.]
[Yeah.]
[As you all can see,]
[this treasure]
appears human
yet is anything but.
Not human?
He's a turtle demon!
Demon?
A demon?
Gentlemen.
Don't worry.
This demon
has been subdued
by a sorcerer's
binding talisman.
He's
powerless
and harmless.
Behold.
See?
How fascinating!
No reaction at all.
No response.
[But, Mr Han,]
[how can you prove]
[he's truly a demon?]
[He seems]
[just an ordinary old man.]
[Yeah.]
[Exactly.]
Gentlemen.
be patient.
What?
Who's he? A sorcerer?
Look,
surprised?
Yes.
Thrilled?
Absolutely!
So thrilling!
This ancient turtle...
Nice.
It's a millennium-old spirit.
Kept within your home,
it can extend life and attract wealth!
Is this not
the finest spiritual treasure?
Indeed.
It'd be a terrible waste
if it's left unclaimed.
[True.]
[Without further ado.]
Same rules as before.
The bidding starts now!
If you are interested,
please raise your placard.
Base price is 500 taels of silver.
550!
- Alright.
- 600!
600?
[Do I hear higher?]
It's one thing if he hunts
for a living.
But he's already possessed consciousness,
no different from humans.
Why humiliated like this?
This is part
of the reason why I came.
[Any higher bids?]
I must save him.
Take your time.
I'll save him first.
There's another
matter to verify.
[800!]
[Do I hear more?]
1,000.
1,000?
1,000!
Jinxiu is indeed generous!
1,000 until now.
Any higher?
1,500.
[1,500!]
Any higher?
1,500...
Jinxiu,
you know, 1,500...
I meant 1,000 taels
of gold.
[Gold!]
[1,000 taels of gold!]
Jinxiu,
are you sure?
1,000 taels of gold?
My carriage is downstairs.
Have someone fetch the gold immediately.
It really is gold!
Gold!
This millennium-old turtle demon
now belongs to Jinxiu!
Mr Han,
you really think
I'd pay 1,000 taels of gold
just for a turtle demon?
Time to bring out
your other rare treasures.
There's more?
More? Really?
Jinxiu, forgive me.
I intended
to save the best
for last.
But since you insist,
I'll
bring it out now
for all to see.
Good!
Show us!
Let's see it!
Come on.
Here it comes.
Here it is.
Gentlemen,
the world
[knows of fox demons' allure]
[and legends of nine-tailed foxes.]
[A nine-tailed fox?]
[This demon]
[is truly exceptional among demons.]
[I acquired him by chance.]
[He was quite]
[deranged and crazy,]
nearly captured by a sorcerer
who almost removed his core.
That would've scattered his soul.
Out
of pity,
I then
brought him to Ganzhou.
[If he's lucky]
[enough]
to be taken home
by one of you
as an attendant or pet,
it'd be his great fortune.
What exactly is this?
A three-tailed fox demon!
[Know what?]
[As a demon pet,]
[he'd be quite suitable.]
[That's right.]
[I often]
[walk dogs with my wife.]
[Never walked a fox before.]
[I'd like to try.]
Lujiu!
You descended
just to find him?
Yes.
You've been searching for him?
He's followed me through lifetimes.
I can't bear to see him suffer so.
Do you know
I still have accounts
to settle with him regarding Cangwu?
Let's go back first.
Where's the fox demon?
How come he's gone?
You can go now,
the farther, the better.
Thanks.
Lujiu's core is severely damaged,
long imprisoned by binding talismans.
His consciousness is fragmented.
Without proper recuperation,
his life
may be in danger.
All fates are preordained.
It's heavenly law.
Hongning...
I have matters to attend.
I'll take my leave.
Hongning,
Lujiu isn't inherently evil.
The fire spread uncontrollably on Cangwu,
something was amiss.
I need to hear his explanation personally.
Killing is killing.
What's the point of questioning?
If it's truly his fault,
would you punish him?
If
he committed grave sins,
as the Punisher, I'd grant him
a proper send-off.
[Even awake, he couldn't explain.]
What are you doing here?
Returning from Wuzhang,
Luyao has also been searching for him.
Yesterday I received word
he's being sold like a pet,
so I came to investigate.
What do you mean
"couldn't explain"?
When Luyao reclaimed the NCR,
I saw her wield Spiritual Flame.
It only scorched Sky Fox,
not harming a single bystander,
perfectly controlled.
But at Cangwu,
Lujiu used it
uncontrollably,
targeting both good and evil.
Even my protective charms
were destroyed
when Lujiu lost control.
I went to the Bridge of Destiny.
The official overseeing reincarnation
told me
Lujiu bore a suppression seal
on his back.
[That may be the root cause.]
[And that seal]
was unique to Master Taiyi.
So you mean
that fire wasn't his fault.
Sir Jinxiu,
it's my fault.
Kill me.
Just do it.
Please kill me.
Please!
That inferno
has been burning
in his nightmares all this time.
Sir Jinxiu. Sir!
Lujiu.
Sir Jinxiu.
You are safe now.
Lujiu...
Yes.
I've made a grave mistake,
dragging you all
into its devastating consequences.
You shouldn't have saved me.
Was it because of the Spiritual Flame?
Yes.
I don't deserve to live.
I thought
it could protect
the whole Cangwu
and save countless lives.
But instead,
it destroyed everything.
Lujiu,
I know you didn't mean to.
You were manipulated.
I failed Cangwu's disciples,
failed Hongning and her family,
failed Sir Jinxiu.
So many suffered because of me.
Hongning...
Hongning,
I'm so sorry.
Since regaining my memories,
nightmares torment me daily.
I remember vividly
a blood-drenched Cangwu
and their
dying faces.
They can never
reincarnate
because of me.
What do you mean?
Those killed by Spiritual Flame,
their souls were incinerated.
They are barred
from rebirth forever.
Jinxiu,
you still won't
explain to them?
Kunlun...
So,
back then,
Sir Jinxiu,
you...
My brother saved us.
Without his intervention,
our souls would've been consumed
by Spiritual Flame.
Only by doing what he did
could we be rescued.
So, you were saving them,
right?
What about my parents?
They've already begun new lives.
May I see them?
I'll return to the NCR
to inform Luyao.
If you wish,
I'll take you to them.
Honey,
come.
[After returning to the Celestial Realm,]
[it took me long to locate them.]
But they don't
remember you in this life.
[Delicious.]
[Smell it.]
[Good?]
[Yes.]
[Good.]
I'll serve you more.
Have some broth.
Okay.
Here.
Hon.
I was just passing by.
Your chicken soup
smelled wonderful.
This girl
looks so familiar.
Yeah.
I feel like
I've seen her before.
I cooked
the congee with
chicken broth.
That's why it smells good.
Miss,
how about you sit down
and have a bowl?
Here,
don't be shy.
Sit here.
Come on.
[This is my bowl.]
[It's clean.]
[Have a bowl of soup.]
[Thanks.]
[It's freshly cooked.]
I simmered it
for hours.
Miss, try it.
Hon,
this is yours.
Go on.
This girl
is so pretty
and elegant.
I really
adore her.
[So tasty.]
[Delicious!]
[What are you doing?]
[Only a little bit left.]
[But,]
[you cooked chicken broth today,]
[and it tastes so good.]
[Why can't I have more?]
[So you know]
[it tastes good.]
[Today is Hongning's birthday.]
[I barely afforded half a chicken,]
[and you ate most of it.]
[Mother,]
[father enjoys it. Let him have more.]
[Here.]
[Look, my girl!]
[See?]
[Go on.]
[Hongning,]
[I'm]
[full now.]
These side dishes
are fresh
from our garden.
All freshly made.
Try it.
What did Lujiu
go through after Wuzhang?
How could he be captured by a sorcerer?
Since you found me,
I've been searching for him.
No trace of him across all Three Realms
or at the Reincarnation Gate.
After regaining his memories,
he's been wandering aimlessly
in a daze,
seeking self-punishment
to atone for his sins.
Even so,
he didn't deserve this.
That Master Han imprisons
and traffics demons,
engaging in shady dealings.
It's utterly intolerable.
Indeed.
The demon trade in Ganzhou grows daily.
He's undoubtedly responsible.
So,
how will you punish him?
The Celestial Realm immortals
must not interfere in mortal affairs.
As the Punisher,
I need to be especially cautious.
Forget it.
The Celestial Realm cares nothing for demons.
I'll
punish him myself.
You're now a deity of Floralia Palace,
bound by heavenly laws.
Don't let impulse
cost you your future.
Besides, right and wrong
shall be judged by mortal laws
instead of personal
grudges.
Then how will he face justice?
19.
20.
21.
22...
These ill-gotten demon profits,
he can't afford
to spend them.
Precisely.
There are no laws on demon trade.
His wealth
is unjustly gained.
Such ill-gotten gains
warrant mortal punishment.
[He deserves it.]
[Exactly.]
He is cruel
and cold-hearted.
Once his ledgers fall into others' hands,
he'd definitely be exposed.
He amassed demon-trade wealth,
yet cannot explain to officials
the source of his riches.
So punishment is certain.
This is what you meant by mortal affairs,
mortal judgment?
Immortals shouldn't interfere.
But I don't think
it's satisfying enough.
He'll be fine.
Jinxiu.
Sir Jinxiu.
Thank you
for finding Lujiu
and breaking his curse.
He served me for lifetimes.
This is what I should do for him.
What will you do next?
I'll take him back home.
He's of nine-tailed fox lineage.
We should restore
our clan together.
If you need help,
just ask Kunlun.
Jinxiu,
if the Celestial Realm found out
you saved Hongning's parents,
you'd be punished
and suffer backlash.
Your descent as the Punisher
will cause you trouble too.
You should go back now.
Don't worry about that.
Hongning!
Wait.
Hongning.
Meddling with mortal fates
brings backlash.
When were you
planning to tell me that?
You don't think
I can face it with you,
do you?
You concealed everything about Cangwu.
After finding Lujiu,
do you still wanna hide the truth from me?
Do you know how I suffered
and how torn I was?
I couldn't force myself to hate you,
I'd only blame myself for lacking principle.
I just didn't know
how to explain
without sounding
like making excuses.
Besides,
it all began because of me.
If not for me,
Sir Taiyi
wouldn't have set Lujiu up,
and none would've happened later.
I tried to tell you,
but what right had I
to say those?
Yet unknowingly,
I wronged you often
and hurt you deeply.
It's my fault.
I failed to take care of you.
I only hope, in time,
you'll see my heart clearly.
[This is Heart Seal.]
[The more you love him,]
[the more you'll suffer,]
[and the tighter it'll bind.]
[Since you wish to prove]
[your love with your life,]
[it serves you well.]