[English subtitles are available]
[Love Never Fails]
[EP19]
Greetings, Empress.
His Majesty is working on the Oceanic Codex.
One interruption
and all is lost.
You proceed
as the council planned.
Legend says the Demon King's power
can summon a Kylin,
blessing a realm
for ten‑thousand years.
The surge
in the NCR
indicates the same.
It's grave,
if the Emperor is not present...
I fought half my life in the Western Sea,
Sir Taiyi.
Do you doubt
I can handle this?
I wouldn't dare.
Then let's begin.
Demons have always been our foe.
Ten thousand years ago, the Demon King
Fuzhu was hurled into Kylin Lair
and turned to ash.
If that power is back,
there are only two explanations.
Either he is alive,
or someone inherited the power.
Kylin skyfire is
the ancient beast's power.
Touch it,
and one will turn to ash.
No one survives.
I say
the King left an heir.
Arguing causes
is useless.
We must
erase that power.
Lead Western Sea troops
to Dragon's Abyss
and trace its source.
But
Dragon's Abyss is NCR territory.
Marching in
may be unwise.
NCR can't help itself.
This threatens all three realms.
If we don’t act,
who will?
Your Majesty is wise and valiant.
Dongxuan?
You?
Prepare to die!
Don't hurt the Matriarch!
Matriarch?
She's only a fox demon.
Add you
and I
purge two pests today.
If Samadhi Fire could stop me,
that stray vixen
wouldn't have fallen.
Where's Lujiu?
I've practiced Dao
a century, suffered,
slew hordes of demons.
I believe
justice means killing evil.
Killing evil is right.
But where is evil?
Evil is demons.
Ha!
Then why am I fine?
Hongning says I'm a demon too.
Who am I, then?
What have I been killing?
Where is my path?
A demon, so what?
You have no ground
despising demons.
Listen up,
I was born a demon
but I walk a righteous path.
I shame neither Heaven nor Earth.
If you can't grasp that,
fade away.
Born a demon,
yet walk a righteous path?
I'm an immortal, not a demon.
A demon?
I'm a demon?
Then who am I?
Who am I?
Fox!
Lujiu!
My god.
Don't tell me he's been
inside her stomach this whole time.
Fox!
Lujiu!
Hongning,
how are you?
Feeling dizzy?
Worried, are you?
You know I am.
Master,
will I always shield you?
Don't turn.
Listen.
I know,
gods must cut love.
I'm just a mortal
but I've
read storybooks.
And maybe..,
I've started to like you.
I once
meant to leave the mountain
and never
keep these feelings.
But just now...
I realized
I can't let go.
My parents said
a deity watched over me as a child.
I've always wanted to find him.
You won't admit it,
but I believe
it was you.
I'm not saying this
to get an answer
nor to get
a promise from you.
It's just...
Dragon's Abyss
is deadly
and we may
not get out,
so I
had to speak.
I'm done.
I swear
I'll keep you safe.
That's a promise.
Life after life,
never break that oath.
I bought this for you.
Master.
Hongning.
What happened?
The old hag
thrashed him.
We found him
like this.
I poured power into Lujiu,
yet it vanished.
His core is cracked.
I must treat him now.
Fox.
Lujiu.
This place is risky.
Go now.
My lord,
one question...
We'll talk about it later.
Master,
you both okay?
You know,
I can carry you both
back to Mt. Cangwu.
Let go.
Move!
Master,
I'll fetch some water.
Good.
Sir.
Matriarch.
Why is Hongning mortal?
She drank NCR Golden Lotus Dew.
Saved her soul
and allowed her cross the Bridge of Destiny.
She had a reincarnation writ?
You
walked her across.
That's why blazing fire tortures you.
You'd go
that far for her?
But have you thought,
she's a demon.
You're the future Emperor.
You two can never be together.
The wound's incurable.
Helping her
and easing her pain
is enough for me.
Easy for you to say.
A ten‑millennia
drop of Golden Lotus Dew,
and you
hand it out
to charm a girl.
Well,
I owe you
and the NCR.
One day
I'll repay.
Don't say that again.
Repay? With what?
You hibernate
on Mt. Cangwu.
But don't expect my thanks.
Hand Lujiu over.
He's royal blood,
an NCR prince.
The King himself
cast him
into Kylin Lair.
Taking him
back now
may harm him.
Yes.
We were parted as children.
I hunted his trail in secret.
I was
too timid,
too cowardly then.
I've paid that price.
Now
I'll bring him home.
The NCR owes him,
a debt he'll claim himself.
What happened to you?
Hongning?
You're a white camellia pixie?
You still remember me?
I...
Are you all right?
I was born able to spot demons,
but do you know me?
Know you?
I'm Baicha,
the one you saved.
Didn't expect
fate to let me see you again.
Fate plays cruel games.
No talking.
You're badly hurt.
I'll take you to Master.
Mas...
What is it?
Hongning,
seeing you
is enough.
You've lost most memories.
I know you mean well,
but your friends,
they may not welcome me.
It's okay. Don't worry.
Master isn't like that.
Come.
Master,
I met someone who claims
he knows me.
He's badly wounded.
Baicha?
You know him?
How did you get out of Kylin Lair?
Sir,
fancy meeting again.
I'd heard the Emperor Star descend
in mortal shells
and remember nothing,
yet you still recall me.
That's irrelevant.
Maybe.
But do you recall
why I was
thrown into that pit,
and what I suffered
to escape?
Hongning,
I should leave.
These cuts
are nothing.
Seeing you has already
untied the knot in my heart.
I could
die content.
Don't talk nonsense.
Master,
he...
I share the blame
for failing you before.
Come to Mt. Cangwu
and heal with us.
Thank you.
Since I saved you,
you owe me answers:
what's going on between you
and Lujiu,
and with Master?
And that shadow‑guy?
You barely have time to eat,
yet you know
half the men in the realm.
None of your business.
I just want to know
who...
who I rescued.
When you need to know, you will.
Explaining now
would only confuse you.
I'd love a sip of your blood.
Bet it's ice‑cold.
Not as cold as your true form.
Good heavens.
Why are you only just getting here?
Only?
Listen, Sir,
the Emperor suddenly
ordered every heavenly guard
to lock down the realm.
I had no choice.
What do you mean, only?
By the way,
what really happened
at Dragon's Abyss?
Forget that for now.
Cover for me.
I'm heading to Heaven.
Hold on!
No, please.
Are we really
going to dance
on the edge of a
death sentence?
Please, no.
Don't do that.
I see no option
but returning to Heaven.
You just...
look after yourself.
I can't protect you too.
No, no, please don't!
Look after myself?
I'm a desk‑flower,
not a sword‑swinger!
I can't do that!
I'm terrified of this
lick‑the‑blade life.
I'm scared!
Let go.
I can't spare you.
I won't.
I'll count to three.
Let go of me.
Three... Two... One.
-Hands off!
-No!
Master?
Go!
Come in.
If you'd stayed in seclusion any longer
I'd have died of worry.
Three days only.
Drink your medicine.
Let me.
[Could that]
[red camellia]
[be the one Master once loved?]
What are you thinking?
Nothing.
It's just,
if you dislike
me feeding you,
next time I'll...
It's not that.
Just...
it's a new experience.
It never
happened before.
Really?
Not even in Heaven?
How are Bailing and Lujiu?
Healing fast.
Bouncing around already.
Good.
That's good.
[Not a word about that red camellia.]
Master,
nothing else you'd like to ask?
Then...
rest well.
I didn't see anything!
Nothing at all!
You don't have
anything to say to me?
Why are you following me?
I...
I'm leaving soon.
I feel familiar with you.
I'd like you to escort me.
We barely know each other.
Why should I?
Bailing,
just in time.
Take care of
your guest.
Greetings, Your Grace.
Rise.
Official Chrysanthemum
descended five times illegally
during the Emperor Stars' trial.
No records in Archives.
For what?
Sir Jinxiu encountered
a mortal girl during his trial.
He's been consulting him
about...
About what?
About...
Romantic affairs.
As expected.
[Should we intervene?]
[In case she hinders his trial.]
No.
Keep watching.
Understood.
Your Grace.
Well?
The Demon King's trace
was found at Dragon Pool.
[But now]
[his energy]
[has appeared elsewhere.]
Where is he now?
Where the Emperor Star resides—
Cangwu Academy.
Greetings, Sage.
I've broken celestial laws,
but I have no choice.
I come to seek your guidance.
Is Hongning's
power truly from
the Demon King?
Any way to suppress it
without harming her?
Thank you.
In the battle at Dragon's Abyss,
Bailing and Hongning
broke rules.
They deserve punishment.
But they acted to save lives
and
eliminated evil.
They upheld Cangwu's
duty and honor.
I'll spare you this time.
Bailing have planted enough trees
to atone for past sins.
From today,
your immortal root is planted.
You may cultivate junior celestial arts.
Thank you, Master.
No more tree-planting!
Bailing,
you discipline yourself
and guide Cangwu's disciples
toward
ascension.
For what you did in the battle,
I witnessed
your sense of duty.
I am proud.
Master...
You're
embarrassing me.
Tiannanxing,
your cultivation progresses well.
From today,
you may practice advanced arts.
Yes, Master.
Baibuqu,
your wisdom
is impressive.
You're
promoted to full disciple.
Thank you, Master.
Master.
I have a request.
Yes?
I excel only
in theory, but lack
practical skills.
Let me
join senior brothers
in demon-hunting.
That requires basic skills.
Without mastery,
you can't protect yourself.
How about this.
From today,
you guard the dungeons.
Study the demons there.
This will prepare you
for future
missions.
Thank you, Master!
I won't
disappoint you!
Why is he thrilled about
this tedious job?
When you first
got the duty,
you were celebrating with wine.
Did I?
Luyao has stayed here for a while.
She'll depart soon.
Lujiu.
In the battle,
she saved your life.
you escort her safely
down the mountain.
Master,
I refuse.
Thank you, Sir.
I didn't say yes!
You'd defy
your Master's order?
I...
Fine.
Why me?
Get this straight.
I'm human,
you're a pixie.
I'm better.
So he would choose me.
You hear me, huh?
What are you muttering?
I'm...
Admiring the flowers.
Your red camellia
looks rather plain.
Since Dragon's Abyss,
I've yet to ask
if you wish to stay at Cangwu?
If not,
I won't force you.
But
I can't bear
to see you risk
your life again.
You want me to stay
just to keep me safe?
Didn't you say
to follow my true heart?
My heart wants
you by my side,
always.
I specially
sought this for you.
Aids cultivation,
ensures safety.
Cangwu's creed:
Always help others.
You help others
while I help you.
So
this is our love token?
Why are you here?
See how you're
drowning your sorrows in wine.
Who said I'm sorrowful?
It's all in your head.
I'm leaving.
With Lujiu.
There's more to it.
My noble nine-tailed princess.
Why explain
your departure to me?
Pointless.
I mourn my years as your slave.
After all...
What pleases nine-tails?
Only three-tails would know.
My blood-spilled efforts
mean nothing.
You'll understand
when memories return.
Boring.
They ruined my cultivation focus.
Why must Master and Hongning
flaunt their romance?
Their love tsunami
drowns us minnows
on the shore!
Pathetic.
But he's our Master.
Can't complain.
But you can complain Hongning?
Not really.
Women
are cultivation's bane.
Stay away from them.
Senior,
have you heard of
a cultivation method called
Dual Practice?
I know it inside out.
Boring.
Impossible.
As a constable,
I met splendid women.
Graceful,
intelligent...
But I was
only focused on cultivation.
When
I descend,
every maiden shall fall for me!
But it's
my heart's fault.
It's not built for monogamy.
You know,
my heart belongs to
every woman out there,
can't be claimed by just one.
Senior,
you've only met one girl,
yet your imagination runs wild.
Impressive!
Junior!
Mourning
Luyao's departure
with wine?
Yeah.
Seems
you've grown attached
to your temple maiden!
Drink up!
Right.
Alright.
[Bottoms up!]
[Let's toast!]
Bye.
Goodbye.
Who's there?
Lujiu?
What's wrong?
Are you the Matriarch?
I am.
They say
praying to you
grants wishes.
[Madam.]
[Can you make me]
[grow nine tails?]
When you're older,
you'll have nine tails.
Really?
She's lying.
You'll never have nine tails.
Lujiu.
She's lying.
-Lujiu.
-She's lying.
-She...
Having nightmares?
Where are we?
Outskirts of Ganzhou.
Ganzhou?
I lost track.
Right, weren't you
going to Xuyun Temple?
Why this detour?
I...
need to handle
something else first.
Make it quick.
I need to return
to Cangwu after this.
You love that place?
Of course.
My master,
those troublemaker juniors,
they're waiting.
What if one day
you had to leave that place?
That won't happen.
Even if Master
banishes me,
I won't leave.
What's wrong?
Hungry?
No.
Then
hurting?
Your wound's bleeding.
Didn't you notice?
I'll get medicine.
Wait here.
He grew into such a fine man.
Wanna ask why I haven't
told him
who I really am?
I don't know.
But I think
he must hate me and Father deeply.
If he knew
my true identity,
would he still treat me kindly?
Baicha!
You're up?
I woke yesterday.
Didn't want to disturb you
while you were happy.
Be my guest.
What is it?
Hongning.
Men and women
should keep distance.
You said
we were friends in our past life.
No need for so many formalities.
We were very close then.
Every time I was bullied,
you protected me.
Always looked out for me.
But then everything
changed.
Changed?
Why?
Unpleasant matters...
[Hongning.]
Master.
Baicha's awake.
Check his injuries.
Wenxin's brewed herbs.
Fetch them.
I'll assess him.
Can't I stay here?
Don't be absurd.
A young lady shouldn't.
Fine.
Sir.
What a perfect timing.
Hongning's human now.
Innocent and pure.
I won't let her be burdened
by past lives.
Won't
or dare not?
How selfish of you.
You erase our bonds
and joy
to hide the fact
that you
wronged her.
Mortal emotions,
love and loss
in past lives
are illusions.
But you remember her.
And I remember her.
You cling to
the memories.
Yet she has
her life decided?
Sir,
have you asked
if she wants this?
Remember.
Every pain she bears
is your making.
She'll never ascend.
Why chain
her here?
Enough!
When you recover,
I'll return you to Mt. Baizhou.
Savor
this time.
Never.
Hongning.
I'll free you from his lies
and suffering.