Did you just get back?
Did you have a good time meeting your friends?
Get to the point. What do you want to say?
Yoon Tae In,
I'm sorry...
I can't...
accept this.
Honestly, I'm not...
Why not?
Is it because you aren't Kang Sun Ju?
How did you...?
To tell you the truth...
My name is In Yoon Ju
Kang Sun Ju is my older twin sister.
I'm really sorry...
I wanted to tell you...
I was going to tell you, but...
Don't you dare say you didn't have the opportunity to tell me!
You had so many chances when you could have told me the truth.
Why did you do it?
Why?
Money...
I desperately needed it.
So... It was about money the whole time.
You're just the same as everyone else.
Anything I say right now will sound like some excuse. I know that it's all my fault...
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, Yoon Tae In...
I told you everything about myself.
But you!
You!
You didn't even tell me your real name,
and now you want me to believe
you're sorry?
Don't you cry.
I can't even trust that.
I ended up here again...
Don't you cry.
I can't even trust that.
I really don't deserve to cry.
Episode 11
What are you saying?
Wait, so...
you are saying
you are not
Dr. Kang Sun Joo?
I'm sorry, Sir.
Come on, Dr. Kang.
Why are you doing this?
Why are you pranking me before you leave?
Dr. Kang Su Joo
is my twin sister.
To tell you the truth,
when we met at the hotel,
I was there to see her.
Dr. Kang Sun Joo?
Thank you so much for coming! I was afraid you wouldn't meet me.
I think you're mistaking me...
I'd like to you be the live-in doctor, Dr. Kang.
Wait a second! I'm not Kang Sun Joo! I'm...
So then why
did you pretend until now
to be your twin sister?
I'm...
So sorry!
Does the real Dr. Kang know what you did?
Not at all!
She has no idea!
I...
I really needed money.
So I've done this on my own.
Oh my gosh!
How in the world...
could this happen!
I will do whatever I have to to pay you back the 50 million won  (~$50k) that I've already received .
Even if you call the police now, I have nothing to say.
I'll accept any punishment you want me to take.
This incident!
I'll just let it slide.
What?
No matter what happens,
I have to protect LUNA from this kind of fraudulent publicity.
Wait...
Tae In...
doesn't know about all this, right?
Dr. Kang,
would you like some breakfast?
In Yoon Joo, is that you?
Ms. Cho Rong!
Here you go...
Have some.
Seriously, I'm fine...
Was that thunder I hear?
This red bean bun is
so much better than the ones you bought me before,
so next time get them only from this bakery.
It is delicious...
Bread tastes good
even in a situation like this.
Why did you ignore me
the last time I saw you?
What happened with your older sister from the States?
Did you get to see her?
Oh gosh...
I think these may be your size.
Gosh, wear them if you want to...
or not.
When you have too many thoughts, it's best to just sleep.
If you're finished eating,
go take a nap.
Gosh...
And if you have nowhere to go,
stay here as much as you want to... Gosh.
Are you saying she just left like that?
And without saying goodbye to us?
I haven't seen her since yesterday.
She may have some urgent work.
Anyway, the contract is going to be over.
How can you say that?
It's fine. It's okay.
It's a little sad,
but Tae In is also better now.
If the conversation is over,
then I would like to go up first.
CEO, does Tae In also know
that Dr. Kang is gone?
Yeah, he knows.
She came to my office this morning, kneeling and begging me to forgive her.
She said that she needed money
and said that she will return whatever money she has taken.
Tae In!
Did anything happen between you and Dr. Kang yesterday?
What are you curious about?
Did you hear
everything from Dr. Knag?
So you knew everything?
You knew that she was fooling me for money and you pretended to not know?
I didn't want to take her chance
of telling the truth and asking for your understanding.
Understanding?
Everything was a lie and you want me to understand?
Do you really think like that?
Everything that she did for you...
- You know the best.
- If a con artist did her best, does that does make her not a con artist?
Tae In, you know that she's not that type of person.
I'm the one who trusted such a person for a month.
You will never understand how I feel.
- Tae In said that he's not going to practice today.
- What?
When he's a stickler for the rules?
He's a little strange. Is it because Dr. Kang left?
Right. Dr. Kang just left without saying a word
and Yoon Tae In is also being weird.
Did something happen between them that we don't know about?
Hey, Shin.
Do you know anything?
Anyway, we are not practicing today.
He's openly ignoring me now.
We should just rest up today.
- Bro!
- Gosh, you scared me.
Knock before entering.
It's a habit now.
What happened? Why are you here?
I'm going to sleep here today.
What a surprise. You were dying to get your room back.
It suddenly felt a little strange to be alone.
Something is weird.
What's weird?
I went to the room, and Dr. Kang's suitcase was still there.
- Did she leave without her suitcase?
- Yes.
I feel like she may come back, so I can't stay in that room.
How urgent was it that she left without her suitcase?
Even without saying a word.
- Something is weird.
- Exactly! I told you.
Should we text her?
Come to think of it,
sleepwalking is not necessarily a bad thing.
Thanks to that, I got to meet you.
I have told you everything about me.
But you, you!
You didn't even tell me your real name.
Please contact us. Is everything all right?
Have you arrived in the States?
Why did you just leave without even saying goodbye? When are you going to take your suitcase back from my room?
Are you going to come back?
We are sad because you suddenly left, but
I will contact you when we go to the States for the tour next time.
Yoon Tae In,
where are you going again instead of sleeping?
What happened to your expression?
Is something not working out?
Didn't you mention about your sister
- you left in Korea?
- Yeah.
My twin sister.
Twi...Twi...?
- Twins.
- Okay.
Right.
You should be catching up
with your twin sister.
I'm sorry.
- I have taken up too much of your time.
- It's okay.
We used to be sisters, but not anymore.
I have a new family. So...
What? This is...
This is you in the photo?
Do you know me?
Do you know my mom?
Oh my goodness!
Hyun Woo has grown up so much and come back.
Just wait a minute.
This...
How do you have this?
Hyun Woo's mother gave me this before leaving this place.
She left? Where did she leave to...?
She told me to give this to
her son if he comes back sometime.
Here.
This is the address where your mother is now.
It rarely happens to people of her age.
She got dementia early.
She has no family to come for her, either.
Ever since she came here, she has been looking out of the window all day long like that.
Maybe she is waiting the whole time.
Excuse me.
Your son arrived.
Mom.
I'm your son.
Please, have some. (Using formal speech)
My son used to like this.
I missed you.
I told you
it may not be as you expected.
Yeah. But I've never expected this.
I thought of
tens of cases that could have happened when I met my mom.
But there was not a case
where I was forgotten.
To be honest,
an adoption agency reached out to me when I was 16
saying that
my mom wanted to see me.
So, why didn't you meet her then?
I didn't have courage to see her.
I guess I was being afraid
of being abandoned again by my
step parents if I met her.
So I rejected their offer.
You've told me,
she doesn't mean anything but a sister in the past to you, right?
Sister is just a sister.
Not from the childhood moment.
Don't make anything to regret,
like me.
Mom, Dad!
We will be back.
Bye.
Good bye.
Gosh, you came again!
- What?
- I feel bad about what happened.
I have told you this earlier, too. This is my home.
I don't know anything.
- What are you talking about?
- Gosh!
This young lady is acting like she's hearing all this for the first time.
Did being conned mess with your head?
Conned?
Why can't you just stay still? You're making me uneasy.
I wanted to do it.
- Is there nothing else to do?
- No, there's nothing to be done.
I have a meeting with my friend.
Make lunch for yourself.
Have fun then.
I like it.
It's nice to have someone to tell me that.
Yes, Yoo Chan's mother!
I have received something strange right now.
It must have arrived then.
- Have you seen it?
- What is this?
Has Yoo Chan also agreed to the cancellation of the contract?
It is just as it's written.
I have already talked to Yoo Chan about everything.
- So, you've been notified.
- Ma'am please, hold on.
- Mr. Moon.
- Oh, Reporter Min.
I'm glad I caught you.
I came by while I was here for Hyo Bin's interview.
Do you have some time?
I'm a little busy today.
- Let's talk later.
- I have heard something strange.
- Strange talk?
- I heard
Yoo Chan is going to sign with Jang Enterprises.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Who's going around
spreading those ridiculous rumors?
Are you sure it's a ridiculous rumor?
I saw Yoo Chan at the Jang Enterprises not long ago
and got worried about the rumor being true.
- Do you want to do something else?
- Acting.
I was thinking of acting again if I got a good project.
I was wondering how it would be.
Yoo Chan! Yoo Chan, are you here?
- Yoo Chan!
- CEO.
You... Let's talk a little.
What?
- What happened?
- Are you doing all this because
I'm not letting you do acting?
- What are you talking about?
- Your mom sent
the contract cancellation documents to the office.
- What?
- If you weren't happy with the company,
you should have come and talked to me first.
You. Are you really going to Jang Enterprises?
- No, it's nothing like that.
- I heard you were offered an acting role,
and you have gone to Jang Enterprises.
Hey, Woo Ga On, why are you going through my stuff?
Let's go together and talk to your mother.
No, I thought I had left something in the room.
CEO, let's talk outside.
I have not done it.
It's true that I got an acting offer from CEO Jang and met him.
But I went to Jang Enterprises
to reject the offer.
I also didn't know that mom
sent those kinds of documents to the office.
I'm sorry.
It's just that recent events
have put me on an edge.
I'll take care of my mom.
You don't have to stress about this.
Also,
I don't have any thoughts of leaving LUNA.
When did you come to Korea?
I was actually in Korea the whole time.
Are you saying you didn't go back to America at that time?
I had urgent work, so I had to stay.
Also, the house you told me you bought.
I went there.
Is it true that you got scammed?
Yes.
I bragged to you to come by,
but I got scammed.
That house is not worthy of this...
I tried my best to forget about everything, but why do you still live like this?
What's so precious about that house?
It's because that time was the happiest time of my life.
That time was everything to me.
You might have forgotten everything,
but to me, our family, the house we used to live in,
and the happy times we spent there,
I couldn't erase all that.
I'm sorry.
Also, I didn't forget,
but I tried to forget that time.
I tried hard to survive where I am and not get neglected.
That's why I pushed you away as well.
I thought you were so content
and that's why you forgot everything.
How can I forget all of our past?
Unni, I'm sorry.
Actually...
Actually, I...
Welcome.
The person you're trying to call is not available right now...
Where did she go without even letting me know?
Then did our Yoon Joo get kicked out with nothing?
That is...
That's terrible.
You told me you liked her.
You said Yoon Tae In also liked Yoon Joo.
I believe Tae In is having a hard time, too.
He trusted Doctor that much.
But still, this is not right.
I know Yoon Joo did wrong, but if his feelings for her were genuine,
I thought he would've tried to understand her even if he might not be able to.
But how can he just kick her out like this?
Hyung, where are you? It's practice time, but why haven't you come yet?
I think nobody's coming. Let's just go.
Wait, Shin Hyung.
What is it?
Do you know about that, too?
About what?
Let's persuade Yoo Chan Hyung together, shall we?
Let's keep working as LUNA together.
What are you talking about it?
The thing is...
CEO came by earlier and made a scene.
I guess Yoo Chan Hyung is going to terminate his contract and go to Jang Entertainment.
What? He's doing what?
I think he wants to do acting again.
Actually, I found a script in his room recently.
Mom, please stop it!
I got it. I'll think about it, so please stop it.
Don't contact the director separately.
So let's try to persuade him not to go. Okay?
Why is my mom not picking up the phone?
Hyung!
You didn't pick up the phone, so I was worried about you.
You didn't come to the practice as well.
That can happen.
Now everything's revealed, so you don't even have to pretend,
is that what it is?
What? What are you talking about?
You were talking about keeping LUNA, but weren't you putting on a show the whole time?
Hey, are you saying that to me right now?
You are a born-to-be actor. You pretended to protect the team the whole time.
What the heck are you saying right now?
Say it straightforwardly.
Hey, Woo Ga On. What's going on with him?
That is... You're not, are you?
You're not going to leave LUNA, right?
What?
I overheard your conversation with the CEO.
I'm sorry.
- It's not like that.
- What's not like that?
Hey, Woo Ga On, why are you sorry?
If you didn't hear that, we might have gotten stabbed in our back.
Hey, Lee Shin!
I don't know what you heard,
but even if I left the team, I wouldn't run away like you without telling first!
You couldn't even take the responsibility until the end.
You are thinking of running away by hiding behind your mom!
How dare you!
Did you just hit me?
How dare you hit me!
Let me go!
Both of you, stop!
Seriously.
Let me go!
Stop it!
Seriously!
Jerk!
You should stop it, too!
Hyung!
What the heck are you doing?
Hey, you!
Who do you think you are? Shut up!
Hey!
- Hyung!
- Let me go!
Stop it!
What the heck are you guys doing?
Hey, you!
If you are going to fight, do it outside. It's noisy.
Hey, Yoon Tae In!
- Can't you say it better than that?
- How do you want me to say it?
You don't even care why we are fighting, do you?
Do I have to know the reason why you two are having a fist fight?
Why?
Right. What can I expect from you?
You only think of us as your sidekicks. We are only here to play your music, am I wrong?!
- What?
- Am I wrong?
You think you're the best, and we are all less than you.
Don't you all agree with me?
Sure.
If that was the issue, you could leave the team.
If you're going to be like this, just leave now.
- Hyung.
- Hey!
Fine! Let's give up.
Do you know why I–
Sure. I'll leave now as you wish.
I don't know why I wanted to stay in LUNA.
Sure.
We can do what you said.
- Hyung! Where are you going?
- Get out of my way!
Are you really going to leave like this?
I'm sorry for everything I did wrong.
I don't want to see you, either, so get away from me!
Hyung!
Did you really mean what you said?
Do you seriously want to give up LUNA?
If you were going to do this, you should've not let Doctor go!
- What?
- You're doing all this because of her.
Stop it.
Do you really not know?
Everyone could tell that she was sincere to you.
I said, stop it!
Why do I have to do more?
She was chased by private debt collectors not that long ago!
She knew things might get dangerous, but she gave up everything
and tried to tell you the truth.
But do you still not know?
It has nothing to do with me anymore.
Fine. You only care about yourself.
You only look at your wound, so you don't see or care about other people's wounds.
I thought you had changed a bit,
but I was mistaken.
The kids fought with each other?
Yes, I think they had a bit of a conflict.
Everyone left the team house last night besides Tae In.
Why? What was the reason?
It was because of the reason why you went to their house yesterday.
I think they had some misunderstanding because of Yoo Chan's case.
So, where is everybody?
Ga On just contacted me to let me know that he's with Yoo Chan at a hotel.
And Woo Yeon and Shin said they want to take a break.
Let's just let them have some rest.
I was taking care of Tae In too much
that I didn't care enough about the other members.
I'll contact them separately.
Okay.
Also, Soon Nam, since Tae In is by himself,
go take care of him.
Yes, I will.
I said I didn't want to eat.
Have a seat.
Even if you don't have any appetite, let's eat a bit.
You were stuck in your room and barely ate the past couple of days.
Hyung, I ordered a spicy rice cake that you like!
Let me sit next to you!
Gosh! Why are you clinging to me so much?
Come on! Let's eat.
I'm hungry.
Spoon for you.
And chopsticks.
Let's eat.
Hyung, what should we do after eating this?
Do you want to play a game?
Or do you want to watch a movie?
After eating this, you should go.
- Why?
- Why do you keep following me?
I just thought you might be lonely.
That's ridiculous.
Why don't you go stay next to Yoon Tae In, whom you like so much?
I'm sorry about yesterday.
I misunderstood you without hearing your story.
I was scared that you might really leave the company.
It's my fault.
Shin Hyung is sorry to you as well.
Hey, forget about it!
I'm more upset about Yoon Tae In than Lee Shin right now.
That jerk will only care about himself forever.
Even if I quit the team, I will do it on my own terms!
Hey, Yoo Chan Hyung.
You quitting LUNA is not the best decision.
It's the worst decision.
What are you saying?
That's what Tae In Hyung told me when I said I'll quit the team.
Did he say something like that?
I think that's Tae In Hyung's true feeling.
I want to do LUNA for a long time with all of you.
So let's stay here for a bit and go back to the team house. Okay?
Let's go back!
Let's go back together!
Forget about it! I'm going to eat the rice cake here. I'm not going.
Come on! Let's eat together and go back together!
You go back by yourself! I'm not going!
Where are you? Do you want to have a drink with me?
Do you remember this place?
Of course, I do.
This is where you older members came to drink without me.
I finally came to this place.
Did you hear about Yoo Chan Hyung from CEO?
Yes. I should say sorry to Yoo Chan Hyung.
I got angry at the time and didn't want to hear his story properly.
I'm sorry.
About what?
When you got someone you loved, I couldn't say anything
or encourage you as an older brother.
There's nothing wrong with what Yoo Chan Hyung said yesterday when I think about it.
I made a scene and broke up in the end.
I bet you are still having a hard time.
I'm trying to forget about her, but it's not easy.
Are you okay?
What about?
Are you okay with Dr. Kang leaving?
I know you had feelings for her, too.
I'm trying to get over her as well.
What?
You did what?
I'm sorry, Unni.
I told the CEO of MM Entertainment that I did this on my own,
so it won't harm you.
That's why Yoon Tae In made that face when he saw me...
Did you meet Yoon Tae In?
He knows one of my patients.
So what are you going to do now?
If they try to make a legal case out of this–
I'll... I'll do what I can do.
Do you know what you have done?
- What were you thinking–
- I had to live.
I really...
I really wanted to find a way to live.
So I'll...
I'll take responsibility no matter what.
You said you pretended to be me.
Then, it's my issue as well.
Yes.
Yoon Tae In, can we talk for a moment?
What is it about?
I'm here to apologize to you for what my younger sister did.
I'm sincerely...
I'm sincerely sorry.
I know I can't correct all of my sister's faults, but if it's okay with you,
I would like to offer you my treatment.
I don't need it.
Please, just go.
It's all because of me.
I always ran away,
and this all happened because I let Yoon Joo take care of everything by herself.
I want to compensate you in any way.
If you wish legal compensation, I will take every responsibility for that as well.
There's nothing to be compensated.
I'm recovered now.
I actually got over my illness.
If you don't have anything else to say, please leave.
You always only care about yourself.
You only look at your wound,
so you don't see nor care about other people's wounds.
Everyone could tell that she was sincere to you.
♫   I can't hide it   ♫
How can that be okay?
When I lost everything I built up,
I felt like my entire world was collapsing.
So what did you do after that?
I couldn't...
do anything.
I just...
I didn't want to do anything after that.
♫   You are my soul   ♫
♫   You are my love forever   ♫
♫   If I can be with you   ♫
Where are you? Yoon Tae In!
♫   I'll only love you forever   ♫
Yoon Tae In!
Are you okay?
Oh, no! How long have you been here like this?
Yoon Tae In!
♫   Even if this world will disappear   ♫
Yoon Tae In! Are you okay?
Are you coming back to consciousness?
Yoon Tae In, please wake up!
Yoon Tae In, please wake up.
I'm sure she lives somewhere around here.
We should've figured it out at that time.
Ms. In Yoon Joo!
Who are you?
If you are hungry, you should eat, sleep when you're sleepy,
and pay back the money if you borrowed it.
I bet you ate well and slept well.
Why don't you pay back our money?
You guys are–!
What's up with your eyes?
I guess we look like pushovers to you.
Who the heck are you guys?
Who the heck are you?
Did you bother her like this until now?
Do you know this woman?
Leave it. You are a very pretty boy.
I guess she's your girlfriend, but this is nothing compared what we did before.
Isn't that right?
Isn't money all you need?
Include the money for this, and tell me.
How much do you need?
Why are you doing this much?
I told you.
I got over my illness thanks to your sister.
It's instead of my treatment fee.
If my sister knows about this, she'll suffer more.
Is she...
Is she doing okay?
Then do you know...
where she is now?
I don't know where she is, either.
Why don't you call her directly?
Don't even cry.
I can't even trust that.
Yoon Tae In.
I missed you.
I missed you as well.
I'll protect you from now on.
♫  My cold heart deeply freezes  ♫
♫  Feel so cold, so cold, it feels so cold, so cold  ♫
♫  The reason why everything has stopped  ♫
♫  You're gone, you're gone, you're gone, you're gone  ♫
Without these ropes, I want to be with you.
That's what I want.
What? Why is our house door unlocked?
Something seemed wrong, so I followed.
Is this the right place?
I'm scared! It looks like a haunted house!
Where are you?
Come out right now!
What was it just now?
Let's just talk for a second.
Please! Someone help us!
I know you were sincere to me.
Thank you for being the happiest memory of my life.
Please wake up. In Yoon Joo!
♫  Like your words full of contradictions  ♫
♫   Maybe a wonderful end would come  ♫
♫  My cold heart deeply freezes  ♫
♫  Feel so cold, so cold, it feels so cold, so cold  ♫