This GEN is not like any other GEN.
We can’t use the old ways with them anymore.
There will be an exam tomorrow.
Shit.
What freaking exam is it now?
The rule for this exam is
you must find a space to sit until the music stops.
When the music stops,
those who aren’t sitting will automatically fail the exam.
I told you to get up!
Beauty, don’t give in.
Come at me!
Bring it on!
Come at me if you dare!
You’ve always made such a confident face.
Don’t fight.
Pennhung doesn’t like it.
Pheng.
Sit down.
I’ll fail this exam.
No, Maki.
- Sit down. - I’ll be fine.
See, White?
Maki gave up her seat for Pheng.
You’re as selfish as me.
Pheng, take my seat
so this bitch can shut up!
Ooh.
I can do it too.
Sit down.
Please stop, everyone.
I shouldn’t have passed in the first place.
Sit down.
There we have our solution.
Bye.
White.
If these chairs are such a problem for us,
just destroy them.
Let nobody pass the exam.
Hey!
What the hell is wrong with you?
Like I said,
if these chairs are such a problem for us,
let nobody pass the exam.
Hey.
If you don’t stop, I’ll deal with you.
I’ll deal with you first.
What’s the point of fighting, guys?
Don’t stop me.
Get yourselves together.
Don’t fight!
Don’t fight! Pennhung doesn’t like it!
Yes!
Punch him!
Beat him!
Go, Tibet!
Go!
Enjoying much?
White!
Let go!
Come here!
Will you stop or not?
Have you forgotten that you failed the exam?
Let me ask you something.
Have you ever thought about why you failed?
Let’s settle this once and for all!
Ouch!
Answer me.
Well…
I got lost in the forest.
That’s why I failed.
Jean and I just weren't as tough as Master Champ.
I couldn’t finish all the questions in time.
Are you sure that’s the reason why you failed?
What other reason could there be, Headmaster?
While waiting for your friends to finish the exam,
think and ask yourselves carefully
why you failed.
That’s enough!
Tibet!
Don’t fight! Pennhung doesn’t like it!
Calm down, Pennhung.
Stop it!
Tibet, that’s enough!
Don’t fight! Pennhung doesn’t like it!
Ouch!
Calm down, Pennhung.
Don’t fight!
Don’t fight! Pennhung doesn’t like it!
Stop it!
Pennhung.
Doing this won’t help!
What do you want us to do?
Let Pheng fail.
Pheng doesn’t deserve to fail.
Pheng sat on the chair before you, Jingjai.
Jingjai is right.
I shouldn’t have passed in the first place.
See?
I have the fairest solution for everyone.
What is that solution?
Let’s start over fairly.
If we keep fighting, we’ll all fail
and in the end, no one will get to contact their family.
Why do I have to start over?
I won’t do it.
Don’t be selfish, Jingjai.
Everyone is selfish.
What’s the use of being considerate?
Would that help you pass the exam?
Everyone.
As long as the music is still playing,
you can either start again or remain sitting.
If you don’t agree to start over,
I will break all the chairs.
Both you and I will lose the chance to contact our families.
You wouldn’t dare, White.
How can you be sure of that, Hugo?
She’s right.
If we don’t start over, we’ll all fail.
Yes.
I agree.
Let’s start over.
How disappointing.
I guess I’m expecting too much from you.
Master, please give us the signal to start.
Of course.
Three,
two,
one.
Go.
Jingjai!
Maki!
Pennhung!
No!
Let go of me!
Pennhung, go!
I will not!
Let go of me!
Let go of me, Maki!
What’s wrong with you?
Go, Pennhung!
Nai, Tibet, let go of me!
Pennhung, go sit down!
Go sit down, Pennhung!
Go!
Come sit down, Pennhung!
You’re ganging up on me?
You deserve it.
Let go!
Ouch! Let go!
I will not!
I won’t let you take that seat, bitch!
I won’t let you either!
Ouch!
I won’t let you win!
Sorry, girl.
Maki, come sit down.
Come sit down, Maki.
Come on, Maki!
Shit.
Hey!
Sorry, handsome.
This is an exam.
Sorry, Jingjai.
Hugo!
Stop it!
Let go!
You can’t steal my seat!
Give me this chair, Jingjai!
It’s my chair!
Let go!
Give me this chair.
No!
Let go, Jingjai!!
No, Hugo!
Move!
Let me have it!
Time’s up for the first round.
Hugo, Jingjai, you failed the exam.
This is all your fault.
How can you blame me?
You tried to steal my chair!
Woohoo!
Good job.
Woo!
Bye.
Shoo!
It serves you right.
Woo!
Here comes the folks who failed the exam.
There’s another one.
These folks failed the exam.
It’s alright.
Damn you.
Don’t be upset, buddy.
We all failed.
We’re all sitting here.
It’s okay.
Come now. Don’t be mad.
Leave me alone.
Sorry, buddy.
He’s so scary.
In this round,
let me remind you
to please listen to the rule carefully.
Think, analyze, and distinguish
the task in this exam thoroughly.
Remember that?
If you’re ready,
you may begin the exam.
Pheng?
I’ve realized that
after I lied to you all,
I shouldn’t have passed the exam in the first place.
I’m sorry, everyone.
Master Praeporn, I withdraw.
If you withdraw,
you will fail and lose the chance to contact your family.
Are you sure about this?
Yes.
I’m sure.
Pheng, you failed the exam.
Good luck, everyone.
Everyone,
please remove the chairs
until there’s only one left.
Why keep only one?
Aren’t we supposed to keep four?
This is the last round of the exam.
In this round, there will only be one chair.
Does that mean only one will pass the exam?
Not necessarily.
More than one of you can pass the exam.
Let me remind you
to please listen to the rule carefully.
Think, analyze, and distinguish
the task in this exam thoroughly.
If you’re ready, ''
you may begin the exam.
Everyone, stop.
What is it, Maki?
I want you all to stop
and think carefully about what Master keeps reminding us.
Why?
What about it?
Every time before we begin the exam,
Master reminds us about the task.
Every time.
Remember that?
Please listen to the rule carefully.
Think, analyze, and distinguish
the task in this exam thoroughly.
Yes.
Master wants us to interpret the task we received
in order to pass the exam.
She said that we may not necessarily pass alone.
What should we do?
There’s only one chair.
Master told us to find a space to sit
until the music stops.
Anyone who doesn’t have a space to sit when the music stops fails the exam.
And?
I don’t get it.
That’s right, Tibet.
Find a space to sit.
What are you doing, Maki?
Master didn’t say we can only sit on the chairs.
We can sit anywhere.
We just have to sit.
This is the way all of us can pass the exam.
Yes.
Maki is right.
The task is only for us to find a space to sit.
Well done.
Congratulations, kids.
All of you passed the exam.
Like I’ve been saying from the beginning,
if you think, analyze, and distinguish,
you’ll certainly pass the exam.
Remember that analyzing is the most basic foundation
of learning.
The last round of the exam
will take place in Master Amin’s office.
He will supervise your exam himself.
I wish you all good luck.
Congratulations to you all for getting to the last round.
This round is easy.
You just have to answer the challenge question that I will give you.
There will be only one question.
You will have one hour to find the answer.
You can do anything to find it
but you will only get one chance to answer.
If your answer is wrong, you fail the exam immediately.
If you have no questions,
you may begin the last round of the exam.
Master Amin,
there’s nothing here.
How can Pennhung answer when there’s no question?
That’s what you have to find an answer for.
The question is in the paper you’re holding.
Once you find the question, you will find the correct answer.
But, Master Amin.
This is a blank paper.
Yes.
I know.
It’s a problem you have to solve.
Don’t forget
that only the one who answers correctly will get the reward.
Alright.
You may split up to find the question and answer.
Meet back here in one hour.
What now?
This round is even harder than the previous ones.
At least, they gave us tasks before.
This time, we got nothing.
Master Amin said the question is in the paper.
We may have to find a way to make it appear.
Does anyone have a good idea?
This is the last round of the exam.
From now on, I think we all will have to be real competitors.
We must find the answer ourselves.
Do this separately?
I don’t think that’s a good idea.
I think we have a better chance of passing if we help each other.
I agree.
I think Master wants to teach us something in this exam.
We all got to this round
because we helped each other.
But in the end, only one will get the reward.
Only one will get to contact their family.
Alright then.
We’ll do it separately this time.
Whoever finds the answer deserves to contact their family.
What?
There’s nothing.
Alright.
Let’s do what they do in Harry Potter.
There’s no mark on the paper at all.
It really is just a blank paper.
If it’s invisible ink,
the letters might be visible again when cooled.
Please let me guess right.
What are you doing with the candle, Pennhung?
During a science class when Pennhung was young,
the teacher asked Pennhung to do an experiment,
Invisible ink and lemon juice.
If we hold the paper close to the heat,
the letters will appear.
I knew this was not going to work.
Shit!
No!
It’s torn up!
Hey.
It’s burning.
My guess is wrong.
Students who are taking the last exam,
please gather in the exam room now.
So?
Do you have an answer for me?
Do you, Pennhung?
Yes.
The answer is blank.
Why do you think so?
Because there’s no question since the beginning
so no matter what way we try to find it,
we can’t find it.
That means it’s blank.
Pennhung’s answer is blank.
Your question and answer are wrong.
You failed the exam, Pennhung.
Please leave the exam room.
Since no one has the answer for me,
I will give you one more hour.
But remember,
once you find the question, you will find the correct answer.
He asked us to find the answer
but he gave us blank papers.
What exactly does he want?
I think those Masters are messing with our heads.
They know we want to contact our families
so they lured us with the phone.
The most annoying thing is
we all want to use the phone,
including me.
You do?
I thought you’re not on good terms with your aunt.
I will use it to call the police
to shut this place down
or call the reporters to come and expose this place
so we can be done with it.
Why are you guys laughing?
I’m very serious.
What about you, Nai?
Why do you want the reward?
I just want to know from my dad
why he sent me to this school.
And you, Tibet?
Why do you want the reward?
It seems like you really want to pass this exam.
I miss my mom.
She was a songwriter.
Since the day my dad passed away many years ago,
she became sick
and quite unhealthy.
Since then, she could never write a song again.
Drink some water, Mom.
I’ve been taking care of her all this time.
She’s everything to me.
Do you want to get some sleep?
I want to be a doctor because of her.
But suddenly one day,
she wanted me to join Home School.
I promise that if Tibet comes to Home School,
I will take care of all his tuition fees
until he graduates with the highest degree
as you and your husband wish.
Moreover, I will continue to support Tibet’s dreams
after you and your husband.
Thank you, Master Amin.
Now I just want to know how my mom is doing.
Is she able to eat?
Does she get a full night’s sleep?
I’m worried about her.
What about you, Maki?
Why do you want the reward?
Actually, I’m not hoping to get the reward
because even if I get it,
I have no one to call.
I’m an orphan.
I don’t have a father or a mother.
I don’t have anyone to miss.
I don’t have anyone to worry about.
Then why are you taking the exam seriously?
I want to know what Master Amin is planning to do.
I want to know his intention.
Why do you want to know?
No special reason.
I guess I just want to win.
How are you going to win?
There’s a way.
I think we should help each other find the answer.
At least, we’ll have a better chance of getting the reward
than when we tried separately earlier.
But there’s no point in helping each other.
Don’t forget that only one will get the reward.
Tibet, think about it.
Since the first round of the exam
until now,
we’ve passed them because we helped each other.
Don’t you think that might be what Master Amin is trying to tell us?
It seems like he's trying to teach us something in this exam.
What do you say, Tibet?
Alright.
Let’s try and help each other.
That’s it.
Let’s help each other.
Both of you are stubborn.
Why these blank papers?
Are they just a trick?
Master Amin said if we can find the question,
we’ll find the answer.
But there’s nothing on these papers.
Maybe the question has nothing to do with the papers.
I don’t think so.
Since we came here, the Masters have been trying to teach
and tell us things.
These blank papers must mean something.
Otherwise, why would he give them to us?
That’s just it.
Why the blank papers?
And he’s making us search for the question ourselves.
What does Master Amin want from us?
White,
you’re so right.
Why would Master Amin do this?
What does he want from us?
Isn’t that a question?
That’s it.
That’s the question missing from the papers.
If every exam is meant to be a lesson,
the only one who has the question is the Master himself.
Do you mean we should just hand these blank papers to Master Amin
and let him write the question down?
Yes.
Are you sure, Tibet?
Just one wrong answer will make us fail the exam.
It doesn’t matter if the answer is right or wrong.
It matters that we help each other.
Do you know now
why you failed the exam?
You failed because you only cared about what you wanted.
You wanted to beat each other so much
that you forgot what the Masters were trying to teach you,
that you could help each other.
Remember,
as Home School students, all of you are friends.
You’re ready to answer, right?
Is this your answer?
Handing in blank papers?
Yes.
This is our answer.
Could you explain
why this is your answer?
Based on all the past exams,
the Masters kept emphasizing that
we should listen, think, analyze, and distinguish.
So we interpreted that these blank papers represent Home School students.
We get the questions and answers through learning from the Masters.
So we believe that our answer depends on what you want to teach us.
Good answer.
You understand the reason behind this exam correctly.
But this is not the end of the exam.
You will need to answer the question first.
The question for the last round is,
who deserves to get the reward?
You must discuss among yourselves who that is
because only one will get to contact their family.
But even though you’re friends,
you can’t always move forward together.
You must learn to sacrifice for others,
even if it means losing what you want.
We found the question together.
We deserve to get the reward together.
Why make us choose among ourselves?
I’ve told you this since the first round of the exam.
Only one will get to contact their family.
I’m not doing anything other than what I said at all.
Since only one will get the reward,
how about we vote?
Okay.
That’s the fairest way to go.
I vote for Tibet.
I want you to be able to contact your mom.
I vote for Tibet too.
We don’t need this as much as you do.
You deserve to contact the person you’re worried about.
Nai?
Who will you vote for?
Tibet.
You found the question.
You deserve the reward.
I vote for you.
We vote for Tibet.
He deserves to contact his family.
Here’s your reward.
You get ten minutes to use it.
Please make the most of it.
If not everyone gets it,
I won’t get it.
Are you sure
you want to give up this opportunity that’s so hard to come by?
I got where I am because I have my friends.
Everyone deserves the reward.
Good.
Then no one will get the reward in this exam.
But even though you won’t get it,
you should be proud of yourselves
for passing the exam.
This is the first time in Home School’s history
that we have this many students pass the exam.
I would like you all to keep improving yourselves.
Don’t stop learning new things.
Remember that whenever you’re willing to listen,
you’ll understand what Home School is trying to tell you.
Master Amin,
I’ve been informed by Master Prasath
that you ordered…
Yes.
I ordered it.
Master Amin, I would like you to reconsider
using that treatment with Run.
I’ve made my decision.
It’s the only way we can get Run back.
What if it’s life-threatening?
Doing that to Run could kill him.
I know what I’m doing
and I will take responsibility for it.
I should have voted for myself
so I could call the police.
Do you think Master Amin would let you make that call?
I think Master Amin had expected us to choose Tibet.
That means he didn’t plan to give us the reward in the first place, right?
That’s right.
I think so.
Still, it’s a waste of opportunity.
We managed to get to the last round
but got nothing.
Hey, we can’t say we got nothing.
We got to learn more about each other.
You’re right.
I think we all got the reward.
The reward called friendship.
Maki,
where are you going?
I have to follow the Masters.
Maki,
what’s going on?
I’m searching for my brother.
It’s the reason I came to study here.
Your brother?
You have a brother here?
Yes.
His name is Run.
He was a student here.
Run?
You mean GEN4’s Run?
Today was the first exam day for the GEN6 students.
One of them reminds me of you.
She passed with flying colors just like you did, Run.
I want you two to meet.
I think you’ll get along well.
Her name is Maki.
It’s time, Run.
DIRECTED BY KANITTHA KWUNYOO
Let go of me!
Do understand, Run.
You must be cured.
Let go!
Where have they gone?
Don’t worry.
We’ll have more chances.
We’ll help each other find your brother.
All students are forbidden from having romantic relationships at Home School.
What kind of rule is that?
It makes absolutely no sense.
You broke the 7th rule of Home School.
The key!