[The Comic Bang]
Mr. Gong Jian.
Why did you quit without waiting for me?
It would be the same
even if you were there.
But why did Qian Ye
fire you?
Ever since Qian Ye
became the chief editor,
he has become more and more arbitrary.
My conflict with him
has been getting worse too.
You know that we had a fight
during the meeting the other day.
Since then,
he has been picking on me.
It's all my fault.
I was going to put up with it,
but I didn't expect
today,
he came to me with the negative reviews
from the readers,
saying that I wasn't capable
to be the executive editor,
and he asked me to leave.
Who does Qian Ye think he is?
But it's good.
At least I don't have to work for Qian Ye.
But it's a pity to give up
the Dragon Boat Festival bonus.
So…
What
are you going to do next?
Look for another job.
I have almost ten years
of working experience.
I can work anywhere.
No.
I can't watch him
fire you like this.
I'll call him now.
If he's firing you,
I'll stop updating the comic.
Ye Qi.
I didn't ask you
to seek justice for me.
I just want to help you.
I know.
But you shouldn't stop updating.
"Let's Fall in Love"
is the result of our joint effort.
If you give it up because of me,
that will be what really hurts me.
Don't worry.
A new executive editor
will come to contact you.
Drink the coffee.
Otherwise
it'll get cold.
[Qian Ye]
Hello?
[Support: Defend the Best Executive Editor
in the World]
I got up really early this morning.
I think it was 6:30 a.m.
or 7:00 a.m.
Six or seven.
I had a bowl of noodles.
No problem.
Hotpot is also fine.
Okay.
That's all for now.
Bye-bye.
What did you just say?
I asked you,
why did you fire Mr. Gong Jian?
Him?
Take a look yourself.
These are the readers' reviews
of the comics he's in charge of
this month.
It's horrible compared to before.
[Negative Reviews Summary; Project, Number
of Negative Reviews, Executive Editor]
The comic with the best performance
["Let's Fall in Love," 87, Gong Jian]
is your "Let's Fall in Love."
But it's just barely a passing grade.
But you've been in charge
of all these comics since last month.
Stop making excuses for him.
How can a man
who's approaching the age of 40
understand
the feelings of the readers
of girls' comics?
I fired him
for the future of our comics
as well as for his good,
so that he can find the right career path
and stop wasting his time.
Mr. Gong Jian's
passion and expertise in girls' comics
are obvious to all of us.
You can't deny it
because of his age.
Besides,
he's only 28 years old.
He just looks mature.
Ye Qi.
You're still a student.
You've never experienced
the cruelty in the workplace.
Don't tell me what to do.
But…
No buts.
I'm busy. Go back.
Go.
I won't draw
"Let's Fall in Love" anymore.
Sure.
Wait.
I always
respect the choice of a cartoonist.
[Comic Serialization Contract
of "Let's Fall in Love"]
Your behavior
will generate liquidated damages.
I hope you can be careful.
Don't get yourself killed. I…
Don't.
Loser.
[Mr. Gong Jian]
Ye Qi.
Don't forget what I told you yesterday.
If you give up on "Let's Fall in Love"
because of me,
that will be unfair to everyone.
Do you remember
the story of the male lead
being rejected
by the cold female lead
that you asked me to draw?
Yes.
Gong Jian rejected it for you.
If I draw it for you now,
will you reconsider Mr. Gong Jian's job?
That depends
on the quality of your drawing.
Okay.
Deal.
He left without finishing his words?
It's his executive editor.
It seems there's something wrong
with the comic.
What was he going to say?
I think
he intended to
confess his love.
How could you bear it?
I'm speechless.
He has failed so many times.
I'm used to it.
Besides, compared to
the confession being interrupted,
I'm more worried about his comic.
I don't know what's wrong with it.
You're a truly good girlfriend.
If I were Ye Qi,
I would confess to you too.
You've already got Ruosong.
By the way,
how are you two getting along recently?
Still so cheesy?
How is it cheesy?
What's that word? We…
Respect to each other.
Since Senior Jieyue is Loreley,
was the way I used to hang around with her
too offensive?
I should be more respectful.
That's Loreley, after all.
Let's go.
Senior Jieyue.
Let me carry your bag.
Why did Ruosong become like this?
Because I know
you are
Loreley.
I should have told you in person.
Tell me. Who ruined my plan?
It doesn't matter who told me.
What matters is
you're not only Loreley
who cured my insomnia,
but also Senior Jieyue who made me obey you
and unable to resist your charm.
Then I'll shake hands with you
as Loreley.
Sure.
How does it feel
to shake hands with Loreley?
It feels like
shaking hands with your favorite NPC
in an escape room.
What kind of strange metaphor is that?
Can I have your autograph?
I can't say no to you.
[Zhou Loreley Jieyue]
So your name is Zhou Loreley Jieyue?
Are you stupid?
My name is Zhou Jieyue. Thank you.
I misunderstood.
Actually, I always have a wish.
I hope I can ask Loreley to help me
when I see her.
Are you thinking of
letting me sing a song
with my beautiful voice?
Then listen.
No, no, no.
It turns out slow songs
can make him fall asleep faster.
Are you crazy?
An aloof beauty.
has become like this.
I can't stand it.
I'm going to see Ye Qi.
I'm Li Lei sitting next to you.
Nice to meet you.
I'm so lucky to sit in the last row.
I won't be found
even if I sleep in class.
What exactly
would a cold person say?
[Good luck]
Actually, I've always…
Wait.
Just go.
Is Qiandai
mad at me?
[Good luck]
It seems that he's drawing a comic
about a cold female lead.
So in his eyes,
the new issue of the comic
is more important than a confession.
I guess he's really in trouble.
She really got mad at me.
But no matter how mad she is,
it's only natural.
Qiandai, what happened yesterday…
[Cut the crap]
Is she going to
punish me by not saying anything?
Qiandai,
what did you have
for lunch today?
[Ramen and pineapple bread in the canteen
& chocolate bread]
You have a good appetite.
It doesn't seem to be a punishment.
In that case,
why doesn't she speak?
How did you
eat the ramen?
She'd rather perform it than say it.
That is
easy to understand.
Qiandai.
Are you okay?
[Is this cool enough?]
I've played a cool girl
to the extreme.
Ye Qi.
Don't let me down.
That's not what cool means, right?
Is she…
Is she not being mad at me
but helping me find inspiration?
[I didn't say that]
Qiandai.
Thank you.
You're still thinking of
helping me at this time.
Once I'm done
with Mr. Gong Jian's matters,
I'll continue
to finish that thing.
It didn't count last time.
It will go smoothly next time.
I'm going home.
I didn't wake you up
since you were asleep.
Do your best, Ye Qi.
[You Li]
Ye Qi, I heard from the editorial office
that you're going to
terminate the contract with Qian Ye.
[Ye Qi]
I haven't decided yet. What's wrong?
[You Li]
If you quit,
take me with you.
I've had enough too.
What happened?
[Ye Qi]
Senior You Li.
Are you moving?
Yes.
I'll change the environment
and start over.
Have you made up your mind
to end the contract with the company?
But if the contract hasn't expired yet,
you'll have to pay the liquidated damages.
It's fine.
I'll pay for my freedom.
It's worth it.
Then,
what made you make this decision?
You must have read my comic.
What do you think?
I think…
I know it
even if you don't tell me.
I used to live in a world of self-comfort
and blocked the sound of criticism.
But last night, I saw a comment
on my website.
I suddenly feel
that I can't go on like this.
What comment?
He said
he was my fan
and liked my previous comics.
But now my comic
is getting weirder.
He started to worry
that if there's something
wrong with my life.
He even thought
someone forced me to draw like this.
He guessed it right.
Qian Ye did force you
to draw many things.
Actually, I've tried to
stand up to Qian Ye.
But it always
ended up with my apology.
Why did you have to apologize to him?
Maybe
I'm a coward.
And I don't have
an executive editor like Mr. Gong Jian,
who can protect me from it.
That's why my comic became like this.
[Yes, I was the one
who had a question for him first.]
[The person who Senior likes is me.]
"Let's Fall in Love"
hasn't failed,
and I owe it all to Mr. Gong Jian
who stood up to Qian Ye for me.
Senior You Li.
Your comic
shouldn't be like this.
No matter what decision you make,
I'll support you.
Thank you.
By the way,
I heard
that Mr. Gong Jian resigned two days ago.
I wonder how he's doing.
Hello?
Yes, I am.
I can come to work tomorrow.
Sure.
Okay.
What?
How much?
800 yuan installation fee?
[Unknown Caller; the number
has been marked as a scam by 68 people]
Ye Qi.
Why are you here?
I was just passing by,
so I came to see you.
[Outstanding Executive Editor, Gong Jian]
Thank you, Mr. Gong Jian.
The meal is coming.
The meal is coming. Take it easy.
Here comes the meal.
Mr. Gong Jian…
You're off work
so early today.
Yes.
It's our boss's birthday
today.
Yes.
So he gave us half a day off.
You're worried about me?
Don't worry about me.
Go back to work.
Otherwise,
I'll break your legs.
Okay, okay.
My grandma is a little deaf.
Who are you talking about?
He…
He is Ye Qi.
He is
one of my colleagues.
A female colleague.
She's so tall.
Come on.
Eat.
Thank you, Grandma.
Grandma has poor eyesight too.
This girl
is so pretty.
Yes.
Look at her left eyebrow.
It's lighter than the one on the right.
Jian
has been stubborn since childhood
and doesn't like to talk to others.
Has he made any trouble at work?
No, no.
Mr. Gong Jian
has been helping us all the way.
We heavily respect Mr. Gong Jian.
So heavy?
He has indeed gained weight.
But he has gained weight
because he has to
work hard
for his family.
It's not easy to make money.
It's just enough for buying the house.
Grandma,
didn't I tell you?
Cream rises to the top.
Yes.
Savings will run out.
I checked
the balance of the debit card last night.
It's running out.
My grandma is funny.
Well.
You're hungry?
Hungry?
Wait.
I'll cook for you.
Go to work
after you're done eating.
Grandma…
I'll go cook.
Thank you, Grandma.
Thank you.
So…
Grandma doesn't know about it yet?
She's old now.
It'll only make her worried.
I plan to
tell her
after my next job is settled.
How was your interview today?
Not very well.
But it's okay.
Cream rises to the top.
Did something happen?
No.
It's just that it's been a long time
since I paid the renewal fee
for the western sapling I adopted.
They notified me
that if I don't pay the renewal fee today,
they will transfer my sapling
to someone else
and remove my name.
Mr. Gong Jian,
I really blame myself.
If it weren't for
protecting "Let's Fall in Love,"
you wouldn't have had
such a big conflict with Qian Ye.
But don't worry.
I'll certainly make you
return to the editorial office.
Ye Qi, listen to me.
Stop having fantasies about Qian Ye.
And stop doing anything
on impulse for me.
I need to answer this call.
Yes.
I'm the one who adopted the sapling,
Mr. Gong.
I would like to ask
if you can give me a few more days.
I'll transfer it to you
as soon as I got the money.
Is that okay?
Is it joy or sorrow?
I can't tell happiness
from sorrow in the waves.
Success. Failure.
I can't tell from the waves.
-Love you…
-Qian Ye.
Have you read the comic I gave you?
You mean that?
Yes.
I think
you handled the twist
of the ending well.
Just draw like this from now on.
You've been
quite smart lately.
Keep it up.
So,
can Mr. Gong Jian come back?
No.
He has been fired.
Where is he going back?
Didn't you promise me
as long as I make you satisfied,
you'll let Mr. Gong Jian come back?
No.
I promised you
I'd reconsider it.
But I've thought about it now.
I don't want him to come back.
Is there a problem?
No problem, right?
Love you or hate you, do you know?
Qian Ye.
For so long,
Mr. Gong Jian has been doing a lot
for "Let's Fall in Love."
Now,
it's time
to let it do something for him.
What do you mean?
Say it again.
Yuyu.
Qiandai.
I'm here to see Ye Qi.
He worked late
on the manuscript yesterday.
I want to see how he's doing.
He didn't come to class today.
He asked me to help him take a sick leave.
Sick leave?
He's sick?
I don't think so.
His voice sounded energetic.
Maybe he's on leave
because he's meeting the deadline.
Is he in trouble again?
I don't know.
I'll visit him after class this afternoon.
Guys,
let's see
the factors that cause procrastination.
How many are there? Three.
[Are you sick?]
Right?
What's the first factor?
Environmental factors. Alright.
What does that mean?
It's the entertainment information
from the outside.
[Gong Shihei; Log In]
[Login successful]
Right?
This is one of the factors.
What's the second one?
Say it together.
The mission characteristics.
Shihei.
Do you know why "Let's Fall in Love"
has been suspended?
Sorry, the subscriber you dialed…
Have you found any clues?
No.
I called Ye Qi but couldn't get through.
I can't reach Mr. Gong Jian either.
Yuyu.
Can you reach Ye Zhen?
Did something happen to Ye Qi?
Ye Qi must have been kidnapped.
I knew it. You think so too?
Look.
The yogurt on the table
hasn't been finished,
which means Ye Qi left in a hurry.
On the ground,
there are more than
one person's footprints,
which means a stranger came in.
I drank the yogurt.
We left the footprints ourselves.
What about the rope on the ground then?
The comic has been suspended.
Ye Qi was kidnapped.
What's the connection between them?
It's easy.
A passionate fan of "Let's Fall in Love"
kidnapped Ye Qi
because he wasn't satisfied
with the plots.
He forced him to suspend the comic
and asked his friends and family
for ransom.
If my guess is correct,
we should
receive the kidnapper's call soon.
Hello?
Hello, is this Ms. Zuo Qiandai?
Yes. Who's speaking?
I am…
Kidnapper!
Are you really the kidnapper?
Please don't kill him. I beg you.
This is a platform for small loans.
Do you need a loan service?
We provide various loan services.
No need.
This kidnapper
is quite cunning.
Ruosong.
Your idea is ridiculous.
In my opinion,
the reason Ye Qi suspended the comic
is that its film and TV
adaptation rights were bought.
And he is going to
pursue a dream in Hollywood.
That's even more ridiculous
than Ruosong's idea.
Or maybe he's going to Hengdian.
Impossible.
Ye Qi won't give up on the comic.
Why hasn't the kidnapper called?
I found a new clue.
What is this?
Password?
Ruosong, you have no common sense.
This is a postal code.
This is a landline phone number.
This kidnapper is so old-school.
He still uses a landline phone.
Qiandai.
Try dialing it.
There might be a clue.
Hello?
It's Ye Qi.
Qiandai.
Ye Qi, are you okay?
Are you with everyone?
I have something personal
to deal with at home.
Why did you turn off your phone?
We are so worried about you.
I broke it on my way back
and sent it to the phone shop.
I was thinking about
telling you after dinner.
Why didn't Ye Zhen reply to us either?
He's cooking with me.
He probably didn't check his phone.
Ye Qi.
Where does the rope
in the corner come from?
I unwrapped the parcel and left it there.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Ye Qi.
What's up with the comic suspension?
Qian Ye fired Mr. Gong Jian.
I think
that continuing to work with him
is a betrayal to Mr. Gong Jian.
It's also irresponsible for our comic.
So,
I terminated the contract with him.
I made the decision on my own
without consulting with you beforehand.
I'm really sorry.
You don't have to be sorry.
I support you.
Me too.
We all support you.
Thank you all.
By the way,
I put your rewards
in the layer under the drawer.
I wanted to give them to you
when I got back.
Since you are all here,
take it away now.
Yuyu.
Please
distribute them.
Okay.
Ye Qi.
When are you coming back?
I…
The fish is almost burnt.
I'll be back in several days.
I have to cook.
I have to go.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
[Gu Zhengxing, Jiang Ruosong,
Chai Ziyu, Zuo Qiandai]
Ye Qi is too polite to us.
How can we
take it?
[Zuo Qiandai]
[Good luck]
Izumi. TSUBAKI/SQUARE ENINIX NOZAKI Projote.
publicize baby. SQUARE ENNIX
(Comic) SERILIZIN GANGAN ONLINE.
MONTHLY GIRLs NOZAKI-KUN
Original. Author Izumi. Twibaki.