[The Comic Bang]
I've got tenosynovitis
due to years of drawing.
[Medical cold compress Anti-inflammatory pain reliever]
Zhou Jieyue, stop running!
Zhou Jieyue! Stop!
Zhou Jieyue is making trouble again!
[Medical cold compress Anti-inflammatory pain reliever]
Since I can't catch him,
I will wait for him.
Bad news! Zhou Jieyue is making trouble again!
I can't catch up with him at all.
The mention of Zhou Jieyue always makes him so enthusiastic.
What should I do?
Good job. Zuo Qiandai.
You introduced your best friend to the guy you like.
And he has fallen in love with her.
Nonsense!
All he does is for his work.
He compliments her in front of you.
He created a character for her in his comic book.
Obviously, he likes her.
You don't know Ye Qi.
You know nothing about men.
He is totally smitten with Zhou Jieyue.
He can’t forget her. No.
I just think Zhou Jieyue is very interesting.
Smitten with her. Isn't he?
I can make him do that too.
Jianzhen travelled to Japan
to teach Buddhism
and spread the profound Chinese culture.
He contributed to Japanese Buddhism, medicine,
architecture and sculpture.
He won respect from Chinese and Japanese people,
as well as Buddhism scholars.
Okay, that's all for today.
Class dismissed.
What are you writing about?
You look so serious.
[Secrets of chasing a man]
Top tips for becoming
the sassy girl that boys can't forget.
Such interesting content was taught in class.
I should've paid attention.
Don't be ridiculous.
This is not what the teacher taught us.
I read it from an official account.
Aren’t those accounts profiting off
people's emotions and anxieties?
Didn't know they provide constructive advice.
You don't understand.
No, I don't.
Let me have a look.
First, make physical contact accidentally.
Second, turn on your charm actively.
Third, change your attitude as soon as
he starts to pay attention to you.
So I can just enjoy being chased by men
after changing my attitude?
Stop!
Stop running!
So I'm the sassy girl
boys can't forget?
No.
You are not.
Zhou Jieyue,
did you pick the lock of your dormitory building?
It has been broken for a week.
You never tried to fix it.
So I removed it for you.
You're fined 200 yuan.
That's another 200!
Goodbye!
Stop!
Don't move! Stop running!
You'll be fined!
Her personality is so impressive.
A mischievous girl like Jieyue
is really eye-catching.
But I don't think I can ever be like her.
What should I do?
[Transformation For the special person Episode 4]
[Mr. Gong Jian]
Hello?
Mr. Gong Jian,
have you read my new manuscript?
What do you think?
The story is decent.
What about the new character?
Do you think it's original?
Yes.
It's pretty good actually.
But I have some issues with the protagonist.
About Mei's feelings.
There are several things that confuses me.
Please clarify them.
Okay.
Wait a moment, please.
First. The upper left panel on page 3.
When Mei gives Lin Mu the lunch box,
[Lin Mu]
what is the dialogue?
She is saying Lin Mu's name.
What about page 5, the sixth panel?
What does Mei say when she sees her love rival?
[Lin Mu]
She is saying Lin Mu's name as well.
What about page 10, the lower right panel?
What does Mei say
after she has defeated her love rival?
[Lin Mu]
Mei has been saying Lin Mu's name during this time.
Mr. Meng Ye,
Don't you think you've made it hard
for readers to understand how Mei feels?
Mei...
She appears this way,
but she's actually a thoughtful person.
Please don't blame her.
I'm blaming you. Okay?
Mr. Meng Ye,
you need look deeper into the character.
Don't I understand Mei enough?
If I were her...
[Ah, is this me]
[No way]
[Mei, I'm here to help you, Lin Mu]
[Advanced Mathematics]
I want to live as Mei
for one day.
Yu Zichai.
If you haven't eaten,
have this, please.
I made it myself.
I wanted to make lunch just for Lin Mu,
but I made too much.
Take it, please.
Lunch made by a man
won't be very good.
What is this?
Looks fancy.
It must taste bad.
It tastes so good!
[Dongsheng University Music Club]
Seniors.
You're awake.
You just fell asleep easily.
You didn't look like suffering from insomnia at all.
Just now...
I think I fell asleep
after listening to one song.
Please send me a copy.
[Loreley]
I didn't expect Loreley's singing
to treat my insomnia caused by Zhou Jieyue,
and help me sleep better.
Maybe Loreley is in there.
But I don't know anyone from the music club.
Hey, you.
Peeping?
No, I'm good.
Who is inviting you to?
I'm looking for Loreley from the music club.
Loreley?
Do you know her?
Are you going to give me her number?
Which name is the coolest?
[Romeo from the drama club Oska from the drama club The prince from the drama club]
Oscar from the drama club is the coolest.
Are you from the drama club?
I'm Gu Zhengxing, president of the drama club.
Department of Architecture. Junior year.
So you're the president of the drama club,
the legendary actor
who never performs on stage.
Junior year.
Then he must know Loreley.
Nice to meet you, senior. I'm Jiang Ruosong,
a freshman majored in Physical Education.
I'm a member of the basketball club.
My favorite dishes are fried pork with chili
and beef stew with Tofu pudding.
Recently, I've suffered from insomnia,
and cured by Loreley from the music club.
So I would like to see her in person.
To summarize your long story,
you want to find out who Loreley is. Right?
I suggest you go in there and ask.
But I don't know anyone from the music club.
And all of them are girls in there.
You're too shy.
It's all right.
Watch and learn.
Hello, everyone.
He may look very serious,
but he doesn't mind how awkward I am.
We've just met,
but he's willing to ask about Loreley for me.
He's a very generous and reliable senior.
Thanks!
How did it go?
We'll perform a musical for the celebration of school anniversary.
I'll tell Lu Dao.
Why are you running off?
Did you ask about Loreley for me?
[Auditorium]
Lu Dao.
Senior.
We will perform a musical for the celebration of school anniversary.
Can we do that?
What kind of musical?
You will start with tightrope walking,
then go through two rings of flames in a row.
After that you'll do 3 backflips while dancing,
and finally, you land on your feet and sing.
No problem.
How come I have no problem with that?
Yeah.
Tightrope walking; going through rings of flames; backflips.
That would be too hard for you.
That's not the problem.
That's not the problem?
Are you saying
you are tone-deaf, so you can't sing?
How is it possible that I'm tone-deaf?
I just...
Yes, I am tone-deaf actually.
Are you disappointed?
No, I'm not.
Many people have things they're not good at.
For example,
I won't become the sassy girl
who is liked by everyone.
You're not helping at all.
What should I do?
Why do I agree on everything he says
without even thinking?
How can I
become a singer?
Oh, yes.
Romeo from the music club.
Loreley.
Yes, Loreley.
Do you know her?
Yes.
I heard that she is not only
good at singing,
but also full of charm.
People who have heard her sing
will never forget her.
They will be enchanted.
If she can teach me to sing...
Can you introduce me to her?
Even the Prince of Dongsheng is attracted to Jieyue.
You want me to teach you to sing?
That's easy.
Kneel down and ask me,
"Please teach me to sing,
Lady Jeiyue!"
Jieyue, she's my friend.
Your request is too juvenile.
Sorry, I'm used to it.
Because in the past...
I only need to kneel down,
Lady Jieyue?
[Music Club]
How can you be so juvenile as well, Lu Dao?
Come.
Sing for me a little.
I must find Loreley this time.
[Dongsheng University Music Club]
Speaking of which, Jieyue is also a member of the music club.
I should ask her.
I've never heard her sing.
Though she won't be as good as Loreley,
she should be good enough.
I got it.
Two options for you.
One, you give up now.
Two, you give up after a year of practice.
Which one would you choose?
Is there
a more hopeful choice?
Actually, I don't wish to sing very well.
I just want to see
my senior smile and say,
"that's not so good".
That would be enough for me.
I see.
Either let Gu give up doing the musical,
or make him forget your performance.
Which one would you choose?
Is it easier to work from Gu's angle ?
Am I really hopeless?
Ruosong.
What are you doing here?
Ye Qi,
I feel so bad for Jieyue.
She is hated on the basketball court,
and she is miserable in the club.
Zhou Jieyue.
Don't worry. I will make him forget about it.
Please do.
Zuo Qiandai.
Ye Qi.
I made too much. This is for you.
Thank you.
Ye Qi made
such a delicate meal just for me.
Could it be
my prayers get answered by the God of Love?
So delicious.
Oh, yes.
Plasters.
This is for you.
So he didn't make lunch only for me.
Are you here to look for materials?
Yes.
Mr. Gong Jian thinks I don't understand
Mei's feelings well enough.
So I decided
to live as Mei for one day.
You're messing around again.
Would you like to join me?
No, I have class.
Should I take this delicious lunch with me?
When someone enjoys the lunch she made,
Mei feels a great sense of gratification.
Who would eat that?
When someone disapproves of what she did,
Mei gets upset
even though she does not talk about it.
Crazy.
Mei's emotions are really fascinating.
Mei.
I'm Mei.
Senior, would you like to play basketball?
Do you want to push your female lead
into men's battlefield?
What did you just say, Senior?
Battlefield.
What's women's battlefield?
Lu Dao,
let's go rehearse together after dinner.
If I make Lu Dao my girlfriend,
Mei will become the enemy of all girls.
This is the battlefield for women.
Are these unwanted plasters
resembling the love I cannot have?
Even if it's just for the delicious lunch,
I shoudn't give up.
How about
I return the lunch box first?
Gu!
Have you seen Ye Qi?
No.
I'm looking for Lu Dao as well.
Lu Dao! Lu Dao!
Come back to the rehearsal with us!
Stop running! Come back to the rehearsal!
Lu Dao!
So this is how it feels to be chased by love rivals.
This is what Mei has been experiencing.
Is it over yet?
Sit tight!
Lu Dao!
Where did she go?
We're late for rehearsal, Shikadima!
We got away.
But why I don't feel fulfilled?
[I can't live without you, Mei. And I can't live without you, Lin Mu.]
Is it because
Lin Mu is not here with me?
Yes.
Mei only makes a great effort
for someone who is special to her.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
You're not the special person.
Why do I feel like I got dumped?
Zuo Qiandai.
Are you here to return the lunch box?
Don't forget your job of blackening tonight.
Only for the special guy,
Mei would make such an effort.
For the special guy, Ye Qi,
I should try harder as well.
Since he likes girls like Zhou Jieyue...
Ye Qi went too far.
He fooled me.
My question is, why did he move you with this?
Because he said I was too heavy.
He didn't want to hurt his arms.
It's easy to lift you up.
I'm sorry.
I forgot that you're a girl.
What's so hard about that?
I can do that too.
Why are you so competitive?
Put me down.
Senior.
Are you here to console me?
I'm here to tell you
the musical is canceled.
Why?
It's so weird.
I asked them to compose music,
but no one agreed to do so.
They looked scared.
As if
someone would beat them up,
if they composed music for me.
Do you think I'm a guy who hits people?
Right?
Zhou Jieyue is indeed reliable.
What was that?
Nothing.
Don't be discouraged.
Let's find a new direction.
Lu Dao,
I've never seen you so enthusiastic.
Sorry. Sorry.
Qiandai.
You...
[Moon Shadow Circus]
I knew it.
It worked even before I get started.
He cleaned up his space for me.
Who was that?
My executive editor, Ms. Gong Jian.
He came here to get my manuscript.
This was Mr. Gong Jian's drink.
I can't drink someone else's drink?
It's very strong...
It's so bitter.
Your home is very tidy.
Really?
That's great.
He really cares about me.
He cares about my opinions a lot.
I was worried
it wasn't tidy enough.
And it left Mr. Gong Jian a bad impression of me.
So he did it all for Mr. Gong Jian.
I, the sassy little witch, cannot lose.
Think fast.
What would Zhou Jieyue do in this situation?
Ye Qi.
You can't be like this.
You're making yourself small.
You don't know how great Mr. Gong Jian is.
What's so great about him?
Tell me.
Mr. Gong Jian is the best executive editor.
He takes his work seriously. He is thoughtful
and responsible.
He replies my messages very quickly.
He was very cute when he was a little boy.
Anyone who sees his childhood photos
will definitely like him.
How cute could he be?
He was really cute.
I can't believe I lost to the executive editor.
No way.
It's time to show my impressive personality.
I'm here to do the blackening,
not to hear you compliment someone.
Hurry up. I've got work to do.
Hurry up.
Sure enough.
Men like this kind of girl.
This is so-called mature women's approach.
All done.
Your blackening is solid as usual.
I've been doing my best.
You act differently today.
I was worried
you wouldn't do it properly.
How different am I?
You've been imitating Zhou Jieyue.
Just be yourself, please.
Why am I doing this?
It's all for you.
I know
that you're doing this for my comic book.
But this is unnecessary.
I could just go observe Zhou Jieyue.
You know nothing.
You don't know how I feel at all.
[Why are you imitating someone? Need attention? Lack confidence?]
I won't blacken for you anymore.
Qiandai.
[Medical cold compress Anti-inflammatory pain reliever]
The nice guy, Ye Qi.
Little angel, Zuo Qiandai.
They are having a fight.
Do you want to consult with me, the relationship expert?
No.
She's just a little embarrassed
because I called her bluff.
She will cool down in a moment.
I... I'll send her a message first.
[Zuo Qiandai]
Would you come and do the blackening the day after tomorrow, please?
Are you sure she'll reply to you?
Yes, of course.
I'm the spokesperson for young girls.
She'll reply to me in less than 10 minutes.
[2 hours later]
Do you think
she hasn't received my message because of netlag?
It's the 5G era now.
How is it possible to have a two-hour delay on the internet?
Is it because
my phone was out of credit?
It's only eight characters.
And your phone is connected to the wireless network.
I'll send her another one.
Is it necessary
to repeat the same mistake?
What do you think I should do?
There are standard answers
to getting along with girls.
[Love Park 3]
The key to unlock a girl's heart
is right here.
[Love Park 3]
[2 hours ago]
Ye Qi is such a straight man
who knows nothing.
How dare he said that to me?
[Why are you imitating someone? Need attention? Lack confidence?]
I won't blacken for you anymore.
Qiandai.
But
I went a bit too far, didn't I?
Come to think of it,
he seemed to have a point.
Would you come and do the blackening the day after tomorrow, please?
[Ye Qi]
Don't try to pretend nothing has happened
by sending a message to me.
It's not that easy.
If you want to show your sincerity,
you should at least
send another one.
I knew you couldn't help it.
[Congratulations! Big discount for you during the event]
[Love Park 3]
[Love Park 3 Game Start]
Can I really find the answer
from this?
Three years ago,
I couldn't talk to girls naturally.
So I started to practice
with the girls in ACG.
And then I went into the real world.
I learned to socialize with different girls.
But gradually, I realized
what I've learned from the girls' games
was only a drop in the bucket.
Are you sure
you haven't gone off the track?
Don't underestimate girls' games.
It's the achievement of countless scholars and experts
who invested significant amounts of time
studying the thoughts
of thousands of girls.
You have a point.
Let's get started then.
Who should I begin with?
First,
pick a name for yourself.
Next,
choose a girl you like to interact with.
Last, you go through many difficulties
to make her your girl.
[Create my role Name Hubby]
Nice to meet you Hubby.
[Level cleared Congratulations]
Does this mean
I clear... clear the level?
Well...
So our answer...
[Love Park 3 Game Loading]
Take it seriously.
No short cuts.
No tricks.
Since it's your first time playing the game,
you'd better focus on one girl only.
[Luo Yuwei Height: 158 cm Age: 16 Occupation: Student Hobbies: Painting]
I choose this girl.
Why does this character
look familiar?
I also think she
looks a bit like Zuo Qiandai.
I don't think so.
Zuo Qiandai wears a white bowknot with red dots.
But her bowknot is red with white dots.
Why do I remember
Qiandai's bowknot is red with white dots?
That's impossible.
You must be wrong.
Am I? Yes.
I just saw her at the door.
I saw her white bowknot with red dots.
But I...
So
did you choose her
because she wears the same bowknot
as Qiandai's?
No.
I read the walkthrough.
This character has the best plot.
So I chose her.
Don't read the spoilers, okay?
Take it seriously.
Do you still want Qiandai to forgive you?
Thank you so much, Qi.
Why does she call me Qi?
It means you two are closer now.
Are you really not going to reply to me?
If a girl doesn't reply to you, it means she's upset.
Do you understand?
How long does a girl stay angry in general?
What if
he'll never come to see me again?
This is the answer.
I had a great time shopping.
Thank you, Qi.
[Ye Qi: Qiandai, let's go shopping this afternoon.]
Qiandai.
Let's go shopping this afternoon.
[Meng Ye Thank you for your support]
Izumi. TSUBAKI/SQUARE NOZAKI. Projote.
publicize baby. SQUARE ENNIX
(Comic) SERILIZIN GANGAN ONLINE.
MONTHLY GIRLs NOZAKI-KUN
Original. Author Izumi. Twibaki.