Why don't you explain what happened that night?
I know nothing at all.
You're the one who hugged me so tightly.
You're the one who got into the bed.
Actually,
having someone by my side
is pretty nice.
♫ I'm unreasonable and sly like a devil in your eyes ♫
♫ Lifting our heads up suddenly, we're clearly out of the loop ♫
♫ Show me. Show me. Your eyes ♫
♫ One step, two steps. I'm in a daze and don't understand easily ♫
♫ Clearing my head, I realize who doesn't care
about the rights and wrongs ♫
♫ Hey, our last playing cards are on the table ♫
♫ Hurry up and write down your promise ♫
♫ Don't change it ♫
♫ In the next moment, tears are falling in the wind like drizzle ♫
♫ When it's sunny, it's my turn to blow haze away for you ♫
♫ Stop hesitating and wandering. Recover from the pain of ♫
♫ Past memories ♫
♫ Strike a fairy-tale match now ♫
♫ And ignite the spark ♫
♫ The little prince in my heart ♫
♫ Plants golden wheat ♫
♫ Your smile is like the sunshine ♫
♫ That will be always on my mind ♫
[Jincherng Metalwork and Design]
♫ In the next moment, tears are falling in the wind like drizzle ♫
♫ When it's sunny, it's my turn to blow haze away for you ♫
♫ Stop hesitating and wandering. Recover from the pain of ♫
♫ Past memories ♫
♫ Strike a fairy-tale match now ♫
♫ And ignite the spark ♫
[Be Loved in House: I Do]
[Episode 6: Indium and Silver]
What are you doing?
- Did you just wake up?
- Y-yes.
Why do you look like this?
Did Little Zhen snore too loud?
Little Zhen?
It's affectionate.
Or... does Little Zhen mind?
Come here. Take a seat. Let's eat together.
Come here. Take a seat.
No wonder there's more food than usual.
Go ahead and eat.
Don't worry. My mom has worked at the hospital before
and knows some nutritionists. After learning about your condition, she must've adjusted her dishes.
Thank you, Auntie.
That's right. All these have no nickel at all so eat with peace of mind.
Look at him. He's been unhealthy since he was little.
And he's even picky.
Mom, I'm not a kid anymore.
Weren't you just sick?
It took me one day to recover!
You're certainly much better than you were as a kid. You don't get sick often.
But whenever you get sick, it's serious.
Isn't it true, Little Zhen?
Auntie, it's truly exhausting to take care of children.
- You worked hard.
- I know.
Mom, who is your son?
Who just said that he isn't a child anymore?
Obviously, you need someone to take care of you, but you're stubborn.
Let me ask you. Have you been dating anyone?
I have to focus on my career first.
But I think you think about love a lot when you're at the design studio.
- Then why does he fail every time he confesses his feelings?
- Mom!
Little Zhen, you're young, capable, and handsome.
A lot of people must like you.
Please teach Lei Lei a few tricks.
Otherwise, every girl he likes will always reject him!
Mom, eat some vegetables.
When your dad was your age, he was already married to me.
Look at yourself. Nobody takes care of you.
I'm so worried about you.
You didn't remarry after Dad passed away.
You're so talkative.
You should eat more.
Auntie, excuse me. Something urgent came up.
We'll have a nice meal together if we have time again.
- Is it that urgent?
- Yes, Auntie. I'm sorry.
Well, don't call me Auntie.
Just call me Big Sis Juan.
- Okay, Big Sis Juan.
- Good.
- I'm your son.
- Oh.
[HWC Roasters]
Welcome...
- It's you.
- What's wrong?
- Am I unwelcome?
- Why are you here now?
Today I went to make up for the missed time,
which is different from a usual working day.
Are you the only one here?
Oh, Cheng Luo doesn't work today.
What about Wan Wan?
- Wan Wan... is being hospitalized.
- It was fine before I left.
It was naughty and ate something it shouldn't have.
I'm so worried.
- Why don't you help take care of it?
- I do!
I mean, I will leave Wan Wan to you.
Do you... want to be lazy?
I need to take care of another one.
Another one?
I took him home from the park last month.
Let's visit the cat after the shop closes.
Okay. I miss it so much.
You haven't seen it for less than half a day.
I also haven't seen you for less than half a day.
- So do you... miss me?
- I do.
T-T-Today's the weekend. Why doesn't Big Sis Cheng Luo work?
Didn't I just say...
she doesn't work today?
The little shop manager is being hospitalized, but
we happen to have one that's available now.
Do you want me to help you cook?
Are you sure?
You're only in charge of drinks and food presentation.
- Take it or leave it.
- I will take it. Of course.
Thank you, Tiny Shop Manager.
Okay. Tiny Shop Manager is ready to work!
- Did you just leave the ore conference?
- Yes.
I also want to catch up with last month's progress,
because we now have a new rule to buy fewer associated metal ores.
Good. The design studio still has a good stock anyway.
Did you just get off work?
I just made up for the missed time. It wasn't really work.
Little Qi Qi was also there just now.
Oh, Si Qi's course starts tomorrow.
- You'll help out tomorrow, won't you?
- I will.
He is already starting his own first course.
Time flies.
We've been together for six years.
Time does fly.
It's even longer than you've worked at the design studio.
♫ Nobody wants to write the wrong time difference in parting ♫
Xiao Qian,
actually I—
Who is Jin Yu Zhen greeting?
I don't know...
So mysterious. He must be up to something.
Have we made up?
I don't know!
[HWC Roasters]
Ever since Jin Yu Zhen moved in,
Bai Xiao Qian hasn't come over.
How much does she hate Jin Yu Zhen?
Big Bro Lei, do you not hate our director now?
I never hated him.
What I hate is the Single Rule, okay?
That doesn't sound right.
You obviously hated him a lot before.
You also took it personally.
Did I?
Why are you nodding, Traitor?
If Big Sis Qian knew your attitude now, she would think of you as a traitor, too.
Wu Si Qi, are you asking to get hit?
Shi Lei, you should think about
what changed your attitude.
Big Bro Gang, can you not be biased towards your junior schoolmate?
Why do you think I'm biased towards him?
- Hi, Cheng Luo.
- Hi, Shi Lei.
Do you have no money to eat again?
Don't say things like that. Big Bro Gang.
Big Bro Gang.
Are you also here for a free meal on a weekend?
I'm here for a free meal indeed.
But I'm not sure what someone's here for.
Don't you think your shop manager is acting really weird lately?
I already found him really weird a long time ago.
He's all smiles every time he sees Si Qi.
We're absolutely not gossiping about both of you.
Love is in the air!
You're not hungry anymore, are you?
- We're hungry, of course.
- We're always hungry.
- We're starving to death.
- So hungry.
Do you also find them odd?
- Since a long time ago.
- Since a long time ago?
Don't you always drink this?
- How thoughtful.
- Just convenient.
Certified organic from Denmark.
No artificial additives, colorings, or preservatives.
The texture of the bubbles is foamy.
I personally recommend the lemon flavor.
So... is it great?
It received the golden award for Denmark's Best Carbonated Drink, so you think it's great?
Were you... busy today?
Not really. Why?
Do you want to find time to talk to my mom?
Talk about what?
She said you're ambitious, and I'm just sitting around.
Did she? But you usually work until late so you don't come home with me.
Oh, I mean...
Xiao... Xiao Qian works till late, too.
Our colleagues at the design studio work very hard.
- That's true.
- Oh,
by the way, are you close to the shop manager trainee of HWC Roasters?
Why are you asking about it?
Nothing.
I... I'll get you a new bottle.
Shi Lei, come help me out.
Oh, okay.
Never mind. Just leave it here. I'll take care of it.
[Home-sharing Rule]
What are you doing behind the door?
You still haven't taken it off?
You also seem happy with only these.
Hey. Hey!
I really think you should explain to my mom.
- She'll understand.
- I'm not talking about the rule.
My mom has been asking me if I'm dating someone.
I've told her that it's impossible with my current job.
Well, I said "impossible,"
not "banned." What do you think?
I'm a true friend, right?
Why didn't you tell her the truth? Then your wish would come true that she would hate me.
You can tell my mom the truth if you want to.
Or you can just abandon this rule.
Do you want to sleep on the bed?
You're changing the subject.
Irresponsible.
Wasn't it because you didn't sleep well that you got into the bed?
Wasn't it because you were hugging me like a koala?
What?
Nothing!
♫ Turning a comma like a kid ♫
♫ Words and expressions run wild, being molded
into the shape of you ♫
No more nightmares.
♫ I guess I'm still the same ♫
It's okay.
♫ I'm carried away by your confusing grammar ♫
♫ I'm like a rendered portrait ♫
♫ A flower blooms on the right side of my chest at dawn ♫
What am I doing?
♫ Nobody wants to write the wrong time difference in parting ♫
♫ I think for a bit, then erase the truth ♫
♫ I want to fly into clouds ♫
♫ It's a little complicated but simple for me to be stubborn ♫
♫ The gentle breeze is blowing into your world ♫
♫ Borrowing could be beautiful ♫
♫ There's no comma leading to a sequel ♫
♫ Who gives a nod? ♫
♫ Who gives precedence to that empty seat? ♫
♫ Why do you always apologize to me? Period ♫
♫ The rain is gently dripping ♫
Hi, everyone. I'm the instructor of this lecture. My name is Wu Si Qi.
Today we're going to get started with the most basic materials and tools.
Due to time constraints, we're going to use soft tin wires today mainly.
Copper is harder, so I'm afraid that
it's more difficult for first-timers to get the hang of it.
Excuse me. Can I add one more student?
That's fine. We're just getting started.
Do you have one more seat, by any chance?
Since we're using some plated metals,
our form reminded everyone about this in advance.
When it comes to metal hypersensitivity, the most common allergy is caused by nickel.
[Jingcherng Metalwork and Design]
♫ Several light years away, this journey is full of obstacles ♫
♫ I'm unreasonable and sly like a devil in your eyes ♫
♫ Lifting our heads up suddenly, we're clearly out of the loop ♫
♫ Show me. Show me. Your eyes ♫
♫ One step, two steps. I'm in a daze and don't understand easily ♫
♫ Clearing my head, I realize who doesn't care
about the rights and wrongs ♫
♫ Hey, our last playing cards are on the table ♫
♫ Hurry up and write down your promise ♫
♫ Don't change it ♫
♫ In the next moment, tears are falling in the wind like drizzle ♫
♫ When it's sunny, it's my turn to blow haze away for you ♫
♫ Stop hesitating and wandering. Recover from
the pain of past memories ♫
♫ Strike a fairy-tale match now ♫
♫ And ignite the spark ♫
Teacher, you haven't given a score.
What do you mean by a score?
What do you think?
I don't know.
There's a romantic air about them.
Not bad.
Big Bro Gang came here to show his support.
Teacher, I'm finished.
Quite special.
I kind of rushed it.
But I came here to wait for someone, anyway.
The person in charge of the design studio invited me to try the course.
Has he arrived?
I forgot to introduce myself. I'm Mu Qiu Liang.
Sorry for making you wait so long.
[HWC Roasters]
Here you are.
Fortunately, you called me over, otherwise, we would have no idea if we were sold out.
I don't think so.
But since they reserved HWC Roasters to discuss things at this time, it's not simple.
I didn't expect the rumor to be true.
- What rumor?
- Oh,
I heard during the ore conference that the week before
an unknown client wanted to place a special order at a high price,
but he insisted on discussions only during a set meeting time.
That's why nobody knows about the contract's contents.
How could this unreliable piece of information draw people's attention?
Because there's no reliable information, it makes so many people want to discuss it.
Even other competitors are interested.
No wonder Jin Yu Zhen has been acting weird lately.
He seems to have been approaching this person.
The course that you just attended,
the instructor is our youngest,
and least experienced teacher.
Also, as I just mentioned,
what we've achieved within the first month since I took over the design studio.
Is that enough for you to rest assured and make a deal with us?
Actually, you don't need to introduce that much.
I'll specify materials and concepts.
Get it done, and I will pay you.
It's as simple as that.
Please tell me.
Main stone: labradorite.
Metal: pure copper.
Effect: weathering.
Does he work in this field?
Since it's customized, you have quite a few requirements,
and we have to provide the main stone.
Adding all these up,
I'm curious to see if you have a budget for it.
Don't worry about it.
I sort of have an idea of the market value.
Give me a quote. I'll pay twice as much.
Wow! It looks like we're getting a raise!
Where is this rich man from?
Once the order is placed, I will pay half of it first.
Once you've confirmed the payment, you can begin to work.
What's the concept?
Love is when you're waiting in the same place without them knowing it.
Waiting for what? Our company doesn't allow romantic relationships.
Exactly.
It's settled.
[HWC Roasters]
- They're going to fight.
- I do want to bet that Shi Lei will win,
but looking at the past, I'll bet on Jin Yu Zhen instead.
I have faith in Big Bro Lei.
Why did you accept this project?
Didn't you hear how much he's willing to pay us?
But don't you think this concept contradicts the Single Rule?
If you had had the meeting at the design studio, you would've shot yourself in the foot.
This is Jingcherng Metalwork and Design's project.
Accepting projects is what a director should do.
I won't sacrifice everyone's interests for personal factors.
I also hope that you're not too emotional to judge these decisions.
It actually makes sense.
But you're against this concept from the bottom of your heart, right?
As the team leader of the design studio, you'll be fully in charge of this project.
Sorry, I'm busy with Chairman Mai's project.
I can wrap it up for you.
- Do you want to take advantage of me?
- Or you can leave it to them.
Hey, I...
may not be able to do it. I can't.
I can't.
Maybe they don't have time.
- Childish.
- Childish?
You're childish.
You accepted the project without discussing it with us.
You didn't consider the practicalities at all.
What if I used my authority as a director
- to force you to do it?
- Okay.
We'll put an end to our relationship.
What did I say? Put an end to our relationship?
What kind of relationship are we in?
A director, a team leader,
and a roommate at most.
Yes, a roommate.
What am I thinking? Shi Lei,
calm down. Calm down.
Breathe in. Breathe out.
Breathe in.
- So what do you want?
- Nothing really.
But as a director, you should take over what other people can't handle, right?
Please take full responsibility.
Okay.
I'll do it.
Little Qi Qi,
Shi Lei actually won the fight!
♫ I do! I do! I do ♫
♫ Because I do! I do! I do ♫
♫ The coffee shop on the street corner ♫
♫ Has the smell of bubbles ♫
♫ I have an indescribable gut feeling ♫
♫ That I may run into someone today ♫
♫ It's finally on the hour ♫
♫ The streets are ablaze with color as usual ♫
♫ Feeling romantic in the breeze alongside the river ♫
♫ I can't help spinning excitedly ♫
♫ The midnight showing got delayed ♫
♫ That day you made a promise ♫
♫ And I wished upon a shooting star ♫
♫ Your face profile, smile and eyes are irresistible ♫
♫ Are irresistible ♫
♫ I'm gonna share with you, my love ♫
♫ I do, do, do ♫
♫ We've promised to meet again in early summer ♫
♫ With the wings that brought us together ♫
♫ I'll fly when sunshine comes after rain ♫
♫ I'll hold it in my hand forever, blooming for you ♫
♫ I know. Oh, oh, oh ♫
Can you tell me
what kind of story
your scar has to tell?