It hurts.
Be careful.
Damn it!
What I worried about most actually happened.
Living under the same roof as that idiot
will be life-threatening.
♫ Show me. Show me. Your eyes ♫
♫ One step, two steps. I’m in a daze and don't understand easily ♫
♫ Clearing my head, I realize who doesn't
care about the rights and wrongs ♫
♫ Hey, our last playing cards are on the table ♫
♫ Hurry up and write down your promise ♫
♫ Don't change it ♫
♫ In the next moment, tears are falling in the wind like drizzle ♫
♫ When it's sunny, it's my turn to blow haze away for you ♫
♫ Stop hesitating and wandering. Recover from the pain of ♫
♫ Past memories ♫
♫ Strike a fairy-tale match now ♫
♫ And ignite the spark ♫
♫ The little prince in my heart ♫
♫ Plants golden wheat ♫
♫ Your smile is like the sunshine ♫
♫ That will be always on my mind ♫
[Jingcherng Metalwork and Design]
♫ In the next moment, tears are falling in the wind like drizzle ♫
♫ When it's sunny, it's my turn to blow haze away for you ♫
♫ Stop hesitating and wandering. Recover from the pain of ♫
♫ Past memories ♫
♫ Strike a fairy-tale match now ♫
♫ And ignite the spark ♫
[Be Loved in House: I Do]
Hi, everyone!
Today we've come to this coffee shop called HWC Roasters.
This is the shop manager of HWC Roasters, Yan Zhao Gang.
He's very handsome, isn't he?
I will tell you what,
the shop manager, staff, customers, and even the cat
are very attractive. Look!
You've arrived.
Wu Si Qi.
Hi, Big Bro Lei.
Why didn't you reply to my messages or answer my calls?
I… forgot to bring my phone with me.
Then why didn't you come to work?
You don't have school until next week, right?
I… will go in the afternoon to make up for the time.
Are you still staying at your friend's place?
Do you need help?
It is okay.
Don't be nervous.
This is what I promised you yesterday.
Thank you.
No, Big Bro Gang.
You have no idea how ridiculous it was yesterday.
But I think the problem over there is more serious.
When did he get here?
A bit earlier than you guys.
Once he came in, he just curled up there without ordering anything.
Red wine.
You drank them all yesterday.
How about malta?
Are you still angry at Wang Jing?
Of course.
He hasn't explained it to me at all since yesterday.
No sense of responsibility whatsoever.
I will keep saying it. So what?
Who dares to be with you?
Are you speaking in his favor? All men are the same.
Where's Cheng Luo? I want her to be the judge.
She seems to be off.
That's perfect. Otherwise, someone would be really disappointed.
Why are you looking at me?
The real culprit is the King of Qin, Jin Yu Zhen, okay?
Exactly. That damn Jin Yu Zhen.
He's a devil indeed. That's okay, my little Qiqi.
We are in the same situation.
Exactly. I'm also moving out today.
Are you going to move in with me? I will pay the rent.
We will sideline him together.
- Why are you so loud?
- I've come up with a plan.
This plan requires the cooperation of you both,
especially Shi Lei.
Me?
I seriously think the fact that Jin Yu Zhen made that damn Single Rule…
I think he must be mentally ill.
Usually, people become mentally ill
due to something that happened in the past
or hidden secrets.
So if we find out about it,
we will have bargaining chips.
The best person for this job is...
But I don't want to live with him. Why me?
You're the closest to him.
Listen to me. No matter how reserved someone is, they'll loosen up at some point.
That's why, as long as you don't move out,
you can keep monitoring him after work. Then—
Then... Then...
There's nothing you can do about things from the past.
If he's in an on-again, off-again relationship, then we can sit back and enjoy the show.
But isn't it a waste of time if we end up finding nothing at all?
Nothing? Then we will create something.
What do those gossip magazines do?
Invent a story. Take something out of context. Who can't do that?
Big Sis Qian, I think this...
This plan is wonderful, isn't it?
That's right. Look,
you got kicked out,
and Shi Lei lost a really good roommate and junior coworker.
Wang Jing became a coward.
What about my wedding ring? What about my wedding?
Aren't you angry?
Don't you want revenge?
This kind of boss is extremely despicable!
Precisely!
Those who are married should quit.
Those with romantic relationships should quit, too.
Why?
Because I'm your director.
- From now on, I will live here.
- But I said we already live here.
It has nothing to do with me.
I have decided to help you get even with him.
The goal is to make Jin Yu Zhen tear off that stupid Single Rule!
Tear off that stupid Single Rule!
I'm starting to admire you.
[Jingcherng Metalwork and Design]
I think we should start an investigation into the people around him.
Do you have any ideas?
No.
You're an underachiever.
All right.
We should
create a stressful workplace.
Even though he's the director,
we can still make him powerless.
Do you mean...
sidelining him?
But we don't really have any projects.
Or... do you have anything in mind?
Nothing.
You're an underachiever, Bai Xiao Qian!
Your whole family is!
Well, what do you have in mind, Si Qi?
Little Qiqi!
Si Qi?
- Si Qi!
- Wu Si Qi!
He...
He went to school already.
Shi Lei,
come to my office.
Seize this chance.
Right. Confirm it for me.
Hopefully, we will get some news by next month.
Okay. Let's keep in touch.
Shouldn't you knock before entering?
How can I help you, Mr. Director?
Do an inventory count of the design studio's current raw materials.
By the end of this month, I want all metals and minerals
that contain nickel to disappear.
Why?
To make our shop friendly to nickel-allergic customers,
where they can shop worry-free, is our future goal.
We can make exceptions under special circumstances.
[Jingcherng Metalwork and Design, Future Management Goals]
We don't use nickel unless a customer requests it.
Have you already started advertising?
If you were hungry, and there was a table full of delicious food right in front of you,
- would you wait until the food cools down before eating?
- What?
Of course not. I eat hot food for sure.
Exactly. If we didn't advertise now,
the food would cool down.
But we have many materials with nickel.
Time is really tight if you want everything gone by the end of this month.
It's hard for you to immediately come up with ideas when you lack experience.
- I think you—
- Don't stick your nose in my business!
Oh,
Wu Si Qi has just qualified as a lecturer, right?
So what?
He has achieved it without even finishing school, not bad at all.
Let him start gaining hands-on experience.
Arrange for him to take the design studio's classes when time permits.
Use up the raw materials simultaneously.
Then... I will go back and work.
You can do it.
Hi, we are from Jingcherng Metalwork and Design.
This is our latest project, where we use only titanium-based hypoallergenic metals.
We have a course where you can make accessories out of metal wire.
I think it's especially suitable for you both.
If you're interested, you can come over here and fill out an application form.
Hi, Sir. We are from Jingcherng Metalwork and Design.
♫ The coffee shop on the street corner ♫
♫ Has the smell of bubbles ♫
♫ I have an indescribable gut feeling ♫
♫ That I may run into someone today ♫
♫ It's finally on the hour ♫
♫ The streets are ablaze with color as usual ♫
♫ Feeling romantic in the breeze alongside the river ♫
♫ I can't help spinning excitedly ♫
♫ The midnight showing got delayed ♫
♫ That day you made a promise ♫
♫ And I wished upon a shooting star ♫
♫ Your face profile, smile and eyes ♫
You can definitely do it.
[Titanium-based hypoallergenic material]
♫ I'm gonna share with you, my love ♫
Wang Jing, this time our ores may...
Wang Jing.
This time our ores...
Bai Xiao Qian.
Senior.
It has been so long since I last saw you.
When did you come back?
At the end of last year. You know, because of the pandemic.
I did hear news of you from time to time.
But...
where did you go these past two, three years?
Senior, you're still the same. You haven't changed much.
As for you, you've changed a lot.
Really?
People from the craft workshop often eat here.
But...
the "Director Jin" that they describe
is very different from the one I know.
You finished work already.
Why don't you head home and rest?
Today... I want to go home later.
Let me know if you want to eat something.
He moved out quickly.
What are you looking at?
- Why are you still here?
- Why not?
Didn't you ask me to give you one day to move out?
So... are you kicking me out now?
Weren't you the one insisting on moving out?
But on second thought,
if I move out right now,
isn't that exactly what you want?
I'm the most experienced employee of the craft workshop, after all.
It is also my right to live here, isn't it?
Didn't you say so yourself?
- What are you doing?
- This is mine.
It doesn't hurt to let me borrow it to dry myself with.
Use this instead.
Are you a pervert?
I'm not leaving anyway.
I will keep an eye on you.
- Your food is ready.
- Thank you.
Is your class finished?
Yes.
I haven't seen this dish before.
Of course. It is the chef's special.
Do you want one?
I want two.
It isn't a good idea to eat that much.
Are you that stressed lately?
I'm so stressed that I'm questioning my life.
This dish is absolutely delicious.
You can cook this at home.
There are more ingredients in the shop than in my home.
I will try my best.
Did you invite Si Qi to your place?
Yes, he's a little tenant.
Is Wu Si Qi staying at your house?
That night, he was crying alone in the park.
After figuring out what happened, I told him
to move in with me. No big deal.
Did you cry? Did you dare to cry?
Why don't you look at who I live with? I should be the one crying.
I really want to move out, too.
Sorry, there are no rooms left.
Yeah. You also have a mission.
If you move in with us, Big Sis Qian will...
I surely will.
Focus on your food.
Just a minute. The food will be ready soon.
Do you happen to be heading home, too?
Yes.
What's with all these knives?
The third Home-sharing Rule says
the kitchen is first come, first served.
Sorry.
I'm full.
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
Stay still.
The wound is so small.
I got hurt, not you.
I can take care of this myself.
I know how to handle knife wounds better than you do.
Aren't you curious to know why I wear gloves?
What... What will you do?
Because this way, I won't leave any fingerprints.
You pervert!
So do you live with a perverted killer now?
Are you doubting me now?
I'm looking at it as a crime solver.
What are you laughing at?
Are you smirking, too?
Did you do the inventory count of the materials that contain or are plated with nickel?
Of course.
One more thing. Come with me.
The purchase and compilation of minerals should be made in the last week of this month.
That's how we stock up on materials for spring.
Why isn't there any progress at all?
Wang Jing is the one who is in charge of this.
He's still not back to himself.
The reason is...
Didn't Bai Xiao Qian help Wang Jing out?
They're not on speaking terms.
As for the reason...
Fine.
Wu Si Qi is just getting on track so we will talk about him later.
What about you?
You're too focused on helping Wang Jing out
to handle the companies that have cooperated with us.
We've lost almost all the orders to our competitors.
I'm not to blame, am I?
Forget it.
I'll come up with ways to get more orders.
Director, you seem very confident in yourself.
Do you dare to make a bet?
- I don't get it.
- You and me.
Let's make a bet. Do you dare?
♫ I do! I do! I do ♫
♫ Because I do! I do! I do ♫
♫ The coffee shop on the street corner ♫
♫ Has the smell of bubbles ♫
♫ I have an indescribable gut feeling ♫
♫ That I may run into someone today ♫
♫ It's finally on the hour ♫
♫ The streets are ablaze with color as usual ♫
♫ Feeling romantic in the breeze alongside the river ♫
♫ I can't help spinning excitedly ♫
♫ The midnight showing got delayed ♫
♫ That day you made a promise ♫
♫ And I wished upon a shooting star ♫
♫ Your face profile, smile and eyes ♫
♫ Are irresistible ♫
♫ I'm gonna share with you, my love ♫
♫ I do, do, do. We've promised to meet again in early summer ♫
♫ With the wings that brought us together ♫
♫ I'll fly when sunshine comes after rain ♫
♫ I'll hold it in my hand forever, blooming for you ♫
♫ I know. Oh, oh, oh ♫
Then what do you want?
To eat you up.