Chairman Park Seong-jin
wasn't murdered by Chairman Hwang Do-won.
It was Martin.
A video of him confessing his crime
was recorded on Aji 3.
I heard that the emergency board meeting
is tomorrow.
I think we should all go--
No.
That won't solve anything.
Then, do you have any other ideas?
I'm going to make sure
they don't use my illness against me
from now on.
Are you going in?
Try some.
When you were young,
I used to get this bread
for you and Min-gyu.
You both loved it so much.
You know about it too, don't you?
I'm talking about Min-gyu.
Do you know about his illness?
Of course, I do.
He suffered from the illness for 15 years.
Fifteen years?
Yes.
It started when his parents passed away.
It's probably because he was deeply hurt
by a lot of people back then.
Sign this.
My dad says if you sign this,
we can live together.
Cheer up, my friend.
No, we're a family now.
Get off! Get away from me!
CLAIM
APPLICANT: HWANG DO-WON
After that day,
Min-gyu locked himself up in this house
for 15 years.
He couldn't have any physical contact
with other people,
he cooked his own food,
and he just endured the pain.
More importantly,
no one came to visit him.
Why didn't you visit him?
I am sorry.
If you're sorry, you need to say it
in order for him to know.
It's apparently because of me.
Min-gyu got sick because of me.
I used to feel really upset.
I couldn't understand
why he was so harsh on me.
how he could treat me that way
when we used to be friends.
I always thought I was the victim.
And I slowly started to
rationalize my actions...
and my dad's actions.
You were young back then.
You didn't know
he had that kind of illness.
I'm sure Min-gyu will understand.
It's not too late.
You can go back to being friends.
Do you really think so?
He probably can't sleep
because of tomorrow's press conference.
Hey, what's up?
What? You're where?
When did you arrive?
Just a while ago.
Are you okay?
Friend Mode.
What's with the frowning?
Do you want me to straighten it out
with an iron?
Who made you feel this way?
Bring them over.
I'll beat the hell out of them.
My gosh, you're cute.
You better not act this cute
around others.
You're the only person
who thinks I'm cute.
What? Why wouldn't anyone
think you're cute?
I know, right?
You're the cutest and prettiest woman
out of all the women I know.
You don't know a lot of women.
Should I get to know some more women then?
I'm going to kill you.
If I'm so cute,
then you can promote me
and start calling me Pretty again.
No, I can't do that.
Why not?
There's another rank
right above the rank of Pretty,
and that's you.
What kind of rank is that?
It's a special rank that I made
just for you with all of your secrets.
Gosh, I told you everything.
There's nothing more to tell.
When? I'm sure there's more.
I already told you everything.
-Do you want me to bring it up again?
-You're so mean.
-I know there's more.
-There's nothing more to tell.
-Gosh, just admit it.
-Hey.
You're driving me crazy.
Do you feel better?
Yes.
Thanks to you,
I'll be able to win the fight tomorrow.
Are you sure you don't need me there?
Do you want me to stand
at the back of the conference room?
No, it's okay.
I'll go by myself.
Wherever I am,
I know that you'll always be by my side.
I wish you all the best.
I'll do my best to win.
We shall begin
the emergency board meeting.
Today's agenda is critical to the future
of KM Financial,
and the board must come
to a quick decision.
Just a second.
Let me say something
before you announce the agenda.
Director Kim is currently holding
a press conference.
It may have a big effect
on today's meeting.
Therefore, I think we should first check
what he'll be announcing.
What are you talking about?
Let's just get on with it.
But he might be announcing
something really important.
Are you sure Director Kim
isn't just trying to trick us?
KM FINANCIAL DIRECTOR KIM MIN-GYU
PRESS CONFERENCE
I'm KM Financial's director,
Kim Min-gyu.
I also...
suffer from...
a human allergy.
As soon as I come into physical contact
with a human being,
I start to have difficulty breathing.
And I start getting rashes on my body.
And because of this,
I always carried around my gloves
and my baton.
I'm sure a lot of you may wonder
how someone like me was able
to work as a director of a big firm.
Every time I came to the office
all the employees thankfully kept
their distance from me.
Therefore, I had no trouble
attending meetings.
And as for my other duties,
I was able to take care of them
without a problem.
Thanks to our capable Mr. Cho.
There's one thing I'm proudly able
to tell everyone.
I'm slowly starting to heal from this
so-called human allergy.
One day, out of the blue,
a robot suddenly came to my life.
I became friends with that robot.
And I tried to connect with it.
Yes.
That's what happened.
That robot...
was sometimes human.
And sometimes a robot.
My emotions
were input
into that robot
and that person.
That's how...
this miracle happened.
That fact
completely changed the way I view things.
This will be yet
another scoop for the reporters present.
KM Financial
will go from financing
Mergers and Acquisitions
to investing in futuristic industries
that involve human sensibilities.
This is your first change
in business strategy in 15 years.
Do you have anything mapped out?
First of all, KM Financial
will invest heavily
in developing robots with AI
that can communicate with us
on an emotional level.
With Doctor Hong Baek-gyun,
a world-class roboticist,
we will bring in
the fourth industrial revolution,
and we will offer any support necessary.
Is Doctor Hong in Seoul?
-Can we interview him?
-Is your allergy curable?
-Look over here.
-Where is that robot?
Can you tell us?
Can you tell us anything else?
Doctor, it looks like
you'll have quite a hassle.
We'll bring in
the fourth industrial revolution.
I suddenly feel a weight on my shoulders.
You're really heavy. Stop it.
Doctor, can I talk to you in private?
Our stock price is soaring.
-Is it really?
-What's going on?
-My goodness.
-It's skyrocketing.
It went up so much.
Look.
May I have your attention, please?
We're running out of time.
We shall now vote
on dismissing Director Kim...
The press conference we just saw
convinced me
beyond a shadow of doubt that Director Kim
is someone we can't do without.
I, therefore,
agree wholeheartedly
with Director Kim's new road map.
As a shareholder
and as Chairman Hwang's representative
on the agenda of Director Kim's dismissal,
I vote no.
What do you mean?
-We came to vote yes.
-What's happening?
-What's going on?
-It's nonsense.
I also support Director Kim Min-gyu.
I'm against his dismissal.
-My goodness.
-What is happening here?
-We came here to get rid of him.
-What are they talking about?
This is a mess.
-Hi, did you watch?
-Yes.
Kim Min-gyu, you were awesome,
incredibly cool.
This is the kind of guy your boyfriend is.
I have to go to the company.
Go and wait somewhere.
I'll come over later.
Thank you.
Okay, good luck wrapping it up.
You have to really do your best.
You know I invested in you, right?
Thank you, but...
will you be okay?
I trust your competence.
That's why I'm excited
about the new future you proposed.
Will there be a lot I can do too?
Actually, Yu-cheol worked harder than I
to convince the directors.
I think I should leave
and let you two talk
about the misunderstandings you've had
for 15 years.
I found out...
what the papers I had given to you meant.
What my dad had tried to do to you.
I found the papers in my dad's study.
But...
I couldn't tell you that I knew.
I pretended not to know what had happened.
I pretended I had not wronged you at all.
I believed my dad hadn't done that
out of malice.
That's how I rationalized it away.
Just to protect myself.
It was coward
and foolish.
Sorry it took so long.
I'm sorry, Min-gyu.
We found evidence
that Martin killed
Chairman Park Seong-jin.
Interpol got involved.
Go and convince your dad.
He has to turn himself in
to get a lower sentence.
Okay.
Thanks for telling me.
I think
I'll be okay this time.
Hi. Where are you?
Shall we meet on the street
we walked on when it was snowing?
Shall we? Okay, I'll be right there.
When...
How long...
have you been standing there?
Quite a while now.
I knocked before coming in.
Have a seat.
You did very well today.
Thank you.
I think we sorted everything out.
What do you think?
Yes, I think so, too.
We should all go home early today.
In that case, I would like you to accept
my letter of resignation.
What?
That...
I already said--
That was your opinion.
I haven't changed my mind...
about resigning.
But--
I stayed because there was a lot to do.
Now that everything's done, so as planned,
I should leave as well.
Mr. Cho.
Please, sir.
Well...
goodbye.
Why do you want to buy clothes?
You'll be swamped
with interview requests now.
I'll wear what I have.
Don't you think Min-gyu
has an unusual charm?
He looks like a little brother at home.
But at work, he has this killer charisma.
He's a director for a reason.
He put up a good fight.
What about me?
I'm used to you, so it's impossible
to find a new side of you.
What is it?
Do you want to go out with me?
What?
How long are you going to stare?
Until you look back at me.
There. Happy?
Do you want to go out with me?
Why are you laughing?
Let's go.
Dr. Hong, aren't you going to answer me?
It's cold. Let's go.
Dad, I'm sorry.
I'm not living the life
you wanted me to live.
But I'll live happily.
I know that deep in your heart,
you would want me to be happy.
That's what I believe.
I thought you were nervous,
but you did so well.
I was really nervous at first,
but I thought of you
after taking a deep breath.
From that point on,
I was able to talk smoothly.
My spirit helped you.
Also,
it was my first time in 15 years
that I had a real conversation
with Yu-cheol.
I even suggested
that we shake hands first.
For some reason,
I thought it would be okay.
-You shook hands?
-Yes.
Were you okay?
Yes.
Once I thought of you, I was fine.
You should take good care
of this treasure of yours.
Gosh, it's so cold.
Come here.
If you're cold,
why are you giving this to me?
To take good care of my treasure.
What do you want to do today?
I'll do anything for you.
Wait. Is this really what you want?
Yes.
Seriously.
Hey.
What is Mr. Cho like?
Once he says no, it's a no.
I see. What kind of person is he to you?
Someone like a dad?
Mr. Cho quit today.
What? Really?
Yes.
I don't know
how to persuade him.
Mr. Cho...
Quit?
Ji-a's brother?
He handed in a resignation letter?
Did you offend him or something?
Maybe a little? It was long ago.
To be honest, a lot. But...
it wasn't anything recent.
I don't think he's the type of person
who hold grudges.
Hey, didn't you see him
sue his own sister?
Grudges?
He's such a stubborn guy.
He must be uncomfortable.
With what?
To have his sister's boyfriend
as his boss.
You're right.
I just imagined it,
and it's so uncomfortable.
Would it be that uncomfortable?
I thought we got along well.
Work is work.
It's different when it's personal.
Is this season two
of turning Kim Min-gyu into a human?
Yes.
I got it. This is it.
What is it?
He doesn't like you as Ji-a's boyfriend.
Hey.
-Watch your mouth.
-Keep that closed.
They were not helpful at all.
Why are you following me in?
I'm going to rest.
-What is it?
-Hey.
Where do kids go for dates these days?
Why are you asking me such a thing?
Why? Can't I ask a question?
You don't have anyone
to go on a date with.
Wait a minute.
Do you?
No way. There are no women around.
Be quiet.
I said be quiet.
Since when?
Hey.
You guys actually look good together.
-Of course.
-I went to a fun place today.
Do you want to know where?
Where is it?
This is for you.
-Thank you.
-No problem.
Hey, did you really quit your job?
Don't worry,
it has nothing to do with you.
What?
You quit your job?
Hong-ju.
Are you kidding me right now?
When you confessed everything to me,
I told you to never lie to me again.
What is this? You quit without telling me?
Well...
I handed in the resignation letter
quite a while ago.
What? You handed in a resignation letter
a while ago?
This is making me really mad. Gosh!
-Hong-ju, calm down.
-Hong-ju.
Stop!
How can I calm down?
Mom, you will scare the baby.
Right. I'm sorry.
How are you so inflexible?
Go get your resignation letter back
right away.
Answer me.
Okay.
You fool.
It's not over yet.
-You can--
-No.
It's over.
They found evidence
where Martin admitted his murder.
You need to confess everything you know
before he gets arrested.
That's the only way
to reduce your sentence.
Impossible!
It's not over for Hwang Do-won!
Come to your senses, Father.
Please.
So, you will pay for a portion of the rent
in exchange for a corner in the café?
Yes. What was it called again? Shop--
-Shop in shop?
-Yes.
I want to do that in a corner
of your café.
I will use it as my office
as well as a showroom.
I like that. Let's do it.
What about development expenses?
Last time, Hong-ju--
She's furious right now. I can't ask her.
Why? Did something happen?
My brother quit his job.
I can see why she's mad.
Ask Kim Min-gyu to invest.
Isn't it an investment company now?
I will make it work on my own.
Something called crowdfunding
or something.
-"Crowdfunding"?
-Yes.
It's a medium
where I publish my idea on the internet
to receive investment.
Then, give me a percentage
of your earnings
instead of paying rent.
Let's go, Cho Ji-a!
Yes!
Now, I...
have to go on a date.
I'll close the café.
Okay.
Are you feeling all right?
Yes. I'm all better now.
I'm just like everyone else.
I can even touch you.
I'm sorry.
-Hey.
Please go ahead.
Well...
It's about your resignation letter.
Yes. The letter...
I think I should...
Well...
The resignation letter...
Okay. I will just process it, then.
It looks like your mind is set.
I would really prefer for you
to stay on the team,
but maybe you're uncomfortable
because of Ji-a.
But...
if you ever change your mind,
please don't hesitate to tell me.
I would welcome you back with open arms.
Yes. What is it?
Where are you?
At Summer Snow.
Should I come over?
I'm working.
What's more important? Me or work?
Work is important, and so are you.
Gosh. I miss you a lot.
I miss you too.
I'll call you when I finish this.
Okay. Bye.
CROWDFUNDING REGISTRATION
I can sit here for a while, right?
You can work. I'll just watch you.
You're not allowed to talk to me.
Fine. What is it? Tell me.
Well...
Mr. Cho--
Right, my brother!
He must have come to see you
to get his registration letter back.
I forgot to tell you.
-What?
-His wife has him under her thumb.
She ordered him to get it back.
It's good news, right?
Did you see him today?
Yes. We met up.
And?
I told him I would process it.
I see.
I'm suddenly getting a headache.
This isn't working. Come over to my house.
What?
My brother won't be able
to take his word back anymore.
So you should come to my house,
and give his letter of resignation back
right in front of my sister-in-law.
Then my brother won't be able to refuse.
I get what you mean.
I think I can do that. Okay.
And...
if I go over to your house,
are you going to show me your room?
No, I can't show you my room.
It's too dirty.
You already saw my room.
Why can't I see yours?
To be honest, I--
You're a fast learner.
I'm going to kill you if you kiss.
You video called me because you knew
I took my makeup off, didn't you?
No. I just wanted to see your face
while we talk.
It hasn't even been that long
since we said goodbye.
You're so cute.
I can't watch this.
Everyone else but me is dating.
This is sad.
Even the sauce container is in a pair.
How annoying.
Eddie?
Jane?
When did you come to Korea?
No, that's not right.
Dear all holy beings, thank you!
There are still a lot of people.
Watching people is fun, too.
This feels nice.
I like it, too.
I think
we spent too much time locked
inside the laboratory.
We develop robots
that communicate with humans,
but we
didn't have much contact
with the outside world.
We were all too busy with research.
Let's do this more often.
Sure.
What do you think is around that corner?
Let's go and find out.
Sure, let's go.
You put on a terrific scheme.
Did you enjoy scamming the naive kids?
Yu-cheol
will soon be reinstated as CEO.
Both Yu-cheol and Ri-el
will live their own lives.
We will run KM Financial in a way
that is very different from before.
You arrogant fool.
You and my dad parted ways as enemies.
Yu-cheol and I are different.
We will not repeat
what went wrong in the past.
Everything is over at last.
How do you feel? Relieved?
I don't feel as relieved or excited
as I thought I would.
I just think
I'm realizing that what happened
in the past no longer hurts me.
That's a huge deal. You're healing.
Though we'll never know
when you'll get hurt again.
I'm well acquainted
with pain at this point.
Yes.
If you comfort yourself along the way,
so that you're less hurt and less sad,
time will pass.
Doctor, I think I need to hang up.
I'm getting an urgent call.
Is it Ji-a?
You're hurting me now, you know.
Doctor Oh.
I'll call you right back. Bye.
Hi. It's me.
My brother's at home right now.
So is Hong-ju.
Oh, really? Okay, then.
I'm wearing a suit right now.
I'm not even wearing a tie.
That's perfect.
Is it? Okay, then.
Hey, what does your niece like?
Why did you go and did what you did?
Sorry, Dong-hyeon.
I'm on your side,
whatever anyone else says.
-Sir.
-Nice to... No.
How are you?
Why are you here?
Oh, Ji-a?
-Ji-a.
-No, I...
I'm here to see you.
It's Kim Min-gyu.
Hi, Cho Dong-hyeon.
How do you know my daughter?
That's...
-A secret.
-A secret?
A secret.
Do you like dak-bokkeum-tang?
Yes.
Have some with us.
Okay.
She was cute.
She was just like how she is now.
I would want to meet you.
What?
Did your allergy go away?
Yes, it did.
The person you said you liked a lot
is my aunt, right?
Yes, it was.
But that's our secret.
I wasn't sure what to buy...
You didn't have to get me anything.
Wow, this is so pretty.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
This is so cute.
It's lovely.
It looks like they're on a blind date.
It does.
Mr. Kim.
Yes?
What brings you here?
Well...
I...
I don't think I can live without Mr. Cho.
What?
Mr. Cho.
I like you.
A lot.
To me, you are
a colleague and mentor
that I want to keep close forever.
Dad, you're so cool.
Yes, he's amazing.
Therefore,
I cannot accept your resignation.
I would like you to tear it up yourself.
I have one condition.
Sure, what is it?
For as long as you date my sister,
let's keep work apart
from our private lives.
I agree.
At work, you're my superior,
but once we leave work,
can I treat you
like my sister's boyfriend?
Yes, please do that.
Okay, Min-gyu.
Okay, then, Jin-bae.
There's really nothing to see in here.
SCISSORS THAT HELP YOU
CUT IN A STRAIGHT LINE.
HEART BALL
What should I do?
Why?
I like you even more.
-I have all this.
-What?
Everything you made
is in my yellow cabinet at home.
That's a lie.
Come and see for yourself.
The cleaning thing too?
Yes.
No way.
You were one of the five people?
Where did you get them? I barely sold any.
Kiss me and I'll tell.
Auntie!
Mom's acting strangely.
Wait, do you need anything?
-No.
-My wallet.
Mom, are you okay?
-Yes.
-She's okay.
Ask Auntie to dress you.
Hurry, we need a car.
Call a taxi.
I'll drive you.
Okay, your car, then.
Dong-hyeon, come on outside.
Take your time.
It's okay, Hong-ju.
It will be okay.
This is our second child.
Don't be so nervous.
It's okay.
Dad, look at me. I grew up pretty well.
You did.
Hold your mom's hand.
Take a deep breath.
MATERNITY WARD
Hong-ju's fine.
The baby's healthy.
My daughter
is beautiful.
Like a princess.
-You're a big sister now.
-Yes.
She looks so pretty.
Like an angel, right?
That's your sister, Dong-hyeon.
Welcome. It's your first day in the world.
2 YEARS LATER
We want to...
make connections to something
and want contact with people.
That's because it's human instinct,
hardwired into our DNA.
The Santa Maria Team
focused on that instinct
while developing our new AI robot.
If there were a robot
that could communicate
on an emotional level,
how would our lives change?
To a person
who is physically and emotionally drained,
what would it mean to have a robot
that comforts them
with emotions
that were programmed into it?
I can tell you with confidence
that it would make us more human.
The something that flows
from human to human.
If we could unravel
the secret behind emotional connections,
I was confident
we could create a revolutionary AI robot.
And finally,
the Santa Maria Team succeeded
in solving part of that secret.
We named the robot
after Daeyang Shipbuilding's
late Chairman Park Seong-jin.
Ladies and gentlemen,
let me introduce the robot
that will rewrite the history of androids.
Hello.
DESTINATION SOKCHO
MANAGING DIRECTOR CHO JIN-BAE
I'll leave right now.
Shall we proceed with this?
Yes. Do more research over the weekend,
and we'll meet again on Monday morning.
-Okay.
-Great.
I have to go.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
We won't be late, will we?
I think we'll be on time.
-The diapers
-Honey.
Oh, dear.
I woke her up.
You just woke up?
-Oh, dear.
-Pack the rest.
We're running late, let's hurry.
Honey, I'm nearly there,
I see the building right now.
See you soon.
Oh, that would be wonderful.
Oh, how about using social media
to release it to the public?
Since its function is based on networking,
I think it could appeal
to a lot of the social media users.
Sure, that's a good idea.
KIM MIN-GYU
I really...
missed you.
Congratulations on your discharge.
Well done.
The day actually came.
Aren't you hungry?
I'm starving.
Let's go. Everyone's waiting for you.
-I have so much to tell you.
-Like what?
I signed a contract
with an overseas buyer.
I'm so happy!
I also have this new idea
that I recently thought of.
It's about...
This is...
when we kiss.
Subtitle translation by Yun Kang