(Sponsors: The Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism...)
(and Korea Creative Content Agency)
(A task had been assigned to the crew members of Antarctica.)
(Jam, )
(fish, and vegetables)
(Their task was to share ingredients...)
(with neighboring stations facing shortages.)
(Then they were off to the first neighboring station.)
(Where did they arrive after leaving the King Sejong Station?)
(Argentina Carlini Base)
(Their base had a lot more members than the King Sejong Station.)
(The Argentine crew gave them a warm welcome.)
(Paik)
(My name is Paik.)
(I am...)
(The crew members of Antarctica...)
(became utterly excited.)
(Afterward, they got to check out their base's signature features.)
(Asado)
(The pride-and-joy kitchen of the Argentine Base)
(As Argentina is known as the country of the meat, )
(no country is more serious than them when it comes to meat.)
(The Argentine people showed them a traditional dish.)
(A traditional South American barbecue)
(Asado)
(Munching)
(The taste was impossible not to give a thumbs-up.)
(The crew members seemed more excited than ever.)
(They set out to eat asado.)
(12pm: Lunchtime)
- It's very delicious.
- Is it very delicious?
- Thank you.
(It's time for lunch.)
(Amazed)
(The cafeteria at the Argentine Base)
This is...
- Hello.
Hello.
- Hello. Welcome.
- Thank you.
There's a family vibe here.
(The crew members are sitting together for lunch.)
There are a lot of people here.
- This has an antique feel.
- Yes.
Look at the photos. They represent their history.
Right.
(The history of Argentina Carlini Base fills a wall.)
My gosh. This is their history. How fancy.
It's amazing.
I see. It's over there.
- Your station's commander...
- It was a present.
gave that to us as a present when he visited our base.
That's nice.
There must be a lot of interaction between two bases.
(Asado is served.)
(This looks amazing.)
(The traditional South American barbecue)
(Asado)
(Place the hot charcoals under the grill.)
(Cook the meat for over 2 hours using the gentle heat of the coals.)
(The South American barbecue coats the meat in a smoky aroma.)
(Only salt is used to season the meat.)
This is crazy.
The meat will taste different here.
(The original flavor and aroma stand out in this dish.)
Doesn't it have a really nice meaty smell?
(The beef asado, the main dish of their lunch)
What's this?
It's stir-fried rice...
- I know that word. It's rice.
- and mushrooms.
Meat isn't the only thing he's good at cooking.
(Stir-fried mushroom rice, made with care)
(And the chef makes the dough fresh every morning.)
(Warm plain bread)
- Thank you for having us.
- Thank you.
Thank you so much for having us.
I'm so grateful that we have this chance to taste...
the traditional Argentine dish...
all the way in Antarctica.
- I'm sure we'll enjoy it.
- Right.
It's my honor to serve you our food.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
I see. Everyone serves themselves like it's a family-style meal.
(The Argentine crew members enjoy asado like any other day.)
(The crew members of Antarctica have a bite of asado too.)
This looks so good.
(Humming in approval)
(The flavor of smoky beef coats their mouth.)
- What?
- It's good.
So the meat in this dish must be frozen too.
Yes. Everything comes in already wrapped and frozen.
(Like any other station and base, the Argentine Base...)
(also gets their ingredients once a year.)
(The chef enhances the authentic flavor of the meat...)
(without using any special seasoning other than salt.)
The flavor all comes from his grilling technique.
It doesn't taste gamey at all.
This is so good.
(The tender, juicy meat with a smoky aroma)
I'm a meat lover. And this tastes amazing.
In Argentina, we usually have it with chimichurri.
Chimichurri.
(A classic Argentine herb sauce paired with meat)
The sauce is made with minced...
Very nice.
Let me tell you about chimichurri.
People in South America put it on top of their asado...
and eat them together. It's a type of sauce.
(A herb sauce that goes on top of the meat)
It was usually made with green vegetables.
- But it's hard to get them here.
- We don't have them here.
(Fresh parsley and oregano are the main ingredients.)
Since I don't have fresh vegetables, I only make it with herbs.
I add olive oil too.
Olive oil? I see.
I see.
(A pleasantly sour and aromatic flavor...)
(with dried herbs, vinegar, and olive oil)
(How will the asado taste with chimichurri?)
I didn't know about this sauce.
(Munching)
(Dipping it generously in chimichurri)
(Humming)
(Relieved)
The meat already tastes great with salt.
But it's even better with chimichurri.
It's much tastier with it.
When I tasted the beef asado that the chef grilled himself...
and chimichurri together,
it was much tastier.
The beefy flavor was rich.
The pairing is great.
It's much tastier.
I think this would really appeal to the Korean palate.
(Chimichurri enhances the flavor of asado.)
It's so good, right?
It's great.
(Smiling)
Everything is perfect.
Sir, does the entire crew here get to eat this every weekend?
We have this meal every Sunday.
- I'm so jealous.
- I see.
At our base, we always gather for a meal.
Everyone comes to the cafeteria when it's time for a meal.
(Always having a meal with families is part of the Argentine culture.)
That must be why. I got this vibe when I got off.
- They look like a family.
- You guys look like a family.
- Right.
- But you're not related, right?
You guys just bonded over asado, right?
Right. We became a family...
while spending time together here in Antarctica.
We must work together to get anything done here.
So we've become a good family and colleagues to each other.
We're just making a new family here.
Right. We care about each other a lot.
(Taking care of one another even during the meal)
(In this isolated environment, )
(they rely on each other like a family does.)
(They naturally build a bond that goes beyond being meal buddies.)
(They're enjoying their delicious meal...)
(in this friendly atmosphere like one big happy family.)
(Chef Andres is secretly preparing something.)
(What has the chef prepared?)
Is he giving us mate?
- Mate.
- This is mate.
- Yes, it's mate.
This is a traditional tea from Argentina.
(Argentine people enjoy mate anytime, anywhere.)
(Here!)
(The Argentine crew members chase away the cold with mate...)
(while working on their assignment.)
(The bitter, yet earthy mate leaves are brewed in the water.)
(Mate, a traditional Argentine beverage)
(There's also a special way to drink this tea.)
When you get the mate, you can keep talking.
But you can't touch the straw or let the straw move.
(The reason behind not touching the straw)
(This rule prevents the leaves from going into the straw.)
(Staring)
Then do we just have to keep watching you drink?
- No.
(This unexpected question makes them laugh.)
No.
So we don't have to mind her and keep on chatting, right?
We can steal glances at her.
(You can carry on the conversation while drinking mate.)
Yes. It's okay.
(Tasting mate just like he was instructed)
(What does mate taste like?)
(Curious)
It's bitter.
- It's bitter.
- Yes.
Is it supposed to be bitter like this?
We enjoy the bitterness of the mate leaves.
But I like the aroma.
(The bitter, leafy aroma and subtle mellow notes...)
(blend together and give it a deep flavor.)
My gosh, it's so bitter.
Now, we all have to share it.
(All of us?)
- Are we all using this same straw?
- Yes.
(We use the same straw.)
- It goes from mouth to mouth?
- Yes.
Oh, my.
Exactly. Yes.
(Is he freaking out?)
(Sharing the tea by drinking from the same straw represents...)
(friendship, communication, equality, and respect.)
- That makes us a family then.
- Yes.
(That's right!)
I see. Okay.
(It's a unique tea culture in Argentina.)
After the cup goes around, do I have to drink it again?
After it gets passed along, I'll have to drink it again?
We are the world.
(A cup of mate creates a global bond.)
I guess he's a comedian.
- I think he's the chef.
- No.
- He is.
(There's a controversy over his culinary qualifications.)
I guess he likes to make people laugh.
He's the chef.
Do you want to try it?
(The Funny Chef of Antarctica)
(He takes the mate Jong Won drank from.)
You can do this.
Do you have to root for him on this?
(SUHO takes a sip of mate.)
Yes.
(How is it?)
Look at him.
(He's not good with bitter drinks.)
- Yes.
- I feel like I'm being punished.
Is it that bitter?
It tastes interesting, doesn't it?
It tastes murky and bitter.
(Curious)
(The seasoning checker is startled.)
It tasted like a mix of super-bitter green tea and herbal tonic.
Wait. It's not bad.
For me, it tasted toasty.
Once I tasted it,
I got similar, yet different notes of green tea.
It had a unique and toasty flavor.
(They share a cup of mate together.)
They were kind enough to share the mate with us.
We learned the meaning behind sharing mate.
We had a full-course meal.
Living in Antarctica is really challenging.
If you don't mind, can I ask you what brought you here?
It was a great opportunity for me both professionally and personally.
I knew that this learning experience would be valuable.
So I decided to come here...
even though I knew it'd be a challenge.
It's like traveling.
Right. This is a valuable experience.
We get this question a lot.
If you get a chance to come back, would you come back?
- Yes.
- I see.
(Impressed)
(You guys are amazing.)
That's so cool.
Some of us have actually been here before.
Another base called us,
and some of our crew members got transferred there.
That's a brave decision.
Yes.
(Grateful)
How about the other crew members?
What made them come here?
He's a diver in the military.
- Diving?
- Yes.
- Diving. Are you divers?
- I really like diving.
- Do you?
I was like a teacher.
A swimming teacher.
- You were a teacher?
- Yes. A swimming teacher.
(Jong Hyeop used to work as a swimming instructor.)
I really like the sea.
Would you like to swim?
- But it's too cold.
- No?
(The water feels cool.)
(The warm, friendly meal is over.)
I would like to thank you sincerely...
for coming to our base on behalf of everyone here.
To show our gratitude,
our carpenter prepared a present for you.
It's a sled.
He made it himself.
(What's the meaning of this sled?)
There's a woodworking shop.
(The only woodworking shop on the island is at their base.)
- It's a sled.
- Yes.
(The crew members of Antarctica visited the shop before the meal.)
(The carpenter makes this sled for fellow crew members...)
(whose journey in Antarctica has ended.)
For his fellow crew members.
This is making me want to join Argentina Base.
This is fascinating.
This is lovely.
Thank you.
Gosh, only Argentine crew members get this wooden sled.
(The Argentine crew members prepared a surprise present.)
On behalf of our base,
I'm giving this to you from the bottom of my heart.
I'm also the oldest member at our base.
I've been here the longest in Antarctica as well.
I'm giving this to you because it may be my last time here.
Thank you.
(Manager Mario will return to his country...)
(after his last assignment here in Antarctica.)
This is the last time he's presenting the sled.
My gosh. Oh, my.
This is a meaningful present.
(To the veteran manager who's retiring soon from Antarctica)
I'm grateful to be here...
in this honored moment.
- Oh, no. He's crying.
- Yes.
- This is so sad.
- I'm getting emotional too.
It was touching.
It felt like all his years of hard work...
and his life were reflected in that moment.
Tears welled up in my eyes before I knew it.
It was touching.
This was his last year in Antarctica.
From what I remember, he was going to retire soon.
So it was even more touching.
My gosh, I can't imagine all the work you've done so far.
Thank you.
- I feel how much it meant to him.
- Right.
(A precious and valuable present made with love and honor)
Well, this is a small gift.
Argentina is famous for its cattle.
Nowadays, this ringing sound represents luck.
We prepared this as a gift for you.
I hope it keeps bringing you luck...
whenever you hear the bell ringing.
(May luck continue on whenever the bell rings.)
(Genuinely wishing each other's happiness)
(The meal with the warm-hearted Argentine crew)
The Argentine crew was so warm-hearted.
I felt so welcomed by them.
That was so heartwarming.
(Episode 4: Temperature of Flavors)
We're going this way.
Be careful.
(Everyone is carrying a big box and heading somewhere.)
It's slippery.
(What are they carrying?)
There are always shortages in Antarctica.
One time, we went to the Argentine Base.
- Yes.
- When we visited last time,
- they were short on jam and fish.
- Okay.
On top of that, their base doesn't have a greenhouse.
So they didn't have vegetables.
It seemed the Argentine crew was struggling with these shortages.
(The crew members of Antarctica...)
(brought scarce ingredients as presents.)
- It looks like a cold storage.
- Yes.
(The Argentine Base has two food storage units.)
(They arrive at the cold storage.)
(Amazed)
- Gosh.
- Look at that.
(What surprises them at the entrance?)
My gosh. There's so much stuff here.
(The storage is filled with mysterious boxes.)
(They're neatly stacked up.)
Gosh, it's all meat.
Why do they have so much meat?
I went to their cold storage. It was all meat.
A whole pig. A whole lamb.
They had all kinds of meat cuts too.
(Excitement shows in his eyebrows.)
(Different cuts of meat)
My gosh. They have so much meat.
(The meat is piled high in storage.)
Argentine people definitely eat a lot of meat.
That's a whole pig.
Gosh, is that the tail?
(Whole suckling pigs are kept frozen.)
- Look at this.
- My gosh. Are they all meat?
It must be for asado.
This is crazy.
- My gosh.
- Yes, they are whole suckling pigs.
(The face of a suckling pig)
We have different cuts of pork,
lamb, and beef. We also have chicken.
Gosh, they have so much meat.
We get our ingredients only once a year.
(Due to the nature of Antarctic stations and bases, )
(Argentina Carlini Base also receive...)
(their supplies once a year.)
We had fish, but we ran out.
(They're already out of seafood.)
Okay.
(Heading to their dry storage)
(A dry storage)
These are all for a year too.
(Entering the storage with the apple jam...)
(that they brought from King Sejong Station)
(Amazed)
(Surprised)
(Something takes Crew Paik by surprise.)
It's really well-organized.
I know.
(What's the reason that shocks everyone?)
(In the dry storage...)
Look how perfectly they are lined up and stacked with labels.
This is incredible.
(Placed in a single line, all facing front)
Did you see that everything was aligned perfectly?
Even losing a bottle of olive oil would raise a big alarm.
It'd be that noticeable.
(The ultimate way of organizing with a product sample attached)
(Attaching a sample to help easily see what it is)
It's dried onions. How interesting.
(When they're heading out, )
(they're being led up to the 2nd floor by a crew member.)
(What's on the 2nd floor?)
Oh, gosh. This is the best spot.
There are alcoholic beverages. It's drinks.
(A liquor storage)
It's drinks. Okay.
(Excited)
(Nodding)
- What is that?
- It looks like wine.
(Wine filling up one side of the storage)
(As Argentina is famous for its wine, )
(Argentina Base has a separate storage for liquor.)
It's a tradition at our base...
to have pizza and drinks every Saturday.
I like wine.
That was an amazing sight I'll never see anywhere else.
(It's the best!)
- All right. Shall we go?
- Yes.
Is it time to start cooking?
It's cooking time.
(It's their workplace!)
(Heading to the kitchen)
We need to check out the kitchen.
Is this the kitchen?
(The kitchen is right next to the dining area.)
The kitchen isn't what I expected.
(Peeking)
(How does the kitchen look?)
This kitchen is very clean and has nothing.
It was neat and small.
It looked pretty small.
(This small kitchen is the only place to cook.)
It's compact,
but it's neat and well-kept.
(A simple kitchen, unlike the one at King Sejong Station)
(A mixer that's not used for making Korean food)
There was nothing in the kitchen.
I saw an oven and a stove that looked barely used.
(The stove and oven)
I didn't see any extra containers,
strainers, or bowls I could use to mix ingredients together.
There was hardly anything there.
(An empty sink)
The kitchen is pretty bare because they mostly just grill meat.
Their main recipe is asado.
It was specialized for grilling.
They don't seem to do any other kind of cooking.
They mostly make salads and bread.
Bread is their staple.
(Meat)
(Braed)
(That's why they mostly use...)
(a brick oven and a standard oven.)
(What will the crew members of Antarctica cook?)
Have a seat for our meeting.
Let's talk about what to cook.
(Current time: 4:30pm, menu meeting)
This is what I think. Since Argentines...
love meat,
how about we try cooking meat...
using a Korean recipe?
(A Korean-style meat dish?)
Since I've actually had asado...
so many times,
when I heard we were visiting the Argentina Base,
I felt like they'd be serving us some asado meat.
(Asado, a South American barbecue)
Doesn't it have a really nice meaty smell?
It doesn't taste gamey at all.
I'm a meat lover. And this tastes amazing.
After having the beef asado,
I wanted to surprise them with our bulgogi.
(Bulgogi)
(A signature Korean meat dish...)
(of thinly sliced, marinated beef that's cooked on a grill)
(A signature dish)
I'm curious...
if Argentines will like this.
(Korean barbecue)
So I'd like to cook bulgogi.
Bulgogi tastes great when it's grilled over charcoal.
- Right.
- With that dish on my mind,
- I got soy sauce and sesame oil.
- I see.
I'm pretty sure they don't have them here.
(I had the big picture in mind.)
(Crew Paik planned everything ahead.)
(Grabbing soy sauce)
(Grabbing sesame oil)
(Taking soy sauce and sesame oil with bulgogi in mind)
It's a Korean grilled meat dish.
I thought they'd love it if we made it for them.
(It sounds good.)
The meat is the most important part. You've already seen it.
If we cut it thick,
we can't serve it until tomorrow evening...
because we need to marinate it overnight.
(The key is to slice the meat as thin as possible.)
(The weather changes frequently in Antarctica.)
- We have to be on the boat by 8pm.
- My gosh.
It's 5pm now.
If we want to be on that boat no later than 7:30pm...
(In 2 hours and 30 minutes, )
(they have to make bulgogi for 30 people.)
(The challenge is slicing the rock-hard frozen meat...)
(thin enough for bulgogi.)
(Having a headache, staring into space)
To make bulgogi,
we need to slice the meat very thin.
That's going to be really tough.
(Worried)
If you want to go back to the station today,
we have to slice the meat as thinly as possible.
It's up to you. I don't mind staying the night here.
- I'm also fine with staying.
- What?
I brought my overnight stuff...
- just in case.
- I...
I want to go back as soon as possible.
- We need to hurry because of him.
- Right.
What a relief.
(Thanks to the most passionate man, they're forced to go back.)
I almost dug myself into a hole.
The crew at King Sejong Station is waiting for us.
They'll starve tomorrow if we don't go back today.
- Exactly.
- How come you're so irresponsible?
(We'll just laugh.)
Are you ready?
- Yes.
- All right.
- Yes, chef.
Chef, I'm leaving my kitchen in your hands.
(Crew members of Antarctica are ready.)
- Let's gather in the kitchen.
- Yes.
It's cooking time.
(They start cooking at 5pm.)
(Jong Won is heading somewhere after getting changed.)
Where is it?
Okay. It looks good.
(The meat for today's cooking)
(Has it already defrosted?)
I heard they took the meat out to defrost...
for their weekend asado. I was so happy with that.
(Defrosted meat for the weekend meals)
(Beef ribs and sirloin)
(The defrosted meat saves them a lot of time.)
All right.
(Grunting)
I almost hurt my back.
Gosh, this is a lot of meat.
(While Jong Won and Jong Hyeop are bringing the meat, )
(the sous chef is walking into the food storage.)
(So is the sous chef of Antarctica.)
Is this sugar?
I see. Okay.
And I need onions.
(Quickly getting ingredients for bulgogi)
(But...)
Does it work manually?
Yes, it does. You need to move it by hand.
(What are they doing when time is running out?)
- I'm happy with this.
- Right.
- We just never had access to this.
- All of them...
We're done here.
You guys can go and hang out.
- Can we really go and hang out?
- Yes.
(Are they already done?)
Chef Andres said he had this machine he cherished, so I went to see it.
(A little while ago)
(Chef Andres saw the defrosted meat.)
Oh, my gosh.
There's a meat slicer in the back, so feel free to use it.
Can I check it out?
Yes! There's a meat slicer.
This will save us so much time.
(Chef Andres quickly noticed and offered the meat slicer.)
People use this to slice ham.
Meat slicers are typically big.
They automatically slice meat at the press of a button.
It even works on frozen meat.
Since this slicer is only for ham, we have to operate it manually.
Even so, this is much quicker than using a knife.
That's the benefit of civilization.
Okay.
(Thank you.)
(Humming happily)
Who knew he'd have a meat slicer?
Once that slicer is working properly on the meat,
you have nothing to worry about.
(Will they be able to reduce the time it takes to cut the meat?)
(Trying it right away)
All that matters is how well it slices.
Please.
(Is it working well?)
- My gosh.
- Does it work well?
- It's really thin.
- Oh, my.
It works.
(Let's do it.)
(It's slicing the meat surprisingly fast.)
Next one.
Let me do it.
(SUHO, who's been watching, quickly prepares the meat.)
This is great.
(Another chunk of meat)
Slicing the meat thin was key,
and I was worried about it.
But the slicer made our preparation easy.
Is it not ready yet?
Yes, it's ready. Are you already done?
You guys are getting faster.
It was a relief...
we had the slicer,
but honestly, I was a little disappointed...
because I wanted to do it myself.
I wanted to use the knife to cut the meat myself.
(Ever since they arrived in Punta Arenas, )
(he's powered through...)
(cutting countless ingredients.)
(The most passionate man, SUHO)
Argentines cook the meat whole, but we cook ours after slicing it.
I wanted to show them the difference.
So I was a little disappointed.
(Full of disappointment)
We need to marinate it first.
(No one notices his disappointment as the pot gets filled with meat.)
It's a lot of meat.
(It's time to marinate the meat.)
(Looking determined)
(While Crew Paik slices the meat, )
- Clean it up here.
- Yes.
(Soo Hyang is setting out the seasonings.)
(He grabs white sugar first.)
(Trembling)
(Pouring)
(Adding the whole bag)
(Garlic, essential for K-food)
(Shaking it out)
(Grabbing the next one)
Taste it and see if it's salty.
(What is Soo Hyang, the seasoning checker, tasting?)
(It's one of the seasonings Soo Hyang received a while ago.)
I have soaked onions.
I rehydrated the dried onions.
- Are they onions?
- Yes.
(Soaked onions, a substitute for scallions)
(The dried onions she saw...)
(in the dry storage before cooking)
(There are no greenhouses at the Argentina Base.)
We don't have the most important ingredient for bulgogi, scallions.
We need that scallion flavor.
Onions would do if they had onions.
It's not salty.
It's sweet.
Can you check the fridge for any leftover Sprite?
- Go check.
- Yes.
(Soy sauce, the essential seasoning for bulgogi)
(Pouring water to adjust the seasoning concentration)
(Adding honey for extra flavor)
(Tasting)
It already tastes good.
(The bulgogi marinade is ready.)
(Sighing)
(SUHO is cleaning the slicer.)
Chef Andres was kind enough to lend it to us,
so we wanted to make sure we gave it back clean.
(Scrubbing)
(Wiping)
We'd have been in big trouble without this slicer.
(Cleaning Freak SUHO)
(Shining)
- Should I just pour it?
- Yes.
(Pouring the marinade over the meat)
Hand me the sesame oil.
(Adding the sesame oil)
Add it generously.
(Pouring)
(Adding a savory flavor)
That's good.
(Mixing)
(Rolling up his sleeve)
(Mixing it up thoroughly)
(The bulgogi is ready to go!)
Once this is grilled over the fire, it will taste awesome.
- Yes.
- Everything is great!
(While crew members of Antarctica are making bulgogi, )
(the Argentine crew is doing their research.)
(They're waiting for today's special meal.)
(Current time: 5:45pm)
(All that's left is grilling the bulgogi.)
But still. We need the fire to rise from here.
(Jong Hyeop is in charge of the brick oven.)
I handled the brick oven.
When would I ever have the chance to use a brick oven?
So I asked if I could learn how to use it.
Then, can I learn how to fire up the brick oven?
- Go ahead.
- Can I?
(Striding)
So I was excited. I was happy at the beginning.
(What happened to Fire Jong Hyeop?)
(Coming to the brick oven)
(Watching)
(Lighting the kindling)
- This is fire.
- Okay.
(Putting it where they light the charcoal)
It's really hot. Be careful.
(Adding more firewood)
- Is that making the fire hotter?
- Yes.
(As the charcoal burns...)
(and gets hot, )
(he just needs to move it over to the grilling area.)
The fire went out right away.
(The fire went out right away.)
(It's not going as he planned since it's his first time.)
The fire went out.
(Failing to maintain the fire)
(The new firewood shows up out of nowhere.)
The fire went out right away. Where's that?
(Crawling)
The fire went out.
(The Argentine crew member watching from the back hands it over to him.)
Put it into the grill.
- Here?
- He said to put it in there.
(Putting in the secret firewood he just got)
Thank you.
I was told it was okay to make the fire stronger.
(Is the fire going to hold up?)
Thank you.
And...
let's get the meat.
I'll take the meat.
I'll start grilling it.
What is it? Oh, my.
The fire is too big. Can I put the meat on this?
(When he goes to grab the meat, )
(it flares up.)
(Burning intensely)
This is crazy. In this case,
do you know what's going to happen?
The meat will burn up the second I put it on.
Okay. First of all...
(Pondering)
I thought...
using this brick oven would be similar...
to building a campfire.
Okay. Can I get this meat...
grilled by 6:30pm? Can I manage to do it?
Can you do it, Jong Hyeop?
(Asking himself calmly)
Like this.
When I'm not sure, let's just go for it.
Should I have grilled it sooner?
(Pulling himself together and starting to grill the meat)
(Continuing to grill the meat while enduring the heat)
It's hot.
I wasn't familiar with a brick oven since it was my first time using it.
It was tough to control the fire.
The fire isn't strong enough. Come on, Jong Hyeop.
(The flame dies down fast.)
(The meat isn't getting cooked.)
I'm in trouble.
(He still has a lot of meat in this pot...)
(waiting to be grilled.)
See? It isn't getting cooked. The fire is too weak.
I still have that much. What time is it now?
It's 6pm.
(Current time: 6pm)
(He has 30 minutes until mealtime.)
I might not be able to serve it on time.
I was focused on getting it done in time for the crew's mealtime.
(No time to waste)
All right. It's not just a single task.
(Adding more firewood)
(Putting it in)
(He works best when he shows off his biceps.)
(Diligently adding more charcoal)
Yes. This is what I'm talking about.
(The meat is picking up a smoky flavor.)
(Breathing out)
(Short of breath)
It's hot.
(The downside is he's also getting hot.)
It's crazy hot in here.
(While Jong Hyeop is wrestling with the fire alone...)
Jong Hyeop, what can I do to help?
- What?
- What can I do?
- SUHO.
- Yes, tell me.
- It's not that I need assistance.
- All right.
- I'm just fighting this heat.
- Okay.
And the fire keeps dying.
I'll need another pair of tongs.
(I'll get another pair of tongs.)
He's cool, isn't he?
"What can I do to help?"
He's the best.
It's everything about SUHO.
The way he talks casually...
and he carries himself...
- shows what a great person he is.
- That's done, right?
- Put it on here.
- That's it.
Is everything ready in the kitchen?
- Yes, we need to finish grilling.
- We just need to get the meat done.
- It's this one. Okay.
- Great.
(Helping Jong Hyeop the best he can)
I need to prepare a salad.
(Angel SUHO is walking away as if it's nothing.)
SUHO is the best.
SUHO, you're the best.
It's cold.
(Meanwhile, Crew Paik is outside all alone.)
How did you press it?
- Did you press it?
- I did it with my hands.
(Soo Hyang also joins them.)
- Oh, my gosh.
- I'm using the cold in Antarctica.
It's going to be delicious. I bet this will be a hit.