ALL NAMES, CHARACTERS,
AND EVENTS ARE FICTIONAL
CHILD AND ANIMAL WELFARE
REGULATIONS WERE OBSERVED
-Did you put the seatbelt on?
-Yes.
Mom.
Hold tight.
It's okay.
Did you see that? Poor Ji-yu.
What? Was their marriage fake?
Goosebumps. It was all a show?
Nice. They were so full of themselves.
They're done for.
Don't look, Ji-yu. Don't look.
Mom!
Mom.
Mom…
Ms. Nam, what's your relationship
with Candidate Cha?
Is your daughter his child?
Rumor has it that
she's an illegitimate child. Any comment?
Ms. Nam Gyeong-ae.
-Ms. Nam Gyeong-ae.
-She's inside!
Ms. Nam?
Do you admit to having an affair?
If you don't respond,
this article will just go out.
-Will you agree to a paternity test?
-When did it begin?
-Ms. Nam.
-Mom.
-Ms. Nam, we know you're in there.
-Ms. Nam.
Just a quick comment.
This won't do.
Let's go to the back.
She's there.
Reporter Kim,
get some shots of the kid's face.
When did the affair start?
What are you doing to a child?
Is Candidate Cha your daughter's father?
-It's my personal life!
-Ms. Nam.
It's my personal life!
Will you agree to a paternity test?
When did the affair start?
-Ms. Cha, are you okay?
-Ms. Cha!
There was a car accident here.
Please come quickly!
-Please hurry.
-Ms. Cha, wake up.
Call 911!
-Ms. Cha.
-This is a scoop. Get some shots.
-Get some shots of their faces.
-Ms. Cha.
Call 911.
-Hello, are you okay?
-Ms. Cha, wake up.
Ms. Cha, wake up.
Hey, call 911.
Yes, please come right away.
All right.
-Ms. Cha.
-Ms. Cha, are you okay?
Ms. Cha!
WE PROMISE SINCERITY!
MARCH 8, 2027
THE 23RD PRESIDENTIAL
TRANSITION COMMITTEE
MY DAUGHTER
The approval rating poll results are out.
NEGATIVE: 44.8%, NOT SURE: 4.2%
POSITIVE: 51%
The numbers are not concerning.
So far, the prevailing view is
to wait and see.
The presidential office
has suddenly postponed the meeting.
They attribute it
to North Korea's missile launch,
but I think they want to wait and see
which way public opinion shifts.
After all, they have no reason to rush.
The person you have reached
is unavailable.
Please try again after…
JI-YU.
Why don't you meet Candidate Bae?
Even in the concession speech,
she didn't mention anything
about the special law.
You don't deserve to be here.
You're not my family.
You don't deserve it.
We can still bring her to our side.
I'M SORRY
We have to hurry
before President Yu moves.
Let's do that.
Arrange a luncheon sometime this week.
Yes, sir.
You may leave now.
JI-YU, ARE YOU OKAY?
CALL
MY DAUGHTER
Did you get back from the academy?
I made some curry.
Heat it up and have it for dinner.
Don't order delivery again.
I'll call you later.
Aren't you going home?
How can I,
when he's been like that
ever since the car accident?
I can't just leave him alone.
This is why people call you
a die-hard loyalist.
Not just me. It's both of us.
Come on. I don't want to be part of it.
I'd rather be buried alone if I die.
So I can finally take my sabbatical there.
These days,
I don't feel like living my life anyways.
I've been working seven days a week
to make him president, and now…
And now?
-What?
-Nothing.
I'm just saying.
Geez, I wish those phones
would just stop ringing already.
Seriously, it's driving me nuts.
I keep hearing the phone ring
in my car and at home.
The staff have been complaining
about it too.
I'm basically everyone's doormat here.
At work, my colleagues harass me and…
And what?
Don't change the subject again,
just say it.
There…
I told you not to change the subject.
No, over there…
Ms. Cha.
Ms. Cha?
Where is he?
I'm sorry.
Outsiders are not allowed to enter.
Outsider?
Please follow the procedure.
I thought it was urgent.
Please speak through your legal counsel.
The petition has been filed, so--
This is a crucial time.
The two-month transition period
will shape the next five years.
There's no time to waste.
The procedure is just as crucial as time.
I'll get in touch to schedule a meeting.
I'm glad you're here.
Let's talk inside.
HASEONG EXPRESS
CARGO / TRANSPORT / MOVING SERVICES
I heard about the car accident.
It wasn't an accident.
The car just slipped a bit.
It looks like you're pretty hurt.
Well, I got about seven stitches.
Things must take a turn for the better.
I'll see this as a starting point.
How's Ji-yu?
She's okay.
I heard from the butler
that she's doing okay.
But she won't answer my calls.
She will need
some time.
Good thinking.
Let's not take this to court.
Why don't we just
settle this amicably?
I forgot about it.
PETITION FOR DIVORCE
But then this reminded me
of how we met,
how we ended up here,
and our time spent together.
I give up everything.
Everything that I have
and was going to have.
Whatever they are,
I give them all up.
I don't need anything else.
All I need is you.
We can live separately like this.
And I won't ask anything of you.
All I want is…
for you to drop the divorce suit.
That's all I need.
As long as we're together,
they'll keep making an issue out of you.
No, it won't be an issue.
Because I'm okay.
Just not divorce…
We still have time.
-So…
-What do you want me to do?
What can I do to change your mind?
I'll do anything you say.
So please, let's not divorce.
Think about everything
we've been through together.
Honey.
For once, can we do as I say,
as Ji-yu's mom?
Don't call me that.
You have no right
to say her name.
PETITION FOR DIVORCE
Whose idea was it?
Why were the clothes sent here,
not to his place?
And it had to be
right when the reporters were here.
With all these empty boxes,
you even made up fake news.
You really had to put on a show like that.
You're the same.
No matter how difficult it got,
you always faced it down confidently.
I didn't expect you to run away
from the reporters like that.
So it was your idea.
Am I right?
I learned from the best.
Right now,
he should be the one being attacked.
Are you challenging me?
I'm only working for the president-elect.
Just like you did.
I wanted him to win.
Likewise.
But for the president-elect to win,
one of us must lose.
Do you really think you can take me down
with a little media spin?
It'll be boring
if I could take you down just with this.
Don't think this is over.
Let's not take this to court.
Why don't we just
settle this amicably?
It'll be boring
if I could take you down just with this.
Hello?
This is Cha Su-yeon.
Hello, Ms. Cha.
What made you call me?
I'm sorry to bother you this late.
No, it's not late.
No matter how late it is,
you're always welcome to call me.
I have something to suggest.
The president-elect and his wife's divorce
has come as a shock to the nation.
I'm here with Ms. Cha Su-yeon now.
Hello.
Your divorce has been
the talk of the town lately.
But since it's your personal life,
we were cautious about inviting you.
But Ms. Cha wanted to appear in our show,
so we're having her here today
on News Magazine Live.
First, I'd like to ask
how the talk of divorce came up.
Right.
Honestly,
I'm not sure myself.
Just like any other couple,
we had conflicts,
we argued, and we fought.
From trivial matters
like who should take out
the food trash and the recycling,
to bigger matters like
our daughter's extracurricular education.
But
we have always tried to be understanding
and generous
for over 20 years
of marriage.
Then since he won
the presidential election…
Good. Close up.
Cha Su-yeon sure knows the show biz.
She's really boosting the ratings.
Camera number three, a little tighter.
Good. Leave it like that.
I'm sorry.
Are you saying
he brought up divorce
after winning the presidential election?
Yes.
And he never mentioned it before?
No.
You said you had conflicts
like any other couple.
Though you may not remember,
maybe you made some mistake.
Does anything come to mind?
No.
I'm not the one
trying to break up this family.
That's why I'm here today.
Some say I asked for a divorce,
and I kicked my husband out.
I wanted to correct
that fake news.
I'm just an ordinary mother and a wife
who wants to
protect this family.
The wife of the president-elect is
not just an ordinary wife.
Suddenly being asked for a divorce
after 20 years of marriage
is not ordinary either.
That's true.
But it is also true that the discord
between the president-elect and you
is being interpreted
not as a private conflict,
but as a political separation.
It's still being investigated,
but there are allegations that
large political funds flowed
from Chairman Yang
to the president-elect through you.
I'll appear exclusively
on News Magazine Live under one condition.
What condition?
Let's not talk about Chairman Yang.
I want this interview to be
solely about my stance on the divorce.
I see.
I understand what you mean.
Don't worry, though.
At the end of the day,
what viewers want to know about
is not the investigation,
but the divorce.
Some even say that your involvement
in Chairman Yang's illegal succession
is the direct cause
of the marital breakdown.
That is not true.
Sir.
-Can we get the breaking news?
-I'll try.
You're getting it.
Yes, sir.
Skip this. We'll cut live
to the prosecutor's office.
Let's see Cha Su-yeon's reaction.
It's connected.
All right.
Reporter Son. Ready.
Action.
This just in.
We'll talk after that.
The president-elect
has formally filed a criminal suit
against Ms. Cha for violations
of the Information Network Act and
the Communications Secrets Protection Act.
The president-elect stated that
he learned only after the election
that Ms. Cha had wiretapped him
for 20 years,
betraying the trust
at the core of their marriage.
The wiretapping devices found
in his pen and tumbler
have been submitted as evidence,
which is adding to the shock.
You've just seen the breaking news.
The president-elect has filed a complaint
against Ms. Cha for wiretapping him.
-Really?
-What?
We'll fact-check that first.
Did you really wiretap him?
EXCLUSIVE LIVE INTERVIEW WITH CHA SU-YEON
Push her.
If you've wiretapped your husband
throughout your marriage,
your claim today that
you're just an ordinary wife
can hardly be convincing.
Push harder.
If the president-elect's claim
of wiretapping is true,
doesn't that make you the one
who broke up the marriage?
Ms. Cha.
Have you wiretapped the president-elect?
Push harder.
Why the silence?
If you can't clear the suspicion
that you wiretapped him,
everything you said today
will inevitably be seen as false.
Let me ask again.
Have you wiretapped him?
Geez. For 20 years?
She deserves to be sued, then.
It wasn't because I didn't trust him.
It was because I couldn't trust
Hyun Min-cheol as a politician.
I wasn't monitoring my husband.
I was monitoring the politicians
who approached Politician Hyun Min-cheol.
I was protecting him from them.
Do you admit that you wiretapped him?
I was protecting him from being deceived
and hurt by politicians.
Because my husband is a politician,
and I'm his wife, and at the same time,
his political partner.
People voted
for the president-elect, not for you.
It is true that you're his wife,
but calling yourself his political partner
sounds like a false claim.
It's not a claim.
It's a fact.
What are you doing?
Push her with the wiretapping.
Ms. Cha.
Wiretapping is a crime.
I'll willingly pay the price
for breaking the law.
However,
to protect Politician Hyun Min-cheol,
what I did was necessary.
Are you saying what you've done
was illegal, but not wrong?
What you just said,
like saying, "I had alcohol,
but I didn't drink and drive,"
could sound contradictory.
I will leave it
up to you to judge.
I believe
you will make a wise judgement
as always.
Well done, Son Min-ju.
"What you've done
was illegal, but not wrong."
"I had alcohol,
but I didn't drink and drive."
Talk about an experienced reporter.
Hey, I'm not a newbie
who needs compliments.
I'm giving you compliments
so you could do better.
I said, stop flattering me.
Fine. I'll stop!
Excuse me.
Wait.
You should return your mic.
Oh, right.
Let me help you.
It's Cha Su-yeon!
Ms. Cha, wait!
Ms. Cha!
-Wait up.
-Ms. Cha!
Wait, Ms. Cha.
-Wiretapping?
-What?
Wiretapping?
-It's Cha Su-yeon.
-It's Cha Su-yeon!
It's Cha Su-yeon!
-It's Cha Su-yeon.
On TV, they say, for 20 years…
Here! Look here!
Is that true?
-It is true.
-Ms. Cha!
Ms. Cha!
Ms. Cha, look here!
Here! Ms. Cha!
Ms. Cha!
-Wait, Ms. Cha!
-Ms. Cha!
Ms. Cha! Just a word, please!
Ms. Cha!
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Right, let me introduce myself.
I'm Lawyer Kang Seon-ho.
The lawyer of Yoon Ki-ju who is booked
for an assault.
I tried but couldn't reach you.
You ignored my texts too.
So I came to you
when I saw you on the live show.
What do you want?
What don't I want, you mean.
I mean…
"I don't want him punished."
That one sentence is all I need.
They give special pardons
when a president is elected.
Show him some mercy.
Pull over.
Or you could do that
in return for me driving you--
Pull over.
You just need to write some words here.
This is all just a formality.
It'll become a hassle for everyone
if he's referred to.
If you were to testify and so on,
reporters would flock again.
It'll be a bother.
Let's just wrap this up nicely.
We'll meet again soon!
Giving up isn't in my dictionary!
"Seon" in my name doesn't mean "kind!"
It means "vicious."
Here's the prescription and the receipt.
-Thank you.
-Have a nice day.
Ga-eun, slow down.
It's dangerous with cars around.
Okay.
Good job. This way.
Look ahead.
Goodness. Look there. It's red light.
-Mom.
-You stop at red light.
Mom.
Shall we go back this way?
-Let's go back slowly.
-Okay.
Let's go. Slowly, together.
You're doing great.
Good job, Ga-eun.
Goodness, where have you been?
Shall we go?
CHA'S REMARK ON POLITICAL PARTNER
CAUSES A HUGE STIR
DOES SHE ADMIT TO BEING THE MASTERMIND?
Let's go.
It's not a model where you can
wiretap real time using Wi-Fi.
It's an old model which you have
to retrieve to check the recording.
It's the same as the one
in the fountain pen.
Let's start with this.
The violation of Network Utilization
and Information Protection Act
and Communications Secrets Act.
Charge her with everything we can.
That'll change the flow.
How long have you known?
From the start?
I apologize.
What's important--
Don't get it wrong.
I'm divorcing for Su-yeon's sake.
I'm trying to prevent her
from going to jail.
So am I.
Can I
take your word for it?
That's enough.
Stop here.
Don't hurt her anymore.
-Hyun Min-cheol!
President Yu started to investigate
Chairman Yang's illegal succession.
He wants to stop the special act.
He can't point his knife at you directly,
but if he starts an investigation
targeted at your wife,
many people will side with him.
While she's secured strong supporters,
she's also made many enemies.
What about Candidate Bae's speech?
She hasn't made it yet.
She seems to be weighing
the pros and cons of the act.
Since you've asked her to join,
she'd need to address it.
Let's see
how the investigation progresses.
If Candidate Bae supports the special act,
President Yu won't be able to stop it.
If Candidate Bae sides with President Yu,
we'll be in a bind.
It's a matter of probability
at this point.
I'll convince Candidate Bae.
No, it's a matter of time.
In the end, the target is me.
Not Su-yeon.
I can't put her in front of reporters.
She won't be able to stand it.
Will your wife accept it?
She'll have a hard time doing so.
She only fights
when she's sure she'll win.
If she finds out
I'm starting a fight that I can't lose,
she'll try to stop me, all the more so
if it's about her.
Let's get divorced.
What?
Let's divorce.
Just for five minutes…
No, let's stay like this for one minute.
Look at this.
Madam Cha admitted to bugging.
"It was for protection, not monitoring."
That's typical of her.
But she might face
a lot of backlash for this.
Hello, Reporter Son.
I was about to call you.
Please, I didn't do much.
It's all thanks to your heads up
that we got the right timing.
I found a malt whisky bar
that you would like.
Let's meet up with Team Leader Cheon soon.
-It's not true.
-It can't be.
Believe in her. She wouldn't do that.
It's not true, is it?
-Of course not.
-It's not.
-My gosh.
-I think it's Su-yeon.
It's Cha Su-yeon.
How long have you been bugging him?
Do you have anything to say to the claim
that you broke the family apart?
Will you cooperate to the police?
If you don't say anything,
we'll publish the news as is.
Ms. Cha, say something.
-Ms. Cha!
Just one word, please!
Ms. Cha Su-yeon!
-Ms. Cha!
-Just one word, Ms. Cha!
-Say something!
-Madam.
-Hang in there.
-Ms. Cha Su-yeon!
Oh, dear.
-Ms. Cha!
-Just a word, Ms. Cha!
-Say something!
Ms. Cha Su-yeon!
Ms. Cha…
Darn it. She didn't say a single thing.
She bugged her husband?
There's no way she would do that.
-It's not true, right?
-What?
Someone must've got it wrong.
Didn't you hear what she said on the show?
I'll willingly pay the price
for breaking the law.
She said herself that she bugged him.
No. Something must've gone wrong.
I believe in Madam Cha.
I can't believe it either.
I thought the divorce was a lie, too.
How could this happen?
It's not true, is it?
Is this one of those fake news?
You know, those fake news made using AI.
It is, isn't it?
Why won't you say anything?
I believe in her.
Ms. Cha.
Are you all right?
Ms. Cha, are you unwell?
I'm okay.
Ms. Cha.
I'm fine.
What about Ji-yu?
She got the stitches removed fine.
What did the doctor say?
That you need to get your stitches removed
and that you should visit the hospital.
He asked me repeatedly,
saying he couldn't reach you.
I understand.
I'll do that.
Ma'am!
PRESIDENT-ELECT SUES CHA SU-YEON
Did you see it?
Bugging and suing, what a mess.
My mom deleted the photo
that she took with Cha from her Instagram.
My mom posted she was close with her.
She shut down her account.
What happens to Ji-yu
if Cha Su-yeon is kicked out?
Either hit rock bottom with her mom
or stay with her dad, I guess.
Ms. Cha.
Are you awake?
I brought you breakfast.
It's by the door.
Have some as soon as you get up.
Why won't you eat?
You'll ruin your health.
Do you not have an appetite?
Ms. Cha.
It's chicken porridge that you like.
Why didn't you have it?
Even if you don't have an appetite,
have a mouthful at least.
Mom.
Mom?
What is it?
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
What is it?
Nothing.
Have you eaten?
Yes. I'm going to cram school now.
Okay.
See you later.
Make sure to eat.
I will.
MISSED CALLS
NEW MESSAGES
Ma'am!
Su-yeon.
A woman in her 30s was stabbed to death
in a multiplex housing
in Namil-dong, Haseong City.
The deceased is the mistress
of Cha Jin-taek,
an Assembly candidate for Haseong
with the illegitimate child controversy…
I…
won't die
like my mom.
VICTORY & GOOD FORTUNE LAW FIRM
You must be prepared to let the world
know all about your private life.
Everything about you
and your daughter will be exposed.
Am I at a disadvantage?
A divorce lawsuit is about
whether you gain what you want.
Tell me what you want.
I'll help you.
What I want
is half of everything he's gained
thanks to me.
And half of everything
he'll gain in the future.
If it's about the assets--
I'm not talking about money.
I'm the one who made him president.
So,
I should take half of
what the President owns.
Isn't that right?
How many do you think
voted for him because of me?
Ten percent?
Twenty percent?
Half at least, don't you think?
You can't get a divorce, then.
If you do, you lose your rights
as the First Lady.
In that case, we must overturn
the plaintiff's argument.
We need to prove you aren't in the wrong.
Since you've already admitted
to bugging him, it will be a hard fight.
Are you saying it's a long shot?
I'm saying we have to fight.
Strike back as much as you were hit,
with the interest on top.
We'll cling onto the plaintiff's
wrongdoing, whatever it may be.
If it results in mud-slinging,
the first to give up loses.
I won't give up first.
Never.
Then we won't lose.
I'll find a way for you.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Okay.
Sorry about that.
It's fine.
All right. Find a way, then.
I'll entrust it to you.
Something urgent came up.
I can't accept this lawsuit.
Then another partner in the firm--
They're handling
another lawsuit right now,
so they can't help.
I apologize.
Is it him?
Does he want to hire you?
What, did he get you a decent position
in the Transition Committee?
HASEONG LEGAL TOWN
I apologize.
We can't accept the case.
We can't accept
a politically sensitive case.
Civil suits related to public officials
are too risky,
starting with media exposure.
We don't specialize in family law.
PRESIDENT-ELECT PRESS CONFERENCE
HASEONG FAMILY COURT
My fellow citizens,
I apologize for causing you worries.
In this crucial period
when the government must look after you,
I'm causing you worries
regarding my marriage.
I'm aware of the love
and support you've given
to my wife and me for a long time.
And I know it must be making you
more disappointed and devastated.
But all I can do now is
to ask you to let us handle it.
I sincerely apologize.
But I promise
that my family issues will not interfere
with national affairs.
Now, we'll accept some questions.
I'm Reporter Park of MBS.
Is the bugging
the main cause of the divorce?
Did you start living apart
when your stuff was delivered?
Is it to bury the illegal--
Ms. Cha.
There's nowhere to go.
There's nowhere else to go.
No lawyer,
and no place to go.
Shall I escort you home?
HOMEROOM TEACHER
Yes, teacher. Hello.
What?
My Ji-yu did that?
Stop, stop it!
Stop!
Let me go.
Let me go!
What are you guys doing?
I want her to be expelled.
As the chair of the foundation,
I should sort this out.
They claim that someone hacked
into the cloud and spread the video.
Did he want my signature
on the divorce paper
so badly that he pushed
his own daughter over the edge?
I'll make the final decision.
You can't decide and act on your own
like you have been anymore. Got it?
I'll do it.
I'll divorce you.
Subtitle translation by: Sunyoung Baek,
Yeeun Kim