This a**hole has the eyes of a murderer.
No matter what...
I'll kill you with my own hands.
I don't know if you'll get to have a turn.
[Personal Information]
Timing and Subtitles
[Rainbow Transportation,
CEO Jang Sung Cheol]
I'm not interested in driving.
Now you worry about my livelihood.
I didn't come here to give you a job.
Did your pain go away because he died?
[Killer Nam Gyu Jung kills
himself in prison]
Don't you still want to take revenge?
[Taxi Driver: 080-505-8282, Don't kill yourself,
take revenge. We will do it for you.]
[Do not enter, personnel only]
[Premium Taxi]
Only victims know the torment
you're going through.
People who haven't experienced
it aren't even interested.
Do you know why your
mother was killed?
Because of the crazy murderer?
No.
It's the fault of this society that
nurtured such a monster
with cheap forgiveness.
Do you still believe in justice by the police,
Prosecutors' Office, and the judges?
Could you entrust that they'll be just?
I've been preparing
for this for a long time.
To fight them.
Do you know where this is?
It's where my parents were brutally
murdered 20 years ago.
I have not forgotten that day.
Not even for a day.
[December 2001]
Forgive?
I'll never forgive.
Won't you take revenge with me?
[Taxi Driver]
[Episode 2]
All right. Please make your choice.
You've made your choice.
Shall we go and take your revenge
with the premium taxi?
[Premium Taxi]
5283 in operation.
Is this the other vault
you were talking about?
How much does one
of these drums cost?
Well? For how many kilograms?
There are 150kg or 200kg.
I'm sure it doesn't cost that much.
It's just for jeotgal.
I don't think it's "just."
What? For one drum...
three million won?
Wow, you're right. This is the vault.
How much was Maria
cheated out of her wages?
Wages and salary. That's my specialty.
But she also did laundry, dishes,
and cleaning inside the boarding house.
Should I calculate that
as a second job or hourly?
Whatever is more.
I'll calculate hourly.
[Wage Calculator]
I sent you a text.
We're short quite a bit.
I'll need to get more, including compensation
for psychological damages.
Hey, who are you?
Who the hell are you?
A**hole. Is he mute?
I'm here to buy jeotgal.
[Hear from a young leader,
CEO Park Joo Chan]
[Social Enterprise, Changsung Jeotgal]
Aigoo, I'm sorry for
screaming at you earlier.
Why did you sneak in like a little rat?
Aigoo, thank you.
Try not to make your own coffee.
If you can, you should serve
a convenience store coffee.
It's tough to take more than one sip.
You're not laughing. That was a joke.
Geez, I'm so embarrassed.
Joo Chan, well...
What?
Well...
Go ahead and talk.
So you're here to buy jeotgal?
Yes.
This isn't a wholesale place where
you can conveniently come in and buy.
If I can't buy conveniently,
should I buy inconveniently?
Geez, you really don't
like jokes, huh? Right?
Let's cut to the chase then.
Okay...
Well...
I'm in charge of the jeotgal.
You can talk to me.
What kind of jeotgal do you need?
What kind do you have?
This and that. We have
all kinds of jeots.
We have sand eel, octopus...
You have octopus, sand eel...
You have it all.
Cool.
Yes.
For now, I'll put 30% down.
Let me buy 50 drums.
Yes, then I'll give you 50 drums...
Fifty drums. That's not
a small amount.
What will you do with that?
Unless you know what it's for,
you won't sell it?
I came all this way since
you're a social enterprise.
I wasted a trip.
- Geez.
- Wait a minute.
When do you need them by?
Please have them ready
by the day after tomorrow.
- I don't have much time.
- For the day after tomorrow...
let's make it a 50% deposit.
Since it's a rush,
we have a lot to prepare.
Well...
Let's do that then.
Bring the contract.
Okay.
Where did you park?
I didn't see a car outside.
- I took a taxi.
- Taxi?
How will you go back?
You can't grab a taxi here.
Sign here.
- Over here?
- Yes, yes.
I'll sign here.
[Representative: Park Jung Hoon]
- There.
- Okay.
Then, have a good day.
Sell a lot.
- I won't see you out.
- Bye.
Good day.
- Hey.
- Yes?
What were you going to say?
Geez, so gross.
How many drums are like this?
- About 12 drums.
- 12? Hey, try eating it.
What? A maggot?
Punk, can't eat it, huh?
If you can't eat it, how could
consumers eat it, a**hole?
I told you to stay alert when
you're working, you bonehead.
- I'm sorry.
- You a**hole.
- Brother-in-law, I'll never do it again.
- D*** it!
Scrape the top and...
send half of it to the troops
and half to schools.
How can I send those
to the troops and schools?
They eat whatever they've given.
They wouldn't know
what they're eating.
Let's have jeotgal as side dishes today.
So what is that guy going
to do with 50 of those...
Who cares? He probably has
some connection somewhere.
Joo Chan, if we send out 12,
we won't have enough to make 50.
When we get jeots from China,
do a label-switch
- and set them aside.
- Okay.
What's a "label-switch"?
They import low-quality
jeotgal from overseas
and put Korean labels on them.
- They switch out the label, so "label-switch."
- Fabricate country of origin?
How cumbersome.
To make a few extra bucks?
Gosh, that scared me.
Geez, why send a text when
she's sitting in the back seat?
She should just say it.
[Korea: 3 million won /
China: 1.5 million won]
You can make twice the money if
you sell Korean jeotgal?
No wonder they switch the labels.
But still, man! You shouldn't do it!
How dare you mess with food?
You can't do that! Terrible!
Oppa, I still found you
a worker quickly, huh?
So what?
The girl you brought
last time is too smart.
She eats a lot, too.
Someone who eats little,
who understands just enough,
someone who works hard.
Someone like that.
Not a level 3. About level 2.5?
Someone like that?
Are you choosing meat
at a butcher shop?
- How should I match that?
- Hey, Choi Jong Sook.
Yes, Oppa.
I think 15% shares of our profit is
more than enough for you.
What do you think?
Of course, Oppa.
I'm always so grateful to you.
You know how I feel.
Let's pay attention.
Yes, Oppa.
You still haven't found the kid
who ran away last time?
Yes. She called me last time.
[Counseling Office]
[Level 3 Maria]
Geez, I just lost my appetite.
And Jo Jong Geun, you crazy bastard.
You should take it easy, you know.
If you're going to make her work,
just let her work.
If you want to fool around, just do that.
Decide which one.
So I can bring you a girl
that works for you.
Hey, say it straight.
What do you mean, fool around?
We're in love. Love. Do you know love?
I'm going to marry her...
How many times is this?
I'm sorry.
Oppa, when she resurfaces
dead or alive,
they should contact me
first and foremost.
Don't worry about it too much, Oppa.
What worry?
I don't want to waste all
the training we put into her.
And honestly,
if she's dead, we're
grateful for that, too.
Did you sign her up
for the life insurance?
Of course.
100 million won in case of death.
I put you down as the beneficiary.
Didn't I do well?
- Cheers.
- Cheers, girl.
When you get the insurance money,
you can't forget to give me my commission.
[Insurance Company]
Maria signed up for ten insurances
through that woman.
Half of the wages she
earned at this place
is automatically being
paid to the insurance.
Do you think Maria knows about this?
She probably doesn't know.
She's never been paid.
If you combine all the
disabled who work there,
there are tens of insurance policies.
Why don't you go in for an insurance
consultation if you're not busy?
[ND Insurance Company]
Excuse me.
How can I help you?
I'd like an insurance consultation.
Did you make an appointment
with an agent?
Well?
How about someone with
the highest performance?
Please come this way.
[Top of the Top! Choi Jong Sook]
[Miri Miri CI Insurance]
My goodness, sir. You make
such a great impression.
Thank you.
How much of a guarantee would
you like for life insurance?
I guess the more,
the better of a guarantee.
I see.
So you're the Agent of the Month?
I guess it just means so many
clients entrust me and work with me.
You speak so kindly.
I guess it's understandable that
those people trust and follow you.
"Those people"?
Ma'am.
Thank you for your help.
Maria...
What's this?
When did you prepare this?
I didn't do anything for you.
Gosh, Maria...
What's this?
Thank you, ma'am.
I'll live diligently.
Be healthy always.
Seriously.
Gosh.
Thank you, Maria.
Maria.
This is a really great place.
The owner is a great man.
I know him well.
So...
no matter what happens,
you just have to trust and
follow what he says.
My Maria...
You'll be fine.
I believe in you, Maria.
Okay?
You'll be fine.
You'll be fine. Really.
Thank you so much.
Thank you for the explanation.
How about the application...
I'll be back real soon.
Okay...
Hi, it's me. How about the bag?
You said you'll get me one this week!
So annoying.
I'm hanging up.
Geez, I'm sorry!
Oh, ma'am!
My gosh, sir.
Oh, no...
I'll pay for the dry cleaning and
sign up for the insurance right away.
Oh, my gosh! I guess you
and I are meant to be.
Sir, then...
Would you like to look
at this and sign up now?
But what should I do?
I have an appointment real soon.
- How about we do this?
- What...
Go in my car and let's talk on the way.
Shall we?
Thank you.
Coolio! I got one.
Okay...
Coolio.
Who are you guys?
Who are you that
you're kidnapping me?
Kidnap? What do you mean?
You got into the car yourself.
In any case, you dress
in a designer label.
Are you sure you made all that
money at the insurance company?
Where are you taking me to?
Our destination is
a food fermentation company.
They provide food and lodging.
It'll be great.
You know it well.
I think you're mistaken.
I'm a social worker.
I'm not a bad person.
That's what I mean. You'll have to go
with us for the sake of social welfare.
Save me! Let me go...
So noisy.
Why are there so many?
Well, many drums are good.
Geez, so cold.
Please save me.
The people I hate the most
are ones who borrow money and die.
Those people are constantly
mistaken about something.
Do you know what that is?
They think they don't have
to pay back when they die.
Keep this in mind.
A person dies, but the money
doesn't die with him.
Even if you die,
the debt you owe will
go to your family,
your cousins and second cousins.
If anyone shares a drop
of blood with you,
I chase them down to
the end and get the money.
You should know what you're
taking with you, at least.
I'll pay you back for sure.
What are you doing?
If you borrowed money,
hurry up and spend it.
Thank you.
Thank you!
Of course. You're always on the dot.
You're so dependable.
Check.
I'm sure it's the right amount.
He's gutsy.
What's he planning to do when he goes
out that he's working out so hard?
It's so pointless.
I should charge you...
for watching him like this.
I'll bring in more people soon.
Okay.
Okay, shall we check
on the guest rooms?
Three, four, three, four.
Five, six...
Thank you. (in Chinese)
Thank you. (in Japanese)
Go.
What's that?
Move your car!
Reverse! Reverse!
Why does he have the high beams on?
What's with that guy...
Hey!
Hey! Move your car...
Who are you?
Me?
- A bandit.
- Give me a break. Hey.
There's no mountain, moron.
True. The ocean is closer
than a mountain.
I guess I could be a pirate.
I'm standing on a road.
Let's say I'm a road thief.
What's he saying? You want to die?
The key is in the truck, right?
You just wait, punk.
You... you're dead.
Hey, you. Geez, that jerk...
Are you kidding me?
I'm in a foul mood as is.
Aigoo...
A young guy just broke his back.
What to do...
Gosh, much better.
As for this incident...
I have never been robbed
by a jeotgal thief in my life.
Gosh...
Gosh, I'm in a bind, though.
What I want is jeotgal, not excuses.
Geez, dang it.
I feel bad asking for a contract cancellation
penalty from a social enterprise.
Geez, what should I do?
First, it's my fault. I'll apologize.
I'm sorry.
Your genuine apology...
I'll pay you highly for it.
While I'm at it, let me add
20 more drums.
But if you miss your deadline again,
you'll pay twice the amount
for the penalty.
- Let's do that.
- Okay!
Aigoo, I'm so cool.
Then have a good day.
Feel better soon.
I'm off.
Be careful going home.
Aigoo, another beautiful day.
What a loser.
The loss we incurred...
I'll deduct it from
your share every month.
But still...
due to this incident,
I got you a little more...
I'm sorry.
Madam Choi!
Your oppa is here.
Oppa, huh?
You look great today.
What brings you here?
I haven't opened the store yet,
and Miss Kim isn't here.
Are you kidding me, Madam Choi?
You think I'm here to gossip
with you in my busy workday?
- Fill it up!
- Come on...
I still have a week left to deposit.
Just have fun with Miss Kim today.
I'll get you some money in a few days.
Geez, give me a freaking break.
A responsible citizen
should pay her dues.
Why count the days?
You end up paying the same
total per year anyway.
Hurry up and fill it.
Gosh.
Fill it. I don't have time.
Oppa.
Let's keep our distance, okay?
Geez.
[Here is Kang Maria's location]
♫ Have a glass ♫
♫ Let's go as far as we can,
have a glass ♫
♫ Tonight ♫
♫ You and I ♫
♫ Will become one, go, go, go ♫
♫ Have a glass ♫
Hey, Hyungnim!
Why don't you answer the phone!
Did you find out what I asked for?
I have the vehicle on the wanted list.
But I haven't heard anything yet.
Just wait.
If it goes around,
the CCTVs will capture it.
Hyungnim, I have good news!
Do you know where I'm headed?
I found her! Kang Maria!
We figured out her location.
I'm on my way to get her.
Hyungnim, you have to
pay me separately for this.
You know that, right?
I got it. I'll pay you. Just bring her back.
This guy and that guy.
They all want money.
What's with that punk?
He's so fast.
Gosh, I won't catch you today.
♫ Tonight ♫
♫ You and I ♫
♫ Will become one ♫
What? It's that punk.
What's that on a premium taxi?
Huh?
What? That crazy bastard.
What the hell? It won't move!
Hey! He's crazy!
Hey!
Whoa! Hey, a**hole!
I'm a police officer of Republic of Korea!
I'm dying!
[Seoul 26, Seo 0923]
It's the taxi that Jo Do Cheol took.
You can't come in here.
Come in.
Was there anyone inside the car?
Only a bag and an electronic
anklet were discovered.
There was no one in it.
Prosecutor.
Do you think Jo Do Cheol
stole the taxi and
set it on fire to destroy the evidence?
No, I'm sure the taxi driver
would've reported it already.
I don't think so.
What?
[Deluxe Taxi/Premium Taxi]
This isn't it.
It's one of the two.
The taxi driver is on Jo Do Cheol's side
or the taxi driver kidnapped Jo Do Cheol.
Here.
Deputy Chief wants to talk to you.
Why?
Yes, Sunbaenim.
Why don't you answer your phone!
Oh, you called?
I left it in the car. I didn't know you called.
Where are you?
Yes...
I got hungry, so I'm out to eat.
Did you eat?
I already told him we're
out at the quarry.
- Why are you telling me now?
- Geez...
I guess there are lots of
foodie places at the quarry.
Get back in the office now!
- Sunbaenim...
- Get over here now!
Geez...
It stinks high heavens.
What the hell are you up to!
What do you think you're doing?
You want to clear out of your office?
You! Get lost!
Want to grab a cup of coffee?
Yes.
All right. Here's coffee...
Thank you.
Try to be understanding,
Prosecutor Kang.
Deputy Chief Jo may
speak harshly, but
he's warmhearted.
I wish he was coldhearted
but spoke nicely.
Can I ask you a question?
Yes, sure. Go ahead.
What qualifications do you need
to drive a premium taxi?
You asked me that last time, too.
Are you investigating a case
connected to premium taxis?
I'm just curious.
Well...
First, not anyone can drive
a premium taxi.
You have to be an experienced driver.
- An experienced driver?
- Yes.
You have to have at least ten years
of accident-free driving record.
Ten years. That means the
driver must be older.
I guess at least mid-40's.
Well, pretty much.
You have to be sophisticated
with good driving manners.
You can never speed.
Have a good relationship
with the police.
Good enough to direct traffic
alongside them.
In a word, someone who is exemplary.
After hearing that, I guess
"premium taxi" sounds suitable.
Right.
Thank you for the information.
Well, I'm grateful if I was helpful to you.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Maria, are you hungry?
Let's go eat something yummy.
I'll do a little bit more of this.
What are you doing?
I was bored, so I was doing this.
I'm certified in Microsoft Word.
In my orphanage,
I was number one.
Daebak.
You did all this?
You're much better than me.
We must eat something
delicious tonight.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
What kind of medicine?
Are you sick?
Oh, if I take one a day,
I heard it prevents sickness and
puts me in a good mood.
Really?
Can I see what it is?
If it's a good one, I want to get one, too.
[Lilac]
[Birth Control Pills]
Let's go.
Something delicious?
It's snowing.
I have to use the restroom.
Okay, go ahead.
Jo Jong Geun, that a**hole.
That a**hole has been giving
Maria birth control pills.
He lied to her saying it's vitamin.
Maria, go to the laundry room.
The laundry is piling up.
Geez, that little rat.
It's f***ing good to see you.
I couldn't eat the jeotgal
you brought last time.
What the f***. Hey.
I prayed to God, Buddha,
and Jesus, so I can meet you.
Gosh, it's snowing, too.
How sentimental. Nice.
Hey, I fell for it once.
You think I'll fall for it again?
Do you think I'm a moron?
Hey, come.
Come, come.
All right.
Oh, cool, cool.
Aren't we cool?
Moron.
What? Moron?
Hey, let's go. Get him!
What are you doing?
Go!
Hurry! Find him!
Where did that rat go?
Hey, did you find him?
Didn't you see him? Answer me.
Didn't you see him?
I know he came here.
Hey!
Look at him. Hey!
What are you doing? Go!
He's right there!
Go!
♫ When the knife of sadness
twists in my heart ♫
Hey, hey!
Hey, get him at once!
What are you doing?
♫ I’m holding in the pain ♫
♫ Tonight ♫
♫ Silence ♫
♫ The tainted world won’t change ♫
♫ It has already broken
down with greed ♫
♫ But watch me ♫
♫  I’m doing this for you ♫
♫ Silence ♫
I give up! Give up!
- Why are you doing this to me?
- That's what I want to ask you.
Why are you doing this?
♫ Now I can say you surrender ♫
♫ I say you are done ♫
♫ I say you surrender ♫
Geez, that bonehead!
Why won't he answer the phone!
Geez!
- The call is not going through.
- That stupid cop won't answer, either!
Morons!
I gave so much money to that a**hole!
Are they all high on drugs or something?
Geez!
D***!
I heard you like BB guns.
I like BB, too.
Baseball.
What are you doing right now?
Wait. Aren't you the one who
was buying the jeotgal?
Hey, you scammer.
Did you steal the jeotgal?
Hey, you...
Gosh, it's a home run.
Wait. Just a moment.
Can't we talk?
I think it would be good to talk.
I'm in excellent condition these days.
Call the police! The police!
Hey, this is a crime.
- I'm calling the police, okay?
- Aigoo, I'm so scared.
Please go easy on us just this once.
We won't do it again.
Aigoo, I was about to call you.
I have to apologize.
I can't reach my employee who
went to pick up the jeotgal.
But don't worry.
I'll have it ready by tomorrow somehow.
Gosh, if you keep breaking
your promise,
I have no choice but
to cancel my order.
- Cancel?
- It's Joo Chan, right?
Joo Chan! Joo Chan!
Please save me, Joo Chan...
If they don't receive goods
worth 70 drums,
it must be a snag for them, too.
You're quite blunt with your words.
I like being blunt, too.
So let's make it work for both of us.
Don't you dare try to gamble with this.
Let's do this.
Prepare jeotgal for me
by tomorrow somehow
and if you can't get them ready again,
all the fallouts, including the
cancellation penalty,
will be on you.
Yes, got–
[Jeotgal from China]
They don't have this, either?
Gosh, Mr. Park Joo Chan.
He spoke so toughly,
but he must be on edge.
He's looking all over
for jeotgal from other places.
That's good.
We happen to have tons of jeotgal.
I set it up, so he'll call us
no matter who he finds.
What are you doing...
[Jeotgal Pig]
He's calling already.
Yes, yes.
Yes, of course.
We were getting rid of
our inventory anyway.
Maria unni!
Noona!
- Who are you guys?
- Is Maria noona here?
Maria?
She told us to visit her.
- What's that?
- We have to give this to Maria unni.
Today is Maria unni's birthday.
You have to give her this? It's nice.
Don't cry. S***.
How did they come here?
Hey, go, go.
Hurry up and go!
Go, go!
Go and study!
You should study.
Go now!
Maria?
Call them.
Call them and tell them to come over.
I bought lots of toys and lots of food.
Tell them to come.
Really?
Of course.
Here, here.
It's done.
All ready.
But a jeotgal factory buys jeotgal?
It's so interesting!
I'm speaking in Busan accent.
I sent you the money.
Stop talking and leave.
The money came in. We're leaving.
Busan people are leaving.
What's wrong with their hair?
Who are you?
You haven't heard the rumor?
I'm jeotgal thief.
Ah, it was you. The one who
stole my things.
You rat.
I'm glad you came, a**hole.
S***!
What?
It was you?
Why the hell are you doing this? You rat!
If I'm a rat...
what should I call you?
A**hole...
You deceived the disabled,
brutally used them,
and stole their wages.
You imprisoned them and
assaulted them.
What should I call you?
Who are you?
Who the hell are you to do this?
You're all grown up.
What's wrong with your face?
I'll wash it for you.
You're still dirty.
When ripen food is edible,
it's called fermentation.
If it's not edible, it's rotted.
Excuse me...
How long does it take guys
like you to ferment?
Save me...
Please save me...
This won't do.
You're already rotten to the core.
Save me, you a**hole!
- Take it away.
- Yes, sir.
I checked.
Does CEO Jang treat you well?
I also need a trustworthy
and dependable worker.
My goodness...
You're just style. The silent type.
Makes me covet you.
Think about it.
I'll pay you as much as you want.
As for all the unpaid wages...
I'll turn the company into a co-op.
The profits will be distributed
directly to the disabled.
Let's resolve it that way.
Is that possible?
Those guys played cheap tricks.
They put the title of the company under
one of the disabled who works there.
So it was taken care of easily.
So the disabled who work there will
become the company CEOs.
How about our taxi fare?
We have the money from
selling the jeotgals.
I'll shut down today's operation.
Yes, sir. Thank you.
Thank you!
Mission complete!
Okay, good job.
Should we go out for dinner together?
Next time for me.
I'm tired. I'll take off.
[Premium Taxi]
Does CEO Jang treat you well?
I also need a trustworthy
and dependable worker.
My goodness...
You're just style. The silent type.
Makes me covet you.
Forgive?
I'll never forgive.
Do you want to take revenge with me?
Then...
how do you plan to do it?
I won't lose to evil.
I'll beat it in my own way.
I'll collect all the trash around us
and isolate them from
the world forever.
I will reform them.
[Do not be overcome by evil,
but overcome evil with good.]
I heard they're laying off
30% of employees.
Since I'm a contractor,
I feel like I'm okay.
But then I worry that they
might cut me loose first.
Don't know.
I'll call you again.
Gosh...
I saw the announcement.
They're hiring less than last year.
There has to be one company
that will hire me.
If he switched the car,
this is the only spot for it.
Geez, they should've put up
a high-quality camera.
How many hours did I sit here?
I feel so heavy.
Gosh, nothing is easy.
I hope I lose some
weight easily, though.
No car went in there.
Where did this car come from?
No blinkers.
It's the same vehicle model.
I'll send you a CCTV clip.
Please ID the vehicle.
[Seoul Northern District
Prosecutors' Office]
Bam.
Ba-bam.
Prosecutor.
Did you sleep here last night?
I'll go home and wash up.
Okay.
See you.
Take your time.
Bam.
Ba-ba-bam.
It's pretty gritty for a taxi company.
Excuse me.
Excuse me. Let me ask you something.
I'm looking for a vehicle...
- Is there another parking lot...
- If you park like this,
do you know how many
cars get backed up?
I was in a rush. I'll move it soon.
The first thing you
should've done was...
to park it inside the lines properly
so it doesn't bother others.
I'll get the info I need and
move it right away.
It would've been fine if
you had answered me quickly.
Is that how you ask for information?
Excuse me, but can I ask you a question?
No. Just move your car.
[Epilogue]
Ms. Maria.
You want some coffee?
I'm okay.
Are you scared of coffee?
That's not it.
If I drink coffee...
- Unni!
- Noona!
How did you get here?
- We came in a taxi.
- A taxi?
- Taxi ahjussi gave us a ride.
- Really?
He bought us toys, too.
Stay right here. Okay?
Timing and Subtitles
Thank you!
Thank you...
Thank you so much for your help!
Thank you!
♫ The tainted world won’t change ♫
[Taxi Driver]
When I identified the vehicle,
this place came up.
Do you know why he's
working with Bluebird?
It was my fault.
Let's forget the past and start
over from the introduction.
The client is young this time.
Let's pay special attention.
It doesn't matter who throws
the stone. It still sinks.
Would they know how I feel?
I wish they'd feel the same thing I feel.
♫ Because your dream is
still alive and breathing ♫
♫ I wanna be your fighter
in this broken world ♫