♪Go to a warm place♪
♪Hold you tight♪
♪Care about you♪
♪Chase the light bravely♪
♪Don't panic♪
♪With me, you won't be sad♪
♪When you feel lost♪
♪I've been secretly accompanying♪
♪You♪
♪Not far away♪
♪Please smile♪
♪Warmth in the heart♪
♪With you by my side♪
♪The sun shines everyday♪
=Discovery of Romance=
(Breakup is a self-deceiving hypnosis)
=Episode 15=
Five years ago,
I chose to follow
my business partner's advice
and be rational about things
when Xia Tian needed me the most.
(Asian Design Award)
After weighing up the options,
I chose honor and dignity
without knowing what I put her through.
I don't want to hurt her again
because of An Ye's being back.
I...
I decide to indulge myself this time.
I choose to follow my heart
instead of my brain.
I will never let An Ye have her way.
I am being emotional.
So what?
(Unbounded)
Yeah.
It was a project
dated back to five years ago.
Ah.
Not mine.
It was from a friend of mine.
Really?
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Well...
When you are back in China,
I'll introduce her to you.
Great.
I'll send her information
to your email, okay?
Okay.
Thank you.
Ah.
Bye.
What is it?
Why are you so happy?
A new project?
I sent Xia Tian's works to Alex.
He really likes her style.
So I think
I'll introduce them to each other
when he is back.
After the last few days,
I thought you'd be rational about this.
But now I see that it only got worse.
You really haven't changed at all.
Of course I have.
I don't even argue with you now.
Peace.
Huh.
At this moment,
you can still be joking around?
What do you say
about the contract termination?
Hey.
What's the hurry?
Just look at her design sketch.
So smart, warm and comforting.
This is special.
It's not like
those unvarying guesthouse designs
in the market at all.
Don't you want something like this
in our company?
Before you say anything,
let's forget that
she's my ex-girlfriend.
Let's be objective about this.
Okay.
I know.
The works are fine.
I never said there's
anything wrong with her works.
But,
according to the financial statements,
it's not convincing enough
that it has to be her.
We only need an executive designer
for this project.
For our company,
we have so many
better choices.
Then I can only say
that all the overruns
are still reasonable.
This is her idea.
It can only be executed by her.
Xu Zehao.
I'm running a business.
Not charity work.
Do you want the whole company
to pay for your unrequited love?
An Ye.
You used to teach me
that we should be able to
establish priority.
I did it as you said.
But now I realize that I was wrong.
For what is
or isn't important,
you don't get the answer
from other people
or from conventional values.
Instead, you should listen to
what your heart tells you.
You are so naive.
You would say this
all because you already got
what you wanted before.
No one
can be greedy.
It's impossible
to have everything you want
without any sacrifice.
From the moment you made the choice,
you've lost the right
to choose another life.
Do you understand?
Then take me as greedy.
Perhaps I'm seeing this in hindsight,
or just coming to awareness.
Maybe I'm being full of myself,
or only self-sentimental.
I didn't have a choice back then.
But now that I have the ability
and the opportunity,
I want to make up for it.
Let me take the chance.
Don't you think
you sounded arrogant and selfish?
How about this?
If I lose,
I'll be responsible
for all the loss in this project.
Okay.
I'm warning you.
If you lose,
I'll take back the share
that belongs to me.
You can rest assured.
I won't drag you down.
(Xia Song Studio)
What are you working on?
A new project?
A new project.
A new client.
I have some new adjustment suggestions
about the sketch of the last room
of the guesthouse.
I've taken care of An Ye.
Come back.
I don't think I'm quite capable
of working with you.
We have a small company.
We should keep our hands
to where our ability reaches.
But it doesn't seem like your style
to give up halfway.
This is not giving up halfway.
I want everything I have
to be earned by my real ability.
Not someone's pity.
Xia Tian.
We are halfway through the project.
I know how hard you worked.
You shouldn't quit now.
I asked you not to go
accept the materials
only because of
my personal reason.
I wanted to avoid you.
I really didn't know
about An Ye's visit.
I didn't handle it right.
I'm sorry.
And,
I dug up
your graduation project.
And I sent it
to your favorite designer, Alex.
After he is back,
I want to
find an opportunity
to introduce you two.
You withdrew from the ADA competition
because of me.
This time,
I want to make up for my mistakes.
I hope you won't give up.
You should carry on your work.
Take a look.
I...
I went to see your dad.
Why did you go?
I wanted to apologize.
For not attending the funeral,
and not taking good care of you.
I promised him
to protect you
and indulge you.
I'm sorry.
I didn't keep the promise.
When he passed away,
why didn't you just tell me?
I thought you could sense it
and feel it.
We were together for five years.
I thought
we understood each other well enough.
I thought as long as I said
that I need you,
you would come to me no matter what.
I always thought
you were just being emotional
because you were sensitive.
I've never thought of
you being in trouble.
I didn't even have the patience
to try to understand you
and ask you if you were really sad.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Xia Tian.
I...
I found out too late.
I'm sorry.
(His body temperature,)
(his tears,)
(and his honesty)
(all made me feel safe.)
(Over the years after dad passed away,)
(I've been avoiding it)
(and didn't know how to deal with it.)
(Now I suddenly feel like)
(I've let all my guard down.)
(As if someone is saying,)
(I got you.)
(Don't be afraid.)
(Like a wanderer)
(who can finally stop)
(and have a good sleep.)
Actually, I didn't even know
that my parents had divorced
until my dad had the accident.
I always thought my parents
had the most perfect marriage.
They didn't communicate much,
but I always thought
that was just
the way they lived together.
Only until that day,
my dad had the accident
with another woman,
I found out that the love had long gone
in their marriage.
Perhaps I never acknowledged the fact,
so I didn't have the courage to face it,
let alone talking about it.
When we went camping
by the sea that day,
he told me a lot
and also requested a lot.
He asked me not to argue with you,
and to always lose to you unconditionally
after we get married.
He asked me to see you
as the last woman I ever loved.
But,
I don't think I've done any of that.
We did have some problems.
But...
It wasn't hopeless to solve them, right?
Well then...
Let's leave that opportunity
to Guan Xin.
I can see it.
He...
He loves you very much.
And also,
he cares about you a lot.
He is better than me.
Xia Tian.
Let's break up.
I didn't know
why we broke up.
And I didn't accept it.
Now I decide to accept it.
Haven't you always hated me?
Let's leave those to memory.
♪You will know♪
This box
is full of what you left me.
Now,
I give it back to you.
I...
Can I hold you one more time?
One last time.
♪And I found my own♪
♪With happiness and the future♪
♪I know I'll hold you♪
♪When you appear in my life again♪
♪Again♪
♪I know♪
I wish you happiness
and
a good life.
♪From night to day♪
♪Hide the feel♪
♪That you wanna say in time♪
♪You will know♪
♪How deep you are in my heart♪
♪And I found you♪
♪And also I understand my own mind♪
♪Because the moment with you♪
♪Is so precious to me♪
♪And I found my own♪
♪With happiness and the future♪
♪I know I'll hold you♪
♪When you appear in my life again♪
♪And I found you♪
♪And also I understand my own mind♪
♪Because the moment with you♪
♪Is so precious to me♪
♪And I found my own♪
♪With happiness and the future♪
♪I know I'll hold you♪
♪When you appear in my life again♪
What are you doing?
We are eating hotpot.
Everyone's waiting.
Hurry up.
♪Cannot say it is love♪
(I said what I wanted to say.)
(Only for this,)
(I haven't got the chance.)
(Five years ago,)
(we went to the place
where we first met.)
Let's break up.
Xia Tian.
Xia Tian!
Hey!
♪The light within my heart♪
♪Has been out for years♪
(I wanted to ask her
to marry me that day.)
(I didn't expect)
(that trip)
(would be our last trip together.)
♪Have made♪
♪Lifelong promises♪
♪When the wind is blowing again♪
♪When I cannot dream of you at will♪
♪When we meet again after everything♪
♪Can I still become♪
♪The right one♪
♪For you♪
♪Again and again♪
♪I walk on this street♪
♪I'll never make you lonely♪
♪I want to say I love you♪
♪But these few words♪
♪Always come too late♪
♪And turn into regret♪
This is good to eat.
Okay.
Thank you.
Why are you being so polite to me today?
Ah.
Can you order something
less spicy next time?
This is too spicy.
You said you wanted something spicy.
This is way too much.
Ugh.
You are so hard to please.
What's wrong?
Can you finish crying first?
How are you going to
eat anything like this?
Yeah.
What happened?
Why can't you tell us?
Xu Zehao came to me.
What?
What did he want?
To break up with me.
Didn't you two break up
five years ago?
Yeah.
He said,
he didn't know why I broke up with him
five years ago.
So he never accepted it.
And I never stopped hating him.
So it didn't count.
But he just accepted it.
So...
We officially broke up.
He wished me happiness.
This is a good thing.
Why are you crying?
Right.
Here.
Don't cry.
Wishing each other happiness
and living one's own life.
There's nothing better.
Yeah.
I shouldn't cry, right?
This is a good thing.
Why would you cry?
Here. Have some meat.
I don't want to cry.
But I can't control it.
The tears just keep running down.
I don't want to.
But I just can't help it.
Then cry if you want.
Crying all the bad things out.
Don't they say it in the show
that people who cry while eating
can smile while living?
Now you finished crying.
You can have a nice meal.
Here.
Xia Tian.
No one is mighty.
Cry if you want.
At least you have us at home.
Yeah.
Don't worry about
the guesthouse project.
Yu Hui and I
will take care of it.
You should see each other less.
Yu Hui?
What?
What's it got to do with him?
What's going on?
I have to...
I owe you an apology.
I'm not a good friend.
There are so many things
I can't even face myself.
So,
I can't share with you.
Be quiet.
Is she okay?
I don't know either.
Should I go wake her up or not?
Don't.
She's definitely not awake yet.
The way she cried last night
just broke my heart.
Morning!
It's all...
Morning.
We made breakfast.
Do you want to have some first?
I'm going out.
Got a date with Guan Xin.
Why is she so happy?
It's terrifying.
Is this what people in love do?
Love?
Never had any.
♪I suddenly found♪
♪You tilted your face♪
♪Like the reflection in the water♪
Xia Tian?
We'll cook together?
Alright.
You cook.
I'll help.
Okay.
♪You're my love♪
♪Right♪
♪Right in this season♪
♪Say the promises♪
♪Just say more♪
♪Let the whole world hear it♪
♪Right♪
♪Right at this time♪
♪Keep what you say♪
♪Just keep the time♪
♪The still time♪
This is great.
We're having more and more of a rapport.
But the longer it gets,
the more problems
we'll find on each other,
and the more tiring
the relationship will become.
I don't think so.
The more memories we have together,
the better and more natural
our relationship will become.
But in this world,
people always change,
and relationships too.
Even if others do,
we won't change.
Look.
We had so many misunderstandings,
and so many fights.
But no one said a word
about breaking up.
But no matter how hard you try,
and how much you love each other,
you still get into fights inevitably.
You get tired
and you change.
That's probably just what people do.
They get tired.
Have you
loved anyone like that?
Ah.
Guess I'm right.
You got hurt deeply?
No.
Just giving out my opinion.
Xia Tian.
I don't know what you've been through.
But I won't change.
If there's any problem between us,
I'll solve it.
As long as you trust me
and love me,
I'll always have
the motivation to love you.
Trust me.
Okay?
Lili.
The operation went very well.
You can go home in a couple of days.
I'll take you to a nice meal after that.
Okay?
Lili is so brave.
After we take off the bandage,
you will be the most beautiful girl
in the world.
What is it, Lili?
Is your forehead hurting?
Lili.
What is it?
You can tell me.
I miss my mom.
Lili.
I am
your family.
I'll always be with you.
Do you trust me?
Don't cry.
Be good.
When I get back,
I'll bring some snacks here
for you, okay?
Don't cry.
Good girl.
(Xia Tian)
(How is it going?)
(Did it go well?)
(It did.)
(I just finished the operation.)
(Coming over right away.)
Dr. Guan.
I'll go home to get something.
We rushed here today.
I forgot something.
I'll send you back.
Don't bother.
I can ride the electric bike.
It's inconvenient to ride a bike
to get those stuff.
Let me give you a ride.
Okay.
Thank you, Dr. Guan.
Up there.
Here we are.
This is my home.
So Lili and you...
You live here?
Yeah.
It's a small place.
But we can live comfortably here.
How do you sleep?
Lili sleeps here.
And me here.
This is really convenient.
It can be a bed at night.
And you can fold it
and put a little table here in the day.
Can you sleep well in this?
Of course.
I sleep very well here.
Pack your clothes
and everything you need.
I'll take you to a hotel.
No need.
That's too expensive.
It's a waste of money.
Lili just had an operation.
This place...
I mean
it's better for her recovery
if you live
in a hotel near the hospital.
Just go.
I'll wait for you.
Okay.
(Guan Xin)
(Xia Tian.)
(I still have some work to do.)
(If I can't finish it)
(tonight,)
(I won't come over.)
Hello.
A room, please.
A single room?
Um...
A standard room.
Okay.
Please show me your IDs.
No.
It's...
It's only for me.
Yes, it's for her.
Then please show me your ID, Miss.
Okay.
(Guan Xin)
(Xia Tian.)
(I still have some work to do.)
(If I can't finish it)
(tonight,)
(I won't come over.)
(Xia Tian)
Hello, Xia Tian.
Hello, Guan Xin.
I just saw your message.
(Sir,)
(are you sure you want a standard room?)
Sir?
Ah.
A standard room.
(Okay. One minute.)
Guan Xin.
(Where are you?)
I'll have the call somewhere else.
Yeah.
Hello, Xia Tian.
I'm at...
I'm at the Jindu Hotel
near the hospital.
(You know that I went to see a kid)
(in the charity house.)
I just finished her operation.
She doesn't have anywhere to live.
So I'm getting a room for her.
Okay.
I'll leave you to it.
I'm okay.
(Okay.)
All done.
Yeah.
You and Lili can live here
for the next few days.
Tell me if there's anything.
Thank you, Dr. Guan.
Don't worry about it.
I'll be on my way then.
Bye.
Oh, wait.
I have some free time the next few days.
I'll get some furniture for you
and redecorate the place.
Don't bother.
Dr. Guan.
I can live...
What did I say?
Lili is at the hospital.
Be careful when you pick her up.
That was my first time
being honest with Xia Tian about this.
Actually, it was not
completely the truth.
Maybe 70 percent.
Because I haven't told her
about Lu Xi.
Xia Tian?
I don't really know
what she's thinking.
Maybe she wants me to be more honest.
Actually,
to tell the truth,
I feel at ease.
It's just...
I'm not a person who's used to lying.
Because...
It feels really bad
when you can't sleep after you lie.
So this time,
you really decide to give her up?
I'm not giving up.
I'm just letting go of
my possessiveness
and unwillingness.
I want her to have a better life.
So what did she say?
I...
It seems
I only realized now
how to love someone.
Another one, please.
Thank you.
(Unbounded Space Design Firm)
Do you know
that a pig can do a better job than you?
Do it again!
I'm sorry.
Sorry, boss.
Are you full?
Should I order another one for you?
Didn't I say
you can't eat on the working table?
I...
I'm sorry, Mr. Xu.
I'm late.
For how long?
One...
One hour.
Why?
The traffic
in the morning...
So it's my fault
for having a meeting in the rush hour.
No, no.
It's my fault.
Buy coffee for everyone.
Thank you, Mr. Xu.
This...
Whose drawing is this?
Boss.
It's mine.
Why did you put the socket here?
After the bedstand comes in,
are you going to dig a hole through it?
Do it again.
Which smart guy did this?
You put a table
next to the radiator.
Can't you see that?
The wood is going to crack
next to the radiator.
Everyone, please.
The thing above your shoulder.
It's not an ornament.
So use it.
Think with your brain.
Um...
Mr. Xu.
The placement of furniture
and the look of the whole place
are supposed to be arranged
by Miss Xia on the site.
She's more familiar with
the details and...
Yu Hui.
Yes.
Call Xia Song Studio.
Okay.
Dismissed.
Boss.
I'm calling them now.
Hello.
Mr. Yu.
What is it?
(Oh.)
(Here's the thing.)
(We have some furniture)
(coming into the guesthouse.)
We need to check with you
about the placement of the furniture.
Xia Tian ordered all the furniture.
Wait a second.
I'll ask Xia Tian to talk to you.
Boss.
Should I talk to Miss Xia?
What?
Um.
We'll do the talking.
Okay.
Go ahead.
Where do we put the desk?
The desk.
The desk should be near the window
in the home office area.
The desk should be in the home office
near the window.
The bedstand?
One or two?
One.
She said,
one bedstand.
The dining table?
Do we have to use elm wood?
The elm wood.
Yes.
Sectional couch
or regular couch?
Sectional.
Sectional couch.
Oh.
Boss.
Anything else?
Ask how she's been doing lately.
I won't.
Ask her yourself.
(You are the one)
(who goes to her house every night.)
(Hey!)
(Hang up!)
Oh, my!
Xu Zehao comes to our house
every night to see you?
♪Right♪
♪Right in this season♪
♪Say the promises♪
♪Just say more♪
♪Let the whole world hear it♪
♪Right♪
♪Right at this time♪
♪Keep what you say♪
♪Just keep the time♪
♪The still time♪
♪Cannot say it is love♪
♪Just want to care for you♪
♪To have relentless talk with you♪
♪The street covered by leaves♪
♪I want to find an excuse♪
♪To walk through it again♪
♪The light within my heart♪
♪Has been out for years♪
♪Until you are here again♪
♪Leafing through the old photos♪
♪You and I♪
♪Have made♪
♪Lifelong promises♪
♪When the wind is blowing again♪
♪When I cannot dream of you at will♪
♪When we meet again after everything♪
♪Can I still become♪
♪The right one♪
♪For you♪
♪Again and again♪
♪I walk on this street♪
♪I'll never make you lonely♪
♪I want to say I love you♪
♪But these few words♪
♪Always come too late♪
♪And turn into regret♪