♪Go to a warm place♪
♪Hold you tight♪
♪Care about you♪
♪Chase the light bravely♪
♪Don't panic♪
♪With me, you won't be sad♪
♪When you feel lost♪
♪I've been secretly accompanying♪
♪You♪
♪Not far away♪
♪Please smile♪
♪Warmth in the heart♪
♪With you by my side♪
♪The sun shines everyday♪
=Discovery of Romance=
(This is the best gift I can give you)
=Episode 20=
Why are you being so serious today?
We'll talk in the car.
Can you tell me
where we are going now?
You'll know in a minute.
Xia Tian.
Will you marry me?
No, no way.
Baby.
Ah?
What's wrong?
I was just thinking about a design.
There are a lot I'm not satisfied with.
I was thinking how to revise it.
Ay.
Today you belong to me.
Don't think about anything else.
Take it easy.
(Pearl Wedding: Tong Mei & Guan Qun)
Today is my parents'
pearl wedding anniversary.
Hello.
This way.
Let's go.
Thank you.
So thoughtful.
Really?
Thank you.
Take a seat.
Long time no see.
Come on.
Congratulations!
Welcome!
Welcome.
Mom.
Hey.
This is Xia Tian.
Auntie and Uncle, hello!
Ha.
Xia Tian.
It's nice to finally meet you.
Dad, mom.
This is a gift from me and Xia Tian.
May you both live
to old age in conjugal bliss
and always be happy.
Thank you.
Guan Xin,
take care of her.
Come and sit!
Thank you very much for coming.
When we were young,
I couldn't give her a proper wedding.
I'll make up for it today.
(Pearl Wedding: Tong Mei & Guan Qun)
Give it to me.
Tong Mei,
thank you for being with me
all these years.
Thank you.
Good!
It's kind of romantic.
- Right.
- Yes.
Don't listen to him.
Actually,
he just missed you guys,
and took advantage of the event
to get you guys together.
He kills two birds with one stone.
Good!
She always tells the truth.
Well...
Let's get some of my old classmates
up here and say some words.
Okay.
Let's welcome my brother Liang.
Welcome brother Liang.
All right, I'm here.
Ay.
We old classmates,
ever since we graduated,
have been far apart
and scattered all over the world.
It's not easy to
get together today.
First, I have to thank the model couple,
old Guan and Tong Mei,
for giving us the opportunity
to get together today.
I'm just so puzzled.
I can understand
them being sweet
when they were young.
But why can you still be so sweet
even when you are at this age now?
You always post
those sweet little articles in Moments.
I'd like to ask you both
for the rest of us,
don't you get tired of each other?
Go ahead.
The handsome guy just now,
you don't understand it, right?
It's called loving
till the end of the world.
Let's not just sum it up.
What is love?
Let's get old Guan and Tong Mei
to show you how.
Yeah!
Where are your screams?
Where's the applause?
Old Guan.
Come on.
Wait till I finish peeling this shrimp.
Action means everything.
See?
Ah?
All learn from them.
Being sweet in public.
What's this?
A great person
with another great person,
this is the symbiotic effect.
What are you talking about?
Tong Mei
is the representative of top women.
She was a belle
in our clinical department.
A lot of boys liked her.
Yes.
Right.
Exactly.
Here. Cheers!
Come on.
I'll give you a toast.
Enjoy yourself.
Guan Xin.
Your girlfriend?
So beautiful.
Hey.
A handsome man and a beautiful woman.
Thank you, Auntie Zhang.
Long time no see.
Among us,
Tong Mei is the most blessed one.
Old Guan loves her so much.
Look at her son.
So handsome,
thoughtful
and considerate.
And he gets a girlfriend
at the marriageable age.
Ay.
Not like my son.
He's been out of the country
for over a year.
He hasn't been back once.
Not to mention getting a girlfriend.
No comparison,
no damage.
Take it easy.
Hey, Guan.
I want to ask you a question.
What beauty treatment
did you give your mom?
Look at her.
She looks a lot younger than us.
Maybe we should all go to
Guan's hospital for a beauty treatment.
- Okay.
I'm in.
You want to go too?
I'll take my wife.
Oh no.
Even though Guan Xin
is a nationally famous plastic surgeon,
I don't really like to
do the beauty treatment.
Pure natural.
Oops.
Look how sweet he is.
Here.
Let's make a toast again.
I wish you happiness.
Thank you.
Thank you all.
Come on, cheers.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Here, Tong Mei, I'll give you a toast.
Come on, everybody, listen to me.
Is the watermelon sweet?
Sweet.
Sorry.
I didn't tell you in advance today.
Right.
I didn't even get a present.
After all, it's my first time
seeing your parents.
I am so embarrassed
by receiving so many presents
from them.
They like you.
How could they not?
I envy them.
At this age,
they are still so energetic.
I want to be like them when I'm old.
Get a bunch of people together,
singing and dancing.
We're done with them for the day.
Let's have a date tonight.
How?
You'll find out later.
Xia Tian.
I know
you might find it a little weird
if I propose to you now.
But I don't want to make a splash.
Because I think
we could do it in a low profile.
Didn't you say you envy my parents?
We will be even happier than they are.
♪Don't panic♪
I hope I will always be with you.
There won't be
any more secrets between us.
Even if we may have a misunderstanding,
or a fight,
I believe
love will make me
fall for you again and again.
So...
Xia Tian.
Will you marry me?
♪With you by my side♪
♪The sun shines every day♪
♪When you feel lost♪
♪I've been secretly accompanying♪
♪You♪
♪Not far away♪
♪Please smile♪
♪Appreciate the good days♪
♪With you by my side♪
♪Warmth in the heart♪
♪When you feel lost♪
♪I've been secretly accompanying♪
I love you.
♪Please smile♪
♪Appreciate the good days♪
♪With you by my side♪
♪Warmth in the heart♪
(Xia Song Studio)
Wow.
This is so big.
Guan Xin spent a lot of money.
Tsk.
Even though
he made a distraction at first,
he did propose on the football field.
Um.
So touching.
Hey.
Am I going to be the maid of honor?
Then I don't even have to
prepare the wedding gift, right?
I'm so happy!
One wedding gift for two good friends.
That's great.
Then I wish you a happy wedding.
Congratulations.
Stop.
Pang!
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Happy 30-year-old birthday to myself.
But,
I'm going to do
something special this year.
Please
give me a little help tomorrow.
No problem.
Then sing the song.
- ♪Happy birthday to you♪
- ♪Happy birthday to me♪
Hey.
This is a special party?
It's so formal.
Don't you know?
Everything today is prepared
by Song herself.
It's so sour.
Hello.
Why are you here?
Good to see you again.
Donghao.
I'm here to celebrate Song's birthday.
Oh.
You're quite nice
to bring a green cake.
Xia Tian.
This is the junior fellow of Song,
Tan Xu.
This is our good friend,
Xia Tian.
Hello.
I've heard so much about you from Song.
Hey.
So many people here.
Xia Tian.
Why are you here?
Song invited me.
Ah.
We've met.
You are...?
In the pub.
Song.
You and another girl
were scolded by Song.
Xia Tian.
Nice to meet you.
Why didn't I know about this?
That day,
you came back with Guan Xin late,
and Song got drunk.
Oh.
Haha!
Right.
I was too busy.
Otherwise Song is always with me.
Xia Tian.
Isn't this our family meal?
Why are there so many guests?
Can't you see that?
Today's party is planned and prepared
by our heroine,
the birthday girl herself.
We're just here to help.
So we need to know our place
in front of the guests
who are here today.
Alright.
Now comes the biggest part of the day.
Welcome
our brightest heroine.
You're all here.
How is it?
Am I
beautiful today?
Ah-choo!
Ah.
Song, don't get cold.
And you don't get cold either.
I'll go inside and get her the coat.
Looks like
we'll have a show here.
Cheers.
Let's celebrate our perfect
Song's birthday.
Happy birthday, Song.
Thank you all.
Happy birthday.
Sit.
Xia Tian, is this...?
She got engaged to Guan Xin.
You can tell Xu Zehao
about it.
Song.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Hello.
Go away!
Song.
Um.
Okay.
Thank you for coming here.
Guan Xin's mom is here
and I have to go meet her.
Just go.
This
is the gift I picked with Guan Xin.
You're going to love it.
Thank you.
You three
take good care of her.
Just go!
Song.
Have a try.
Okay.
This is the...
Matcha Mousse.
The one I like best.
I ordered it for you 10 days in advance.
Thank you.
Hey.
Xu.
Such a little piece.
It's not even enough for me.
Next time, buy a bigger one.
Song.
Um?
This is my happiness tree for you.
It's easy to keep.
Look, there are many
copper coins hanging on it.
It means fortune,
happiness,
and beauty.
This is
a pine tree?
Of course.
A pine tree for Song,
[*Pine tree sounds like Song in Chinese.]
of course.
Mr. Yu.
Are you celebrating someone's birthday?
It's like
for the opening of a bathhouse.
What are you doing?
Then what's your gift for me?
I have to use the bathroom.
On the second floor.
The birth...
Hey.
That guy...
Wait.
The toilet
on the second floor is broken.
It's under repair.
Go to the one on the first floor.
Didn't I just come from the first floor?
Then check the basement floor.
There is one on the basement floor.
Basement floor.
There is a toilet on the basement floor?
Yes.
Yeah.
Go.
Didn't I tell you...?
Song.
Li Donghao.
What are you doing upstairs by yourself?
Song.
Didn't you ask
what gift I will give you?
I'm telling you.
The gift I'm going to give you
is particularly special.
That cake is delicious,
but it will make you fat.
And the pine tree.
Come on.
It's a new era now.
A pine tree?
And you have to water it.
What a waste of resources.
My gift
will keep you from worries.
Here.
Come.
Let me show you.
Why are you covering my eyes?
I'm telling you.
I'm sure you'll be
thanking me for this forever.
Are you going to get me some diamond,
or gold?
Are you ready?
3.
2.
1.
Ta-da!
(For Song)
How is it?
Even if you don't flush after you poop,
the intelligent closestool
will flush it for you.
The moment you get up,
you'll only get just one word,
cool.
Especially for a woman like you
who's always constipated,
it's the most thoughtful
and practical gift of all.
Don't you think I know you so well?
Are you touched?
Li Donghao.
You really don't know
anything about women.
Piss off.
Did I pick the wrong color?
I'm really pissed off.
If I only have an EQ of 59,
then Li Donghao's EQ
is negative for sure.
I really wonder
how he got into the medical college.
People who study well
can't even figure things out?
Intelligent closestool?
Auntie, why are you here?
I passed by,
and stopped by to see you.
I also brought you some care products.
Here.
Take a seat.
Thank you, Auntie.
I wanted to go to your house.
But it would be inappropriate
to visit all of a sudden.
So I decided to meet you here.
Please don't blame me
for not telling you in advance.
Uh, no.
I should have visited you first.
I ordered you a cup of coffee
and a piece of cake.
Just have it.
Thank you, Auntie.
This is an old and expensive community.
The houses are not cheap here.
You bought the house you're living in,
or...?
My mom's.
But I pay the rent.
You pay rent to your mom?
That's interesting.
Some other day,
we can meet up.
I've heard so much about your mom.
I kind of like getting along with
educated people.
I heard
you have a studio
for your own business.
How's the business this year?
I just got a nicely paid
guesthouse project.
So...
I think it should be okay this year.
That's nice.
Women should have our own career.
But as long as
you can find the right balance
between career and family.
Hey, eat this.
Try the cake.
Okay.
Do you make money management?
Do you have any fixed invested stocks?
I don't pay much attention to this area.
But,
I can learn about it in the future.
It's okay.
I can teach you that in the future.
Women should be more careful
about the family's finance.
Well,
as long as you're a girl
who Guan Xin likes,
I will like you too.
And I'm not a difficult person.
You'll find it out later.
(Premarital Examination for Women)
This is a premarital examination.
I've asked someone
to arrange it for you.
If you have time next week,
ask Guan Xin to go with you.
And then,
(Premarital Agreement)
this is a premarital agreement.
You and Guan Xin need to notarize
your premarital property.
Your income after marriage
will be your common property.
But you can rest assured.
We won't treat you wrong.
For the marriage of you and Guan Xin,
we'll buy the house in full payment.
On the house proprietary certificate,
your name will be included too.
Auntie.
Guan Xin and I
may not be in such a hurry.
This has to be done.
Don't think of me as being indifferent.
A marriage
is no small thing after all.
After considering all these things now,
in the future,
it would save a lot of trouble.
I didn't mean that.
Auntie.
I can understand your...
That's good.
You can leave the wedding to me.
My besties and I often get together
to talk about things about wedding.
We know what girls like.
In the future,
we can be good friends
who can talk about everything.
(Happy forever)
Song.
Ay.
What's with the long face?
It's your birthday.
You should smile.
It's alright.
Ay.
I've just met my bane.
Well...
Song.
Actually,
I've been thinking about it
for a long time.
Ay.
What's wrong?
Today,
I want to
introduce myself seriously.
Take a seat.
I am
32 years old.
I have been single.
I don't really like to
have an ambiguous relationship
like those young people do.
I don't really like
the uncertain feelings either.
You and I,
no matter at work,
or in private,
have known each other a lot.
I don't know how to say it,
so I wrote a letter.
Please take a look.
After you read it,
well,
then you can consider whether
I am a suitable romantic partner,
or
a life partner.
Yu Hui.
Why are you bothering our birthday girl?
Here.
Eat more.
Song.
Don't you like
the color of the closestool?
I'm telling you.
I'll change it into a black one.
Look at you in all black.
You like black, right?
Here.
Take a seat.
Sit tight.
What?
Let's swing for a while.
Does it have to be
in such a straightforward way?
I would never have chosen
this outdated way of confession.
It's too low.
Ah.
I'll kick your bottom.
Here, you two, be careful.
Watch out.
Slow down.
Hey.
This one.
Be careful.
And slow down.
Hey.
Be careful.
Slow down.
Okay.
When will you come over?
- Give me that.
- Ah?
Mr. Xu.
The furnishings and furniture here
will soon be finished moving in.
This is the list.
Take a look.
If there's no problem,
please sign here.
Did you reserve the place
for the woodwork as I told you before?
Yes.
You can rest assured.
Thank you.
It's our pleasure.
Then I'm leaving.
Bye.
Hey.
Watch out for that one.
Boss.
I'm back.
Well,
do you know that?
What?
Guan Xin proposed to Xia Tian.
I...
I'll go get busy.
It's actually
a nice way to end it.
The project is over.
And Xia Tian
lives a happy life.
I hate to admit it,
but
Guan Xin does seem to
be more suitable for her than me.
I just hope that Xia Tian
can have a joyful
and happy life.
That's it.
I'm sorry.
Let's...
Let's call it a day.
Sis.
Long time no see.
Wow.
You still look so good.
Haha!
You are late.
I don't have much time.
Hurry up.
Well,
sis, you know I am a man
of science and technology.
I can do things like calculus
even with my eyes closed.
But I am illiterate
in words expression.
This is a special case.
Success or failure
hinges on this one action.
So can you help me
write a love letter
that would move the one who reads it
and make her marry me?
A love letter?
What's the style of that girl?
That girl
is kind of hard to describe.
She is not sensitive at all,
with low emotional intelligence
and a voracious appetite.
But,
she and I have the same selection
for late night snack.
But she speaks without thinking,
and hits me when she gets angry.
Her legs are a little short.
The boobs
are just fine.
But her look
is really not my type at all.
And on top of that,
I can't believe she has bad hygiene.
She won't flush the closestool
after using it.
She behaves disgracefully
after getting drunk.
She is totally in a mess.
What do you like
about a girl like this?
Right?
I might as well forget it.
I agree with you.
Why would I like a girl like Song?
It feels like I've been poisoned.
This feeling...
Stop.
I'll help you.
Tell me.
What style do you want?
I want a romantic one,
like the way of movie
and TV characters talking.
What can I do?
I just fell in love with her.
Just help me.
Something like that.
How much will you pay?
Five deluxe hydro lifting packages.
Ten.
Deal.
Please.
Just go.
Hey!
Surprise!
Have a look.
Is it for me?
I think so.
Wow.
It's a pair of new sneakers.
It's a beautiful color.
Do you like it?
And new clothes.
Thank you.
Granny.
I think it's more accurate
to call me auntie.
Thank you, Auntie.
Why did you buy me sneakers?
Well,
this pair of sneakers
is a free gift from an event.
They said only those
who play football can wear them.
I like this pair of sneakers.
But
I don't play football.
So I...
I thought of you.
Thank you, Auntie.
You're welcome.
I have new sneakers.
Wow.
These sneakers are so nice.
Cool!
Awesome.
Are you ready
to take over the whole mess?
We shall see.
So how do you think about us?
I've thought about it
120 times seriously.
Ah.
The results are not very satisfying.
So I think
you might as well forget it.
120 times?
You thought about it from day to night.
You're so focused on me.
Relax.
Take your time.
We are far from being old anyway.
Huh!
50 years old
is still far from being old?
If people can live till 100 years old,
we still have 50 years
to talk of everything,
to travel around,
and to eat and drink.
Right?
Ay.
Hey.
Let's have lunch together.
Here.
It's stuffed with mackerel.
Don't be such a vegetarian.
It's not that hard for old friends
to build a family.
In the past,
we met
once a week.
In the future,
we'll meet 7 times a day.
Right?
Hey.
It's like two kinds of
stuffing dumplings.
It would be nice to mix up.
Can you be quiet for a minute?
Ah.
(WeChat messages with Lu Xi)
(Running Deer)
(Where are you?)
(I'll go find you!)
(Lu Xi)
(Sorry! The subscriber you called
is not answered.)
Dr. Guan.
Why are you here?
Why didn't you reply to my messages?
And you didn't answer my calls.
Why is your phone powered off?
I...
I have been busy lately.
Did you have your supper?
I'm going to make my supper.
Put down these things.
I'll take you to have dinner nearby.
Let me help you.
Don't bother.
I can handle it.
What is it?
You don't look well.
Are you sick?
Ah.
I just caught a cold.
Why do you have that pity look
on your face?
Do I need to be pitied with a cold?
Don't do that.
No.
I'm not pitying you.
I'm just caring for you.
Eat more.
Dr. Guan.
The other day,
you said at dinner
that if my brother shows up
and recognizes me,
he'd pretend he doesn't know me.
I haven't asked you
why he would do that.
Maybe,
he doesn't want to lose what he has.
What does he have?
Right.
Maybe
in the eyes of others,
he comes from a decent family.
So he doesn't want others
to know he was adopted.
What's wrong with adoption?
I...
I know it.
He has his difficulties.
Maybe
his foster parents
don't want others to judge them.
He could have told me in secret.
I won't tell anyone.
Is it that hard?
Ah?
The last thing he wants to deal with
is his conscience.
He left you behind,
and got adopted himself.
♪Right♪
♪Right in this season♪
♪Say the promises♪
♪Just say more♪
♪Let the whole world hear it♪
♪Right♪
♪Right at this time♪
♪Keep what you say♪
♪Just keep the time♪
♪The still time♪
♪Cannot say it is love♪
♪Just want to care for you♪
♪To have relentless talk with you♪
♪The street covered by leaves♪
♪I want to find an excuse♪
♪To walk through it again♪
♪The light within my heart♪
♪Has been out for years♪
♪Until you are here again♪
♪Leafing through the old photos♪
♪You and I♪
♪Have made♪
♪Lifelong promises♪
♪When the wind is blowing again♪
♪When I cannot dream of you at will♪
♪When we meet again after everything♪
♪Can I still become♪
♪The right one♪
♪For you♪
♪Again and again♪
♪I walk on this street♪
♪I'll never make you lonely♪
♪I want to say I love you♪
♪But these few words♪
♪Always come too late♪
♪And turn into regret♪