♪Go to a warm place♪
♪Hold you tight♪
♪Care about you♪
♪Chase the light bravely♪
♪Don't panic♪
♪With me, you won't be sad♪
♪When you feel lost♪
♪I've been secretly accompanying♪
♪You♪
♪Not far away♪
♪Please smile♪
♪Warmth in the heart♪
♪With you by my side♪
♪The sun shines everyday♪
=Discovery of Romance=
(I'm not a saint. I'm tempted)
=Episode 18=
Why are you here?
And these flowers.
What do you want?
Go back.
Do you hear that?
I meant you.
Go back.
Me?
What do you mean?
Um.
Just ignore him.
Is there anything you want to say to me?
Um.
Bro.
Please
leave us alone.
Haha!
I won't leave.
As her brother,
I have four words for you.
You don't deserve it.
What makes you think
he doesn't deserve it?
I found you're so funny.
This man made you cry for once,
and he will make you cry again.
The wrong guy
will stay wrong no matter how.
Do you know that?
Can you figure it out?
Piss off.
I told you to go back inside.
Psycho.
He's in now.
Say whatever you want to.
Sorry.
Song.
Back then,
I knew exactly how you felt about me,
but I pretended not knowing.
And I made you pay for my car repairing.
I didn't realize how much it hurt you.
I did some self-examination afterwards.
I was so confused back then.
So,
I am sorry.
I sincerely apologize to you.
Huh!
Song won't forgive you that easy.
Thank you.
You're blocking my view.
Song.
You had fun with Yu Hui
in the team building,
and you also accepted Tan Xu's flowers.
You must like one of them.
You like one of them,
or not?
I cannot tell exactly right now.
It's yet to be determined.
No way!
You want to date with two people?
Before we enter a relationship,
we should go on a few dates first.
No.
You can't.
Why?
Well...
If you date them,
I don't know
who will have night snacks with me.
What?
All you know is eating.
You're getting so fat.
I'll stop having
night snacks from now on.
I won't have them anymore.
Go away!
Ah.
Li Donghao.
You bad man!
Hey.
Put my flowers down.
Aren't you allergic to pollen?
Li Donghao.
Stop walking around.
You're making me dizzy.
Hey.
My personal life
got a little complicated,
which I didn't expect.
How is it?
(WeChat messages from Tan Xu and Yu Hui)
Isn't that wonderful?
These two.
Which one do you prefer?
I don't know either.
Yu Hui,
is older.
But he's
careful,
considerate
and mature.
He's a nice guy.
But I always feel like...
Tsk.
And Tan Xu,
I don't like him that much already.
But,
Tan Xu has really changed me a lot.
Look.
I learned financial management
because of him.
Fund, insurance, something like that.
Otherwise,
I don't know any of these.
And most importantly,
Tan Xu likes me now.
Isn't that nice?
No.
There's one person
I'm struggling with right now.
As long as it's not Li Donghao.
Um.
Our Li Donghao?
Song.
Ah?
Where are you going?
I'm going to have a meeting
at Xu Zehao's company.
Alright.
I'll drive you there.
Ay.
No need.
I got a cab.
Bye.
Hey.
No.
Wait for me.
Oops.
Are you alright?
Song.
Let me drive you there.
Lisianthus is beautiful
and well-cultivated.
Its meaning
is true and unchanging love.
These are the best flowers for a woman.
Li Donghao.
What's in your hand?
Nothing.
You're hiding it from me?
No.
What's wrong?
Take it out.
I just saw it.
Do you really want to see it?
Do you?
Hi, Xia Tian.
Where did you get this?
Tell me.
The auntie gave them to me
when I bought her scallion.
She gave you these?
Here you are.
For you.
Do you know that?
He just did a lot of weird things.
For example,
we made a chair
with a leg missing.
You can see him no matter where.
It's just
so eye-catching, you know?
Stop laughing.
And...
I asked myself a serious question.
What exactly do I need?
Wealth, family background,
education background,
talent, appearance, height.
I don't think any of them
matters to me now.
Maybe when I was 20,
I cared a lot about them.
But now,
I only care about two things.
One,
take me as a woman.
Two,
except for taking me as a woman,
treat me as a human being.
But our Li Donghao
just takes me as a buddy,
never as a woman.
Even so,
you still like Donghao.
Look, you like people for a reason,
except Donghao.
Right?
I can't tell you why myself.
But there's no reason to like someone.
It just happens for no reason.
By the time you know it,
you already like him.
It doesn't matter
whether you know nothing
about him.
Have you experienced that?
Tell me more about it.
Like,
his favorites,
his hates,
his horoscope,
and his birth date.
You don't know any of them,
but you still like him.
Maybe even
love at first sight.
It's not visible
or suspicious.
By the time you know it,
it just happened
naturally.
There's no room for regret.
That's when you realize
that maybe your heart
works a little faster than your mind.
That's it.
Haven't you really experienced it?
I really hate Xu Zehao.
Xia Tian, are you crazy?
Do you even know
what you were talking about?
What do you mean by "your heart
works a little faster than your mind?"
What do you mean
by "it just happened naturally"?
Do you have any idea of
how hard it is for me
to play dumb between you two?
I really can't understand
what is going on with you two.
You broke up five years ago.
And you broke up for the second time
after five years.
And you?
You would cry when you heard him
saying those nonsense.
What's wrong with you?
You are tempted by him again?
Yes.
I'm tempted.
How could I not?
He's Xu Zehao,
not somebody else.
What Xu Zehao means to me,
don't you know?
We were together at our simplest time
for five years.
We grew up together.
By far,
he's still the one who knows me best
and has seen the worst of me.
Sometimes, he knows me
even better than you and Donghao.
How could I not?
But what can I do?
I know I shouldn't wait for him.
But I did.
I know there are many words
I shouldn't say.
But I did.
But other than that,
what else have I done?
Did I sleep with him?
Did I run off with him?
Anyway,
I know exactly what I'm supposed to do.
I've never run away from it.
And I know where I should be.
I'm doing my best to be in my place.
But I'm not a saint.
I'm just a human being.
I'm just tempted.
What should I do?
I'm sorry.
I was too harsh on you.
It's okay.
I know these things
are hard to understand sometimes.
It's not that I don't understand.
I am just worrying about you.
Do you understand?
Isn't that what people do?
When others fall in love,
they may think
they are naive and ridiculous,
like psychos.
I can't understand them either.
But you're Song.
I don't care what others say,
except you.
I know.
I was wrong.
I won't do it again.
Don't worry.
I know.
I love Guan Xin now.
I was too young when I was with Xu Zehao
back then.
I can't see anything else
but him.
Love always came first.
But I know
Guan Xin.
And the more I know him,
the more I like him.
I feel safe with him.
I can always be spoiled by him.
I can do whatever I want.
So I won't leave him
and I don't want to.
I trust you.
Huh.
Don't ever say that again.
I will always be
on your side.
Boss.
I'm going over to
Sheng Group this afternoon
to talk about the townhouse.
Okay.
And...
Miss Xia will be here this afternoon.
I got it.
Are you alright?
Of course.
Of course okay.
How can we work together
if we are not okay?
And you said,
time will heal everything.
It will pass.
Okay.
Then I can give you the files.
Oh.
Wait.
Um.
The client said he wanted
to plant a tree in the yard
in front of the house, right?
Um.
Tell them it's not possible.
Because after 10 years,
or 20 years,
when this tree grows,
it will definitely
affect the sunlight to the townhouse.
We can't just cut it down then.
It's a life after all.
We can't just think about the present
but not the future.
Boss.
Now I see
why you're so obsessed with Xia Tian.
What do you want?
Because she said the same thing as you
when she saw the tree
in this proposal.
You look like a bad man right now.
Do I?
I...
I have to go now.
That's the general guideline.
I'll be there again
before the furniture is installed.
Mr. Xu, any opinion?
Nothing.
Thank you.
Guys,
the meeting is over.
It's almost finished.
I'm kind of looking forward
to seeing it done.
Yes.
We'll be busy for a few more days.
Go for it.
Thank you.
You're here.
I know.
The old rule.
No shrimps.
More clams.
Yeah.
Pick one place and sit.
Chef,
one without shrimps,
more clams.
I hope you won't mind me sitting here.
You said it,
we can be just Party A and Party B.
It's common
that colleagues share a table
when they meet at a restaurant.
Since the last time you drove me home,
I haven't been to your house.
At work,
I think I didn't embarrass you
by talking about the work.
No.
Suit yourself.
Hey.
Here come the noodles.
One with lots of beans and fungus.
One without shrimps but with more clams.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
Are you as lazy as ever?
Are shrimps that hard to peel?
What a hassle it is to peel shrimps.
It's handier
to eat clams.
You too.
With lots of beans and fungus.
(Guan Xin)
Hello.
(Hello.)
(It's me.)
(Have you finished eating?)
(I'm eating with Xu Zehao.)
(We're at the final sprint
of the project.)
It will be over when it's done.
Ah.
What about tonight?
Do you have any plans?
Ah.
Nothing.
I may have to work overtime tonight.
You enjoy yourselves.
Okay.
Bye.
Here.
Three spare ribs in sauce.
Right.
We used to take two,
and had to fight for it.
Right.
It's funny to fight about something
like that.
Also the instant noodles with cheese
or not.
Bean curd jelly sweet or salty.
Scrambled eggs with tomatoes
with salt or sugar.
Potatoes hard
or soft.
Ah.
And...
The cola.
Pepsi
or Coca.
So annoying.
I don't know
how I put up with all these back then.
If you ask me,
I'd say we should have broken up
the first time we fought.
I'm the one who should say that.
I won't order beer.
Just in case after getting drunk,
something that couldn't
be fixed happens.
As long as you won't drink too much
and send me messages
in the middle of the night,
there will be nothing we can't fix.
Hey.
That was the only time I did wrong.
Do you want to always bring it up?
Waiter.
A bundle of protoplasmic beer.
Ah.
Okay.
That's it.
I think it's okay for you, right?
Okay.
I really didn't eat seafood noodles
until I met you.
Before that,
I didn't even eat any noodle.
So did I.
Before I started dating you,
I had never seen a movie before.
Don't mention about TV dramas.
All because of you.
And camera.
Taking photos.
I began to learn the tree language.
I listened to Jay Chou's songs
and watched his movies
because of you.
I read the romance novels
like My Sunshine
because of you.
You have to dip in vinegar
when eating dumplings.
You have to dip in sauce
when having hot pot.
I just want to know
why a hamburger
has to come with a milkshake.
I don't know
why you dip chips
in sweet and sour sauce.
Tsk.
Hey.
When I think about it,
at least half of my habits
were changed because of you.
Me too.
But I still can't accept
the wasabi thing.
I can't accept durian either.
Even if I keep it in the fridge,
its smell will be all over the room.
It's a pity
that you don't get its delicious taste.
But you are probably
the only one in the world
that can be so scared by Train to Busan.
Be serious.
Train to Busan is really scary, okay?
Why didn't you mention
Monkey King: Hero Is Back?
For a cartoon,
you cried so hard.
Was I the only one crying in the cinema?
More than half the people cried, okay?
When others cried,
at least they didn't blow their nose
on other's clothes.
Didn't you cry?
Didn't you ask me for tissue?
I...
Well...
When there was a cockroach in the house,
didn't you always jump on my back?
I took care of
that rat last time.
Rats are really scary.
Girl are all afraid of cockroaches.
Are your father and mother all right?
Yes.
They have fun all the time,
and never come home.
Are they really
traveling around the world?
It's been three years.
Except for a postcard
I received from them last month,
I haven't heard from them since.
I really admire you.
Your parents love each other so much
and they love you so much.
But in such a privileged environment,
why are you
so difficult to get along with?
That's weird.
Are you cold?
Unfortunately,
we're not in a relationship
where you can take off the coat for me.
Haha.
Who wants to take off the coat for you?
Don't flatter yourself.
You used to be like this.
You like to sing Karen Mok's songs
alone.
I told you to sing
Hiroshima Love with me,
but you rejected it.
I really don't get it.
What's wrong with out of tune?
I was not afraid of that.
There has always been a saying
that whenever couples sing this song,
they will break up.
Even if you tried so hard to avoid it,
didn't we break up in the end?
Is it bad to break up?
Now I can sing whatever I want.
I don't have to be so careful.
Maybe we'll get along
and can still be friends.
Friends?
With you?
I'd prefer Song.
Tsk.
I'm okay now
with being completely disconnected
after the breakup
and not knowing
how the other one is doing.
Didn't we always do so
before we met?
(Surely, we still can't be friends.)
(I want to)
(hold his hand.)
(Can I pretend to be drunk)
(and hold her hand?)
(When can I touch his face)
(like I did the other day,)
(pretending to be drunk?)
♪I want to find an excuse♪
(It would be hard)
(for Xia Tian)
(if I say I still love her.)
♪When the wind is blowing again♪
♪When I cannot dream of you at will♪
♪When we meet again after everything♪
♪Can I still become♪
♪The right one♪
♪For you♪
(The subscriber you called
is not answered.)
(Please try later.)
(Sorry! The subscriber you called
is not answered.)
Hello!
What's wrong?
Donghao.
Are you up?
Ay.
This is weekend,
and I have to sleep more.
What is it?
Where is Xia Tian?
Xia Tian.
Ah.
I'll go and check.
Xia Tian.
Xia Tian is not here.
Isn't she at home?
She may have gone
for a walk on the seaside.
She likes to go to the seaside
a lot these days.
Oh.
I got it.
Ah.
Morning.
Where is Xia Tian?
Is she out?
Didn't she come back?
I think she's with Guan Xin.
What?
She's not home.
Guan Xin just called me
looking for Xia Tian just now.
She didn't come back?
You are tempted by him again?
Yes.
I'm tempted.
Xia Tian had a meeting
with Xu Zehao yesterday.
Oh no.
What did you say to Guan Xin?
I said she went for a walk
on the seaside.
What kind of nonsense did you say?
What was I supposed to say?
Weird.
(I'm eating with Xu Zehao.)
(We're at the final sprint
of the project.)
(It will be over when it's done.)
(What about tonight?)
(Do you have any plans?)
Ah.
Nothing.
I...
I may have to work overtime tonight.
You enjoy yourselves.
I had the wrong phone
with that man you met
on the day you went on a blind date.
When I went back to him
to get my phone back,
I slept at his place
because I was too drunk.
You are the one who picked up the phone?
Why is he here?
He's my client.
Yeah.
I'm the one who picked up the phone
and also her client.
(I hope you're on the seaside.)
(No matter which sea,)
(I'll find you.)
This is not good.
Why isn't Xu Zehao answering his phone?
Hey.
What did Guan Xin say?
I haven't talked to Guan Xin yet.
Do you think
Xia Tian is with Xu Zehao?
I knew it was only a matter of time.
What is it?
Is she crazy?
Are you crazy?
I need you to watch your mouth.
What?
She's like this.
What can I say?
I'm telling you.
Li Donghao.
You can't say a word
to Guan Xin later.
Or I'll rip out your tongue.
What?
If she's with Xu Zehao,
I'll never see her again.
I'll stop being friends with her.
Whatever.
Alright.
It's not going to solve anything
with or without you.
Do you have any idea?
During this period,
she and Xu Zehao were together
for the right reasons,
either as partners or as exes.
That's why I kept it from Guan Xin.
But if they were together last night,
what else can I hide?
Shut up.
Li Donghao.
I'm telling you.
No matter Xia Tian slept with Xu Zehao
or not,
she's my friend.
Do you hear me?
Oops.
So powerful.
Hello!
Song.
(Hello!)
(Yu Hui.)
Hey.
What is it? Calling me at the weekend.
Um.
Is Xu Zehao with you?
Mr. Xu?
No.
I just wanted to talk to him
and called him,
but he didn't answer it.
What about last night?
Were you two together?
I've been busy with something else
since yesterday afternoon.
(He was having a meeting with Xia Tian.)
(Then...)
What?
What's going on?
Didn't you just hear all that?
Yu Hui is now going to Xu Zehao's house.
Then?
What about next?
Ay.
We can know
only after he arrives.
So many questions!
You just know to ask questions.
Wait.
Send a message to Xia Tian now.
Ay.
I got it.
Shut up.
You just shut up!
You're so annoying.
(Verified successfully.)
(Please open the door.)
The shoes are hidden.
Smart!
What are you doing?
Oops.
Where is she?
Who?
Xia Tian.
Why would she be here?
Did she go back?
Are you done?
Are you nuts?
(Xia Tian's location: Yinshe Yard)
Chen.
Get her out of bed.
Xia Tian.
Wake up.
It is 11 now.
Xia Tian.
(Guan Xin's missing call)
Are you crazy?
Is that who I am?
Is Xia Tian like this?
How could she cheat on
her boyfriend?
Huh!
So where did you send her last night?
You never wore heels before.
Why are you wearing them now?
Let me see.
Does it hurt?
Should I get you to the hospital?
Why are you crying?
I don't know.
Don't cry.
Seeing you cry in front of me,
I feel terrible too.
I don't think it's serious.
I'll send you home.
No.
I'll go to my mom's house.
You'll go to your mom's house?
Why?
Ask her why she had me.
Life is hard enough to live.
Why did she have me?
Go ask her.
I want to know too.
♪Right♪
♪Right in this season♪
♪Say the promises♪
♪Just say more♪
♪Let the whole world hear it♪
♪Right♪
♪Right at this time♪
♪Keep what you say♪
♪Just keep the time♪
♪The still time♪
♪Cannot say it is love♪
♪Just want to care for you♪
♪To have relentless talk with you♪
♪The street covered by leaves♪
♪I want to find an excuse♪
♪To walk through it again♪
♪The light within my heart♪
♪Has been out for years♪
♪Until you are here again♪
♪Leafing through the old photos♪
♪You and I♪
♪Have made♪
♪Lifelong promises♪
♪When the wind is blowing again♪
♪When I cannot dream of you at will♪
♪When we meet again after everything♪
♪Can I still become♪
♪The right one♪
♪For you♪
♪Again and again♪
♪I walk on this street♪
♪I'll never make you lonely♪
♪I want to say I love you♪
♪But these few words♪
♪Always come too late♪
♪And turn into regret♪