♪Go to a warm place♪
♪Hold you tight♪
♪Care about you♪
♪Chase the light bravely♪
♪Don't panic♪
♪With me, you won't be sad♪
♪When you feel lost♪
♪I've been secretly accompanying♪
♪You♪
♪Not far away♪
♪Please smile♪
♪Warmth in the heart♪
♪With you by my side♪
♪The sun shines everyday♪
=Discovery of Romance=
(Even when the sky falls down,
I won't be with you)
=Episode 10=
[K💖I💖S💖S💖K💖H]
(Xia Tian's dad died.)
(A month before you
broke up with Xia Tian.)
(No one)
(would choose to break up with Xia Tian)
(at that time,)
(but you did.)
Hey.
The ex-boyfriend
Xia Tian said is you, right?
What did you do to that girl
back then?
She still hates you now.
Just take me home.
Okay.
Forward.
Back to your position.
Watch the ball.
Over here.
Go! Pass!
Watch out for others.
You had a bad day at football.
You are not focused,
completely absent-minded.
Are you talking to me?
I think so.
The sneakers don't fit me anymore.
I cannot run as I wish.
Tell your grandma to buy you a new pair.
Lace up.
My grandma said,
the sneakers are too expensive.
How do you know about my grandma?
Do you two know each other?
Not really.
I saw her pick you up.
My grandma told me
not to talk to strangers.
I'm going to play football.
Oh.
This is the grandchild of Xia
and that woman, right?
I'm so glad.
You came to see him,
which means
you don't hate him anymore.
What's that got to do with him?
This kid...
This kid is pathetic.
Actually,
Xia is quite pathetic too.
He's just got a strange temper.
All those years of working with him,
I can't say
I like him,
but I really don't think he is bad.
Are you done?
Yes.
Director.
Can we talk for a second?
Sure.
Would you stop bothering me?
Stop following me around all day long.
You're invading my privacy.
Do you know that?
You and I know each other well.
What kind of privacy is there?
I know all about you.
Well...
I'll stay away from you a bit.
I think that's enough, right?
Go further away.
Hey.
Don't go.
Hello.
Could you call
Dr. Guan Xin for me, please?
Okay.
Hold on.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Lu Xi.
Dr. Guan.
I brought you afternoon tea,
your favorite Americano
and the cake I just made.
Lu Xi.
Thank you for the coffee and cake,
as well as your kindness.
But,
I don't really need it.
You know what we do here.
We are so busy every day.
Sometimes they have to be thrown away
if I cannot eat them.
So, don't give me these any more.
I want to thank you with these.
If it's not convenient,
then forget it.
Is there anything else?
(I was going to ask)
(if I could still send you
afternoon tea every day.)
Oh.
I also want to ask
about treatment scheme for another kid.
When can I know about it?
Um.
Let me take a look.
Next Wednesday.
Next Friday.
I'll be free these two days.
Oh.
Okay.
I will not bother you anyway.
Lu Xi.
Take
them back.
As long as it's about the surgery,
you can talk to me any time.
I'll help you in any way I can.
I see.
Dr. Guan.
(Yinshe Yard)
Why are you here today?
I miss you.
Oh?
Not me.
You miss your dad.
If you really miss him, go visit him.
You can go alone
if you don't want to go with me.
It's from a colleague.
Just drink it.
Oh.
What a surprise.
The new project is paid partly.
I'll pay you partly too.
Save it for your marriage to Guan Xin.
Do you mean those I owed before...
No way.
You can pay me after getting married.
I knew it.
Are you really getting married?
I don't know yet.
A little hesitant.
I feel like both of us
haven't shown our true selves yet.
He seems to be hiding something from me.
But so do I.
Like what happened to my dad,
I never told him about it.
Or
he doesn't know
how the studio works.
If we do get married,
I think we should all be
a little more honest.
You
are too pride,
just like me.
You don't want to show your dark side.
It means,
you're not capable of
facing who you really are.
But that doesn't stop you
from trusting people.
Will the people who really love you
care any of these?
Do you care?
What?
Um.
Huh?
Nice coffee today.
I really got it wrong?
That's impossible.
How could I forget
Xia Tian's dad's death?
Did you make this by yourself?
Yes.
It's made from cherry.
Do you know what cherry tree means?
I don't know.
What is it?
The one and only love.
The one and only me.
Help me wear it.
The gifts are still there.
Xu Zehao.
Why are you back?
What time is it now?
It's 2:30 PM.
Oh.
I'm sorry. I forgot it.
Do I mean nothing to you?
No.
I told you so many times
today not to be late.
Why were you still late?
In that case, you shouldn't be late.
I waited for you
at the station with my friends
for two and a half hours today.
I called you and you didn't pick up.
Do you know
how
awkward I was?
In the end, they went by themselves
and I came back alone.
Do you take it for granted
that you can stand me up?
I didn't mean that.
Hey. No.
Please.
I've been waiting three months
for this camera.
I was late.
I was wrong.
I apologize to you, okay?
Don't.
Ah.
Give it to me.
Come on.
Alright.
Don't be mad.
Ah.
I promise
I will never be late again, okay?
You just don't have me in your mind.
Why would you want to be with me?
How can it be?
I'm with you only because I like you.
In your world,
I'm the least important one.
Work,
friends,
and even hobbies
are more important than me.
Hey.
Don't think so.
Let me make it up to you.
Let's go to have hot pot.
Cattle stomach.
Abnormally spicy.
Okay.
You just think I can be easily bullied.
That's why I like you.
There's no way I remember this wrong.
They're all there.
Or
did Xia Tian deliberately forget it?
Why didn't you tell me
about uncle's death?
I've told you.
You just forgot it.
No.
You've never told me about it.
At the meal yesterday,
I remember
both of those things you said,
the marshmallow and hot dog.
Although the details we remember
are a little different,
it's all in my mind.
Xia Tian.
I admit
I may have overlooked you
when we broke up five years ago.
That's because you became a part
of my habit.
I didn't have to worry about you,
read your mind,
or figure out what you think anymore.
Even when you got angry,
I would think it would pass.
Sorry.
I'm sorry for the way
I treated you at that time.
I remember all these things
I didn't do well.
But I really don't remember anything
about uncle's death.
Why?
Even as a friend,
I shouldn't have found it out until now.
Right?
Are you sure you remember everything?
Are you so sure of your memories?
I must have given you a call.
(Sorry! The subscriber you dialed)
(is not answered at the moment.
Please try later.)
(Sorry! The subscriber you dialed...)
(Xia Tian)
(Are you busy?)
(Why didn't you pick up the phone?)
(Pick up the phone, please.)
Hello!
(What's wrong?)
(Why did you call me so many times?)
I wonder if you could come.
(I'm working overtime.)
(What's wrong?)
Don't ask.
Just come.
(I really can't make it.)
(I'll talk to you when I'm done.)
(OK?)
Remember it now?
One call, two calls, three calls,
four calls, five calls, or six calls.
I've been trying
to reach you on the phone.
Did you ever ask me why?
Did you ever ask me why I needed you?
You didn't even ask,
just telling me you were working overtime,
you were busy,
and you had no time for me.
You wouldn't remember
even if I tell you which call it was.
But,
something so important
like uncle's death,
you should at least tell me clearly.
What's the point
of talking all about it now?
Our relationship was over
a long time ago.
It ended completely five years ago.
I never felt like it ends.
You will come back to me eventually.
Unless the sky falls down.
It will.
You know that.
I've never failed in anything
I've tried to do.
Then you should now know
that the rules of the game in this world
are not set by you.
And I know exactly
who I like right now.
So what?
There is no relationship
in this world that is constant.
Just like five years ago.
We used to be so sweet,
but we broke up in the end, right?
It's been so many years,
and you still care
all about your own feelings,
never caring about others.
Get yourself a tetanus this afternoon.
I think that nail is rusty too.
Otherwise you'll get a fever
and infected.
You're always reckless
regardless of the consequences.
Leave.
If I ask you out to dinner right now,
I don't think you're going to say yes.
Leave now.
Okay.
I'm leaving.
Thank you.
Bye.
Xu Zehao will definitely not know
what love is in his life.
No kidding!
I never said the word love.
I just said I fell for her again.
That's all.
She is thinking too much.
They are two different things.
How can the word love
be said so casually?
Can't he just grow up?
After breaking up, we can just
offer the blessing generously.
Is it that hard?
No blessing at all.
And he said he fell for me.
Does that make any sense?
Blessing?
Okay.
With me.
If she's with someone else,
do I have to pretend to be generous
and wish her happiness?
So he will never know
what tolerance and understanding mean.
Tolerance
and understanding?
I'm OK with it.
Just give me a chance.
I'll make you feel it.
Ah.
(Qingshan Charity House)
Who is this?
Tell me.
George.
This is George?
I don't know.
Who is it?
This is Peggy.
This is Grandma.
Uncle Li, I'm here.
Lu Xi's here.
I bought you something to eat.
I'll check on everyone.
Okay.
They're in there.
What's this, Cherry?
Ms. Zhang.
Hey.
I'm here.
Lu is here.
Um.
Are you good today?
Sis Lu Xi!
Slow down.
Here, are you good today?
Here is your reward.
Don't rush.
In order.
Lemon, pink.
You're welcome.
Ms. Zhang.
Help me share them.
Okay.
You all have one.
All have one.
Kid!
Kid,
what's your name?
Lili.
Why aren't you happy today?
You didn't reach for a snack.
It's okay.
Here.
I brought you the best one.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Um.
Ms. Zhang,
what's that scar
on Lili's forehead?
Ay.
Lili just got here.
She's so pathetic.
Her parents fought in the kitchen.
Her father was drunk
and wanted to burn down the kitchen.
At a young age,
she went to take care of her mother,
but she burned her forehead.
Luckily, she didn't
burn her eyes.
Where are her parents now?
They are in jail by selling fake drugs.
Her relatives had no choice
but to send her here,
so she's always been introverted.
Ms. Zhang.
Yes.
I have to go there.
(Running Deer)
(Dr. Guan.)
(Are you free in next few days?)
(There's a child)
(I want to talk to you about.)
(Guan Xin)
(Okay.)
(You can meet me
at the hospital after work tomorrow.)
(I'll get to know more about her.)
Here.
Try this beef in sauce.
It tastes good.
Wow.
Director Jianmin,
did you make this on your own?
I can't do that.
A gift from a friend.
A friend?
Man or woman?
A woman.
A teammate from the hiking team.
Wow.
A woman.
Are you in love?
No way.
Love has to be mutual.
I'll eat what I like.
Thank you.
Don't mind it.
She is just a female teammate.
She has unrequited love for me.
But I rejected her
because I'm so determined.
What does that have to do with me?
Of course it does.
Ms. Wu.
Can I ask you a very professional
and personal question?
I don't know if you...
Well...
Haha.
Oh.
Oops.
- I'm stuffed with the beef.
- I'm full.
I'm full too.
Oops.
Take a walk.
Oh, my God.
What do you mean?
Hey.
Let me ask you.
What is a man's sexy brain?
Sexy brain?
I hate it when you say that.
Why?
Just admit you're ugly if you're ugly.
Don't put on some labels
like sexy brain.
If you have to talk about sexy brain,
Einstein would have one.
Then why did she say
I have a sexy brain?
That lady who gave you the beef
said that to you?
Director.
I suggest you to wake up.
Your brain is so simple.
Now it looks like
you have a more decent face.
Really?
Well...
In your mind,
what kind of image do I have?
Say something nice about you?
You're wearing a pair of glasses,
with not so many hairs left,
no visible beer belly,
but the body
doesn't look strong, either.
What's the advantage?
It's hard to describe,
a bit abstract.
Please make it a bit more specific.
Am I the right type for you?
Why are you so cheeky?
You can't fall in love
without being cheeky.
Eat your beef.
You really don't want to try it?
Then I won't eat it, either.
I won't eat it if you won't.
Huh!
Ay.
Hey.
Does Director Jianmin like auntie?
He doesn't stand a chance.
No one would like a woman
like my mom.
I think you just don't have
eyes to find beauty.
Auntie is so charming.
If I want to be in a relationship,
I would never choose you two.
I'll look for an elegant woman
like auntie.
What's wrong?
Look.
Xia Tian.
Turn it off.
What do you think?
Are you going out?
I'm going out to battle.
I'm busy today,
so I cannot go to
the construction site.
Who are you going to battle for?
The university association
has a gathering today.
That bad man?
No.
Oh.
Then why don't you go now?
Still staying here.
You don't understand.
The important one
is always the last one to come out.
When Tan Xu is burning with anxiety
while waiting for me,
I'll appear in front of him
at the right time.
Well.
If he's really anxious,
won't he call you?
So I turned my phone off too.
Fine.
Song's here.
Come on.
Hello.
I'm sorry.
I'm late.
We're all waiting for you.
We've all had enough.
I got a little stuck in traffic.
Drink three cups of wine first.
You were stuck in the road.
I'm stuck in the heart.
So slow.
This is...
Oh.
Let me introduce.
This is Song.
We are all from the same school
and same association.
This is Alice.
Tan Xu's girlfriend.
Hello.
I've heard so much about you
from Tan Xu.
Tan Xu,
when you were in college,
there were so many girls pursuing you,
and you didn't even fall in love.
You make such a great move now.
Such a gorgeous beauty.
A gorgeous beauty.
Right.
I'll drink with the gorgeous beauty.
Here.
Drink with the gorgeous beauty.
Cheers!
How long have you two been together?
More than half a year.
We joined the company together.
Why haven't I heard you
mention her before?
What?
Oh.
I didn't take it seriously.
You didn't take it seriously?
It was in the middle of ambiguity,
so you didn't want to talk about it.
Look now,
he took her here, right?
I think Tan Xu
is being serious this time.
Let me ask you.
Has anyone ever seen him
take another girl out?
Have you?
No.
Ah?
What about you?
No.
Doesn't he usually hang out with Song?
Right.
Alice,
it's really nice to see you.
Oh, wait.
So how old are you?
23.
I just graduated this year.
Nice to meet you.
23!
Tan Xu,
you're great.
You are good at it.
He's quite good at it.
Tan Xu, I understand it until today.
When you just got your job,
you said you were busy.
You asked me
to feed the fish at your place,
so you were just too busy dating.
You gave me the key to your apartment.
You asked me to clean up your place.
Was it all because
you were too busy in love?
Okay.
Go out with your girlfriend
in the clothes I bought you?
You are so cheeky.
Tan Xu,
you and I have known
each other for a long time.
What do you take me for?
A maid?
A cleaner?
Asking me to come and go
as you wish?
Song.
I know your feelings.
You just shut up!
You bad man!
Shame on you!
Song.
Drink, Song!
Let's drink.
Come on.
Don't want to escape it.
Drink!
What are you doing?
You came late, and you drank late too?
Come on.
Drink less.
Don't drink too much.
Ay.
I didn't drive here.
I'm happy today.
I didn't drive here, either.
I'm dizzy.
Why is it always you?
I didn't drive, either.
What's wrong?
Excuse me,
I'm busy today.
I'm leaving, guys.
Hey.
No way.
You just got here.
Ask her to stay.
Yeah.
I have other plans later today.
I just came by.
I haven't seen you all for a while.
So I came here to see everyone.
That's it.
I...
See you next time.
I am leaving.
Stay a little longer.
Aren't you and Tan Xu good friends?
I've been waiting for you
to tell me about his dark history.
Yes.
Leave after telling us all about it.
Ay.
Dark history of Tan Xu.
Well...
Don't you know all about it?
You know the most.
Tell us.
I'm really running out of time.
I have to leave.
See you next time.
I'll tell you about it another time.
Bye.
Don't.
Well.
Song.
Then you take care.
Have a drink before you go.
Go to Binhai Road.
Okay.
Hey.
Drink less.
Don't drink too much.
I didn't drive here. It's okay.
Not Binhai Road.
Jianshe Road first, please.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
Hey, girl.
What a grudge you've got here.
I've been a maid for him for years.
Is it enough?
Oh.
What happened?
A man dumped you
and didn't want to marry you?
I wonder if the world has changed.
Two people
did so many things together.
In the end,
he told me we are nothing
more than friends.
We didn't even hold hands.
Oops.
Did he just waste your time?
You should do it.
A girl's youth is the last thing
one can waste.
Hey.
What's wrong?
In an early morning,
you woke me up for a running.
Why does a person
who doesn't exercise run this morning?
Don't you know running
is good for our health?
Are you in poor health?
Let me check.
Oh, my God.
You've been putting on a long face
since last night.
If you don't speak,
no one will treat you as a mute.
Can you just shut up?
So annoying.
Will you run or not?
Hello?
(You scratched my car. Why?)
What's wrong?
Are you feeling well?
Do you have any proof?
What makes you think
she scratched your car?
Is it because she likes you?
You brought her here to pay for it.
Look at me.
Tell me. Do you think
she can be easily bullied?
Watch it yourself.
Sometimes, she's just...
She's
kind of hard to figure out.
But this one is pretty high definition.
It must be her.
I'm sorry.
She's just a psycho.
You know that?
It's really beyond my endurance.
She sends me messages every day,
and calls me at all hours.
She cannot get me and gets me trouble.
And now she has done such a thing.
I wanted to be good friends with her.
After all, we've known
each other for so long.
But this is too...
She's such a psycho.
Tan Xu,
you bad man!
You bad man,
give me back everything
I gave you.
Shame on you!
You bad man!
Stop.
Hey.
Bro.
Come back.
The money was transferred to you.
Thank you for keeping it private.
I'm so sorry.
Song is just like this.
She doesn't know how to control herself.
If you still don't feel well
in the next few days,
just come to my hospital.
I'll check for you for free.
It's alright.
Keep an eye on her.
I don't want her in my face ever again.
Okay.
You stupid, crazy, little psycho.
Why do you like a guy like this?
Ah?
It's over now.
Why are you still crying?
Let's go home.
I don't want to go home.
So where do you want to go?
I'll be with you.
Don't cry.
You're so ugly.
Alright.
Let's go.
Put on your shoes.
Hey.
What are you doing? Look at you.
Bad man.
All men are bad.
Let's go. I'm begging you.
You bad man!
What's wrong?
I'm sorry, uncle.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
She's drunk.
Let's go.
Stop it.
He doesn't look good at all.
Stop drinking.
You're going to have a beard
and become a man.
Let me ask you.
Am I not attractive enough?
Do I look unattractive to you?
I don't have any charm at all?
Why are you taking off clothes
in broad daylight?
Please just stop it and let's go.
Your parents would cut me down
if they find out.
I don't want to go.
Let's go.
Don't touch me.
Hey.
She said don't touch her.
Ah?
Why did you push me?
Why did I push you?
I pushed you for a reason.
Go.
Young girl,
where do you live?
I will send you home.
Mr. Zhang,
don't mess with me here.
What's wrong?
A misunderstanding.
Okay.
We are fine now.
You guys keep drinking.
Stop drinking.
Stop drinking. Let's go.
The two of them are friends,
not like what you think.
We can continue.
What?
Continue?
You want to continue?
You still want to drink more?
I have several surgeries
lining up this afternoon.
I need to do the eyelids surgery,
hyaluronic acid
and botox treatment for a living.
You know that?
Stop messing around.
Hey.
All you can think about right now
is to take her to the hotel, right?
Hotel?
Yes.
What do you mean?
Who is she?
My sister.
How many sisters do you have?
Two.
Why do you have so many sisters?
You cannot stop, right?
Stop that.
Well,
let me tell you.
I've known them for years.
It's not like what you think.
So what is their relationship?
Psycho.
Hey.
Who are you calling psycho?
Alright.
Look at you!
So drunk.
I'm really impressed.
Drinking so much.
What is this?
I shouldn't worry so much about you.
Oh, this smell of wine...
Ay.
I'm really impressed.
I respect you.
Drinking that much
with so little capacity for liquor.
Don't drink so much next time.
I'm begging you.
Do I owe you?
I don't know...
Donghao.
Today you are
super handsome.
You're very handsome.
Song.
I'll get you a glass of
honey water.
(She's still not in the office today.)
This batch of wood is quite good.
Miss Xia said
she won't be here in the next few days.
I know.
I didn't ask you about it.
Hey.
The newly arrived wood
is really of good quality.
Miss Xia is right about it.
Then maybe she should check it out.
Call her
and tell her to come to the office.
Okay.
Oh, wait.
You know what? I'll go find her
and talk with her about the furniture.
Hey!
You forgot?
You have a meeting this afternoon.
Just change it to an online meeting.
Does the time stay the same?
You are so annoying today.
Why do you talk so much?
(Oh no.)
(I must be crazy.)
(I am sick.)
(I haven't seen her for a few days.)
(But I can't stop thinking about her.)
(After talking to her about her dad
the other day,)
(she seems to have been avoiding me.)
(Fortunately,)
(at least I have a chance)
(to see her for work.)
(Open)
Hey.
(Closed)
I'm not here for nothing.
I'm here to talk about work.
These are some raw materials
from the manufacturers today.
Help me check which ones are suitable.
Leave them there.
I'll check tonight.
Tonight?
I said I'll check tonight.
I have my own orders to work for.
Why would I fit in with your schedule?
The guesthouse project
isn't finished yet.
You...
You started to take jobs from others?
First come, first served.
You should check mine first.
Hurry up.
Yes, Mr. Xu.
(She looks pretty when she works hard.)
What are you looking at?
(She looks pretty
even when she's angry.)
All suitable samples are here,
with labels.
Please leave now.
Oh.
Alright.
I have an appointment tonight,
by the way.
Aren't you curious?
I don't care.
It's related to you.
With Guan Xin.
What do you want with my boyfriend?
Are you worried?
Come with me if you're worried.
Fine.
In that case,
I'll go on my own.
But let me clear this first.
If something gets out of hand tonight,
that's not my responsibility.
It's yours.
I'm leaving.
Bye.
Thank you for today, Dr. Guan.
I was going to
bring that little girl here,
but she suddenly got a fever.
I'll bring her here next time.
Um.
Okay.
I'll go check on my surgery schedule.
Feel free to contact me.
Okay.
Ah?
It's out of power.
Let me send you back.
I live nearby,
and it's quick to drive home.
Well.
I'll give you a ride on my way home.
I won't see her in private anymore.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
What is it?
Oh.
No.
♪Right♪
♪Right in this season♪
♪Say the promises♪
♪Just say more♪
♪Let the whole world hear it♪
♪Right♪
♪Right at this time♪
♪Keep what you say♪
♪Just keep the time♪
♪The still time♪
♪Cannot say it is love♪
♪Just want to care for you♪
♪To have relentless talk with you♪
♪The street covered by leaves♪
♪I want to find an excuse♪
♪To walk through it again♪
♪The light within my heart♪
♪Has been out for years♪
♪Until you are here again♪
♪Leafing through the old photos♪
♪You and I♪
♪Have made♪
♪Lifelong promises♪
♪When the wind is blowing again♪
♪When I cannot dream of you at will♪
♪When we meet again after everything♪
♪Can I still become♪
♪The right one♪
♪For you♪
♪Again and again♪
♪I walk on this street♪
♪I'll never make you lonely♪
♪I want to say I love you♪
♪But these few words♪
♪Always come too late♪
♪And turn into regret♪