♪Go to a warm place♪
♪Hold you tight♪
♪Care about you♪
♪Chase the light bravely♪
♪Don't panic♪
♪With me, you won't be sad♪
♪When you feel lost♪
♪I've been secretly accompanying♪
♪You♪
♪Not far away♪
♪Please smile♪
♪Warmth in the heart♪
♪With you by my side♪
♪The sun shines everyday♪
=Discovery of Romance=
(As long as you don't break up with me,
I can still love you)
=Episode 23=
Wow!
Oh, my god.
Our life quality has improved a lot.
Smells great.
Guan Xin is really a nice person.
Hey.
I kind of regret
saying bad things about him
the first time I met him.
It's nice to be roommates with Guan Xin.
That way I can
have great breakfast every day.
Look at this.
Eastern plus western style.
How wonderful.
It's useless to say so now.
He's getting married soon.
If you can make do with it,
just go live in their living room.
Living in the living room
is better than sharing a house with you.
I'm tired of eating takeout every day.
What's wrong with takeout?
This is to promote
economic and social development.
You have to think when ordering takeout.
You have to order
the delicious and cheap food.
You're not aware
that you are living a happy life.
Then I'll go to their house
to have dinner.
You order your own takeout every day.
Then I'll learn to cook.
Li Donghao.
I need you to come out.
What is it?
Why did you ask me out here?
It's quite cold.
I saw it.
What did you see?
I saw there's a wooden box
in Xia Tian's room.
It contains photos of her and Xu Zehao
and love letters from Xia Tian.
They must have been together for years.
They went to the cinema together.
They went to the aquarium.
And,
I saw a picture of the four of you.
Sorry.
I didn't mean to.
It's not what it looks like.
You kept it from me for so long,
and you said you didn't mean to.
Li Donghao.
Do you take me for a fool?
Xia Tian thinks me as a fool,
and you too?
No.
You misunderstood.
I told Xia Tian not to say it.
I had no idea they'd be
working together for so long.
I wanted to keep you
from thinking too much.
It was a white lie.
Why did you let her take that job?
You've been around me for so long,
seeing me being uneasy
and suspicious,
and you were still trying
to convince me to be generous.
You must be glad.
You're glad it wasn't you.
Right?
You know that's not who I am.
I really don't know who you are.
Do you ever think of me as a friend?
I am your friend,
so I know you love her.
If I told you the truth,
can you let it go?
You could just tell me about it,
come clean with me,
and then let her take the job.
It would be totally different from
me finding it out myself.
Don't you understand that?
Now you were all cheating me.
Every one of you
is cheating me.
It's been a long time
since they broke up.
They knew the boundaries.
How am I supposed to tell you?
I'm undercover every day.
Am I not tired?
You didn't tell me
because you are tired?
Xia Tian didn't tell me,
but at least you should.
Could you understand if I told you?
It really isn't what it looks like.
Ever since Xia Tian met you,
you're the only person she cares about.
Yeah.
They were in love.
You know the whole truth now.
Can you break up?
You can do it if you can.
I don't understand
how they could work together
after they broke up.
How could she be friends
with someone she loved so much?
Xia Tian knows what she wants.
If she still loves Xu Zehao,
she won't take your ring.
And now you're at this point.
You need to let it go
and get ready to get married.
I've tried to be generous.
But I can't do that now.
Where are the other two?
They went out.
Ay.
Did you two solve the thing?
He allowed me to take it.
That's really awesome.
Now it's perfect.
But why did he overreact like this?
He saw Yu Hui coming yesterday.
Why did Yu Hui come?
To give me
the information about the bid.
How did he know we are going to bid?
Xu Zehao again?
Ay.
You two have a terrible connection.
Then what I did last night...
Sorry.
I can't help you this time.
You're on your own now.
Do you think
I still love Xu Zehao?
You'd better not.
Then why do you think
I'm still with Guan Xin?
Because of the virtues
or my kindness?
I'm not as sacred as you think.
The only reason
that I choose Guan Xin now
is that I love him.
So if you change your mind,
would you still choose Xu Zehao?
Why not?
I would go for him immediately.
Or who am I going to lie to?
Guan Xin or me?
I can't be a puppet
around Guan Xin, right?
Woman,
you're playing with fire.
If we have a bullet screen in real life,
now the screen would
be full of insults to you.
They are back.
What did you two talk about?
Um?
Nothing.
About work.
I poured you a bowl of congee.
Have some.
Which of these would you like to eat?
This one, okay?
How about a dumpling?
Let's go.
I'll wait for you at the door.
I'll be right there.
Guan Xin.
We're not going to the wedding house.
We're going to the aquarium.
Something serious happened.
What is it?
Didn't you notice something
was wrong with Guan Xin just now?
Um.
A little.
What did you two talk about out there?
Guan Xin found out
Xu Zehao is Xia Tian's ex.
Oh no!
Oh, my God.
This time, it's over.
How did he know?
You told him that?
I didn't.
He found it out on his own.
Then how did he know?
What about the wedding?
The wedding cannot be canceled, right?
What about Xia Tian?
He just took Xia Tian out.
I'm at my wit's end.
Leave it to fate.
No way.
I have to calm down.
There shouldn't be a problem.
Guan Xin is so nice.
And he doesn't seem
so mean
or petty.
Right?
And most importantly,
he loves Xia Tian,
and Xia Tian loves him.
So,
don't think too much.
No problem.
There will be absolutely no problem.
So,
you can't be unfaithful in love
or be ambiguous
between different people.
In the end, it will go against you.
But Xia Tian is not
being unfaithful in love.
She's just
working on a project with her ex.
It's my fault.
I only see the money.
I'm not talking about Xia Tian.
I'm talking about you.
What's with me?
A like is a like.
A dislike is a dislike.
Do not hesitate
and make it a mess.
You date A, B and C at the same time.
Hello!
Tan Xu.
Why did you bring me here?
I need to go to the bathroom.
Follow me.
You knew it?
Why did you keep putting up with it?
You used to act coquettishly
in such cases.
So you didn't say anything the whole way
just to punish me, right?
Even if I don't know what I did wrong,
I'd rather let you punish then.
What's going on?
I saw the wooden box
in your room.
I wanted to put up with it
till the day I die.
But I found I couldn't do it.
Since you've broken up,
why didn't you just throw them away?
Why are you still keeping those photos?
Sorry.
Have you ever done anything wrong to me?
Sorry, Guan Xin.
Sorry.
What are you sorry for?
Sorry, Guan Xin.
For what?
Sorry.
Sorry again.
Do you know that every time
you say sorry to me,
I feel really upset?
Ever since you met that man,
you just kept apologizing to me.
I really don't want to see
you look guilty.
But what can I do?
I never opened that box.
I don't even know what you saw.
I was going to throw it away.
But I just missed
the perfect time to do so.
Well...
There's something, you know...
If you miss it,
you just miss it.
Sorry, Guan Xin.
Would you stop saying you're sorry
and stop doing things
that you need to apologize for?
If you still can't accept it,
we can take a break from each other.
Why can you say that so easily?
We're already going to get married.
Does your foot still hurt?
I'll send you back home.
(I sincerely accept Guan Xin's proposal)
(and want to marry him.)
(In fact, I am ready)
(to be with Guan Xin forever.)
(But there are always
unexpected things happening.)
(It's like some excuse, no matter what.)
(All I did are wrong.)
(Why did I forgive her?)
(Because I don't want to let her go.)
(And I can't.)
(This is a war between men.)
(Everyone around us is a referee.)
(No one's going to bet on me.)
(But the more it does,
the more I have to win.)
(Xia Tian has said yes to my proposal.)
(I will not lose.)
(Song took my flowers.)
(I think she likes me.)
(Song took my pine tree.)
(Three men who like Song)
(get together now.)
(Is it an emperor choosing a concubine?)
Hello.
Why are you here?
(Because I like you.)
I'm your brother, so I have to be here.
As your family,
I have to give you advice.
Just ignore him.
Think of him as air.
I'm calling you here today
to share my thoughts with you.
I want to avoid causing
some unnecessary suspicion
or misunderstanding.
I think this is good for you,
for you,
and
for
us.
I've been getting messages
from you guys for a while.
To be honest,
this is the first time
that I have experienced
such a thing since I grew up.
I really don't know how to reply.
So I might as well
make things clear today.
Tan Xu.
I like you.
Since we started being friends,
I've really changed a lot for you.
I want to be better
because of you.
Thank you.
But,
I always felt
we are not destined.
When I liked you,
you did not like me.
When you like me now,
I get a new way
of thinking about relationship.
Sorry,
Tan Xu.
I already have a crush on someone else.
Yu Hui.
Mr. Yu.
You really are
a very, very nice guy.
You are very gentle,
considerate and kind.
And
you're rich.
We've known each other for so long.
And we do come to a stage
where we can make further contact.
Right.
But I never
had that feeling in my heart,
which can make me
take another step forward.
Do you get me?
Take another step forward?
I'm sorry.
I may have been a little direct.
But I still want
that impulse of love,
a feeling that can
make my heart beat fast.
I'm sorry.
I'm done.
Song.
I think there's been
some misunderstanding between us.
After all, we've known
each other for 10 years.
We like each other, don't we?
I admit
that I've done a lot of things
that made you feel bad about.
So please give me a chance
to make it up to you.
Can we start over as friends?
Song.
All you've ever seen
about me is at work.
If you'd like to spend
a little more time
to get to know me more,
and see me in private more,
maybe you'll get
that impulse of love.
Give me a chance, okay?
You guys are crazy.
She said she doesn't like you.
Didn't your teacher ever teach you
not to touch a girl's hand?
Then what are you doing?
I don't listen to teachers.
Why are you here?
Don't eat the cookies.
Do you have any idea
how many projects you missed
while you were away?
Tell me you're not here to blame me.
You think too much.
I'm here to tell you
that Sheng Group decided
to continue the cooperation with us.
I know.
But,
I'm not interested in
making guesthouses anymore.
Because we can't do anything better.
Guixin Guesthouse Project was a success.
It earns reputation in the industry
and is of good business value.
I had dinner with Mr. Sheng yesterday,
and he wanted to talk to you.
Next Wednesday,
there will be a business summit.
Big bosses will all go there.
You can attend it
on behalf of the company.
Next Friday,
there will be a live sharing
of guesthouse designs.
I want you to get ready.
Okay?
But I don't have time.
And since when is our industry
involved with Internet traffic?
We should also adapt to
the development of the times.
It's just some packaging publicity.
Some promotion for a project,
it's so normal.
Isn't it the same for you to attend?
You can attend for me.
I've been working on
a different project.
I'm busy.
Xu Zehao.
You just made something.
Don't retreat now, okay?
Aren't you afraid of
being outpaced by others?
I still have the confidence.
If I would be outpaced by others
just because I took a few days off,
I guess
I deserve it.
Alright.
So you've been working on
Alex's project, right?
He told me
that you recommended someone to him.
Xia Tian, right?
Yeah.
Xia Tian.
Don't you recognize her ability too?
Yes.
I recognize her talent.
But I don't recognize you
to lose profits of the company
for personal reasons.
Block design,
what is there to design?
You can only get a trophy.
Moreover,
what does this trophy
have to do with you?
What's the business value of it?
What's the profit for the company?
And,
do you think the opportunity
to work with a big company
is that easy to get?
If I were Xia Tian,
I will blame you
for not doing so.
You don't know about Xia Tian.
You are not her.
A company has its logic.
A company needs to spend
the least amount of money and efforts
to earn the most money.
But Xia Tian is not a business person.
She still has a passion for design.
It's not about profit.
Besides,
what company profits can she affect?
I'll make it straight.
You can take all of Sheng's project.
You can use any staff you want.
I won't ask.
That's
why you came to me today, right?
But you're a businessman.
Is it worth all the sacrifices
you made,
but she doesn't even know anything?
If my relationship with Xia Tian
is a business,
just think of me
as a venture capitalist.
Maybe
I will lose everything
I have,
but I want to try it anyway.
It's all over now.
Hey, we got two days left
on the countdown.
December 18th,
I hope nothing will happen on that day.
(December 18th)
(is Xu Zehao's birthday.)
(During the years after the breakup,)
(I could not help)
(thinking about him
at this time of year.)
Stop working.
(I don't need anyone to remind me.)
(I just came up with it.)
So many?
Are you tired?
Um.
So many.
Hurry!
(I can't believe I like)
(such a rude girl.)
(It makes my heart skip a beat
to see her like this.)
(Well, I am done.)
(I'm getting worse now.)
(Song is so beautiful now.)
Song.
Um?
Can you do me a favor?
What is it?
Try calling me names.
Song.
These are all for you.
Eat slowly.
Take it easy.
Don't be angry, either.
Although you are still pretty
when you're angry.
(Hello, boss.)
(Most of the bidders
for the Old Block project)
(are listed companies.)
(The competition is very fierce.)
(That doesn't look good)
(for Xia Song Studio.)
Alright.
I see.
(Info of bidding companies)
(Info of Xia Song Studio)
(December 18th,
deadline for ADA bidding)
♪Cannot say it is love♪
♪Just want to care for you♪
♪To have relentless talk with you♪
♪The street covered by leaves♪
♪I want to find an excuse♪
♪To walk through it again♪
♪The light within my heart♪
♪Has been out for years♪
♪Until you are here again♪
♪Leafing through the old photos♪
♪You and I♪
♪Have made♪
♪Lifelong promises♪
♪You and I♪
♪Have made lifelong promises♪
♪Without me♪
♪The romance still cheery♪
♪I should let you go♪
♪No longer owing to each other♪
♪When the wind is blowing again♪
♪When I cannot dream of you at will♪
♪When we meet again after everything♪
♪Can I still become♪
♪The right one♪
♪For you♪
♪When the wind is blowing again♪
♪In my last dream, you didn't go♪
♪After the regrets, after the love♪
♪When I turn around♪
♪No excuses♪
♪After what was said♪
♪If I turn around first♪
♪At the crossroad♪
♪Maybe♪
♪I could be the one♪
♪For you♪
I'm just here today
to take a look at the site
and take some photos.
How's the bidding proposal going?
After all, Alex is pretty demanding.
The basic proposal has been finalized.
With the symbol of the old block,
I'll make it into
a vintage national style.
There will be three main blocks.
Block A will be for coffee,
bakery and restaurant.
Block B will be
for books and audio culture.
Block C will be for lifestyle trend.
So the overall style will be vintage...
Are you kidding me?
Eight out of ten companies
would think in the same way.
An old block with a vintage style.
Whoever with a brain
would think of that.
There are seven companies
bidding for the project.
On size and cost,
you can't beat Shida.
On the vintage style,
you can't beat T-Art.
On the literature and art,
you can't beat Hongcheng Culture either.
If you put this stuff up for bidding,
wouldn't that be suicidal?
This is not just a project.
Alex said,
if this project is done well,
he's probably going to take it
to compete for the ADA Award.
Don't forget your original intention.
I remember you told me that once.
You want to bring
the most primitive and simplest things
from nature to the city.
I know what you're capable of.
(A simple, pure)
(and slow paced way of life.)
Thank you.
(Xu Zehao WeChat Voice Message)
(The pictures I just sent)
(are the manuscripts of Colorful Life
Creative Market from my friend.)
(There are some design elements
that you can refer to.)
(Xu Zehao WeChat Voice Message)
(This website contains)
(a theme about urban forest tent life.)
(There are materials of creative market
booths for your reference.)
I think only the second one works
in those things you sent to me just now.
Xu Zehao.
You sent these...
Hello!
Xia Tian.
It's me.
Sorry.
I have been talking about work.
So,
I didn't get a good look
when picking up the phone.
(I'm sorry.)
What time is it?
It is 12 o'clock.
Are you busy?
Yes.
I have been working.
And I didn't get much sleep either.
That's why I'm so confused.
Oh.
Well...
Take a rest early,
and don't stay up late.
Okay.
I'll go to bed after finishing it.
(I want to say something sweet,)
(but I just can't do so.)
(If a relationship has several stages,)
(what stage are we in right now?)
(After we get married,)
(will this often happen?)
(If we stick on,)
(will it get better?)
I...
I love you.
I love you too.
Well...
Take a rest early.
Good night.
Um.
(We've been dating for a long time,)
(but that was the first time
I said I love you to Xia Tian)
(not from the bottom of my heart.)
(I feel so tired.)
(Is that what happens
to all lovers in the world?)
(Even if they don't have
the passion to say I love you,)
(they would still say it)
(to maintain the relationship?)
(But we have to live together
for the rest of life.)
(Is it going to be
a problem most of the time?)
(Would Xia Tian)
(feel the same way as I do?)
♪Right♪
♪Right in this season♪
♪Say the promises♪
♪Just say more♪
♪Let the whole world hear it♪
♪Right♪
♪Right at this time♪
♪Keep what you say♪
♪Just keep the time♪
♪The still time♪
♪Cannot say it is love♪
♪Just want to care for you♪
♪To have relentless talk with you♪
♪The street covered by leaves♪
♪I want to find an excuse♪
♪To walk through it again♪
♪The light within my heart♪
♪Has been out for years♪
♪Until you are here again♪
♪Leafing through the old photos♪
♪You and I♪
♪Have made♪
♪Lifelong promises♪
♪When the wind is blowing again♪
♪When I cannot dream of you at will♪
♪When we meet again after everything♪
♪Can I still become♪
♪The right one♪
♪For you♪
♪Again and again♪
♪I walk on this street♪
♪I'll never make you lonely♪
♪I want to say I love you♪
♪But these few words♪
♪Always come too late♪
♪And turn into regret♪