♪Go to a warm place♪
♪Hold you tight♪
♪Care about you♪
♪Chase the light bravely♪
♪Don't panic♪
♪With me, you won't be sad♪
♪When you feel lost♪
♪I've been secretly accompanying♪
♪You♪
♪Not far away♪
♪Please smile♪
♪Warmth in the heart♪
♪With you by my side♪
♪The sun shines everyday♪
=Discovery of Romance=
(Love is not about reasoning but fate)
=Episode 24=
(Waiting Room)
Guan Xin.
Why are you still sleeping?
It's so late now.
Today is the weekend.
Hang out with me.
Guan Xin.
Mom.
Why are you taking these pills again?
Why are you here?
You slept on the couch.
No matter how busy you are,
you should take care of your body.
You can easily catch cold
sleeping on the couch.
Will you stop taking this medicine?
Come on.
Get up.
Go clean up.
Let's go out after breakfast.
Let's buy some stuff for your new house.
Don't take this medicine anymore.
Um.
Hello, this is DeRUCCI.
We are professionals in
creating a healthy sleep system.
You can come in and try it out.
Okay.
This is
our new mattress this year.
You can take a look.
The biggest advantage
of this space resin ball mattress
is that it can dynamically adapt to
and actively fit into the body shape.
Generally speaking,
it can provide
the feeling of sleeping in a hug.
It is suitable for
all sleeping positions.
And it can improve sleep quality.
Auntie.
Are you using it for yourself?
No.
My son is getting married soon.
For their new house.
Oh, I see.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Auntie.
You have such a good taste.
To your choice of furniture,
your daughter-in-law must be...
(What is Xia Tian doing now?)
(Is she with him?)
(If I call her now...)
Guan Xin.
(whether she would...)
Um?
What are you thinking?
I told you to have a try.
You haven't been sleeping well
and under a lot of pressure lately.
You should get a better mattress.
Okay.
You can come and try it.
Just lie down.
My son is a doctor.
He is so busy every day,
and he can't sleep well.
I see.
Then this mattress is a perfect fit.
What do you think?
It feels okay.
Did you
buy a mattress from us before?
What's your feedback after using it?
You've been here before?
They might remember it wrong.
I guess so.
Alright.
I'll take this mattress.
Okay.
Please follow me.
Put your legs up here.
Wow.
What do you think?
Um.
Look here.
Do you need any adjustment
anywhere?
I think this is nice enough.
(The number you have dialed
does not exist.)
(Please check...)
(The number you have dialed
does not exist.)
(Please check and dial again.)
(The number you have dialed
does not exist.)
(Please check and dial again.)
(Lu Xi has moved out.)
(I don't know exactly where she went.)
(I always thought)
(there's still time
to make it up to her.)
(But I didn't expect)
(I would've lost her again)
(without noticing.)
(Yinshe Yard)
Right?
It's late now.
Can you go back for sleep now?
Of course, I need sleep.
Go back...
Don't you think it's a long way
for me to go back?
But you can't always sleep here.
I don't have to sleep here.
What are you going to do?
Do you think you and I
have a pretty good relationship?
It will be if I go upstairs.
Come back.
What are you doing?
That's my bottom line.
Isn't bottom line made to be crossed?
Take this and sleep well.
Don't dream it anymore.
I'm a very picky person.
I'm not.
I will think of it as you.
It helps me sleep like my loved one.
Hey.
Can I go upstairs and take a shower?
No way.
(Xia Song Studio)
Case introduction.
Song.
Um?
Did you get the pictures
of the guesthouse project?
No.
Didn't Yu Hui send them to you?
Not in your email box?
I thought he sent them to you.
I'll call him now.
Where's my phone?
Hey.
Mr. Yu.
Well...
The guesthouse...
Do you still have those pictures
of the guesthouse project
when it was completed?
(The pictures of the guesthouse?)
(Oh.)
(I think they're in the company camera.)
(Do you need them?)
I need them urgently.
Is the company still open now?
We'll go get it.
(Yes.)
(But it's not safe for you
to pick them up at this hour.)
(Or...)
That's good.
Thank you.
The company is still open now.
Maybe we should go there and get them.
Can you go there?
I haven't finished this report yet.
Okay.
Let's split up.
Be careful.
(Unbounded Space Design Firm)
Why are you here?
Today,
don't you have any plans?
What are you talking about?
You came to me for...?
I came here to get pictures
of the guesthouse project.
We need materials for the bidding.
I'll go export them for you.
(Sheng Wang Flea Market)
Why do you help me?
Nothing.
Just a while ago,
I happened to meet Alex.
Didn't you say that
you love his works?
And I think
this is a good chance.
Because of your dad's accident,
your dream of being a big artist
were on hold.
I think
it's not too late to try hard now.
You're only 30.
Many great artists
did not devote themselves
to creation until 40.
And I didn't help much.
It's not all settled yet, is it?
Why are you being so nice to me?
♪Lifelong promises♪
Because when we were together,
I didn't treat you well,
or really understand you,
or love you enough.
I want to make up for those regrets.
♪When we meet again after everything♪
♪Can I still become♪
I think you should export the pictures.
♪For you♪
♪You and I♪
♪Have made lifelong promises♪
♪Without me♪
♪The romance still cheery♪
♪I should let you go♪
♪No longer owing to each other♪
♪When the wind is blowing again♪
♪In my last dream, you didn't go♪
♪After the regrets, after the love♪
♪When I turn around♪
♪No excuses♪
♪After what was said♪
♪If I turn around first♪
♪At the crossroad♪
♪Maybe♪
♪I could be the one♪
♪For you♪
Happy birthday.
I won't sing the birthday song.
But at least
I can do this for you.
♪Happy birthday to you♪
Happy birthday.
What's your gift for me?
That's it?
What's wrong?
I don't have money for gifts.
At least you got an internship.
This is...
Alright.
What's this?
A coupon for a no-show.
A coupon for a hug.
A coupon for a kiss.
A coupon for forgiving...
Well.
These are things I could do.
Since when they become gifts?
The last one is blank.
Don't say I didn't give you a chance.
Does that mean
I can fill out anything on this one?
Anything?
Thank you, honey.
I love you.
Really?
Yes.
Let me interview you again.
Really?
Yes.
I swear to god.
Let me touch it.
How's it?
Do you feel my sincerity?
So what did you wish for this year?
First,
I hope I can spend more time with you
for the rest of the year.
Second,
I hope I can fulfill my dream
of starting a studio
and earn more money.
Third,
I hope you
can be a famous designer.
The famous designer, Xia Tian,
would win the ADA Award.
I promise to fulfill the task.
You are very confident.
I just said it casually.
That's how confident I am.
I can't do anything else for you,
but this.
Let me interview you.
What did you wish for this year?
My wish is
to become Xia Tian,
you.
I want to know why you cried.
I want to know what you were thinking
on the day we left the noodle shop.
I want to know
why you took pictures of me
after the guesthouse was finished.
I want to know
why you waited for me every night.
I want to know all of these.
I know you wouldn't tell me.
So I want to become you.
But what then if you do?
What can you do?
If you were thinking the same as I,
I want to hold your hand right now,
leave everything behind,
and run as far as we can.
I admit I still love you.
I can't get over you.
So I want to be with you again
if I get a chance.
Xia Tian.
Come back to me.
I know you still love me.
You just have to take one small step,
just one small step.
I'll take care of the rest
of your worries.
I'm not going to take that small step.
I just came here to get the pictures
and say happy birthday to you.
Don't sway me anymore.
♪Never fade away♪
♪I love you all the way♪
♪From night to day♪
♪Hide the feel♪
♪That you wanna say in time♪
♪You will know♪
♪How deep you are in my heart♪
♪And I found you♪
♪And also I understand my own mind♪
♪Because the moment with you♪
♪Is so precious to me♪
Why are you crying?
Answer me.
♪I know I'll hold you♪
♪When you appear in my life again♪
♪Again♪
♪I know♪
We need to talk.
Let me get this straight.
I don't want to see you anymore.
And,
I won't allow Xia Tian
to work with you anymore.
Why are you making the decision?
You said you wouldn't
interfere with Xia Tian's work.
That's what I thought before.
But now I have changed my mind.
I'll convince her.
Don't you have
any confidence in Xia Tian?
Don't you know she's going to marry me?
So what?
You love Xia Tian.
But she loves herself.
She does love herself.
But she loves me too.
Otherwise, she wouldn't
have agreed to marry me.
Do you really think
she is going to marry you
because she loves you?
Xia Tian is not a person
who would be content
to be around other people.
She won't feel happy
clinging to someone.
Do you know her?
Do you know what she needs?
Do you know what her dream is?
Do you know what she gave up for you?
You don't even deserve to be with her.
And you do?
At least I know
what she needs most now.
At least I know what she wants most.
And you?
You...
You know nothing.
Crap.
If you get in the way again,
I'm going to kill you.
Would you please stop talking like that?
I won't get in the way
of you and Xia Tian.
And I can't.
But please don't
interfere with her work either.
What Xia Tian wants to do
is her own choice.
Neither of us is qualified
to decide anything for her.
Xia Tian does not need anyone
to give her self-righteous happiness.
She is a person who shines on her own.
You...
You won't last long with her.
Stop.
Take it easy.
You two are great.
Ah.
A boss
and a doctor.
Two decent men.
It's no problem
if you're jealous because of a girl.
But you started a fight?
You two are amazing!
I don't understand
what love
is.
Can it be eaten as a dish?
In a world where it's hard to get food
and sleep tight,
you two fought?
I think you guys are too idle.
Then
I am telling you.
You have to pay for all the things
you broke today.
Hey.
Ms.,
you are here.
Ay.
I'm sorry.
Look,
we are all regular customers.
We were friendly.
But,
today is really an exception.
I'm sorry.
Right.
I know you are regular customers.
That's not
what regular customers can do.
Look at them.
He is in anger.
And he is not convinced.
They haven't fought enough.
Continue.
Continue to break things.
Ah.
And then double my compensation
according to the bill.
Ay.
Okay.
You can rest assured.
I'll do it.
What are you doing?
We share.
Ah.
Let's go, boss.
You go back first.
Leave me alone.
Even big things will pass.
You're still so naive.
Ms.
Do you think
that no matter how much you love her,
as long as the time apart
is long enough,
she would eventually
become a passerby?
Of course.
The deepest love of all
will also pass in the end.
But I've known Xia Tian for 10 years.
We had been dating for five years,
and broke up five years ago.
So far,
I still can't
think of her as a passerby.
And I know...
I know she still loves me.
You know?
Then go get her back.
I've tried.
I've tried hard.
But...
But I can't make it.
Let me ask you.
Do you think
that you've tried your best
in your relationship?
If you have,
no matter what happens in the future,
you won't regret it.
Look at you now,
10 years older.
Ah.
What happened
to that swagger you had
10 years ago?
Won't you earn the money?
Won't you eat?
Won't you want to live?
That's right.
Good.
That's the good boy.
Listen to me.
Let's
have a good drink here today.
Then you go home,
take a shower
and have a good sleep.
Tomorrow
will be another brand new day.
Thank you.
Silly boy.
Why were you squatting
on the ground and crying just now?
What's in such a hurry?
You went over there
in the middle of the night.
Let's break up.
Guan Xin.
Xia Tian.
Don't do that.
We're going to get married.
So what do you want me to do?
Today
I am angry.
But it's OK.
If you explain it to me,
I'll be okay.
Don't tell me that you'll be OK anymore.
Guan Xin.
Don't force yourself to take it, either.
And you know it,
if we keep going like this,
we'll only break up in the end.
How do you know we won't get closer
and sweeter?
I just know it.
In the beginning,
we stick with each other.
Gradually,
we'll disgust each other.
And we'll end up hating each other.
This is what we've become.
Do you know that?
Guan Xin.
You have to accept
that we're at the end of the road.
Is this the end?
Is that all you can do?
Is that as far as you can go?
I can keep walking.
I won't mind how far I should go.
How far can we go?
Far, far away.
How much more do you
want me to hurt you?
Do you think that makes me feel good?
How much more do you want to hate me?
Well, Xia Tian.
Do you know so much about love?
Who did you learn about love from?
From Xu Zehao.
Is it the answer you want?
Let's end it up here.
Guan Xin.
Xia Tian.
How's it?
Two men were fighting for you.
Are you happy now?
You shut up!
Guan Xin is still outside.
Shut up.
I'll go find him.
How is she?
You're in a situation like this,
and you are still worrying about her?
I had a quarrel with her.
She said a lot of outrageous things.
So did I.
Then why did you fight with Xu Zehao?
Xia Tian
got out of Xu Zehao's company,
and cried.
It was the second time she cried
in front of Xu Zehao.
I asked her why.
She just wouldn't tell me.
What Xia Tian wants to do
is her own choice.
Neither of us is qualified
to decide anything for her.
Xia Tian does not need anyone
to give her self-righteous happiness.
She is a person who shines on her own.
You...
You won't last long with her.
Actually, I know
why she wouldn't tell me.
Because she knows
I can't accept the answer.
(What else am I supposed to tell him?)
(Do I have to say)
(I love someone else,)
(or I fall in love with Xu Zehao again?)
(It's too cruel.)
(I really can't say that.)
Hey.
Where's Guan Xin?
How's it?
I sent him away.
Where is Xia Tian?
I haven't got the nerve
to go in there yet.
Poor Guan Xin.
Throw it away for me.
You figured it out?
Then I'll just assume
you and Guan Xin are still together,
and you two just had a quarrel.
Let's sleep together.
I know you can't fall asleep.
What a coincidence,
I can't fall asleep, either.
Now that you've chosen Xu Zehao,
just go for it.
I'll be there with you
if you get scolded.
How about Guan Xin?
How is he?
Don't worry.
Guan Xin's already home.
Actually,
it's good to choose Guan Xin.
I don't want to think about it anymore.
I've got the answer long ago.
Donghao was right.
I knew it
when I saw the two of them at the pub.
It's over.
For both of them,
I'm really not a good person.
Now that you've made your decision,
just go for it.
Um?
But I think
Guan Xin is not ready for a breakup.
Just give him some time.
What about you?
Are you ready?
Don't people like me
deserve to suffer?
(For Xu Zehao and Guan Xin,)
(I am not a good person indeed.)
(But)
(love is something)
(that nobody else can tell)
(except the parties involved.)
♪Right♪
♪Right in this season♪
♪Say the promises♪
♪Just say more♪
♪Let the whole world hear it♪
♪Right♪
♪Right at this time♪
♪Keep what you say♪
♪Just keep the time♪
♪The still time♪
♪Cannot say it is love♪
♪Just want to care for you♪
♪To have relentless talk with you♪
♪The street covered by leaves♪
♪I want to find an excuse♪
♪To walk through it again♪
♪The light within my heart♪
♪Has been out for years♪
♪Until you are here again♪
♪Leafing through the old photos♪
♪You and I♪
♪Have made♪
♪Lifelong promises♪
♪When the wind is blowing again♪
♪When I cannot dream of you at will♪
♪When we meet again after everything♪
♪Can I still become♪
♪The right one♪
♪For you♪
♪Again and again♪
♪I walk on this street♪
♪I'll never make you lonely♪
♪I want to say I love you♪
♪But these few words♪
♪Always come too late♪
♪And turn into regret♪