♪I think feelings are indescribable♪
♪It rains and the clouds get frozen♪
♪I immerse myself
in the depths of your eyes♪
♪A rainbow will appear
around the next corner♪
[Hidden Love for You]
[Episode 19 You Won't Be Alone Anymore]
You two go on your date.
I'm heading back to Nanwu.
Why are you leaving so suddenly?
I've got nothing to do here.
And... stay safe.
I've planned
where to take you this weekend.
And now you're leaving.
Do I need
a kid like you to show me around?
You don't even have a job. Why go back?
I have things to do.
What do you mean by no work?
Can't you stay a few more days?
Why are you crying?
I can't just stay here
like a guard dog for Duan Jiaxu, right?
Did that guy treat you badly?
No.
Then... unhappy with the internship?
Mm.
Someone bullied me.
Then just quit.
You don't need that money.
So I got pushed around for nothing.
You even blocked me,
stole my red packet,
and came here to scold me.
I was just messing with you.
My round-trip flight cost more than 800.
I'll transfer it to you.
Also,
since when is lecturing you scolding?
As if I've ever
said anything nice to you before.
Anyway, take care of yourself.
We'll meet again.
No need to cry like this.
Aren't you embarrassed?
No.
Nineteen going on nine, huh?
I'm leaving now.
Text me when you get home.
Mm.
Take care of her for me.
Bye.
Okay, okay, okay...
Cheer up.
Why are you crying so bitterly?
I'm right here,
yet you cried this hard
over another guy.
Still crying nonstop at your age.
I don't want to talk about it.
And crying over an internship
is so embarrassing.
What's embarrassing about it?
You've cried in front of me plenty.
That was when I was little.
I don't cry much now.
And I'm not a crybaby.
You're totally a crybaby.
If you think
crying is just for kids,
then stay a kid forever,
okay?
I'm here for you.
Mm.
Missing home?
Okay, I'll take leave
and go back with you.
Mm.
And what's up with your company?
Making you cry like this.
Oh,
should I go have a word with your boss?
You sound like
when I got bullied at school
and you wanted to
confront the principal.
Sang Zhi.
I don't just want to be your boyfriend.
I want to be someone you can rely on.
What kind of garbage report is this?
[Transfer: ¥5,000. Living expenses]
Sang Yan,
at least you have some conscience.
The AC isn't broken, right?
Duan Jiaxu,
my AC is broken.
I made the bed for you
and replaced the bathroom stuff.
Let me know if you need anything else.
When did you prepare all this?
I'll go take a shower.
Mm.
Does Duan Jiaxu have other ideas?
- Zhizhi?
- Hmm?
Help me with something.
You want some too?
No.
My clothes are a bit tight.
Can you help me with this?
Can't you do it yourself?
Kid,
don't you know what foreplay is?
I'll turn on the AC.
♪As the sun set,
the wind blows across the sky♪
You'll catch a cold.
♪I can't tell how warm it is♪
♪No one but you can feel this moment♪
Happy now?
So half-hearted.
Don't worry.
I won't touch you.
But…
wanna inspect the goods first?
Uh?
Duan Jiaxu really is... No way.
Jiaxu, I'm going to my room.
Sleep early.
Oh.
What's with you?
So guarded against me?
Goodnight.
What just happened?
I actually got seduced by him.
And I couldn't hold back.
So embarrassing.
♪It rains and the clouds get frozen♪
♪I immerse myself
in the depths of your eyes♪
I need to go out for a bit.
Breakfast is in the kitchen.
Breakfast in the fridge.
Heat it up in the microwave.
Let me know when you wake up.
You're back.
Yeah.
Why are you only eating breakfast now?
It's already noon.
It's all because of you.
It's the weekend, so I slept in a bit.
Why'd you get up so early?
Oh,
my mom's death anniversary.
I visited her grave.
What's wrong?
Why didn't you let me join you?
That place is depressing.
And it's the weekend.
I wanted you to sleep in,
and not to feel down.
Didn't sleep well?
Duan Jiaxu.
Hmm?
I can share your sadness with you.
I'm done eating. I'll do the dishes.
♪I want to tell you it's sunny today♪
♪Not with any ulterior motives♪
♪Chaotic emotions overshadow the view♪
If you're unhappy,
you can cry too.
And I won't call you a crybaby.
I can treat you like a kid.
Okay.
Mm.
Then hug your kid a little longer.
Jiaxu,
from now on,
you won't be alone anymore.
I'll always be with you.
♪I can't see or force a smile♪
♪I'll just forget it♪
♪If I can't cover
the corners of my eyes♪
♪If we meet again, don't hug me♪
♪I don't want it this way♪
♪I can't see or force a smile♪
♪I'll just forget it♪
♪If I can't cover
the corners of my eyes♪
♪How will my tears roll down?♪
♪You actually know it's so hard for me♪