When will you catch that guy for me?
Why did my mom and dad die?
The man who was interviewing
our dad is Yuji Tsuda.
-Just let me hear your side.
-I'm busy.
-He won a newcomer award in university.
-I'll come by again tonight.
Right after the incident,
Tsuda disappeared.
He fled because he's the killer?
What are you going to do?
What will you do…
if you find Tsuda?
He was brought in this morning.
He didn't have an ID, but said his name.
Is it really Tsuda?
There's no way I would mistake him.
But…
Pancreatic cancer, stage four.
He went into septic shock…
and is now in a coma.
The cancer has metastasized
to the liver and lungs.
He has about six months to live.
About this patient--
He wasn't receiving treatment.
There are no signs he ever had
standard treatment, such as surgery.
He likely had reasons
he couldn't go to a hospital.
His injuries may be from--
I don't care.
Will he regain consciousness?
Currently, we are using vasopressors
to maintain his blood pressure,
but the situation is very grim.
Is it possible he might never wake up?
Don't screw with me.
Another case?
Hello?
There's a suspected arson-murder
in Kanagawa Ward.
Let's go.
Who cares about that?
-This isn't an investigation!
-So what?
They will notice detectives
hanging around.
We won't be able to get close to Tsuda!
In that case,
we'll do it before then.
Makoto…
We can't let a disease kill him!
The possibility isn't zero yet.
If the antibiotics and vasopressors work,
there's a chance
he'll regain consciousness.
Even if Tsuda isn't long for the world,
it's enough time to find out his motive.
It's ironic, but…
right now, we've no choice
but to believe in him.
Around 10:30 p.m.,
following a report from a passerby,
we discovered an apartment fire.
The other residents evacuated,
but the resident of the room
where the fire broke out, Aiko Mizusawa,
was taken to the hospital
and pronounced dead.
Firefighters said it started
at the entrance.
It seems a burning object was pushed in
through the mail slot.
Wait, Mr. Tagusari.
Hello.
Make no mistake, it was arson and murder.
And she was so young too.
Still, it's the second floor.
She could've escaped through the window.
From the condition of the bathroom,
it's likely she had just finished bathing.
Then, a flyer was set on fire
and thrown in.
It ignited a spray can
left at the entrance
and caused it to burst.
From there, the fire seems
to have spread rapidly.
-Let's film the onlookers.
-Onlookers?
Nosy folks.
Oh, right.
Right.
Quite a crowd has gathered.
Probably filming
for social media or something.
Ishizaka.
Face this way. You're looking too much.
-A bit to the right.
-Okay.
Yes, right there.
Mr. Tagusari, you take photos too.
Hey, are you listening?
Arsonists sometimes return
to the scene, you know.
They're probably gone by now.
Those kinds of people just
want to see things burning.
Wait, don't take photos so blatantly.
Something is stuck here.
Is it a fragment of something?
Ms. Kiritani, send this to forensics.
Yes, sir.
Please pay attention.
Okay.
The cause of death
was carbon monoxide poisoning?
She inhaled the smoke
that filled the room.
Why didn't she notice
a burning flyer being thrown
into the mail slot?
It seems she was using
a hair dryer after her shower.
I see.
Did you lose big at the races?
What?
Since yesterday, you've been
even more unmotivated than usual.
What's wrong?
Please go on ahead.
-Tell us.
-I have nothing to say.
I'll come by again tonight.
You two aren't alike at all, are you?
I can't believe
you're both in the police force.
Both?
Why didn't you become
a forensic scientist?
With that much knowledge,
it wouldn't be strange for you
to follow that path.
That was my intention, a long time ago.
Then why the police?
Oh!
Mr. Tagusari!
I brought the autopsy report.
-Oh, excuse me.
-Goodbye.
The body found in the apartment
was identified by her driver's license
as resident Aiko Mizusawa, 20 years old.
She worked part-time at a food factory.
However, we haven't looked into
her relationships yet.
Are her parents far away?
Her family home is in Akita,
but her father is serving time
for fraud and assault,
and her mother is deceased.
After her father's arrest,
she was taken into a foster home,
so it seems she's estranged
from relatives.
Any witnesses?
None have come up so far.
No security cameras were installed
in the apartment.
Please report the autopsy results.
The cause of death
is carbon monoxide poisoning.
No sleeping pills were detected,
and no signs of a struggle were found.
Is there anything else?
Nothing.
Her father is in prison, huh?
Her life must have been tough.
Don't go off on your own again.
I'll be careful.
If Tsuda's condition changes,
the hospital will contact us immediately.
Until then, don't act on your own.
I know.
Ms. Mizusawa started working here
about a year ago, I think.
Did you hear anything
about her having any troubles?
No, nothing.
Any employees she's close with?
None.
That girl was unsociable
and only spoke about work.
Oh, I have to go.
She sounds like you, Mr. Tagusari.
Aiko Mizusawa also lacked social skills,
so finding any relationships
might be difficult.
Don't liken me to her.
So you do have friends?
Minoru.
He's your brother!
Yes.
Yes, this is Kudo.
From Aiko Mizusawa's smartphone, we found
the person she contacted before she died.
A woman named Saki Yokokura.
We're helping First Division
look for witnesses. Look into this.
I'm Kudo from the Aoi Station.
What do the police need from me?
You know Aiko Mizusawa, don't you?
Yes.
Excuse me, but what was your relationship
with her?
We're friends.
Did something happen to Aiko?
She died in a fire.
What?
Before she died,
it seems she contacted you.
What were you doing yesterday
around 10:30 p.m.?
I was working overtime.
Please wait a moment.
Excuse me.
You can check with my company.
Thank you.
And one more thing.
The last message Ms. Mizusawa sent you
mentioned wanting to talk
about this "Togo" person.
What does this mean?
Do you know something?
I don't know the details,
but Aiko said
she was being stalked by this man.
Hey, Mr. Tagusari!
Thank goodness, I made it in time.
Forensics sent us the results for the
substance found under her nails.
Thank you.
-See you later.
-See you.
AUTOPSY REPORT
Did the hospital call?
No.
Still investigating?
It wrapped up just now.
I'm going for a drink.
I can't sleep if I go home anyway.
In that case, come with me for a bit.
We're heading to the crime scene?
Forensics sent back Aiko Mizusawa--
Listen!
What was found under her fingernails
was rush grass.
Rush grass?
If it's in the room,
it must be the tatami mats.
Must have clawed them
when she couldn't breathe.
Why not open the window?
It's not that Aiko Mizusawa
couldn't escape.
Is there a reason she didn't run?
-Hello.
She passed away here, so…
The rush grass must be
from these tatami mats.
What's wrong?
Someone moved the bed recently.
Wait, hold that side.
Sure.
It's heavy!
Were tatami mats always this heavy?
I don't often carry tatami mats around…
Don't you remember?
Remember what?
Back in the day, you made a fuss,
saying you saw a tiny samurai at home.
We lifted up the tatami
because you said he escaped into the gap.
A tiny samurai?
Never mind.
Oh, it's budging!
Lift it!
And push!
Whew.
Gold bars were found
under this tatami mat,
and are being inspected.
If you go to the scene,
at least let me know.
I didn't intend to investigate.
I was the one who asked.
I wanted to see the scene once more.
I'm sorry.
Report the situation.
If the gold bars are real,
they're worth about 100 million yen.
One hundred million?
Aiko Mizusawa gave up
on putting out the fire,
and tried to move the bed to take
the gold from under it.
But before she could,
she died from carbon monoxide poisoning.
But Aiko Mizusawa was only 20 years old.
So many gold bars…
Maybe her father got them through fraud.
Cross-check the gold bars
with theft reports.
Yes, sir!
She was being stalked by a man
named Togo, wasn't she?
Maybe he was after those gold bars.
Mr. Hyuga.
Any info about Togo?
We didn't get any information at all.
His relationship with her is also unknown.
Who on earth is this Togo?
We might find their connection
through the gold bars.
Until the results come back, let's check
Mizusawa's relationships again.
Haruko.
Have a moment?
I'm busy right now.
Come on. Just this once.
-I've heard that about 100 times already.
-Then this is the 101st.
Oh, how rare.
You're with a girl today?
What?
Kudo, why are you here?
If you keep acting on your own,
it will affect my evaluation too.
Only terrible men
mistreat ladies, you know.
Do whatever you want.
Find a man named Togo,
who was stalking this woman.
Togo?
Which is it, really?
Not sure if you're motivated or not…
I'm just a little curious.
-Who is this woman?
-Her name is Aiko Mizusawa.
-She had 100 million in gold at her home.
-Hey!
Don't leak that info to a civilian!
I'll give you cash,
so go out and buy some Big Katsu.
What?
What you're doing will get us in trouble.
Only if you tell someone.
It's just getting good.
Can you hurry and let me continue reading?
Who is that person?
What is your relationship with Ms. Haruko?
Just an acquaintance.
Your range of "acquaintance"
is quite broad, huh.
I'm kind of hungry.
Want some ramen before going home?
Just us?
Sure. I don't see anyone else here.
Since you came to our station,
we've never gone for lunch.
So let's hang out.
You really need to think that hard?
Well…
-Let's go!
-Next time.
I'll order a big one. That will show him…
PREMIUM MILK
Welcome.
You're playing that again.
Starving, aren't you?
Shut up.
Just got off work?
There was an autopsy at Yomogida Station.
Get me the same one.
All right.
What happened to the gold bars?
We should know the origin soon.
Why would she have gold bars…
Who knows?
But it has nothing to do with her father.
Why?
Her father went to prison 13 years ago.
At that time,
Aiko Mizusawa was only seven.
Oh, right.
You wouldn't entrust 100 million
in gold bars to a child.
Right.
You guys talking about treasure?
Come on, tell me. Where is it?
The scene of a fire.
It was at an apartment in Kanagawa Ward.
I hate fires.
1995, APRIL 26
Oh, today is the day
you cook for the whole week, right?
Oh, yes.
How is Ms. Fumi's leg?
Not very good, it seems.
They say it will probably require surgery.
Accidents in the mountains
are scary, aren't they?
Anyway, I'll go prepare this week's meals.
Okay.
KOJIMA GOLD FACTORY
Let me know if you need anything.
I'm sorry, Mogi.
I can't do anything by myself.
It's okay.
I'll borrow your kitchen.
Sure.
Paramedics!
Over here!
-Male victim, possible airway injury!
-Paramedics!
Darling!
In the factory…
There is another…
-Possible victim in the factory!
-The factory!
-Prepare to reenter!
-Roger!
Roger!
Anyone in there?
Can you hear me?
-Anyone in there?
Anyone there?
Found the victim!
-Are you okay?
-Can you hear me?
Let's move him!
Okay. One, two, three!
Just forget about it already.
Things will soon be over.
Over?
They found Tsuda.
What?
You can't bribe me
with dumplings, you know.
I see.
Mogi's are excellent, though.
Minoru?
Is this really a pawnshop?
Want to try pawning something?
What?
I will buy anything you've got.
No, thanks.
What brings you here today?
I figured Makoto probably didn't tell you.
What?
I ought to tell you, Haruko.
Tell me?
Tsuda is currently
hospitalized at Shosen Medical University.
I don't know why
he came back here, though.
Haruko, you…
You really took care of us.
You spoke to us back then.
What's wrong?
Where are my mom and dad?
Where are they?
Now, it is time for the final farewell.
Minoru…
Both of us…
were able to see our parents
one last time.
Since then,
you've always stayed by our side.
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday dear
Minoru!
You even helped us look for Tsuda.
We…
took up so much of your time, Haruko.
Minoru…
I'm sorry.
Why are you saying that now?
That guy left me scarred too.
Well, I'm going back to work.
Eat the gyoza while they're hot, okay?
Is this your final job?
Is there no other way?
You should visit Mogi sometimes.
I'm sure he'll be lonely.
A year ago,
there was a robbery of 400 million yen
in gold bars in Akita Prefecture.
The gold bars stolen then
match the ones found
in Aiko Mizusawa's home.
What do we know about this robbery?
One of the four robbers
had a tattoo on the side
of his neck. Just that.
However…
It's highly possible that Mizusawa
was also a member.
We assumed that this crime
was committed by people
lured by a shady part-time-job posting
on social media.
It's believed a criminal group,
including a handler,
exists behind the scenes.
Mizusawa likely participated
in the robbery itself,
then ran off with the gold.
So Togo, the man stalking her,
was one of the other three robbers,
or perhaps the handler?
Did he set the fire in retaliation
because he couldn't find the gold?
We will cooperate with Akita police
and pursue Togo as a person of interest.
-Yes.
-Yes!
HARUKO ASHIKAGA: CAN WE MEET UP?
Tagusari! Come here for a second.
Maybe because of
your solo investigation again.
Honestly, what a pain.
The "again" part makes it hard to defend.
Just go and get chewed out.
Kudo.
Yes?
Where is Makoto?
He is currently being detained
and lectured.
Oh, I see.
Right…
Here.
-List of people named Togo.
-Thank you.
There were several with that name
in the prefecture,
but they were all either in prison
or overseas.
All dead ends.
You've already investigated that much?
Those gold bars
were from the Akita robbery, right?
How do you know that?
I have friends who work as reporters.
One of the robbers had a tattoo,
and Aiko Mizusawa was also a member.
Oh, it's here! Got one!
Amazing!
Come on.
My dad was a fisherman,
I used to help him often.
Okay.
Want to try?
Oh… I'm a professional at the eating part.
Oh, you must've been raised well.
MOM
To be honest,
my parents never took me to the sea.
Is that so?
Well…
What's your relationship with
Mr. Tagusari?
We used to live in the same neighborhood.
You could say we go way back.
So that's why
you're helping him investigate?
What?
Nothing.
We don't even know his face.
No way to look for him.
Besides, Togo is probably from Akita.
Oh, thanks.
Want one, Mr. Tagusari?
This…
This isn't a tattoo, it's a birthmark.
A birthmark?
Makes sense.
The position is the same.
So one of the robbers
was at the scene of the arson?
That man is the arsonist…
It might be Togo.
This case is going to be a relay.
First, we need all CCTV and dashcam data
from near the apartment.
All right, let's go.
-Yes!
-Okay.
-My ramen…
-Let's go.
-You can eat it later!
-But…
Please watch my ramen for me.
Sorry to bother you.
I'm from the Aoi Station.
I would like to ask a few questions.
Hello?
Makoto, can we talk now?
Sure.
The hospital called.
And Tsuda?
He just woke up.
They said we'll be able to visit
once he's stable.
Okay.
Once he can talk, let's go and see him.
Sorry, I have an autopsy now.
Mr. Tagusari. Let's go get CCTV footage
on the east side too.
Right.
Mr. Koike, let's go.
Okay.
Here's more.
You can't even see
a neck birthmark in this.
My back is going to explode.
Relay investigations
are a race against time.
If the footage is overwritten, it's over.
I know that, but still. There's so much…
The investigation division
will help starting tomorrow.
They are experts in analysis, after all.
Give it here. Come on.
What?
What's wrong, Mr. Tagusari?
Usually, he'll complain
about how much of a pain it is.
I just want to finish this and go home.
The initial examination is finished.
We found no traces of foul play.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Hello.
Yes?
Did you have an autopsy here?
I finished just now.
-Stocking up on food?
-Yes. Looks like we're not finishing soon.
Is Makoto doing his job properly?
He's not slacking off, is he?
I wonder if something good
happened to him.
He's working hard,
saying he wants to finish quickly.
Is that so?
I'm going back to the prefectural HQ.
Must be tough working late.
Same for you.
But I'm counting on you.
If the medical examiner
makes a wrong judgment,
a crime might be overlooked.
From the victim's perspective,
you're the last line of defense.
So…
I'm pretty cool, huh.
Tooting your own horn now?
It's not a job someone like me
should be doing.
CONFERENCE ROOM
Excuse me.
Are you a family member?
Do you know his name or anything?
He's an acquaintance.
-Oh, I see.
-Sorry.
Excuse me.
What did you come here for?
Sorry.
I got worried after all.
This man…
I thought we might be able to talk a bit,
but he seems to still be asleep.
Once you hear
about that incident from Tsuda…
After that,
what will you…
do with him?
I think you already know.
Minoru?
However…
I'll be the one to do it.
What?
Since that incident,
Makoto has been carrying everything.
Even me, back when I couldn't do anything
and started avoiding people.
That's why,
I will carry him at the end.
Don't tell Makoto.
I won't.
I won't tell him, but…
Minoru?
Are you really okay with this?
You won't be able to do the things
you actually want to do anymore!
I would have loved to…
graduate from medical school
and be a forensic scientist.
But…
on the day of the accident,
I threw all of that away.
He's currently sleeping under medication,
but he might be able to talk tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
I understand.
Shall we go?
Time to open your shop, Mogi.
Any word from the hospital?
Tsuda still can't talk?
He's currently sleeping under medication,
but he might be able to talk tomorrow.
They said it will take
two or three days until he's stable.
I see.
And on your end?
Tomorrow will be another day
of checking footage.
You'll go back to the station?
Just let me be already.
I'll have a drink too.
Don't push yourself.
Want a snack?
I'll cook something.
Well…
Then, hayashi rice.
That's not exactly a snack.
Mom never really made this
for us, did she?
That's because
we kept saying her cooking sucks.
She wasn't good at cooking to begin with,
so she practiced while working
at Mogi's place.
The food at our house was Chinese
almost every day.
Thanks to that,
Mogi's shop's taste is the taste of home.
You're using that again?
It's delicious!
You guys want to try some?
No!
-Let me put it on for you! Hey!
-No!
1995, APRIL 26
Makoto, you should learn
to cook a little too.
Why?
You'll ruin your health
if you only eat out.
I'll be fine, as long as you are here.
This was in Mizusawa's house too.
I guess all houses in Kanagawa
got a flyer like that.
No, but the numbers…
FITNESS GYM
8,000 YEN A MONTH
The monthly price was different.
5,000 YEN A MONTH
Yes, it was a lot of trouble.
We suddenly had to stop everything.
What about the misprinted flyers?
Well…
We had already finished delivering
flyers here. So we just sent out a notice.
Hello?
Yes, management office.
I'm Tagusari, from the Aoi Station.
Can we speak for a moment?
Please open up!
Can you wait until later?
Tsuda is dead.
Minoru.
Did Tsuda say anything?
Don't screw with me.
Why did you just go and die on your own?
If you're going to die,
tell us everything first.
What were the two of us even doing
for over 30 years?
The clothes and personal effects
from when Mr. Tsuda was brought in.
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
Someone related to him
might know something.
There must be a clue somewhere.
Is it a phone number?
Hello.
Who is this?
Hello?
You know a man
named Yuji Tsuda, don't you?
Maybe we should've left them alone.
You mean there's another culprit
besides Tsuda?
Is that key the only clue left?
No way…
Subtitle translation by: Nix S.