Charging while walking
Unknowingly
The charging journey has reached its final destination
The expedition group will witness
"The last teardrop of the Atlantic"
Discovering the tranquil realm between
Tianshan Mountains and the basin
This is where
Following the expedition group
We welcome the final charge
Still watermelon
Watermelon
Right
He chose that one
I'll pick this one
Now all three of us have different choices
We'll assign today's energy points based on the sweetness of four melon types
and distribute today's energy values accordingly
I can tell mine won't be much
Why do I have so many?
But mine was the sweetest one
We have three types of vehicles in total
that can take you to
our best viewing spot
Audi car - five power units
seats four people
Motorcycle - three power units
You can also choose to walk
No power consumption needed
Walk there
Are you really this frugal, bro?
You'll freeze and pass out soon
What's this lake called again?
Sairam Lake
Sairam Lake supposedly means
"May you be safe and sound"
So people usually come here
and say a prayer to the lake
Let's say one too, all three of us
Okay, let's do it
One, two, three
Sairam Lake
First say "Sairam"
then say "Sairam Lake"
One, two, three
Sairam
Good
Wishing everyone safety too
Now you can choose your vehicle
I'll ride the motorcycle
I want to ride in the car
Audi
Q4 e-tron
I'll drive
You drive, brother
Everyone pick a melon
Watermelon
Honeydew melon
Hami melon
Then I'll take the honeydew
I choose the little silly
There's no "little silly" option
Is this the little silly?
This is a melon
Then I want the little silly too
Here's your little silly
There's only one little fool
Xiao Bai
The melon you chose has the lowest sweetness
Your selected melon is the least sweet
So you got the lowest power level
Because when the little fool calls out
Their heart is the sweetest
And receives the highest power level
Alright
Take a look
Have a look
Just one quick photo
Yes, take a photo, go ahead
Sorry about that
Your sweetness level is too low
Eat two more pieces
You're really not sweet enough
Not as sweet as we are
Okay, check this out
That's amazing
The three of you can now choose your
means of transportation
Who can ride a motorcycle?
Motorcycle
It's actually quite cool
But I can't
Even if you give me three power levels
I still can't ride it
Shall we go?
These few
One person each, right?
In the back
And we've got four more
Then mine
Mine's good
Got four more as soon as we boarded
What's up?
You all are taking one car
No room for you
You'll have to take Brother Bing's motorcycle
I'll pay three power units
Who should we kick off?
Okay
Okay, no problem
You pay three units, then Brother Sha gets off
Add one more, five people
Add one more
Come on, get in, Jinzhou
Alright
Then my three units are a bit too much
You pay two units, Brother Teng rides free
Can you drive?
Sure
Fair?
Fair
You pay two units
Paying two units works
Who's this?
They look so mismatched.
Better keep quiet.
We choose watermelon, Brother Yue.
Which of these four melons will you choose?
We'd like to choose watermelon.
I haven't chosen yet.
But you're already holding it.
Does holding it count as choosing?
No, you can choose for yourself.
I think...
The girl already chose for me.
Then watermelon it is.
Power up.
Now choose your transportation.
Let's go.
Go.
No hesitation.
Their team is full.
Start another vehicle
You can spend battery power
After that's done
Kick the people out of this vehicle
I'll throw the person out for you
I'll spend some battery power to remove one person
You
No matter how much you spend, you can't get back in
I told Ziyi
I'm still a guest here, bro
I'm still a human being
Do you even treat me as human?
Fine
Right?
Alright
Here's what you do - you two spend some (battery power)
You two start another vehicle
The two of us will spend five battery power together
Right?
Yes
Come on, let's play rock-paper-scissors
Ziyi gets three battery power
You get two battery power
Winner gets two power units.
Loser gives three power units.
Miss, we've only been together for two minutes.
You've already ordered me around three times.
I have to do everything you say.
I'll put in three power units.
We're not close, we just met.
You two just met.
Just met.
Just now you made me choose the watermelon.
Then gave it to me.
How can you say such things?
On the plane...
Didn't we come on the same flight?
That was you.
That's me without makeup, what's wrong?
I really couldn't tell
Hey Brother Sha, are you comfortable sitting in the back?
Why don't you use some power points
and ride with us in one car
No
I'll just spend one power point here
If you also spend one, I'll come over
You spend one
The two of us will spend two each
You spend one, okay?
Alright then, I'll come over
Him coming over works
But from my car
You've been sitting here so long
That one power point still needs to be spent
One power point
I'm comfortable there, it's cramped here
It's just one, right?
Let me see how many points you have
Don't worry about how many I have
Is it just one?
Is it just one point for you?
One point
One
Brother Sha, you've got the status, Brother Sha
Actually you could just sit in the front seat
Senior brother
You've arranged things nicely for yourself
You're really treating him like a driver
Yue, he really thinks you're his driver
The front seat's empty
Come sit up front
You insist on sitting next to the beauty
We're close
Got forced to come up front
Come
Who
Daxi couple (battery)
No way, it's Daxi's birthday today
Today Daxi is the boss
Won't charge you (battery) today
For real?
I'll contribute some (battery)
Right, Daxi should definitely contribute (battery)
The birthday person must spend some money
How to split?
We're one person short
I still have to drive
I'll have to pay extra
Three ice cubes (battery) for myself
Still pretty cold
Shall we go?
Let's go
We're leaving
So beautiful
The key colors are beautiful
Are these clouds above the lake?
So low
This is truly beautiful
So beautiful
Sairam Lake
I just looked it up
Do you know how clear the water is?
Thirty meters
Twelve meters
Twelve meters is quite deep
Visibility of twelve meters
Very clean
Do you know what's in this lake?
Fish
Because they were introduced from
Russia in 1998
Right
Have you tried it?
No
I had some last night
You ate the Coregonus peled last night?
They prepared it
Good
I believe the people in that car
Probably don't know
This lake is so huge
Eighty to ninety kilometers around the lake
So blue
Xiao Bai, tell us
I keep feeling like we're pulling two people
He just mentioned the clouds are low
Yes, that's what he said
Three words
Since getting in the car
Can you recover that battery power?
You're on this trip, Xiao Bai
You've talked about clouds
The mountains are beautiful
And the water?
And the grass?
So yellow
How beautiful, let's go play in the lake for a while.
Let's go
I'll take my usual seat
Take the seat of honor
Yesterday everyone asked
who was close with Ziyi
but no one really was
Then Chengcheng said
what was it called again
"Little Drama Queen"
Cute cute
Is this rated by netizens or
But now everyone says I'm
just very much a
intellectual woman
truly a "little drama queen"
Now you understand
why I directed you three times when we first met
Come
Welcome everyone to
the warm Sayram Lake
Now let's invite Teacher Dabao to introduce
Hello everyone, we meet again
Welcome to
Xinjiang's recharge journey
Today we've arrived at
the place of half lake and half mountains
Sayram Lake
As you can see
there are very beautiful snow mountains here
and here we have
super beautiful lake water
This Sayram Lake is also called
"The Last Tear of the Atlantic"
Because Sayram Lake
is at the junction of China's eastern monsoon
and the westerlies belt
So all the rain here
comes from the Atlantic
At the same time there are many mountain peaks here
glaciers
rivers
all converging into this lake
And precisely because
the lake contains lots of glacial meltwater
its color is exceptionally beautiful
We all know Xinjiang has abundant fruits
But there's only one fruit in all of China
that's named after a city
That's the Hami melon
It actually originated in Africa
Then it spread to Central Asia
where it underwent
its first domestication
before finally reaching China
So while this family
originated in Africa
the best varieties come from
our region
This confirms the ancient
cultural exchanges between nations
and dissemination
Thank you
Okay
Understood
Thanks
Based on Teacher Dabao's explanation
we come to today's
first challenge
The Hami melon pantomime challenge
The rules are simple
See who can use their body
to portray the largest Hami melon
Alright
I understand now
Okay, let's start with Ziyi
Okay
Hami melon
Hami melon-ha
You have to give me
Here you go
She's giving it to me with her eyes
Ha
Hami melon
Hami melon-ha
I receive it
Hami melon
Hami melon-ha
Oh no, now you have to stand up
Now you have to do the "Flying Swallow" move
Hami melon
Hami melon ha
Your feet are still on the ground
Hami melon
Hami melon ha
My little circle
I’m still leaving you a way out
Hami melon
Hami melon ha
This
Ha
What is this? Some weird melon
Here, Brother Teng’s melon
Get on the motorcycle
Hami melon
Ha
This is a game that tests physical strength
Hami melon
This round isn't over yet
This is just the beginning
Alright
Come back before dark
Don't get lost, turn on your navigation
Hami melon
Ha
This is way too big
Hami melon
Go up the mountain
Swallow
Hami melon
Ha
Hami melon ha
Oh no, where should I run to now?
Head to the opposite mountain
He's already gone up the mountain
No need to be this big
This is way too big
Hami melon
Lost weight
Ha
This is the end
Based on everyone's performance so far
Can anyone run farther than Chengcheng?
Otherwise, Chengcheng will take first place
Xiao Ba
Beat him
You must beat him, little brother
Xiao Ba
Climb over the second mountain
You're a natural athlete
It'd be a waste if you don't run
Seriously, go for it
Hurry up
Ha
So competitive
That's youth for you
Yes, follow with the drone
Give Xiao Ba a walkie-talkie
This melon of his is indeed huge
Go for it
Pass it to me
Passed it to you
Cue
Ha
Come
Dagua, let's go
How can this even happen
Hami melon
We can really move on to the next part now.
Haha
Melon
Ha
This game
If you happen to encounter
someone in the group with poor conditions
they really can't play it
Good grief
We'll be setting sail soon.
This time, Brother Teng and Brother Bing took first place.
They earned eight power units.
What?
Good.
And then, Xiao Bai...
Chengcheng...
Brother Yue
Second place, tied for second
Right, five (battery levels)
Ziyi
Great joy
With Brother Sha
You three (battery levels)
Okay
As long as we have it
Alright, that works
Hope in the final episode
Everyone can be in nature
Fully charged
Good
Such beautiful scenery
And we even have lactose-free milk here
I'll make some lattes for everyone
Brother
Is there any difference using lactose-free milk?
Our lactose-free milk contains no lactose
People with lactose intolerance
Can drink it without worry
And it has a particularly refreshing sweetness
Not only can it supplement nutrition for breakfast
But it's also good for drinking coffee like this
Learned something new
Choose lactose-free if you're intolerant
Get two cups for them
Does it taste good, bro?
Good
Everyone
You'll compete through strategy
To complete a fast-charging battle
Everyone will submit power values in turn
If the total range from eight people's submissions
Is between twenty-seven (power)
And thirty-five (power)
The power you submitted
Will be doubled and returned
If not within range
All submitted power values
Will be confiscated
So this tests
How well you understand each other
Understood
After this round
Whoever has the most power
Will gain special advantages next
Then let's discuss it together as eight people.
How many (power units) do you have?
Then we'll see if there are any "bad apples" among us.
Right, little brother?
Right.
My brother is correct.
Let's discuss this, brother.
How many (power units) per person?
How many of us are there?
Eight people.
Eight people
That makes thirty-two (power units)
Right
Four times five is twenty
Four times five—eight people—four times five is twenty
Three times eight is twenty-four
Four times five is twenty, no problem, right?
So stubborn
Four times five is twenty, that's correct
But with eight people
How does four times five equal twenty?
Why did I say four times five is twenty?
Stop being stubborn
Each person takes four (power units)
Thirty-two (power units)
But what if someone cheats?
I take ten (power units) at once
Right?
Should we make a vow or something, bro?
I swear I’ll only take four
Absolutely only four
I think
If anyone refuses to contribute one (power unit)
We’ll deal with them later
We just won’t play with them
Isolate them
Check the replay and delete their contact
But what if someone doesn’t care?
Right, little bro?
You go.
I'll go.
Just submit four (charges), don't submit more.
Got it.
Submit four (charges).
Done.
I'm finished.
You submitted four (charges), bro.
A man.
Does winning or losing matter?
You've got to keep your word.
Of course.
A promise is a promise.
Right.
Otherwise, where's the charm in that?
Would your brother be so petty?
A man must be sincere.
Definitely didn't submit.
The more you say that, the more suspicious it is.
The more you try to cover it up.
You didn't submit a single (charge).
With all this buildup.
There's definitely a twist coming.
Oh no.
Trouble, big trouble.
Big trouble.
Chengcheng got caught.
Chengcheng probably didn't submit.
People would only submit more.
No one would not submit.
They would.
Someone wouldn't submit.
What if it doesn't work out?
Because he didn't contribute.
What he has is already more than everyone else.
Right.
Watch closely.
Everyone, submit properly.
It's a misunderstanding.
This can't be real.
He doesn't have it on him.
I...
I'll kowtow to you, senior.
Don't.
He's not worth it.
He really isn't.
But he definitely has it.
Are you really going to kowtow?
Want some?
Come on
Want it or not?
Yes
Wanna see
Yes, come on
Come
Look
Got any?
Check your pockets
What if someone took it?
Really don’t have any
What's this?
Tell everyone what this is.
Wait a sec, Brother Teng.
Brother Teng.
Bro.
Don't go through my pockets.
How many (power units) inside?
A handful.
I put in two (power units).
Didn't put any, trust me.
Everyone should throw in five (power units) later.
Bing threw five (power units).
Okay.
Then I'll go.
Alright.
Brother Sha, how many (power units) should I put in?
I think you should put five (power units).
Because Chengcheng definitely didn't contribute.
This way it's safer, right?
Right.
Fine.
Just wait until the end.
Oh no, Daxi.
I think both of us threw ours in.
Now we just need to figure out...
Yueyue.
Yueyue, you went inside...
and took two (power units) back.
No I didn't.
Look at this pocketful, look.
Yueyue, how many (power units) did you actually contribute?
Earlier we agreed everyone would contribute five (power units).
Where's that sincerity now?
I'm being sincere now too.
I've always been sincere.
Let me check your pocket.
Now everyone's checking pockets.
Why should I let you check my pocket?
Something's fishy.
I'd like to say the same to my brother.
But why should my brother check my pocket?
Are you hiding something?
I'm clean.
You can't lie.
I won't.
No, let go.
Let me check this pocket.
It's not even your pockets
These aren't your pockets
They're all the same pocket
What's going on?
You're all like this
So should I invest or not?
Now I don't want to be part of this scheme
I think this investment is risky
This circle is too hard to navigate
You can't fall for the production team's
trap, you know?
We need to work together to double it
So the audience will see
that we're both smart
and loyal
both smart
After falling for the production team's trap
we look "foolish"
and then get "screwed" by them
Senior brother, you're right about this
Brother Bai didn't go
Brother Bai threw five (power units)
Then we can balance our numbers
Damn
If you want us to win, we must invest more
Would Xiao Bai really play tricks?
Xiao Bai
About Xiao Bai, I think
this kid's character is decent.
Xiao Bai, right.
Not necessarily.
Xiao Bai's character
I think it's worlds apart compared to Chengcheng.
Completely different from Chengcheng.
Good grief.
Definitely better than Chengcheng.
Bai
How many did you vote for? (power level)
Xiao Bai, how many did you vote for?
Can we talk about this?
Five (power level)
I
didn't vote
It's over
Everything's messed up
Probably didn't vote
None of you are real friends
So are we voting or not?
Why didn't any of you vote?
No, as long as he's not lying
Xiao Bai's situation is
Xiao Bai didn't vote
But Xiao Bai didn't deny it either
Right?
Right
He didn't lie
Correct
So it's essentially the same
No, his character is still better than yours
Different, how can they be the same?
How could they be the same?
He didn't vote
But he didn't mess up our calculations
If Xiao Bai doesn't invest any (power units)
Teng
then you invest everything
Invest everything
Everything
I'm not even aiming for profit
I just want my brothers and sisters
to not lose money
Don't let these "bad guys" ruin things
It's enough
But the way you talk makes it seem
"Zizuo" if I have any problems, tell me
"Zizuo"
"Tenghuai" I think you have issues
"Tenghuai"
"Zizuo" "Tenghuai"
Five (power units)
I have five (power units)
Eight (power units) total
Eight, thirteen (power units)
Still have fourteen left (power units)
Fourteen remaining (power units)
Must have twenty-nine (power units)
Twenty-seven (power units)
Thirteen plus fourteen
Bro, maybe you shouldn't invest, just quit
If you don't want to, I'll invest for you
Must
It's truly good up to that number
Must be at 27 (power level)
Must be 27 (power level)
27 (power level) is the minimum
From 27 (power level)
To 35 (power level)
Then what are we afraid of?
Just discard them all
What does it matter if he invested those three (power levels) or not?
As long as you all invested enough
You did invest four (power levels), right?
He keeps doubting me
I really did four (power levels)
Great joy
I also did four (power levels)
You don't need to doubt me
Rest assured
Asked the three most trustworthy people three times already
So I just need to confirm with people I trust
Five (battery)
Count it as eight times
Eighteen (battery)
Like this
I'll put in ten (battery)
What if it explodes?
Alright then
Then I'll put in nine (battery)
Okay
Who do we think we can trust, Brother Teng?
Right
You're talking nonsense
You keep blabbering
Don't you dare come out
Calculate it properly for us
Would I do that?
You would
No
Fine, go ahead
Can we trust you?
Why are you reminding me of this?
Brother Teng, you wouldn't lie, right?
Ziyi
Today you'll get to know me
I think he's trying to deceive people.
I'm not even aiming for profit.
I just want my brothers and sisters
to not lose money, that's all.
Don't let those "bad apples" ruin things.
They told me to invest nine (units).
So I'll invest nine (units).
Did you invest, Brother Teng?
Whatever amount was agreed.
So how much did you invest just now?
Nine (power units).
Then I'll go invest.
Okay.
Ziyi.
It's important.
I think it's appropriate.
But don't invest too much.
Alright.
Brother Teng, do you think the success rate is high?
I think I'll trust her.
I want to trust her.
I trust her too.
You just arrived, right?
I'm back.
I won't even ask you.
You definitely didn't cheat.
Of course.
Ziyi definitely didn't cheat.
I really didn't cheat.
Come on.
Investing is done.
Okay, this round.
Within the range.
Congratulations, everyone.
Within range.
This round.
It exploded.
The number is.
Thirty-eight (power units).
All invested power units are reset to zero.
Good thing we didn't invest.
Brother Sha.
You suspect me.
Earlier, Brother Sha told Shen Teng to invest less.
That means he must have invested a lot.
He was afraid Brother Teng would overinvest.
If it were my senior brother.
I want to "jump into the lake"
It couldn't be you, could it?
I voted according to the numbers too.
He smiled
Xiao Bai
Xiao Bai might have overinvested
Xiao Bai should have already done it by now.
Xiao Bai might not have voted either.
Xiao Bai went all out.
I guarantee when it's my turn to vote,
everyone will definitely be on average, no problem.
When it's my turn to vote,
I might just fill in the gaps or something.
But I don't have that much
Brother Sha and Jin Chen
I think they're quite reliable
Four
Ziyi should be pretty reliable
And Brother Bing
They do as they say
Five (power units)
Chengcheng and Brother Yue
I don't think they voted
Not even one (power unit)
Let's take a gamble
Because I think they...
The previous contributions were probably fewer.
I contributed eight (power units).
I was just following
the same pace as before.
Don’t look so suspicious of others.
You’re also a suspect.
Brother,
did you contribute all of yours, Brother Teng?
Even if he contributed all, it’d only be eleven (power units).
Right.
Is this the two (units) I’m short?
He went over.
That much over? How much?
Over thirty (units).
Only three (units) over.
Just your two (units) short.
No,
Xiao Bai contributed four (units).
More than that.
Even more.
Because by the time it was my turn,
some had already stopped contributing.
I had to adjust
So Xiao Bai contributed extra.
But not that much extra.
I contributed based on thirty (units).
How many did you contribute?
Five (power units)
Her, it's her
The "bad one" is here
What did I do?
She only has five (power units) total
If she gets "worse" she'll have
only five (power units)
She has more than five (power units)
Eight (power units)
Just now she gave me
a slightly eerie smile
Ziyi contributed too much too
Did you contribute everything?
You definitely contributed everything
Look, if we contribute again
this won't help everyone
Now we're creating resentment
We don't resent those who didn't contribute
We resent those who over-contributed
Isn't over-contributing because earlier
someone didn't contribute?
Didn't those who over-contribute think
those people hadn't contributed?
You over-contributed too
I think Xiao Bai didn't contribute
Then Chengcheng didn't contribute, Yueyue didn't contribute
I contributed eight (power units), my full amount
You two over-contributed
Why not follow the total amount?
How can we survive like this?
Taking matters into your own hands
Being too clever for your own good
Weren't you told to contribute five (power units)?
Afraid it wouldn't be enough, right girl?
You were told to contribute five (power units)
You contributed eight (power units)
How many did you contribute?
You were told to contribute five (power units)
You contributed eight (power units)
If you'd contributed five (power units) we'd be perfect
You say we don't resent those who didn't contribute
We just resent you two
What does this have to do with me?
Look how well you two handled this
Go, head over there
Are they going to "drown themselves in the lake"?
So precise even when turning around
These four people
Don't listen
It's not that our logic is wrong, it's still the same logic.
Or are you saying those who don't vote
should be considered untrustworthy?
Yes.
Especially Yueyue.
Right, we can't blame Brother Bai and the others.
Why are you scolding both sides at once?
After walking around, your tone changed again.
It's not about being dumb.
It's about being both dumb and smart.
No, it's about being scared, dumb, and diligent.
No.
What?
What? What are you trying to say?
Sometimes I really don't understand.
My brother's jokes.
No, we...
In the end, we figured it out.
We realized...
In the end, it all comes down to character.
Even though we lost,
our understanding was correct.
The two who didn't vote still have issues.
That's true.
Let's congratulate...
Fan Chengcheng.
Not a single clap, see?
So many...
In the next game,
Fan Chengcheng will also have a special advantage.
Alright, we've already lost.
Brother Teng is still upset.
Seems like Brother Teng hates me the most now.
Can't get over it.
Then next,
we'll proceed to the next challenge.
Xinjiang is one of China's three major
swan habitats.
Sairam Lake is also famous for its swans.
Baby swans in their infancy
often ride on their mother's back.
Now we'll experience
this process of swans protecting their young.
Eight members will pair up in teams of two.
Within their designated areas,
they can attack other teams at any time.
The swans must protect their babies
from being hit by sandbags.
If a baby gets hit three times,
that team is eliminated.
Until the last remaining team wins.
I already have a baby.
We have a baby.
What about you two?
Who's whose baby?
This one already has a baby.
Hasn't even hatched yet.
We're a team.
Protect your sister.
Quick, go protect your sister.
Do you need me?
No.
Brother, look at yourself in the mirror.
You can't protect anyone.
If you don't need it,
I'll just pick someone to protect me.
Let's split up like this.
Brother Bing, and Da Xi.
Okay.
Then Xiao Bai and Zi Yi.
Alright.
You two, us two, that's settled then.
You two.
Cheng Cheng will protect you.
You're Cheng Cheng's baby.
I've been waiting to see this.
Is that okay with you?
Fine.
Cheng Cheng.
Your energy level is the highest.
So your team
gets two extra "lives."
Let's let them go first.
Okay.
Alright.
Sure.
Let's go.
Corner.
Where are you going, brother?
Picking the four corners?
Stand behind me, I need to protect you.
Here.
Why do we have to be in the four corners?
It's fair for grabbing the bag.
Grab the bag.
Okay, ready.
Three.
Two.
One.
Quick, grab the sandbag!
Start.
Go.
Begin.
Wasting energy.
No rush.
Grab it!
Quick, Xiao Bai, grab it!
Hurry, Xiao Bai, grab it!
Xiao Bai, block them!
Should I hit?
Just stay in this corner and don't move.
Can't hit from this far away.
You just sacrificed your own pet.
Attack now!
Hold on tight to me.
Even the baby got thrown off
Then got swung to death
Missed it
The best spot is right by Bing
Old Bing, over there
Old Bing, quick! Give us a lob!
Bro, take it easy, bro
For Xiao Bai, okay
Okay
Below
Spanking
Old baby
That was too powerful
Handsome
Is this "Three Heroes Fight Lü Bu"?
To be honest
If he joins us, we'll give him three power units
Starting to bribe now, aren't we?
Quick
Okay, hit
Beautiful
Brother Bing
Isn't he your beloved Brother Teng anymore?
Just hit the legs
Alliance, Xiao Bai, hurry and form an alliance
Alliance
No benefits
Forming an alliance with them
A real alliance
Who can I trust in this situation?
The team has already fallen apart
Give it to me
He has four "lives"
Alliance
Take him out
Then it'll be fair for the three of us
Little Bai Alliance
Attack Brother Bing first
Quick, over here
Here
Chengcheng is so mean
Playing like this, huh Fan Chengcheng
No
I meant the alliance, I passed it to you
You were hitting me, I saw it
Great, our only ally is gone now
Bro
With his attitude
I feel like smashing my head on the sandbag
Nope
Alright, everyone
Now we share "lives"
Not just protecting the baby anymore
Then we can't protect it
No, we should stick to this plan
Also
We'll add another sandbag in the arena
Double sandbags
Hurry up
Just toss it over
No, we'll place it in the middle
Don't get in the shot
Otherwise, we can't film
Two, we have two
You don't have the right to throw, baby
Says who?
Baby doesn't have the right to throw
What? I'll fight together with my "mom"
No way
Three two one, throw
Why are you tricking me?
Baby's wings aren't strong yet
Attack Brother Ice
Three two one
Go, throw
Why did you suddenly change direction?
Go pick it up
Fall back
Quick, pick it up, baby
Hurry
You go first
You go
You attack first
I won't move, I definitely won't move
No, just kidding around.
Bring in another punching bag
Give me one more
Pick it up quickly
You're so clumsy
Hit
Am I trustworthy?
One for each of us
Worth it
Let's all attack that way
Okay
We'll hit them eventually
Agreed
Okay
Brother Bai, you can trust me completely
Should we trust them?
I'll trust Brother Bing first
What about me?
Actually, two people would work too.
Trust
Okay
Good
No
Let go, we all let go
Okay
Protect your legs a bit
Missed
What are you doing?
Chengcheng
Pick that up, Xiao Bai
Are you okay?
Sorry, are you okay?
I'm fine
Just hit the legs
Alliance, Xiao Bai
Hit
Come here and let us hit you
Alliance
Little Bai Alliance
Let's take them down first
Form an alliance directly
I trust you
I said I could fall for it twice
Here's one for you
All three are with them
This isn't the outcome you wanted either.
Now let's fight each other
They will definitely win
It's all here with us
They're all handled by us
Handle
Brother Yue
Alliance
Good
You threw one at me
This doesn't concern you
I'll fight Xiao Bai, you...
Alright, come on
I heard everything
What are you two plotting over there?
One, two
Brother Sha, what are you doing?
This isn't the result you wanted either.
Look, the "bad guy" is over there.
Look, the bad guy is over there.
It's over
Brother Bing, flank them from behind.
Here, give them another punching bag.
Let's go, both of us move down.
Is anyone coming to save us?
I'll lend Yueyue and them one "life."
We have two "lives," come on.
Brother Bing lent us one "life."
Go down.
Didn't catch it.
Coordinate the attack.
Come on.
Why are you attacking us after fighting them for so long?
What did we ever do to you?
Don't headshot my brother.
My brother isn't that smart to begin with.
Hit
Hurry
Don't throw all the sandbags out
No one will be able to hit anything
Beautiful
The end
Bag
White
Got it
It's over
You guys are amazing
So they're first place again
Alright, let me announce the results
We're in first place
Chengcheng and Brother Teng got 19 (power units)
Second place: Brother Bing and Daxi, 8 (power units)
Third place: Xiaobai and Ziyi, 7 (power units)
No fourth place
Each group, discuss how to distribute them
Give them all to Daxi
No
No, share some with me, bro
If you're going to be like this, then
He can keep one (power unit)
The rest are mine
No way
Then I'll take 10 (power units)
You take 9 (power units)
To be fair, your contribution this round wasn't much
Just give us the power units
She gets 4 (power units)
So each of us gets 4 (power units)
Everyone
The rules for this Power Fast Charge battle are
All eight members will submit
their power unit guesses
Whose guessed total
is closest to the actual total submitted
wins all the submitted power units
Current total power units: 85
How much should we bet this round?
Hard to say
How much do you have, Daxi?
You have quite a lot.
Over a dozen.
Xiao Bai.
Four.
Ziyi.
Ziyi has four.
You two have eight together.
Bing, you two switch seats
You and Bing switch seats, you two
What's wrong?
You two switch seats first
Let's form an alliance.
It's not me
You can have these ten power units
Bai Sect, to your place
What's up?
Nothing much
Not with you
You're leaving us out, right?
Right
Nine
You also have nine
I have eleven
Together we have twenty
The two of us make twenty
Twenty-eight
Twenty-eight plus seventeen
Forty-five
With forty-five we can manipulate the market
Yes
We must manipulate it
We're the market manipulators
Let's make it seven, bro
Why are you excluding me?
Just exclude him, he won't let go
Isn't that
Just offering a different approach
That can also be calculated.
Then it's settled.
Those who don't vote don't participate.
Whoever gets closest to that number
gets to take it all.
I think it's good.
Chengcheng votes first.
I won't vote yet.
Right, Chengcheng you go first.
I'll hold off for now.
You vote first.
I'm the battery king, you go ahead.
I'd forgotten until you mentioned it.
We haven't really discussed yet.
This strategy.
You discuss it first.
Then I'll vote last.
I can have this little authority, right?
There's definitely something wrong.
I'm telling you, he's waiting for us all to vote
then he'll blow it up.
He's holding more than twenty.
The deciding power lies
with him.
It's in Fan Chengcheng's hands.
Then his "suicidal" approach
Right.
He'll have to go "suicidal" too.
In that case,
Where's Brother Shen Teng's follow-up director?
Give me your earpiece.
What do you want to hear?
Listen to what they're saying.
Listen to his return feed.
Who cheated first last round?
Was it Chengcheng who cheated first?
Not this time.
Anyway, he won't...
Let's team up against Chengcheng.
Deal.
Here's our plan:
Let's pool together fifty total.
Right.
I'm putting all nine of mine in.
You're going all in?
All in.
You're really going all in?
Then we'll do nine.
Just focus on those nine points
Are you guys done talking?
Done.
Let's vote.
I won't even listen to you.
Fine.
This is it
This one
Brother, do it again.
How did he see it?
Useless
I think no matter how we discuss it, it's pointless
One of our seven must have betrayed us
If we unite, we can succeed
There's no way we can unite with me here
That's why I said not to include you
You two are worthless
This game is literally unplayable now
Your choice this round is trash
You decide for yourself
No matter how I choose, it'll be garbage, don't worry
No amount of discussion will help
It's just that everyone
can invest however much they want
Just make a rough estimate
and invest
Wow
Brother Bai definitely invested all nine
Absolutely, he invested everything
Good intentions will surely be rewarded
Shall we discuss?
I voted for all.
Eleven.
What about you?
I voted for all.
Don't believe it.
The elders don't act their age.
The young don't act their age either.
This show of yours...
Tell the truth.
Are you two trying to steal my battery?
Didn't we all vote?
Bro, there's no camera now.
Speak freely.
Tell the truth.
Tell the truth to your senior.
Cover my hair.
Cover it and tell the truth.
How many did you vote for?
Speak properly.
Can I choose not to say?
Can I choose not to speak?
Did you lie just now?
I lied.
Suddenly, you suggested playing a game
Two big guys showed up
It was really intense
Did they lie or not?
They lied
Haven't decided yet.
Let me calculate.
Brother Bing definitely has nine.
Brother Bing is honest.
Brother Bai definitely voted for all four.
Ziyi has three.
Brother Teng has eleven.
I don’t think he voted that many.
I think he only voted for one.
Brother Yue.
He probably voted for one too.
Brother Sha likely has one as well.
Daxi probably voted for more.
Let’s count hers as ten.
Ten, twenty, twenty-four, twenty-eight.
Thirty.
I’ll vote for one.
I can’t let you see.
My count is absolutely accurate.
You wrote it before the voting was finished.
Don't worry.
For example, if both of us are close...
We'll split it evenly.
Splitting is fine.
Okay.
Yueyue must earn the power points.
One more number
These must all be the same
Great joy
Do you really have to guard against me like this?
I've already handed it all in
Is it finalized?
No one wants to chat with me?
It's finalized.
We've already submitted it.
No more changes.
It's not that I didn't participate in the discussion.
You can discuss it yourself.
You definitely submitted one.
If you could submit two,
I'd "kneel in admiration."
Okay
Let's announce the results of this round
So exciting
Someone guessed it right
The final number
And not just one person
Let's announce the first one
Xiao Bai
The winner
I see through you all
After so many episodes
I've seen through all of you
Really now
The second place
The one who saw through everyone is
Brother Teng
You
So many people have seen through it
Then let's announce the third one
What's this... this...
The third place goes to
Daxi
Come on, everyone say what number you have
Sixteen
No vote means no participation
One vote is the most reasonable
So everyone should vote one
Bing voted nine
Nine plus seven makes sixteen
So the total is sixteen
Really, one vote per person
Brother Bing voted nine
Now let's talk about others
Brother Sha
Fifteen
Just one short
Brother Yue nineteen
Ziyi eighteen
Let's talk about the two most outrageous
Brother Bing guessed forty
Chengcheng guessed thirty
I was calculating how
You should've voted three each
And I actually trusted you guys
How many did you vote?
I was here analyzing everything
Calculating away
If he had voted more
Wouldn't he have guessed right?
These sixteen are split among three of them
Right
There's one extra, who gets it?
Three winners
Give it to Daxi
Daxi's birthday
Brother will give you some energy
Thanks bro
Everyone's been talking about the white salmon
Next we'll head to the restaurant
To taste this delicacy
Now let's go
Let's go
No matter what time it is now,
the Shu Hua sponsored 9 o'clock store
is now open.
Nutritious and easily absorbed, for a great start.
Today's Shu Hua clue milk
has also been placed in position.
Only one bottle available.
Everyone, hurry up!
Please quickly
and accurately recite the following tongue twister.
Can't even read it properly
You two got it completely backwards
You'll bite your tongue
I laughed till I cried
My eyes aren't good
Remember to drink your milk
Okay
Brother Teng
Now you can obtain the clue card
Alright
Thank you
Why did you go look by yourself?
My clue.
Gave him his own.
Let him see it again.
I didn't get to see.
I missed it.
I thought you'd share with me.
Why would I share with you?
Our 9 o'clock store has one more skill card.
It can help you later in the game.
This skill card.
will be auctioned.
Starting bid: one energy unit.
Four (energy units).
Four going once.
Nine (energy units).
All in.
Seventeen (battery units)
He has
Does he really have that much battery?
Yes
He does - over twenty (battery units)
Sorry about that, brother
No problem
Congratulations Chengcheng for obtaining this skill card
Let's go eat
Wait for me
Hurry up little brother, my dear brother
It's this big, right here
And there's a red carpet too
Pilaf
Making such a big fuss
This is like a banquet
Eat, hurry up
Eat
I'll eat
What I want to eat is over there
You went straight for the staple food
This fish is the same type prepared differently
I'll have some white salmon.
Have some.
Delicious.
Take a bite.
Steamed to perfection.
The pilaf is pretty good.
So tasty.
Have some soup to warm up.
You have to drink this soup.
This meatball soup is good.
The meatball soup is really good.
Pretty good
Really nice
I suddenly regret sitting here
at this four-person table.
Everyone's so close, two people eating—
I can't even reach the dishes on that side.
Then I'll start moving around.
Keep it circulating.
Eat around the table.
Lamb.
Just now, Ziyi
Did my sandbag hit your head?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
There are so many points outside the show.
It's all in the past.
Haven't even asked.
What about in the show?
Then outside the show...
Even if we asked, it wouldn't be recorded, right?
Ziyi, did you get the medicine I brought you earlier?
You kept it, right?
There's still medicine.
Brother Teng just got the clue card.
It's about the upcoming dance competition.
A little dance after dinner
has become this show's dinner
regular feature.
Look how much more we're doing since you arrived.
Who?
You.
It's all dancing now.
Before you came,
we never danced at all.
Dance King.
I just missed that one time.
Okay.
In nature,
there are some talented dancing waterfowl,
like grebes.
They use
a complex dance
to identify if you're their companion.
Today we're playing
a dance version of "Werewolf."
"Dance Out My Companion."
We can't even play regular Werewolf right,
and now there's a dance version.
Everyone put on your headphones.
Understood
Simple
Come on
You recognized your identity just by hearing it, right?
Yes
The silent one is the werewolf.
Our game hasn't started yet.
You're the only one bold enough to ask.
I've been silent too.
Honestly, I've been silent as well.
Still pretending to move around.
The key is the silence.
Everyone's staying pretty calm.
I saw you moving, but I didn’t dare.
Wait, no.
The Emperor's New Clothes.
Alright.
Ready.
Start.
Exposed!
That person's exposed!
Great joy
I thought everyone was still that
Drama queen. She's such a drama queen.
I think we can vote now.
Three, two, one.
Stop.
Can't switch in time.
I noticed.
This.
What's wrong with me?
Brother Teng and Daxi.
No.
I'll vote for him too.
I won't vote.
I can vote for Daxi.
But I won't vote for Brother Teng.
Then I'll follow your vote. I'll vote for Daxi.
I thought.
No.
I thought everyone was on the same music.
No, you were totally into it, you know?
Others already switched songs.
Yet you were still into it.
Then the song changed, right?
The second one was him.
There were some fast and some slow songs.
You didn't know.
Don't play dumb.
I know.
Switched.
What do you know?
I switched songs too.
I just.
To be honest.
We didn't know.
When the song changed, I panicked.
I was still dancing to it.
Right.
Me too.
I was afraid I'd give myself away.
Yeah.
I didn't know we should change dance moves when the song changes
Let's try another round
Try one round
Once more
Another round
Okay
You do ballet
Ballet, I'll do ballet
Then you go with ballet
You naturally look elegant anyway
Ballet
All my moves are like this
We'll just mirror each other
Three
Two
One
Begin
Then you can't copy me
Whether they're undercover or not doesn't matter
Okay, 3-2-1, stop.
That's it?
This? Just this?
What's wrong with me?
And you still voted for me?
The key is our mirrored actions - I saw it clearly.
I noticed Xiao Bai wasn't moving much.
Barely moved.
Did Xiao Bai not move?
I couldn't see because my back was turned.
Didn't move.
Xiao Bai.
Even if you're wrongly accused,
it's because you can't dance.
Dance King.
That self-introduction on the first day,
that introduction was wasted.
Xiao Bai, how can you both dance,
ride horses,
and hit high notes?
Then why didn't you dance just now?
That makes it even more suspicious.
You didn't even glance at me.
How do you know I didn't dance?
I was watching from here.
I think it's Bai.
It's not me, really not me.
Then give me a reason, Bai.
Why didn't you move?
I was doing small rhythmic movements.
Of course I understand.
When we practice, we always start with these small movements.
That's true.
Hard to communicate.
What's so hard about communicating?
Exactly.
Small movements - I've seen small movements.
People's small movements look really nice.
I don't quite understand
why so many people
are directing the momentum straight at me
I think if I hadn't jumped
others wouldn't have jumped so dramatically
A few people immediately set the tone
Brother Bai was the most aggressive
He's my senior brother
Now it's my turn
Vote for Brother Teng
Senior brother, you're
being unprincipled
This is malice
Malicious harm
My senior brother is harming me maliciously
I think during testing
and this round you should have
used two different tracks
The exact same music
is indeed
I just want to say
Ziyi and I are the good ones
I'm not your brother
I'm truly innocent
You don't
You are innocent
You can't do this
Because Ziyi said
mentioned a detail
Right, she revealed the detail
Correct
Same as last round's pattern
Yes
Though this detail shouldn't be exposed
But she revealed it
Right
Though it's basic
But she proved herself
Basic
Fine
I can confirm she's telling the truth
Right? So I'm innocent too
You make sense
I also think you're innocent
I've explained this much
Yet my senior still suspects me
Meaning he might not know the truth
Do innocents need to prove themselves?
No need, senior
This round votes for you
Big twist
Brother Sha, you're making people
If I say all this
and you still doubt me
it proves you don't even know
what we're talking about
You don't even know the details
Listen to me
Either Xiao Bai or him
Just these two
Why keep suspecting me?
You're suspecting me
You suspect me when I vouched for you
I even mirrored your moves
to prove my innocence
You old wolf, you go first
Two rounds and I've shown no flaws
We're almost fighting over this small matter
How interesting
They were completely copying my movements
Then they couldn't keep up when the song changed
Missed the beat change.
Fell behind.
These are your details.
Right.
Why are you mirroring me?
Just trying to copy my moves.
Brother Teng, if you're the mole,
I think you're really clever.
You're playing it perfectly.
Anyway, Brother Teng,
You shouldn't have smiled at me like that.
Even this you nitpick?
What kind of timing is this?
How could I possibly control my expression so well?
If we can't decide,
then let's keep the music going.
No, this round isn't over yet.
I've only analyzed a few people.
I really want to take someone out.
Xiao Bai, speak up.
Don't just talk about your style.
Whatever "Fan Xiao" or whatever.
We've all seen Xiao Fan's.
Now to prove myself,
should I perform again
that last round's move?
Do it again? Sure.
I just have one signature move.
Not Xiao Bai
Still Brother Teng
Right?
Still him
Just this
He doesn't even know what it is
Get out
Won't see you again
Just leave this time
Brother Teng, you're like this
Tell us what this is
Which tooth is stuck?
Just say which tooth is stuck
Right
Let me see, generally speaking
Molar tooth
Just vote for Brother Teng
Why vote for me?
Just because he doesn't know what this is
It's Brother Teng then
But I really don't understand
We all know
Even someone as unfashionable as me
Knows about it
Left behind by the times
You've been left behind by the times
This is crazy
Maybe he really doesn't
Use those apps normally
Not only do I not use them
I even criticize Chengcheng
I tell him to browse something useful daily
Is it Chengcheng?
Voting for you
Choose then
Go ahead and vote
Wait, let me argue first
I have to make my case
Go on
Why should I be eliminated?
Ziyi just now...
Dragging Ziyi into this again
Why I believe she's innocent
Because she revealed crucial information
That I caught
And actually you weren't paying attention
I also mentioned
I said we played one and a half songs
See, even though my play was weak
But I had no choice
I'm not surviving because I want to
I just don't want
To let the werewolves take advantage
I'm nearly in tears
Villagers must try harder
Not that I'm saying I'm a villager
I don't care
No, you can't not care
If you don't care, you're giving up
You're just giving the werewolves
A chance to survive
But right now it seems
Like a werewolf begging for a chance
I'm making such crucial points
Fine
Now prepare to vote
From right to left
Each person corresponds to a number
Okay
We just raise hands, right?
Raise hands
Yes
No bandwagon voting
Come on
One, two, three
Raise hands
What?
What do you mean?
No
Didn't you say after calling number one
everyone would raise their hands together?
Or raise hands for number two?
It's all you.
Why are you calling other numbers?
No, these few aren't—
They don’t know.
They are—
They're all number one
I know, I know everything
Senior brother, you definitely aren't
But let me tell you
I'll leave these earphones here and go now
I'll hang these earphones here for you
I'll make you regret it
Regret and suffer
Although I'm out of the game,
I can still do whatever I want, right?
Then why are you still wearing it?
Alright, get ready.
Three, two, one, go!
Not released
Don’t panic
Grey Cranes (werewolves), don’t panic—it’s not released yet
You didn't release me.
I wronged you.
Forget it.
Three, two, one.
Stop.
He was wronged.
Don't pull this act.
He was wronged
I'm not buying your act
I know who it is
Who?
Get out
You couldn’t have missed this at first glance
Got him
Stop jumping
Stupid game
Caught him
He’d definitely jump at this
When this was swapped immediately
He still went along with it
This is so unlike him
Then it was swapped again later
Even after swapping, he still jumped at it
He still followed me here
This is so embarrassing
Good luck with that Gray Crane (werewolf)
Try to survive a bit longer
I think I know
who the other Gray Crane (werewolf) is
I know too
I think I'm about to figure it out
Now I know too
Alright, get ready
Begin
What's wrong?
Five pairs of eyes are staring at me
I'm thinking, what is this?
Even a little hint would help
Right
They won't dance
So we can't learn
I was really startled at the time
There wasn't a single song in my headphones.
Brother Wei suddenly made a loud noise behind me.
The chair shook.
Then everyone looked at me.
Then I noticed Meng Ziyi staring at me.
I said I was done.
I said, "You all heard that?"
How do I explain this?
That song switching thing...
Just now I saw him do this in my peripheral vision.
I'll just
I'm out of ideas
This is too hard to act out
I can't keep pretending
Can't fake it
Okay
Then our first round ends
Grebes (civilians) gain +5 charge each
Now, round two
Don't make me do it again
Can't take it, really can't
What are you?
I'm voting for you this time
Ready
Three
A bit nervous
Two
One
Start
You
Not me
Three two one
Stop
Come on, our first round
Me
You must know this
I know this
But it wasn't placed here
Daxi
I'm all about energetic songs and dances
You two
Daxi
These two
They don't know
My senior brother definitely is
Right next to me
I don't even know what you're doing
Senior brother
I didn't pay much attention
I noticed these two
You're leaving me an opportunity like this
Is that okay?
Okay
Next time, alright?
I'll stand here
There won't be a next time
With my back to you
Who's giving me another chance?
I'm not saying I must have this chance
I just
As a civilian, I must work hard
Civilians must put in effort
My effort is to not give the werewolves any chance
You know
I need to play seriously
These words sound so familiar
Brother Teng said these exact words last round
And got eliminated
Me
Let's do it together
I just got into position
And it's starting already
It's not the curve of the upper chest and waist
I kinda feel like stepping on you
He can't be both
Not necessarily
Last round he wasn't the Gray Crane (Werewolf)
Right, not last round
I'll use you to clear my name
Senior brother
This round I think
Especially since Daxi's birthday
They
Need to vote out
Must vote
Ziyi just arrived
Haven't had a good chance to show yet
Right?
Senior brother, you must go out this round
It's not about winning or losing anymore
My senior brother is number two
We didn't see over there
From my side, Daxi looks
Daxi is indeed too obvious
I was really singing and dancing energetically
What?
In the middle of dancing
Let's vote
It's Daxi
What's wrong?
Let's vote
Okay, come on
Come on
Everyone get ready
This, number two
My senior brother is number two
Okay
Three
Two, one
Raise your hands
Tie
Tied vote
So it's just you two, right?
Me?
Then you two should dance battle
You two dance battle
Whoever dances better stays
Then I'm definitely out
Daxi can just roll around
Right
Brother Sha is already done for
The heartthrob of PLA Art College class of '97
You think I'm joking?
Now I can only do this
This
That's it
Just these three steps
This is...
Senior, do us proud
Bring honor to PLA Art College, okay?
If I really... then...
It'll just be embarrassing
We can't do this
Our school's dignity
Still needs to be preserved
No more dance battles
Let's appeal instead
Can we use our words?
I surrender
Alright then
Voted out
My senior got eliminated
Are you going to fight or not?
If you can't dance, what's the point of a dance battle?
Then you two debate.
Debate.
Daxi, you go first.
I've been dancing continuously.
That's it.
I've been constantly...
Immersed in this music.
It's her.
No, I'm not good with words.
But I'm definitely good.
Definitely good.
I'm just a commoner.
It's you.
I think Brother Sha is suspicious.
I'm suspicious?
It's not just a song.
It represents the emotions of many people.
At the beginning,
I struggled to find a dance move
to express my feelings.
This emotional expression...
Get to the key point, bro.
You should say this, right.
That's the key information.
Then you're out.
But you can't reveal key information
and still have to debate.
Then I've already said my piece.
Alright, let's vote again.
Three, two...
My senior is number two.
One, vote!
So stubborn.
At this moment,
you're still stepping on me.
Both of you are invalid on the competition stage.
Only I voted for my senior.
Come on.
Everyone ready.
Three, two, one...
Begin!
Come on, 3-2-1, stop
What's your number, Ziyi?
Not me
This guy's just strolling around
Don't step on me
Let them figure it out themselves
Number five, I vote for number five
Number five is...
Me
Why vote for me? I already said
But your rhythm
Is really different from ours
I don’t understand Cantonese
I think it’s a bit like
Brother Bing
Like me
Don’t you think the song sounds like me?
Now for survival, everyone's starting
to reveal critical information
repeatedly leaking key details
I need to test Xiao Bai
Xiao Bai's pretending to be a coach now
I think he's probably fine
We both got caught in the chaos earlier
We match up
You two match up
Then you two go together
Is our analysis on point?
No problem
Right?
No wonder you two are from the Military Arts
Now you two are friends again
When it comes to dealing with "bad guys"
We stand united against them
Completely aligned
Good friends
Two good friends
Alright then
So be it
My senior brother goes first
That could work
My senior brother is number two
I
I really am a fool
But there's no one else
Never mind, no one's left
Think it through carefully
Analyze it properly
Aren't you my "guardian angel"?
Can't figure it out?
Tell my senior brother number two
Analyze it carefully
Okay
Let's go
Don't vote randomly
Three, two, one - vote
Eliminated by majority vote
What else can I say
Let them play by themselves
Voted correctly
Everyone
Game continues
Continue
Definitely continue
Last chance
Final opportunity
Not the chest-waist curve
Come on
Three, two, one
Release
Not this one.
This is the one.
Changed the song.
What are you doing?
What are you guys doing?
What do you want?
Brother Teng
Jump quickly!
Brother
What are you doing?
I won’t cover for you anymore, Ziyi.
And you’re blaming me?
Now I finally know why
he tried to copy my dance moves earlier.
He was listening to the song in my earphones.
I saw Xiao Bai go over there.
You were observing from behind.
I thought you were observing, but when I looked closely,
you were eavesdropping.
I caught you
Vote them out
My junior brother is number one
Let's vote
No, no one's summarizing
Whatever you say is useless
Useless
No, this is the final round now
Final round of voting
If I were to...
Then...
The civilians would win
Should I sing it out?
You sing
You sing it
Breaking the rules, huh?
Breaking
Swords and blades flashing
You're exposed
Then vote for Xiao Bai
Then let's pick Xiao Yueyue
No
We can't do that this round
If we lose, we lose
Right.
If you win, you win.
Okay.
Then what? Who should we vote for?
Go ahead, ask him to start.
Just let him start and you'll see.
So what now? Who are you voting for?
Can you vote for me?
Then I'll vote for Bing.
I vote for Ba.
My junior is number one.
Three, two, one, vote.
Alright, continue.
Game over.
There's really nothing here.
Acting up to this point.
Still swinging swords (flashing blades).
You're really good at acting.
Brother Teng.
Did you figure it out?
What song were they playing?
Something like "Young and Dangerous"?
How did you know?
It's the clues you guys gave away.
Nostalgia and all that.
He told me what was just sung.
Was it "Young and Dangerous"?
But that's not the song you sang.
Not this one.
Guessed wrong.
Let's have Brother Teng and Daxi listen.
Go ahead, play it out loud.
What's up with Daxi?
Then how did I get it wrong?
Well,
You saw me and Xiao Bai do it.
You saw us dance like this.
It felt like a sudden realization.
Yeah,
That's it.
This is quite difficult
Come on, everyone, put on your headphones
Come on
I'll just observe this round
Me too
I won't reveal myself
Want to dance with me?
Okay
Let's do the final round
Three, two, one
Begin
Got it
Three two one, stop
He
No way, didn't even realize it stopped
My brain was spinning just now
Xiao Bai
I
I thought this
No, I thought mine was
The intro to this dance track
Because mine isn't
The kind you heard before
It has a melody
I thought this had that same feel
I was still grooving to it
Because mine has a melody
This has that same feel
No, I thought mine
Mine is the intro to a dance track
I thought everyone was like this
Because they weren't dancing either
So they just kept watching
Everyone looked very serious
Just observing
Then I saw my "dad" here
I thought he was just pretending
I remained quite calm
I even said it must be him
I was listening carefully
No, but he was actually pretending
He's up next round
Number two
I was
This was totally our music
What music?
Can we get close?
Okay, 3-2-1, start
Don't wait for the song to end
Go ahead
How did we end up in the Northeast?
Use the yangko dance to lure him for two eight-beat measures
Only then did he get hooked
I really couldn't hold back anymore
It's too familiar
You two
I listen to my own song
I've been wrestling with myself
for how long
before changing it to yangge
A bit schizophrenic, right?
Absolutely
A bit split
No
Mine's easy to get into
Easy access
I can enter anytime
Come on everyone, vote
Number two
Then it's over
Three
Then we lose
Two, one
Okay, number two is out
Everyone gather in the middle
Game
over
What song?
It's my song
Rap
You can't listen to this song without reacting
(Lyrics) We don’t play
Right after the song ends, you pull this on them
You go first
I can't find the beat
I can't find it
You go first
I can't find the beat
I can't find this point.
Everyone please return to your seats and rest.
I'm dying of laughter.
Everyone,
The simple little game has ended.
Who won?
Who won just now?
Ziyi and Brother Bing won the most.
Because all six of us have been undercover.
Just now, except for those two,
everyone else had ten power points each.
Each of us two won
fifteen (power points).
Fifteen (power points).
Alright then.
Today our power champion is
Daxi.
Congratulations Daxi.
Happy birthday to you
Wishing you happiness and health
Then I'll make a wish
Wishing everyone good health
Happiness every day
Happy birthday Jin Chen
Fleece the sheep
Begin
Defend
If we drive them out, we win
I'll flank from behind
Surround them
Go
They're fast
Reinforcements
Block them
Brother Teng, what are you doing?
Can't cross the line
I didn't cross the line
Snow Mountain
How are you?
A proper international competition
Even skipping stones has style
No problem
I'm coming
This is good
I want to eat skewers
I'll grill them later
Skewers
That's the idea
This works
This works, Brother Teng
Let's go in then
Do you admit it?
Okay, ice
Okay
Too ruthless
"All or Nothing" Part 2
Should we change the actress?
Beautiful
I want to play ten more rounds
This is the last episode of the season
This time I feel
Maybe everyone still thinks I'm quiet
Rather introverted
But I've already made breakthroughs
I'm also someone who doesn't talk much
But I'm still very happy
Beautiful
This lake is 70 million years old.
Seventy million years ago, there were still dinosaurs.
I often watch this show while eating.
Not too tired, right, Brother Sha?
Actually, I'm also a guest (on this show)
You two keep asking me
The fried instant noodles I made yesterday were really good
Did anyone else besides you get to try a bite?
Brother Bai
You should be grateful to him for your entire life.
Isn't it quite delicious?
Each person opens a jar.
and receives a corresponding amount of power value.
They can choose to continue or stop at any time.
Three (power)
Five (power)
One (power)
I don’t want to draw anymore.
Draw one more time.
Push beyond your limits.
You're so mean
Each of you praise me once
Whoever praises me the best will...
The 3-billion (box office) leading lady is so beautiful
Then you
Go for it
Keep going
Three (battery) - three again (battery)
Surpass me
Let me try too
Again?
What kind of kid is this?
Break through your limits
I'm so nervous