No matter what time it is now,
The 9 o'clock store sponsored by Shuhua is now open.
Nutritious and easily absorbed.
Start your day in great shape.
Today's Shuhua clue milk has been placed in position.
Play a mini-game with the production team.
Drink the clue milk
to obtain a crucial clue.
Please combine the following characters into one Chinese character:
Person, Sun, Three
Me
It's truly "spring"
Congratulations Jin Chen
for receiving our Shu Hua Milk special clue card
You're about to begin a "life-and-death" game
Please note
The food chain has its own elimination rules
Hide yourself well
Don't be discovered by your natural enemies
Okay
Everyone, because these past two days we've all
collectively completed
a short film shoot
so everyone can receive
100 power points
There's also a clue card behind it
Does anyone want it?
I want it
Where is it?
Chengcheng already got it
In later segments
you can designate one member
to obtain their clue
Good
Now we'll officially begin
today's challenge
Alright
Hello everyone
Hello
Today we're going to talk about
the knowledge of food chains
The food chain is a theory proposed
by British zoologist Elton in 1927
Simply put,
in the natural world,
every species has
its own level in the food system
Now, the Xinjiang region where we are
is both a special biodiversity area
and a fragile zone
For example, if our spruce trees
were affected by pests or diseases
all the birds dependent on spruce
would disappear
Then the snakes that prey on these birds
or some large raptors
would also become extinct
Therefore,
protecting the food chain
and ecosystem here is particularly crucial
I hope everyone understands
how precious
this land we inhabit is
Don't worry, teacher
Expedition Team Members
Welcome to continue unlocking Xinjiang's wonders
In Xinjiang's natural realm
there exists its own food chain
The expedition team members
will simulate the local food chain
and participate one by one
becoming links in the food chain
Through missions
they'll obtain their identities
and their positions in the food chain
Following ecological rankings
they'll engage in chain-style attacks
Food Chain
When one link in the food chain
is eliminated,
the next creature automatically becomes the attack target.
Any attacks that don't follow the chain cycle
are considered invalid.
Congratulations to all members
You've become part of the food chain
Everyone can participate in small challenges
to reveal your identity information
Alright
We will now give
the first person to obtain identity information
The challenge rules
Team members will stand up in order
and say "Let's all go to Xinjiang"
"How many people came"
Mistakes lead to elimination
Final three can get identity clues
Plus fifty power points
Come on
Let's go
Don't understand
Still don't get it
Say "one person came" in order
Then two
Then three
Then four
Then five six seven
Then seven six five four three two one
Right
Understand?
It's that simple
The number means how many came together
Still confused
Play one round and you'll get it
Let's begin
Okay, ready? Three two one
One person came
Two people came
Three people came
Brother, your turn
Three people must say "three came"
Just us three now
Correct
After him would be four
Then I won't speak
Those standing won't speak
The three of us came
Once you stand, don't speak
Then it's his turn
Right?
Those standing shout
Say "the three of us came"
I know
I know I came with the three of you
But wasn't this your idea?
Didn't I stand up with you?
What I mean is
The three of us should shout together
I
Then sit down after shouting
After shouting and sitting down
Do we need four people then?
Then I'll
They have four people
You're among the three
The four of us, without you
Understood
Got it
Come on
Who starts?
This time with elimination
Starting with
Cheng Cheng starts
Go
3, 2, 1, everyone say "Xinjiang" together
I came alone
Came with two people
Came with three people
Came with four people
Came with five people
Came with six people
Came with seven people
What's wrong with me?
What did I do?
This is ridiculous
This is wrong
Six, we
Hani Kezi was wrong, right
Hani Kezi was wrong
3, 2, 1, everyone say "Xinjiang" together
I came alone
Came with two people
Came with three people
Came with four people
Came with five people
Came with six people
Came with seven people
Correct
Eliminated
Hani Kezi
Okay
My senior is doing butterfly stroke here
One two three four five six
Go up to six then back
Everyone wake up
Who goes first
Change it
Xiao Bai
Xiao Bai goes first
Let's all go to Xinjiang together
I came alone
Two people came
Three people came
Four people came
Brother Sha
Four people also came
He's definitely doing it on purpose
He just doesn't want to play
No
I always thought we were on the same level
Don't say "same level"
Brother Sha, you're like this
Your punishment for losing is
You have to sit facing the sun
Then give me your glasses
Wait, why do I have a punishment?
Give another chance
What? Another chance?
Then give Hanikezi another chance too
Hanikezi is revived too
Okay, revived
Okay
We have to start again
We'll play until dark
The tenth round officially begins
Brother Teng, you go first
You first, change the approach
I just want to go to Xinjiang alone
I came alone
Two people came
Three people came
Four people came
Five people came
Six people came
Seven people came.
Why is there one extra?
Just now, was it...
Daxi?
What?
Bing, probably.
When there were six people...
Who shouldn't have stood up?
Let's deduce this.
Look, me alone.
Two people.
Three people.
Four people.
The four of us.
Then five people.
Five people.
Five people, right?
Six people.
I stood up - six people.
Me? No...
That's wrong.
Seize them.
Incorrect.
Mistaken.
His mistake.
Made a mistake.
As Brother Teng's punishment, turn around.
Don't move your eyeballs.
Stare at the sun.
Didn't expect it to be you.
You hid well.
Figured it out?
As you wish.
Go, look directly at the sun.
Don't close your eyes
Keep watching until you cry
Come on, let's begin
Everyone come to Xinjiang together
I came alone
Two people came
Three people came
Four people came
Hani Kezi
You, go get a stool
Come sit here
Go sit over there
Keep your eyes open and look up
Keep your eyes open and look
Look upward
This is too harsh
If you don't shed tears, you can't come back
Familiar, isn't it? Xinjiang's sun
You're quite familiar with it
It looks so unfamiliar to me
No, I've never looked at it like this before
Come on
Brother Bing goes first
Okay
Let's tour Xinjiang together
One person came
Two people came
Three people came
Four people came
Five people came
Six people came
Everyone must stand
Five, four, three, two, one
Where's six?
Where are the six people?
That was Fan Chengcheng's mistake
Go see the sun
The four of us
Just the four of us
We four are the quick ones
Brother Yi starts
Count to four, back to three
What was the phrase again?
Everyone come to Xinjiang together
Came alone
Came as a pair
Came as three
Came as four
Daxi, come see the sunrise too
Hurry up
No space left
Second row
Second row needs to be higher
Then the sun won't hit our faces
That's enough
Me? I'm a gaming wasteland.
Yet somehow I made it to the end, look at this.
Never thought I'd make top three.
Should we three keep playing?
No need to continue.
Why not?
We're already in top three.
You two must decide one winner.
It's more intense with two players.
Ready?
Yours.
Go.
Everyone come to Xinjiang together.
I came alone.
We came as two.
We came as three.
Who's wrong?
Let's do it this way.
Let's take it slow.
Who said it first just now?
I came alone.
We came as two.
Turning like this is wrong, senior.
Get out here, you!
Then we came as three.
Then I said we came as two.
So it should be two.
Which means not you.
"Dad."
Aren't these two people?
"Dad," go sunbathe.
Come on.
Don't even give him a chair.
Take off your sunglasses.
Okay.
So blinding.
Then you two play
How do two people play?
Two people is the most intense
Just two people
Then how to play?
How to play?
Everyone come to Xinjiang together
I came alone
Came with someone
Came alone
See? You're wrong
Two people is the most intense
This round is about who gets tired first
Right
Come on
I'll do it, come on
Let's tour Xinjiang together
I came alone
Came with someone
Came alone
I lost
Xiao Bai can still play alone
Came alone
Who's next?
I'll do it myself
Do it myself
I'll prepare food for you
Brother, what's for dinner today?
Today
Braised lamb
Stewed fish head with tofu
Awesome
Main course
I love tofu
Xiao Bai
From those who lost to you
Choose two people
To get the clue cards
Xiao Bai
No
You picked the ones we've been exposed to the longest
Our eyes are already blind
I
No need to pick the longer ones
We can't see anymore
Can't even see the clue cards now
I want to see them duel again as two people
Duel as two people
You must decide on one person
Pairs make the most intense matches
Exactly two people
Brother Bai can still play alone
Brother Bai
Choose two people
Go get the clue card
Me, Brother Bai
Pick those of us who’ve been waiting longer
Brother Bai
Starting with Brother Teng
Turn like this
Okay
Come
From one to five
From five back to one
Good
Let's go
Let's all tour Xinjiang together
I came alone
Two people came
Three people came
Four people came
No need.
When I saw he wasn't standing, I stood up.
Then you're wrong too.
Wrong.
Should I have stood up?
I came alone.
But I didn't stand.
Even if he stood, it's still wrong.
Him standing was also wrong.
He shouldn't have stood.
Fine then.
Let's go get that information.
Alright.
Okay?
Let's just stop playing.
What's the matter?
That's not fair
Is it okay?
Alright
Okay
I've seen enough too
Xiao Bai
It's not like this, Xiao Bai
We haven't had our ultimate showdown yet
Let's go
We're aggrieved
Fine
Okay
We'll reluctantly follow you
Go
Can't do it this way
Teacher Bai
Where to?
We'll go one by one
One by one
One at a time
Right
Okay
Then you go first, senior
No
Then I'll go first
I'm afraid you'll regret it later
Hurry up
Quick
It's inside, right?
Yes
Hello, Teacher Dabao
Please sit first
Here
Do you want to ask about my own identity
Or someone else's identity?
So I can only ask one question, right?
Then I'll ask myself.
What is your identity?
This is a very important role.
Black Kite.
A Black Kite is a large eagle.
A bird of prey.
At the top of the food chain.
The ruler of the entire grassland.
We're still arguing here
You three decide again
Still analyzing the situation
Still feeling wronged, these three
Give us some clues
Let's have another round between us three
Even half a clue would do
This is too pitiful
Even one word would help
Let's add one more person
Okay
You start
You decide who in the middle starts
Everyone come to Xinjiang together
I came alone
We came as two
Three of us came
Two people came
Eliminate two
I (won)
She didn't stand
It's her
She should stand
Ultimate showdown
I'll let you go first
You start first
I came alone
Two people came
One person came
The true king
No
You were wrong first
Where is it?
You didn't say
Let's all tour Xinjiang together
This is the truth
Let's have a one-on-one
One-on-one, you in?
Come on
Let's not sit
Come on, like this
Okay
Must do squats
You're still being reasonable
I've been squatting for ages
Come on
Come
You go first
Everyone, come to Xinjiang together
I came alone
We came as two
Came alone
We two came together
Came as two
The sound has already gone out
Just the body didn't get up
Then Brother Teng's opportunity
Can be transferred to Chengcheng
We'll still have three people
What?
All for nothing
Went through all that trouble for nothing
I understand
Clue
Great
Congratulations, senior brother
Senior brother, I congratulate you
Okay
Go ahead
You go later
My chance was taken away again
I told you we should go earlier
Delays breed troubles
Who took it away?
We had another round of competition
Don't you know your own skill level?
And you still competed again?
I'm sorry
Straight into the pot, tonight you're dinner.
State your choice.
Your identity.
I want my own.
Your identity is.
Central Asian pit viper.
This species inhabits Central Asia.
An important snake species in Xinjiang.
A nightmare for birds.
Good.
Your identity is.
Nymphalid butterfly.
The nymphalid butterfly preys on dandelions.
They gave me this thing.
Alright, I understand.
But I think the dandelion person.
must be Brother Teng.
Why?
Easy to bully.
Whether flying in the sky or running on the ground
Never mind
What is Brother Teng?
I think he must be a dandelion
Those who know the clues have all fallen silent.
You're at the bottom of the food chain.
The very bottom.
Can you fly?
Now the sun is gone.
Stop pretending.
You've hit the nail on the head, I see.
Now the sun is gone.
Big old eagle.
Look how high it's flying.
There really is.
Everyone.
The first round of habitat competition.
Now officially begins.
There are five tents scattered across the mountains.
These tents will be your habitats.
You need to choose.
And claim one habitat.
Attention.
Each habitat.
Can hold at most two people.
If you happen to choose the same habitat.
As your natural predator.
Then you'll be eliminated.
Xiao Bai won first place.
So Xiao Bai gets to decide the order.
He decides, right?
Alright.
"Dad," go quickly.
I'll go.
Let Chengcheng go.
Let's go.
Hurry up and choose.
Let Brother Teng go.
Alright then.
White Dragon Horse.
Do you want this one?
Are you here?
This is closer.
I don't mind.
Okay.
It's over
Don't even know what I am
Right
Know nothing at all
Hanikezi, you'll be
alone in one tent, right?
Yes
The dandelion should be Brother Teng
Easy to bully
You want to be "eaten" by me, huh?
I want to "eat" you
Do you want to be "eaten" by me?
Do you know your own identity?
I don’t know
Don’t tell me the game will end just like that for him
Brother Bing
Let's choose.
Choose what?
Right now, all five tents are already taken.
You pick one.
Your identity is the Central Asian pit viper.
A nightmare for birds.
Can it fly?
You've hit the nail on the head, it seems.
I'll take a gamble
I'm with my "dad"
That room is full.
Have you two confirmed?
Have you decided?
Confirmed.
Are you sure you won't change this tent?
I can leave now, right?
Has Brother Teng confirmed it?
I'm leaving.
Then I'll follow.
Come
Come over here, Brother
Come on, Tengteng
Brother, get out of here
I'm going to "devour" him
You go now
No, I won't leave
Why should I go?
You go
I'm not leaving
I'll take care of him for you
Don't stop me from finishing him
Our team is full
Sorry
What are you, senior brother?
I definitely won't harm you.
Really?
I have a feeling about us.
We should be poles apart.
Are you sure?
Are you sure it's this tent?
The more they ask like this,
the less there's to worry about.
Right.
With your little tricks.
I confirm.
Little tricks, I'm sure.
Good.
I'm sure, absolutely certain.
Okay.
Who "eats" whom again?
Who does the dandelion "eat" again?
There are seven.
I can't memorize them either.
The smallest is the saprophyte.
Saprophyte.
The largest is the black kite.
The saprophyte "eats" the black kite.
That is to say,
that saprophyte.
When the black kite "dies," the saprophyte
can just
decompose it, right?
Announce it.
Just me and my junior brother left.
The two of us.
Teacher Sha Yi unfortunately met his natural enemy.
Eliminated from the food chain.
I really "ate" my senior brother.
I don't want to "eat" him.
Come here, come to me.
Come here, Tengteng.
I definitely won't harm you.
We should be poles apart.
I don't feel involved at all
I'll go cook
Off to cook
Time to cook
He's a saprophyte
My brother's dignified appearance
Nothing like a saprophyte
Keep it down
They don't know
That's too toxic of you
You're a toxic saprophyte
Caused such a big misunderstanding
Top of the food chain
Not your fault
You really have no info
Don't know
I really have no info
Who was "eating" me again?
Dandelion, stay out of the way
The dandelion "eats" you
Got it
Let's go
Move out
What a mess
Where are you going?
What are you up to?
If that's the case, then I'll go ahead and...
sit with Hanikezi.
What are you?
I've got my eyes on you today.
"Dead" serious staring.
No seats.
Only two seats in this room.
I'll sit on the side.
Sister Xi's spot is empty.
Hani Kezi.
Don't leave, Hani Kezi.
I'll do it. I'll take you on. Come on.
Let's see who's tougher.
Not necessarily, we might...
Brother Bing, sorry about this.
You've met your natural predator.
Eliminated from this food chain.
Brother Bing doesn't even know what he is.
And he's already out.
Go cook something, Brother Bing.
What's it playing at?
Really, I just...
Feel bad for you.
Hurry up and go.
Go ahead.
Played to no avail.
Xiao Bai, what follows is...
The person Brother Bing was going to "eat".
Now it's your turn to "eat" him.
Sister Xi
We both know nothing about this
Should we...
We should be able to coexist peacefully
Really
I think...
Okay
Let them fight it out first
Let's just...
Soak up some sun
Have a little chat
Who do you think resembles a dandelion?
Dandelion
The dandelion face would burst open
Brother Teng
Then it must be Brother Teng
You're coexisting peacefully
Then let's not switch
Let's keep it this way
Yes
How many were eliminated?
Two
That's quite a high elimination rate
Seriously
Logically speaking
There might have been no eliminations
Of course
Alright, let's announce
the results of this round
Our Brother Bing
has been eliminated
You've been eliminated too
First round
Eliminated in the first round
No way
The thing is, I'm confused about being eliminated
I'm really confused about this elimination
I don't know what I was
Nor do I know what he was
Just got a notification
Saying I lost
So I was out
You insisted on sitting with me
I said don't sit together
But you insisted (on sitting together)
(And got) eliminated by me
Alright
Now the other eliminated one
is our Brother Sha
Didn't expect that
I'm at the top of the food chain
What's the scientific name?
Black Kite
I'm at the top of the food chain
Got taken down by saprophytic bacteria
You are the saprophytic bacteria
If he says it, won't I be exposed?
After he says it
Then it's over
You're that saprophytic bacteria
Bro
Bro, I forgot
The game's not over yet
No, he's exposed himself
Then he's in deep trouble later
Everyone will go after him
You won't escape even with wings
It's fine, senior brother
I'll play with them openly
They have real and fake moves against me
Just watch for a while
Who insists on sharing a tent with you
Right
That would actually expose him too
Actually playing this way...
Right, Chengcheng?
Now I'm trying to figure out who the Central Asian viper is
Right?
Play openly, yes
Who is the Central Asian viper
Dash, you saw me
What about me? I...
What did I do? I...
Who was eating saprophytic fungi?
Dandelion
Or maybe dandelion
Is cooking over there
Dandelion is stir-frying right now
Little brother
You can't just focus on dandelions now
Butterflies might also be your natural enemy
Possibly
Big brother can't protect you anymore
Originally I thought
I'd take care of them all for you
Me, such a large raptor
Got corrupted by you
That's about right
Never expected
To let my brother leave hungry
Then what we'll do next
is start the second mini-challenge
Each person represents one cannon
Take turns calling out which cannon aims at which
Mistakes in calling or positioning will eliminate you
The winner gets 50 power points
Alright, I'm Cannon One
Cannon Three
Okay
I'm Third Cannon
You can only be Third Cannon
Let's try one round
My First Cannon targets Fourth Cannon
My Fourth Cannon targets First Cannon
You're not
Your cannon has no recoil at all
Your cannon has no recoil whatsoever
Still want recoil?
My Fourth Cannon targets First Cannon
My First Cannon targets Third Cannon
My Third Cannon targets Fourth Cannon
My Fourth Cannon targets First Cannon
My First Cannon targets Fourth Cannon
My Fourth Cannon
targets Fifth Cannon
My Fifth Cannon targets Sixth Cannon
My Sixth Cannon targets First Cannon
My First Cannon targets Second Cannon
My Second Cannon targets Fourth Cannon
My Fourth Cannon targets First Cannon
My First Cannon targets Fourth Cannon
My Fourth Cannon targets
Got it?
This is too easy
We took one down
Now we know who to target
Okay
Just like before
My first cannon targets the fourth
My fourth cannon targets the first
My fourth cannon targets the fifth
My fifth cannon targets the sixth
My sixth cannon targets the second
My second cannon targets the fourth
My fourth cannon targets the second
My fourth cannon targets the first
My first cannon targets the fourth
My fourth cannon targets the third
My third cannon targets the fourth
My fourth cannon targets the fifth
My fifth cannon targets the first
My first cannon targets
Why are you suddenly aiming at me?
Shouldn't you be aiming at Chengcheng?
Let's all aim at him together.
I really can't find the numbers here.
It's over.
The most competitive shot...
got aimed away.
No, I've even tied my mouth shut.
I got eliminated by the shot.
It's okay.
I won, I'll give that chance to you.
Alright, bro.
There are five people now, right?
Five people now.
Who should start?
My sixth shot aims at the fifth.
My fifth shot aims at the fourth.
My fourth shot aims at the second.
My second shot aims at the fourth.
My fourth shot aims at the third.
My third shot aims at the fourth.
Too hasty
This desire to win
Is a bit too impatient
Rushed it
Come on
Four cannons
Four cannons, come on
My four cannons target two
My four aim at two
What the heck
Chengcheng
Messed up myself
Bring it, baby
Can't afford to miss now
We've already got the card, right?
No
These two going at it is the most fun
is the last remaining winner
Choose two people to bring in
Right
Come on, Three-Five-Six Cannons, go
Then who starts?
Three Cannon
My Three Cannon aims at Five Cannon
My Five Cannon aims at Six Cannon
My Six Cannon aims at Five Cannon
With this kind of speech
How did you end up with just three people left?
Showdown
Another peak showdown
Now it's back to testing stamina
Go
Five Cannon goes first
My Five Cannon aims at Three Cannon
My Three Cannon aims at Five Cannon
Hanikezi messed up first
And messed up three times in a row
Was she just speaking Uyghur?
I was just speaking Uyghur
Say something in Uyghur
Okay
You say it in Uyghur
Xiao Bai says it in Beijing slang
Go
Come
My five cannons target your three
Done
That's it
Xiao Ba
My three cannons target your five
Xiao Ba, you can go faster
Three cannons target five
My three cannons hit your five
Again?
Xiao Ba wins
Xiao Ba did win
I win
Xiao Ba, pick me this time
Xiao Ba wins
Choose Chengcheng
Should we take Hani Kezi along?
Okay, Hani Kezi.
Let's go.
I'll go first.
I think you should go in now.
You know you're doing great.
This is his second time going in.
He can recognize others now.
Right.
It's over.
Xiao Bai.
You shouldn't have let him (go in).
Should've let Sister Xi.
Yes.
Should've let Daxi (go).
Come back.
Come back, yours is invalid now.
It's invalid.
Invalid now.
Come back.
I'm done testing.
Too late.
It's okay.
Let Hani Kezi go.
I'm the only one who doesn't know.
I'll go in and ask you.
Alright.
Then I won't tell you.
What? Calling me?
Nothing.
It's nothing.
Pretending.
No problem.
I want to know mine.
Okay, your identity is...
Dandelion.
Brother Teng.
Okay, got it. Thanks.
What's your identity?
What are you?
What about you?
You what?
Let's compare (ourselves).
What if you're lying to me?
I don't trust you.
I'm Dandelion.
You're Dandelion.
I'm Butterfly.
Okay.
Okay
No one's telling the truth
Let me think first
Now
Brother Sha is the Black Kite
Then Brother Teng is the Saprophyte
Chengcheng should be the Butterfly
I want to ask about Jinchen's
Jinchen's identity is the Mantis
Good
So members
This round our habitats
Have been reduced from five to three
We'll still let the winner decide the order
I'll go later
Brother Teng should go first
Brother Teng, Chengcheng
Dare to stay in a tent with me?
No need
No, you can't handle me anyway
We can only have peace
Is that so?
Hanikezi, go ahead.
I'm going over.
Go ahead.
It's close, I'll stay here.
Did you ask what you are?
No.
Really?
You really don't know?
Run quickly, I'm a dandelion.
Run quickly!
If you're going to be like this,
I'll protect you too.
I'll "eat" your boss.
Alright, I really can't lie.
Seeing you...
Do you know who you are now?
We can go find Tengteng.
Tengteng.
Find Chengcheng.
Really? You're the one who can "eliminate" him.
Great joy!
Or you come here.
What?
You come here.
We two can coexist peacefully.
Right, we two are coexisting peacefully.
Then let's have all three of us together.
You
Xiao Bai
Let me put it this way
Chengcheng sold you out
You gave the opportunity to Chengcheng
Letting him have a second identity
He investigated your
Bai Jingting's identity is the Central Asian pit viper
Okay
Xiao Bai is the Central Asian pit viper
Xiao Bai really is the Central Asian pit viper
I investigated him
You need to "eliminate" him
Did you really investigate
Are you tricking me?
I'd be a dog if I'm lying, absolutely not tricking you
Let's talk about Chengcheng
Xiao Bai is the Central Asian pit viper
Now the viper needs to eliminate the mantis
I can only "eliminate" the dandelion
These two are a bit unclear
What can my skill card do?
In the next phase
You can designate one member
To get their clue
Then I'll use it
I want to ask about Jin Chen's identity
Jin Chen's identity is the mantis
You see
Then Hanikezi must be the dandelion
Alright
Do you know what you are?
I know
She can "eliminate" me
You're the dandelion
Then why don't you eliminate him?
He eliminated you
Then I'll eliminate him
So we're playing with open cards now?
What am I?
You're a mantis.
Go "get" Chengcheng.
You'll win if you "get" Chengcheng.
Make him expose me.
Go.
This is hail.
Big hailstones.
Hurry.
What are you doing here?
You betrayed me, Fan Chengcheng.
The three of us are stuck here.
Then I'll switch.
It can't be the rain trapping me here.
Locked you up as your food.
You're about to be "eaten" by me.
We're here because of the heavy rain.
We're not sure about that.
Let me tell you
If you dare come in, I'll go out
Then I'll leave
You're leaving?
Yes, once I'm gone
No one will protect you, right?
It's fine, if he dares come in
I'll go find Sister Xi
You "run for your life" then
Where's Xiao Bai?
Over there
Xiao Bai
Big brother's here, Xiao Bai
I'm leaving
Big brother's here
Gone
Where are you going, Xiao Bai?
Xiao Bai
Why did you come back?
Where are you going, Xiao Bai?
Xiao Bai
Little did they know at that moment
They would meet again
Where are you going, Xiao Bai?
Don't come any closer
I'll wait until you're exhausted, Xiao Bai
The three of us together are safe
We can't coexist - he'll "consume" me
All four are outside
I won't go in then
Brother Teng, let's three enter this room
Then you'll "consume" her
He'll win alone by "consuming" me
That's not it
What should we do then?
As you can see,
in any ecosystem,
various food chains always work together.
Between them,
there is mutual promotion
and mutual restriction.
The loss of any link in the food chain
will affect the entire ecosystem
and cause
a chain reaction of ecological disasters.
Therefore, maintaining nature's balance
is the true law of natural survival.
Brother Bing, be careful
Protect the vegetables
Keep it up
You've worked hard
Come out
Are you tired, Bing?
You two are being a bit fake
Has it stopped outside?
Let's go check outside.
I'll help Brother Bing cook.
You handle this part.
Almost done, right Bing?
I'll make the fried egg sauce.
I'll start cooking too.
Brother.
Is it still edible?
Will it still be edible?
You're underestimating me.
I might be even more popular than this.
I'll use the last two episodes to "take down" my brother.
Everyone's cooking now.
Then you work hard.
No problem.
I'm going in.
Go in.
I want to share the stage with him.
Compete on the same stage.
Stir-fried instant noodles.
What if there's not enough noodles?
It's enough, definitely enough.
One pack is sufficient.
Impossible
One more, the last one
Four packs
Why hasn't my water boiled yet?
Who can't make some noise
We need to start shouting
What's wrong with my fire
His sauce is a bit too fragrant
A little
Right in front of me
Like a show of dominance
Those two dishes are ready
Finish them quickly
I'll crack an egg
I've been practicing cracking eggs at home these past few days
Exactly
Brother Bai is still working on it
Let's eat first
Okay, go ahead and eat, brother
We won't wait for you
Okay
The big fish is here
Thanks for your hard work
What's up? Ice
What kind of guests are coming over like this?
Let's have some
A whole eggplant, this guy
Absolutely solid
I'll have a piece of eggplant too
Let's have some tofu
This time with the noodles
This time it's good
This time it's really good
Super delicious
Because the flavors have soaked in
Delicious
So tasty
Where's Chengcheng?
Turn off the heat
Can't lift it
Too heavy to carry
Add oil
Add eggs
Okay, let me check the ingredients
One spoon of light soy sauce
Half a spoon of dark soy sauce
One spoon of oyster sauce
One spoon of chili sauce
Half a spoon of sugar
I saw Brother doing it like this earlier
Take a bite
No, it's a bit bland.
Too much sugar
Add some salt
It smells so good
So beautiful
Chengcheng
Why are there other dishes?
Cover the spicy chicken.
I'll join in.
I'll join in too.
I don't eat that stuff.
See, young people love eating this.
No.
Not bad.
That's the idea.
Noodles.
Is it okay?
It's fine.
The instant noodles are good.
Selling it myself.
Let me try.
Here, Brother.
Let me have a bite.
No need to bring it all over.
This instant noodles has quite a lot of ingredients
There's even egg
Not bad
Brother Sha Yi
First time trying Brother Bing's cooking
Give us your review
This isn't my first time
He's definitely not a first-timer
He's had it many times in Beijing
He eats it often
Averages about ten days a year
Really?
About that
More or less
I've had his dumplings and buns too
I've tried all his signature dishes
Eat from two bowls alternately
Who's next?
Your chopstick portion is all gone.
Who else is coming?
Then it's not my fault.
The noodles are just this long.
Yes.
I can't take it anymore
My belt
is starting to feel tight
I've been eating too well these past two days
Xinjiang cuisine is truly delicious
just a bit too much sugar and oil
At my age, it's hard to handle
Don't we need
some Shuhua Antangjian?
With its
corn silk and mulberry leaves
it slows sugar absorption while eating
We definitely need some
After drinking it, we can eat without worry
What are we doing tomorrow?
We're going there tomorrow.
The lake.
You can go boating.
Or try skydiving.
You're scared of this?
Paragliding is fun.
Would you dare try it, bro?
Right, you're fearless.
Nothing scares me.
I'll try anything once.
Do you use a parachute for paragliding, bro?
Gliding.
Come on.
Now that everyone's eaten and drunk their fill,
let's announce the energy levels.
Brother Bai has 200.
Everyone else has 100.
Let's congratulate
Brother Bai as today's Energy King!
Energy King again?
Your Energy King badge.
We're so jealous it "kills" us
Envious
This game
"Lady Luck" is chasing Brother Bai
Well then today
We used the duration of one mission
to experience and simulate
the rise and fall of a food chain
We hope through today's program
everyone can understand that all nature's creatures
none can be missing
Just like our expedition team members
If one is missing
we wouldn't have this current happiness
Yes
Finally let us
thank Hanikezi for four days of companionship
Thank you
Our Xinjiang has many
many beautiful places
These mountains, these plants
are truly beautiful
So lovely
I'm home
Fully recharged
In this environment
it's like being recharged
Brother
That direct feeling
is hard to put into words
So wonderful, so blissful
So happy
Are you okay?
Hanikezi
Right now
let's go
Beautiful
So beautiful
Glacier
This feeling is truly breathtaking
Snow-capped mountains in September
Welcome two new friends
Thank you
Thanks
Thank you everyone
Dance version of "Werewolf"
Pretending to wander here
He doesn't even know what this is
Which tooth is stuck?
Molar tooth
Of course
Do you admit it or not?
Your head is full of hair extensions now
Naturally
Will you admit it?
You have the best body among male artists
Absolutely
You two wouldn't be taking the act too seriously, would you?
Too ruthless
Fan Chengcheng's limits
Meaning he has no limits
Grab the sandbag
Let's let them go first
Okay
Brother Bing
Isn't he your beloved Brother Teng anymore?
Give it to Xiao Bai, good
Hit
Is this "Three Heroes Fight Lü Bu"?
Give it to Xiao Bai, good, quick
Too amazing
Handsome, handsome, handsome
Hit, hit, hit
Xiao Bai Alliance
Attack Brother Bing first
Lucky "Power Shop"
Eight people submitted power values
between 27 and 35
Submitted power will be doubled
More contributions mean more winnings doubled
If everyone thinks this way, we're doomed
How many did you actually submit?
He's muddying the waters here
Really didn't
What's this?
Go ahead, read it
Deep in the forest lived a veterinarian's family
The vet is Brother Teng
On his way home
the vet found an injured man
The vet took him home
This man was Fan Chengcheng
Brother Teng met Fan Chengcheng on the road
and could bring him home
I think
The big wolf is me
The second wolf is Bing
The third wolf is Xiaobai
poured poisoned mutton into
the first prince's pot
First prince
Who did the first prince bother?
The second prince deeply loved the little white lamb
But the little white lamb was
his brother's killer's daughter
He was in a dilemma
The third prince liked the little white lamb
He was in a triple dilemma
The leader was in a dilemma
So difficult
It's even harder for me
The "assassin" man
turned out to be her ideal type
Scene one, take one
Ready to start
Which actor is blocking the way?
Leader, eat the grapes. Leader!
The leader really doesn’t want to eat grapes anymore.
Brother Teng, get ready—watch him.
It's him
Cut! Great performance
Amazing
We've wrapped up filming