♫ Chasing wind, I set out afar ♫
♫ The road ahead lost, my voice unheard ♫
♫ I've tasted joy and sorrow ♫
♫ Laying low, I plan every move ♫
♫ With a mortal heart and lingering ties ♫
♫ I'm roaming far and wide ♫
♫ A twist of fate in desperate times ♫
♫ A bond that outlives the dust of life ♫
♫ Still chasing what immortality means ♫
♫ Even eternity flashes by in a blink ♫
♫ Don't mock my ordinary life ♫
♫ I fight alone as chaos shakes the world ♫
♫ Don't scorn my humble roots ♫
♫ Kind at heart, ruthless when I must be ♫
♫ Fate stirs with joy and grief beneath ♫
♫ I hold the tide between life and death ♫
♫ Faith carries me through endless dark ♫
♫ And I return with a heart refined ♫
♫ Forged by trial, I rise through three realms ♫
♫ Reborn in the wheel of fate ♫
Violet Monkey Blossom.
Celestial Essence Fruit.
Jade Marrow Mushroom.
Being born to a prestigious clan
sure is a privilege.
While Senior Chen failed to get anything
in the Bloody Trial Ground,
she nonetheless obtained two Foundation Pills
thanks to her family.
For those who were born to cultivate,
two pills will probably suffice.
But knowing my lack of talent,
I need more than ten Foundation Pills
to even stand a chance.
It works!
The quality is good too.
♫ That day I first saw you... ♫
Right.
♫ We made a promise to reunite ♫
♫ And walked into the unknown ♫
♫ But now that we've met again... ♫
♫ Only silence fills the space
as we lock eyes... ♫
Let me try two first.
♫ With no way to know when we'll return... ♫
These pills are too intense.
♫ So be it, I set myself free ♫
♫ To be one who stands tall
between heaven and earth ♫
♫ Never let yourself become a hollow husk
of what you once were ♫
♫ The ones before once told me ♫
♫ There's still hardship ahead... ♫
How long has it been?
♫ Even though it mocks loudly ♫
♫ We're just fleeting mortals ♫
♫ Time slipped by before we knew... ♫
I feel warm.
Is it the residual effect from the pills?
♫ Into this starry sky ♫
♫ Starlight fades into the Milky Way ♫
♫ While the mayfly dies in the whirlpool... ♫
Again.
♫ Playing the fleeting game of life ♫
♫ Each step of fate's game unclear... ♫
To build a foundation
is to shed your skin,
to rearrange your physique,
and to condense qi into liquid.
♫ Through all the joy and sorrow ♫
♫ How do I choose the way... ♫
This hurts so much!
Yan Ru Yan, I invested so much to achieve this.
Don't you let me down now.
Elder Liu.
- My Lord.
- You came at the right time.
His technique works wonders on Yan.
He said he could wake Yan up
if I promised him one thing.
What does he want?
- He wants Yan to be his wife.
- No. You cannot trust him.
Let alone let him marry your daughter.
Elder Liu, what do you mean?
You brought him here, didn't you?
May we speak privately?
I just saw the technique he used to heal Miss Yan.
It is an evil art that absorbs others' power.
Not only is it against nature,
but it might bring about dire consequences too.
Enough.
I've always respected your advice, but this time,
he's my only choice.
My Lord!
That man merely saw Young Lady once
and decided to marry her.
He's extorting you.
I'm sure he wants more out of our clan.
Please think twice, My Lord.
Elder Liu, do you think I'm sacrificing
our clan to save Yan?
On the contrary,
I'm trying to save our clan's future.
What holds the Seven Sects together
is not the disciples or various resources,
but the elusive Nascent Soul Stage elders.
Everything below the Nascent Soul Stage
is as puny as ants.
Yan is bestowed with the heavenly spirit root.
She is the only one in our clan
who can possibly attain the Nascent Soul Stage.
She is our only hope
to leverage against the Seven Sects.
Elder Liu, surely you know about this.
If you've made up your mind,
there's no need for me to convince you otherwise.
But please give me some time
to investigate his background with others.
Even commoners ask about the groom's family
when they marry their daughters off.
Fine.
But Yan doesn't have much time.
Make it quick.
Understood.
Elder Liu.
What do you want exactly?
This isn't what we agreed upon.
What I want isn't important.
What's important is
how we do it.
We had a deal.
I put in good words for you in front of Lord Yan
and you'll pay me 1,000 gems.
You are so eager, aren't you?
I... I just want to know
where my gems are.
Relax.
The gems are ready.
Now that I have the gems, we are even.
I'll leave the Yan Clan Stronghold now.
I have nothing to do with what you do here.
Wait.
Why the hurry?
Are you going
to snitch me out to the other sects?
My Lord, Elder Liu hasn't returned after he left
to meet the target.
I fear the worst has happened.
I see.
You're dismissed.
- My Lord, should I...
- Just go.
Come out already.
Your reputation precedes you, Lord Yan.
As expected of the only Core Formation
Stage cultivator of your clan in the last century.
Your spirit sense is impressive.
Be it treating or betrothing Yan,
they are just your pretexts.
Tell me your real objective.
Lord Yan, do you remember
the promise centuries ago?
Of course.
Were it not for our shared past, do you think
I would still keep you alive now?
You sure are a sentimental person.
In that case, why don't we
continue our shared history
so the Yan Clan can return to its rightful master?
My father is thirsty
for someone powerful like you.
You must be joking.
My clan has settled down in the Yue Kingdom.
We left the Ghost Spirit Sect 300 years ago,
and we don't plan to return.
You're mistaken, Lord Yan.
What I mean is
the Seven Sects have ruled the Yue Kingdom
for long enough.
My sect can help you
become the future ruler of Yue.
When that happens, you won't have to beg
for one spirit herb.
Truth be told,
the Six Demonic Sects have rallied armies
and will attack soon.
The Seven Sects will turn into dust.
Alas, the Yan Clan Stronghold
is located on the border.
It will feel the brunt of the invasion.
What will become of it?
The war hasn't begun.
No one knows who the victor is yet.
Isn't it arrogant of your father
to ask me to take his side now?
Besides, your father has sired many children.
His sister, Hong Fen, is still there.
Do you truly have a say in regards
to your sect's matters?
Lord Yan,
this is both my father's and my wish.
Look.
An exceptionally rare dark spirit root?
Exactly.
Your daughter is born
with the heavenly spirit root.
And I have the dark spirit root.
We make the best pair
to study the Blood Spirit Spell.
And knowing her potential and mine,
we're likely to attain the Nascent Soul Stage,
let alone the Core Formation Stage.
Imagine this.
Your clan will have
two Nascent Soul Stage cultivators.
You will be stronger than the Seven Sects.
Additionally...
Additionally, I promise that our child
will become the successor
of both my sect and your clan.
You come up with this plan yourself?
I will take over my sect.
But I need you as my ally,
more so than my father or Aunt Hong Fen.
I ask for your
cooperation.
Will you swear
a Truedeath Oath with me?
Han Li.
Could it be him?
This is the last pill.
I have to make this work.
By swallowing this golden pill,
I shall defy my predestined fate!
Oh, no.
If I don't put the extra
power within me to use,
my body will be overwhelmed.
Qingyuan Sword Manual!
Did I do it?
I've also reached Tier Four
of the Qingyuan Sword Manual.
Despite my fake spirit root,
I'm now in the Foundation Establishment Stage.
One Foundation Pill left.
Chen Qiao Qian, stop getting distracted.
You can't let your family down again.
I can't stand it anymore.
- What's wrong?
- What's the matter?
I'm sick of it.
I know. He's sick of you.
Me? What did I do?
All you do is stare at the sky
in hopes that Xuan Er will appear.
Pot calling the kettle black.
You keep staring at Senior Liu too.
No, I didn't.
What's so good about dating anyway?
You might as well use the time to cultivate.
Look over there.
It seems our sect has one more...
No. Two more Foundation
Establishment Stage cultivators.
Wonderful!
Mentor Xu.
I saw a column of light here just now.
Did someone reach the Foundation
Establishment Stage as well?
Han Li did it.
Who would have thought?
He and his fake spirit root
have proved so many people wrong.
Where is he now?
He just left.
You arrived a second too late.
He is... You're just as impatient as he is.
Han Li!
Han.
- Wait.
- Senior Chen?
Han.
Congratulations. You have reached
the Foundation Establishment Stage.
Likewise.
You saved me that day, didn't you?
What do you mean?
You killed Senior Lu
before the Bloody Trial Ground.
Quit joking around, Senior Chen.
Senior Lu is an excellent
Qi Refining Stage cultivator.
I am not strong enough to kill him.
But you escaped the dangerous
Bloody Trial Ground unscathed.
Grandmaster Li even took you in as his disciple.
It was just a stroke of luck.
I have things to do. Farewell.
Why won't you admit that you saved me?
I should have given her more Oblivion Pills.
I know it was you even if you don't admit it.
Can you feel it?
Do you know I'm performing cupping on your back?
It will remove the cold energy
and the bad energy from you.
All of it.
You're not doing it properly.
I don't think Han Li did this
when he was helping me.
If you're this good, do it yourself.
If I can do it myself, I won't ask you for help.
Mentor Ma.
Mentor Wu.
You've attained
the Foundation Establishment Stage?
Not too shabby.
You've attained
the Foundation Establishment Stage.
Nice one.
It's all thanks to you, Mentor Ma.
I wouldn't have achieved what I did
had you not let me tend to this garden.
Then, you should address me differently now.
Call me Senior Ma.
Now that you're
in the Foundation Establishment Stage,
my garden is of no use to you.
Pack up and find your master now.
Go.
Go now.
Make haste.
♫ The ripples disappear into the river ♫
♫ My robe is soaked under the drizzle ♫
♫ I drink alone
as the moonlight melts with the liquor ♫
♫ The current flows swiftly,
the mountains weigh heavily... ♫
They say you see things differently
once you're in the Foundation Establishment Stage.
But all I see are familiar scenes.
♫ The breeze brushes through the corridor ♫
♫ As the swallows whisper overhead ♫
♫ The setting sun graces the bamboo forest
for whom do I harmonize? ♫
♫ Leaning against the rails,
water ripples below me ♫
♫ The wind whispers to the forest ♫
♫ I wander into the dream
under the clear galaxy... ♫
I won't forget you, Herbs Garden.
Just go!
♫ This journey that spans across the universe ♫
♫ Feels both familiar and unfamiliar ♫
♫ Looking at the various faces of our world ♫
♫ Each word, each utterance ♫
♫ Carries the hopes of a lifetime... ♫
Come up.
You can't bring those weary eyes of yours.
Present yourself properly.
Again.
Come up.
Greetings, I am Han Li.
You're greeting your master. You have to kneel.
All right. Get up.
Thanks, Master.
As per our tradition, before Master takes you in,
I have to give you a test.
I am but an average disciple.
I ask for your leniency.
Relax.
It's just a simple test.
If you can understand my flute notes,
I consider you passed.
Close your eyes.
Open your eyes.
What did you hear?
Silence speaks louder than words.
You passed. In the Foundation Establishment Stage,
you will be able to sense the power in all beings.
It's as if you have one more sense
on top of your five senses.
Do not forget this.
Thank you, Senior.
My turn now.
Remove the bird's ability to fly
without hurting it.
Then, you'll pass.
How kind of you, Senior.
You wanted me to help you
free a trapped bird, right?
Yes.
Since Senior Liu approves of you,
I consider you passed.
All right. It's my turn now.
Dodge all three of my sand pouches.
Then, you'll pass.
Here I go.
Good.
You passed.
Listen up.
Cultivation is important.
But don't forget to train your body as well.
If you live a long life and don't move a lot,
you're no different from a tortoise.
It's my turn now.
- Enough, Wu Xuan.
- No. He's better than this.
Tier Four?
Upon reaching Tier Four
of the Qingyuan Sword Manual,
you can guard against blades automatically.
The manual states that when attacked,
the shield will block any blades.
You've reached Tier Four of the manual?
Don't you know you should stop at Tier Three?
Did you feel something off
when you were cultivating?
My progress slows down a lot at Tier Four.
After a while, the spirit power I gathered
will slowly disappear.
It's the dissipation.
Dissipation?
Upon reaching Tier Four
of the Qingyuan Sword Manual,
your power dissipates every few days.
But Master didn't tell me about this
when he taught me.
Calm down, Han.
At Tier Four, only 1/10 of your power
will dissipate.
At Tier Five, another 1/10 of your power
That's too much.
I trained so hard to reach Tier Four
just for it to backfire on me?
It is a flawed but unique technique.
I was told that each tier you reached
would expand your Meridian system
and deepen your energy pool.
You will have much more power reserve
than your peers.
That's right.
Perhaps this is why your power dissipates.
Unfortunately, the manual we have is incomplete.
The sect only possesses
the first nine tiers of the manual.
What do I do?
Master, Han Li is here.
He is?
Right away. I'm coming.
Give me a moment.
Greetings, Master.
Forget it.
At ease.
It's a hassle. Just get up.
As cultivators, we seek simplicity.
From now on, you are my disciple.
Cultivate diligently from now on.
Don't bring dishonor to my name.
Yes, Master.
You see, cultivation
is a way to defy your destiny.
Look at yourself.
The Foundation Pill has transformed your body.
You no longer possess a mortal body.
But to go further, you must train your mind too
in order to complete your internal
and external transformation.
Do enlighten me.
Mortals have desires.
Therefore, they have obsessions.
When you are obsessed, it'll affect your progress.
You'll hit a bottleneck
as it turns into your inner demon.
In serious cases, you might lose your progress
or your life.
Master, do you mean we should forsake our desires?
Not at all.
See? I knew you would think that way.
You're wrong.
Cultivation is about easement.
To forsake all desires is to go against
the purpose of cultivation.
But true easement is hard to achieve.
Therefore, I ask my disciples
to accept all outcomes with grace.
Accept your failures and
you make peace with yourself.
Make peace with yourself?
This is very important.
Make peace with yourself.
Ask your seniors.
I became the top Core Formation Stage cultivator
in our sect thanks to this philosophy.
Greetings, Grandmaster Hong Fu.
Hong Fu.
Well, I meant to say
the top male Core Formation Stage cultivator.
I need to borrow your master for some quick words.
But carry on. I can wait.
We're done.
Han Li, you're now
in the Foundation Establishment Stage.
You can have your own cavern.
Show him where to get the map
to the back of the mountain
as well as the array for the cavern.
Go now.
- Yes, Master.
Hong Fu, just some quick words?
It could be more.
- Well, you...
- Farewell, Master.
- Go.
- Farewell, Grandmaster.
You're so long-winded.
Just go already.
Farewell.
That silly kid.
Go ahead.
The Clear Void Sect brought us some news.
Fu Yun Zi conducted an investigation for a year.
He reported that half of the surviving disciples
in the Trial Ground
said that Spirit Beast Mountain was fishy.
300 years ago, that sect split from
the Beast Taming Sect of the Six Demonic Sects.
It's not a stretch to think
that they are consorting with the demonic sects.
Remember who suggested that we changed
the opening date of the Trial Ground?
And who insisted that
they knew where the demonic sects were?
The Beast Taming Sect.
I remember that.
You know what? There's no use speculating.
Bring them over and interrogate them.
All right.
I'll be leaving, then.
You're leaving?
So that's all.
I rehearsed my greetings so many times
only for it to end so abruptly.
Can I trust this master of mine?
He doesn't look like someone enlightened.
Making peace with yourself.
What does that even mean?
Han, stop ruminating.
Making peace with yourself
is not something you get
by thinking very hard about it.
Master was very cryptic about it.
Would you care to explain to me?
Obsessions can be huge or small.
We want different things,
so we each have different obsessions.
Oh.
For Senior Liu, his obsession
is to kill all evil perpetrators.
Wu Xuan's obsession is Xuan Er.
- Wei Niang's obsession is...
- Shut your mouth.
My obsession is to have a real fight with you.
Senior Song, you know I can't defeat you.
Work hard then.
I'll be waiting.
Han, there's no need to obsess over it.
Making peace with yourself
is easier said than done.
Look at our master.
Grandmaster Hong Fu came and was like,
"I need to borrow your master
for some quick words."
Just some quick words?
You silly kid.
You're so long-winded.
Just go already.
Just go!
- We're talking about you.
- You weren't aware?
If you get easily distracted in your progress,
how can you achieve true peace?
Congratulations, Wan.
You have returned to the Core Formation Stage.
I've nonetheless lost a lot of progress.
It's all that fool's fault.
Who?
I was asking if our disciples
have been cultivating properly or not.
Wan, I've had a feeling that
something is on your mind
after you left the Bloody Trial Ground.
Tell me already.
What exactly happened there?
My name is Han Li.
Shoo.
Shoo?
No.
I mean the sun.
The sun is bright today.
You... Since you care so much about our sect,
tend to those pending tasks accumulated
while you were cultivating in solitude.
You just returned to the Core Formation Stage.
Your mind is still clamoring.
We don't want any inner demon now, do we?
Anyway, I was expecting you.
Thanks to the Green Vial,
I have an abundance of pills.
But the dissipation of my power is an issue.
They also said I could have my own cavern.
How do I do that?
Perhaps I should ask Mentor Wu.
I'm so pissed.
If I don't get rid of Han Li,
I'll have an inner demon sooner or later.
Grandmaster.
Yes?
Yellow Maple Valley sent us a jade scroll.
Cultivator Li Hua Yuan
invites all Core Formation Stage cultivators
of the Seven Sects to discuss a strategy.
Got it.
What strategy?
He just wants someone to play mahjong with him.
But I do like the food there.
All right.
This can be my excuse.
My senior can't stop me.
And it's not about the food too.
I can use this visit
to check if that he told anyone or not.
If he did, I'd make him pay.
I need to kill him sooner or later.
Mentor Wu.
Just call me Senior Wu.
I'm used to it already.
You taught me so many things
when I first came here.
If you hadn't done that,
I wouldn't have been able
to enter the Bloody Trial Ground.
Allow me to keep this appellation, Mentor Wu.
It doesn't matter anyway.
I saw you studying mugwort therapy
in Herbs Garden last time.
These two vials can help
reduce the foul energy on you.
It's more convenient too.
Just let me know
if you want to steam some mugwort.
Thanks.
It's very considerate of you.
Oh.
Have you found a place for your cavern?
The array we distribute barely suffice.
You need to pull some tricks.
That said, I can't help you in this regard.
Head to Treasure House to find a spirit beast.
A spirit beast?
It can help you.
Wise choice, Mr. Li.
This is a Treasure-Hunting Mouse
that reached Grade Two recently.
It can find herbs, steal gems,
and even locate a secret realm.
Locate a secret realm?
How much for it?
A lot.
I'll take it.
Come.
This is a lot.
♫ Shards of dreams inside a dream ♫
♫ A pale moon falls into mirrored skies ♫
♫ Years slipped by as I lingered on ♫
♫ Old scenes rise again ♫
♫ Too hard to forget ♫
♫ Easier just to miss ♫
♫ They say the past fades like smoke ♫
♫ But looking back still stirs the ache ♫
♫ This noisy world, this lonely page ♫
♫ Swept away by time ♫
♫ Eyes once looked far ♫
♫ Now lost in the shift ♫
♫ Autumn winds stir ♫
♫ Smoke curls once more ♫
♫ Like clouds on the edge of sky ♫
♫ Returning to my eyes ♫
♫ Looking back from the mountaintop ♫
♫ Time lost its name ♫
♫ Was it yesterday ♫
♫ Or tomorrow? ♫
♫ The world has changed ♫
♫ Beyond recall ♫
♫ Time will fade ♫
♫ All the words ever spoken ♫
♫ Only this longing remains ♫
♫ Crossing centuries and days ♫
♫ In a fleeting moment ♫
♫ we call eternity ♫
♫ called eternity ♫