(Acceptance email from a foreign company)
What should I tell Sunbae?
Ian, what are you doing?
What are you hiding?
Ah...
It's nothing.
You're acting a bit strange lately.
Trying to gloss it over with cuteness?
If you noticed, just pretend you didn't.
I can handle things like that well... I'm just worried.
I haven't sorted out my thoughts yet.
I'll tell you when I'm ready.
Alright.
There's still so much I want to do with Sunbae.
I want to keep being with him like this...
Sunbae probably feels the same way...
What should I do?
You're okay, right?
Yes, really! I'm fine.
Maybe because my past sins are so great...
Even if your expression changes slightly, Ian,
I get worried.
You were still worrying about that?
Of course I am.
When you were struggling with job hunting,
instead of comforting you,
I treated you coldly.
Hmm...
Did you?
I forgot everything, I don't remember a thing.
That's why
when you look even a little bit troubled,
I feel worse and get more concerned.
Ian?
What do I do? I like you even more now, Hyung.
Then just like me more.
It's almost our 1st anniversary. What shall we do?
Well...
Isn't there anything you wanted to do?
Since it's your first relationship.
I told you not to say that.
Your reaction is so cute,
I can't help but want to do it.
Ah, forget it.
Since it's your first, I want to make it extra special.
I want you to do everything you've wanted to do.
Mr. Ian?
Are you asleep?
Goodnight.
I was also looking forward to a special 1st anniversary with Sunbae...
Sunbae, should I just not leave?
Should I just give up everything and stay by your side?
I said I'd wait until you tell me, but...
what kind of worry is it that you can't even speak about it?
Was this what you were worried about?
(Juhyeok Hyung)
(I finish early today. Want to grab a beer?)
Did he notice?
Did I make it too obvious?
I haven't even organized what to say yet...
I used to come here often alone.
Alone?
Yeah.
When I had a lot on my mind.
Back when I couldn't convey my true feelings to you.
I drank here alone frequently.
Did coming here solve things?
Didn't you just get drunk?
Hmm...
Since I came here out of habit,
it was good for clearing my head.
The day you first asked to meet me,
I sat here alone and worried about it too.
So we were able to meet thanks to this place.
Right?
Then, today as well...
did you bring me here to organize my thoughts?
Well, partly that, and...
I was thinking about where you could speak comfortably,
and this was the result.
Ian.
Don't you have something to tell me?