♪Trap my frame♪
♪Plagues demand I bow in shame♪
♪Snare my soul♪
♪Rules command I swallow my pride♪
♪Mock my way♪
♪Chained me where I must stay♪
♪Taught me to kneel, not to speak♪
♪And to let my life pass by in silence♪
♪But I heard the wind♪
♪From the sea and the sky♪
♪It said don't bend♪
♪Bow your head, and your chains begin♪
♪You are the wave♪
♪And the wind that won't behave♪
♪How could you be chained?♪
♪Untamed, uncaged, unclaimed♪
♪You're the blade in my gaze♪
♪This world will leave you no space♪
♪Then pierce it with your blaze♪
♪My silent grind♪
♪My aching pain♪
♪Will one day turn...♪
♪I am who I am♪
♪My greatest ambition♪
♪If the world can't contain me♪
♪Then I'll break through it♪
♪Become who I am♪
[Wild Ambition Bloom]
[Adapted from Stone and Water's novel,
The Uncaged Flame]
[Episode 25]
If I bump into him again,
could you keep playing along?
No way. Count me out.
I've got standards.
I'm only using you as a cover.
It's not like we're actually together.
I won't fake a relationship
at the cost of my reputation.
Besides,
playing your fiancé is seriously risky.
You said it like it was no big deal,
and I almost died.
Zhiqiu, please help me.
So what's in it for me?
What do you want?
Next month,
change the packaging of Hugu Pill.
Okay.
You'll be
in charge of Xia Yuan's election
as guild president.
No problem.
Also,
show a little more respect.
Stop flipping out over everything.
After all, I'm the boss.
Okay, boss.
I'll try not to lose it again.
Alright.
That's it.
Really?
Thank you, Zhiqiu.
Wait, you're kind of off today.
You're one to talk.
You're back.
I was wondering
why the door was left open.
Why are you here?
Been waiting on you.
How was your day?
Well. It was good.
Guess who I saw?
Who?
Xia Chu.
Didn't he go to France?
He's back.
And he showed up...
with his girlfriend.
He has a girlfriend?
They're a good match,
and they seem happy.
Maybe this is how it was meant to end.
Alright.
What about Wen Zhiqiu?
I met him too.
Did he tell you?
He told you too?
Of course, I had to know.
Yes.
How did you respond?
Nothing special.
I think his idea is very good.
And then?
Elaborate further.
Then...
I'll work harder.
What exactly
did Wen Zhiqiu tell you?
The prospects of Wen's Pharmacy.
And then? That's it?
What else could there be?
Guess this is the best I could hope for.
I feel so fortunate
to have you as a friend,
to be building my own career,
and to work with Wen Zhiqiu.
[Blue Stone Apartment]
Sir, we're here.
Here, thank you.
Thank you, sir.
Wen Zhiqiu.
Why are you here?
Thought you could use some comfort.
You should...
congratulate me.
Be careful.
I'm Chu Shaohua's fiancé.
Shaohua told me everything.
Xia Chu is back.
You didn't confess to her.
After everything you did,
why not fight for what you want?
You know what she's like.
She has always been...
so composed,
clear-minded...
and...
razor-sharp.
Yes.
Like a blade.
A blade of ice.
But today, the frost in her eyes
began to melt.
And the heat she'd buried
for so long started to rise.
I always thought
we were two souls in love,
growing side by side.
I thought I knew her.
But that's not what she needed.
What she needed...
was to feel the spark again.
So, are you going to light it,
or back down when things get hard?
I'm going to find the fire.
Right?
Love never plays
by the rules.
Hold this for me.
You're the expert in love, aren't you?
Alright, stop making fun of me.
Where are they?
Check these out.
I carved them myself.
That is
Chichun Apothecary.
[Chichun Apothecary]
[Wen and Chu's Residence]
This one,
and our...
Shaohua told me very seriously
that you're a good partner to her.
I'm going up.
Do you get what I meant?
You mean more than you realize.
[Chichun Apothecary]
[Wen and Chu's Residence]
♪Strayed from the path,
ask who turns away♪
♪Keep silent to try to forget,
yet it clings to memory♪
♪Even good medicine can't heal the soul♪
♪The machinations of my conscience
drive me into perdition♪
♪Let my breath run ragged, run ragged♪
♪Lost in love,
how could I ever fool myself again?♪
Shaohua,
let's take Xuan to France!
You both
deserve a broader world.
♪When walking towards the same thorns♪
Three days later,
let's meet at the crossroads.
Wait for me.
I'll wait for you.
♪Like a fish stranded on land,
you stay silent♪
♪For you, I dive deep beneath the sea♪
♪If I had once surrendered to destiny♪
♪Then meeting you
was always meant to be♪
♪How can I leave you?♪
♪A lifelong riddle with no answers♪
[Wen and Chu's Residence]
♪Today I see through
fate's cunning trick♪
♪Yet I decree your presence
written in my stars♪
[Wen's Pharmacy]
Good morning.
Good morning,
my dear fiancée.
Let's be clear.
I'm only your fiancée
on rare occasions.
Any chance we can make it more regular?
No.
Why?
I'm afraid
it might harm your reputation.
Now I don't even care about my life,
so reputation? Please.
Dying's no big deal,
but losing face is catastrophic.
So now you understand that.
I'm being serious.
We need to talk
about something important.
Among the members of the TCM Guild,
Mr. Tian still holds
the highest approval rating,
at 30%,
while Mr. Xia trails behind
with just 20% support.
What about the other 50%?
Wen's Pharmacy.
Mr. Xia.
I'll discuss this with Shaohua.
Understood.
Okay, I'll get back to you later.
Mr. Xia came to us for help.
Help with what?
He said that three months ago,
through Mr. Lu's connections,
he managed to get
a batch of anti-epidemic powder
added to the procurement list
of the Zhejiang-Shanghai Allied Forces.
But less than a month later,
the allied forces were defeated.
Now there's no way to sell that batch.
So he's asking us for help.
How big is the batch?
Half a million boxes.
If we help him distribute them,
we can sell 300 boxes a month at most.
Even with all the branches
of Jujing Apothecary,
selling 500,000 boxes
would take 20 years.
But if over 300 pharmacies in Shanghai
joined in,
they could clear the whole batch
in just six months.
The only reason they'd help
is if there's a significant profit
to be made.
The only option now
is to offload it at a loss.
Okay then, help me figure out
what kind of loss we're looking at.
Since it's a loss anyway,
make it a complete one.
[Jujing Apothecary]
Give them away for free?
Yes.
There are 500,000 blue-collar workers
in Shanghai.
One box per person would be perfect.
Do you have any idea
what 500,000 boxes
of anti-epidemic powder
are worth?
A hundred thousand silver dollars,
but your cost is only 30,000.
"Only"?
That's a pretty bold claim.
Or there's another way.
Based on our numbers,
if we bring the ex-factory price
down to five wen,
and set the retail price at forty,
more than 300 pharmacies across Shanghai
would be willing to help distribute it.
Customers will be willing to buy,
and we can sell out
within two months.
Wouldn't that mean a loss?
Twenty-eight thousand silver dollars.
That's a steep hit, don't you think?
No.
Absolutely not.
We have no choice.
I think
we should ship all this
to the north of China.
With so many customers
for Shouyuan Apothecary,
selling them shouldn't be a problem.
This batch of anti-epidemic powder
was tailored for Zhejiang.
If we send it up north,
it won't be nearly as effective.
That could damage our reputation.
Maybe we should put it on hold
for now.
Let's talk about the TCM Guild election.
Right now,
half the guild
thinks you're just a northerner
who came to Shanghai
to make a quick buck.
They say you are mercenary
and cold-hearted.
So if we want to change their minds
and turn things around
in a short time,
we'll need to put in real work
to reshape your public image.
I've done a rough estimate of the costs
for reporter interviews,
newspaper and magazine ads,
plus fliers and posters.
Also...
Also, you need to spend more time
connecting with other members
of the TCM Guild.
Altogether, these expenses will come to
around 32,000 silver dollars.
This is just the bare minimum.
Yes.
That much?
We're already spending a fortune
on this.
Selling at a loss isn't an option,
and giving it away? No chance.
No,
we're doing it.
Let's give every last box
to the workers in Shanghai. No charge.
Mr. Xia, should we reconsider...?
Miss Chu,
we'll leave this
in your hands.
No problem.
[Baoxing Cotton Mill]
Excuse me,
is today a day off?
Yes, it is.
Where did the other female workers go?
They're all over there,
listening to the speech.
Thank you.
Who built the railways?
Who drives the trains?
Who made the machines?
It's always been us, the workers.
No homes without builders.
No clothes without makers.
No future without workers.
Sure, workers are great.
Then why are we still struggling?
Because we're fated to suffer.
No, poverty isn't fate.
It's because there are classes
and exploitation.
Why do capitalists exploit?
Because they hold power.
The workers grow poorer
as the capitalists grow richer.
That's how this system works.
To end poverty,
we must take power.
We need to overthrow the old regime,
and build a society
free of class and exploitation,
a society where all are equal!
- Well said!
- Nice!
- Splendid!
- Great!
Shaohua,
do you know
what the true tide of history is?
The greatness of a nation
is to serve its country and its people.
- Splendid!
- Great!
- Well said!
- Nice!
Shaohua?
Shaohua.
Amei.
Shaohua,
thank you.
After I took the medicine you sent,
my back pain went away almost instantly.
That's great.
I'll bring you some more next time.
The medicine's so expensive.
I can't keep accepting it.
It's fine.
Shaohua,
I'll introduce you to someone.
Who?
Let's go.
Fight for equal rights.
Mr. Xia.
No need.
Mr. Xia,
this is Miss Chu, whom I told you about.
Amei said
you're giving free medicine
to every blue-collar worker in the city?
Yes.
But there are too many workers.
Miss Chu doesn't know where to start.
Going through the Municipal Council
won't work.
Factories aren't safe either.
The foremen will skim off the top.
Leave it to us.
We've got the Workers' Club,
League of Comrades,
and Workers' Mutual Aid Society.
All are run by workers
and they reach every factory,
dock, and station in Shanghai.
We'll make sure every pack of medicine
goes straight to the workers.
Thank you.
Actually, we owe you the thanks.
I heard
you've been supporting female workers
with free checkups and medicine
these past few years.
Shaohua
used to work here.
She even led us in a strike.
But back then,
she went by a different name.
Is that so?
Mr. Xia,
when the workers
distribute the anti-epidemic powder,
could they also hand out business cards
for Jujing Apothecary
and Wen's Pharmacy?
No problem.
Additionally,
I suggest printing a line
on the packaging,
encouraging workers to unite
and fight for equal treatment.
Okay.
Excuse me,
Mr. Xia,
I'm from Domestic
and Foreign Cotton Mill No. 8.
We'd love to have you speak
at our place tomorrow night.
No problem.
Mr. Xia,
we are from the Printers' Union.
Are you available
to give us a talk on Wednesday?
I'll be doing research
at Zhabei Dock during the day,
but I'm free in the evening.
Okay, see you then.
Okay.
Mr. Xia,
I represent the seamen from CMSNC.
We also want to join
the Shanghai General Labor Union.
We'd love to.
- Okay.
- Mr. Xia.
Some workers are waiting
for you at the gate.
For what's next,
just check in with Yin Amei.
Excuse me.
Okay, see you.
- Shaohua.
Let's go get some water over there.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
[Wen's Pharmacy]
Wen's Pharmacy.
Zheng.
I know.
Isn't that money due next week?
It's only Wednesday today.
Alright.
I understand.
Okay.
That's it.
Shaohua.
Chu Shaohua.
Mr. Wen,
Ms. Chu went out.
Um,
have the accounts
from Songjiang been prepared?
Yes.
Give them to me.
They've all been compiled
and given to Ms. Chu.
Where is she?
Sun took leave,
so Ms. Chu took over the delivery
of anti-epidemic powder.
Where'd she go?
Zhabei Cargo Dock.
Okay.
Thank you.
Please wait a moment.
Okay.
Hello, sir.
May I ask where Mr. Pang is?
Over by the wooden house.
Okay, thank you.
Much obliged, thanks.
If this pie
represents the handling fees
paid by the cargo owners,
look,
the dock capitalists took a big chunk,
the compradors grabbed their share,
and the foremen still took a slice.
Workers are left
with just this tiny bit.
We did all the work,
but they walked away
with most of the money.
That's exploitation!
If we don't want this to keep happening,
we've got to stand together
and build a union,
so we can get organized
and start a revolution.
Get back to work!
- You can go.
- Get up!
- Go ahead.
- Hurry up!
A bunch of slackers!
Mr. Pang, the number you reported
to the Dockworkers' Union
was 416.
I've got
exactly 416 boxes
of anti-epidemic powder right here.
Check them.
If there are no problems,
[Anti-epidemic Powder]
please sign here.
[Dispatching Room]
Why are you here?
Mr. Zheng from Songjiang says
he's got a family emergency
and needs some money.
He wants to settle
next month's accounts ahead of time.
Since you've got the ledger,
I came to find you.
It's in the third drawer of my desk.
Aren't you coming back with me?
I need to go to the Seamen's Union
to collect some documents.
Okay.
Help! Someone fell into the water!
Hurry up and save him!
Anyone here know how to swim?
Save him!
Quick!
Get him out!
- Can you swim?
- Hurry!
Is there anyone who can swim?
Hurry and go down.
Move aside!
Here, grab this!
Hold onto it!
Quick!
Hurry!
Come back this way!
What are you doing? Get back to work!
- What are you doing?
- What do you think you are doing?
Get back to work!
You don't want your wages anymore, huh?
Move it, back to work!
Get back to shore!
Get to work. Hurry up!
- Hurry up!
- Quick!
Xia Chu.
Get to work! I'm talking to you!
And you lot, get back to work!
- Get to work!
- Hurry up!
This way!
Hurry up!
Get to work!
Let's pull him up.
Here, come on.
Put him here.
Let him lie on his side.
On his side.
Come on!
- Pull him up!
- Give him a hand!
Pitch in.
Pull! Quick!
Come on!
Move aside.
Wake up.
Come on.
Wake up!
Help me
get him up.
- Buddy!
- He's awake.
Buddy.
Thank you, Mr. Xia.
We'll never forget this, Mr. Xia.
No need for that.
- It's no big deal.
- Thanks a lot, Mr. Xia.
Please get up.
We owe you, Mr. Xia.
You call the shots
on union matters.
We'll do whatever you say.
- Right!
- Whatever you say.
- We're with you!
- You've got our support!
Okay.
Get a doctor, now!
Easy.
Buddy.
Get to work.
Hurry up!
Let's go.
You've known each other a while, huh?
I need to go to the Seamen's Union.
Can you give me a ride?
Okay, let's go.
By the way, I'm done being your fiancé.
Why?
There's no need for that.
If you're feeling awkward,
I won't push you.
Feels like you're the one uncomfortable.
Me? What do you mean?
Why haven't you told him you're single?
Or is he the one
you can't forget?
Wen Zhiqiu.
You came here for him, didn't you?
Why didn't you talk to him?
Is that really how you see me?
You don't know a thing.
Yeah, I don't.
I don't get it. You're always so bold,
asking for everything out loud,
and now you're suddenly awkward?
Say that again,
and I'll throw you in the river.
I'm really disappointed in you.
[Spring Garden Restaurant]
Shaohua,
this is our hall.
I've hired musicians for that stage.
There'll be music here soon.
Check out this bar.
I designed it myself.
It's wonderful.
I really like
that mirror over there.
The second floor's all private rooms.
Come on, I'll show you.
Okay.
There are a total
of seven private rooms upstairs.
This is the largest one.
Isn't this lamp gorgeous?
Yeah.
I had a friend pick this up in France.
This tablecloth is Italian.
Inside here,
there's a smaller room tucked away.
Super discreet.
Erniu,
from the looks of it,
you must have put in a ton of efforts.
But it must've cost a lot, right?
It's alright.
Mu paid for it all.
He's the major shareholder.
Oh, right, I've got
another spot to show you.
Come with me.
Okay.
I've told everyone
this terrace
is just for the two of us.
Really? Just the two of us?
Yes.
So, are you planning
to keep making movies?
Definitely.
Mu's good to me right now,
but who knows what the future holds?
I've got to leave myself a backup plan.
That's great.
You didn't let love cloud your judgment.
After suffering so much,
I need to learn my lesson.
What about you?
Me? You mean what?
Are you really planning
to live alone for the rest of your life?
Living alone for a lifetime
might not be so bad.
That sounds really lonely.
Well, I've got my career,
so it's not too bad.
That's right.
Money keeps you from feeling too alone.
Erniu,
have you ever thought about
doing something meaningful,
you know, beyond just making money?
Like what?
Like...
I don't know.
I
ran into him again.
Xia Chu.
Do you still love him?
If you do,
go find him.
But maybe I'm no longer in his heart.
If you don't ask him,
how would you ever know?
He has got a girlfriend
and has already moved on with his life.
[Wen's Pharmacy]
Down with imperialism!
Take back our concessions!
- Take back our concessions!
Shanghai belongs to us!
- Shanghai belongs to us!
Down with imperialism!
- Down with imperialism!
Take back our concessions!
- Take back our concessions!
Shanghai belongs to us!
- Shanghai belongs to us!
Shaohua!
Down with imperialism!
Shaohua.
- Down with imperialism!
Amei, where are you all going?
We're going to Louza Police Station
on Nanjing Road to petition
for the release
of the arrested students.
If I didn't have to deliver medicine,
I'd be standing right beside you.
You've given so much already.
That means a lot to us.
How long do you plan to stay there?
We're not leaving
until they let them go.
Alright, once I'm done with my errands,
I'll drop by with food and drinks.
Okay, see you later.
Okay.
[Spring Garden Restaurant]
Get enough mantou for 200 people
and a few pots of hot soup ready.
Send them over
to Louza Police Station on Nanjing Road.
I'll pay you later.
How about this?
I'll prepare 400 portions.
You cover 200,
and I'll take care of the other 200.
Erniu,
thank you.
I'm Chinese too.
- Mu.
- Do not go out today.
Why?
I just got word
that Everson's already sent
a large force of armed police.
They've arrived
at Louza Police Station on Nanjing Road,
and all the Indian officers
have been authorized to open fire.
Something big is about to happen.
Oh my goodness.
Things are going to get messy out there.
Don't go out, no matter what.
And don't open for business.
I understand.
Shaohua.
Where are you going?
Resist Japanese oppression!
- Resist Japanese oppression!
Unite, fellow workers!
- Unite, fellow workers!
Sir, please hurry.
Okay.
- Down with imperialism!
We must stand tall!
Oppose the Four Anti-Chinese Proposals!
Boycott Japanese goods!
Raise funds
to support struggling workers!
Drive the Japanese out of Shanghai!
Shanghai belongs to China!
Boycott Japanese goods!
Down with imperialism!
- Down with imperialism!
Take back Shanghai!
Drive the Japanese out!
Shanghai belongs to China!
Down with Japanese imperialism!
- Down with imperialism!
Take back our concessions!
- Take back our concessions!
Resist Japanese oppression!
- Resist Japanese oppression!
- Shanghai belongs to us!
Down with imperialism!
- Down with imperialism!
Take back our concessions!
- Take back our concessions!
Unite, fellow workers!
- Unite, fellow workers!
Shanghai belongs to us!
- Shanghai belongs to us!
Take back our concessions!
- Take back our concessions!
Shanghai belongs to us!
- Shanghai belongs to us!
Down with imperialism!
- Down with imperialism!
Take back our concessions!
- Take back our concessions!
Shanghai belongs to us!
What are you doing?
Step back!
Keep your distance!
Down with imperialism!
Move back!
Any further forward
and we won't be polite!
The government arrested
patriotic students!
The imperialists fired at us!
We must rise up and resist!
He's shot! Quick!
He's hit!
The police are opening fire!
- Run!
- Hurry!
Quick!
Over there.
I'm leaving him to you.
Okay.
Over here.
Be careful.
Quick.
Go that way!
Hurry!
Go over there!
Xia Chu!
Xia Chu.
You are hurt.
Shaohua.
We'll never
be separated again.
Okay.
Where is Ms. Chu?
She went to Spring Garden Restaurant.
Gao.
Everyone's here?
Yes.
Li.
Mr. Wen.
Has the field staff come back yet?
Yeah, everyone's back
except Zhang Linyi.
He took leave and went home
the day before yesterday.
Mr. Wen.
Miss Bai called
to ask if Miss Chu has come back.
Wasn't she supposed to be at her place?
She said Miss Chu
headed to Nanjing Road later.
Yes.
Stay inside
until things are clear.
Okay, Mr. Wen.
Mr. Wen, Nanjing Road is dangerous.
They've started shooting!
Mr. Wen, it's not safe.
They told me...
that
you were dead.
That part of me is gone.
But I came back different.
Shaohua.
♪Your voice drifts to me,
never near, never far♪
If I'd known you were alive,
I would've waited.
Even if it meant dying...
♪Photo curled inside my worn wallet♪
I'd still wait for you.
It's not too late, is it?
We still
have a chance, don't we?
♪As seasons shift and fade♪
Of course.
It's never too late.
♪See the leaf fall at my toe♪
I have to rush back to the command post.
♪Like time quietly slipping away♪
I'll come to you later.
I'll wait for you.
♪And I couldn't quite understand♪
♪Why are answers always silent?♪
♪We walk through ordinary days♪
♪What remains flows like rivers wide♪
♪That fleeting light I failed to chase♪
♪Still lights each frame along my way♪
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Are all the staff alright?
They're all fine.
What happened to our people
is heartbreaking.
Seems a storm is needed
to make things right.
Unless a satisfactory agreement
is reached,
we vow not to reopen for business!
[Wen's Pharmacy]
[Closed in mourning. Awaiting justice.]
Extra!
Read about the third day
of the Concession strike!
[The Fifth Day of the Strike]
Extra!
Read about the fifth day
of the Concession strike!
[The Seventh Day of the Strike]
Extra!
Read about the seventh day
of the Concession strike!
[Donation Box]
[Support the strike.
Justice for the fallen.]
As of June,
our joint donations
with Jujing Apothecary
have reached eight thousand...
Eight thousand eight hundred
and nine silver dollars.
And fractional silver coins...
Eight thousand one hundred and fifteen.
Copper coins...
Ninety-eight thousand three hundred
and one.
Though businesses have reopened,
fund-raising
and support for the strikers
are still going strong.
Now that businesses
are back up and running,
we should kick off
our expansion plan too.
I've visited a few locations
these past few days.
Nanjing Road,
Wusong Road, and East Yan'an Road.
I think,
with some fresh ideas...
Mr. Wen, we're off the clock.
Since you're treating me to dinner,
can we not talk about work?
I'm buying you dinner
to talk about work.
If we're not talking about work,
then you're buying.
Alright.
No haggling with me?
Fine.
You were better
when you were stingy and money-obsessed.
Focused only on your career.
No feelings, no distractions.
But now?
How am I supposed
to trust you with my work?
I know what you mean.
But Mr. Wen,
there are things in this world
more valuable than money.
Don't tell me you mean love.
Love is one of them.
Looks like Mr. Xia's got you
all turned around.
Don't even bring him up.
I haven't seen him for a long time.
I thought you were
burning with desire.
What happened?
He's too busy.
I haven't seen him
since that day on Nanjing Road.
That was over a month ago.
What's keeping him so busy?
I don't know the specifics.
He probably doesn't
want to see you, right?
He's working on things
that serve the greater good.
Is that so?
Since you haven't seen
each other for so long,
wouldn't that affect your relationship?
Not really.
So sure?
Let me put it this way.
He and I
may go years without seeing each other,
or even without knowing
if the other is still alive.
But when we meet again,
it'll be just like before.
Got somewhere to be?
Or is it boring to talk about me?
It's not boring,
just a little cheesy.
Since we sat down,
you've checked your watch three times.
You're clearly up to something.
Is it a date?
Who is it?
Is it a girl?
Is she pretty?
Prettier than you.
How long have you known each other?
Not long.
You keep dodging the topic.
Are you into her?
So you get to be head over heels,
but I can't fall for someone?
No, I'm happy for you.
It's about time.
I'm leaving.
Alright, go ahead.
Hope it all works out between you two.
Hope you meet up again soon.
Okay.
He's got a date,
but still asked me to dinner...
ordered half the menu...
and I'm the one paying?
[Borgna Café]
[The Northeastern Army entered Shanghai
to ease Sino-foreign tensions.]
♪A blanket lying on the snow♪
♪Melting frost in silent glow♪
♪On endless snowy roads, I roam♪
♪Seeking the shore within my soul♪
♪Winds howl wild♪
♪My soul, near torn♪
♪A blanket hidden deep within his heart♪
♪Warming slowly every part of his heart♪
♪He whispers spring is near♪
♪He says winter is brief♪
♪The eternal shore♪
♪Calls out once more♪
♪Fate, day by day♪
♪Earnest and brave♪
♪Leaves no regrets♪
♪Dawn, bit by bit♪
♪Glorious and scorching♪
♪No longer alone♪
♪Flames light the way
where despair once lay♪
♪I shield you, my very soul entwined♪
♪Through hardship, to the goal♪
♪We reach, at last♪
♪The shore we hold fast♪
♪Fate, day by day♪
♪Earnest and brave♪
♪Leaves no regrets♪
♪Dawn, bit by bit♪
♪Glorious and scorching♪
♪No longer alone♪
♪Flames light the way
where despair once lay♪
♪I shield you, my very soul entwined♪
♪Through hardship, to the goal♪
♪We reach, at last♪
♪The shore we hold fast♪