♪Trap my frame♪
♪Plagues demand I bow in shame♪
♪Snare my soul♪
♪Rules command I swallow my pride♪
♪Mock my way♪
♪Chained me where I must stay♪
♪Taught me to kneel, not to speak♪
♪And to let my life pass by in silence♪
♪But I heard the wind♪
♪From the sea and the sky♪
♪It said don't bend♪
♪Bow your head, and your chains begin♪
♪You are the wave♪
♪And the wind that won't behave♪
♪How could you be chained?♪
♪Untamed, uncaged, unclaimed♪
♪You're the blade in my gaze♪
♪This world will leave you no space♪
♪Then pierce it with your blaze♪
♪My silent grind♪
♪My aching pain♪
♪Will one day turn...♪
♪I am who I am♪
♪My greatest ambition♪
♪If the world can't contain me♪
♪Then I'll break through it♪
♪Become who I am♪
[Wild Ambition Bloom]
[Adapted from Stone and Water's novel,
The Uncaged Flame]
[Episode 5]
Who are you?
I'm his sister-in-law.
Great, then.
Go get Chen Ershun.
We've sent someone.
But the round trip
will take about four hours.
That's fine. We'll wait.
Either he pays today,
or we're not going anywhere.
Alright, no problem.
But I think
such a long wait
would be exhausting for you.
Why don't you all come inside?
We'll get you some tea and snacks.
Wouldn't it be better to have a seat
while you wait?
Waiting here or inside, same thing.
He can hide all he wants.
But he won't escape forever.
Please.
Shitou, get tea and snacks ready.
Okay.
Ma'am,
why did you let them in?
What? Are we going
to let them loiter by the entrance
and scare off business?
No, but they're hard
to shake off once let in.
Don't worry.
Someone will take care of it.
[Chen's Apothecary]
Didn't you say he'd be back by noon?
Why hasn't
he shown up yet?
Are you messing with us?
Don't bother with her.
If he doesn't pay up,
we're going to smash this place!
Gentlemen,
let's try to be reasonable
and talk this out, alright?
Dashun.
What do you want?
What are you doing?
Dashun.
What do you want?
Father, just leave it
to us.
You are Chen Ershun's father?
Then you're responsible
for his debt. Pay up.
What debt?
The money Chen Ershun owes us.
Who are you?
This is Mr. Huang from Shuangfeng House.
This is Mr. Du from Deyi House.
This is Mr. Bai from Quyuan House.
[*All are brothels]
You're saying Ershun owes you money?
Any proof?
Of course.
Check this out.
[Deyi House Credit Slip]
He signed these IOUs himself.
Not only do I have the bills here,
but I also have witnesses.
How about I get the girls, Jinfeng,
Fengxian, and Yukui
here
to confront him?
Look,
he signed all of these.
Such a scoundrel.
So, how do you plan on solving this?
How much does he owe you?
He owes us 340 silver dollars.
Us, 500.
I'm owed 275.
That's a total of 1,115.
How much money do we have
in our accounts?
1,557.
A debt must be paid.
I like how straightforward you are.
Sir,
come by my place sometime.
Mr. Chen, I owe you a drink.
Our ladies at Shuangfeng House
would love to entertain you.
Alright, that's enough.
Why is there so much less?
What's wrong?
Dashun.
I figured
it'd be short by 200 or 300 tops.
I didn't expect this.
How much is missing?
There are only 870 silver dollars
in the cash box now.
What are you talking about?
Father, it's nothing, we...
Dashun.
Shaohua.
You can't cover for him now.
Tell Father the truth.
- Speak!
- I...
Go ahead.
Tell me!
Father, it's like this.
These past two months,
I've been recovering
after giving birth to Xuan.
So I let Ershun handle
purchasing and accounting himself.
And
then...
Father.
You've got some nerve coming back.
Father, I was wrong.
You were wrong?
You disgrace! I'll beat you to death!
To death!
Darling, stop hitting him!
Stop!
If you keep this up, you'll kill him!
That's enough!
Sleepy time, little one.
If you keep this up, you'll kill him!
- Stop!
- When you grow up...
Ershun, say you were wrong!
Ershun!
Father, I was wrong!
I won't dare to do it again!
Please forgive me!
It was all my fault.
When you grow up,
you'll walk through school gates,
meet books and stories,
and learn what life creates.
Father told Ershun to leave tonight.
Back to Qizhou?
Song Ping is staying here
to take care of Mother and Xuan.
But Father also said
starting tomorrow,
you'll be in charge of Yurong Powder.
Understood.
[Linfang Pavilion]
Gentlemen, come in and have some fun.
Sir.
Come in and enjoy yourself for a bit.
Chen Ershun's sister-in-law?
Yes.
She asked you to go over there
and check the accounts with her.
I've got no time for this.
Tell her to bring the ledger here.
But our madam...
So what?
I'm the envoy's wife, you know.
She wants me to go to her place?
Yes.
Ma'am,
why not just give me the ledger
and let me check it with her?
But only I can make sense
of the messy accounts
Chen Ershun left behind.
Then what should we do?
[Juxian Teahouse]
It's just a brothel.
Let's go.
Chen Ershun promised me a commission.
Does that still count?
Yes.
Good to hear that.
Please come in.
Mr. Zhou!
You haven't been here for a long time.
Is that so?
Where's my dear Lu Ningxiang?
She's been expecting you.
Really?
I'll take you there.
You've slimmed down.
Ningxiang.
Alright.
Where's Madam Yan?
Madam Yan?
She's with a guest right now.
Then please tell her
that we've finished checking
and her bills are sorted
and left on the table.
Okay, got it.
Then we'll take our leave.
Alright.
I'll teach you a lesson
for that attitude!
You're actually hitting me?
How dare you
speak to a guest like that!
So arrogant, huh?
Signed your body away,
and still putting on airs?
Think you're still a virgin?
Come here!
Kang Erniu!
Erniu.
Lu Ningxiang.
My name is Lu Ningxiang.
You've got the wrong person.
You are Erniu.
They know each other?
That must hurt so much.
I'm used to it.
Have some water.
How did you
end up here?
It's my miserable fate, I guess.
Where's Wu?
I don't know.
How much
would it cost to buy your freedom?
What did you just say?
I want to take you out of here.
Why would I leave?
This place eats you alive.
Shaohua!
You see it as a place of ruin,
but I think it suits me just fine.
I don't have to toil in the fields.
I eat my fill every day
and dress up nice.
The wind doesn't bite,
the rain doesn't soak,
and the sun doesn't burn.
Look at my face.
Really?
Back home,
my father beat me day after day.
At least at home,
you still had your dignity.
But here, do you have it?
Come in.
Ma'am.
I was just looking.
You want to know
why I'm here?
Before Wu and I came to Peking,
we took some money from the Xia family.
At first, things were good.
We had food, drinks, everything.
But it didn't last.
I asked him to work,
but he thought it was too tiring.
He thought gambling
was an easier way to make money.
Does anyone ever truly win at gambling?
You know what,
he actually won at first.
But the longer it went on,
the more miserably he lost.
At last, he borrowed from loan sharks.
When those people came
to collect the debt from him,
he sold me here.
Where is he?
I don't know.
He said
he'd earn enough to buy my freedom.
But after that, he disappeared.
Erniu,
don't worry.
I will get you out of here.
Shaohua,
with those words,
our friendship wasn't in vain.
But I won't leave.
Why?
I've been touched by too many hands.
I'm nothing but filth.
My life's already ruined.
No.
Just leave me alone.
Let me waste away in this place
like I was meant to.
It's fine.
No.
I never thought I'd see you again.
Seeing you today,
so full of life,
I'm truly happy for you.
But after this,
let's not meet again.
No.
You don't get to decide this.
Promise me.
Out you go.
Erniu.
Even if you give up on yourself,
I won't.
I'll come to you.
Mrs. Chen Junior.
Lu Ningxiang asked me
to give you a message.
Don't come again.
Even if you do,
she won't see you.
Then tell her,
since we shared a childhood,
she should understand what I am like.
Having a nice little break, are we?
Already gone?
Who are you asking about?
Mrs. Chen Junior
or Mr. Zhou?
Mrs. Chen Junior.
She left and won't be coming back.
Mr. Zhou isn't coming either.
Isn't that great?
Nice to have a little peace for once.
Mr. Chen has invited Miss Lu Ningxiang
to the Shunwang Room
at Chunhua Restaurant.
Alright.
Hurry up and get ready.
Business is here.
Don't give me any more trouble.
You're not hitting me anymore?
Mr. Chen.
Didn't I tell you
we shouldn't see each other again?
Why are you back?
Do you remember when we were kids,
washing clothes together by the river?
I tried to help you grab those
that had drifted off,
and I slipped right into the water.
You reacted so fast
and grabbed me.
But we were little
and weak.
You couldn't get me back to shore.
We were stuck there, holding on.
I told you,
"Let go,
or you'll fall in too."
But you wouldn't.
You just kept holding on
until someone finally came and saved us.
You didn't let go back then,
and I'm not letting go now.
Enough about the past.
You can pull me out of this mess,
but you can't give me back
what I've lost.
Erniu.
Do you still remember this?
Back then at Qizhou's Medicine Market,
we only had enough to buy this.
It wasn't worth much,
just a few wen.
But you were
so happy, wearing it in your hair.
In my heart,
this red hair tie is the best.
Even the most expensive beaded hairpin
can't compare.
You were the most beautiful
at the Medicine Market.
I was quite happy then.
But my red hair tie
is missing.
Just keep it
if you want.
It's okay if you lost yours.
Mine is still here, isn't it?
I'll give you mine.
Back then, when you wore it,
you were the most beautiful girl
at the Medicine Market.
Now,
just wear it again,
and you'll still be that girl,
always, no matter what.
I'm not worthy anymore.
So what if you were unlucky in love?
So what if you lived
as a courtesan for a while?
No matter what you've been through,
you'll always be the most beautiful girl
in my heart.
Who says you can't go back?
As long as you don't give up,
you can always start over.
Do you think
I can still start over?
Absolutely.
Really?
There's nothing you can't do,
as long as you truly want to.
Three thousand silver dollars.
What?
How much?
And the clothes and jewelry on you,
the furnishings in this room,
all need to be left behind.
You're too greedy.
When Wu sold me to you,
it was only for 200, wasn't it?
It's been so many years.
I've helped you earn
at least 1,000.
You got it back long ago.
Why don't you calculate
how much money I've spent on you?
Every bite you take,
every drink you sip,
what you wear,
what you put on your face,
on your lips, in your hair.
I paid for masters to teach you
music, art, poetry, and songs.
Even how to charm men.
Was there anything
I didn't spend money on?
Why are you shouting at me?
If you want to calculate it that way...
Madam Yan,
so it's 3,000.
Alright.
I need to talk it over with my family.
Xuan is asleep?
What's wrong?
I want to...
borrow some money from you.
"Borrow" is not a word we use, is it?
How much do you want?
Three thousand silver dollars.
What do you need so much money for?
I met Erniu today.
She's at Linfang Pavilion.
I want to buy her freedom.
Wait a minute.
Erniu?
My best friend.
Linfang Pavilion?
She was tricked.
You want to buy her freedom?
That madam
asked for 3,000.
I must rescue her.
Shaohua,
do you have any idea what 3,000 means?
That's a huge amount of money.
I know.
But...
after thinking it over and over,
I could only ask you.
There's no other way.
Shaohua,
I started doing business
with my father when I was 15.
And after all these years,
I've only managed
to save a little over 200.
I gave some to you
and some to Shaozhong.
I'm down to about 100 at the moment.
But what about Erniu?
You can only come up with 100?
Then what about me?
How about
you bear with it for another year?
Another year?
Yes.
So you're telling me to stay here
and let those filthy men
lay their hands on me for another year?
But it's just one year, really.
Just one year, huh?
Why don't you stay here?
Let's switch places. Not even a year,
one night.
Erniu, I...
Chu Shaohua, I've already told you
to let me waste away in this place.
Why did you have to meddle?
I was already in despair.
Why did you give me hope?
And now you just throw it away, saying,
"The money's not enough"?
Then what am I supposed to do?
You don't have to save me
since I'm dying.
But can you please not make me
suffer over and over again?
Erniu, I promise,
in a year, I will raise the money
to buy your freedom.
I've heard those words all before.
Wu said the same thing.
So did Mr. Wang.
Even Mr. Zhou.
But where are they now?
Chu Shaohua,
I finally see you for who you are.
You're no different
from those filthy men.
Erniu, I'm not like that.
Get out.
Go!
Do you know
how big a sum of money that is?
Doesn't the Chen family
run an apothecary in Peking?
Don't they do big business?
The business belongs to Dashun's father,
not his.
They're all just excuses.
You all have money,
but no one is willing to save me.
I mean it!
No, you don't!
It's all false, Chu Shaohua.
You're full of lies.
You don't even realize it anymore.
All that talk about our bond? Fake.
Saving me? Just another lie.
When it's time to put down real money,
that's when your true colors show.
Kang Erniu.
Get this straight.
I don't owe you anything.
You insisted on running away
with Wu back then.
I advised you, but did you listen?
You brought this on yourself.
Chu Shaohua, listen,
the person I hate most now
isn't Wu anymore.
It's you!
He just threw me into the water.
You pulled me out of the water,
let me take a breath,
and then pushed me down hard again.
You're even crueler than all of them!
Fine.
Since that's the case,
Kang Erniu,
we're done.
Get lost!
I'm done meddling
in Lu Ningxiang's affairs.
Take care, ma'am.
If you want to make more money,
you can try selling this.
I guarantee it'll earn more than selling
the ointment for a social disease.
Alright.
So, how much commission
will you give me for this?
I'll give you a ten percent commission
for every box you sell.
I'll have to see if it sells well.
Isn't this Mrs. Chen Junior?
Madam Yan,
long time no see.
Are you also here to see a physician?
Not really.
I knew it.
Mr. Zhang and I are discussing business.
Is there something you need?
What a coincidence.
I've got business
to discuss with you too.
Can we talk over there for a second?
Is Shitou making mistakes recently?
It has nothing to do with him.
Are you dissatisfied with Yurong Powder?
No, it's not.
Yurong Powder is quite effective.
Then what is it about?
Please go ahead.
Ma'am,
are you still planning
to redeem Lu Ningxiang?
Please don't bring her up.
I helped her out of kindness,
but ended up the bad guy.
She lost her head for a moment.
Don't let it ruin your sisterhood.
We have different surnames,
definitely not sisters.
You were even planning
to buy her freedom.
That's quite a deep bond.
She begged me so desperately,
and since we're from the same place,
I just wanted to do the right thing.
I thought
she was only worth
a few tens of silver dollars.
Who would have thought
her price would be so high?
Ma'am,
if you still want to buy her freedom,
two thousand silver dollars is enough.
I've already told you
I'm not getting involved
in her matters anymore.
Madam Yan, if there's nothing else,
I'll be heading off.
I have to check accounts with others.
Hey, wait.
Fifteen hundred.
One thousand.
Madam Yan,
let me be frank with you.
I was willing to help her before
because I had calculated the costs.
My younger brother back
in the countryside is slow-witted.
Girls from proper families
wouldn't marry him.
I thought
a bit of money
was enough to redeem Lu Ningxiang.
It'd be like finding my brother a wife.
I could manage that cost.
But if you're talking about 1,000,
that's definitely not going to work.
Then,
how much can you offer?
Eighty, perhaps.
I need to save some for their wedding.
Ma'am,
with a price like that,
there's really nothing to talk about.
Well, I've laid all my cards
on the table.
Why don't you make a serious offer too?
Five hundred silver dollars.
Five hundred silver dollars?
If you can't even come up with 500,
I'll find someone else.
I believe someone
would take Lu Ningxiang
for that price.
Well, 500 silver dollars...
I'll need some time to think it through.
Then it's settled.
Before sunset tomorrow,
you bring the money to Linfang Pavilion.
We'll exchange money for the person.
No, you...
It's settled.
Don't you think that's a little rushed?
These are Qingya Parlor's accounts
for last month.
Please take a look.
Why did you come in person?
Business has been hectic lately.
Shitou's swamped.
Oh, right, Madam Tao.
I've got a friend
who seems to have taken a liking
to Lu Ningxiang from Linfang Pavilion.
He's thinking of buying her freedom.
What do you think would be a fair price?
Lu Ningxiang?
You don't know yet?
Don't know what?
She's about to die.
Mr. Zhao, I appreciate your support.
Thank you, Madam Yan.
Madam Yan.
About Lu Ningxiang,
five hundred silver dollars
is out of the question.
Even if it were 50,
I wouldn't be interested.
What are you saying?
It struck me as odd.
She was priced at 3,000 before,
then suddenly it dropped to 500.
Apparently,
she's contracted a filthy illness.
Her body is decaying,
and the smell is overwhelming.
Even Physician Zhang is at a loss.
And you still told me
to bring the money tomorrow.
You're scared
she won't last another day with you.
Who told you that?
That doesn't matter.
I don't want her anymore.
Let anyone else have her.
Hold on.
Why are you arrogant?
You're taking her,
whether you want to or not.
Who are you?
You don't know Mr. Zhao?
And you're still doing business
around here?
Even if it's Mr. Zhao,
we can't force a sale, can we?
I never
force anyone to buy or sell.
You're the one who wanted her.
You must buy her.
But I asked for someone alive
instead of a dead one.
She's not dead.
Everyone on the street is saying
she's dying.
Doesn't your family
run an apothecary?
Can't you whip up
a couple of doses to help her?
What if it can't be cured?
You can send her back.
Cured or not,
I'm done with her.
Can't I just change my mind?
No way!
I'm telling you,
if you dare to change your mind,
your family can forget
about doing business in this hutong.
Alright.
I can take her.
But I can't pay 500.
I need to save 200 for her medicine.
Then 300 it is.
I have another condition.
Speak.
You have to help me find someone.
Who?
Wu.
Why look for him?
Just don't ask too much.
If I don't ask,
how do you expect me to find him?
He's a distant relative of mine.
His family members want to find him.
I'm just helping to ask.
It's been a long time
since I last saw him.
I don't know where he is.
You're the famous Mr. Zhao.
You've got a lot of men at your command.
If you want,
you will find him.
The money I'm putting up
to take Lu Ningxiang back
is just a gamble.
All I'm asking
is for you to help me find Wu
and give him to me.
What do you say?
I agree.
But I also have one condition.
If Lu Ningxiang dies here,
I'll accept it.
If she dies at your place,
don't come back.
Alright then.
[Linfang Pavilion]
Do you know someone named Wu?
Wu?
Yes, he's from Qizhou.
I don't know.
Thank you.
Alright.
Go.
Sir,
what was that woman asking you about?
[Li the Fortune Teller]
Go.
She went to many places along the way.
Gambling houses, restaurants, and inns.
She also asked around in other hutongs.
All just to find Wu?
Yes.
Did she say
why she's in such a hurry to find him?
One moment she says Wu is her brother,
that his mother's dying,
and she needs to see him one last time.
Then she turns around
and says Wu is her brother-in-law,
that her sister's dying,
and she needs to see him one last time.
Not a single word
out of her mouth is true.
Exactly.
But she told the truth to Blind Li.
She went to him too?
Yes.
She asked him to help her figure out
where Wu is now.
Blind Li said,
"You have to tell me
why you're looking for him.
Only then can I calculate accurately."
So she told the truth.
What did she say?
She, Wu, and Lu Ningxiang
are indeed from the same hometown.
When Wu and Lu Ningxiang
left their hometown,
they stole a sum of money
from their employer,
and
a top-notch Renshen.
That employer
is now offering a reward of 5,000
to find the Renshen.
Five thousand silver dollars?
Yes.
I knew something was off.
She knew Lu Ningxiang was dying,
but still insisted on buying her.
There was clearly more to it.
And just as I suspected.
Three hundred silver dollars for 5,000.
That's a very shrewd calculation.
Want to play these tricks with me?
In her dreams.
Send out the word.
Mobilize everyone
to find Wu.
I stand by my word.
She can have Wu.
However,
the Renshen
must be mine.
Go.
Yes.
There're 103 silver dollars.
So, that's still 197 short.
Where else can I get money?
How about borrowing some
from Father and Mother?
Father wouldn't go near anything
that doesn't make money.
As for Mother...
Okay, I know.
Exactly, you know what she's like.
What should I do?
I do have a few business partners.
I can gather some from them.
But you need this money
by tomorrow afternoon.
It'll definitely be too late.
Does it have to be tomorrow?
I'm afraid of further complications
if we delay.
With the way things are for Erniu,
we need to get her out fast.
It's the only way to keep her safe.
Alright then.
I'll get all the money for you
by tomorrow morning.
How will you get it?
Don't worry, I have a way.
Dashun.
Thank you.
You're still using those words?
I'll put it away
for now.
Alright.
[Linfang Pavilion]
It stinks so much.
Exactly.
It clings to everything
and won't go away.
Ma'am,
please take a good look.
She is breathing.
Where's Wu?
Mr. Zhao's tracking him.
Don't worry,
he'll bring him to you
within three days.
I trust Mr. Zhao.
He'll get things done right.
You can count it.
We're all set.
Mr. Zhao!
Don't hit me!
Please!
Don't!
Wu!
Come.
Does it hurt?
Yes.
Just tell me where the Renshen is.
I really have no idea.
Really.
I don't know where it is.
Where is it?
I'll ask you one more time.
Wu.
Where is the Renshen?
I really don't know.
I don't know.
Beat him up!
Are you done?
Meal's ready.
I'm free.
Yes, you are.
You only need
to take a dose of the medicine
the size of a fingernail each day.
After an hour,
your whole body will emit
an extremely foul odor.
As for this packet of powder,
after mixing it with water,
apply it to the key areas of your body.
It will
look as if your skin is festering.
Others won't be able to tell?
Don't worry.
With a foul odor on your body,
most people won't dare to come close.
Let alone touch it.
Also,
from now on,
you have to eat and drink less
to make yourself look thinner
day by day.
Your head and face
should be as dirty as possible.
Within ten
to 15 days,
Madam Yan will be convinced
that you're gravely ill
and beyond saving.
How did you come up with this?
Don't forget
how my father died.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Are you ready?
So you only have 100?
Madam Yan called me in
to examine Lu Ningxiang.
According to your instructions,
I told her
that Ningxiang had contracted
the most dangerous form
of great pox, black pox,
and that it had reached its final stage.
I also said it would be best
to get rid of her as soon as possible,
otherwise, everyone might get infected.
Here, take this.
Thank you, ma'am.
If something like this comes up again,
you know where to find me.
You can try selling this.
I guarantee it'll earn more
than selling the ointment
for a social disease.
Alright.
Isn't this Mrs. Chen Junior?
Shaohua.
How can I ever repay you?
♪A blanket lying on the snow♪
♪Melting frost in silent glow♪
♪On endless snowy roads, I roam♪
♪Seeking the shore within my soul♪
♪Winds howl wild♪
♪My soul, near torn♪
♪A blanket hidden deep within his heart♪
♪Warming slowly every part of his heart♪
♪He whispers spring is near♪
♪He says winter is brief♪
♪The eternal shore♪
♪Calls out once more♪
♪Fate, day by day♪
♪Earnest and brave♪
♪Leaves no regrets♪
♪Dawn, bit by bit♪
♪Glorious and scorching♪
♪No longer alone♪
♪Flames light the way
where despair once lay♪
♪I shield you, my very soul entwined♪
♪Through hardship, to the goal♪
♪We reach, at last♪
♪The shore we hold fast♪
♪Fate, day by day♪
♪Earnest and brave♪
♪Leaves no regrets♪
♪Dawn, bit by bit♪
♪Glorious and scorching♪
♪No longer alone♪
♪Flames light the way
where despair once lay♪
♪I shield you, my very soul entwined♪
♪Through hardship, to the goal♪
♪We reach, at last♪
♪The shore we hold fast♪