♪Trap my frame♪
♪Plagues demand I bow in shame♪
♪Snare my soul♪
♪Rules command I swallow my pride♪
♪Mock my way♪
♪Chained me where I must stay♪
♪Taught me to kneel, not to speak♪
♪And to let my life pass by in silence♪
♪But I heard the wind♪
♪From the sea and the sky♪
♪It said don't bend♪
♪Bow your head, and your chains begin♪
♪You are the wave♪
♪And the wind that won't behave♪
♪How could you be chained?♪
♪Untamed, uncaged, unclaimed♪
♪You're the blade in my gaze♪
♪This world will leave you no space♪
♪Then pierce it with your blaze♪
♪My silent grind♪
♪My aching pain♪
♪Will one day turn...♪
♪I am who I am♪
♪My greatest ambition♪
♪If the world can't contain me♪
♪Then I'll break through it♪
♪Become who I am♪
[Wild Ambition Bloom]
[Adapted from Stone and Water's novel,
The Uncaged Flame]
[Episode 37]
You...
should go talk to Mr. Xia.
He knows more than I do.
Mr. Xia?
All he cares about
is profit.
Justice and truth don't even register.
But you're different.
He brought me into the business.
How could I be any different?
Deep down,
you're nothing like him.
Xia Yuan
is my boss,
my mentor,
and the one I owe everything to.
I would never betray him.
But the Mr. Gao I know
would never go against his conscience.
Mr. Gao,
when I began managing an apothecary,
I met you.
Even though we didn't meet often,
your humility and integrity
have always earned my deepest respect.
It made me swear to myself
I'd manage my business just as you did,
with honesty
and
integrity.
So I'm here waiting for you,
just to ask you one question.
Did my mother really sell
the Miracle Pill formula
to Mr. Xia?
Mr. Gao.
Miss Chu,
I am no longer
the same person I used to be.
I'll take my leave.
Dig in.
Come on.
Shaozhong.
Shaohua?
You're back.
Shaozhong,
how are you holding up?
I'm fine.
Really.
Where's Bao?
He's working as an apprentice
and comes back once a week.
What about Song Ping?
She's at Mr. Wang's.
Why are you back?
Things are getting worse in North China.
I want to take you all to Shanghai.
Also,
I want to ask you something important.
That's not true.
Are you sure?
Of course.
Mr. Yi talked to me
a few times back then,
but only about buying
Chichun Apothecary.
He never once mentioned
the Miracle Pill.
And
even if it really had been sold,
Mother and Zhou Yan would've told me.
Is there a chance
they sold it
but didn't dare tell you?
No.
I've seen the contract.
It only mentioned the signboard.
Miracle Pill wasn't in it at all.
And it was only sold
for 160 silver dollars,
not 180.
Where is that contract now?
Can you still find it?
That was over 20 years ago.
Where would I even find it now?
Shaozhong,
maybe we should try looking again.
It's definitely gone.
Shaozhong,
are any of Mother's fingerprints
still in the house?
No.
What about Zhou Yan's?
None either.
If it's truly nowhere to be found,
I'll return to Shanghai with you.
If Xia Yuan insists on
seizing the Miracle Pill,
I'll fight him to the very end.
At worst, we'll both go down.
Shaozhong, don't worry.
Even if we can't find it,
we still have other ways.
What other ways?
Isn't this contract in triplicate?
We have one.
Xia Yuan does too.
So does Anke Hall.
Since the Qizhou Medicine Market
shut down,
Anke Hall closed with it.
But we can still track down
the one in charge, right?
If we can find Lei Yuting,
we still have a chance.
Lei Yuting?
He died in 1930.
How could this be?
Sir,
are there old contracts
from Anke Hall here?
They're all piled up inside.
[Anke Hall]
Can we go in and take a look?
Sir, please help us.
Come with me.
Come on, they're all in here.
Okay.
Is this the right key?
Don't get it wrong.
It can't be wrong.
Last month, I used this key
to open this lock.
It's open.
Okay.
Go ahead and check for yourselves.
No one came for over a decade.
Then there were two visits this month.
How strange.
Shaozhong, how about this?
You look over there,
and I'll look here.
Let's start from 1916.
Okay.
About my height.
Big eyes. Very thin.
You mean that woman from the North?
Zhou, right?
Yes.
Do you know where she is now?
She's dead.
The year of 1917.
Shaohua.
Is this it?
Let me see.
[Land Deed. Year 1916]
Let's go over there.
- Come on.
- Okay.
Here.
Shaozhong.
This is it.
The situation
is not looking good for Shaohua.
We need to blur the facts.
Just find a few random fingerprints
and claim they belong to her mother
and Zhou Yan.
The prints can't be confirmed,
and the judge won't know either.
No need, Wen.
Shaohua found key evidence in Qizhou,
enough to prove that Xia Yuan's contract
is a forgery.
That's great.
Mr. Xia.
[Shanghai Public Court]
Miss Chu,
you can still change your mind.
Mr. Xia.
Truth doesn't change,
and lies won't hold up.
Once we're in court,
the Miracle Pill's as good as mine.
Your Honor,
based on the witnesses, testimonies,
and evidence presented,
[Plaintiff]
we request a ruling
that Shaohua Pharmaceuticals
[Defendant]
return the Miracle Pill formula
to Shouyuan Apothecary.
All prior profits
from its sale
should also be returned.
Defense Lawyer,
do you have any arguments to present
regarding the plaintiff's
evidence and claims?
Your Honor,
the sales contract submitted
by the plaintiff
is forged.
You need evidence to support that.
Defense Lawyer,
do you have any evidence
to support your statement?
Your Honor,
the submitted contract states:
"Empty words prove nothing.
This sales contract is the evidence,
issued in triplicate.
One copy each is held by the signatory,
the contract holder, and Anke Hall."
While the signatory's copy
is no longer available,
we have located
the original contract
in the Qizhou Anke Hall archives.
Please note
that while the two contracts
are very similar,
the copy archived by Anke Hall
does not contain the phrase
"Miracle Pill formula."
Since the relevant parties
are either missing
or have passed away,
comparatively,
the copy archived by Anke Hall
is more credible.
Your Honor,
we request a thorough review
of the defendant's evidence.
Your Honor,
it's the defendant's contract
that's forged.
You need evidence to support that.
The signatures and fingerprints
of Xia Yuan and Gao Qianyi
are not theirs at all.
If you keep talking nonsense,
I swear I'll knock you out.
Of the six people who left fingerprints,
three have passed away,
and one is missing.
But Xia Yuan and Gao Qianyi
are still alive,
and present in this courtroom.
We request
immediate fingerprint verification.
Sure, do it.
We'll see who's bluffing.
No one came for over a decade.
Then there were two visits this month.
How strange.
Miss Chu, do you agree
to the on-site identification?
No need.
Why?
We've been tricked.
What do you mean?
The contract we brought back
from Anke Hall
is a forgery.
How is that possible?
Looks like Xia Yuan
placed a fake contract
in the archives,
hoping we'd fall for it.
Your Honor,
we do not agree
to the on-site identification.
Feeling guilty, are you?
Due to unforeseen circumstances,
we request a brief recess.
That won't do,
unless you acknowledge
the evidence was forged.
Order.
Witness Gao Qianyi,
please take the stand.
Witness,
please state your identity.
My name is Gao Qianyi,
and I am the second shopkeeper
of Shouyuan Apothecary.
Present the evidence.
Take his fingerprints.
Your Honor,
even without collecting fingerprints,
we can still determine
the contract submitted by Miss Chu
is evidently forged.
There's a whorl fingerprint
on the contract,
but all my fingers have loop patterns.
Mr. Xia's contract
does contain my fingerprint.
But
his copy
is also fake.
I stamped it myself
twenty days ago.
And I remember
that the contract back then
didn't mention the Miracle Pill at all.
Gao Qianyi, you ungrateful wretch!
Save it for later.
Mr. Gao, thank you.
I truly didn't expect
that you would come to my defense
at the most crucial moment.
Actually,
Xia Yuan's tactics
in acquiring Chichun Apothecary
were nothing short of despicable.
If he were to seize the Miracle Pill
in the same ruthless way,
that would be downright unjust.
I couldn't just stand by,
so I chose to speak out.
When my family sold
Chichun Apothecary to Xia Yuan,
it was out of desperation,
but the decision was still our own.
Miss Chu, as you know,
back then, Shouyuan Apothecary
dealt exclusively
in wholesale raw medicinal materials.
Back in 1916,
Xia Yuan sought to enter
the prepared medicine market,
so he set his sights on acquiring
the century-old Chichun Apothecary.
But your brother flat-out refused.
At the same time,
the Guandong and Qizhou Trade Guilds
were locked in a years-long struggle
to control pricing power
in the Qizhou Medicine Market
with neither side
gaining the upper hand.
So Xia Yuan devised a plan
that served both his ambitions.
He first had Yi Dajin use fake Huangqi
to replace the genuine stock
held by the Guandong Trade Guild,
damaging their reputation and business
in the process.
Then he arranged for someone
to resell that original batch of Huangqi
to your brother.
That was quicker than expected.
Later, under the guise
of assisting the investigation,
he caught your brother in the act
and handed him over to Mr. Yang
to deal with.
That gave him leverage over Mr. Yang.
Meanwhile, your brother,
in order to purchase
all the genuine Huangqi,
took on loan shark debt,
which ultimately forced your family
to hand over Chichun Apothecary to him.
So...
it was Xia Yuan all along.
Precisely.
However, there was
an interesting side story to this.
Yi Dajin
had originally planned for Wu
to expose the Guandong Trade Guild
for selling fake Huangqi.
But when it was time for him to testify,
he vanished.
In the end, it was you
who uncovered the fake Huangqi
and brought the truth to light.
Thanks to that,
Shaozhong was later released
by Mr. Yang.
Wu, however, was penalized
with a six-month salary deduction.
Resentful,
he fled with a sum of money.
And just like that, Erniu's fate
was rewritten.
I should board the ship now.
What are your plans moving forward?
None, really.
After years of being entangled
in business power plays,
I'm truly exhausted.
Coming home feels like
the right moment to breathe.
Miracle Pill was saved,
but it cost you your job.
I'm truly sorry.
You don't need to feel guilty.
Honestly, I'd long planned
to leave Xia Yuan.
It's just
I couldn't bring myself
to break the loyalty I felt,
or the respect I owed him as a mentor.
And of course,
I wasn't quite ready
to give up the paycheck.
It wasn't until that moment in court
that I finally made up my mind.
Why was that?
Miss Chu, as you know,
the Japanese are now
shareholders in Shouyuan Apothecary.
If the Miracle Pill formula
ends up in Shouyuan's hands,
it would inevitably
fall into theirs as well.
I may be an ordinary man,
but when it comes
to national interest and justice,
I stand firm.
Mr. Gao,
you have my deepest respect.
Please don't.
Whenever you're ready to return,
you'll always have a place
at Chichun Apothecary.
Miss...
Ms. Chu.
We shall meet again.
Farewell.
Here's your wonton.
Thank you.
She always goes on Wednesday evenings
to the stall by Kongjia Longtang
to eat a bowl of wontons.
By herself?
Yes.
I checked it out.
That intersection is quiet at night,
making it easy to make a move.
Mr. Xia, things have been sensitive.
Is that so?
Two days ago, Chiang Kai-shek
published an article
in the Japanese magazine
Economic Exchange.
In it, he wrote:
"China's concessions
and compromises to Japan
do have certain limits."
Furthermore,
he instructed the Ambassador
to Japan, Chiang Tso-pin,
to inform our government
that should the Chinese government
be pushed beyond endurance,
it will resist the aggressors
at all costs.
Didn't he use to take
a strictly non-confrontational approach?
But recently,
in politics, military affairs,
national defense, diplomacy, and beyond,
he's been quietly maneuvering.
It seems his stance has shifted.
Is he really preparing for war?
I doubt it.
But given how things are now,
he might not have a choice.
I believe
the war between China and Japan
is inevitable.
You must hurry
and secure what we want
before war breaks out.
Alright.
I'll make the arrangements.
That's the situation with Marketing.
What about your side?
It's about the new factory site.
We had a good plot of land all set,
and we were just about to sign
when the owner suddenly pulled out.
I asked around,
and it turns out they got threatened
by some officials.
Ma Juncai's guys?
Probably.
Why not look elsewhere?
I think
Southwest China seems promising.
We don't have to stay tied
to Shanghai or Nanjing.
I'll get on it right away.
Okay.
Great work today, everyone.
Let's call it a day.
Go home and get some rest.
Shaohua,
heading straight home later?
I'm craving a bowl of wontons
before I go.
I'll come with you.
Don't you usually skip supper
to keep your figure?
I just felt like having some today.
You usually go alone,
but tonight, I'm joining you.
Alright.
Cheng Hui, you coming?
I need to head to the factory later.
I'll pass.
You two go ahead.
Alright, we're off.
Oh, and Shaohua,
watch yourself, alright?
Okay.
Don't worry, I'm here.
It's right there.
Pretty packed today.
Go take a seat.
Excuse me,
two bowls of wontons.
Alright.
Is something wrong?
Feels like someone's been
keeping an eye on me.
Could it be Ma Juncai's guys?
Hard to say.
Thank you.
Did they send
those three bullets?
Those guys
love using scare tactics.
I heard Yang Xingfo and Shi Liangcai
were both killed by them.
Shaohua,
I'm afraid they'll lay a hand on you.
Thank you.
Let's finish up quickly
and get going.
Be extra careful these days
and try not to go out alone.
I'll go add some cilantro.
Okay.
Sir, I'd like more cilantro.
Alright, help yourself.
Okay.
Shaohua, watch out!
Erniu!
Hurry! Get a ride!
Okay.
Erniu, hang in there.
Shaohua,
I've actually been shot.
It hurts so much.
I'm taking you to the hospital.
Ouch.
Hang in there.
[Operating Room]
Doctor.
Good thing it missed anything vital.
Don't worry.
You're awake.
Where am I?
The hospital.
The doctor just operated on you.
The bullet has been removed.
I can't believe they actually fired.
Thankfully, you're alright.
The doctor said you lost a lot of blood
and need proper rest.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
But you almost...
You knew
they were going to kill me.
Why did you run toward them?
Why didn't you dodge?
If it were you,
you'd have done the same,
wouldn't you?
I don't know.
I'm not as brave as you.
I'm not brave.
I just
don't want to lose you.
Erniu.
Thank you.
We don't do formalities,
do we?
You can go get the medicine now.
Get some more rest.
I'll get it for you.
Shaohua.
I just meant to scare her!
Why'd you actually shoot?
I didn't think the other woman
would be so fierce.
She even tried to grab my gun,
and it went off by accident.
You told me
Chu Shaohua was usually there
by herself!
But last night, there was another woman.
I told you to handle it fast and clean,
without a fuss,
but you still managed
to mess everything up!
Mr. Ma, how about we try again?
No need.
This should be enough to send a message.
As for what happens next...
I'll take care of
the Patrol Office myself.
You guys,
lay low for a few days.
- Yes.
Get lost.
Hello, Chi...
Miss Chu, this is Ma Juncai.
Mr. Ma,
is there something you need?
I heard
your Deputy General Manager, Miss Bai,
was caught in a robbery
and was shot.
I'm calling to send my regards.
You are indeed well-informed.
The robbers didn't
happen to tell you that, did they?
I heard it from the Patrol Office.
You know,
I have a good relationship
with the Patrol Office.
They'll back me up,
no matter how serious it gets.
Are you saying
you can do whatever you want
and get away with it?
No.
What I mean is,
things aren't safe out there.
You need to be extra careful
when you go out,
especially when you're walking alone
at night,
and try not to carry anything valuable.
People get targeted
not for who they are,
but for what they have.
If you were to run into robbers again,
you could
lose your life.
Ma Juncai,
tell whoever you answer to
that even if I lose my life,
I will never yield.
Should you reconsider
our collaboration, Miss Chu,
please do not hesitate to contact me.
I tolerated seeing
you and Bai Bingxin together
all the time.
You made me throw all shame aside,
create a scene,
and drive her away.
I did that too.
I can't believe
you would kick me out
and even abandon
your own kids.
Why?
I have my plans.
They're
all about money, aren't they?
Shufen,
in this world,
you don't have to trust anyone,
not even me.
But you must trust money.
The money I gave you
is more than enough for you
and our children
to live out your days in comfort.
Yes.
That's the only thing you left behind.
Thank you for understanding.
Understanding?
I've just seen through it all.
All these years,
you've never loved me.
You married me back then
only because
I had a generous dowry.
I've worked hard for decades,
but in your eyes,
I was nothing more than
a maid for your parents,
a housekeeper for your affairs,
and a vessel to bear your children.
Not entirely.
We are family.
Well, it's all over now.
After years of serving this family,
now
I can finally live for myself.
Thank you.
Shufen.
Take good care of our children
and yourself.
Make sure you hold on to that money.
You're on your own now. Good luck.
[Public Shanghai Hospital]
You don't need to help me walk.
I'm feeling much better today.
Shaohua.
I came to check on you.
You look much better than yesterday.
Yes,
the doctor said
I can be discharged tomorrow.
You can get to work.
I'll keep her company.
Okay.
I can't wait
to go back to work.
I've been going stir-crazy.
Erniu,
you can't go back yet.
Why not?
I need to lay low too.
What's wrong?
The Patrol Office has closed the case
on your shooting incident.
They claimed it was a random robber.
How could they close it like that?
It was obviously Ma Juncai's men.
He didn't even bother to cover it up.
He threatened me outright.
If I don't cooperate,
they won't stop
until they get what they want.
It seems they are determined
to get the Miracle Pill formula.
Erniu,
you took a bullet for me this time.
Otherwise,
I might not have made it.
But
next time, I might not be
so lucky.
Let's take them to court.
With a world this wide,
there has to be somewhere
we can still find justice.
Erniu,
I'm afraid I won't live to see the day
justice is served.
Don't talk nonsense.
I'm not afraid to die.
What scares me is that once I'm gone,
the Miracle Pill might be lost forever.
Shaohua,
you'll be fine.
Erniu,
you're the one I trust most
in this world.
So please,
I have a favor to ask.
Go ahead.
I made a backup
of the Miracle Pill formula.
I want to leave it in your care.
Leave it with me?
Can I really trust you?
Of course you can.
Then you have to promise me two things.
First,
don't open this envelope
until after I'm gone.
Second,
once you have the formula,
help me keep the Miracle Pill
alive and thriving.
Maybe you shouldn't
give me the Miracle Pill formula.
What's wrong?
I don't feel like I deserve it.
Erniu.
Deep down,
I believe you're the right person.
We grew up side by side,
and we've been through so much together.
What we share
is more than trust.
It's a bond forged
through life and death.
That's why I feel much more at ease
leaving the Miracle Pill in your hands.
Are you sure?
Absolutely.
Alright.
I just hope
I never have to open this envelope.
That would be for the best.
Whatever happens to me down the road,
I can face it with peace of mind now.
Shaohua,
you've got luck on your side.
You'll be fine.
Right, I need to take care of something
at Chichun Apothecary.
I should get going.
Okay, go ahead.
See you tomorrow.
It's me.
I got it.
♪A blanket lying on the snow♪
♪Melting frost in silent glow♪
♪On endless snowy roads, I roam♪
♪Seeking the shore within my soul♪
♪Winds howl wild♪
♪My soul, near torn♪
♪A blanket hidden deep within his heart♪
♪Warming slowly every part of his heart♪
♪He whispers spring is near♪
♪He says winter is brief♪
♪The eternal shore♪
♪Calls out once more♪
♪Fate, day by day♪
♪Earnest and brave♪
♪Leaves no regrets♪
♪Dawn, bit by bit♪
♪Glorious and scorching♪
♪No longer alone♪
♪Flames light the way
where despair once lay♪
♪I shield you, my very soul entwined♪
♪Through hardship, to the goal♪
♪We reach, at last♪
♪The shore we hold fast♪
♪Fate, day by day♪
♪Earnest and brave♪
♪Leaves no regrets♪
♪Dawn, bit by bit♪
♪Glorious and scorching♪
♪No longer alone♪
♪Flames light the way
where despair once lay♪
♪I shield you, my very soul entwined♪
♪Through hardship, to the goal♪
♪We reach, at last♪
♪The shore we hold fast♪