♪Trap my frame♪
♪Plagues demand I bow in shame♪
♪Snare my soul♪
♪Rules command I swallow my pride♪
♪Mock my way♪
♪Chained me where I must stay♪
♪Taught me to kneel, not to speak♪
♪And to let my life pass by in silence♪
♪But I heard the wind♪
♪From the sea and the sky♪
♪It said don't bend♪
♪Bow your head, and your chains begin♪
♪You are the wave♪
♪And the wind that won't behave♪
♪How could you be chained?♪
♪Untamed, uncaged, unclaimed♪
♪You're the blade in my gaze♪
♪This world will leave you no space♪
♪Then pierce it with your blaze♪
♪My silent grind♪
♪My aching pain♪
♪Will one day turn...♪
♪I am who I am♪
♪My greatest ambition♪
♪If the world can't contain me♪
♪Then I'll break through it♪
♪Become who I am♪
[Wild Ambition Bloom]
[Adapted from Stone and Water's novel,
The Uncaged Flame]
[Episode 21]
And whenever he gets drunk,
he calls out his daughter's name.
All parents who lose their own child
suffers the profoundest anguish,
and they will pay any price
to find their lost child.
Yes.
If we can help him find his daughter,
he will surely return the favor.
But China is so vast.
How should we locate her?
He's searched
for two years with no luck,
so she's probably not in Shanghai.
Following Russian traditions,
if she's not here,
she may be somewhere in the northeast.
Hongnian,
send a telegram to Mr. Yang now.
Ask him to use all available resources
to find Natasha.
You must not give up.
Use all your connections
to keep searching.
Got it.
Alright.
So have you found Natasha?
Mr. Yang's family
has operated in the northeast
for over a century.
They have connections in every town
in three provinces in the northeast.
Once he gave the order,
an apothecary
doing business with them
responded immediately
and said she was in Tsitsihar.
She went to Tsitsihar?
Shortly after arriving in Shanghai,
she dumped the man who had lured her.
Ashamed to face her father,
she fled there alone to make a living.
So Glebov looked in the wrong place.
Indeed.
Learning this precise information,
he didn't hesitate
to partner with us.
I think in about a week,
they will be reunited.
Alright then. Whatever happens,
at least this matter ended well.
But after this case,
I'm afraid it'll be harder
for you to marry Mr. Tian.
Then
should I back down
when facing difficulty?
Cut.
Pass!
Bingxin.
Well done!
Wrap it up here.
What brings you here?
I came to pick you up!
Are you done filming?
If yes, let's go dancing!
The case is over now.
I am of no use.
What does it have to do with the case?
Enough already.
Your family knows what I did
and I know you never took me seriously.
Should we still go dancing?
Do you think it makes sense?
What are you talking about?
You know nothing?
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Exactly.
The case is crucial.
Tongdao wouldn't let you know.
Tongdao?
He walks as himself. I stand as myself.
No matter how he sees you,
isn't it enough that I love you?
Tongxin,
let's part ways.
Here's your ring back.
You're dumping me?
Think of it that way if you must.
No way.
I've been the one to walk away first.
Nobody's ever walked away from me.
Mr. Tian,
there's a first time for everything.
You'll get used to it.
Bai Bingxin,
are you crazy?
I am Mr. Tian,
Deputy General Manager
of Tian's Apothecary!
So what?
You'll regret this.
Fine.
I'll spend my whole life regretting it
and wish you happiness.
But you said before
you'd love and marry me
in this life.
I've changed my mind.
Dare you say you don't love me?
I don't love you.
To be precise, I never did.
Bai Bingxin!
Bingxin!
I refuse to leave your side.
I must stay with you forever.
Stop talking.
Let's part ways from now on.
Don't come to me again.
Bingxin.
Open the door.
Please, Bingxin.
[From Mu Ziru]
Bingxin, let's discuss this calmly.
Bingxin.
I know you're angry with me.
Tell me whatever you desire,
I'll buy it for you.
Bingxin.
Don't treat me like this, Bingxin.
My apologies.
This... well...
[Oriental Bunao Pills sold out today]
Sold out again.
Again!
Sold out!
Our apologies.
Today's supply of Oriental Bunao Pill
has been sold out.
I've been waiting in line for two hours.
Oh!
Me, too.
Truly sorry about this.
It's sold out today.
I feel
we will have a long-term cooperation
with Wen's Pharmacy.
We'll restock very soon!
Don't worry. It'll be available soon.
Please come back another day.
Thanks so much!
How long would that take?
Just wait patiently.
They came out.
Ladies and gentlemen,
don't stand in the queue today.
Only 200 boxes left.
When it's your turn,
the pills will be sold out.
What?
We've waited over two hours!
No more pills left today.
Will there be stock tomorrow?
Going to Xia Yuan's place for dinner?
A family gathering.
Li.
Who will be there from their family?
Just family members.
I think I won't go after all.
Why?
I'm not comfortable visiting
others' homes.
But they specifically invited you!
I'm not feeling well.
I haven't told you the day yet.
I may not feel well any day.
Hey.
Didn't you work overtime today?
Miss Bai, the phone call.
Coming.
Who's calling?
That Mr. Tian again?
Tell him I'm out.
Whenever he calls, tell him I'm out.
Mr. Tian?
Yes.
I've dumped him,
but he just won't give up
and keeps pestering me.
He thinks there's hope.
Tell me
how I can make him give up completely.
I don't know.
I don't even know
how I should move on entirely.
Haven't moved on?
I thought I could move past it.
But
those old memories
keep bubbling up.
It's okay.
As long as we keep running forward,
even if it bubbles up again,
it won't cling to us, right?
Let's hope so.
Mr. Xia!
Just saw Wen's Pharmacy mentioned
in the newspaper
and here you are.
What's the news?
In Shanghai's top 10 TCM apothecaries,
Wen's Pharmacy ranks ninth!
I thought they wouldn't make it
till later this year.
How impatient these reporters are!
Well-deserved!
Please have a seat.
But credit also goes to Mr. Tian.
If he hadn't held Professor Claudy
in such high regard,
Oriental Bunao Pill
wouldn't have been out of stock.
It's still flying off shelves?
Though with two more workshops,
I still can't guarantee a stable supply.
Mr. Wen,
congratulations on booming business!
Mr. Xia, shared prosperity indeed!
Did you come alone?
Where's Shaohua?
She felt a bit unwell today.
Serious?
Should be fine.
Just worn out from these busy days.
Rest should fix her right up.
Alright then.
Let her get some good rest.
Come on, try this tea.
From England?
Black tea.
Give it a taste!
My brother
specifically sent it from Europe.
You have a brother?
Studying in France now.
That's him over there.
Exceptionally handsome and promising!
Absolutely!
He's way better looking than I am.
Besides,
he's seriously smart.
He always topped every subject!
Later he went to study in Japan,
and pursued two majors,
both with straight A's.
After that,
he went to France for further study!
This is a photo he took
with his classmates in Paris.
Is this his wife?
His girlfriend.
But I guess
they'll marry soon.
Mother.
This must be Mr. Wen.
Mother, let me introduce.
This is Wen Zhiqiu,
owner of Wen's Pharmacy.
Good day, Madam.
How do you do?
Xia Yuan often mentions
that you're capable.
Seeing you today,
I can see what a dashing person you are!
You flattered me!
Your sons are truly exceptional.
How can they ever compare with you?
Indeed.
I pale in comparison.
Mr. Wen, you're joking!
This is my wife.
Mrs. Xia.
Greetings, Mr. Wen!
Shall we take our seats?
Mother.
Please.
- Please.
- Come.
Mother.
Mr. Wen, this way please.
I thought Ms. Chu would join us today.
She's unwell,
so won't be attending.
Today
I had our chef prepared
some Qizhou dishes for her.
Too bad she'll miss out on them!
Indeed.
Perhaps
have some Qizhou dishes packed
and sent to her.
Good idea!
Oh right!
Also send over those Qizhou specialties
Mr. Gao brought back.
Okay.
Understood.
Mother,
I think we should send them
a few days later.
Why?
She hasn't been feeling well lately.
If she sees familiar things,
I worry remembering past events
will make her even sadder.
Oh! I completely missed that angle!
What are the past events?
You don't know?
She's never once mentioned it to me.
Because what happened to her
made headlines back then.
I assumed you knew all about them!
Yes.
When reading the news years ago,
I thought how miserable she was.
But later Xia Yuan told me
after losing her husband and daughter,
and suffering the family ruin,
she didn't collapse under grief.
Instead, she's built with you
something truly thriving!
She truly embodies
a modern-day Mulan!
Thinking back, I…
Mother,
shall we begin the feast now?
Yes, let's enjoy!
Come now!
Mr. Wen.
Mr. Xia,
welcome!
Please.
After losing her husband and daughter,
and suffering the family ruin,
she didn't collapse under grief.
Instead, she's built with you
something truly thriving.
She truly embodies
a modern-day Mulan!
[Yangchun Noodles]
I thought you dined at Xia Yuan's place.
Why are you here for wontons?
Didn't get enough to eat?
Want a bowl?
Sure!
Boss! One more bowl of wontons!
Oh right.
You want to discuss with me, huh?
Xia Yuan mentioned
we could collaborate further.
What do you think?
I think it's a great idea!
Did he mention the details?
No details given.
Who did you meet at his place today?
His mother
and his wife.
Didn't see his children.
They seem to board at school.
Only learned today
that he has a brother
studying in France.
Your wontons are ready!
- Thanks!
- Thanks.
Enjoy your meal.
Has his…
Thank you.
Has his brother
got married yet?
Not yet, but soon.
She must be very beautiful, right?
Yes.
Truly stunning.
I used to think you were strange.
Didn't realize you had a profound past.
Everyone has past.
I mean
Sanshou Gang and Huashun Apothecary.
You had a daughter.
Eat now. Let's drop this topic.
Saw it in the papers before,
but didn't connect the dots.
Always felt...
Let's stop.
Speak it out and you may feel better.
I've long since let go of it.
If you hadn't brought it up,
I wouldn't have remembered it.
Letting go of or avoiding it?
What am I avoiding?
Otherwise why
would you refuse to go with me today?
Fear of seeing old acquaintances?
Or perhaps...
Just eat wontons!
Do you consider me a friend?
No.
We're just partners.
That direct, huh?
Fine.
I just hope you can
live happily and more lightheartedly.
I am truly happy
and lightheartedly.
Thank you for caring.
It doesn't seem so.
Truly, I want to help you.
I don't need your help.
Nor do I want anyone's pity.
That's not what I meant.
Whether I can let go
or move on or not,
that's my own business.
All I want is to care about you.
None of your business.
Are the Cost Statement
and Income and Expenditure Statement
ready?
On your desk.
Qingyu Apothecary's contract...
Will be ready by 10 AM.
And that merchant on Sima Road…
The figure missing
will be filled in by this afternoon.
Come in!
Wu.
Mr. Wen, Ms. Chu,
would you two honor
my wedding next month?
Thank you.
Impressive!
You really kept it quiet.
Who's the bride?
A girl from my hometown.
We grew up together.
Childhood sweethearts.
And would you do me a favor?
Mr. Wen,
could you be my wedding witness?
Of course!
Ms. Chu, would you host the ceremony?
Me?
She won't do.
Why?
She is not good at speaking.
Few can match her eloquence.
Let me host it.
But you will be the witness.
I can do both.
Can you handle both?
No problem.
Perhaps you can be the host
and Ms. Chu the witness.
She might not have time for the wedding.
Ms. Chu, you won't make it?
She has a business trip scheduled.
That's such a pity.
Truly, such a pity.
The business trip
can be pushed back.
Wu, don't worry.
I'll absolutely be at your wedding.
Also
you can count on me for hosting duties.
That's perfect!
When bringing me lunch last time,
my girlfriend saw you
and was charmed
by your poise and talent.
She mentioned it repeatedly
that we must have you at our wedding.
Thank you.
Thanks, Ms. Chu.
Thanks, Mr. Wen.
May your love endure forever!
Thank you.
I know you were caring about me.
Worried I might get upset
during the wedding.
So you know I care about you.
Yesterday
I acted on impulse.
Sorry.
From now on,
you don't have to consider my feelings.
Because I've grown
thick skin anyway.
I know you have.
That's why I provoked you yesterday,
forcing you to confront your true self.
Make a qipao!
Why bother?
You're attending a wedding.
It's not my wedding.
But please consider
upholding Wen's Pharmacy's reputation.
If we're talking about that,
then yes.
But you'll cover the cost.
You're also our shareholder.
Why should I?
I never intended to make a qipao.
You asked me to.
And you're the majority shareholder.
Deal.
Also
I think it's time to swap out my shoes.
These ones are…
Don't push it.
And I should
buy a new bag.
Ms. Chu,
go on a business trip to Suzhou.
Come in.
Mr. Wen, today's newspaper.
Thanks!
Mr. Wen, Evernew Department then.
It's settled then.
[Full Text
of Tian Tongxin's Suicide Note]
[Another Stir
Between Tian Tongxin and Bai Bingxin]
Erniu!
What's wrong?
Mr. Tian has committed suicide!
I thought it was something serious!
Sun told me
he took pills last night,
and he is alright now.
But aren't you going to visit him?
Why would I?
He tried to kill himself for you.
Attempted suicide over a breakup.
How utterly contemptible!
Guess how many pills he took?
Three.
Three?
If they hadn't sent him
to the hospital in time,
before starting a stomach pump,
he would've woken up.
But I think you should go see him.
You two shared something special,
after all.
Don't be so harsh.
Remember how he treated Ni Xiangying?
That was truly harsh.
I've done all I could for him!
But to marry him,
you tried every trick in the book.
Why did you change so fast?
I should thank you for that.
Me?
If not for your lawsuit,
I'd still be living in fantasy
of marrying into his family.
Only now do I realize
they never saw me
as one of their own.
Precisely speaking,
they didn't even treat me as a human.
Since this is a dead end,
I must make a better choice.
It's good you think this way.
Truly comforting.
Rest assured.
Arrived this early?
Wait for me.
I'll change clothes and come down.
Who's he?
A man.
But you said you'd make a better choice.
His name's Mu Ziru,
the fourth man in Qing Gang,
rich and powerful.
He came from poor roots
and his parents are gone.
But he is a better choice
than Tongxin.
Erniu,
still leaning on men?
Who else can I depend on
if not men?
Women don't need men
to find their way forward!
What other choice do I have?
Maybe this is my best choice.
But he belongs to Qing Gang.
I fear he might harm you.
Don't worry.
On this path,
with or without men,
I stay true to myself.
As long as I'm being heartless,
no one can truly hurt me.
I'm leaving now.
Take care.
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
Not at all!
Please, get in the car.
[Shanghai Hospital]
Just for wretched Bai,
you tried to kill yourself.
You've utterly humiliated our family!
What happened?
You're here just in time.
Curse him out for me!
Talk sense into him!
Tongxin,
I thought you loved each other!
How come you broke up suddenly?
I have no idea.
She has toyed with him
and the Tian family.
How dare she oppose Tian's Apothecary!
Who is backing her?
I don't care.
If she opposes us, I'll crush her.
Don't, Tongdao!
Come on! Show some backbone already!
But I like her.
Tongxin,
don't act like this!
Miss Bai is indeed beautiful,
but gorgeous women
can be found everywhere,
even someone identical to her,
right?
Why cling so stubbornly to her,
I refuse.
I want only her.
Look!
Why don't you just kill yourself?
I was planning to kill myself.
But you saved me!
Fine.
Stop arguing, alright?
Zhou,
what did you just say?
You said there is someone
identical to Wretched Bai.
Yes.
That prostitute I knew in Peking
shares the same figure and eyes
with Bai Bingxin.
Prostitute?
Never
let my wife know that.
You said they look exactly the same?
I can't tell them apart.
No way!
I don't believe it.
Bingxin is absolutely one of a kind.
You're not my brother,
but my ancestor!
See you, Tongdao.
Zhou,
where is the prostitute
you mentioned?
Why are you
asking about her?
I want to find her
to disgust Wretched Bai.
And to cool my jets.
Better drop it.
Why?
I don't dare get mixed up
with her again.
Nothing will happen.
Tell me her name
and current whereabouts.
I'll handle everything else.
You won't be implicated.
You fancy a pair
of pink-glazed vases, huh?
Lu Ningxiang
at Linfang Pavilion.
What are they?
You'll host the wedding.
Those dark circles under your eyes...
Your face
needs some pampering.
Mr. Wen,
why are you suddenly so generous?
Got my eye on you.
Oh, give me a break!
I want you to gladly dedicate to work.
As long as the paycheck
and shares are generous enough,
I'll gladly dedicate to work.
If a box of bird's nest is enough,
why bother with the rest?
So that's your angle.
Pretty smart, huh?
I won't hold back on this gift,
the salary or the stake.
You're a sharp calculator.
Impressive, huh?
Mr. Wen, Ms. Chu, something went wrong.
[Wen's Pharmacy]
The seized drugs
total 23,500 silver dollar in value.
All scheduled to be shipped to Hangzhou.
Go to the police department
for their official stance.
I'll inquire through other channels.
Got it.
Don't you know
why they were seized?
We have no idea.
Someone reported you,
accusing Wen's Pharmacy
of openly trading in herbs,
but secretly smuggling opium.
That's absolutely impossible!
A simple investigation
would reveal the truth.
How long will it take?
Hard to say exactly.
At best, six months.
At worst, three to five years.
That means
our goods will be held
for at least six months?
If nothing is found wrong,
we'll return it immediately.
If something,
you'll be put into prison.
Who made the report then?
I can't tell you that.
Since someone reported,
he wouldn't do that blindly.
He must have shown evidence.
The report counts as evidence.
According to your logic,
as long as there's a report,
whether backed by proof or not,
even if it's baseless hearsay,
you can just seize the goods.
That's it.
Fine then.
[Wanted: Jin Handing & Huang Yucheng]
Sir!
I want to report.
Report what?
He's in cahoots
with Jin Handing and Huang Yucheng!
Don't speak groundlessly.
He knows exactly
where they are hiding.
That could get me killed!
Arrest him first.
Investigate him for six months.
Don't listen to her.
She's talking nonsense!
No evidence at all.
The report counts as evidence.
Young lady,
what are you trying to do?
I just want to know
why you're seizing our goods
for no reason.
Let me be frank with you.
I have no idea about that.
Mr. Wang instructed us to do that.
We're just carrying out orders.
We have no choice.
Mr. Wang?
Yes.
You can't just meet Mr. Wang
as you like.
I have urgent business
to consult with him personally.
No.
Please kindly deliver my message.
I don't have time.
Come on, sir.
Sir.
Mr. Wang.
Good day, Mr. Wang.
I'm Chu Shaohua,
General Manager of Wen's Pharmacy.
Mr. Wang,
you look pale,
with swelling under your eyes
and ashen lips.
Have you been experiencing
frequent dizziness,
weakness in the lower back and knees
and cold extremities lately?
Talking nonsense!
Do you often have trouble
falling asleep,
get up frequently at night
and are struggle with sexual affairs?
Stop!
Or I'll arrest you!
Please calm down.
That stems from weakened vital fire.
You need to tonify your middle jiao
and boost qi,
as well as nourish essence
and replenish marrow.
Wen's Pharmacy's Jinkui Shenqi Pill
works wonders for your symptoms!
Take it for three consecutive days,
your condition will greatly improve.
Additionally, our Oriental Bunao Pill
can instantly relieve your dizziness.
Mr. Wang,
give them a try.
You're from Wen's Pharmacy.
Yes, here's my business card.
Mr. Wang,
we have a batch of finished medicine
called Oriental Bunao Pill.
This very one.
Your subordinates seized it.
They insisted it was smuggled opium!
We're wronged!
That's why I come here at once
to see you
for an opportunity to appeal.
We'll know if you're wronged
once our investigation concludes.
You may return and await notification.
How long will it take?
Just three to five days, I suppose.
That's wonderful news!
Mr. Wang, thank you so much!
I won't take up any more of your time.
Alright.
Thank you.
Mr. Wang,
remember to take the pills.
Alright.
See you.
[Wen's Pharmacy]
[Manager's Office]
Tomorrow, bring him
more Jinkui Shenqi Pill
and Oriental Bunao Pill.
Also, strengthen the relationship.
Hope for the best.
That won't work. I've learned
Mr. Tian is the one behind all this.
Mr. Tian?
The Tian family
is connected
to Songhu Police Department.
So after Wang Guodong took office,
Mr. Tian poured a lot into him.
By seizing our goods,
he is taking revenge on us.
What did Mr. Xia say?
He reached out to a few industry peers.
But all the connections
he secured were
on Lu Yongxiang's side.
Wang Guodong answers to Qi Xieyuan,
disregarding Lu Yongxiang.
How intriguing!
I even turned
to a friend of Wang Guodong for help
to invite Wang Guodong to dinner.
But he's so arrogant,
so hard to get a hold of him.
Hello!
Yunlong!
We were just talking about you.
Yeah.
Alright, got it.
Thanks!
Wang Guodong
agreed to come out for dinner.
Really?
But
he requested that you join him.
Me?
You know what?
Oriental Bunao Pill works wonders!
Last night I took a whole bottle
of the pills you gave me,
my condition improved dramatically.
That's wonderful news!
Mr. Wang,
alleviating patients' suffering
is precisely the founding principle
of Wen's Pharmacy.
Yes, ever since we opened our doors,
we've always adhered
to our ancestors' teachings.
Smuggling opium is something
we would never do.
Mr. Wang, please take a look.
Here are the contracts signed
with several Suzhou merchants
for that batch of goods,
along with the payment receipts,
warehouse dispatch records,
the packing records
and contracts with
the freight forwarder.
By comparing with physical things,
you'll see
the opium smuggling allegations
are completely baseless!
With these vague claims
and a few documents,
you expect me to fully trust you?
I'm afraid that's simply impossible.
No.
Over 20 apothecaries
of Shanghai TCM Guild
stand ready to testify on our behalf.
Yes.
This is impossible, isn't it?
Mr. Wang,
if that's your final decision,
we must close forever.
Not really.
You have no idea.
To open this apothecary,
Mr. Wen mortgaged all his assets,
and took on massive debts.
After great efforts,
Oriental Bunao Pill just
opened up an outlet.
But
such an absurd incident happened.
If we can't retrieve the goods,
Mr. Wen
has to beg for food on Nanjing Road.
And I
will lose my job.
You'll also have to suffer?
I absolutely won't allow that.
Mr. Wang,
please show us some mercy
and let our goods go.
Ms. Chu,
let me tell you frankly.
By acting pitiful
and miserable,
you will never
get your goods back.
Yes, exactly as I said.
Right.
Finally Mr. Wang
dines with us,
but we've been discussing work.
Mr. Wang,
I raise my glass to you!
Yunlong couldn't
make it back this time,
so he asked me to raise a toast
in his place.
Yunlong is your friend?
Yes.
Then you are also my friend.
It's nothing.
Let's have a drink.
Thank you, Mr. Wang!
Thank you!
Please give us more support!
Yunlong and I were classmates
at Beifang Police Academy.
Since he's spoken up,
I can hardly turn down his request.
But speaking of that,
upon closer reflection,
I found our schoolmate connection
won't carry enough weight.
Then
what if I add this?
Actually,
it's not that complicated.
If you want your goods back,
just agree to one condition from me.
Please tell us what it is.
If you become
my eighth concubine,
I'll release the goods immediately.
I…
You must be joking!
He is surely making a joke.
Mr. Wang,
making jokes calls for a penalty drink!
But I never joke.
I'm completely serious.
In this case,
I'll give you my serious reply.
That's impossible.
I believe
nothing is impossible in my world.
You old rascal!
Wait!
Hold on a second.
Mr. Wang, look at her.
She has a quick temper.
Alright.
Put it down.
I like her quick temper.
That's interesting.
- Old pervert!
- Easy. Easy.
Rascal!
You weak old man!
Chu Shaohua.
Let go.
Wait a moment.
Mr. Wang,
if you fancy this type,
later I can find you two
better than her.
No.
I insist on her.
It's not appropriate.
She
has been married and had a child.
This isn't good.
Wen,
let me tell you frankly.
Among my seven concubines,
there are students,
actresses,
but not a female manager yet.
Make way.
Chu Shaohua.
Mr. Wang,
I spoke recklessly just now,
carried away by impulse.
This drink here is my apology for that.
Exactly.
You were being disrespectful just now.
You deserve it,
right?
A single glass won't do for an apology.
At least a whole bottle!
You're absolutely right.
A full bottle as punishment!
I'll drink it for her instead.
No need. Give it to me.
Chu...
She is bold.
The bolder you are, the more I like you.
Mr. Wang,
you see
this is just my nature.
What do you say?
If you marry me,
your household may be chaotic.
No.
The ladies in my household
are all very virtuous.
They'll surely treat you well.
Impossible!
A fortune-teller once said
her fate is too strong.
She brought misfortune to her father,
and after she married,
she brought death to her husband.
Wonderful!
The fortune-teller said
I carry killing energy in my fate.
A stronger woman can better support me.
Mr. Wang,
to be honest,
I
have a fiancé.
You have a fiancé?
Who is he?
Him.
Then it's simple.
♪A blanket lying on the snow♪
♪Melting frost in silent glow♪
♪On endless snowy roads, I roam♪
♪Seeking the shore within my soul♪
♪Winds howl wild♪
♪My soul, near torn♪
♪A blanket hidden deep within his heart♪
♪Warming slowly every part of his heart♪
♪He whispers spring is near♪
♪He says winter is brief♪
♪The eternal shore♪
♪Calls out once more♪
♪Fate, day by day♪
♪Earnest and brave♪
♪Leaves no regrets♪
♪Dawn, bit by bit♪
♪Glorious and scorching♪
♪No longer alone♪
♪Flames light the way
where despair once lay♪
♪I shield you, my very soul entwined♪
♪Through hardship, to the goal♪
♪We reach, at last♪
♪The shore we hold fast♪
♪Fate, day by day♪
♪Earnest and brave♪
♪Leaves no regrets♪
♪Dawn, bit by bit♪
♪Glorious and scorching♪
♪No longer alone♪
♪Flames light the way
where despair once lay♪
♪I shield you, my very soul entwined♪
♪Through hardship, to the goal♪
♪We reach, at last♪
♪The shore we hold fast♪