[slow rock music plays]
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa, oh, yeah… ♪
[Pond] Time is a strange thing.
I always feel my time is
longer than everybody else's.
I thought life was gonna get better
after the statute of limitations expired.
But I guess I forgot
that some people can't wait that long.
Even if we never see each other again,
always remember that I love you.
♪ Oh, yeah… ♪
[Mam] You can't expect us
to keep running with you.
And you're still
sending money to that family.
When is it all gonna stop?
Enough is enough. If you really love
our children, it's best we separate.
♪ And I will say goodbye to you… ♪
[Pond] The truth took
everything I loved from me.
♪ Want my freedom ♪
TITLE DEED
TAKUA PA, PHANG NGA
LOAN CONTRACT
♪ Want my freedom, yeah… ♪
[Pond] But eventually,
lying gave me a new life.
- [man] Captain!
- [crew cheering]
Yeah!
♪ Hey, hey, this is what life… ♪
[man] In July 1997, suffering
from speculative attacks,
the Thai government was forced
to float the Thai baht.
The Thai economy collapsed,
and ultimately fell under the mercy of
the International Monetary Fund, or IMF.
[Pond] Life kept toying with me.
The inflation rate had doubled my debt.
That fake little deed also cost me.
- Let's go.
- Six months in jail.
♪ Want my freedom… ♪
Hi, boss.
♪ Ooh, oh, oh, yeah ♪
[Pond] But I wasn't gonna give up.
[boss] Oh-ho-ho!
[chuckling]
I can't believe my fuckin' eyes.
Mr. Pond here has come to borrow my money.
Life is full of ups and downs.
And today is… just not my day.
[boss] Oh-ho.
Because of you,
the ship's been confiscated.
Haven't you learned?
Huh.
You'll get your money back.
How much you want?
Five million.
I don't think you'll
be able to handle that.
[moody music plays]
But all right.
I'll lend it to you.
20% monthly interest.
And if you can't pay me back…
[chuckles]
…you'll just have
to come work for me here.
[laughs]
Till you're dead.
[boss laughing]
I'll take cash.
[man] Continuing
with recent breaking news.
Sometime in the middle of the night
on November the 19th, 1999,
a major fire broke out in a warehouse
in the Rangsit area.
According to an eyewitness,
there was a loud bang
from the maintenance room.
Then, the fire spread quickly.
The fire burned nonstop for several hours,
destroying all the products
stored at the facility.
The authorities suspect
the cause of the fire was a short circuit,
but the arson squad was called in
to rule out foul play.
Further investigation
into the actual cause is ongoing.
[Pond] But fate
had to screw me over one more time.
Fuck!
Did I really have
nothing left to live for?
[pager buzzing]
YOUR DAD'S SERIOUSLY ILL.
PLEASE BRING OUR GRANDKIDS
TO SEE HIM, POND / MOM
[upbeat country music playing]
[Bung scoffs]
You get lost in Bangkok.
How are you gonna cope in America?
You're such a shitty navigator! I told you
to ask that old man for directions.
[Keg] The map's too small.
It's so hard to read.
Should be able to enlarge it.
[Bung groans]
Who do you think this Mr. Noi is?
I wonder what kind of work
Pond does for him.
Pond is so mysterious.
[Keg tuts] Maybe Pond's a…
spy or something?
- [Bung snorts]
- [Keg chuckles]
Yeah. I kind of feel like a spy myself,
with all this role-playing.
You know what?
A call center agent's sorta like a spy.
You know all these secrets,
but you can't tell anyone.
Are there any secrets you can tell me?
Yeah.
But if I tell you,
I'll have to kill you.
- [Bung sighs]
- [Keg chuckles]
Forget about it, then. Mmph.
Knowing secrets is only useful
when you know whose secrets they are.
Sometimes, it's not a secret.
It's just stuff other people don't know.
Can you look at my dad's?
- Do you wanna know?
- Mm-hmm.
I'd rather know than not know.
They say that once you know,
you'll get hurt.
How the hell do they know that?
[Keg] Hmm.
What if I tell you…
that Yuyee has a boyfriend?
Gimme your hand.
What?
Say it again.
Yuyee's got a lover.
A boyfriend.
What? You said you wanted to know.
Now I don't wanna tell you anything.
I said I could handle it.
I just don't want you
to waste your time on her.
[engine revving]
[Bung] You sure we won't get lost again?
[Keg] Positive.
- [engine idling]
- [Bung] Are you sure this is the place?
- It looks abandoned.
- [engine switches off]
What did the pager say?
Warehouse 7.
[vehicle approaching]
- [Keg] Hey.
- [Bung] Hmm?
- Mmph.
- [starts engine]
[moody music plays]
[engine switches off]
NO UNAUTHORIZED ENTRY
WAREHOUSE 7
Why would Pond come here?
Beats me.
[creaking]
[rattling sounds]
[man] Hey!
How'd you get in here?
Didn't you see the sign outside?
You need permission to get in!
W-we're looking for Pond.
We heard he works here.
We need to bring him back home.
How did you know he worked here?
Who told you?
[wheels clattering]
[glass clinking]
Dad!
- Where have you been?
- Hey, hey, hey! Stop! What are you doin'?
You can't come in here.
I said you can't come in, shit for brains!
[Pond] Hey!
Are these your kids?
Yeah.
They don't know any better.
I'll handle it.
If Mr. Noi finds out,
we'll be in big shit.
[device whirrs]
[Bung] Where have you been?
We sent messages. You didn't respond.
You need to go back.
Get your bag and we'll go.
How'd you get here?
This is too dangerous. You should leave.
Grandma passed away.
You should be there for the cremation.
Grandpa really wants to talk to you.
This is a family matter. Not your problem.
It's too late for that.
[Pond] In that case…
say goodbye to Grandma for me.
- How could you say that?
- [pouring]
[grabs mug]
I didn't expect you to be such a loser.
I'm trying to be understanding
and sympathetic here,
but you're behaving like a bitter runaway.
And you're still a kid who
thinks the world is a wonderful place.
But life…
isn't all sunshine and flowers, Bung.
[Keg sighs]
It's too late anyway. You two should go.
[Keg] Pond.
You might not think of me as family,
but to me, she's my grandma.
Stop running away from things.
Grandma asked me to tell you,
you shouldn't wait for someone to die
before seeing your family.
[man] Hey! Hey! Your time's up!
You gotta go!
How did she go?
She died in her sleep.
How's Grandpa?
[Bung] He's doing okay.
He's been strong.
Hey! Pond!
Where the hell do you think you're going?
I'm not going anywhere.
Just showing them out.
So you can stop screaming now.
You may have been hot shit a while ago,
but I'm your boss now. You got that?
Just go.
Say goodbye to Grandma for me.
[tuts] Pond.
Go on.
Just leave.
[melancholy music plays]
[Keg sighs]
[car door opens]
[engine starts]
[boss] Stop moping around!
Get back to work!
[music fades]
[knocking at door]
[door opens]
Hey. What are you doing?
Well, Sodsai once told me
to donate these things to those who
can make use of them when she died.
- Let me give you a hand.
- Okay.
Oh!
[laughs]
I bet she was hot stuff
when she was younger.
[Kew] Oh yeah.
She was the prettiest girl around.
Do you know
who I had to compete with
for her affections?
[Lilly chuckles]
A policeman,
a sheriff,
and a banker.
How'd you two meet, anyway?
Uh…
She needed her photo taken
for a job application.
Yeah. She wanted to apply
for this lucrative accounting job
in Bangkok.
I teased her and said my studio was
also looking for an accountant.
- [chuckles]
- [Lilly] Ooh!
[emotional music plays]
- And what did she say?
- Of course she said no.
- [laughs]
- She said that, uh…
Oh yeah. She asked me
if I could even afford to hire her.
[laughs] That must've left you
pretty stunned, huh?
Not really.
So I lied to her and I said
that the photo I'd taken wasn't good.
- Hmm.
- I asked her to come back for a retake.
After that, I kept making up excuses
for us to see each other.
Oh, you…
Then, finally, she just…
- changed her mind about leaving.
- Hmm.
She didn't go to Bangkok.
- Applied for a job at the mine instead.
- Oh! [laughs]
- So you got yourself a wife instead of…
- Yes.
…an accountant.
[both laugh]
[Lilly] Hah!
[both chuckle]
This… is that first photo.
[doorbell rings]
Um… do you want me
to say we're closed today?
Uh…
No. We'd better keep it open.
We should do something,
or Sodsai'll complain.
[music fades]
Mam, you go mind the store.
If you need help, shout.
[Lilly] All right.
- Hello.
Are you here to get your photo taken
or to print photos?
[suspenseful music plays]
[Kew] Mam! Where are my pills again?
They're on the table in your bedroom, Dad.
Is your name, uh, Mam?
Yeah.
[Lilly chuckles]
Um…
I'm applying for a job
and I need my photo taken.
Oh. Uh…
Dad, uh, can you come?
DADDY POND
A customer wants her photo taken.
- Just a minute.
- Sure.
[music fades]
[musical bleeping]
[bleep]
Oh.
Uh, miss?
Your pet's dying.
[Lilly chuckles]
Do you have one too?
I have a panda.
- Do you mind?
- Go ahead.
I've been so busy.
I haven't really had time
to look after it.
[Mag] Oh…
Your pet's fully grown now.
It's ready to have a family.
It'll be sad if you let it die.
[Lilly] Hmm.
I'll try not to.
If you don't have time to care for it,
just press these two buttons.
It'll pause the game.
When you're ready to play again,
press the same two buttons.
Really? I didn't know you could do that.
- [bleeping]
- Wow.
- Thank you so much!
- Yeah.
[chuckles] Come on. Let me help you.
Has this studio been in business for long?
[Lilly] Mm…
Yeah. I think it's been a while.
[Mag] Mmm.
You don't live here, then?
No, I don't.
This place belongs to my in-laws.
I saw your family photo.
You've got a nice family.
Um…
Is your husband here with you?
[Lilly] No.
He's working out of town right now.
Oh. Okay.
[door opens]
Hello, sir.
[Kew] Hello, young lady.
Hey.
You don't look familiar.
Are you new in town?
No, I'm just visiting here.
- Uh, sir?
- Yes, miss?
Does my hair look all right?
Uh…
Maybe put your hair back.
And sit up nice and straight.
Okay.
- Hey, Mam.
- [Lilly] Yeah?
- [door opens]
- [Kew] Uh…
Say, have you heard
from Mag and Mon at all?
- It's a long drive and I'm a bit worried.
- [Lilly] Hmm…
That's sweet of you to worry about them.
- I'll page them for you, okay?
- [Kew] Thanks.
Y-your grandchildren on a trip?
They went to get their father.
They should be back in a few days.
- Mmm.
- [Mag] Hmm.
- Uh, sir?
- Yes?
Do you remember me?
Hmm.
Well, have you had your photo taken here?
I don't remember you.
I'm sorry. I don't.
[sentimental music plays]
- It was when I was very young.
- [Kew] Oh really?
Well, you're all grown up now.
Yup. [chuckles]
You ready?
Hold still. Here we go.
You can give me a little smile.
- All right. I'll count to three.
- [winds camera]
One, two, three.
[shutter clicks]
[Lilly] What's your name?
[music fades]
It's uh, Fiona.
[writing]
[Lilly] Come back at four to pick them up.
SAENG ARTHIT PHOTO STUDIO
[suspenseful music plays]
[dialogue inaudible]
[man] Uh, really? How do you know
they're pretending to be us?
Mon, listen to me.
What are the odds that
Dad's new wife is called Mam?
And their kids are Mag and Mon?
Don't you think that's weird?
Uh… um, should we call the police?
I haven't got proof yet.
And besides,
Grandpa didn't even recognize me.
I'm not surprised.
We were only, what, three or four
when he last saw us?
So… so what should we do now?
They're bringing Dad back.
The two of them who are supposed to be us.
I'm gonna wait around a bit to see Dad.
I don't know what's going on here.
It's so weird.
Just be careful.
Okay? Let's talk when you get back.
THE CREMATION OF MRS. SODSAI JUENGNIRAN
[wind chimes tinkling]
Hello there, Grandma.
Do you remember me?
MRS. SODSAI JUENGNIRAN
It's me, Mag.
I'm the real Mag.
Excuse me.
Do you know how she died?
[music fades]
I heard she died in her sleep
while she was in Bangkok.
Her grandchildren brought her back.
Hmm.
Do her son and
grandchildren live up there?
Uh…
I… used to help her out sometimes.
Back then, she didn't live with her son.
Well, she'd been living here
with her husband.
He got really sick last month,
and her son brought the grandkids
down here to visit them.
[suspenseful music plays]
MRS. SODSAI JUENGNIRAN
RELIGIOUS CEREMONY 29 DECEMBER 1999
HOSTED BY THE JUENGNIRAN FAMILY
MR. ARTHIT, MR. TAWAN, MRS. ALISA,
MS. LALITA, AND MR. SARANYU JUENGNIRAN
- It's about time, man.
- What's up?
Here. Drink up. [sniffs]
[music fades]
[sighs]
[bleeping]
[buzzing]
UNCLE, WHERE ARE YOU?
GRANDMA CAME TO VISIT
GET BACK TO ME ASAP / KEG
WHERE ARE YOU? A BUNCH OF US MISS YOU
UNCLE, CALL ME BACK ASAP / KEG
PLEASE COME HOME, POND
FROM MOM
[sentimental music plays]
[Pond sniffles]
[pager buzzes]
- [breathing shakily]
- [music fades]
I'M WAITING FOR YOU.
CALL ME BACK AT 038-252401
ROOM 301. FROM KEG
[sniffles]
[sentimental music resumes]
[music fades]
It was Sodsai's.
She was really hoping that Pond would
propose to his girlfriend with that ring.
[music resumes]
But Pond ran away
before she could give it to him.
Now, I'm giving it to you on her behalf.
Try it on.
I think it suits you.
[gasps]
Thanks so much.
Thank you, Mom.
[inhales shakily]
[sobs]
[exhales shakily]
[sighs]
[pop music playing in distance]
I'm not sad that he's leaving.
I'm just sad
that he didn't tell me about it.
What kind of mother am I?
Why doesn't my son confide in me?
[Ruk] I'm sure he has his reasons.
He'll tell you when he's ready.
Don't you worry.
Oh! Wait.
What do you think about this dress?
Is Keg okay with it?
[chuckles] Of course he is.
He picked it out himself.
[laughs]
Isn't it pretty?
Why do you wanna go
back to modeling again?
Come on. It's my life.
Look. This is why…
Keg doesn't tell you stuff.
He wants to go to America
because he feels uncomfortable here.
[emotional music plays]
What are you talking about?
I raised him. I know him.
He never acted uncomfortable
or embarrassed.
- Not once.
- Because he loves you.
- You don't know him better than I do.
- Of course I do.
You can only talk to him as a mom.
But I… I get to talk to him as a friend.
I got a job at the call center
so I could work with him.
Ruk, come on!
[sighs]
And you say you want to be a family again?
If he finds out, he'll never forgive you.
I had to become his friend
because you wouldn't let me be his father.
I wanted to get to know him,
and be close to him.
But now, I'm ready to be his father again.
[sobbing]
Pupae.
It's time to face the truth here, honey.
You've got to admit
that what you're doing
makes him feel uncomfortable.
And I'll tell him the truth.
I'll apologize.
But what if he feels betrayed
and never wants to talk to us again?
Pupae.
Don't you worry.
We'll get through this together.
I know Keg loves you very much.
All I want to do right now
is reunite our family.
[lightbulb buzzing]
[music fades]
[sighs]
[Bung humming "A Hard Day's Night"]]
[stops humming]
Hey.
You're back.
- [closes zip]
- Anything to eat down there?
What do you want?
There's a convenience store
and a noodle stall.
Wash your hands.
[runs water]
[turns water off]
[under breath] Shiiiiit.
[brushing teeth]
Mon, Mon, Mon, Mon, Mon,
Mon, Mon, Mon, Mon, Mon, Mon, Mon…
[exhales]
[Keg] Hey, Bung?
Don't you think those guys
at the warehouse were kinda creepy?
I wonder how Pond got involved with them.
[Bung] Hmm. He probably owes them money.
Oh.
Mm-hmm.
[phone rings]
[tense music plays]
[creaking]
[insects chirping]
[panting]
Wait. Pond won't see us
if we turn the lights off.
Yeah. But then those creeps
could see us before Pond does.
Hmm. Good call.
Which warehouse again?
The same one. Warehouse 7.
You stay and wait in the car.
I'll go and take a look. It's dangerous.
Mmm.
Don't turn off the engine.
You can take off fast if things go wrong.
If I'm not back in 30 minutes,
leave without me.
And don't look back.
[scoffs]
You watch too many movies.
[music stops]
[tuts] I'm serious.
Leave if things go south.
I'm worried about you.
Mmm.
I'm worried about you too.
Brother.
Sister.
[Bung] Be careful out there.
[tense music plays]
Shit!
[gasps]
- I'm so sorry! Please don't hurt me.
- Quiet! Be quiet.
[Keg shivering]
Quiet. Shh.
Hey. It's me.
- You scared me.
- Shh!
[tuts] I almost punched you.
Thank God I saw you first.
- Easy. You'll be throwing punches soon.
- Huh?
- They probably know I've escaped by now.
- What?
[gasps] So, what now?
- Where's Bung?
- She's in the alley, in the car.
[footsteps]
[Keg] Oh!
[whimpering]
[footsteps]
Hey.
[music intensifies]
Oh!
Let's go.
[boss] Where you goin', bro?
[rock music plays]
[man 1] Hey! Who's there?
Think I wouldn't see ya,
sneakin' around here like that?
Don't bother tryin' to run, either.
We've been good buddies for ages.
Let's not settle this the hard way.
Come back with me.
Don't worry, bro.
I won't tell Mr. Noi.
But you belong to Mr. Noi.
You have to stay here.
Heh.
You talk way too much.
[music stops]
[fast rock music resumes]
Pond!
Yaah!
Keg, run!
Fuck you, Pond!
Go get water! Put out the fire!
- Get the goods out!
- [man 2] Come on!
- [boss] The liquor!
- [man 2] Let's go!
No water in here!
Fuck you, Pond!
- [man 1] Hey!
- Shit!
[tires squealing]
[man 1] Follow them!
Go!
[tires squealing]
[boss] Hey! Follow them!
Pond, Bung's here.
[horn blares]
Hey! Are you seriously leaving us here?
Just catch up!
- [tires squealing]
- Pond! Look!
- [Pond] Shit! Run! Go on!
- [Keg] Shit! Yeah!
Hah!
- [gasps]
- Are you guys okay?
[Keg] Yeah. Where's Pond?
- [tires squeal]
- Pond, hurry!
[Bung] Pond!
- Pond, look out!
- Pond!
Run him over!
- Shit!
- [Bung and Keg gasp]
[groans]
[boss] Pond, you piece of shit! [groans]
[engine revving]
- Hey!
- Pond, get in.
- [boss] My Game Boy!
- [Keg] Go, go, go!
[boss] Fuck you, Pond! Pond, you…
- [groans]
- [Pond] Go!
Shit! You're gonna pay for this!
[Pond] Slow down, Bung. You can relax now.
[laughs]
This is so fun.
The way you stood in front of the car?
That was cool.
Thanks a lot, Pond.
You even took a beating for me.
Don't worry about it.
This is my fault
for dragging you into this.
[both laugh]
Uh. Pond?
I know it's none of my business,
but you should talk to Grandpa.
Of course it is.
[chuckles] We're family, aren't we?
[Keg chuckles]
[laughs]
I know how you feel.
Every family's got its own problems.
My dad had a mistress.
And a son.
I just found out about it.
And the worst part is,
my dad expects me to take care of his kid.
We have our share.
My mother used to be a nude model.
When I was young,
her photos were everywhere.
My friends used to masturbate
to her pictures.
[under breath] Shit!
I love her.
But I don't wanna tell anyone
she's my mom.
Is she why you wanna go to America?
If this job makes her happy,
I should be the one to go.
Huh. What is this?
Are we sharing secrets now? Hmm?
They're our family secrets.
[all chuckle]
Thank you
for coming all this way to rescue me.
Are you… going to live with Grandpa now?
[soft, emotional music plays]
[sighs]
One, two, five, zero, eight, three.
I'm not running away.
I just need to take care of something
first, then I'll be back. From Pond.
Seven, zero, zero, seven, three, seven.
I'm coming home.
See you soon, Mom.
From Pond.
Thank you.
[sighs]
[car door opens]
[car door slams]
I just need to page my mom.
One, four, one, two, two, two.
Don't worry, Mom.
I'll be back for the countdown.
From Keg.
[pager vibrates]
I'M NOT RUNNING AWAY. I JUST NEED
TO TAKE CARE OF SOMETHING FIRST.
THEN I'LL BE BACK.
[dialing]
[ringing tone]
Nine, zero, one, nine, nine, nine.
- [woman] Yes, sir.
- You dick!
Uh, sir?
You are dead meat! From Mr. Noi!
Swear words aren't allowed, sir.
Why? Why the fuck aren't they? [grunting]
[pager buzzes]
YOU'RE A BAD DUDE.
DON'T EVER LET ME SEE YOU AGAIN
[chuckles]
[buzzing]
I'M COMING HOME. SEE YOU SOON, MOM / POND
[emotional music continues]
[music fades]
[rock music plays]
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa, oh yeah ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ I will say goodbye to you ♪
♪ Want my freedom ♪
♪ Want my freedom, yeah ♪
♪ Na, na, na-na, na-na-na-na ♪
♪ Na-na, na-na, na-na-na-na ♪
♪ Na-na, na-na, na-na-na-na, na ♪
♪ Na-na-na, na-na, na-na ♪
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ This is what life should be ♪
♪ Want my freedom ♪
♪ Whoo, ooh, oh, yeah ♪
[music fades]
[upbeat pop song plays]