That place is in Wuzhu Village, Hepu, in the Gui Region.
It's my hometown.
For generations, villagers have fished for pearls.
They dive for clams and get pearls.
In our ancestral hall is the God of Water.
On its roof ridge, there are animals of Immortals Leading the Way.
Actually, in Xiaoshang River, when I painted for the first time,
I saw the vision from the shadow of water.
But before I finished it, I didn't know what it was.
I was too shocked to tell anyone about it.
And I didn't know you guys would see the same vision one after another.
The shadow of water is one thing while the vision is another.
How can you be sure the exact thing in your village is what we are after?
Because I smashed the last animal.
It was my hands that took it away.
- Why didn't you tell us?
- Because I hate that place!
Wuzhu Village.
Glad we have an address now.
I'll check the map.
It's a small village.
You can't find it on the map.
I can take you there.
But there is a condition.
Tell me.
Keep me safe.
Deal.
The cool bartender isn't here.
He isn't here.
I'll serve you.
Sorry about that.
- Fine, then.
- Oh, poor me.
Xiao Luo took away Thirteen-Thousand.
The workload isn't a problem.
I just feel way too lonely.
I'm a party person, after all.
Luckily, Master is here with me.
Or how could I live?
I even feel life is meaningless.
Life is actually meaningless.
What would you like, Sir?
I've got this.
You can sit for a while.
But this is an area for paid food.
You can use this.
Is Mu Dai here?
You know her?
Tell her her senior is here.
Who?
You... You... look fine.
My master punished him severely for that.
He's still recovering. His arms and legs are broken.
Your limbs have recovered?
You look intact.
What did she tell you?
No, no.
- Nothing. I just...
- Senior.
You've an able body.
Oh, gosh.
When did you come?
Get in there.
You have a new hairstyle.
I hate washing my hair.
Didn't you ask me to get you a job?
- You got one?
- Yes.
Go with me for an interview. Come on.
- Where are we going?
- Huacheng.
Huacheng? I need to get packed.
No need.
It's just 30 kilometers away. You'll be back soon.
- You're right.
- Let's go.
Tell Uncle Zhang I'm leaving with my senior.
- What's your name?
- Cao.
Xiao Cao.
Thanks for taking care of Mu Dai.
Life is meaningful in some ways.
Yes, whatever you say.
Go get my purse.
Hurry. The train is leaving.
Be right there. Hurry.
- Bye- bye.
- I want to talk to him.
Such a medical miracle!
Fancy house, indeed.
A fancy house doesn't mean anything.
All are made of clay bricks.
Senior.
Can I really be a bodyguard?
Of course. You're my junior. You can do anything.
Then... What should I do in the interview?
Nothing. Just be yourself.
Don't put on an act.
They'll test you. You'll test them, too.
If you feel upset, leave immediately.
Don't hesitate.
And remember. In your life, you must respect yourself.
It makes sense.
There you go.
Old Yan, we're here.
A minute, please.
Here, Junior.
Remember. Don't put on an act.
- Hello.
- Mu Dai, huh?
See the stone table in front of you?
Yes.
There are words on it. Read them out.
"Gems bath in the moonlight."
"And soil can't obscure them."
Well done!
Junior, I've told you many times to be gentle.
What if you choke her?
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Someone recommended your clan.
Hong Sha has never traveled alone.
I want a female bodyguard to travel with her.
Four or five days at most.
This trip is all-inclusive.
The pay is 20 thousand.
It's the deposit.
10 thousand.
Senior.
Quite a lot of money.
If necessary, I'll give you more.
Where are we going then?
What will we do?
Hong Sha.
Tell her about it.
We're treasure hunters.
Have you heard of it?
Treasures refer to gems.
They're priceless.
Can we get them, then?
Be patient, okay?
Equipment is needed for the gems in the mine.
We don't do such hard jobs.
Do you remember the remark on the table? What is it?
"Soil can't obscure them."
"Gems bath in the moonlight."
"And soil can't obscure them."
We only hunt this kind of gem.
Why do you think you can get this kind of gem?
People would get them first.
Such an ignorant amateur.
Do you think gems will shine where they are?
They're either encased in stone or wrapped in earth.
They're invisible to ordinary guys.
Special eyes are needed to detect their spreading light.
Got it?
We don't dig from the earth.
We only dive in water or wells.
In water, we get pears and jade.
In wells, we get gems.
According to ancient books,
"If there are gems in a well, the air will look crystal."
- "Pearls are in the deep..."
- Hong Sha.
This is too elusive to be understood.
Let me tell you.
Treasure hunters like us
need the eye training.
We locate the treasures with our eyes.
But it exhausts our eyes terribly.
So, we end up half-blind for the rest of our lives.
I have a son.
He's Hong Sha's uncle.
Instead of using this skill, he uses his own way.
Some days ago, he went to the Gui Region.
For some treasures.
The other day, when I called him, I couldn't get through.
When I could get through, he didn't answer.
I located him.
He was in that region.
I'm really worried.
But I have trouble moving around.
So, I want you to take Hong Sha there.
Gui Region?
Around the Plateau Lake?
Can you tell me the exact location?
Wuzhu Village, Hepu.
What a coincidence.
The tunnel is closed. Go another way.
Thirteen-Thousand, the tunnel isn't available.
In such remote areas, the navigation often goes wrong.
Trust me.
Go through the tunnel, and Wuzhu Village is just a few miles away.
I remember the route clearly.
The navigation is accurate.
That's impossible.
Drive through the tunnel and we'll arrive.
It'll take a whole day if we go another way.
I don't know why the tunnel is closed.
My luggage.
I'm your bodyguard, not your personal assistant.
Oh, right.
When we're in Hepu, what vehicle will we take?
Where will we live after our mission?
Have you arranged it? Have you got a plan?
Your grandpa said this trip would be all-inclusive.
So, arrange everything.
I invited you over for a dance. It was lively, indeed.
- It tastes great.
- Look at this.
Madam. Have you heard of a Wuzhu Village nearby?
Yes. You're going there?
Before, you could go through the old tunnel.
But it's closed now.
You'll have to take a detour.
You can go by train. It's available there.
Do you know why the tunnel is closed?
Because no one is there. The village is empty.
Empty?
I've heard people in this village do pearl hunting.
For generations.
How come it is empty?
It's true.
No pearls are available.
So, people moved away.
No pearls?
But I heard there were many clams in the lake.
There should have been pearls.
Dude, you have no idea.
On one Mid-Autumn night,
Clams Basking in the Moon actually happened.
Clams were everywhere on the shore.
But a naughty boy burned them with gasoline.
What a terrible kid. So wicked.
That's right.
I've heard, since then, no pearls have been found here.
According to the locals, they offended the God of Water and had their comeuppance.
Well, I think everything has a soul.
When the clams were burned, they would hate this place.
So, they'd never come again.
- Right?
- Maybe.
Why are you going there? Nothing's left there.
I've also heard that the village is haunted now.
Really?
You don't know?
Hey, stop. Sounds creepy.
- Let's drink.
- Okay.
- Come on.
- Here.
- No.
- Join us.
I have allergies.
Second Uncle.
Hey, Second Uncle.
Hello?
Hey, Second Uncle. Can you hear me?
Sorry, the subscriber you dialed cannot be connected.
Please redial later.
Sorry...
Mu Dai.
Wake up.
Wake up now.
What's wrong?
Get up now.
What happened?
Something's wrong.
Sorry...
Why can't I get through to him?
Your uncle was missing.
But he called you just now. Isn't it great?
Maybe his phone is dead.
He'll call you after charging it.
Come on, he answered.
He just didn't say anything.
Is he in trouble?
Maybe he couldn't say anything because of the low battery.
My dream was horrible.
It felt so real.
People say dreams aren't real.
Stop worrying.
Go back to sleep.
I'm so tired.
It's not easy to be a bodyguard.
I'm tired too.
How did this happen?
Where's everyone?
Are you sure we'll get a ride here?
Don't worry. I've arranged everything.
This is a professional driver.
Poor bodyguard.
You aren't observant at all.
Here.
Not this one?
Hello, ladies.
Which one of you is Miss Yan?
So, this is your fancy cart?
That's right. Fancy cart.
Yeah. Let's get in.
Come on. Hold on tight.
We're about to go.
I've got this too.
How did this happen?
My home is still here.
This is...
your home?
Aren't we supposed to have a final division?
Why do you have to guard the lake?
Our village head is foresighted.
He fears neighboring thieves.
If they steal, we'll get fewer pearls.
Each family will get a smaller share.
For Jiang Zhao's school life, we'll afford fewer erasers or pencils.
Am I right?
I should go.
Be very careful.
I'm wearing my talisman.
Don't worry.
We're here alone.
If something is on your mind and bothers you, you can talk to me.
You know.
Villagers here live off pearls.
Waters with clams are just like farmlands.
They aren't all fertile.
Some have more clams while some have fewer.
Everybody wants the best part.
Stop fighting.
In the division of water, we fought with the neighboring village.
- At first, they agreed to wait for the authorities' solution.
- Stop it!
But guys from the neighboring village
sneaked in to steal clams.
Things were out of control.
This is our territory! Go back to your own village.
Go away. Get out of here.
Get away! Leave.
Send them away.
Throw them off.
My father...
fell into the water
and died during this fight.
But a pearl fisher should be a good swimmer.
That's right.
Who knows?
Maybe he fell and cramped up.
Accidents happen.
Right?
We didn't even find his body.
After he died, my mother became delirious.
She couldn't distinguish between illusion and reality.
Mom, where are you going?
To see your father.
Mom, the wind's blowing really hard. Don't go.
Mom!
Did you hear?
He's yelling for help.
He's hunting pearls.
He can't pull so many pearls.
- I need to go now.
- Mom, you can't go.
The wind's blowing hard. Mom! Mom!
Get out of my way!
Mom!
Mom! Mom!
Mom! Don't go!
Come back!
- You can't go!
- Let me go!
- You can't go.
Don't be silly. You'll get killed.
You can't go.
Chief, please save my mother.
Such strong waves. How can I save her?
Nobody can get down to save her!
Or they will just die!
You're a madwoman.
- Mom!
- She's insane!
Let me go!
Mom!
That night, the wind blew strongly on the water.
Nobody saved her.
The next morning,
she couldn't be found.
Do you think I was really unlucky?
I thought so, anyway.
During that time, I often sneaked into the ancestral hall.
I asked the God of Water what I had done wrong
or what my family had done wrong.
I asked how we offended him.
But he didn't reply.
Close the door.
I got you guys here to talk about Jiang Zhao.
He's a poor kid.
He needs a lot of money for his school and marriage.
Why don't we split the cost evenly?
Okay. Whatever you say.
That's fine with me.
Jiang Liu, say something.
Chief, this is unfair.
You didn't save his father. Why do I have to pay?
Nonsense. I didn't kill him.
I didn't push him into the water.
You were just beside him. Why didn't you save him?
It was too chaotic.
We might not manage to save him.
Anyway, his death isn't in vain.
At least, we own the lake now.
Yeah.
We lost a man and they were guilty.
They were too ashamed to come.
The authorities pitied us too.
Then, this lake was given to us.
So, Jiang Zhao's father is our hero.
We should take care of Jiang Zhao and raise him.
- Don't be stingy on such small expenses.
- Fine, then.
- Clams are basking in the moon.
- Clams.
- In the moon.
It's really happening.
Let's take a look.
- Let's go.
- Clams.
- Move.
- Be quick, Chief.
I'll screw this.
Then, what is Clams Basking in the Moon?
Clams Basking in the Moon?
That's just a ridiculous legend here.
During the Mid-Autumn Festival, if the clams come onto the shore,
open their shells and bask in the moon,
there will be a great harvest of pearls for the next year.
Enough moonshine can make the pearls bigger and rounder.
But did they deserve the pearls?
They watched my father die heartlessly.
Do you think they deserved that?
A great harvest?
Then what happened?
What happened?
I took some diesel there and burned the clams.
I climbed onto the roof and smashed Hangshi.
Then, I ran away.
After that, I never told anyone about this.
Am I to blame?
Thirteen-Thousand...
what's gone is gone.
What matters
is to live a good life now.
Yes.
You're right.
We're here to save Ping Ting.
Tell me. Where are we going now?
The ancestral hall.
The corner of its roof appeared in the vision.
We'll find a clue there.
Here we are.
Someone cleans this hall regularly, or it wouldn't be so clean.
Yeah. I noticed that, too.
Does someone come back to clean this hall?
Hey.
Do you guys here believe in this?
No.
People here honor the God of Water.
But we don't believe in retribution.
Here we are.
This is it?
My cart can't get through that path.
Ladies, you'll have to walk from here.
Keep walking in this direction.
Wuzhu Village is on the opposite hill.
Climb up and you'll see an old ancestral hall. That's it.
Will we go along the way?
You can't go straight there.
See? You must take the outer path.
In the middle is a swamp.
You'll get stuck.
Call me if you need a ride when you're back.
Why are you going that way?
Isn't that the center of the lake?
There's a swamp. We'll get stuck.
Where are you going?
Let's just go straight.
Don't take a detour. Isn't it exhausting?
According to my analysis, this terrain is like a divided soft-boiled egg.
In the middle is the lake. Around the lake is the inaccessible swamp.
But as it goes out, it gets more solid.
Horses and cars can ride on it.
Between two points, the straight line is the shortest.
We should walk near the center as far as we can.
It saves time and energy.
The lake bottom.
Thirteen-Thousand.
What's that noise?
Don't need to see it.
It's the pearl lugger.
According to our custom,
a shell wind bell is tied to the pole
to get good luck for clams and pearls.
Let's take a look.
Are you sure we'll walk there?
What a terrible route you've chosen.
Look.
So what?
A bodyguard can't even endure this?
See for yourself. Aren't we getting closer?
Look.
Come on.
I'm talking to you. Be polite, okay?
Do you feel there's something underground?
No.
Don't be so suspicious.
Thirteen-Thousand.
The food was freshly made.
Is it the guy we saw just now?
This is where he lives for now.
But why does he live on a boat instead of living in the village?
Hey, Mu Dai. What's up?
Hey, Luo Ren. Are you in Wuzhu Village?
Yes. What's wrong?
Luo Ren, I'm also here.
You're also here?
Mu Dai. I'm sinking.
Mu Dai. Mu Dai!
Mu Dai.
- What's wrong?
- Hello?
Mu Dai, I'm stuck.
Mu Dai, I'm stuck!
Mu Dai, help me!
Help me!
- Hello?
- Something's in the lake bottom.
Come and help us.
- Hello?
- What's wrong?
Lake bottom.
Mu Dai, help me!
Mu Dai!
Mu Dai! Mu Dai, help me!
Mu Dai! Mu Dai.
♫  The sky splits the dawn's horizon  ♫
Are you okay?
Come on.
♫  (The end) Is about to gently appear  ♫
♫  Like a whisper in my mind, a fleeting touch across my face  ♫
♫  Yet I find myself in the dark  ♫
'Palm Print' - An Qi
♫  The sky splits the dawn's horizon  ♫
♫  It's telling me the end  ♫
♫  (The end) Is about to gently appear  ♫
♫  Like a whisper in my mind, a fleeting touch across my face  ♫
♫  Yet I find myself in the dark  ♫
♫  Every hand has two sides  ♫
♫  One offers blessings  ♫
♫  One waits in silence  ♫
♫  There's no end to this game  ♫
♫  Following the traces left behind  ♫
♫  If you were me  ♫
♫  You'd understand every tear of mine  ♫
♫  (The reason they fall)  ♫
♫  If I were you  ♫
♫  I'd feel each breath you take  ♫
♫  Then we'd move forward  ♫
♫  The sky splits the dawn's horizon  ♫
♫  It's telling me the end  ♫
♫  (The end) Is about to gently appear  ♫
♫  Like a whisper in my mind, a fleeting touch across my face  ♫
♫  Yet I find myself in the dark  ♫
♫  The sky splits the dawn's horizon  ♫
♫  It's telling me the end  ♫
♫  (The end) Is about to gently appear  ♫
♫  Like a whisper in my mind, a fleeting touch across my face  ♫
♫  Yet I find myself in the dark  ♫
♫  The sky splits the dawn's horizon  ♫
♫  It's telling me the end  ♫
♫  (The end) Is about to gently appear  ♫
♫  Like a whisper in my mind, a fleeting touch across my face  ♫
♫  Yet I find myself in the dark  ♫