[This is a work of fiction]
[The Seven Relics of ill Omen]
[Adapted from Weiyu's novel,
The Seven Relics of ill Omen]
[Episode 31]
This tree looks exactly like the one
I saw in the vision.
Everyone,
don't make any rash moves.
This is the final battle.
This tree...
Free!
Catch it!
Free.
You're tall enough. You can reach it.
Free, don't act impulsively.
Is it hungry? Haven't you...?
I've been feeding it all along.
Do you think Free might be influenced
by the seventh relic of ill omen,
and now it's acting like a woodpecker?
I saw light flowing
within the burl in the vision.
Now Free is chasing after it.
Is the relic of ill omen
inside the burl?
I don't think so.
We had such a perilous time
getting the first six.
Would the seventh
just be left for us to take?
How would we know unless we try?
Well?
It seems like the relic of ill omen
is really inside.
Is it really there?
- I think...
- Be careful.
I'll cut it down.
It's appearing.
[Phoenix Reborn]
[Forged in Flames, Rising Anew]
Be careful.
Don't jostle it out.
So what if I do?
It's just a freebie anyway.
Is it gonna cause any trouble?
What's wrong?
I just checked on the relics of ill omen
through the surveillance.
Their color
is still fading.
Shouldn't
the cycle of seven sevens restart?
Let's hope it's just a slow reaction.
Mu Dai.
This one
was too easy to subdue.
I feel like something is off
Then let's not rush back.
Should we observe at Fengzi Ridge
for a couple more days?
I'll have my senior
securely send over
the relics of ill omen from Lixi.
The reunion of all seven
should lead to new clues.
[Mu Dai]
The color seems
to have faded quite a bit.
Come on.
You're quite strong.
Now, we'll let your family reunite.
Three, two, one, go!
- Oh my god!
How did these seven
get twisted together?
Radishie, draw some blood.
Don't just stand there.
Let's see if there's
any shadow of water this time.
Come on.
I'll seal you away
even if it kills me!
It's just a life.
Take it!
Take care. I'll be right there!
It's just a death ritual.
I'll go ahead!
So,
this time you saw
a different shadow of water?
Previously, it was always the story
of the Literate Dog.
Why is it like this now?
The previous
shadows of water released
the memories of the Literate Dog.
This time is different.
With all seven gathered,
it should release more crucial
and significant memories.
Why does it look like
the scene
of the previous sealing?
Exactly.
They're dressed in ancient costumes,
and
they look very familiar.
I remember now.
Last time we went
to the Guansi Memorial Archway.
Didn't Yu Qiaoran, Meihua Yizhao
and others
look like this?
Wait, what are you guys talking about?
Am I the only one
worried about the death ritual?
What's a "death ritual"?
The records
in the Guansi Memorial Archway
never mention a death ritual.
Do you still remember?
The relics of ill omen will grow.
I analyze
that with each growth,
their energy will strengthen.
Consequently,
the methods to subdue them
will also change.
Perhaps during the era
of the Great Virtuous One,
they could be lured
into the wooden slips
and sealed
with the Feng-Huang-Luan Buckle.
However,
during the era of Meihua Yizhao,
the difficulty increased.
His letter also stated,
"This time, subduing it
will not be easy."
So, aside from the death ritual,
do we have no other options
to completely seal them?
Well,
we can only seal them by sacrificing.
And if we can't seal them, we'll die.
Look how clever this is.
We've been
through a life-or-death struggle!
Death?
I'm concerned about my life.
After surviving all those
near-death experiences,
you still want me to die?
Why should I die?
I'm no saint.
Let anyone die if they must.
We're all doomed!
[Ilta Constellation Event Approaches]
In just two days, the Ilta Star
will reach its optimal observation time.
Astronomers say
this phenomenon occurs only once
every 289 years.
However, it is important to note
that under the influence
of the Ilta Constellation,
the geomagnetic indices
will experience sustained fluctuations.
This may trigger extreme weather
or even natural disasters
in some regions.
Citizens are advised
to minimize outdoor activities.
[I'll arrive tomorrow morning.
Don't lose hope.]
Mr. Kun said
he's on his way.
He told us not to lose hope.
Not to lose hope?
What good is that?
Meihua Yizhao had the Imperishable Wood
and the Feng-Huang-Luan Buckle,
yet still needed a death ritual.
And us?
We've got nothing.
Not even worthy of a death ritual.
What are you doing?
Come back!
Drink up.
Order whatever you like.
There might not be many chances left.
Drink up!
Come on.
♪In the deepest night,
longing takes shape♪
♪Warm memories slowly embrace you tight♪
♪The path of growth
is inevitably lonely♪
♪But someone will shine on you
like the stars♪
♪Though fate may be muddy,
through the storm♪
Yan Hongsha,
happy birthday.
♪Stubbornness and courage
keep you strong♪
♪In the gaps of time within memories♪
♪There will be light,
gently warming you♪
♪The long road of life
is scarred and cruel♪
♪But some will heal your pain♪
Mu Dai?
♪Companionship and care
are like gentle beams of light♪
Where is she?
Thirteen-Thousand?
Chubby?
♪Happy birthday to you♪
Happy birthday, Hongsha.
Happy birthday!
Why didn't you tell us
it was your birthday?
I thought you all were feeling down,
so I didn't want to bother you.
♪Stubbornness and courage
keep you strong♪
I'm afraid too.
I'm afraid this might be
my last birthday.
♪In the gaps of time within memories♪
It won't be.
♪There will be light,
gently warming you♪
I just don't understand.
My grandpa always told me
good people are rewarded.
We've always been doing
what's right and just.
But
why is the world so unfair?
Why do we
end up like this?
I can't figure it out.
♪Companionship and care
are like gentle beams of light♪
Come on.
Enough with the gloom.
Some of us still have birthdays coming.
The next one's still half a year away.
Let's celebrate yours tonight.
We'll join in and make it a group thing.
Right?
Yeah.
See?
And I even scoured
to three convenience stores
to piece together this cake.
It was a bit rushed.
But you have to accept it.
Happy birthday!
♪Companionship and care
are like gentle beams of light♪
The birthday star shouldn't cry.
Wipe those tears away.
Make a wish.
Okay.
♪Embark on the journey,
healing all loneliness♪
I hope we find a new way
to subdue
the relics of ill omen tomorrow.
Why did you wish for that?
Make a wish for yourself.
Alright.
I wish the heavens favor the just
and we can all make it through.
Many years later,
we'll still be together.
Even when our hair turns gray,
we'll still celebrate birthdays
and hang out together.
- Happy birthday!
Happy birthday, Yan Hongsha!
- Thank you.
- Let's drink up.
- Come on.
Drink up.
Party time.
Here, the bottle opener.
To the Phoenix Squad!
- Cheers!
I think Chubby is right.
We have been walking the right path.
Good people should be rewarded.
This can't be how it ends.
You're right.
Yes, it shouldn't be like this.
We'll never accept it.
Doesn't sealing the relics of ill omen
require a lot of power?
What power do the dead have?
Wake up!
The siblings,
parents, uncles and aunts,
and grandparents
of the relics of ill omen are all here!
Mr. Kun.
What is wrong with you?
I've repeatedly emphasized
not to lose hope.
There's always a way
around every difficulty, right?
I even splurged
on my favorite chicken bucket
to cheer you up.
Look at you
all moping around.
Morning.
Where's Radishie?
He said he needed some fresh air.
No idea where he went.
What's wrong with all of you?
Anyone wants to give it a try?
Connect to the exit in ten seconds.
The prize is 500 yuan!
[Maze Game, 500 Yuan Prize]
I'll do it.
Ready?
Yes.
Go.
Time's up.
This is a scam.
The maze is huge and chaotic.
Even tracing the solution
would take a minute.
Ten seconds
is impossible.
How is it impossible?
One second is enough.
One second?
Show me.
Then you try.
You're not following the rules.
- Is this allowed?
- Drawing like this?
If that counts,
anyone can do it.
- Exactly.
- Indeed.
The rule says to connect to the exit.
But it never said
you had to follow the lines.
Facing a dead end,
sticking to the rules leads nowhere.
Only by thinking outside the box
can you find a new way.
What was that?
What nonsense.
Let's get out of here.
Let's go.
Scammer.
On the way,
I kept thinking
that if the Imperishable Wood
is a vessel that stabilizes
the activity of the relics of ill omen,
then the Feng-Huang-Luan Buckle
is the inhibitor
that reduces their activity.
So, as long as we have
these two functions,
we can seal the relics of ill omen
even without the Imperishable Wood
and the Feng-Huang-Luan Buckle.
Mr. Kun is right.
We have what we need in this room.
Luo?
The solution's right here in this room.
Where?
Let's be clear.
We refuse a death ritual.
But we can't just give up, right?
Even if we want to give up,
once the cycle of seven sevens ends
and the relics of ill omen escape,
will they spare us?
And they already
know everything
about our families and friends.
I'm really worried they'll target them.
We lack the Feng-Huang-Luan Buckle
and the Imperishable Wood
and can't complete
the so-called death ritual.
So we have to find another way.
What's your idea?
My idea is
the Living Buckle.
Living Buckle?
The Living Buckle means
drawing the relics of ill omen
into our bodies.
We'll use our bodies
as living Feng-Huang-Luan Buckle
and Imperishable Wood.
Who?
Well, I have to say
Radishie's idea
is quite interesting.
You are indeed
living vessels and inhibitors.
Mr. Kun, does that mean it's feasible?
Well, not really.
I...
It's unprecedented.
I can't guarantee anything.
But it's definitely unconventional.
There's potential
for unexpected success.
So what's the success rate
of this unexpected victory?
Either it succeeds or fails.
Fifty-fifty.
Fifty percent, I guess.
Fifty percent.
Fifty.
If it's 50%, I'm in.
Better than a 100% fatal death ritual.
Right?
Count me in.
Me too.
We don't have other options anyway.
This is what the Plum Blossom Sect does.
If not us, then who?
Right, Master?
Kill all demonic blocks.
Let's go take our chances.
Alright.
Then let's go
take our chances tomorrow.
Come on.
Also,
I got you a massage chair.
I know. I've been worried
about your back.
And Dad's drinking.
Hello, Mr. Zhang.
Don't push him too hard.
How's business at the shop lately?
I don't think quitting is the answer.
I'll send him some good stuff.
Listen, stop sourcing from Beard.
Most of the wine he sells
is counterfeit.
If you're shorthanded,
just hire a few helpers.
You'll manage.
I just wanted to say
if I don't make it back this time,
just sell everything
in my room.
Or throw it all away if you prefer.
I'm not terminally ill.
Memorize my bank card PIN.
You can tell Pingting.
Alright. That's all.
Mr. Zheng.
It's nothing.
I'll hang up now.
Finished your call?
What?
You're not calling Madam Hong?
After careful consideration,
I've decided not to.
The more I say, the more
she'll overthink things.
Ren,
it'll be fine.
Human determination conquers all.
Everyone will be safe.
The slopes at Fengzi Ridge
are quite challenging indeed.
I really don't get it.
If we're just
absorbing the relics of ill omen,
why can't we do it
lying in our beds?
Why trek all the way
to this so-called origin site?
The ancient texts state
all previous sealings
occurred at the origin site.
There must be a reason.
We should follow the records.
Exactly.
Something this important
deserves proper ceremony.
You're just lazy.
You call this lazy?
So heavy.
Is this the tree?
Yes.
Could this be where the meteorite fell
millions of years ago?
♪Whenever memories whisper silently♪
Mu Dai.
♪Gazing at each other's
burning teardrops♪
It's snowing.
♪Together we brave the storms
of adversity, oh♪
Perfect timing
for the snow.
Then these phoenixes
will be the first to turn white.
♪This fickle fate♪
♪Is like a cliff of thorns♪
Mu Dai.
♪Through the pain we march on♪
When we return safely...
♪Dreams arrive
where perseverance holds fast♪
let's get married.
♪See our future, I believe, I believe,
I believe love's horizon awaits♪
We'll come back when we're old.
♪Just want to slowly love you
with all my hope, oh♪
Phoenixes whitened by snow,
couples growing old together.
Alright.
We'll come back when we're old.
♪Through all the time
we've spent together♪
♪Countless memories forever♪
♪Just want to slowly,
slowly hold you tight♪
♪Shatter the mirage in fading light♪
♪Face the authentic future ahead♪
♪I'll take your hand
till the world ends♪
This snow is beautiful.
Like a wedding veil.
Almost makes me want to fall in love.
♪See our future, I believe, I believe,
I believe love's horizon awaits♪
♪Just want to slowly love you
with all my hope, oh♪
I really hate to ruin the moment.
♪Through all the time
we've spent together♪
But shouldn't we be doing something?
It does kill the mood.
Let's begin.
It's time.
You go first.
Well...
I'll go first.
Mr. Kun,
if...
If anything happens to me,
don't hesitate.
Radishie,
it's been ten minutes.
You were the first one injected.
Do you feel anything?
Not really.
Nothing at all?
What about you two?
Do you feel any different?
My neck hurts a little.
Did I sleep on it wrong?
Most likely.
And you? Any changes?
Me? Nothing.
Just feeling warm by the fire.
Any different sensations for you guys?
Anything at all?
I don't feel anything.
Just hungry.
I want to eat something.
I do.
I need to take a dump.
That's it?
Nothing else?
Then that means no feeling.
Mr. Kun.
You're
feeling it now?
No.
My car's still at Ding Laojiu's place.
Take it back for me.
The one I spent ages modifying.
You're not feeling anything,
yet you're talking
- about your car?
- Mr. Kun.
I've got a request too.
If I die,
can you take care of Free Cao for me?
Just one thing.
You love chicken too much.
Can you quit it?
Then you take care of Madam Hong
for me too.
I...
Kids say the darndest things.
They speak without restraint.
You're not feeling anything,
yet you're making
all these arrangements?
No feeling is a good thing.
You scared me to death.
I was so nervous.
I broke into a sweat.
Listen, this is a historic moment!
Really?
This is a moment worth remembering!
Just now, with the two of you
standing here
and snow falling from the sky,
it was breathtaking.
Let's take a photo.
So beautiful.
Come on, stand over here.
Hurry up, come on!
Stand over here.
Make sure the tree's in the shot.
Good point.
Get the whole tree in.
This is a good thing.
We're fine!
We were due for some luck, right?
Alright.
Come on, strike a pose.
No side effects at all.
It's been ages since we took a photo.
You've lost weight.
Right?
- Look over here!
- Photogenic.
Come on.
Three, two, one.
Got it. Let's see.
Now, switch up your pose.
I like his idea.
The heart shape would be cute.
Strike a new pose.
No, move a little.
Just adjust slightly.
Can you hear me?
Move a little.
What's wrong with...?
Oh no.
Where is this?
What kind of place is this?
Weren't we just taking a photo?
Did we get pulled into the photo?
Mu Dai.
Are you feeling alright?
I'm fine.
This is creepy.
Let's split up and look around.
Don't bother.
Zhang Guanghua?
It's you.
Welcome
to my world.
No.
He's not Zhang Guanghua.
If I'm not mistaken,
you're the seventh relic of ill omen.
You're right
and also wrong.
With all seven gathered,
I, the leader, have been fully awakened.
Under my guidance,
you've smoothly implanted
the relics of ill omen into your bodies.
Facing a dead end,
sticking to the rules leads nowhere.
Only by thinking outside the box
can you find a new way.
So that person was arranged by you?
You deliberately guided us.
Exactly.
You're sharp.
Quick to connect the dots.
Then what is this place?
How to describe it?
Your bodies remain where they were.
You're simply trapped
in the vision I created for you.
Or more precisely,
I
am
inside your minds.
You're messing with our brains now?
Get out!
No wonder subduing
the seventh relic of ill omen
was so easy.
So this was the trap.
What a sneaky scumbag.
He's trying to turn us into idiots.
I'm warning you,
let us out.
I need to take a dump!
Childish.
Because every one of you
holds something I want in your minds.
What do you mean?
All along,
you've been dealing
with individual relics of ill omen.
But the seven were always
meant to be one.
This kind of convergence
last occurred
during the era of Bo Yangzi.
The one your kind called
the Great Star Lord.
He just vanished?
Where did he go?
I can tell you this.
To reunite as one,
we need the connectors.
And there are
five of them.
Those things
are inside our minds?
When we finally achieved union
and were ready to thrive,
Bo Yangzi shattered and sealed us
into wooden slips.
Knowing it was irreversible,
so
the Great Star Lord
left a contingency plan.
Bo Yangzi
took the seven relics of ill omen.
But the five connectors...
Five disciples
fell unconscious for days,
their lives in grave danger.
It seemed they might not survive.
Yet seven days later,
they were all fine.
You planted the five connectors
in five disciples
of the Great Virtuous One.
Clever.
The connectors are passed down by blood.
Hidden deep within your minds,
buried
in your subconscious.
You're saying
the five of us
are descendants of those disciples?
Exactly.
But his disciples had many descendants,
scattered everywhere.
I picked you five
because the connectors within you guys
remain most intact.
So all our encounters
with the relics of ill omen
were never coincidences.
Of course not.
Why else would the relics of ill omen
keep appearing
among those connected to you?
All by my design.
I orchestrated your meeting
and dragged you into this.
Mom!
It was destined
that you'd come here
to complete our union ritual.
Can you hear me?
Can you see me?
At last, we're about
to fulfill our purpose.
You lowlifes
will be crushed beneath me.
If you're in such a hurry,
then let's begin!
Ren.
Ren?
Hongsha?
Chubby? Thirteen-Thousand?
Mu Dai.
Where am I?
Where are my friends?
This is the origin point.
Your friends are each
at their own origin points.
What kind of trick are you pulling now?
Pitiful humans.
Your time flows in one direction,
ever forward,
never back.
But here,
everything can begin anew.
Do you see?
Every moment of your life is here.
Regrets can be undone.
Wounds can be healed.
Your story can be rewritten as you wish.
I...
What's past is past.
I like the life I have now.
I don't need to rewrite it.
Is that so?
Don't worry. I won't force you.
I'm just offering you the choice.
Your life,
your decision.
Where's Free Cao?
Free Cao?
No time to worry about that now.
Hey,
Jiu.
Listen,
I've got a minor situation here.
Any chance you could get me a ride?
Yeah, I...
I know cars can't get in here.
Of course,
I know cars can't get in here!
I mean, get me like an ox cart,
a horse cart, or a donkey cart.
Any kind of cart will do.
I'll pay you a generous amount, alright?
If that's not enough, I'll write you
a letter of commendation.
And I'll give you
a certificate of merit.
You can hang it on your wall.
How prestigious would that be, right?
Tomorrow morning?
Jiu, is there any way
you could speed things up?
Make it fast.
Say,
show up in an hour or so?
That'd really make my day.
Is tomorrow morning the earliest?
Fine, okay.
Just get here as fast as you can, okay?
Please.
Stay warm out there in the mountains?
Stay warm.
Got it. I'll be careful.
Alright. Thank you.
Bye.
What's going on?
Well...
What's going on here?
♪The sky splits the dawn's horizon♪
♪Telling me the end♪
♪Is about to gently appear♪
♪Like a whisper in my mind♪
♪A fleeting touch across my face♪
♪And I remain in darkness♪
♪Every hand has two sides♪
♪One offers blessings♪
♪One waits in silence♪
♪This game has no ending♪
♪Following the traces left behind♪
♪If you were me♪
♪You'd understand every tear of mine♪
♪The reason they fall♪
♪If I were you♪
♪I'd feel each breath you take♪
♪Then we'd move forward♪
♪The sky splits the dawn's horizon♪
♪Telling me the end♪
♪Is about to gently appear♪
♪Like a whisper in my mind♪
♪A fleeting touch across my face♪
♪And I remain in darkness♪
♪The sky splits the dawn's horizon♪
♪Telling me the end♪
♪Is about to gently appear♪
♪Like a whisper in my mind♪
♪A fleeting touch across my face♪
♪And I remain in darkness♪
♪The sky splits the dawn's horizon♪
♪Telling me the end♪
♪Is about to gently appear♪
♪Like a whisper in my mind♪
♪A fleeting touch across my face♪
♪And I remain in darkness♪