[Derailment]
[Adapted from the Original Novel Derailment
by Priest on Jinjiang Literature City]
[Episode 6]
It's me.
Well,
I have good news for you.
I passed the assessment.
Pretty impressive, huh?
I'm such a genius.
Congratulations.
Are you done with work?
I'm at your door.
(Did you come to me?)
No.
I was just passing by.
When are you free?
It's only right and proper
for me to treat you to a meal
to thank you.
Not today.
I'm on a business trip out of town.
If you don't want to come, just say so.
Don't make such an excuse.
I'm really on a business trip.
We can eat together
when I get back tomorrow night.
All right.
See you tomorrow night.
(Dear passengers,)
(the train is about to arrive
at Baiyang County station.)
(Passengers)
(for Baiyang County station,)
(please take your luggage)
(and prepare to get off.)
[Baiyang County]
Mrs. Jiang.
Long time no see.
Lian?
It's me.
I haven't seen you
for a long time.
I can hardly recognize you.
Lian.
Let me get you some water.
Mrs. Jiang, please sit down.
No need.
Please sit down.
Sit down.
Well...
Lian.
Do you know where Xiaoyuan is?
It's been a year,
and I haven't heard from her.
I can't reach her on the phone.
Someone said
she's also in trouble.
Don't worry.
Just tell me.
Mrs. Jiang.
Xiaoyuan is fine.
I saw her a few days ago.
That's good.
Is she in
some kind of trouble?
It's been so long.
Why hasn't she come back to see me?
When was
the last time
Xiaoyuan came to see you?
Almost a year ago.
At that time,
I was seriously ill,
almost at death's door.
She came back
without telling anyone
and left me 100,000 yuan.
When Xiaoyuan got into college,
I was seriously ill,
undergoing surgery and hospitalization.
Money was running out like water.
She suffered a lot during that time.
(She insisted on leaving home
to earn money)
(to pay for my treatment.)
(She was out there)
(without a college degree.)
(What kind of job could she get?)
(The jobs she found)
(were all about physical work.)
(She was stubborn)
(and wouldn't listen to me.)
Why did you come so late?
It's on me today.
What's the matter?
I got a month's pay.
If I remember correctly,
you only make 2,000 yuan
a month.
2,000 yuan is enough
to treat you to dinner.
Besides, I've been promoted
to intern stylist.
Next month,
I'll receive the performance bonus.
I treat you to dinner
mainly to express
my sincere gratitude.
According to tradition,
let me drink three toasts to you.
Thank you for generously imparting
your knowledge to me.
If you hadn't taught me well,
I wouldn't have
passed the assessment so smoothly.
I remember you didn't drink before.
I didn't, but I do now.
And sometimes,
work requires it.
(She's a girl.)
(What good job can she find)
(that pays 100,000 in one go?)
(The last time she came back,)
she seemed different.
She picked up
smoking and drinking.
People in the village even said
that she's gone astray.
Well,
this kid
dropped out of school
just for
my lowly life.
(If I had known,)
(I would have died.)
The second toast.
Drinking too much is bad for your health.
I appreciate it.
You don't have to
be so formal with me.
By the way,
here's the 713 yuan I owe you.
Take it.
I said I'd drink three toasts to you.
I never
take advantage of others,
and I always
keep my promises.
Jiang Xiaoyuan.
Let's talk.
There's nothing to talk about.
Do you want to bring up the past again?
I just want to treat you to dinner.
Besides, everyone has secrets.
I won't pry into yours,
and you shouldn't pry into mine.
Can't we do that?
I'm not obligated to tell you everything
about my life, am I?
That's right.
You're not obligated to do that.
What about the past?
Don't you have any questions
to ask me?
(Was there any conflict)
(or emotional entanglement)
(between the previous Jiang Xiaoyuan
and him?)
No.
But I've been waiting for you to ask me
why I didn't show up
six years ago,
why I left
without saying goodbye,
why I never came back
to Baiyang County,
and why I knew
you needed help
but still were gone for four years.
Even when I came back,
I didn't
come to you immediately.
(The thing is I don't know)
(what happened.)
Jiang Xiaoyuan,
you said you always keep your promises,
and I believe I do too.
But I've gone back on my word.
Don't you want to
ask me why?
Let's not talk about it.
Let's eat.
Jiang Xiaoyuan.
If you blame me
for not keeping my promise,
you can hit me or scold me.
You can take it out on me as you want.
But can you stop
acting like
you don't know anything?
Are you finished?
I've said
that I don't want to bring up the past.
Besides,
I told you earlier,
but you don't believe it.
Qi Lian.
I'm only treating you to dinner.
Why are you treating me like this?
I know you feel guilty
about the former Jiang Xiaoyuan.
You can't forget her,
and that's why
you've been so good to me.
But I've told you
I'm not that Jiang Xiaoyuan.
I don't know
what happened to her,
and I can't respond to you
on behalf of her.
If you feel like
you're at a disadvantage,
we can just end it.
Jiang Xiaoyuan.
You still don't get it.
I've never felt
that I've been at a disadvantage.
It's such a big umbrella.
Can't we use it together?
♪Hey♪
♪When you're helpless♪
♪I'm here♪
I won't ask anymore.
I won't ask about the past.
♪I'm getting closer♪
Jiang Xiaoyuan.
Although we can't go back to the past，
we can still be friends
in the future,
right?
Let go of me first.
To be frank,
I have no family
in this world,
and I really need friends.
And you're the first person
to reach out
to me.
But I hope
you can see us
as new friends,
rather than you making concessions
to your old lover.
I'm not her.
Can you understand?
♪I could just go anywhere with you♪
♪'Cause you're my favorite thing to do♪
♪Like moonlight in my hand♪
I understand.
I promise you.
Friends will go through
thick and thin together.
Do you need to think it through?
If you need anything,
you can come to me.
I...
I mean it's mutual,
not me
taking advantage of you.
You've always been fair,
and you keep your promises.
Okay.
From now on,
we're friends.
♪Waiting for you♪
Friends.
[Phone contacts]
[Friend]
(Although I don't know)
(what happened)
(between him
and the original Jiang Xiaoyuan.)
(Fortunately,)
(he's still willing to be friends with me)
(after knowing the truth.)
[Fashion Hairdressing Salon]
Welcome.
Li.
Ms. Lan, here you are.
Wash my hair for me.
Sure. Come with me.
Okay.
Welcome to come again.
- Welcome to come again.
Why are you still standing here?
What are you doing?
Go to the back.
Why?
I'm sorry, Ms. Ling.
She's new and doesn't know the rules.
Sorry.
What?
Why are you afraid of her?
Our positions
are based on performance.
Last month,
Ms. Ling was number one.
What's more,
she's senior
to all of us.
We all respect her a lot.
Does seniority matter
even in hair washing?
In that case,
we'll have to let her get on top of us.
We've all gone through this,
year after year.
Just get used to it.
Ms. Ling.
Mr. Wang is at the door,
waiting for you to wash his hair.
This way, please.
Please.
[Fashion Hairdressing Salon]
You must use the shampoo
I recommend to you.
It's really good
and suitable for your hair.
Take care.
Seriously?
Did you get no one?
How could I get any customers?
I've been standing in the back.
I can't beat the ones in front.
Besides, the clients know
that those in the back
have less experience.
They would rather wait
a few more minutes
for Ms. Ling to come
and wash their hair.
Welcome.
Come on.
Wash my hair for me.
I'm a little tired.
You do it.
Go ahead.
How is the pressure?
It's good.
I feel sore and swollen here.
I notice that your eyes
are bloodshot.
I'll press some acupoints
to relieve your fatigue.
Okay, thank you.
You know what,
I think it's working.
Right?
Let me massage for you a little longer.
Little girl.
I remember
Mr. Chen doesn't teach
massage techniques.
I haven't enjoyed
such good treatment
for many years.
Well,
has there been any reformation
or something?
Did no one know
how to do massages before?
It's not like that.
Acupressure is difficult.
They didn't learn it well
and gave massages without proper skills,
resulting in
poor customer experience.
Later on, they stopped teaching massages
and only request you
to wash hair well.
However,
your technique is impressive.
Among so many people,
you must be the only one who can do it.
No matter how good my technique is,
I can't put it to use
unless I meet someone like you
who can appreciate it.
You washed my hair well.
Next time,
I'll still come to you.
Thank you.
By the way,
I'm No. 27.
Okay.
(That's right.)
(I can develop)
(my speciality)
(and attract my own regular customers.)
Why are you dragging me here
instead of welcoming customers?
I've figured it out.
It's no use for us to wait around.
Think about it.
The better the performance,
the better the position,
and the more
customers.
It's unfair to newcomers
like us.
We don't have enough customers,
and it's hard for us to get promoted.
But you can't
just stay negative.
I'm not being negative.
I want to break the rules.
We're no worse
than anyone else, right?
We need to find a way
to let the customers know that.
How to do it?
I've figured it out.
Let me tell you.
I think
we can...
Then...
What do you think?
Hello, miss.
Here's some fruit for you.
Do you serve fruit here?
Yes, we do.
Hello.
Here's some fruit for you.
Do you serve fruit here?
Of course.
If you're satisfied
with our service,
could you please
leave a good review online?
If you could mention
the names of the new stylists,
we would be even more grateful.
My name is Jiang Xiaoyuan.
You can also call me No. 27.
Okay.
Thank you.
Hello.
[A good review for No. 27]
I'm the new stylist, No. 27.
My name is Jiang Xiaoyuan.
[A good review for No. 27]
I hope you can remember me.
Thank you.
It feels good.
What's your number?
I'm No. 27.
[A good review for No. 27]
My name is Jiang Xiaoyuan.
I hope you can remember me.
Inside, please.
Welcome.
I'm looking for Number 23.
It's me.
Let's go.
This way, please.
Ms. Ling.
Look at this review.
"I'm a regular customer of this salon
and have been satisfied
with the service.
There is
a smart girl today
with excellent massage skills
and acupressure techniques.
I recommend her
to those who work overtime
and need hair washing.
Be sure to go to
No. 27."
There's another one.
"I took the advice
and went to No. 27.
She's really good."
That's why the customers
all looked for them today.
These two little girls
are quite scheming.
Yeah.
No wonder.
- Welcome.
Mr. Wang.
Inside, please.
Ling.
I want No. 27
to serve me today.
No. 27 is not here.
Let me wash your hair.
She's not here.
I'm here.
Hello.
I'm No. 27, Jiang Xiaoyuan.
Come with me.
Do you want to wash your hair?
I heard your massage skills are good.
I'd like to have a try.
All right.
You can't imagine
the look on her face today.
It was satisfying.
You know what,
in our salon,
I used to stand there alone
with all of them ahead of me.
Every time a customer came in,
they wouldn't choose me.
I just stood there
by myself.
But it's different now.
Now there are
still many people ahead of me,
and I'm still standing there.
But every customer who comes in says,
"Number 27."
It felt great,
you know.
Why are you looking at me?
Just eat.
Cheers.
Let me see who dares
to look down on me now.
Well done.
In less than a week,
you've ranked third in performance,
and we even have
more customers now.
I heard that many people
came for your scalp massage.
It's so-so.
But this scalp massage
is indeed highly praised.
Boss.
Would you consider
adding a new service
and giving me a raise?
You wish.
Look,
I'm going to the head office
in Chongqing
for a meeting in the next few days.
While I'm away,
take care of yourself
and don't get into
any unnecessary trouble.
Don't you and Qi Lian own this salon?
Why is there a head office?
This is a chain franchise store.
We have to listen to the head office
for important matters.
I'll leave the salon
to Helen for now.
Don't mess with her.
Be smart.
Smart.
Okay.
And,
before I go,
let me share a piece
of insider information with you.
Next month,
we'll have two vacancies
for junior stylists.
If you rank first
in performance this month,
you know what it means.
What's a junior stylist?
It's food
that you eat.
Let me give you a lesson.
Junior stylists
will not only get a raise
but also learn hairdressing.
They can have people with a lower rank
assist them.
Most importantly,
working your way up
in just one month
through your own efforts
sounds quite an accomplishment.
Who would dare to bully you again?
That's right.
Okay. I'll do it.
Go for it.
I'm going to work.
Go ahead.
[Fashion Hairdressing Salon]
Inside, please.
Let me get you a glass of water.
Okay.
Please sit here and wait a moment.
Helen will be back soon.
Okay. Thank you.
Wait.
I'd like a piece of cake
without peanut butter.
I'm allergic to peanuts.
Okay.
- Welcome.
- Welcome
Sir, please come inside.
Jiang Xiaoyuan.
Helen asked you
to attend to her customer.
Why should I
attend to her customer?
You're famous now.
Who else could it be?
Hello.
Would you like me
to wash your hair first?
No.
I'll wait for Helen.
Okay.
Wait.
Where is the cake
I asked for?
All right, just a moment.
I'll get it for you now.
Why are you eating so late?
You know what,
the popularity ranking
for junior stylists
is taking shape.
I think we can make
some interesting videos
to increase
online exposure, you know?
Then there will be
many people
specially
coming for us.
Xiaoyuan.
You're smart.
But
I don't think
we should do that.
What's wrong?
Last time, you took Ms. Ling's customer.
If you outperform her again
this month,
she'll be very upset.
Actually, Ms. Ling
has been good to us newcomers.
I just don't think
this is a good idea.
Why are you afraid of her?
We are doing our job well
on our own.
Who are we offending?
I'm leaving.
Xiaoyuan.
- The cake...
- K.
Ms. Ling.
What are you looking at?
Stay out of this.
Come here.
Hello. Here's your cake.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Please enjoy.
Just call me if you need anything.
Wait!
What's the matter?
What's wrong with you?
I told you
I'm allergic to peanuts,
and you still brought me
the one with peanut butter.
I'm sorry.
You must do it on purpose.
Just wait to receive a complaint!
The customer is allergic to peanuts.
Why didn't you tell me?
How would I know?
She's not my customer.
Don't you ask your customers
what they're allergic to
before serving them?
Don't go.
Do you know
that a serious peanut allergy
can lead to shock?
I don't know anything.
Don't slander me.
What are you doing?
Luckily, the customer is fine.
Ling,
as a senior employee,
how could you do such a thing?
And you.
You've always said
that you'd make a living
based on your ability,
but today
you made a scene
in front of so many customers.
Was that professional?
You all know
about the promotion opportunities
and have your own plans.
Let me tell you two now,
you're disqualified
from being promoted,
and your performance for this month
will be cleared.
Why do you disqualify me?
Because I'm the acting manager.
If you disagree,
resign and get out.
[Fashion Hairdressing Salon]
Xiaoyuan.
Stop going against
Ms. Ling and the others.
They're seniors.
Newcomers can't
win the experienced ones.
You're the one
I trust the most here.
I didn't expect this.
I don't know what to do, Xiaoyuan.
Ms. Ling said
that if I ruin
her plan,
I would be
her next target.
So, did you just stand by
and do nothing?
I'm sorry, Xiaoyuan.
I didn't know.
I didn't know
things would turn out.
We're not the same kind of people.
You should leave.
(I must be out of my mind.)
(This is the world I time traveled to.)
(Why do I care so much?)
(It's important to find a way back.)
[Time Travel]
[Time Travel Forum]
[Has there been anyone around you]
[who suddenly disappeared?]
(Has there been anyone around you
(who suddenly disappeared?)
(My classmate, Xu,)
(was my closest friend in high school.)
(But one day,)
(he disappeared for no reason.)
(My classmates,)
(my parents,)
(and my teachers)
(don't remember Xu.)
(He became someone who only exists)
(in my memory.)
[Baiyang County Nanchuan High School]
(Jiang Xiaoyuan.)
(Don't run!)
(It's time for class.)
(Xiaoyuan.)
(Xiaoyuan!)
(Hiuwon. Jiang Xiaoyuan.)
(Jiang Xiaoyuan.)
Qi Lian.
Why did I suddenly faint again?
The doctor said
you've been too tired lately,
which weakened your immune system.
And you got too emotional.
I've heard about what happened today.
Do you need any help?
It's just a small matter.
I can take care of it myself.
Thank you.
Okay.
I believe it's not your fault.
Take your medicine first.
Why are you so good to me?
Aren't we friends?
I know
you'll pay me back
once you get your salary.
[Fashion Hairdressing Salon]
Do you know
that a serious peanut allergy
can lead to shock?
I don't know anything.
Don't slander me.
Am I slandering you?
Don't grab me.
I'm grabbing you.
(The hair-washing attendant, Ling,)
(who knew the customer)
(is allergic to peanuts)
(still prepared a snack
containing peanuts)
(for the customer.)
(The she had)
(her coworker who didn't know this)
(deliver the snack to the customer.)
(Fortunately, the customer
discovered it in time,)
(preventing)
(potentially severe consequences.)
(Hair-washing attendant like Ling...)
Good morning.
What are you looking at?
Jiang Xiaoyuan.
Don't think I don't know it.
Did you make this video?
Are you trying to get me fired?
What video?
- Drop the act.
- What are you doing?
Is there an end?
What are you doing?
Do you want to rebel?
Don't you have to work anymore?
Get out of here.
Listen,
from now on, you're suspended.
You don't need to come to work
until the manager comes back.
Hello.
Jiang Xiaoyuan.
Did you post
the video online?
Would I post that kind of video?
Ling made a mistake,
and I'll punish her when I get back.
But now,
you've turned it into a big deal,
which will not only damage
our reputation
but also
alarm the head office.
I won't be able to fix it by then.
I said
I didn't post that video.
Ling is the one who made the mistake.
Now everyone is siding with her,
making me the only villain,
right?
Mr. Chen.
I want to stay
and work in your salon,
but if you wrong me
like this,
I should just quit.
♪If time were to reset♪
♪Would you dare to join me yet?♪
♪At the start of this quest♪
♪Would you wait, put to the test?♪
♪In endless night♪
♪A distant beacon bright♪
♪Is it you guiding me right?♪
♪You are the only one♪
♪My light♪
♪My life♪
♪The mist along the way♪
♪Twists through my world, becoming rain♪
♪Bestows upon me a clear sky♪
♪You never want to look down♪
♪On my tiny struggles♪
♪Bound by naive dreams♪
♪You'd rather not wake up♪
♪Drawing near with proud armor♪
♪Embrace, then mutually soften♪
♪You are the only one♪
♪My light♪
♪My life♪
♪Did you hear it?♪
♪What melted all the deadlines
for the future♪
♪Before the break of day♪
♪You are the one I want♪
♪Only you♪
♪In this sea♪
♪Your light shines
brighter than the stars♪
♪Racing towards my yearning♪
♪My love♪