[Derailment]
[Adapted from Derailment by Priest
on Jinjiang Literature City]
[Episode 2]
[Jiang Xiaoyuan]
(This...)
(This isn't my ID card.)
(My domicile is in Chongqing.)
(Wasn't I knocked off the bridge?)
(Where is this place?)
Awake now?
Miss, don't be scared.
I saw you lying alone
by the road
and injured,
so I picked you up.
I was just delivering goods
to the downtown.
It got late,
so I thought I could use some company.
Don't be afraid. I'm not a bad person.
Here's my work ID
and my name.
It has our company's phone number
and address on it.
[Zhang Xiuqin]
Give it a try.
You'll get through.
Miss,
is your head injury serious?
We'll soon be in the city,
I can take you to the hospital.
Just a minor scrape,
no big deal.
Does your car go
towards Chongqing downtown?
Chongqing?
Chongqing is too far.
This mountain road leads out
to Luoshan.
But I...
But I fell into the river
in Chongqing.
What did you say?
[Luoshan Road Transport Administration]
Ms. Zhang,
could I borrow your phone
for a moment?
My phone's died.
Sure,
here.
But my phone
is quite old.
Probably no signal in mountains.
We need to get out of here.
Miss, hurry.
My daughter is home alone.
Hello, welcome.
Hello,
my phone's out of battery.
Can I use your telephone?
Thank you.
Hello, sir,
what kind of fuel?
No. 98. Fill up.
Okay.
(What is)
(Mr. Xu's cell number?)
(Forget it, I'll call my dad.)
Hello.
The subscriber you dialed
cannot be connected at the moment.
Please try again later.
Sorry...
2018?
2018...
Why are you still using
a 2018 calendar?
If not 2018,
then what?
Of course, 2025.
This year is 2018,
not 2025.
It's 2025 this year.
How much?
Pump number 30, 150 yuan.
Pay inside, please.
Hello?
Are you the one who called me just now?
No,
it's a public telephone.
Probably that girl who just left.
She made the call.
(Forget it.)
(I need to find Xu Jingyang first.)
Pump number 30.
(Now is 10 PM, October 23rd,)
(2018,)
(Beijing time.)
(Music Radio Station)
(is broadcasting on time.)
(How could this happen?)
(How did I go from 2025)
(back to 2018?)
(What is this?)
(Time travel?)
Miss,
we're in the city now.
Maybe I should take you
to the hospital to check up.
I'm worried
about your injuries.
Is this your first time out?
You didn't tell your parents, did you?
Where do you want to go? I'll take you.
Don't be scared,
okay?
May I make another call?
Sure,
here you go.
Thank you.
Don't worry.
♪Now every time I can feel the wind♪
♪The whole world draws back as it roars♪
♪No need to tell me what to do♪
♪In this rush, I feel, I see♪
♪Just let me flow♪
Sorry.
The subscriber you dialed
cannot be connected at the moment.
Please try again later.
Sorry.
The subscriber you dialed
cannot be connected at the moment.
What's wrong?
How about this?
If you have nowhere
to go tonight,
you can come to my place.
It's just me and my daughter at home,
so it's quite convenient.
Don't worry,
okay?
What do you think?
It's okay.
(Xu Jingyang.)
(Is that you?)
Hurry up.
Be careful.
Come on, quickly.
Don't worry, it's okay.
Miss,
hurry up.
Be careful, it's slippery.
Follow me.
It's okay.
We'll be there in no time.
What's wrong?
Tong!
You scared her.
Why aren't you at home sleeping so late?
What are you doing here?
Come on.
Your mom's going to scold you.
It's okay.
This kid,
he got sick.
It damaged his brain.
It's okay, don't be scared.
Here we are.
Come on in.
Tian.
Mom,
you're back.
I'm back.
Say hello to this lady.
Who is she?
Why should I greet her?
Don't be rude!
Have you finished your homework?
Once you're done, just go to bed.
Here.
Have some water.
Take it.
You can make do
for the night.
I'll get you a bed.
(I really traveled back
to seven years ago.)
(This is too unbelievable.)
(No.)
(I must find a way back.)
(Even though the year has changed,)
(as long as I can get back to Chongqing,)
(I should be able to go home.)
(I'll have to take a flight back, right?)
(But I only have 520 yuan.)
(A train will do too.)
(Five hundred and twenty yuan
for a train ticket)
(shouldn't be a problem.)
[Participant in a Fight Incident]
[Settler of a Fight Incident]
[Party Involved in a Fight Incident]
(Lian,)
(when you came
to report the case five years ago,)
you said
that you searched for a long time
but couldn't find any news
about Xu Jingyang.
We also investigated thoroughly
but couldn't gather any information
about him.
Everyone is saying
that Xu Jingyang
doesn't even exist.
Officer Chen,
do you think I'm lying,
or do you think
I have delusions?
Can I access the records
of the fight
I was involved in back then?
You don't have the right
to access the records.
If you want
to check personal information,
you need to go to the police station
of your domicile with your ID card
to submit an application.
But you can only access
your personal information
and criminal record.
(Xu Jingyang,)
(the coordinates were sent by you, right?)
(Then whose blood was it)
(at the scene?)
Don't block the way.
Who taught you
to mistake rudeness for personality?
Tian.
The lunchbox.
Mom.
Why are you so hasty
and careless?
Here.
Be careful on the road.
Do you hear me?
Ms. Zhang.
What's going on here?
What happened?
Ms. Zhang.
Whose kid is this?
Little rascal!
Ms. Zhang.
Are you blind?
Someone call the ambulance.
What's the point?
It will be too late
when it arrives.
Come on.
Give me a hand.
Quick!
You are her relative, right?
Why are you standing there?
Let's go!
Go!
Quickly.
[Luoshan Hospital]
Zhang Tian.
Over here.
Where's my mom?
Is she okay?
Your mom's fine.
She's in the ward.
You came just in time.
This is the bill.
Go get your family here.
Miss,
I don't have that much money.
Now you call me Miss.
Save it.
Right now,
I am not the rich heiress anymore.
Miss!
Miss, I'm begging you.
Please save my mom.
My mom has been so good to you.
Miss.
Please help me.
I'm begging you, Miss.
Miss.
Two hundred.
That's all I can give you.
Miss.
It's not that I don't want to help.
It won't be enough
even if I give you my all.
I have some.
Is that all?
That's all.
It's still not enough.
Thank you.
Doctor,
we were in a rush
and didn't bring enough money.
We're 48 yuan short.
We're both here.
We won't skip out on the bill.
Could you please put us on the list first?
We'll pay the rest soon.
Our hospital has rules.
Look.
I'll make an application.
Just wait a moment.
Alright.
♪If time were to reset♪
♪Would you dare to join me yet?♪
♪At the start of this quest♪
♪Would you wait for me?♪
♪In endless night,
a distant beacon bright♪
♪Is it you guiding me right?♪
Saving lives is the priority.
Doctor.
We have enough money now.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Hurry up.
Excuse me.
Leave it.
The movie's about to start.
(This is such a waste.)
(Pick it up)
(or not?)
(Forget it. I'd rather be hungry.)
(Jiang Xiaoyuan, oh Jiang Xiaoyuan,)
(why did you have to be a hero?)
(Wouldn't you be better off)
(with the 520 yuan?)
(Now look,)
(you don't even have enough money
for a bus ticket.)
(No way.)
(Is he already here to collect debts?)
That 50 yuan I borrowed earlier,
make sure to get it back
from the mother and daughter.
Goodbye.
What happened to your head?
Is it any of your business?
Are we even close?
(Why...)
(why is she pretending not to know me?)
You're awake.
Mr. Qi Lian,
I've asked around
for you.
Our hospital didn't have any patients
from Feng County yesterday.
You just have
low blood sugar.
Remember to eat breakfast,
okay?
I've disinfected your wound.
Don't let it get wet
for the next few days.
Nurse,
how much is the bill?
He's already paid for you.
You men
always pretend to be nice
when you see pretty women, right?
You stared at me for a long time
at the toll booth, didn't you?
Do you really think I'm naive
and gullible?
There are not so many kind-hearted people
in this world.
Trying to hit on me, huh?
I'll scare you to death.
I'm the daughter
of Jiang Group's CEO from Chongqing.
Trying to make a move on me?
You should weigh
your own worth.
Jiang Group?
CEO's daughter?
Scared?
If you don't believe me,
I can call my dad right now.
Hello.
You're calling my cell phone.
How is this possible?
Why is your cell phone number
the same as my dad's?
My dad is Jiang Tianfeng,
from Jiang Group in Chongqing.
Your dad Jiang Tianfeng
passed away in 2009.
Here's the news from back then.
[Jiang Tianfeng and his wife,
Cheng Ying, tragically died.]
Impossible.
Jiang Xiaoyuan.
[Jiang Xiaoyuan]
You were born in 1993,
on January 27th,
originally from Kangjiadong
of Lureed Village,
Baiyang County, Yunhe Town.
This isn't my ID card.
There's no Jiang Group
in Chongqing.
[No search results
for Jiang Group in Chongqing]
[Silence]
Why did you leave me?
Why did you come to her world?
(Could it be that I'm not)
(back to seven years ago,)
(but in)
(a parallel universe?)
(I'm not the Jiang Xiaoyuan)
(of this world,)
(nor is this my world.)
Right,
you don't belong here.
Then who are you?
♪I'll keep on rising♪
♪Never stop rising♪
♪I'll keep on fighting♪
♪I'll keep on rising♪
(This world)
(and my original world)
(must have some connection.)
(I fell into the river)
(and then traveled here.)
(Could the way back be)
(in this river?)
(Might as well swim.)
Help! Somebody help!
Someone's jumped into the river!
Is there anyone who can swim?
Help!
Somebody, please help!
Somebody, help!
Someone's jumped into the river!
Help!
(What's happening?)
(I'm not back yet.)
Let go of me, I can swim!
[Xinqiao Police Station]
You're Jiang Xiaoyuan, right?
Tell me,
why did you jump into the river?
Heartbroken?
I've told you so many times,
it's not suicide.
It was them being nosy,
insisting on dragging me ashore.
Please let me go.
I have important things to do.
Young lady,
don't be in such a hurry to leave.
Your jumping into the river
did cause trouble
for others.
Jumping into a river
in public like that,
if I say
you disrupted public order,
it wouldn't be an exaggeration.
According to the regulations,
we can detain you.
If your attempt to commit suicide
resulted in injury or death of those
who tried to save you,
or blocking the river
and affecting transportation,
your detention would be even longer
and your legal responsibility
would be pursued
according to the actual situation.
It's the first time I've heard
that suicide is illegal.
So you admit it was a suicide attempt.
Because of a broken heart, right?
I've told you it wasn't.
Then why?
Speak up,
so we can help you.
Officer Chen.
You're here.
Come with me for a moment.
This way.
Liuzi.
Take a seat.
Is she your classmate
or your friend?
A classmate.
Qi Lian,
let me remind you.
You young people,
be it making friends
or dating,
must be cautious.
If this girl
attempted something drastic
because of emotional entanglements
with you,
you would bear a great responsibility.
I understand.
Take her back
and talk to her properly.
Her emotion is unstable right now.
Advise her not to do
anything foolish again.
Take a look at this.
If there's no issue,
please sign here.
Officer Chen,
did you receive any reports
from Feng County's riverside last night?
No, we didn't.
Liuzi,
let her go.
Someone's here to pick her up.
Officer Chen,
if there's any news about Xu Jingyang,
please inform me immediately.
I've told you many times,
we've thoroughly
checked multiple times
about the missing person Xu Jingyang
you reported.
And this person simply doesn't exist.
You should head back.
♪If time were to reset♪
♪Would you dare to join me yet?♪
♪At the start of this quest♪
♪Would you wait for me?♪
♪In endless night♪
♪A distant beacon bright♪
♪Is it you guiding me right?♪
♪You are the only one♪
♪My light♪
♪My life♪
♪The mist along the way♪
♪Bypassed my world and turned into rain♪
♪Bestowing upon me a clear sky♪
♪You never want to look down♪
♪On my tiny struggles♪
♪Bound by naive dreams♪
♪You'd rather not wake me up♪
♪Drawing near with proud armor♪
♪We embrace,
then mutually soften each other♪
♪You are the only one♪
♪My light♪
♪My life♪
♪Did you hear it?♪
♪Something melted all the deadlines
for the future♪
♪Before the break of day♪
♪You are the one I want♪
♪Only you♪
♪In this sea♪
♪Your light shines
brighter than the stars♪
♪Racing towards my yearning♪
♪My love♪