Hmm... Well then.
Yeah.
Ah~ I guess I can go a little further.
Geez Im fine.
Mishima...
Oh, sorry!
You probably don’t wanna be touched by a guy right now.
Sorry. I... I’m going home.
No.
It might even be the opposite.
Actually, I...
still get
a little scared on the way home.
Thank you... really... Yumeno.
This fictional drama is set in the 1990s and contains outdated language that may be deemed inappropriate today.
Hahaha! Hahaha!
So goood!!!
The boss's vegetables are the best, right?
So wild!
- Wild?
Ah, wild, huh?
Hey, Futoshi!
You’re one hella lucky kid,
getting to eat such delicious veggies every day.
Wild vegetables, right?
- Yes.
Hm? You look glowing today.
For real you're really glowing.
Could it be our boy is in love?
Woo! Woo!
No Im not, really!
Just take your time, kay?
If ya get a girl, introduce her to us.
Little Futoshi used to be so small...
Boss! You've come all this way...
Since Takeshi-san passed away,
you've taken care of Futoshi all on your own...
Why are you the one crying?
Boss, who was all alone in the world...
finally found happiness, but now...
Ok! You guys...
Every time, without a fail!
Stop crying!
I don’t get it?
Yanagida just quitting like that.
I always thought that sensei from Tokyo would...
leave sooner or later.
Street says there was a love triangle between Sawada, Yanagida, and Uekusa.
Actually, I happened to see Sawada and Yanagida kissing.
Huh? Where?
Right here.
- What!?
Ya two were there and ya didn’t even notice.
No way.
- That’s crazy!
But actually!
Just now...
I saw something incredible...
I wanna tell someone about it soon!
Something incredible?
Mishima’s...
You know, Kaya’s son... what’s his name, um...
her son... Futoshi?
- Ohh...
Futoshi, and... um, you know...
that foreigner’s son,
Yumeno!
And?
- Him and Yumeno's son...
Were ho...
- Ho?
Araki Towa
Sono Shunta
Fujimoto Kodai
Sakai Wakana
Abe Alan
Smells Like Green Spirit
raw by Magicstar, english subbed by paprikart
episode 6
How do I say this, your lunch is always pretty unique.
Even though I keep saying Im fine cuz I can make one myself...
my mom always makes one for me.
That LABE supposed to be LOVE, right?
Hahaha.
Hehe.
Well your lunch is always super fancy too.
Well, yeah...
Yumeno can be pretty stupid, and immature, but
he has his good points too.
Huh? What ya sayin all of a sudden?
On that day...
Mishima!
You bastard!
He was kinda cool.
I almost fell for him.
So what ya gonna do bout it?
What am I gonna do...?
Nothing.
Because...
Guess you’re right.
There’s nothing you can do bout it.
Yeah.
Besides, his eyes are totally different from ours.
Oh right,
I brought something pretty!
What? What is it?
- Ta-da!
I found it inside my mom's vanity.
This is, um... eyelashes curler!
Yeah, I’ve always wanted fake lashes, though...
I want to use it, I want to use it.
How do we use this?
Nope, I’m first!
Hey... wait!
Watch, okay? Yeah.
Ah, ouch! Ah...
I pinched my eyelid.
Give it! I'll do it for you.
Huh?
- Over here. Ready?
Look up a little.
So cuteee!
- Really?
It curled up.
Lets do the other side too!
Ouch!
Hey… you pinch my eyelid!
Sorry! sorry!
- You did it on purpose!
Heya!
Yumeno, what about club practice?
Oh shit, Edogawa!
Hey, Yumeno!
Hey! I told ya, if you skip club practice today, you’re out.
The match is coming up. What the hell were ya thinking?
I told you, I have a stomachache.
You said that last time, too.
Come on, stop making excuses.
Just trust what your student says for once.
Let’s go, Mishima!
- Oy, Yumeno.
Oy, your teammates… Oy, Yumeno! Wait!
Ugh, my stomach hurts.
- Your teammates need you too!
Shut up!
By the way,
when did you and Kirino start getting along?
Huh?
Oh…
Maybe we have something unexpected in common.
Something in common?
- Yeah.
Like what?
Hmm… it’s a secret.
What?
Tsk… What the heck?
Say Yumeno,
Didn’t ya hate me?
Here, Kaya.
- Ah~
Thank you, Thomas.
My son loves corn.
Same here!
Thank you very much for the generous amount of cucumbers.
My idiot son, Taro, also loves cucumbers!
That’s great.
No matter how wild our cucumbers are
eating only that would get boring,
so it’s a good trade!
Lets always trade!
Mmm! Mmm~ Haha.
These wild cucumbers are so good!
Mmm! Haha!
You were always
daydreaming right?
Even in class, you’re always staring outside,
It’s hard to know what you’re always thinkin bout.
and I’ve never even seen ya smile...
Even though you have those big eyes...
it feels like nothing is reflected in them.
That’s how I see it...
y’know how your seat is in front of mine...
when your hair fluttered in the wind...
you almost look surreal.
So I wanna know
if you really exists.
Even if I reach out my hand,
I feel like I still wouldn’t be able to touch you.
That’s why you’ve always been on my mind.
Cuz of that I’ve always wanted to touch you... to talk to you.
I feel kinda embarrassed.
- Huh?
Ah, sorry...
So then Kirino was like...
"Isn’t Mishima seriously gross and creepy”
“let's mess with him a bit," he said
and I went along with it...
And that’s why you bullied me?
Ah, sorry!
I thought that I finally get to touch you
and get closer with you...
I wanted to touch your hair...
Oh, I really think we got too far when we cut it,
I'm really sorry!
Yumeno, you know...
Huh?
you’re kinda nice, y’know?
You’re nice.
Huh? Haha... huh?
Really?
Haha... hehe...
Haha...
I probably...
I... I like you...
So...
Even though I like you, I still bullied you.
I'm sorry.
Haha, hahaha! Haha!
It's so hot, damn it.
Ah...
How about we try going to the stream?
It’s so cool.
- It’s really cold, yeah?
What?
- Woo!
Oy... you...
- Whoa... cold!
It’s cold!
Ah, it’s cooler in the shade.
Ah, hey,...
Watch your step.
Im fine.
- It’s slippery.
It’s fine.
Whoa!
Watch out!
Mishima...
Can...
Can I kiss you?
Huh? Mishima’s son, Futoshi?
Yes, that’s right.
He was with that foreigner’s son, and...
they were hugging tight on the street.
Huh? Wait,
You mean they were holding each other?
No way, two boys hugging!
Wh-why didn’t ya closing your eyes?
Well you didn’t either!
Can I do it again?
Yeah.
I can’t breathe...
Breathe through your nose.
One more time.
Huh, wait...
Shit... Shit... I can't stop.
What should I do, Mishima?
Wait...
Wait... Yumeno...
You’re salty.
You’re sweaty too.
Shut up.
Wai...
Hey, hey, did ya hear? Did ya hear?
- What?
About Mishima’s son?
- It’s amazing, two boys...
hugging each other naked,
rolling around, panting like crazy!
“Ha... ha...”!?
Yumeno...
Oh... I just remembered, my dad asked me to cut the grass.
Huh?
I gotta go home.
Huh...
Hot! It’s so hot.
Alright...
Yup, yup, yup, yup.
Ugh! Hot!!!
Oh, come on... haha.
Futoshi~ your favorite corn is ready.
From Thomas-san.
From Yumeno Farmers.
Futoshi~?
Mmm, so good!
It’s definitely wild, isn’t it?
Kayo’s cucumber.
- Mmm, for sure.
It’s so delicious.
- Hey, Taro, have some too.
You liked salted cucumbers, right?
These are Mishima’s cucumbers.
Thanks for the meal.
Wait, what’s wrong?
You haven't eaten at all yet.
Im not that hungry...
- Huh?
Taro, come back! Come back, Taro!
If you eat a wild cucumber, you’ll feel better.
Oy, Taro! Oy!
Come back! Here’s a cucumber! Oy, Taro...
Dad, I’m counting on ya.
Mmm… mmm…
Oyy, Mishima!
Aren't you going to eat?
My head hurts...
Did something happen with Yumeno?
Hey, Mishima!
I want you to tell me properly.
Um…
What should I say…
I want you to properly say
that you like me.
Um…
Uh, um… uh…
I like you, Machida-san
I mean…Machi-chan, I like you.
Hehe.
Ah!
Fu… Fujii-san, my glasses…
I confessed to Mishima.
Then I asked if I could kiss him...
So we kissed, and then…
I… couldn’t stop, and then…
I… took off his pants.
And then…
I ran away.
Huh!?
Because Mishima has a dick…
Obviously!!!
I’ve imagined Mishima doing lewd things a lot of times.
But in my fantasies, Mishima didn’t have…
any breasts...
He didn’t have a dick either.
I’ve called Mishima “homo ” a lot of times…
I should’ve known…
Of course, its not like I thought he was a girl...
But when I saw Mishima’s dick,
I felt my excitement fade.
I thought, “Oh, this isn’t right”
Huh?
Ugh... Ugh...
Why’re you cryin, Kirino?
But, we were just calling him homo to bully him...
It’s not like he’s actually a homo, right?
You’re hopeless!
I knew it...
That's why I didn't want this to happen!
Kirino?
You’re...
Me too...
(He used “Atashi” = girl “I”)
Mishima~!
I’m totally fine.
Its not like l have feelings for him.
He’s not even my type anyway.
The kiss was just spur of the moment.
I’m totally fine.
I also did the same thing to Fujii-san...
But when its between guys...
it's only natural to be faced with rejection
I’m totally fine.