Music
Sound Effects
You're a trap again.
You're really something.
Take Tingzhuo out.
Here.
Don't worry.
I've prepared everything.
I won't let him get away this time.
You're really here?
I have to explain.
It's He Feng.
I'll help you.
He Feng.
It's nothing.
Just take the medicine.
I'll give you a prescription.
Thank you, Dr. Jiu.
Miss.
I heard you calling me last night.
But I don't know what happened.
I can hear you, but I can't open my ears.
I can't move.
You're possessed by a demon.
That demon was hurt by me.
It won't be able to come back for a while.
Just in case,
the government should immediately report it to the city.
No one can play the game of Zhao Lixian anymore.
You're asking us to send a notice like this?
How can the people of the room think of our government?
Then just buy all the pears.
What?
Who...
Banxia, come here.
What are you doing?
I'm fine.
I feel like you're going to faint.
What are you doing?
Shen Ye.
Banxia, come here.
No, what's wrong with you?
I'm fine.
What's wrong with you?
What are you doing?
That demon hasn't died yet.
It's very likely that it will come back.
If you're in danger, you have to wake me up.
If you can't wake me up,
then use this to stab me.
Why would I stab you?
Do you understand what I just said?
I understand.
But what's wrong with you?
I'm too sleepy.
I want to sleep.
Where are they going?
To sleep.
Sleep?
That's not good.
Shen Ye used the sword.
What does the sword have to do with sleep?
Every time he uses the sword, he gets different reactions.
He can eat with the greedy and sleep with the greedy.
But he can't drag my lady.
This demon is hard to deal with.
Who can protect your lady except Shen Ye?
You Huang, where are you going?
You Huang, I'm talking to you.
Every time you call me, you always say,
You Huang, wait for me.
What should I do now?
What do you mean?
Because of the demon, I don't dare to go home.
Let's go to the inn.
Shen Ye.
I'm so thirsty.
I want to drink some water.
You're shy.
You don't know how hard it is to be a man and a woman?
I'm a person who has been engaged.
If I get pushed out, will you marry me?
I'm sorry.
This...
I said I don't want to...
This floor...
This...
What are you doing?
We didn't do anything wrong.
Why are you taking our name?
This is what the government bought for you.
You can ask for money from the government.
This...
Mr. Chen, I have some pears to sell at home.
The government can't take it.
You should have said earlier.
You can't leave without sending them to the government.
Yes, I'll go get them.
What's wrong?
That Chinese medicine master is very powerful.
I can't beat him.
We can't stay here.
Pack up.
We're leaving the city tonight.
You're badly injured.
We're not here to see you.
I'm sorry.
Where else can we go if we're not here?
You can rest here.
When you're better, we can go back to the factory.
How's the situation outside?
Everything is normal.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm sorry.
I thought you wouldn't be able to come tonight.
I have something to do at the workshop.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
I'll wait for my wife.
I'm willing to wait for her for as long as possible.
Although our marriage is a bit complicated,
my father still agreed.
He also said he would send us a shop.
But the condition is that
we can't invite friends on the wedding day.
We can't have a big wedding at home.
I understand his concern.
He's actually very moved by that shop.
But after thinking about it,
I still refused.
Because I promised you
I must prove your name.
I also want everyone in the city to know
that you will marry me.
You are the most beautiful woman in the world.
I don't want to be a burden.
Let's leave this place together.
Go to a place where no one knows us.
I still have some savings.
I can keep you warm and cook for you.
As long as I can be with you,
even if it's just a good day for a year,
my life is worth it.
You don't want to?
I do.
It's my pleasure to have you in my life.
I'm sorry.
Who are you?
What do you want?
Don't you want to be with him?
Then be with him forever.
A Li.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Why are you here with the mirror on?
Didn't we agree that when the mirror is on,
it's the time when I'm not convenient?
Between you and me,
what else is inconvenient?
Or
do you have any secrets that you don't want me to know?
Nothing.
Just some women's affairs.
Why are you here?
I came to send you a gift.
It's washed.
Eat it.
Didn't you promise me that
you wouldn't kill anyone to get the gift until the time is up?
That's what you said.
But he made a wish.
I have to fulfill it.
I don't want to eat it.
A Li, be good.
Don't make me angry.
That's good.
Why is there no smell of star in this pear?
I forgot.
When this person
just ate it,
I couldn't help but do it.
Actually, I was going to wait for seven days.
But I really couldn't help it.
When I saw his face,
I couldn't wait for him to disappear immediately.
Didn't you people often say
that you can eat whatever you want?
The owner of this pear is a scholar.
I think
this pear
also has a little bit of the smell of books.
If you eat it,
you will know what kind of wine
is in the hand of the person who cut it.
I'm not sure.
You will know what it is called
to keep your duty and never leave it.
Anxia.
You're awake.
Oh, Tingzhao and Chi Xue
went to buy food for me.
Are you hungry?
I cooked porridge.
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
Why did you leave?
Didn't I tell you not to leave me?
I didn't leave Danshan Hall.
I didn't go out.
You slept for three days in a row.
We were tied up in one place.
I always have to eat and drink water.
I think it's good to wash your face.
I didn't think it through.
I know you're worried about my safety.
But actually,
there's a simpler way
to protect me.
What way?
Draw me a secret weapon.
I'm afraid
that monster hasn't been caught yet.
I'm sorry.
It's done.
Xueyan.
I see a scar on your chest.
When did you get hurt?
I saw it by accident.
It's scary to see a scar.
I don't remember.
You don't remember?
That was a puncture wound.
And it was so close to the heart.
It almost died.
How could you not remember?
I don't remember anything from my childhood.
What are you looking at?
You still have to add some more.
Xuanye, can I go back and change my clothes?
I haven't changed for three days.
It's smelly.
I'll go back with you after I finish eating.
Okay.
Hao, Hao, something bad happened again.
What happened?
Another military case.
The victim is Zhou Jinyuan, 24 years old, a local from Guangming.
He was found dead this morning.
He's in the same condition as Tianrui.
But the way he looked when he died didn't turn into a dead body.
He's just a little bit older.
Didn't turn into a dead body?
Are you Chu Putuo?
Yes.
Stand up and speak.
Zhang is the one who reported the case.
Yes.
Mr. Chai, I'm a businessman.
I don't know how to suppress and crack the case.
They've lived for most of their lives.
I've never seen anything so strange.
Can I see your body?
Mr. Chai, please.
My son.
You should hold your mother's heart.
Son.
Son, what's wrong with you?
My son.
Aunt, aunt.
Cuiying.
Hurry, call the doctor.
Uncle, Zhou Jueyang's room is right behind us.
Let's go and have a look.
Come on.
Take it all.
Okay.
Take care.
It's hard to think of death, but it's harder to think of speed.
I can't get out of your heart.
Linglong.
I love you.
Because I promised you, I must make you my wife.
I also want everyone in the city to know that you will marry me as your wife.
You are the most beautiful woman in the world.
I love you.
How could it be so coincidental?
Miss.
Why are you shouting? It's scary.
I've been in for a long time.
What are you thinking about, Miss?
You are so familiar.
I'm not thinking about anything.
Hurry up and clean up.
Okay.
You changed your clothes?
I thought about it.
Before you catch Jin Yao, you must stay with me.
Okay.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Miss Li.
Miss Duan. What a coincidence.
Why are you here?
I'm a mouse.
I'm here to buy some medicine.
You're still selling medicine?
Miss Duan.
I have to go.
Shi Xuan.
What did that woman buy?
Medicine.
Anything else?
There's a bottle of Chong You.
What is Chong You?
It's about you.
Someone died this morning.
The deceased was a young scholar.
But he turned into a middle-aged woman after he died.
That woman just questioned the deceased.
I think they know each other.
But I think it's a bit strange.
Chong You is a blood-sucking substance.
It's effective in breaking the body of the demon.
It's not difficult to kill the demon.
That's right.
Then your daughter must know where the demon is.
Where is she?
I said they were from the Cloud Gate and the Five Directions.
Cloud Gate and the Five Directions?
The one who died in Yanlai House last time, Tian Rui's henchman,
is also from the Cloud Gate and the Five Directions.
Let's go find her.
The deceased was a young scholar.
Why did he turn into a middle-aged woman this time?
Didn't Dr. Jiu say that
the body of the demon needs to be kept for seven days
before it can completely absorb the host's life.
I'm afraid it's not time yet.
Then the demon will make a reason.
Is that right, Dr. Jiu?
Maybe.
Then why did he do that?
You remember the time wrongly.
How can you remember the time wrongly in such a thing?
The demon only knows to kill people and has no brains.
What's so strange about that?
Is that true?
It's also possible that he can't wait
and wants to take that person's life right away.
Chief Chu.
Banxia.
Why are you here?
We're here to find Miss Ji Li.
Sister Ji Li has left.
She left? Where did she go?
Yesterday she told the chief that she was going to the south.
She has already left the Five Directions.
How long have we not been like this?
Sit down and have a meal.
Every time you came, you asked me to eat the Jade pear.
There's a smell of star in that pear.
It's hard to eat.
After a long time, every time I see you,
I will remember that smell.
That's why I'm arguing with you.
Now I think,
it's really not right.
Today, I met an old lady who was walking around the street.
She had a thick skin and a cold all over her face.
At first glance, she looked scary.
This woman's youth is even shorter.
It's only been one or two decades.
She's like a flower.
She hasn't had time to appreciate it,
and then she's gone.
What a pity.
But it's okay.
I have you.
You love me and spoil me.
You've been training me to become a Jade pear.
You've been helping me to live a long and happy life.
This is something that many people have been dreaming of.
But I'm not content to argue with you.
I said I would hurt you,
and do things that you don't like.
Now that I think about it,
I'm really not sensible.
I don't blame you.
Really?
Yes.
Xiao Chuan, thank you.
A'Li,
don't cry.
Let bygones be bygones.
As long as we're together,
nothing else matters.
I've already thought about it.
Once we leave here,
we'll go to Jiangnan
and look for a place with mountains and water.
I'll be waiting for you.
I don't want to see you again.
I just want to be with you,
wash clothes and cook for you,
and be your wife.
I don't want to see anyone else again.
Okay?
I've been looking forward to that kind of life
for a long time.
for a long time too.
Do you have to do this?
How many times have I told you?
Do you really want me to die?
I'm so good to you.
You betrayed me.
I don't blame you for being in a relationship with someone else.
You've disappointed me.
I'm sorry.
Sir, do you need electricity?
I'm from the government.
Officer.
Have you ever seen a girl with a short body
and a deep eye?
She must be here alone.
I've never seen her.
Think about it.
She's very fair, very thin, and very pretty.
I've never seen her before.
Sir, I think I've seen the person you're talking about.
Where?
The second room on the left.
That girl looks like the person in the painting. She's very sexy.
I heard from other sirs that she's a dancer from Yunmeng Dance House.
Where is this?
What kind of show are you playing?
That's right.
I forgot.
You don't remember anything.
Let me help you recall it.
Back then, you were sold to the house as a dancer.
Your early days were pretty good.
But gradually, you grew old and lost your youth.
You lost your love.
Even the servants in the house
could easily bully you and play with you.
You're very unwilling to make a wish in front of the mirror every day.
Hoping to regain your youth.
It was me.
Hearing your voice,
stepping on your side,
and fulfilling your wish.
You not only care about your beauty,
I also helped you take revenge.
Killing those people who hurt you.
You're talking nonsense!
I'm talking nonsense?
Mirror.
The one who finally called me
was Ren Xi.
Greed
is something that has to pay a price.
Look at your face.
How young and how beautiful.
It's really beautiful.
Such a beautiful skin
is used to pay for so many lives.
These past years,
how many people have you killed?
That stupid book.
If it knew your beautiful appearance,
it would have been a dead end.
Will it still love you?
Will it? Will it?
I didn't!
You didn't?
You didn't do anything?
You didn't kill anyone?
Or you didn't kill anyone?
Don't tell me
you don't know how Li got here.
Li, don't be like this.
You're too hypocritical.
I died.
Yes, I died!
You didn't allow it. You stopped me!
If you really want to die,
I can still watch you.
You left on your own.
To admit that you're cruel and cold-blooded,
is that so hard?
You're such a devil.
It was you. You lied to me.
You lied to me that I could embrace youth and live forever.
You lied to me and made me become a monster like you.
Li,
people
can't want everything.
I just want to leave you.
What did you say?
I don't know why I met you.
You must have bewitched me.
I don't want to eat that ugly pear anymore.
I just want to be with the person I love.
You're delusional!
After you got the benefits of being a human,
you still want to live the normal life.
I'd rather die than be with you.
They said you're a man of your word.
They said you like to seduce men.
They said you're born with a bone.
I don't believe it! I don't believe it!
I love you so much.
Have you forgotten?
You monster, you're not human.
Do you know what love is? Do you know love?
Every moment I'm with you, I hate myself.
You're not love at all. You don't deserve to be loved.
I don't deserve it.
I've loved you all my life.
I don't deserve it. Do you deserve it?
I don't deserve it either.
I've ruined myself.
I hate you.
I hate myself even more.
They're right. I'm a man of my word.
I love to seduce men.
I can be with anyone. Anyone!
I can't be with you.
I'd rather die than be with you.
Don't say that!
I knew it.
You think that after so many years,
you'd really be the first to fall in love with someone else?
we'd be together?
What do you mean by that?
It's okay.
Don't be afraid.
After today,
we can be like before.
Don't touch me!
Love and hate are like branches that need to be cut off.
It's hard to find a way to make up for the past.
The years are long gone.
I'll have a drink to forget the past.
I will never forget your kindness