=In Marriage and Beyond=
=Episode 5=
It's almost time.
Let's see if he's on time today.
Stop pretending to work.
Today's workload isn't that heavy.
Leave early
before you get stuck in traffic.
Let's go!
Don't you guys think
our new director is pretty funny?
He's more punctual about leaving work
than he is about coming in.
Qian, do you really love
working overtime that much?
Do you even have a life outside of work?
Come on,
let me tell you what "life" really is.
Take "life" as living
and "life" as alive.
When the two of you are separate,
it's super chill.
But one day,
when you're combined,
you'll understand what life truly is.
That kind of makes sense.
Who are you trying to match up, though?
So boring.
See you tomorrow.
See you.
Wait for me!
Why are you just sitting there?
Grab a drink, have a drink!
- Let's all drink together!
- Right?
It's been years. Come on!
Hey, what's this?
What?
I've already had one, aren't you
going to clink glasses with me?
- Hi! Long time no see.
- Long time no see.
What, no invite for me?
Hu,
if I remember correctly,
your wife works
for some foreign company now, right?
Nonsense.
Hu's wife is a public interest lawyer.
No, wasn't she
Hu's boss before?
She switched careers to become a lawyer?
That's my ex-wife.
That was ages ago.
- Oh, I didn't know.
- Let's drink.
Can't keep it all straight.
Come on.
You did that on purpose, didn't you?
Do you know where he got
his first fortune?
Where?
Wasn't it from
divorcing his wealthy ex-wife?
And now he's here pretending
to be some start-up elite.
Well,
now he's rich.
Right?
It's so easy for him to just trade up
and marry some do-gooder lawyer.
What's he trying to balance out?
I'm not putting up with him.
Remember back in college?
He even stole our stuff.
Stop making stuff up.
He didn't steal from you.
You remember it wrong.
I remember it wrong?
- Come on, cheers!
- Long time no see.
Let's drink!
Come on, cheers.
Sorry everyone,
I'm late.
Xuanxuan!
- Xuanxuan!
You finally made it!
Alright, let's make room
for the school belle,
shall we?
- Go back to your seat.
- I do.
- Come on.
Still pretending?
- Your goddess is here.
- Xuanxuan.
It's been ages.
It really has.
You've changed so much,
I almost didn't recognize you.
You haven't changed a bit.
Still the same as always.
Can you not butt in?
Xuanxuan,
let me introduce properly.
This is Hu...
Wait,
we can't call him Hu anymore.
He's now Mr. Hu.
Mr. Hu.
CEO of a soon-to-be-listed company.
He's super busy these days.
If it weren't for
your visit back home,
we probably wouldn't
have had the chance to see him.
Does anyone here still remember
back in school,
Mr. Hu wrote
something
to Xuanxuan.
- A love letter.
- Love letter.
Right!
There was no love letter!
Stop picking on me, seriously.
No love letter.
Why can't I remember this at all?
They're both denying it,
- but I'm sure there was one.
- Xuanxuan.
I have to say,
anyone can forget about it,
yet you can't have forgotten that.
You broke Mr. Hu's heart.
Don't make stuff up.
Then again,
Xuanxuan was so beautiful back then.
She must have received
loads of love letters.
It's normal if she doesn't remember.
But,
Hu
only wrote a love letter
to one person in his entire life,
right?
Hu, is that true?
I think he's underestimating me.
Hu,
that's an interesting comment.
- Is that how it is?
- Good for you.
Hu says he doesn't remember.
Should I spill the beans?
- Go ahead.
- Sure.
Alright, I'll skip
the steamy details.
Who told you to skip that part?
Have you seen my watch?
Where's my watch? Move!
- What are you doing?
- Searching your place.
What are you doing? Stop.
Why are you searching my stuff?
Why are you suspecting me?
I am suspecting you.
So what?
You're always in the dorm reading.
If it wasn't you, who else could it be?
I'm telling you,
give my watch back now,
or I swear I'll beat you up!
Let's go eat.
Did you see the love letter
he wrote to Xuanxuan?
Talk about a toad lusting after a swan.
Like the campus belle would ever
look at a bookworm like him.
You're overacting.
Mind your own business.
How about this,
- later...
- Yeah.
Guys.
Mr. Hu has prepared
some small gifts for everyone.
Let me hand them out.
Hu.
- Is this appropriate?
- Come on.
It's just some promotional items
from a business project
my company is working on.
Just take it for fun.
Please take it.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Here.
- Let me see.
- You're so kind.
Look, look.
- Take it.
- It's too kind.
Yeah.
Hu.
- Sorry.
- Let's toast to Hu.
That's it.
I've got one at home.
Sorry.
The market price for this
is 7,000 to 8,000 yuan!
- More like 8,000 plus!
- Come on.
Check it out. Am I right?
Yeah.
This is way too generous.
- By the way,
- Right?
about your son's school,
I've already spoken to the principal.
Next week, you can take your son
to register.
This...
I have to come
thank you personally,
Hu.
I've been worrying about this
for ages.
I can't thank you enough.
- No need. It was nothing.
- Come on.
Mr. Hu,
my company just developed a new app.
- We'll talk about it.
- My financing...
- Hu. Hu.
- Don't worry.
- I'll keep all your matters in mind.
- Come on.
What are you doing?
Let's toast to Mr. Hu!
Cheers.
We're all old classmates.
We're classmates.
- Hu Cheng.
- We must not be estranged.
Let me add you on WeChat.
- Sure.
- Let's help each other out, right?
Okay.
You two should add each other too.
We should meet up more often, Hu.
- Absolutely.
- Yeah.
Thanks for everything.
You're welcome.
Well, wait until the weekends.
- I'll be free.
- Okay.
Don't worry.
Just call me by then.
- Bye.
- Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
Hold him.
What's wrong?
Hu Cheng, what's wrong?
Why didn't you approve
my WeChat request?
Bad signal?
Why are you here?
Come in.
What's up?
Nothing.
I just wanted to check on you.
Did the gathering upset you?
It's better not to go.
Whatever happens,
I'm always here for you.
I know.
You'll always stay by my side.
Did I wake you up?
Did the gathering go well?
It went great.
Very great.
We had such a good time,
and even lost track of time.
Didn't expect it to go so late.
Still up this late?
You've got time to
listen to this music.
It's just that
whenever I see this group of guys,
it reminds me
of the happy,
carefree days in college.
What are you doing?
- Searching your place.
- Stop.
Why are you searching my stuff?
What are you suspecting me?
I am suspecting you.
So what?
You're always in the dorm reading.
If it wasn't you, who else could it be?
We don't stay in touch much,
but
they're a group of
genuinely close friends.
Mr. Hu,
didn't you write
something to Xuanxuan?
- A love letter.
- Love letter.
Exactly! Hu was so determined
to win you over.
Every weekend, he'd go learn piano,
while the rest of us
hit the internet cafe for gaming.
- I can vouch for that.
- He worked so hard,
sacrificing everything for it.
The most amazing thing is,
after all these years,
they haven't changed a bit.
No pretentiousness,
no ulterior motives,
just pure,
genuine friendships.
It's like they'd give you
their hearts if you asked.
As long as you're happy.
I am.
Honey.
Go get some rest.
I want to stay here a little longer.
Alright.
But don't stay up too late.
Whatever happens,
I'm always here for you.
I know.
You'll always stay by my side.
- The path is a bit rough.
- Careful.
What kind of place is this?
Seriously,
I think this is nice.
You think this is nice?
We drove for an hour,
walked forever,
and there's nothing here!
What do you mean "nothing"?
There are mountains, water,
flowers, grass, sunlight.
And most importantly,
there are
fish.
So we did all this
just to go fishing?
Hurry, take out the food.
I told you
the boss loves fishing.
You didn't believe me.
Do whatever you want.
Didn't you say
this was a team-building trip?
Exactly.
Fishing
improves
teamwork
and strengthens bonds within the team.
You're just using this
as an excuse for your own fun.
I want to take photos.
I want to have a picnic.
I want to gossip.
Why am I the only woman
in this department?
Boss, can't we hire another girl?
I need some company!
We're fully staffed.
Why don't we play Werewolf?
Or poker?
Or maybe a game online?
Straight guys.
Still working while we're out?
Boring.
You young people don't understand life.
Am I working right now?
No, I'm providing for my family.
You're just middle-aged.
Look over there, we've got an old man.
Boss, you're still young.
Why do you act like an old man?
Thanks for the blessing.
I hope I'll still enjoy this
when I'm old.
The ultimate overachiever.
How about a game of cards?
(Starlight Kindergarten)
Sorry.
Ziyuan.
Mommy! Mommy!
You aren't the first
to pick me up today.
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
Tomorrow I'll be the first, okay?
- Bye-bye!
- Okay.
Let's go home.
Mommy, Mommy!
I want to wait with Qin Jiaojiao
until her mom comes.
Otherwise, she'll cry again.
Her mom hasn't come yet?
She's crying. Her mom's not here.
Jiaojiao,
don't cry, poor thing.
Qin Jiaojiao,
will your mom pick you up today?
Of course, my mom
always picks me up every day.
You're lying!
Recently, your mom hasn't been coming.
You're the liar!
Jiaojiao, let's not cry anymore, okay?
No more crying.
How about this,
me and Ziyuan
will stay here with you
until your mom comes.
Alright?
Auntie,
you know what?
Today is my birthday.
My mom will definitely
come to pick me up.
Your mom will absolutely come.
Jiaojiao,
happy birthday.
Happy birthday, Qin Jiaojiao.
Here's a gift for you.
Jiaojiao,
your family's driver
will come to pick you up soon.
Don't worry.
Mommy is mean!
Mommy's a liar!
Ziyuan, think of something.
Qin Jiaojiao,
stop crying.
I'll play with you, okay?
How about Ziyuan plays with you?
We'll celebrate your birthday early.
Let's go to the slide!
Come on, go!
Take care.
Careful.
What's up with Jiaojiao's mom?
Not even picking up her kid
on her birthday?
I heard Jiaojiao's mom
just got promoted.
She's an executive now,
working overtime every day.
This past month,
- I haven't seen her even once.
- I'll go first.
Careful.
And her dad?
Even busier.
Honestly,
Jiaojiao's family is well off.
If her parents don't pick her up,
there's still a driver to take her home.
Imagine regular working-class families,
that's the real struggle.
There's always a way.
No need to stress yourself out.
You probably don't know,
we're all so envious of you.
You don't have to worry about anything.
It's such a blessing!
Honey, we're back.
Dad.
You're back, son.
Why so late today?
Were you causing trouble again?
Dad.
Today,
Mom and I waited with Qin Jiaojiao
for her mom to come pick her up.
Who's Qin Jiaojiao?
Qin Jiaojiao
is his classmate.
My classmate.
Honey,
I felt so looked down on today.
Who dared to look down on you?
His teacher.
She talked about Jiaojiao's mom
with such admiration.
She said Jiaojiao's mom
is a strong, capable woman,
a company executive
flying all over the world
for business deals.
And then she looked at me.
It's like
I'm just some mom
who only picks up and drops off kids.
Are you saying
you want to go back to work?
I think
I've had
enough rest.
It's time for me to get back out there.
I'm going to put my bag away.
(Organizer Association)
This association's president
(Organizer)
is actually my client.
They've helped a lot of
stay-at-home moms
who've been away from work
for a long time.
Of course,
I know this job
might not be your dream role.
But,
your online reputation
is still taking hits.
It still affects you a lot.
Finding a perfect job
won't be easy for you
right now.
I have sent out resumes before,
but they all ended up going nowhere.
Being a professional organizer
sounds trendy.
Exactly!
It's in demand.
You know, it requires
extensive training
and expertise.
It's very good.
It could even help me
organize our home better.
Right?
Honey,
I'll support you no matter what.
Whatever job you choose,
you'll be amazing at it.
He allows me to go out.
But if I want freedom?
Fine,
(Organizer Association)
but only on his terms.
Everything
has to go according to his plan.
What about the service center?
Isn't that okay?
Back then,
he thought I was just killing time
at the service center.
Who knew I'd actually succeed there?
Now,
he wants to completely kill my dream
of being a lawyer.
A man like Hu Cheng
doesn't want a wife.
He wants a perfectly controlled
chess piece.
You've seen plenty of men
like that, haven't you?
Yes.
Seeing so many
has made it clear.
Do you think
I should reach out to the director?
With his connections,
getting me an entry-level job
shouldn't be hard.
Entry-level?
You want to start from scratch?
What Hu Cheng said
wasn't an exaggeration.
Because of Congcong's situation,
finding a suitable job
is really difficult for me right now.
(Director, are you busy these days?
I'd like to come by and chat with you.)
(Confirm deletion)
Honey,
did you send your resume
to the Organizer Association?
Don't rush me!
I'm still
tweaking my wording,
trying to make it perfect
before I send it over.
Alright,
no rush.
Anyway,
I've already spoken to them.
I know them well.
Just let me know when you're ready.
Don't worry.
Director,
this is
the situation.
Now
I really hope
to return to the law firm.
Well,
our firm now is like a puzzle,
every piece fits perfectly.
There's no one we could ask to leave.
Ning,
if only you had come back to work
right after your maternity leave,
things would be different now,
wouldn't they?
Back then, I insisted on
keeping your position open for you.
Come in.
Director.
Qin, you're here.
Ning Yue!
Qin.
Here to see Director?
Long time no see.
Qin,
here are the files you wanted.
And this contract.
- Take a seat.
- Director Zhou,
I brought you a small gift.
I'll leave it here.
Great.
Have some water.
I can get it myself.
Qin,
how's your new position at Zhongzhi?
Everything going smoothly?
It's a career shift for you.
A lot of the work overlaps
with my previous experience.
For the unfamiliar areas,
I'm catching up quickly.
Qin,
did you switch to legal affairs?
Yes.
See?
Even your mentor is surprised.
Ning,
do you remember
when Qin first joined our firm?
He was just a rookie.
Then he became your assistant,
and in five years,
he rose to senior attorney.
That was some impressive progress.
Honestly, not staying as a lawyer
is such a waste for you.
Yue,
what are you working on these days?
By the way, Qin,
is your company hiring right now?
I don't think we have any openings.
Oh, wait,
there's an assistant position
still available.
Yue,
I didn't know
Director was asking for you.
You're an excellent lawyer,
and with your skills,
you'll find a suitable job in no time.
I could be
your assistant.
I know, I know.
Still up?
Go to bed first.
I just wanted to let you know
I got a job.
How's it going?
It's going great.
He's an old friend,
very kind and helpful.
That's good to hear.
Get some rest soon.
Okay.
Can you give me an exact time?
When will the sample be ready?
Our company's legal department
is split into three divisions.
Our division handles
intellectual property, data,
investments,
and internal audits.
Mainly about these.
Some cases,
like patent rights in IP,
are very similar
to the commercial litigation
we handled before.
For now, your top priority
is to catch up on the updated regulations
from the past two years.
Also, Pan Jie will help you
understand the situation.
There are a few closed case files
you can start reviewing.
Got it.
Yue, have a seat.
I still feel a bit off
about making you a legal assistant.
Director Qin,
I really need this job.
Thank you so much
for giving me this opportunity.
Whether I can handle it or not,
just watch my performance.
Then aim to move up to legal specialist.
Yue,
let's start fresh.
I'll get to work now.
This stack is for you.
Take what you need.
She's the new assistant?
Didn't Boss say
he didn't want an assistant?
Must be a connection.
No way.
Come in.
Director.
This is the contract just came
from the Procurement Department.
- Take a look.
- Thanks.
I'm getting back to work.
(Technical Equipment
Procurement Project Contract)
(Yaofeng Tech)
(Yaofeng Technology Co., Ltd.
Representative: Yang Qing)
(Yaofeng Tech?)
Have some water.
Thank you.
Mr. Hu,
I came today
mainly to talk
about this contract.
Let's not rush into it just yet.
No rush, no rush.
Yaofeng and Zhongzhi
are old partners, after all.
And besides,
Mr. Chen,
you wouldn't delay me, would you?
When Zhang was here,
it only took one word from me
to get things done.
But now that he's gone,
we've got a new
legal department director.
What's his name?
I'm not too familiar with him yet.
Can't quite figure him out.
So
why don't we have dinner together
to get to know each other?
The usual rules.
The usual spot.
Here, Director Qin,
this way.
Mr. Chen, I can't stay too long today.
I have other matters later.
Director Qin, you're already here.
Everyone's waiting for you.
Everyone?
All familiar people.
Our long-term
strategic partners.
I told them
I have high hopes for you.
Because
you are the rising star
of our Legal Department.
Please.
I'm free these days.
It depends on your schedule.
Let me know in advance
once you decide,
and we can book the room
ahead of time.
Mr. Hu, Manager Tian,
sorry to keep you waiting.
Let me introduce you.
This is
the director of Legal Department,
Qin Can.
(Qin Can)
I'm Mr. Song's attorney,
Qin Can.
Hu Cheng from Yaofeng Tech.
And this is
Hu Cheng, founder of Yaofeng Tech.
Mr. Hu, we meet again.
You two
know each other?
Not only do we know each other,
but Mr. Hu also taught me
a very important lesson.
We're all old friends here.
Knowing each other
makes things easier.
Lawyer Qin,
we really seem to have a connection.
Now
you've joined Zhongzhi?
You advised me
to change careers before,
but I didn't agree.
Looking at it now,
since I'm working
with Mr. Hu anyway,
I might as well choose
a more comfortable
environment for myself.
Lawyer Qin,
you're like gold.
You'll shine wherever you go.
Mr. Hu,
I'm not a lawyer anymore.
Since we're all old friends,
let's skip the formalities.
Let's sit, eat,
and catch up properly.
- Come on, let's sit.
- Okay.
I won't eat.
Mr. Chen, don't worry.
I'll handle Mr. Hu's project
carefully
and won't let anything slide.
Take your time eating.
I'll take my leave first.
It's already dinnertime.
Wait, wait.
I'll walk you out, Director Qin.
I'll take care of it.
Director Qin, wait.
Director Qin,
is there any bad blood
between you and Mr. Hu?
No.
That's good to hear.
Go ahead and get busy.
Next time, let's set aside some time
to discuss
how to expedite
this contract process.
I'm always thinking about
the company's best interests.
Don't worry, Mr. Chen.
I'll prioritize
the company's interests.
See? We're on the same page.
Take care, take care.
Leave a margin for others,
so you can meet again.
Caught in his hands, huh?
Whose side are you on?
I'm on whoever treats me well.
Alright,
such a greenhorn
won't trouble our Mr. Hu.
You're a sly fox.
Nothing can stump you.
Don't be angry.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye-bye, bye-bye.
Ziyuan!
Sorry.
Mommy!
Good boy.
Mommy, you finally came!
I'm sorry, Mommy was late.
Ziyuan's mom,
have you
started working?
Yes, I've just started,
and I'm still adjusting.
I'm really sorry.
I hurried as much as I could.
It's fine.
We just finished school,
and the kids who are still here
can keep playing for a while.
- Thank you.
- It's fine.
Ziyuan, you need to be more
understanding of your mom.
She works really hard.
I know, teacher.
When Dad gets home tired,
he doesn't do housework.
Mom doesn't have to do it today either.
If Mom doesn't cook,
what will you eat?
I'll treat Mom to dinner.
You'll treat Mom?
Where did you get the money?
I want to be like Dad
and make lots of money
to treat Mom to dinner.
Ziyuan,
Mom doesn't need you
to make lots of money.
Mom only needs you
to be healthy
and happy,
okay?
Okay, Mom.
But
Dad said that
a man must make lots of money
to protect his family.
Protecting your family
isn't just about making money.
There are many ways to do it.
The most important thing
is to be honest and kind
to your family.
I understand, Mom.
What's with this long list
of penalties?
Since when has Yaofeng signed
such unfair contracts?
Of course, delete them all.
Do you even need to ask?
Who's the legal expert here,
you or me?
If not, just give me your salary
and quit!
Dad,
don't be mad.
I'm not mad.
I'm just frustrated
with my subordinate.
Being so incompetent,
yet still getting paid so much.
Making money has become
way too easy for them.
Dad,
the most important thing
for a man isn't making money.
Then what is it?
It's being honest.
Who told you that?
I did.
Is it wrong?
How will we live if there's no money?
Hello,
did you get it done?
Sure, I told you to delete them.
Have the soup.
Still up?
I'm waiting for you.
Honey, I've had lots of things going on.
It's annoying.
Honey, I wanted to talk to you
about my job.
Honey,
I'm really tired today.
Let's talk tomorrow.
Alright, get some rest.
By the way,
there's a big company event tomorrow.
I might come home late.
Don't wait up,
go to bed early.
(Yaofeng Tech
Appreciation Banquet)
I'll have Nie attend as well.
Tian Qiuzi should also be there.
Let's hope they can gather
some useful information.
Tell Nie
this is the last time.
I've almost finalized
the house purchase.
Next week, I'll sign the contract
and pay the deposit.
After that,
I'll formally file for divorce with him.
(Yaofeng Tech Appreciation Banquet)
Mr. Yao, Mr. Zhang,
thank you for coming.
Mr. Zhang, it seems
you're doing well financially.
Really?
Congratulations!
Mr. Zhang, you must
lead us to make big money!
Of course.
- Let's drink.
- This is more like it.
Director Tian,
long time no see.
You're here in a hurry, aren't you?
Yes.
Do we have
any new projects coming up?
Your red dress today looks stunning.
Let's make money together.
- Very elegant.
- Really? Thank you.
Here.
(Make a good speech later.)
(Don't forget to recommend me.)
Ning,
here are the professional
materials you needed.
I've got them prepared.
Thank you, Director.
I'll return them as soon as I'm done.
No need,
just keep them.
They're no use to me anyway.
Ning,
you and Qin
used to be my right-hand people.
Now you're both in new positions,
starting fresh.
It's not easy.
Director Qin is much more
capable than me now.
I can't compare.
Don't say that.
Do you know
how much he admired you back then?
You've been his inspiration and goal
for all these years.
Yue,
here's your file for the fieldwork.
Qin, on duty now.
Sure.
But now, seeing me like this,
he must be disappointed, right?
Not at all.
If it weren't for the severe illness
you had after childbirth,
things wouldn't have
turned out this way, right?
Director,
that day
you mentioned
after my maternity leave,
you had kept my position open for me.
Yes,
I kept it open for you all along.
But then your
severe postpartum depression
made it impossible for you to return.
I did experience
postpartum depression for a while,
but it wasn't very severe
or long-lasting.
How did you
hear about this?
Your husband told us.
My husband?
Did he also say
that I had severe postpartum depression
and violent tendencies,
and that I could
harm people around me,
including my child?
Yes, that's exactly what he said.
We've always thought highly of you
and wanted you to return.
To be cautious,
I even sent you a message on WeChat.
You replied,
saying you had no will to live
and didn't want to work anymore.
So, we couldn't do anything.
But I never
received your message.
That's impossible.
It must have been my husband
replying to you using my phone.
Your husband?
Why would he do that?
I'm not surprised at all.
This is exactly
the kind of thing he would do.
When I got used to
Mending the broken halves of my heart, one stitch at a time
I forgot that, in truth
What seemed shattered, though not quite, could never truly be whole
When I believed
That piecing it all together, bit by bit, would keep me from being alone
I then realized that the incompleteness
is something no one can ever fill
For all that went unspoken,
what I was not offered, what I was unwilling to let go
Why bother chasing them anymore?
For all the things I've held onto, the things I've released,
the starts and the endings
No need to look back
How I cry, how I laugh
How I speakno need for pretense
Just head towards the next beautiful scenery
For all what's left unsaid,
what I was not offered, what I was unwilling to let go
Why bother chasing them anymore?
For all the things I've held onto, the things I've released,
the starts and the endings
No need to look back
How I cry, how I laugh
How I speakno need for pretense
Just head towards this journey, at peace with myself