=In Marriage and Beyond=
=Episode 2=
Once upon a time,
there was a scorpion
who wanted to cross a river,
but it couldn’t swim.
At that moment,
a frog came by.
The scorpion asked the frog,
"Can you carry me across the river?"
The frog replied,
"No, I can't.
If I carry you across,
you'll sting me on my back."
The scorpion said,
"Don't worry,
I can't swim.
If I do that,
we'll both drown."
So the frog trusted the scorpion's words
and agreed to carry it across the river.
But who would've thought,
halfway across,
the scorpion still stung the frog.
(peaceful sleep every day.)
At the very moment
when they were about to sink,
the frog asked the scorpion,
"Why did you do that?"
The scorpion replied,
"Because
It's just
in my nature.”
Mr. Hu,
The post I put online,
was seen by Congcong.
I didn't expect that kid to jump off the building because of it.
What should I do now?
What can we learn from the story?
The scorpion is a bad guy.
It tells us that the little frog
Shouldn't have trusted the scorpion's words.
You need to understand one thing:
no matter where or
no matter when,
you should never trust others.
Just trust yourself.
What about you and mom?
Can I trust you?
Just trust yourself.
This is a pop-up book made by Ning Yue for him
You're giving him this?
Don't think like an adult.
He's a little kid.
Kids love these kinds of things.
My baby wife is always right.
What's wrong?
This color
doesn't suit you at all.
Darker shades look better on you.
This family really can't do without you.
Of course!
Dad.
- Hello, Mr. Hu.
- Mr. Hu.
- Take a seat.
Let me see…
Mr. Hu, their noodles are really good.
Right, super chewy.
- Smells amazing.
- Alright.
I'll have this too.
Let me.
Mr. Hu,
Song, come join us for lunch.
These noodles are really delicious.
Want a serving?
The doctor said I need to eat something light for now.
I still need some time
to recover.
Stay back.
This sauce might stain your clothes, it'll be hard to wash off.
Look,
how considerate Song is.
Yes.
Mr. Hu,
I remember
your old tie was a dark color,
why did you switch to a lighter one?
The dark ones
are much more dignified,
they really match your aura,
don't you think?
I think
you have the same taste
as my wife.
Am I?
Song,
how's your health recovering?
The doctor said the surgery went pretty smoothly.
But it needs time to recover.
I've been thinking,
with so many new products coming out in our company,
I couldn't rest easy.
So I had to come by.
You're worrying too much.
We have so many employees,
you're not indispensable.
Well, Song,
I think you should rest
when you need it.
Our company
values humanistic care a lot.
You're telling me to exploit and pressure
someone who's sick?
Wouldn't that be unethical?
No, I…
Song,
What you've done for the company
I'll keep it in my heart.
But
I really think you should take the rest you need.
Listen to me,
just go home.
Give the younger folks
a chance to show their talents,
right?
Cheng,
Song
is one of the pioneers who helped us build the company.
Think it over.
I know he has his issues, but I can handle it.
Haven't I given him a decent severance?
That's not the point.
I'm just worried that
if you let him go,
it might hurt the team's morale.
Don't worry.
It won't.
Everyone, listen up.
Today,
I've made
a very painful decision.
I've just let go of
an old employee who started the business with me.
Why did I let him go?
It's simple.
He's been taking a high salary,
but he's gotten too comfortable.
He's no longer contributing to the company.
On top of that,
he's been lining his own pockets.
I, Yao Feng,
don't keep freeloaders.
And today, I've made another decision.
The team in charge of launching new product,
besides the year-end bonus,
will get a 20% salary increase
starting next month.
Good.
Well said.
Darling,
this isn't the same cheongsam you wore last time, right?
By the way, how's the charity going?
I've stopped doing it.
I understand.
Not everyone can keep up with
this self-sacrificial act of helping others.
By the way,
our company's in-house lawyer is on leave for a few days.
I've got something I need to consult you about.
I'll pay you of course.
Let me send you a screenshot of the contract.
Can I have your WeChat?
Sure.
Ms. Lan,
your company's in-house lawyer
hasn't come back yet?
Mr. Hu,
I'm borrowing your big lawyer for a bit.
You won't mind, right?
When my wife was a lawyer,
she handled all the big cases in the company.
She charged by the minute,
you know.
Well then,
how about a friendship discount?
I told you,
my wife doesn't drink.
Ms. Lan,
actually, I'm pretty familiar with
your company's situation.
I'll be free the day after tomorrow afternoon.
You can come by Yao Feng.
I'll have our legal team
go over the contract for you.
Honey,
can you check if Ziyuan is asleep?
Sure, I'll go check.
Enjoy your meal.
Cheers, Ms. Lan.
Cheers.
If that's the case,
it's great.
Indeed, this way,
our three-party cooperation will bring more benefits.
- Rest assured. I'll handle it.
- Exactly.
Sure.
I'll leave it to you.
No problem.
Ms. Lan,
you can trust Mr. Zhou.
Okay.
Cheng is responsible for supervising me.
He's my boss.
I'll go cut up some fruit for you all.
You changed your clothes.
It's too tight.
Alright, Mr. Hu,
We're leaving.
- Okay, then.
- Alright.
I'll walk Ms. Lan and the others out.
- Bye.
- Yue, bye.
- Don't you want some fruit before you go?
- Yue.
- No, we're good.
- Thanks for hosting us.
We're full already.
Zhou Wei,
why do I feel like
Mr. Hu
doesn't really like me interacting too much with his wife?
No way.
You're overthinking it.
No WeChat,
no drinking,
and I'm the one overthinking?
Mr. Hu,
He just loves his wife very much.
That's how he protects his family.
Stop looking at it.
It'll get better.
Honey,
you drank.
I did.
You know
I don't want you to drink.
My wife is the best.
(Qi Ming Law Firm Qin Can Practicing Lawyer)
A fine case of biting the hand that feeds.
Mr. Qin, honestly,
my request is pretty simple.
I just want to
get more compensation.
Mr. Song,
I can't guarantee anything
unless we have solid evidence.
But if what you say is true
and the evidence is sufficient,
I believe I can help you seek justice.
Make sure to handle things well with the hospital,
especially the cost issues.
Everything needs to
be resolved properly.
No more complications.
Don't worry, Mr. Hu.
I'll take care of it.
I've already arranged
everything in Shanghai.
After you finish this,
you can head there immediately.
After some time,
if you want to return to the company, you're welcome to.
Alright.
- Zhu.
- Mr. Zhou.
Long time no see.
Mr. Hu.
Mr. Zhou, I'll take my leave.
When did Zhu return to the company?
Didn't you assign him to the service station
to look after Yue?
Yue isn't there anymore,
so I think
we don't need the station anymore.
By the way,
Song's lawyer will be arriving soon.
Do you still want to meet him in person?
This needs to be handled cautiously.
Let's see what they have to say.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I got delayed by a meeting.
Pour them a glass of water.
Mr. Hu, nice to meet you.
(Qin Can)
I'm Mr. Song's attorney.
Qin Can.
Hu Cheng from Yao Feng Technology.
I didn’t expect Song
to hire such a young lawyer.
Please, have a seat.
I was going
to let my lawyer talk to you directly,
but then I figured
I'd better say a few words myself.
I am not
an unscrupulous capitalist.
Mr. Song
is a veteran employee of ours.
What he's contributed to the company
I've kept them in my heart.
During his hospitalization
and surgery,
you can check,
our company provided him with a lot of support,
That's the rights he should have under labor laws.
I'm a busy man
and don't have time to argue here.
What I want to say is,
during Mr. Song's employment,
there were no personal grievances
between us.
We fairly, reasonably, and lawfully terminated
an employee who no longer brought any value to the company,
and we gave him full compensation.
And what did we get in return?
His betrayal
and gross slander
have put my company
at great risk.
I won't tolerate it,
nor will I let this kind of thing happen.
An incapable employee gets dismissed
and then retaliates against the company.
If I allow this precedent,
how will I answer to my employees in the future?
What I must do
is to protect the company's interests,
and the interests of every employee in this company.
Alright.
I've said my piece.
You two
can handle the rest.
Mr. Hu, wait.
I hope you're prepared.
We do not accept a settlement.
Nonsense.
Song must have acted rashly.
Today.
I'll go talk to him again today.
Mr. Zhou, Mr. Hu,
Ms. Tian.
our legal department has a contract
that needs Mr. Hu's review.
Alright,
you all go ahead and talk.
Why didn’t you let me know you were coming?
Upset?
That's okay.
I know how to cheer you up.
This is
the compensation Mr. Hu is giving you.
You must accept it.
Don't worry,
I'll settle all your hospital bills.
(Emergency Observation Room)
Ms. Ho,
The one who just came in was my colleague Zhu, right?
What was he here for?
Ms. Ning,
Let's just end this here.
My family doesn't want to see you anymore.
Please don't come again.
Sorry,
The number you've dialed is temporarily unavailable.
Zhu,
Zhu!
Didn't you say she wouldn't come here?
She hasn't come before.
She doesn't come to check up on things.
So why are you so nervous?
It has nothing to do with checking up.
Then what does it have to do with?
I don't like surprises.
If you're coming next time,
let me know in advance.
It's going to rain.
Let me drive you back.
Okay.
Do you enjoy
this kind of thrill
that something's always at your beck and call?
The things I raise,
why can't I control them?
Honey,
What's wrong?
Why do you
look so down?
Why did Zhu give Ms. Ho money?
You already know?
What else are you hiding from me?
Where's Zhu?
Zhu is my employee.
I intentionally arranged for him to go to the service station.
I thought
since you haven't worked for a while,
you might have trouble adjusting.
I wanted to have someone who can look after you.
And as for
the incident with Congcong getting hurt,
it has nothing to do with you.
Even Congcong's mom knows this.
She's just taking her anger out on you.
I gave her money for two reasons.
First,
she'll stop talking online.
Second,
I think, taking the child into account,
it's right
to close this chapter for you.
Honey,
the reason I didn't tell you earlier
was because I didn't want
to put too much pressure on you
or
make you upset.
Actually,
Niuniu's mom was also arranged by me.
I admit,
I've been a bit over-involved.
But
I just want you to be happy.
Honey,
You've suffered these past few days.
I really want to share some of that burden.
Is there anything else?
What else do you want to know?
Confession gets leniency.
I confess.
Honey,
everything I do
is for you
and for this family.
Everything I do
is for you
and for this family.
Mom,
have some water.
Mr. Hu
really cares about your mother.
He calls every day to check on her.
I've never seen such a good son-in-law.
Isn't that right?
Since your mother fell last time,
Mr. Hu has been constantly reminding us,
saying we must make sure nothing happens to her again.
My son-in-law is a smart man.
He knows
that treating me well means treating my daughter well.
As for my son-in-law,
I would say
he's pretty much perfect.
I can’t find any faults.
That's what I'm talking about.
Mr. Zhou,
Mr. Zhou.
The contract with Ms. Lan is brilliant.
You've brought the company tremendous profits.
Great job!
Cheng,
about Song,
considering Yao Feng is preparing to go public,
we should give him more compensation.
It's better to settle this peacefully.
He's already promised me
he won't cause us any more trouble.
He'll sign the settlement agreement and send it to me today.
Mr. Zhou
I'll leave everything
to you to handle.
I knew you
was magnanimous
and tolerant,
with great composure.
What's been settled?
You heard me.
It's been settled.
Mr. Song, given Mr. Hu Cheng's usual style and demeanor,
I don't believe he'll give you a fair and satisfactory result.
And such case,
if he's not punished as he should be,
will continue
to happen at Yao Feng Technology.
Does Mr. Hu get something on you?
If so, tell me everything.
I'll make sure we win this lawsuit.
You're absolutely right
about fairness and justice.
I totally agree.
But Yao Feng's standing in the industry
is something I can't afford to offend.
I have a family to feed,
and I'm already dealing with my own health problems.
So all the overtime and late nights
we’ve put in recently
will go to waste?
Mr. Qin,
I appreciate it.
As for…
the fees we discussed earlier,
I'll pay them in full.
Alright?
Really, thank you so much.
- You've worked hard.
- Wait. Let me pour you a glass of water.
It's not about the fees.
It's that Hu Cheng should have been punished...
Li!
Are you okay?
(Haikang Hospital)
He already has a stomach ulcer.
How could you let him work overtime like this?
He can't even guarantee
a basic regular diet
right now.
From the preliminary results
of the gastroscopy,
the ulcer has already developed into a proliferative lesion.
The nature of it still needs further tests
to make a proper judgment.
Are you vampires?
Draining people dry…
Isn’t that enough?
Sorry, madam,
We'll cover all of Li's medical expenses.
Money, money, money.
All you care about is money.
I'm sorry.
Ms. Lan, this project…
It's not easy for us
to collaborate smoothly
and sign the contract.
- No, it's not.
- Cheers.
- To a successful partnership.
- To a happy collaboration.
Thank you, Ms. Lan, for your trust.
We'll do our best.
- Let's work hard together.
- Sure.
- Help yourself.
- Okay.
Enjoy the meal.
Try this.
This was made by Yue.
My wife is a pretty good cook.
Yue is really impressive now.
- Ms. Lan.
- Zhou Wei, have more.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Ms. Lan.
- Help yourself.
- Okay.
Mr. Hu, I toast to you.
I hope we have more opportunities to work together in the future.
Yeah, yeah, more communication.
Definitely.
(Your husband is staying at my home. Why haven't you divorced him yet?)
Cheers.
This wine's pretty good.
Yue,
you took the wrong phone.
Sorry about that.
No problem, I often grab the wrong phone too.
My job is to take care of you.
That last project...
Yue, what's wrong?
Honey.
Excuse me, nature calls.
Cheers.
Thank you for leading us.
Yue,
that text message earlier
was from my best friend.
She's just messing with me.
Actually,
I didn't even read it clearly.
Honestly,
my relationship with my husband is pretty good.
A message like that,
how could that be?
Right?
(Back in the car)
Honey,
what did Ms. Lan talk to you about?
Affair.
Her husband…
You knew about that already?
I just found out.
Her husband
is bad news.
I don't understand,
why would such a capable woman like Ms. Lan
put up with it?
Maybe it's because
their interests are so deeply tied together.
Some things,
if you don't deal with them,
they don’t exist.
Ms. Lan is a smart woman,
she knows what's what.
I'm not that smart,
and I don't want to
be like her.
Honey,
how could I let you be like her?
When you used to watch horror movies,
You'd always hug me.
Why…
Why aren't you scared today?
Who told you
I hugged you
because I was scared?
(Yao Feng Technology)
Mr. Qin,
Song choosing
to settle with us
must have surprised you.
You're an ambitious person.
You want to defeat me, an evil capitalist,
to show off your heroism.
Let me give you a piece of advice:
Try some creative work
or write articles criticizing the world.
That'll be more helpful
to achieve your ideals.
Goodbye.
I hope you can approve.
(Resignation Letter Qin Can)
(Resignation Letter)
Qin,
in just five years,
you've gone from assistant
to a senior lawyer.
You've worked hard,
and your professional skills
are outstanding.
You're now a role model for those interns.
But I feel ashamed.
I watch my clients suffer unfairness,
yet can't provide them
with practical help.
As their lawyer,
I feel powerless.
Qin,
you're still too young,
and you view things too one-sidedly.
You still need more experience
to grow and improve.
Anyway,
from the company's side or from mine personally,
we truly hope you'll stay.
Please think about it again.
(Resignation Letter)
Director,
I've thought it over.
I just want you to be happy.
Go talk to Mr. Hu and make sure
he won't withdraw the funding.
Hu Cheng,
he really treats his wife well.
He actually pays out of his own pocket
to keep his wife happy.
(Emergency Observation Room)
Mom,
look!
Look!
Dad said
the water plants you trim
are the prettiest.
He wants you to do the trimming.
Mom,
what's wrong?
I'm fine.
I love you.
I love you the most, Ziyuan.
Ziyuan,
do you know
why we trim the water plants?
Because if you don't trim them,
they’ll take nutrients from others,
occupy their resources.
Water plants are really powerful.
The little fish,
the little shrimp,
they're all afraid of them.
But we're not afraid,
because
we're not small fish or shrimp.
We want to be lions,
be tigers.
♪When I got used to♪
♪Mending the broken halves of my heart, one stitch at a time♪
♪I forgot that, in truth♪
♪What seemed shattered, though not quite, could never truly be whole♪
♪When I believed♪
♪That piecing it all together, bit by bit, would keep me from being alone♪
♪I then realized that the incompleteness♪
♪ is something no one can ever fill♪
♪For all that went unspoken,♪
♪what I was not offered, what I was unwilling to let go♪
♪Why bother chasing them anymore?♪
♪For all the things I've held onto, the things I've released, ♪
♪the starts and the endings♪
♪No need to look back♪
♪How I cry, how I laugh♪
♪How I speak—no need for pretense♪
♪Just head towards the next beautiful scenery♪
♪For all what's left unsaid,♪
♪what I was not offered, what I was unwilling to let go♪
♪Why bother chasing them anymore?♪
♪For all the things I've held onto, the things I've released, ♪
♪the starts and the endings♪
♪No need to look back♪
♪How I cry, how I laugh♪
♪How I speak—no need for pretense♪
♪Just head towards this journey, at peace with myself♪