=Married=
=Episode 24=
I'm embarrassing.
It should have been me
treating the client to a meal,
letting him help me with the contract,
but now he's ended up
working at my place.
Can the client easily let you bribe him?
The dishes look great.
Stop playing, it's time to eat.
Come, Ziyuan, time to eat.
Jiaojiao.
I need to take a photo.
This is too nice.
- Someone's being rude.
- Ziyuan.
Why do I see you've already started?
- The adults haven't started yet.
- Has Mom announced it yet?
Wait a moment.
- Okay.
- Come on.
- OK.
Let Mom announce it.
- It's time to eat now.
- OK.
Time to eat.
- Eat.
- Come on.
Uncle.
You haven't taken me out
to play in a while.
- OK.
- Uncle Qin,
I want to learn how to fish.
How about we go
for a picnic this weekend?
Good.
Try to finish all your food, okay?
- OK.
- Drink up.
- I'll take you fishing this weekend.
- I just want to eat.
(Party A: Yaofeng Technology Co., Ltd.)
(Article 1: Subscription
and Investment Purposes)
(I've settled everything here.)
(When can I see Ziyuan?)
(Come pick up Ziyuan tomorrow.)
Ziyuan.
Daddy's over there.
Go on.
Go.
Daddy.
I missed you, Daddy.
I'm sorry.
I missed you so much.
Daddy.
Why did you come so late?
I came late.
Daddy.
Good boy.
I missed you too.
Mom said that
today, I can stay with you.
Great.
Today,
you can stay with me.
Be good.
Good boy.
Get in the car
and wait for Daddy, okay?
OK.
Thank you.
Bring him back on Sunday.
Don't delay his classes on Monday.
I
rented a place.
Don't worry.
I won't let Ziyuan see anyone else.
Ziyuan,
go to Daddy's place.
Don't play too rough.
Be good.
We're leaving now.
Ziyuan,
Daddy bought you so many toys,
but you still
love to play with this one.
Because I haven't played
with Daddy in so long,
so I'll play with this first.
When Daddy's not around,
does Mommy play with you?
But
she doesn't allow me
to play on the floor
or walk barefoot.
Look.
You little troublemaker.
Naughty boy.
Look what you've done
to this rocket.
What now?
Daddy can't clean it up.
I'll rest a bit too.
Daddy's so clumsy.
You're the clumsy one!
You can't even catch it.
Ziyuan,
you're already a big boy.
You should start
brushing your own teeth.
Daddy, I can brush my teeth,
you just don't know.
Daddy, you're a big dinosaur.
Don't take it from me.
I haven't put on the pillowcase.
Daddy, now you're a big dinosaur.
Big dinosaur is coming!
- The big dinosaur will eat you now!
- Come on.
Daddy,
it's so late,
do you still have time to sleep with me?
Daddy's not
as busy with work now,
so I can spend more time with you.
Are you happy?
Yes.
Daddy,
can you
stop working
and just play with me?
I haven't seen you in a long time.
I've missed you.
Daddy.
Are you happy
playing with me?
Of course I am!
Why do you ask?
I feel like
when you
used to be with me,
you seemed happier working
than when you were with me.
Daddy,
Mom said
before,
you couldn't be with us
because you made a mistake.
Is that true?
I...
I did make a serious mistake.
I can't
live with you and Mom
anymore.
But
Daddy will always...
Daddy,
please don't make any more mistakes.
I don't want to lose you again.
Daddy.
I won't.
I won't make mistakes again.
Aren't your eyes tired?
Your hair's gone white.
Don't you sleep?
I will, I will sleep soon.
Let me finish reading this.
I've already prepared his schoolbag
and his clothes are washed.
Mom,
to be honest,
this year,
if it weren't for you,
I would have broken down.
Like you've never broken down.
Yes, yes, it's my fault.
I tend to
unconsciously take my anger out
on the people closest to me.
Thinking back,
when Hu Cheng was busy with work,
no matter how stressed he was,
he never lost
his temper with me.
He's pitiful too.
♪The heart♪
♪Gradually drifts away♪
♪You're in the mirror♪
♪So distant away♪
♪Who♪
♪Pieces together the memories♪
♪I can't see myself clearly♪
♪Where should I go♪
♪Suddenly♪
(I haven't had this real feeling)
(in a long time.)
♪Suddenly♪
(The last time)
(was when the three of us
were together.)
♪Do you remember♪
(I thought)
(those days would never change.)
(I thought our happiness)
(would last forever.)
Honey, it's me.
Look, I'm here.
(It was Ning Yue's tolerance and love)
(that made us happy.)
(But)
(it was ruined)
(by my stubbornness and arrogance.)
(I ignored Ning Yue's feelings)
(and destroyed my own happiness.)
I want to work.
I won't allow it.
Why can't you allow it?
I gave up my dignity,
I gave up my sweat!
So I could earn enough money
to provide you with a life of ease!
I hate you for locking me at home,
not letting me doing anything
under the guise of protecting me.
♪Forget it♪
I hate you.
You destroyed my career
and my dignity.
I won't let her leave me.
Hu Cheng, let go.
♪I'll venture out♪
♪To chase through the crowd♪
I don't want to live like this!
I just can't live like this anymore.
I can't stand this kind of life
for even one more day!
Honey,
don't leave me.
♪Finally I decide to let go♪
Let's get a divorce.
Dad.
(It's too late to regret now.)
(If there's anything I can do...)
♪Let all the dreams fade away♪
(What can I do?)
♪On the long journey, we'll bloom♪
♪Be ourselves♪
Ziyuan, get off the car.
Ziyuan.
You're back so late.
You still have to
wake up early tomorrow.
Mom,
Daddy could make my bed.
I didn't know that before.
Really?
Well, Daddy didn't know
you could brush your teeth.
I can do a lot of other things.
But Daddy doesn't know.
Alright,
you can show Daddy slowly in the future,
okay?
Next week,
I want to play with Daddy again.
Ziyuan has grown up now.
Now,
you can even be my teacher.
I am Teacher Ziyuan.
In the past,
I thought work made me the happiest.
Because it allowed me
to provide the best conditions for you,
so you could live well.
But
I didn't spend enough time with you.
Now I know
the happiest and most joyful thing
is being with you.
Dad, you need to stay happy.
I will.
Alright,
we're heading upstairs.
Bye, Daddy.
Listen to Mom, alright?
Bye.
Did you have fun?
Yes, I did.
That's good.
This color
doesn't suit you at all.
Deep color is more suitable for you.
You must come tomorrow.
Don't be late,
alright?
I'll wait for you
to come back victoriously,
and we'll start over again.
Tomorrow, wait for me.
Tian Qiuzi,
why do you keep
haunting us like a ghost?
What do you want now?
What,
are you planning
to hide behind another man
and let him support you?
Miss Tian,
today's meeting
is Yaofeng's shareholders' meeting.
You have no right to attend.
If you continue like this,
we'll have to call security.
I would like to clarify that
my attendance today
is on behalf of Mr. Jiang.
Now do I have the right?
She's representing Mr. Jiang?
Mr. Jiang?
Ning Yue,
in the year you replaced Hu Cheng
as the general manager and president,
many long-term shareholders
withdrew their shares.
Do you know the reason behind it?
If it weren't for Mr. Jiang
consistently acquiring
those scattered shares,
Yaofeng
wouldn't have survived until today.
You really planned everything.
I don't know how you managed
to team up with Mr. Jiang.
Over the past year,
our shares have indeed been
gradually acquired.
But whether this process is compliant
and legal,
we don't know.
Don't worry,
I will get to the bottom of it
and not let it slide.
Before worrying about that,
you should be concerned
about yourself first.
Today, I'm here
on behalf of Mr. Jiang
to remove Ning Yue from
the position of general manager.
Removing Ning Yue?
That's inappropriate.
First of all,
this topic is not
on today's meeting agenda.
Secondly,
with the limited shares Mr. Jiang holds,
he doesn't have enough votes
to remove me from my position.
I knew you'd say that.
Yes,
right now,
you hold 25.5% of the shares,
and with the shareholders
you've kept in the dark,
Mr. Jiang's 30%
indeed isn't enough.
But let's not forget,
there's been someone absent
this entire year.
If we include his votes,
do you think I can
remove you from your position?
It wouldn't be Hu Cheng, would it?
Is it Hu Cheng?
It's Hu Cheng, isn't it?
Yes,
it's Hu Cheng.
(Yaofeng Tech)
- Mr. Hu.
Mr. Hu.
Hu Cheng is the one
who built Yaofeng into what it is today,
step by step,
bringing everyone to this point.
Ning Yue,
when Hu Cheng was at his lowest,
you kicked him while he was down
and filed for divorce.
You know exactly
how you got your shares,
don't you?
It's Mr. Hu.
It really is Mr. Hu.
Sorry, everyone.
I'm late.
Not just for today,
but for over a year of absence.
Due to my rash decisions,
the company
has suffered significant losses.
I'm not here
to defend myself
or make excuses.
But,
some issues
must be addressed promptly
to prevent further risks to the company.
Thank you all
for trusting Yaofeng.
During its most difficult time,
you chose not to leave,
but to support
and help Yaofeng
get out of the trough.
I hope you will continue
to support and trust Yaofeng.
With all of you,
Yaofeng will
go further,
and get even better.
During my absence of more than a year,
it was Ning Yue
who saved Yaofeng.
She has proven her ability
and shown that she can lead Yaofeng
to greater heights.
One of the main reasons
I came today is that
I need to announce something.
I will transfer
my 25.5% shares
unconditionally to Ning Yue.
From now on,
I have nothing to do
with Yaofeng.
Thank you all.
Do you have to do it this way?
Sorry.
Are you even a man?
Loser!
I did all of this for you,
for you!
Sorry.
Is it that you
still have feelings for her?
Do you care for her, Hu Cheng?
It's okay, I understand.
I'll go find Mr. Jiang again.
Don't rush to make a decision yet.
I will make sure you wake up to reality.
I'll help you win Yaofeng back,
okay?
This path
was wrong from the start.
We shouldn't be together.
You're still young.
You still have a chance to start over.
What do you mean?
Now you want to be a good person?
I've never been a good person.
But I know
you have it harder than me.
I don't care.
I don't care what others
say behind my back.
I just want you to be well.
I just want you to win in the end.
Hu Cheng, I beg you.
Don't let me lose.
I beg you.
Winning
at all costs
is only a temporary victory.
What we lose
is our personality and dignity.
Perhaps even freedom.
One day,
you'll feel
that it was all not worth it.
I know it's hard for you now.
This
is my savings.
You can take it.
I don't need your charity!
This
is all my savings.
I... I don't know
what more I can do for you.
I...
I hope
you can live well.
Live a good life.
We really made a mistake.
I'm sorry.
I'll pour you a cup of tea.
Grandma.
Qiuzi.
I feel happy when I look at you.
Really?
I'll come and stay with you
every day, okay?
I'll stay here and not leave.
I'll be by your side every day.
No.
You have your career
that you love so much to pursue.
Before, your eyes were sparkling
when you talked to me about your work.
I support you in doing what you love.
I just want you to be happy.
Come visit me when you have time.
- Okay?
- OK.
So
no matter what happens to me,
you will always cherish me, right?
Yes.
Qiuzi is always my dearest girl.
You will never leave me,
right?
Never.
Okay.
I love you.
Ziyuan, play for a while,
then take a break.
Uncle Qin.
Quiet down.
It's okay, it's okay.
By the way, Ziyuan,
do you want to
go on a picnic tomorrow?
Let's invite Qin Jiaojiao to join us.
Yes.
Mom, do you want to join us too?
Your mom has a charity event tomorrow.
Wouldn't it be better
if it's just the three of us?
Okay.
Mom, what do you think?
No problem, you guys go ahead.
Be safe tomorrow.
Okay.
Slow down, be careful.
- Okay.
- Look how beautiful it is ahead.
Right?
It is really beautiful.
Be careful.
Qin Jiaojiao.
Please be more careful next time.
Be careful.
This place is so beautiful.
Uncle Qin.
The view here is so beautiful.
Could you take a few pictures for me?
I want to show them to Mom.
Okay.
But
you two stay here and wait for me.
This place is very dangerous.
- I'll go.
- Alright.
Let me see.
Move down a little.
Uncle, be careful.
Don't worry.
- Uncle Qin!
- Uncle!
(Ziyuan)
Ziyuan, how is it?
Are you on your way back?
Mom.
Uncle Qin fell.
What happened?
Did he fall? Is it serious?
He went to the roadside
to take pictures for me
and then he fell.
Ziyuan.
I'm fine down here.
Take care of yourself.
Ziyuan, don't worry yet.
Stay calm, stay with Jiaojiao there.
Mom will come soon.
Do you remember what I taught you?
- Send me the location.
- Yes.
Quickly send one to me.
I'm on my way.
Uncle, Uncle.
- Uncle Qin.
- Uncle.
Ziyuan, Mom is here.
- Mom.
- Are you okay?
Are you alright?
You're fine, right?
- Are you okay?
- Is Jiaojiao okay?
Where is Uncle Qin?
He's right there.
Don't move, don't move.
Don't move, you stay still.
You and Jiaojiao stay here, don't move.
Jiaojiao, you stay still.
Okay.
Mom, you need to be careful too.
Director Qin.
Yue.
I'm fine.
Don't worry, okay?
I've already called for help.
They'll be here soon.
Don't worry, I'm fine.
See?
Alright, don't move.
Don't move.
Ziyuan.
You and Jiaojiao stay up there.
I'm going to check what he's doing.
Is that okay?
- Mom.
- Don't move.
Be careful too.
Okay, take good care of Jiaojiao.
Don't move at all.
Yue, be careful.
You've just injured your leg, right?
It's okay.
Be careful.
Okay.
What happened to your face?
Did you scrape it?
Just a scratch.
Is it this side?
You can't move at all?
Let's wait for
the rescue team to arrive.
Yue.
You can't pull me up.
It's so dangerous here.
Did you come down
to watch the scenery with me?
Don't they say
that the injured person
is the most vulnerable?
Then, when you're the most vulnerable,
someone has to be with you, right?
If I stay with you,
you'll be more comfortable.
Ziyuan and Jiaojiao are still up there.
They are more vulnerable than me.
That's hard to say.
Want to give it a try?
Ziyuan.
Jiaojiao.
Are you guys okay?
We're fine.
How's Uncle Qin?
I'm fine.
Did you see that?
Aren't they stronger than you?
Fine.
I'll be
the most vulnerable kid.
Of course.
Which normal adult
would roll down a mountain
just to take a photo?
I...
I was playing with Ziyuan at that time.
Then I went to take a photo.
I saw a really nice spot.
And I accidentally
fell from there.
I was too happy playing and forgot.
That's great.
This means
you weren't just playing with Ziyuan,
you were enjoying it too.
When I was little,
I always liked coming
to the mountains to play.
My parents used to stop me
and didn't let me come.
After I grew up,
they didn't care for me anymore.
But because of work and other things,
I don't have time
to come and play in the mountains.
I never expected
that today, in this way,
I've realized my childhood dream.
Well, you paid a high price
for that childhood dream of yours.
But with you here,
it's not the same
as when I was a kid.
So I think
it's still worth it.
Then let this price
be a little heavier.
Yue.
I'm really worried about my uncle.
It's fine, Qin Jiaojiao.
My mom is taking care
of your uncle down there.
I'm up here taking care of you.
It's really beautiful.
I hope time
can stay in this moment forever.
Hi, we are here.
Right here.
Is there anyone down there?
We're the rescue team.
We're here.
Don't move! Stay there.
Wait for us to come down.
How did they get here so quickly?
Don't move!
I'll come down in a minute.
♪I forgot that, in truth♪
♪What seemed shattered, though
not quite, could never truly be whole♪
♪When I believed♪
♪That piecing it all together, bit by bit,
would keep me from being alone♪
♪I then realized that
the incompleteness♪
♪Is something no one can ever fill♪
♪For all that went unspoken♪
♪What I was not offered,
what I was unwilling to let go♪
(Fu'anli Non-profit Service Station)
(Build Dreams for Public Welfare,
Move All the Way Forward)
♪The starts and the endings♪
♪No need to look back♪
♪How I cry, how I laugh♪
♪How I speak—no need for pretense♪
♪Just head towards
the next beautiful scenery♪
♪For all what's left unsaid♪
♪What I was not offered,
what I was unwilling to let go♪
♪Why bother chasing them anymore♪
♪For all the things I've held onto,
the things I've released♪
♪The starts and the endings♪
♪No need to look back♪
♪How I cry, how I laugh♪
♪How I speak—no need for pretense♪
♪Just head towards this journey,
at peace with myself♪
♪Just head towards this journey♪
(Legal Services)
(Build Dreams for Public Welfare,
Move All the Way Forward)
♪When I got used to♪
♪Mending the broken halves of my heart, one stitch at a time♪
♪I forgot that, in truth♪
♪What seemed shattered, though not quite, could never truly be whole♪
♪When I believed♪
♪That piecing it all together, bit by bit, would keep me from being alone♪
♪I then realized that the incompleteness♪
♪ is something no one can ever fill♪
♪For all that went unspoken,♪
♪what I was not offered, what I was unwilling to let go♪
♪Why bother chasing them anymore?♪
♪For all the things I've held onto, the things I've released, ♪
♪the starts and the endings♪
♪No need to look back♪
♪How I cry, how I laugh♪
♪How I speak—no need for pretense♪
♪Just head towards the next beautiful scenery♪
♪For all what's left unsaid,♪
♪what I was not offered, what I was unwilling to let go♪
♪Why bother chasing them anymore?♪
♪For all the things I've held onto, the things I've released, ♪
♪the starts and the endings♪
♪No need to look back♪
♪How I cry, how I laugh♪
♪How I speak—no need for pretense♪
♪Just head towards this journey, at peace with myself♪