Go inside.
But still...
Stay inside.
What are they? A new type of assassin?
I don't know what they are, but there are a lot of them.
Episode 14
Outside, there's a group of robbers...
It's dangerous. Stay here and don't go out.
- What do they want?
- What do you think?
Including our lives, they're ready to take everything of value.
It's towards the carriage.
They're gifts we're going to take to the Crown Prince in South Buyeo.
We can't stand idly by and let them take everything.
- What are you doing?!
- They don't even have proper weapons.
We can't harm them.
During the day, they starve. At night, they're robbers.
Are you in your right mind? We're about to lose all the gifts meant for South Buyeo!
Still, we can't kill them.
You're just going to send them off like this?
What are you?
Through this incident, if the Queen Dowager or His Majesty face danger,
I don't think I'll be able to leave you alone.
Even after seeing how the people live, are you siding with the King?
- What?
- An incompetent, foolish, and fearful king?
You really!
Stop it.
Did they come knowing we'd pass by?
They seem like local robbers.
They're just farmers.
Farmers?
People who had farms near the borders starved and became robbers.
Are you saying that ordinary people become robbers?
So, the peace offerings prepared for the royal family in South Buyeo,
and our travel expenses, have all been taken?
I apologize. I'll chase them down now and find them.
It's no use. They can hardly make ends meet.
They've probably already sold it all over the place by now.
If it wasn't for you, this would not have happened.
Why did you go that far?
They're lowly peasants that have nothing to do with you.
What's the reason for going that far to save their lives?
You said they're ordinary farmers.
You said they were the subjects.
Within Silla there isn't a subject who can die for no reason.
I won't return to the capital.
However, you said we're going to make peace. We can't go empty handed.
Since we also lost all our food, going in this state would be difficult.
In three days, it will be the King's birthday.
Because Crown Prince Chang of South Buyeo is hostile,
he could use that day as an excuse to attack Silla.
Before that happens, we must stop him.
Hurry up with the preparations.
I will become strong in the Hwarang. Mother.
Why are you standing there like that instead of coming to take my pulse?
I came to tell you that I can no longer take your pulse.
Why?
There's a plague in Cheonin village.
- I must go to treat them.
- Send another doctor.
Does it make sense that you won't treat me because of mere Cheonins? (lowest class in Silla)
No. Why don't you let the palace doctor take your pulse from now on.
I can't trust other doctors.
Didn't I tell you?
It's a matter that doesn't involve me.
Do you dare to disobey the Queen Dowager's command?
- So,
are you going to kill me as well?
- You resent me as usual.
- Resentment can only occur when there is something to look forward to.
I do not expect anything from Your Highness. Except,
that I no longer wish to see you anymore.
You can't do this to me now.
Right now...
If you also leave me,
I don't have anyone.
It seems you are mistaken about something.
I'm not leaving you.
Since I've never returned to Your Highness.
Once, there was a time when my world would come crashing down with one word from you. However,
now, even with your tears,
I am so cold.
It seems like we'll have to sleep outdoors today.
You want us to sleep here? When the Princess is also here?
There is no inn in the vicinity. We don't even have silver coins to use.
You two bring some firewood. I'll set up something so we can spend the night here.
- Officer, sir.
- Yes.
Please go and obtain some food.
Yes, I will.
- Who are you to order people around?
- Do you have any other idea?
If you don't, follow me.
About the time you kissed me without my permission.
Until I bring that up,
what should I do?
Apologize or confess?
Apologize.
Aigoo! It's young and fresh.
But then, Lady Doctor you're mean.
You should accept him. He's a palace guard about to go to war.
- How can you reject him?
- But,
what do that woman and that palace guard look like?
Do they look like that beautiful lady and that noble over there?
I saw the noble but the woman is here.
I'm being serious. She looks a lot like me. She looks like me.
Right here.
Whoa.
Give it to me.
Carry it.
You're so clumsy. How could you miss that?
What did you just say?
♬ When the path on which I fearlessly ♬
- You want us to have a go?
- Yes. I want us to have a go.
♬ You were there. Like a dream ♬
♬ then another world which I came to know ♬
- Don't regret it.
- I'm Kim Soo Ho. What do you mean by regret?
♬ became a light in your breath.♬
♬ I'm fine with you as the only one. ♬
♬ I will find the star. Until I reach the dream suspended high in the sky ♬
♬ Even if darkness surrounds me  ♬
♬ You are the only one I will never throw away ♬
♫  Always be mine  ♫
Now that I look at it, it seems like a familiar incense pouch.
- What?
- By any chance, does Soo Yeon
like you?
♬ If my harsh fate ♬
That wouldn't happen. But even if it does, don't accept her.
I think we're finally getting close.
That would make things awkward.
♬ You are the one answer from the skill of god, shining on me. ♬
♬  If I even try to ask my heart over and over ♬
This is nice.
♬ No matter what anyone says ultimately for me it's you. ♬
Are you okay, Princess?
Stop it! Stop it!
No?
Two people have to take turns keeping a night watch. There might be robbers here.
You just can't do this right...
I.
I apologize.
It seems that we'll be starving today.
I don't think so.
Are you saying that you found all of these in the mountains?
Generosity has no boundaries.
In a place where people live, if you have affection for each other, you should share your food. Don't you think so?
What are you doing not eating?
Please eat. It's food that I got.
I was trying to kill you.
But, why are you taking care of me?
I don't know how you've lived,
but the people I know call this affection.
No matter how much I hate you. Feeding and caring for someone.
Also, you said I'm your personal doctor. A doctor takes care of their patient. What should I do?
Okay. All done. Try moving it slowly.
Huh, it feels better? That's interesting. You're a healer, a healer.
- I'm not a healer.
- You must be a real healer.
Am I a bit like one? Then should I be considered a healer?
You are a healer.
No matter where she goes I'm sure your sister will survive.
Is that why I like her?
I told you I liked her.
I think your game is going on for too long.
I've never toyed with her.
I envy you.
And I also feel bad.
That you have a sister like her, I'm jealous.
And, out of all people, that it has to be your sister, I feel bad.
Why does it have to be Ah Ro?
She's my only person.
The only one in the world.
That's why I desperately need her.
Are you saying you came here because of her?
I told you I was desperate.
Fine. But,
she is everything to me.
Not because I want or need her.
She is the reason I'm still alive and breathing.
I think we will have to sleep together tonight.
We'll arrive there by tomorrow anyway,
so please endure it a little bit even if you're uncomfortable.
Excuse me. I keep wondering about this...
Why, out of all people, did you bring me all the way here?
You're not looking for answers.
Should I just say you have to confirm something?
Did you use me
because you wanted to bring my brother?
Whether I want to bring or use someone,
why do I need to tell you?
Your Highness,
what do you remember about your brother?
By any chance,
if you think Seon Woo is your brother,
you are mistaken.
My brother is not your brother.
Those things don't matter.
I did use you as bait to bring Seon Woo into this delegation.
He's someone I want to keep close by.
Are you born with those things?
When I think about it, you have the talent to lead people.
And you're saying that you don't?
What do you think?
Am I able to lead people?
If you were the King,
how would you change Silla?
The people can't endure starvation so they're becoming robbers.
What should the King do?
While saying you're not the King,
why are you concerned about that?
I know, right?
What are you doing here?
Are you playing at Kang Tae Gong again?
(Kang Tae Gong was a famous scholar in China who loved fishing.)
There's nothing better than fishing to pass time.
Strangely enough, whatever I do today progresses slowly.
Aigoo.
They say that an empty seat makes its mark compared to an occupied one.
It's strangely empty and it makes me uneasy.
That's why I
brought scorched rice.
I gave up my cook's pride. Ba Ba Bak Bak. I pressed it down a lot.
This scorched rice is slightly burnt, so let's just feed it to the fish.
There we go.
Aish. Hey, where are you going?
I'm going to have a drink.
I noticed that you always leave me out and go alone.
You didn't even put your fishing pole away!
Geez.
The book on military strategy says that the best tactic
is not going to war.
When is Seon Woo coming?
I wonder.
Well, he'll probably come back after preventing the war.
Where is he?
- Do you like Dog-Bird that much?
- Yeah.
Then, what about me?
- I don't like you.
- Sheesh!
"Sheesh"?
I'll see you later.
Are you...crying?
What do you mean? Who's crying?
I don't know what happened, but
this isn't a place a 22-year-old should shed tears.
Or think of me as a hyung and vent to me.
Ow, gosh darn it.
Two Nangdoos gathered to cry at a place where there are no Hwarang...
Well, there's nothing bad about crying in advance.
What are you talking about?
Do you guys really think the Hwarang can come back?
Gosh, again!
Tell me properly before I kill you.
No matter if they are our masters. Whether one or two Hwarang die or not,
- it doesn't matter to you anyway!
- What do you mean die? Tell me properly!
Do you think Yeong Sil Gong is going to keep that delegation alive?
Their lives are over. They will never come back!
Hey!
I think he has some difficulty catching up with the others.
Useless bastard.
Han Seong isn't your younger brother, he's the master you must serve. How many times have I told you?
However, you make him into an idiot who can't do anything?
He's the only descendant of the Seok family.
Train Han Seong until your bones break.
Make him into the best Hwarang. Do you understand?
Yes.
I hit Dan Se instead of you.
Come to your senses.
Yes, Grandfather.
Grandfather has also grown old.
He's weaker than in the past.
Hyung...
- Move it.
- Yes.
The items are here.
All of the items here are going to be sent to the Crown Prince of South Buyeo.
Take them to him
so that they arrive before the King's birthday.
Yes.
I wonder if Ban Ryu will be okay...
Since I requested it of him, he'll probably succeed.
So, you've captured another Silla citizen who crossed the border?
Yes, Your Highness. (South Buyeo's Crown Prince Chang)
Haven't we run out of jails to put them in?
Therefore, I made a temporary jail and incarcerated them there.
At this point, isn't it better to go to war?
What about persuading His Majesty?
I have confidence that we will win.
The delegation from Shilla that was sent to make peace will arrive shortly.
Farming and hunting on someone else's territory. What is this "making peace"?
Crown Prince, the delegation from Silla arrived.
Silla Princess, Sook Myeong is my name.
I came to smooth over the misunderstanding with South Buyeo.
What is this? Are they blatantly ignoring us?
This isn't right.
Hold it in.
Until you're done eating, I'll wait for you.
If that's what you want.
Okay. What did you come with?
In order to make peace, did you bring a gift that will convince me,
or did you not?
I came as a representative of Silla.
I am asking for a private meeting with you.
Is this all?
It's a memento on behalf of making peace. It's not a tribute.
Do you wish Buddha's mercy from me?
South Buyeo and Shilla have forged an alliance for a long time.
Breaking that alliance means that we are volunteering to become subject states to Goguryeo.
How old are you?
Don't you know how countries solidify peace?
Marriage.
Don't misunderstand me. It's not that as a man I desire you.
That's the conventional means of cementing an alliance.
However, I already have many wives.
Did you also come from Silla?
Way over there.
Did you come from Silla?
How hungry you must have been that you came all the way over here.
No. I can't accept this.
But where did you get this from?
I don't think this is a trivial item.
Then I'll put it in my hair for a moment and return it to you.
- Hey!
- Why are you doing this? Wait!
Why are you doing this?
He is a thief and he tried to sell stolen items and came all the way over here.
He's just a child who can't speak. He's not someone who can steal!
What is this? Look at this.
So you're teamed with him. Aren't you?
No, I'm not. I came from Silla...
I'm not. I'm an envoy from Silla! Why are you doing this?
Please let go!
I'm not a thief! Orabeoni!
I'm not a thief! Orabeoni! Orabeoni!
What?
Didn't you hear sounds?
Sounds?
Please let go. I said please let go!
I'm not a thief. I am an envoy from Silla who escorted the Princess!
Look here! Look here!
Orabeoni...
Since you're so flustered,
I'm even more flustered.
Are you just naive, or are you a fool?
If they sent a prince, I would have thought you were going to war,
but they sent a princess.
What does it mean?
If you don't like the gift, I will prepare another one.
However, please discard the desire to go to war with Silla.
Gift?
There must have been silk and gold.
But you must have gotten robbed.
We captured Silla thieves who were selling those items on South Buyeo's land.
The Princess is working hard to prevent a war, but
the subjects are stealing peace offerings from you. It appears the Silla subjects don't even have a sense of honor.
Forget the gift because I have it in my hand already.
Instead of making peace with South Buyeo, what I told you about
is making peace. But
it could turn into a war.
After two days,
on the King's birthday
I am intending to give the gift of the expansion of South Buyeo's territory.
If you need time, I'll give you as much as you need.
We're in big trouble! Doctor Ah Ro got dragged away by soldiers!
Stop right there!
You can't use swords.
We can't? Why not?
If you take your swords out, it will start a war.
What crazy bastard would go for a war with so few people?
If you wield a sword, the peace-making is over.
Catch them!
What is the matter?
I think there is a misunderstanding.
- Get them!
- Yes!
Don't cause more conflicts.
The Hwarang started a conflict?
It seems that the doctor who accompanied them is temporarily in jail due to a misunderstanding by our troops.
That's strange. All the Hwarang started this because of that one doctor?
What shall we do?
Take them and lock them up!
Yes!
It's the Crown Prince's order. Quietly stay here.
Aish.
All of them are ill.
I didn't bring much medicine with me.
Excuse me...
I'm a doctor. Come over here. I can take a look at that for you.
Are...are you scared that it will be painful?
This can hurt a little bit, but the effects are amazing!
Because it's medicine made by my father who is the most skilled doctor in the three kingdoms of Korea.
Have you been well?
Is that the item I mentioned last time?
Yes.
It's a small token sent to Crown Prince Chang from my master, Park Yeong Sil.
Open it.
This time, I have something to tell His Majesty directly.
Your Highness, Hwi Gyeong Gong is...Hwi Gyeong Gong is...
You really look as if you've seen a ghost.
Are you not going to tell your brother to sit down when his legs are uncomfortable?
Sit down.
Why are you here?
After chasing your son outside of the palace and taking the throne,
even though you send the Princess into a deadly situation, you seem very comfortable.
It figures.
You framed your one and only companion and violently got rid of him.
What is it that you want to say?
I heard that you hid the King in Hwarang.
That Ahn Ji Gong's son Seon Woo is Jin Heung.
If Seon Woo comes back alive from South Buyeo,
you should abdicate. I will help you.
You appear after 10 years, and you're telling me to make Ahn Ji Gong's son the King?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Hwa Joong Jae Wang (There is a King among Hwarang). Was I mistaken?
They say Silla has many kings. It must be true.
Okay. What is it that you want?
He said that he will tell you by contacting you separately.
Contacting me separately?
Yes.
How dare you look at his face?
If it wasn't for the gold you brought,
I would have pulled out your eyeballs with my hands.
Aigoo. I apologize.
- Get out.
- Yes.
Yeong Sil Gong asked me to secretly relay this to you.
I almost got my eyeballs pulled out.
But I still saw the face of South Buyeo's Crown Prince.
Let's go.
"The faceless King is there."
"Therefore, do as you wish".
He wants me to kill him?
Does he want me
to kill the King?
Rather than the Princess,
it would be better to go against the King.
I apologize.
They locked up Doctor Ah Ro and we couldn't stand idly by.
What does it matter if that half-blood doctor gets locked up or dies?
For the sake of Silla's people,
do you know the loneliness and unfair treatment I'm going through?
But Hwarang are who are supposed to help me when I need them the most.
Just look at you!
If you think that it's unfair, wouldn't fighting solve matters?
Especially if that fight is on behalf of the people,
it seems like we wouldn't have to face this kind of incident ever again.
Injustice is not to be tolerated but corrected.
You said you came on behalf of Silla.
Then don't be afraid, don't blame anyone,
and say it yourself!
Princess!
General.
Even if Silla's citizens crossed South Buyeo's land and built farms,
beheading and killing them is cruel treatment!
They are not soldiers holding swords, but only farmers!
Don't you think seizing someone's land without a war
is crueler treatment?
Although it's wrong of my people to have crossed the border,
what kind of father would watch and leave his child to die of starvation!
This isn't something to have a war over. It's a matter to be solved through diplomacy!
Since you came to make peace, then...
how about solving it through marriage?
I am already betrothed.
They said that those of the sacred bone marry each other.
Are you speaking of that faceless king?
According to what I heard today,
one of the Hwarang is that King.
If I kill all of them, your betrothed will also cease to exist.
Isn't that so?
Princess!
I will say it again. There will be no marriage.
Also, you killing Silla's King will also not happen.
Bind them and drag them out.
Aigoo, Oh my!
I heard that Silla's King is here.
Therefore, whoever he is, I will have him reveal his identity,
and make him take responsibility for this matter.
If there's a king amongst you, reveal your kinghood.
If not, every fifteen minutes,
I will chop off a head to send to Silla.
- Aunt, give us two bowls of rice soup.
- Yes.
I've never asked for a drinking buddy.
Hwi Gyeong Gong.
I heard that in Seonmoon, a poster saying "Hwa Joong Jae Wang"(There is a king among Hwarang) was posted.
Is there really a king in there?
How would I know a faceless king?
Father thought I would die early. A prince who inherited the perfect blood of the sacred bone
being born in this state.
It was something that shouldn't have happened.
Father took me, wrapped in swaddling clothes, and
left me in a cold, empty room to die.
However, as three days, four days passed, I didn't die.
And I'm hiding somewhere in the capital
like this and living like a ghost.
Do you think Jin Heung is the answer?
If there is someone more suitable, wouldn't it be nice if the king changed?
Surpassing the bone rank system, a new and better king who can uphold Silla.
If there is a prince like that,
even if it's not necessarily Jin Heung, wouldn't it be alright?
Couldn't the faceless king be that kind of king?
The reason I'm against a regency is because the mother doesn't trust her son.
Taking possession of the bone rank system's throne would be against reason.
However, there will never be an incident that will treat the royal family unfairly
or throw Silla into chaos.
Father! No, Father!
No! Please save us!
When fifteen minutes pass, I will behead them.
So before then, Silla's King should affirm his own kinghood.
What a pity, fifteen minutes hasn't passed yet.
Was it a bit too soon?
Now, you've wasted half of fifteen minutes.
I am..
the King.
I am
Silla's King!