Let me take a look.
Episode 16
I'm sorry.
For avoiding you.
I know you did that
to protect me.
I thought I was going to die
holding back my desire to run to you.
♫ One step at time as the distance increases ♫
I'm not really sure what to say
in this kind of situation.
♫  How much I held onto you with my heart  ♫
♫  Will it have to hurt to forget?  ♫
I love you.
♫  Don't worry about me anymore  ♫
♬ Only you can let go of this hand ♬
♬ If it's the path that is best for you ♬
♬ Wherever that may be, it's alright ♬
♬ Even if I go far away ♬
♬ Don't cry too sadly ♬
I am...Silla's King!
The King!
What do you mean by asking a bachelor to take care of a child?
You were a bachelor?
A pure one! From head to toe!
A completely innocent bachelor!
I didn't know you were in that situation.
In any case, please look after her.
Hey, what's with you?
By doing this, do you think someone will take care of...
you?
Don't you think the world is really beautiful so far?
Where?
The world is drab and depressing.
I don't know why I'm living.
- Gosh, I'm so frustrated!
- What a scare you gave me.
Hey, your brother and Ban Ryu returned safely. What's wrong?
After returning from South Buyeo, Ban Ryu hasn't sent any word.
This means he's changed his mind, right?
Tell me the truth. Didn't he meet another girl in South Buyeo?
Hey, we didn't have that kind of time to spare.
Then why is he acting like this towards me?
By all means, a relationship between a man and a woman
has its good times and bad.
Sometimes the sun shines, sometimes it rains.
That's what it's about.
Trust this unni and wait a little while. Everything will be okay.
Really?
Are you not listening to Yeong Sil Gong?
- Or are you unable to hear him?
- Get lost.
This has never happened to me before, but right now, I feel sorry for you.
What are you talking about?
Take a look. I'm also curious.
No Yi Moo Gong.
Although you worked hard, it was all in vain.
Doesn't it seem like your father has abandoned you?
Shut up.
You're finished. Yeong Sil Gong no longer has
any expectation from you now.
l told you to shut up!
Our Ban Ryu, this is the first time seeing such a facial expression.
You're totally scared.
Doctor Ah Ro!
How are you feeling?
Thanks to you.
Come in, I'll take a look at your wound.
Are weeds raw vegetables?
That tactless rascal!
This.
It's the arrow that was stuck in your shoulder.
Wow, that one really hurt.
I heard you got hit in place of my brother.
Well, I only did what I had to.
Even though you're his friend, I'd rather you had not.
Thank you.
I didn't know the arrow... would hurt...that much.
By the way, have we really never dated before?
No, we haven't.
That's strange. I thought I had dated all of Soo Yeon's friends.
Well, even though you're not my type,
you wouldn't make a bad date.
I'm here.
You came... (switching to formal language)
How are you feeling?
I'm...alright. (formal speech)
What's wrong with your speech?
Me?  (Back to informal)
What?
Here, let me have a look.
Does it somehow feel more painful than before?
The doctor is doing a good job. Why are you being a crybaby?
My stamina must have weakened.
Should I exercise more?
♬ When the path was more than I could bear ♬
♬ You were there. Like a dream ♬
♬ then another world ♬
Thanks.
♬  which I came to know ♬
For what?
This and that.
♬ became a light in your breath ♬
♬ I'm fine with you as the only one ♬
♬ I will find the star ♬
Now I feel like we're finally back.
- Then did you think we weren't going to return?
- No.
The truth is...
I thought everything would be okay if you were safe.
There is someone who would put their life on the line for me.
I'm happy because there's someone who cherishes me this much.
Even if I died now, I wouldn't have any regrets.
So, please stay safe. I had that kind of thought.
If you die, then so do I.
If you're not okay, then I'm not okay either.
No matter what situation arises, I will always put you first.
So if you really want to help me,
think about yourself first.
Promise me.
You're a good girl. You are.
But you don't seem like such a kind brother.
You're right. I'm not kind.
What are you doing, kid?
Those two aren't siblings anymore, right?
What are you talking about?
Since when have you been so kind?
He's like that because he learned how to treat a sister from Soo Ho.
But they're not siblings.
Wait, if Seon Woo is the King,
they're not siblings.
Is that how it works?
Then what are those two?
What should we do?
Wait! Wait! There's something in your eye...
Ahn Ji Gong's son revealed himself as the King.
He risked his life and fought.
He rescued the citizens and returned, right?
What do you think of that Hwarang?
It's not important what I think about him.
I'm going to decide whether it's important or not.
He is righteous and has no fear.
He seems to have great leadership.
By chance, are you keeping him close to your heart?
Of course not.
You take after me too much.
That makes me nervous.
Before the Hwarang, there were the Won Hwa, two appointed heads of a society of maidens chosen for beauty and filial piety.
The Hwarang has become too strong.
The citizens praise the Hwarang and follow them.
So I can no longer hold the Hwarang in my hands.
So,
I'm planning to make you a Won Hwa.
Do you know what kind of fate the Won Hwa
faced?
Both Won Hwa faced death.
You aren't afraid?
Since I'm very much like you, Mother.
The subject you are learning about today is the Book of Odes.
The Book of Odes is the songs of the people which have been passed down by word of mouth from a long time ago.
Inside are the lamentations of the people's difficult lives
yet positive images.
In addition, there is also resentment and pity for the powerless King.
Today, I'm going to show you a poem.
The title is 'Large Rat.'
Who would like to read it?
Ji Dwi, try reading it.
"Rat, rat, large rat. Don't eat my barley."
"I took care of you for a long time, you aren't looking after me."
"Surely, I will leave you"
"and leave to go to that happy nation."
"Happy place, happy place."
"I will find a way to justify myself there."
Here, the rat symbolizes the ruler.
In this poem, the King doesn't take care of his people. He's hiding and eating the grain.
Just like someone.
If a big rat eats the people's livelihood, all those people will leave.
A king without his people is no longer a king.
- Do you understand the meaning of this poem?
- Yes!
What brings you, the chief guard, here?
The Queen Dowager wishes to recognize the distinguished service of the delegation that went to South Buyeo.
Only the delegation?
Yes, that's right.
Then what about me?
I was the one who sent, organized, and returned with the Hwarang.
Does she not know that?
If she doesn't, then I can't do anything about it.
I got it, so you can leave.
There is no one who can withstand an epidemic.
In a situation where they're already starving, we can't even obtain medicine.
You should go back.
If you stay here without medicine, you'll also get infected.
Earlier, you told me that there is a way to get medicine.
Where is it?
Even if you are going to get the medicine,
I don't know if you will be able to bring it here.
What do you mean by that?
A Cheonin (lowest class in Silla) from the village must not climb over the castle gate.
Do you know why that law exists?
That's because they want to maintain the bone rank system and prevent Cheonin from entering the capital.
You're so naive.
This is Silla's source for gold.
The gold that is stacked up in the royal family and Park Yeong Sil's storage
all comes from here.
People work all day with their backs bent over looking for gold sediment.
If they want it in its entirety, the Cheonin must not know
the tremendous worth of that gold.
Then,
in order to get gold, they're keeping this place isolated on purpose?
It isn't gold, but power.
In another word, it's also the military.
In the future, it's Silla's supremacy.
Just go back. Nothing will be solved by staying here.
Or,
by whatever means,
you can obtain the medicine.
I mean, why must I also go?
Seon Woo, please enter the palace.
Before the Hwarang, there were two Won Hwa. (Groups of youth who maintained manners and order in society while training in the martial arts)
Nam Mo and Joon Jeong. The two Won Hwa led the Nangdoo.
I heard that your sister comforted the citizens well in South Buyeo.
So,
I'm planning to keep your sister beside me as a Won Hwa.
Am I not enough?
I'm taking advantage of her because I want to use you properly,
because she has the power to move you.
If you declared yourself to be King, continue acting like one.
That's what being a monarch is about. You must fool the world, the citizens,
and yourself.
If it means protecting Silla's prince, I am capable of doing anything.
As long as my son can ascend the throne, I'm not afraid of anything.
I am prepared to fool you, my son,
and also the entire world.
So, you do the same
if you don't want to lose your sister.
Why isn't he coming? Did something happen?
Since you saw him after a long time, I'm sure you have lots of things to say.
I told you it isn't that kind of atmosphere.
What's with you having that expression all day? Is something wrong?
- Mind your own business.
- You're being abrasive again.
But where is Ji...
Ji...Ji Dwi. Where did he go?
It's been quite a while for someone to use the outhouse.
How did you come to this place?
This place isn't even well known by the court ladies.
I lost my way.
This is not a place you can get lost in.
Unless you searched for it on purpose.
How would I know the capital?
Seeing that I have difficulty finding the palace outhouse, I just ended up here.
- Then, if you'll excuse me.
- Orabeoni!
You're His Majesty, aren't you?
You're mistaken, Princess.
Stop!
Why didn't I recognize you?
How long have you lived like this?
The amount of time is something you can't imagine.
Does it make sense that we came all the way over here and can't even see Her Majesty, the Queen Dowager?
It's Her Majesty, the Queen Dowager.
Are you safe?
Are you hurt anywhere?
I'm safe, for now.
The more you disobey my commands,
don't you know that things will only become more difficult for you?
I think she saw me. I should go and greet her.
That I, Kim Soo Ho, came back alive from South Buyeo.
Why don't we just go.
Your Highness.
You dropped this.
Hwarang Kim Soo Ho, upholds Your Highness' command.
I came back safely from South Buyeo.
Please take good care of Seon Woo, Soo Ho.
Everyone knows you as the King. I will use you as bait.
You will face the danger that my son has to face.
So endure it. If you can survive, do so.
I also hope that you will endure it.
That way, I and my son will be able to buy some time.
Exactly what did he talk about with Her Highness, the Queen Dowager?
Is it because he said he was the King?
Where on earth is he?
No Yi Moo Gong.
Although you worked hard, it was all in vain.
Why didn't I recognize you?
How long have you lived like this?
The next time we meet again, at that time,
let's end the hunt. Jin Heung.
What are you thinking about?
It's nothing.
"Now this Seonmoon won't be the same as before." Well, something to that effect.
What do you mean?
I better go do some fishing because I have things to think about. Here.
Ban Ryu.
It's me, Soo Yeon.
♬ went out and searched for the small dream♬
I waited for a long time after hearing that you returned safely.
I mean, I'm not saying that I resented you, but I thought that at least I should come.
From now on, don't like a guy like me.
♫  Like a dream then another world which I came to know ♬
Ban Ryu...
I'm not going to see you again.
Ban Ryu!
♬ and even a shard of my crushed heart ♬
♬ became a light ♬
Ban Ryu!
♫  in your breath  ♫
Who's doing what?
What are you doing?
I did wrong.
Is this the answer to "No Yi Moo Gong"?
Please don't abandon me.
Once more... Please give me one more chance, Father.
I thought of you as a king, but now I've changed my mind.
I'll have to become king. I can't trust others.
Then, I will help you.
Are you saying that you will help me become king?
Yes. I will do that.
Even if I have to grind my bones, I will definitely help.
Are you sure that you will definitely help?
Am I saying I'm the King? The King.
Sheesh. Wine tastes the best before it cools. I guess you don't know how to enjoy it yet.
I don't think I ever told you to sit.
There's no better friend than a drinking buddy.
It turns out that I'm alone, and I want to drink with a young fellow like you. Can't I do that?
Please get lost.
From what I heard, you are the King. You beat Baekje's Crown Prince Chang to a pulp.
Is that true?
The citizens are joyful because the King showed up among the Hwarang. They're saying the world will change.
However, if you don't turn out to be the real king,
the disappointment will also be great.
If you have the power to change the world,
don't you have any thoughts of becoming the real king?
I could make you into one.
There's a long way to go until the sun will rise.
It seems what I'm trying to catch is on the hook.
That kind of king cannot become king.
What about the people? What will happen to the people that are here?
They will pay for their sins with their death.
What nonsense is that?!
I am..the King!
I am...Silla's King!
Who is this?
Isn't he a rat?
I'm talking about the large rat who couldn't open his mouth
to say "I'm the King!" in front of the enemy's crown prince.
That's right.
I have no qualification to be a king. I'm scared that I will get caught or someone will recognize me.
It's bad enough that I've been trembling in fear and living in hiding all my life.
Even when the enemy nation's crown prince asked who the King is,
I couldn't come forward.
I'm only a coward. I'm always hiding, and ready to hide my face.
That kind of coward.
I don't know if my words will help,
but there are many cowardly kings in the world.
But there aren't many kings who would call themselves a coward.
Because calling yourself a coward is another act of bravery.
Could a person like that really become a king?
Your Majesty, you must deal with it.
Whatever it is,
whether it's a high place, a low place, a dirty place, a beautiful place, a dangerous place, or a dark place.
if there is something you must do as a KingI
I'm telling you that you should take charge of it all.
This is my answer.
♫ You were so far away ♫
♫ Without being able to see you I ♫
♫ I have never once dreamed ♫
♫ You would be the person in front of me ♫
♫ Don't get hurt ♫
♫ Don't come any closer ♫
♫ My frozen heart ♫
If you have the power to change the world, if that is the right thing to do,
is there any reason to hesitate?
Are you going to go over the castle wall and lose another friend?
♫ In my two red eyes I boxed you up ♫
♫ I want to go back again to turn back the clock ♫
♫  to when it was beautiful ♫
Ahn Ji Gong, what are you doing here?
I heard there is a cornering and hoarding of the plague medicine.
Who said nonsense like that? Do you think that's true?
Please donate the white peony, the star anise, fennel, ginseng and the rest of the medicinal herbs.
Even if I have that kind of medicine,
do you think I could give it to you for free?
I'm not here as a merchant.
After practicing medicine all of my life, as a doctor who has never received payment,
I am sitting in front of you, the Gakgan, who has the duty to take care of the Silla people.
If we can't stop the plague from spreading in the Cheonin village, the capital will not be safe.
Wait a little longer.
It seems that the people's fear isn't great enough to spend their entire fortune to buy medicine yet.
Once the plague spreads a bit more,
then I will distribute some of the medicine.
In order to raise the price of the medicine,
are you saying now that you will allow the plague to spread?
Just wait three more days,
and if there isn't an increase, then wait for seven more days.
And if there still isn't much happening, then ten days.
People don't die that easily.
Is the man who just left the one who fooled everyone into thinking his son is Sam Maek Jong and made him into a Hwarang?
The people's unrest is extraordinary.
At this rate, we might be left helplessly watching Jin Heung ascend the throne.
It figures that you must be anxious.
How many of the true bone are left in the Seok family?
Would there be a true bone who would propose marriage to a family that is diminishing day by day?
Just keep your promise.
If things work out well, you must adopt our family
through marriage.
As long as things work out, what would be difficult?
Nine hundred ninety one. If you do nine more, it will be 1000.
What kind of nonsense is this?
It's unfair. You have great swordsmanship
and I don't even like this kind of stuff!
What does fair mean to you?
It's 1000 times. If you can't win one match, then I'm going to leave the household for good.
Ah, what... What do you want me to do?
Don't whine. You promised as a man.
Later on, don't say otherwise.
Do it again.
Why do you think Ji So wants to see me?
Perhaps she wants to make a fuss over the bribe you gave to Crown Prince Chang?
What do you mean by bribe?
The friendship between South Buyeo's royal family and the Park family extends over 100 years.
Between friends, how could a bribe be possible?
I apologize.
What did you just say?
I said I will step down from my regency.
Abdicating at this time, why all of a sudden?
You always told me to step down from the regency. You don't seem to be welcoming it.
What is she planning this time?
You must have heard that Jin Heung beat South Buyeo's Crown Prince Chang.
He returned after achieving such a meritorious deed.
There is no reason for me to stay in this position any longer.
It's finished, Gakgan. I won and you lost.
The young King slowly got stronger without his mother and returned.
Didn't you also see His Majesty's bravery?
The royal family will become stronger now.
I'm saying that there is nothing else for you to do.
If Sam Maek Jong ascends the throne now, all of your plans will vanish into thin air.
Who knew Ji So would make that move?
Even though you abdicate, it will be too difficult for His Majesty Jin Heung
to manage political affairs immediately.
Abdication?
There will be no such thing as an abdication.
This time, we must make Park Yeong Sil believe Seon Woo is Sam Maek Jong.
- That way, no one will suspect Sam Maek Jong again.
- Then...?
Sam Maek Jong is only a child. If he ascends the throne now, what can he do?
However, will Ahn Ji Gong's son just stand idly by?
Don't you know full well what type of person he is?
No.
He will not be able to refuse.
If I tell him not to make any noise breathing, he will not.
Because I'm in control of his lifeline.
Are you feeling alright?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I just have body aches from overworking myself for a few days.
By the way, if you can't obtain the medicine,
then what will happen to the people there?
I will have to get it, no matter what.
It's a relief that you came back safely.
I was very worried.
Father.
I am worried about Orabeoni.
After saying that he's the King in order to save me,
there's a misunderstanding that he's His Majesty, King Jin Heung.
It seems that through that incident, he incurred the wrath of the Queen Dowager.
He didn't come home during his day off. I'm really worried.
What are you doing here?
Then what about you?
Because I have nowhere to go.
Me too.
I'm more handsome than you thought, right?
For a King.
Everyone is saying that you're the King,
but I figured that you're the only one who still thinks I'm the King.
Did you live like this all your life?
That King. Worrying if someone will harm him,
or if the people around him will get hurt. So anxious that he can't fall asleep.
I feel that way.
That must not be all.
If it's not all, then what?
How can he turn the world upside down?
Can only the King live comfortably?
Would he think those things as well?
There's no way a king who was never treated like one would think that way.
That King
knows how the subjects feel?
It's not that he knows the subjects...
He must have lived like one.
I heard that the King who is like a subject kills anyone who sees his face.
That's right.
He probably does.
Whether they found out later,
there must have been times when people didn't know and passed by him.
But overall, he probably didn't know people died because of him.
He's stupid,
foolish,
and he doesn't have the strength...to tell them to stop the killings.
Then what can the King do?
Can he change the world?
Why does he still have to be alive?
I said why does he have to stay alive?!
Do you want to kill him?
Then kill him.
Didn't you miss me? I missed you a lot.
My apologies. I thought you were my brother.
What brings you here?
I have something I must ask you.
Because I really like you,
if we build a farm together, have a baby,
and want to live as ordinary citizens,
would you want to live with me?
I can't do anything for you. I have no treasures or silver coins that you like.
There is a chance that we will not have a proper house. However,
I'm telling you that I would exchange Silla's throne
for you.
Will you go with me? No, let's go.
It's okay if that guy is not your brother. Even if you liked him, that's fine. However.
Now, come to me.
Because I'll live not as anyone's king, but as your Jin Heung.
♬ Like the brilliant day ♬
♬ like when the moonlight lit the space between you and me♬
Are you using me as an excuse to run away?
♬ So that all our moments won't disappear♬
Your Majesty lived while asking yourself over and over
why you have to be the King.
It's because you knew very well why you have to be King, and what you need to do as King,
that you have overcame hardships, tiredness, and fear.
What do you know?
If you look into the eyes of someone
who has given up, then you know.
Your Majesty has never given up.
♬ somehow I keep being afraid ♬
♬ I'm afraid my place will be empty, ♬
♬ when standing in front of you ♬
♬ Even if my eyes are closed and ♬
♬  if I bring and am filled with you ♬
♬ Because I really can't leave ♬
Your Majesty, you have lived too long.
Towards the pond.
If you make a noise, your head will go flying off.
- Who are you?
- Me?
The real owner of the bracelet. The person you've been looking for.
The faceless King.
I thought the King was Ahn Ji Gong's son.
No. It's me.
I'm your Lord, Jin Heung.
By chance, are you here to kill the King?
Attack!
Are you okay?
This is Seonmoon where Silla's Hwarang are staying.
How dare you step foot in here so fearlessly?
Poong Wol Joo! Poong Wol Joo! Poong Wol Joo!
Aigo, what?!
There's big trouble!
Ah, what is it, Bu Jae?
There's no need for this. The one they want is me!
What are you talking about? If they entered this place, they came to attack us!
Dog-Bird!
Protect Seon Woo.
♫ A slight sprinkle is falling. Black tears cover me  ♫
♫ In my two red eyes, I boxed you up  ♫
♫ I want to go back again  ♫