What gives you the right to take her?
Because you're a policeman?
-Do you have a warrant?
-She's my friend.
I won't let her spend
the night with a stranger.
-Then you can stay with us.
-No!
You can't stay here. Let's go home.
-Stay!
-Come on...
-Let's go, Bongsoon.
-Okay.
Secretary Do!
Business is business.
You're the one who's mixing things.
According to the Labor Standard Act
Chapter 4 Article 50,
maximum working hours
is 40 weekly or 209 monthly.
Meaning she shouldn't work more than
eight hours a day till late night.
What business can she have late at night,
at the owner's house?
Can you give me a convincing reason?
A reason? There's no reason.
According to the Labor Standard Act
Article 100, you may be sentenced up to,
two years imprisonment
or fined up to 10 million won.
Arrest me, then.
Gukdoo.
It's confidential...
...and I can't tell you...
...but there's something I have to do.
What is it?
Well, it's confidential...
That makes me even more curious.
What is it?
-She told you she can't tell.
-Do Bongsoon.
You were like this at school
and you haven't changed at work.
You slept all day long during exams
and studied at the library at night.
How can I comply with
the Labor Standard Act...
...when I'm working with
someone like that?
Did you call your mom?
No, I was about to call her.
I'll talk to her mother.
If she doesn't approve...
...I will take her no matter
how urgent this matter may be.
Help yourself.
-Hello?
-Hello, this is Gukdoo.
Hi, Gukdoo. What's going on?
I'm at Bongsoon's boss's house.
She's going to spend the night here,
working with her boss.
I thought we would need your permission.
So she's going to sleep there
with her boss?
I mean stay up all night with him, right?
-Yes, ma'am.
-I see.
She must be overly motivated
with her new job.
That's good.
Anyway. Forget about her.
What are you doing there?
Work only as much as you're paid.
Go home now.
Aren't you busy?
You have cases to solve
but you have time for Bongsoon's roman...
I mean, to worry about her work?
-Put her on the phone.
-Okay.
-Hello, mom.
-You.
Good luck with that.
Good luck with what?
I shouldn't say this to my own daughter,
but no matter what you do there...
...regardless of what you have in mind,
it's all your own destiny.
Don't spare yourself.
Mom!
Tell Gukdoo to go home.
Why did he go there in the first place?
It's not his turf.
Mom.
Okay. Don't worry.
Gosh, I'm just working.
Yes, mom. Don't worry. Goodnight.
Was that Bongsoon?
She'll stay the whole night with her boss.
Why are you so happy?
I can't hide my feelings.
Do you want more noodles, Bonggi?
No, I'm fine.
Why is she staying with her boss?
-Tell her to come right away!
-You're so unprofessional.
She could have ended up unemployed.
But she found the motivation
to work all night.
You'll be standing in her way
if you ask her to come home.
Why does she have to work all night?
She's a bodyguard.
You know, in life,
history is always made at night.
-Oh, it's so tasty.
-It really is good.
I want more noodles.
You had enough. You'll poo too much.
Just a little.
-It's good.
-Jeez.
What exactly does she do?
Another reason I don't like the police.
They always interrogate.
This is ridiculous.
I think our encounter
deserves an introduction.
-We met at the police station.
-I know.
We met before. Don't be so defensive.
You're a policeman.
You can check my background.
You checked it
when I was there as a witness.
There have been recurrent incidents
in my jurisdiction.
Bongsoon heard the offender's voice.
And he saw her face.
The officer that was
protecting her was attacked.
-And in broad daylight.
-I know that already.
In such circumstances,
I can't let her stay with someone
that was in the crime scene.
Gukdoo, that case and the officer
being attacked aren't connected.
That man is bearing Mr. An a grudge.
Are you the police?
Did you investigate it?
No, but...
They aren't connected.
That's for sure.
Then you shouldn't be here.
Will you come with me?
-Why?
-To interrogate you as a witness.
Have some manners.
Is this how you exercise
your official duties?
What comes around goes around.
That officer leaves the hospital tomorrow.
I'll testify once he does.
Then please come tomorrow to testify.
Okay.
-Bongsoon, let's get some sleep.
-What?
To comply with the Labor Standard Act.
Let's abide by the law.
Though we live in a country,
where the police can break in
at night without a warrant.
So, we, at least...
...should abide by the law.
I'm going to bed.
The bathroom's over there.
Wash up before you go to bed.
You can stay here, too.
Why would you have a female bodyguard?
He actually likes men,
so to prevent any scandals...
He's a freak.
-Bongsoon.
-Yes?
I don't understand you.
I'm his secretary, you see.
And I have some reasons.
Why does a secretary stay up all night
with her boss outside of working hours?
Don't worry, Gukdoo. I'm not so naive.
Let's go. Come on.
Okay, okay.
I'm leaving.
-Okay.
-Give me your hand.
My hand?
Wear this.
It's a wearable alert device.
Do you see this button?
Press it and the nearest patrol
will come within five minutes.
-Okay?
-Okay.
And come to the station tomorrow with him.
Okay.
Press it if he does anything to you, okay?
-Okay.
-All men are dogs!
Don't insult dogs like that.
I'm off.
He's gone!
Where is he?
Wow!
Wow, what's all this?
Wow...
Where are you?
I don't feel like playing hide and seek.
Gosh...
Are you not here?
What's this?
What is that painting doing there?
Oh, it opens.
Wow!
Wow, what's this?
Is this a secret passage?
Wow, it's going down!
Wow!
Whoa... Wait a second.
What's this?
Whoa...
What kind of place is this?
An underground dungeon.
It's where my game characters
come to life.
Welcome to my playground.
The things you can do when you're rich.
What did you say?
Did you criticize me?
No. Why would I?
Feeling so victimized.
Name, Jung Juntae.
Address, Seoul Seongdong-gu,
Seongsu-dong 1-Ga 164,
Chowon Apartment 103.
The info of the owner of that bike.
-Let's go there now!
-Tonight, let's just...
Let's protect each other
as promised and stay here.
That's what we promised.
Let's go in the morning.
Okay. If that's what you want.
Your friend was very worried about you.
When he's not going to date you anyway.
Did that jerk, I mean that cop
give you that necklace?
No, my dad got it for me
for my graduation.
Stop asking about my private life.
Okay.
-Let's sleep.
-What?
I meant just sleeping in the same room.
-I told you to not get ideas.
-But we can't sleep in the same room.
-That's not the life I've led.
-Are you kidding me?
Listen, I'm scared tonight!
-Come here.
-Come on.
You have a bedroom, a living room,
and a guest room and you sleep here? Why?
Have you ever received
blackmail calls as a wake-up call?
I guess not.
Your life is too simple to understand
a complicated life like mine.
You sleep on the couch.
I'll sleep here in my sleeping bag.
-What are you doing?
-I'm going to sleep.
This is so annoying.
Sleeping on the couch.
It's an expensive couch.
Good night.
Wow!
A fairy tale I read
when I was a kid said...
...people become stars when they die.
And I believed in that.
In the fairy tales I read,
when people die, they become ghosts.
How can people become stars?
So I can see my mom every night.
Did your mom pass away?
Before she died when I was six...
...she took me to my father.
My older brothers locked me in a wardrobe
and bullied me back then.
So my father gave them a good beating.
Then why did you make the wardrobe
the entrance to your dungeon?
Though they locked me in the wardrobe...
...I felt more comfortable in there.
Nobody was bullying me.
I could sleep better, and...
...and it's fun.
The bad guy and the police
can't find me here.
I think you dislike the police
more than the bad guy.
My father was a gangster.
He made money in his gang
and bought the police off with that money.
He even made friends with prosecutors.
He surely did a lot of bad things,
but he never went to jail.
He never met a good cop.
There are many good cops.
Why do you like cops?
Sorry. Wrong question.
What do you like about that cop?
Gukdoo?
Yes.
Well, he's...
Forget it.
When did you start having a crush on him?
I met Gukdoo for the first time
when I was in the sixth grade.
Break time's over.
He's a transfer student from Gangnam.
Gukdoo, say hello to your classmates.
Hello, I'm In Gukdoo.
I hope we get along well.
He used to be the best student
in his previous school.
There. There's a seat next to Bongsoon.
You can take that seat, Gukdoo.
Excuse me.
You're drooling.
Drooling.
What are you doing?
Get out of the way.
Let me see.
Gukdoo!
He's the only person
that makes me powerless.
In Gukdoo...
He's a bad guy.
He didn't ask for your love.
You fell in love with him. Why blame him?
Hey, wake up!
Let's do it.
What?
Die!
-What?
-Oh, yeah!
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
You're a loser.
Hey!
Hey.
I enjoyed the game.
I'm going to bed now.
The couch is mine. Don't say anything
more and go to your sleeping bag.
Just one more game.
No, thanks.
Hey...
Are you asleep?
Wow, that's quick.
What are you doing?
Why are you here?
What on earth?
Keep dreaming.
The floor was too cold.
I thought my face was going numb.
-I was so scared all night long.
-Scared of what?
Scared that you would attack me.
Make me breakfast!
One meal a day, remember?
-Make a proper breakfast.
-Gosh.
-What?
-I'm on my way.
You're crazy.
Don't be so impressed.
My mom is such a princess...
...that she made me cook everything
since I was little.
So I know how to cook.
I'm not impressed.
The dishes are all carbohydrates.
Sauteed potatoes,
sugar coated sweet potatoes...
...no whole grains. Only white rice.
Look at this rice. It's as white as milk.
So white it hurts my eyes.
But I'll take your effort
into consideration and eat.
-I'll eat it.
-You know what? Don't!
What a temper.
When you get married,
you'll make your wife's life so miser...
Well, I shouldn't worry about that. Right?
Your friend keeps coming to my mind.
Especially his butt.
He's got a nice butt.
Apple butt. Nice!
You're very raunchy.
I like guys with pretty butts.
You talk too much.
What will you do if you catch him?
I'll find out who's behind him.
I'll make him talk.
Do I have to make him talk?
You'll ask for extra pay if I ask.
Of course.
Then I'll do it.
Then all I have to do is catch him?
Yes.
Will you report it to the police
once you find out who's behind it?
No, I'll take care of it.
You're lawless.
You're the center of the universe.
That's up to me.
Then, what are you going to tell
the police when we get there?
I don't have to report private matters.
You'll end up mentioning it
when you start testifying.
I'll only tell them about that officer
getting assaulted.
Then you'll mislead their investigation
towards the Dobong-dong murder suspect.
The police will be misled.
-I'm going to keep an eye on him.
-What?
I mean your friend.
I'll see how he directs the investigation.
Gosh.
Poor Gukdoo.
He's not good with knives.
He was very clumsy.
It's clear that
he didn't want to kill her.
He used a stationary cutter.
He slit once and ran away surprised.
Did you see his face?
Yes, I remember it clearly.
It's not him.
He was much older than this guy.
This man is wearing a mask.
How do you know?
His face was very rough.
Hello. I live next door.
Did you run the washing
machine last night?
It was so noisy I couldn't sleep.
I didn't.
I don't wash my clothes.
Then why do you think it was so noisy?
Who are you?
Can I see if you have a washing machine?
-You're crazy.
-Excuse me.
Who are you?
She just breaks in.
Hey, hey.
Who are you?
Do you really live next door?
Oh, no.
Hello, sir. I'm actually Do Bongsoon
and I live in Dobong-dong, Dobong-gu.
License plate, "Cha 4458".
It's your bike, right?
Are you Jung Juntae?
-Who are you?
-You are.
-Can you come with me?
-What?
I need to talk to you about your bike.
You break in my house and
what's this rubbish you're talking about?
I should just...
Rubbish?
It'll only take a minute.
Who are you?
Coming in a single man's house...
-You're quite a daring woman.
-What the heck?
Huh?
Hey!
Mister!
Mister! Mister! Mister!
Oh, no. I'm sorry.
What do I do?
Mister?
I didn't even hit him.
He hit himself.
Please, understand.
You should pay me more.
I never intended this.
What are you doing? Start the car!
Huh?
Are we going to the dungeon?
Oh, okay...
Yes, so her belly...
Geez. Hands off.
Who is it?
They're so good.
Mr. An.
She lives there. You should come.
There.
You didn't kill him, did you?
No, he's breathing.
I don't think he's breathing.
He is. He is.
His face is swollen.
Did you beat him?
What? No.
You did. Look at his face.
I didn't beat him. He beat himself.
He hurt himself with his own hands?
Why? There must be a reason.
Well, he didn't exactly hurt himself...
Oh! He's awake now!
Hey, I need him to be conscious
to ask him questions.
-Stop hitting him.
-I didn't hit him!
Who are you?
Why are you doing this to me?
What did I do?
Mister, let me tie your hands.
-What are you doing?
-Just a minute.
Don't just stand there.
Find a chair or something.
I have to do all the work.
-My cousin is a cop.
-Oh, is he?
And a friend of my ex-girlfriend's uncle
works in the prosecutor's office.
-And...
-Mister, please hold this a minute.
And close your legs, okay?
Just a minute.
It hurts!
-Oh!
-What? What happened?
No, no, no. I didn't do anything!
He did that to himself.
What's wrong with him?
You really make things better.
Are we doing it well?
Did that sound like a compliment?
-Hey!
-But he was like...
-Hey, wake up.
-That's powerful.
I think I should go home now.
I worked too much today.
-Goodbye, then.
-What the heck? Hey!
Come here.
Who sent you?
Someone stole my bike
so I reported it to the police.
But the police didn't get back to me.
That's why I don't like the police.
-So your bike was stolen?
-Yes...
I worked the night shift for six months...
...in a restaurant to buy that bike!
Oh no.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Mister.
I'll untie this for you.
I'm sorry.
Darn it!
What will you do now?
You got the wrong man!
Do you know what happens
when I misuse my strength?
We're in trouble now!
I'm so sorry.
-Please, leave. Please.
-Okay.
Shoot!
Poor man!
He's barefooted.
Okay! Stop whining.
-What's your relationship with Kim Jiwon?
-He's Kim Jiwon's fiancé.
It's not him.
We investigated and he has a motive.
They had a big fight
the day before she got kidnapped...
...and she said she would
cancel the wedding.
Are we recording his voice?
What? Yes.
It's not him. I'm sure.
The footprints that we found
are the size of his feet.
Hey, it's not his feet. Look at his eyes.
He's worried about his fiancé.
That's why the other team said
it's not the same guy...
...that murdered Jung Hyangsook.
I think it's the same guy.
It was in the same crime scene,
but we found two different footprints.
He's playing with us!
He disguised himself as a doctor to sneak
into the victim's room in the hospital.
-He can do more than that!
-It's not him.
His motives aren't strong enough.
And Kim Jiwon...
She's alive.
Lieutenant In.
Yes.
So you're saying the kidnapping
in Dobong-dong is not connected...
...to the attack of the police officer?
-Exactly.
-Then why was the officer attacked?
The police must investigate it.
The police must provide security
and protect the citizen, right?
But the citizen has the right
to solve his own problems.
So let me solve my problems on my own.
-Look.
-I'm looking.
I will be in charge of protecting
Do Bongsoon from now on.
-As you please.
-Gukdoo, let me explain as his secretary.
As you can already tell,
he's a little craz...
I mean, he's a little peculiar.
So I think he has many enemies.
Ms. Do, you're making me
look like a psycho.
I'm not making you look like a psycho.
Anyway, so someone mistakenly thought
the officer was his bodyguard.
That's why he got attacked.
A surprise attack. Sudden attack!
Then you should have hired
a proper bodyguard.
I did. She's my body...
-What's wrong?
-Gukdoo.
I'm really fine. Don't be so worried.
I'm not worried about you.
I'm worried about the witness
of this case.
Anyway, I'm in charge of
protecting Ms. Do Bongsoon.
In case she's exposed to
dangerous situations at work...
...or in case she goes anywhere
where security is lax...
...someone must accompany her.
Your company must provide all necessary
security measures to protect her.
To protect her?
-I should be the one to be protected.
-By the way, Gukdoo.
Did you find any clues about the murderer?
-No, not yet.
-Okay, got it.
Lieutenant In!
Doctor Jo is off tonight.
We should go to the hospital.
Okay.
911.
-Oh, it hurts.
-What's wrong?
It hurts!
I think I broke my toe.
I can't feel it.
What?
I'm so sorry. Does it hurt a lot?
It not only hurts. It's embarrassing.
Should I take you to the hospital?
Whatever you touch with your hands
or feet get hurt. Get out of my way!
I'm sorry! But I never meant to hurt you!
It's not hard to know my schedule.
All they have to do is call
the outpatient department and ask.
My schedule is shared
in the database system.
It's not hard for the criminal
to disguise himself as a doctor.
It's the footage of all the CCTVs
in the operation rooms...
...and night duty rooms of that day.
Oh, thanks.
Thank you for cooperating.
Take it. Let's go.
Detective, I'll go and check on my friend.
Your friend?
Okay.
Here. You have a really fine crack.
My goodness.
It's cracked?
You'll have to wear pads for a while
and don't strain your foot.
And apply ice packs often.
Hey, Bongsoon.
Oh. He's my boss, Bonggi.
Oh! How are you?
As you can see, not very well.
-Did you stomp on him?
-Yes, just a little. Very gently.
But why?
I need to be hospitalized.
What? It's just a fine crack.
Oh, because it's not your toe, right?
It hurts like hell!
You want me to walk with a limp
and look like an idiot?
Would you like a room in the VIP ward?
No, that's boring.
Is Mr. Kong's tailbone fine now?
Hey.
It's been a while.
Sorry, Heeji.
It's this way.
Let's go on a lot of dates
once this case is solved.
Okay.
My friend is a resident in this hospital.
I made an appointment with
the orthopedist. I'll come with you.
Okay.
You want a wheelchair just
because you hurt your toe?
The toe is very important.
Then wear a patient gown.
I don't want to be a fashion terrorist.
What kind of style is that?
Mr. Kong's room is this way.
Mr. Kong, it's me.
Mr. An! What brought you here?
Huh?
You’re on a wheelchair?
I have a crack in my toe.
I can't believe it's happening.
What happened?
Bongsoon stomped on me.
Yum. Come on. Try.
You have to chew. Yum.
You have to eat to get well!
Say ah. Come on. Ah!
Ah! Ah! Wider!
Ah! There.
Now chew. Chew.
Yum.
-Yum.
-Boss!
-Hey!
-She's here!
-Who?
-Do Bongsoon!
Do Bongsoon?
Do Bongsoon is here!
-What are you doing? Call the police!
-Oh, yes. The police.
Oh no! Why is she here?!
Call the police quick.
-Boss, are you okay?
-Oh, no. Boss!
When can you sit up properly?
It's getting better.
I might lie on my side tomorrow.
Does it still hurt?
I feel the pain all over my butt
just by coughing.
Gosh, I feel bad for you.
The human body is so mysterious.
Mr. An, those thugs that Bongsoon beat
that day are in the next room.
What's more surprising is that
her twin brother is a resident here.
It feels like Bongsoon is at
the center of the universe.
The sister gives you the pain,
the brother offers the medicine.
A fantastic combination.
What's wrong with you lately?
Do you know how many people are
hospitalized here after you beat them?
Be more careful.
Why did you get so reckless?
Gosh, don't get me started.
I'm trying my best.
But lately I can't control my strength.
Geez...
I have to go.
Gukdoo's girlfriend is here.
What?
Gukdoo's girlfriend?
-It hurts!
-Oh, I'm sorry.
Hey, but where?
-Hey, Gukdoo.
-Oh, hi.
-Hello.
You have to wait 30 more minutes
to consult with the professor.
You can leave her with me if you're busy.
No, I'll wait.
Hey, what are you doing here?
What?
Mr. An Minhyuk...
Well, he hurt his toe so I came with him.
Say hello. She's my friend Bongsoon.
She's his twin sister.
Hello, I'm Jo Heeji.
I've heard a lot about you.
Oh. Hi.
I'll take you to his room.
I think we better take your x-ray
before he gets to his room.
Okay.
You come with me.
What are your symptoms?
I'm having a concert very soon, so
I've been practicing a little too much.
My wrist and fingers hurt.
I feel the pain up to my elbow
and I can't even lift anything.
-Do you play the cello?
-Yes.
It could be a problem
with your finger extensor muscle.
An inflammation in the extensor
for overusing your finger muscles.
We could give a definite diagnosis
after an x-ray and a blood test.
Which wrist is it?
-It's my left wrist.
-Let me see.
Is it here?
Or here?
Yes, there.
Oh, okay.
Make your job description clear.
Why are you so ambiguous about yes or no?
Why does a secretary have to
take care of him 24 hours a day?
You're not his nurse.
Well, right now he doesn't have
a secretary so...
Why?
I told you his secretary
hurt his tailbone.
After the one-legged fight...
What's wrong with his employees?
Bongsoon, don't trust men so easily.
Kind men are womanizers,
rude men are crooks.
That's what men are!
Anyway, I think your boss is weird.
Why are you doing this to me?
What?
You have a girlfriend.
So why are you so nice to me?
What are you talking about?
I'll take you to radiology.
Hey!
What are you doing there?
I've been looking for you everywhere.
Do you have to make me come here?
You're back?
Why do you look so sad?
As if you've met
the girlfriend of your crush.
I can tell.
Everything is so obvious about you.
My goodness!
She...
Do Bongsoon. Do Bongsoon...
Keep quiet.
Am I wrong?
Why won't you answer?
-Why won't you answer?
-No, but...
-Are you ignoring me?
-No, sir.
-Hey!
-Yes?
Where is she?
Stay still.
She's a cellist and her finger hurts.
Please take good care of her.
We'll take the x-ray. Don't move.
Choonshim! Mom didn't feed you?
Gosh!
Eat up.
Mom, where are you going?
You go around everywhere. Where to?
Did you sleep with him?
Did you?
-I did.
-Really?
Yes, I slept really well.
So you mean you only slept?
Mom! He doesn't like women.
I told you already.
I used to hate dogs until I met Choonshim.
Now I love dogs.
People change.
People and dogs are different.
Stop talking nonsense!
-You're so pathetic.
-Mom.
We might be poor,
but let's keep our pride.
You think you can keep it
when you're poor?
You're a fool and a stupid girl.
I marinated dried corvina.
Cook that for Bonggi for dinner.
And make radish soup with lots of perilla.
I need to wash up and go out again.
I don't know! You do it.
My goodness.
She could just attack him.
She's strong but useless.
Gosh, how frustrating.
"Rude Boss"
What now?
Hi.
You can't disappear without telling me.
What if an assassin storms in here?
I came home to get changed.
You have an attitude issue.
You don't understand
the concept of office regulations.
I need to wash myself, too.
It's about my personal hygiene.
Your boss is worried about his safety
and you care about your personal hygiene?
Okay. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I cared about
my personal hygiene.
Come here as soon as you're done.
Don't even dry your hair. Got it?
But...
What a jerk.
Gosh.
What should I do to have fun?
Big Boss!
-Big boss.
-Welcome.
How are you, sir?
Trap...
...is everyone here?
That's quite serious.
He lost four teeth.
I heard a woman beat you up.
-Is that correct?
-W-Well... t-that’s...
That's true.
We're so ashamed.
We couldn't tell you because we felt
we caused you a lot of trouble.
It's hard to believe, but that's true.
And she's not even from our industry.
Is that true?
We checked on that.
Her name is Do Bongsoon.
Her parents run a walnut shop.
She's working in Ainsoft as a secretary.
Ainsoft?
What a coincidence.
Meet her and make her
an offer if she's really good.
Or get rid of her!
I will get rid of her, Sir.
Let me take care of it!
Don't blow on my ears!
You shut up!
You let yourself get beaten up by a woman?
The rumors spread across
the mountains and the oceans!
This is humiliating!
You disgraced my name!
Shut up!
-I didn't say anything, sir.
-Him, not you!
Boss.
He bit his tongue.
Bring her to me.
If I find out it's not true,
I will kill you myself!
-Yes, sir!
It's getting hard to control my power.
I think it all started that day.
Are you drying your hair?
I said come right away!
We need to go somewhere.
I'm scared that I might kill him.
I'm coming.
She's no joke.
How old does she look like?
-She's old.
-What?
-Like a college student?
-No, just a woman.
-You idiot! Just die!
-Hey, hey.
Hurry up. I want to go home.
-Gosh. Not again.
-I'm bored.
Hello, ma'am.
Hi.
Oh...
Okay, okay.
Hey. Did you really do this?
Oh.
I think so.
Really?
Fix it! Or I'll rip you!
You can't fix what's already ripped.
-I can't do that.
-Are you crazy?
Let's take that from you.
Search her bag. Fix it or pay.
You're looking for trouble.
Are you broke? You have no money?
Money is competence, you see.
Sorry.
Life has been hard on me lately.
There should be 30,000 won.
Is there not?
There's only 3,000 won, you idiot.
It's only full of receipts.
Really?
Then a beating instead, okay?
A good beating, okay?
Hey, I hate to be hit on the head.
I also hate it when my stuff is touched.
You did both of them one after another.
You'd better not.
Oh, how scary!
Gosh, I'm terrified!
So what will you do, huh?
What will you do?
You little punk.
Hey! Didn't I warn you?
-Please don't.
-There's a lot of fine dust in the air.
Do you want some air up here?
-Huh?
-Please don't hurt me.
People should lead a good life.
They didn't teach you that in school?
-I'll behave!
-Seriously!
You! Get in there.
Ride that!
-Come here.
-Go, go!
Hold the handle tight.
It gets dangerous.
I'll take you to Hong Kong, China. Here we go!
Are you having fun?
Do you want to visit America, too?
-No!
Everyone gather.
Move faster.
Come on!
I'll give you one hour...
...to collect one kilogram of trash
around this area.
Only garbage you find on the ground.
Then I'll let you go.
Or you can take another ride.
-You choose.
-We'll collect trash!
-We will!
-Yeah, I think that's better.
And be nice, okay? Study hard.
Buy yourself something with those money.
-Bye.
-Thank you! Bye, sister!
-Bye!
-And about Mr. Kim...
-Postpone it to next week.
Great job.
Move faster.
Come with me.
-Help me.
-See you tomorrow, Sir!
-Okay.
-Don't catch a cold!
-The cold in the chest is bad!
-Try to lie on your side.
It's her.
-Can we go a little slowly?
-We are.
This makes no sense.
It makes no sense at all.
What's that?
Big Boss!
He just peed!
Oh, no.
How could you do that?
Let's go.
I'm keeping record of your overtime,
so stop complaining.
But what's wrong with my attudite?
I can't tolerate being treated like this
and getting that kind of appreciation.
-And...
-It's attitude.
-What?
-Repeat after me. Attitude.
No. You understood. That's the point.
You didn't study at school, did you?
Jeez.
Let's go.
So uncomfortable.
Oh, I feel good in mind and body.
Don't talk to me. I want some rest.
But where are we going?
Shut up and go.
Here we go.
"White Day
March 14th"
I'll take that one.
Sorry. Did I make you wait?
No, I just got here.
-Did you get your wrist checked?
-Yes, your friend was very kind.
Really?
I got this...
-What's this?
-It's just for White Day.
You'll be on duty on White Day, right?
Yeah.
Try it.
It's soft and sweet.
When will we get as sweet as this?
We'll meet three suspects tonight.
Be alert and find
who the prime suspect is.
Come in.
We've been waiting for you.
Oh, she's my personal secretary.
Hello, I'm Do Bongsoon.
I see.
It's a family meeting,
please wait outside...
She's my secretary. It's okay.
She knows we're just acting as family.
That looks so good.
Don't just eat and find the suspect.
I asked you to gather today...
...to announce unofficially...
...the heir of my company.
I didn't call the lawyer because...
...it's not about inheritance
or handing over my shares.
It's about deciding who will be the heir
and announcing it to everyone here.
Because I'll resign soon.
-Honey, what are you talking about?
-Father.
I started the business
as Osung Constructions...
...and expanded it to Osung Foods.
I was only very lucky.
The company is at a crossroad.
Will we remain as a mediocre
medium-size constructor...
...or will we grow into a big corporation?
The next CEO can ignore
the hierarchy at home.
Forget about hierarchy!
I will hand it over to the best manager.
You do it, Minhyuk.
You made the right choice, Father.
Minhyuk will do a good job.
How can you decide this
without discussing it with us?
Because it's his business.
He can do whatever he wants.
Okay.
I'm running my own company.
I'll see if we can merge both businesses
on amicable terms.
What? Who are you?
Who are you to merge on amicable terms?
The game market is a blue ocean.
If Ainsoft becomes
an affiliate of Osung Group...
...the company's image will change.
It's just a game company.
He makes money from children that gamble.
And you want to leave it to him?
Yes! It's just a game company...
"Attack
Defense"
And made operating profits of 180 billion.
I am impressed with his performance.
Did you ever do anything like that?
No, honey! Please!
Please, honey.
Please, sit down.
No matter which way I look at it,
I think your father is the one.
Yes.
Why would my father try to hurt me?
Why did I think you could ever help? Jeez.
He has the typical face of a suspect.
Shut it and go to Dobong-dong.
What? What about you?
I'll drive home.
I hurt one toe,
but it doesn't mean I can't drive.
After all the fuss you made for your toe.
I can hear you.
Okay.
Should I play some music?
-No, just go.
-Okay...
-What?
-What? I didn't say anything.
-You said something.
-No.We're heading to Dobong-dong, sir.
-Cheers!
Hey, you!
Did you ask for a designated driver?
Oh, yes.
I'm getting off here.
It's not your house.
I'm so stressed out that...
Because of you, jerk.
I need a painkiller.
I'm going to the pharmacy.
Bye, Mr. An!
Secretary Do!
Come to my house tomorrow.
Early in the morning.
Are you not going to the hospital?
It's just a cracked toe, why?
That's what I want to say, you jerk.
Go.
-Bye.
-Okay.
-Hey!
-You scared me.
Did he give you a ride again?
Are you on the guard here?
You're everywhere.
Your boss must have nothing better to do.
Is that why he's giving you rides?
Yes. He's someone who really
has nothing better to do.
You're my daughter, but you know
that you lack many things, don't you?
Then you should try harder.
Try harder on what?
Try to look sexy.
Look at me. See?
Women should never give up trying
to be sexy no matter their age.
Anyway, if you keep this up, you'll end up
with a miserable life. Do you get it?
I'm going to the pharmacy.
You go home.
You're so clueless.
-I'm coming with you!
-What seems to be the problem?
I've been having headaches lately.
It's because I'm so stressed out.
-Can I get a painkiller, please?
-Okay.
I need this.
-Hey, look.
-Mom!
Stop! Stop! Mom, stop!
My dear daughter...
-Hello.
-Hey, the spray is good.
-Bandages and antiseptics.
-Stop it!
What's wrong? Let's buy this one.
Go.
-No!
-I faked it.
I didn't spray it.
Thank you.
We'll take this one, too.
-Cheers!
How is my daughter doing at work?
-Do you like your job?
-Like it?  It's so-so.
-Is your boss pushy?
-Of course, that's his job.
Does he harass you sexually
and give you strange looks?
You should clean your ears.
How many times did I tell you?
Her boss likes men.
I'm still disappointed.
Are you sure he likes men?
Yes, I'm sure.
I think he likes Gukdoo.
-Who? Gukdoo?
-What? Your boss is really handsome.
Tell me about it.
His face is as shiny as Choonshim's bowl.
If he were not gay,
he'd be so promiscuous.
Gukdoo is standing in your way, then?
Mom stop it. Keep your pride.
But you should never give up.
What do you lack compared to Gukdoo?
Anyway, her boss is peculiar.
He gets hospitalized for nothing
and also leaves as he pleases.
-Hospitalized?
-Yes.
She trampled on his foot
and he hurt his toe.
Why did you trample on his foot?
When you should be washing his feet.
-Hello?
-I'm Heeji.
-Oh, hi.
-Thank you for everything at the hospital.
I'd like to treat you to a meal.
When are you available?
Oh, but you don't have to.
Please, don't refuse.
Okay. Tomorrow I'm on night duty,
so lunch will be fine.
Okay. I'll call you when I get there.
Okay.
Who was that?
Gukdoo's girlfriend.
And why does Gukdoo's girlfriend call you?
She wants to have lunch together.
Don't have lunch with just any girl.
She has a boyfriend, doesn't she?
And she's not even pretty.
-She's really pretty.
-Yeah, right.
Flirting by making eyes.
You should do that, too.
Is that illegal? Will you be fined?
You should also flirt with your boss
by making eyes at him.
-Don't trample on his feet.
-Will you stop it?
Are you going to meet her?
It'll be weird if I refuse.
She could come with Gukdoo.
No! Don't meet her.
Mom, you told me to sleep
in my boss's house...
...and you won't let him
have lunch with a girl?
He's not like you. One is for import
and the other for export.
You sell at a high price
and buy at a low price.
My goodness!
Who are we exporting
and who are we importing?
I don't know!
We drank all the beer.
Go and get some beer.
-Okay, I'm going.
-Should I go?
No, I'll go.
Let me out.
Excuse me. Open the door.
Please let me out!
I had an uneasy hunch that
I would soon have to use my strength.
"Strong Woman Do Bongsoon"
Boss, the world is so dark
and you are the light!
-You're the hope!
-The hope! Be our boss!
I like women that are as light
and soft as the cosmos.
Someone you want to protect.
Do Bongsoon, we're friends.
I also get mad and hurt!
You're so weird.
Rice! I want rice!
I don't know what I'll do if I get mad.
-It hurts!
-I'm going to take your butt away!
She's extremely cute.
She's having fun.
She seems to be very cheerful.
Follow her. Smoothly.
I've been blackmailed.
-Mr. An!
-It's the same guy.
If I catch them, I'll kill them.
-I think I should hold you.
-Is this the voice you heard?
-Sorry.
-We have a report of a missing person.
I think it's connected.