-Hey, Do Bongsoon.
-Who are you?
How dare you touch her!
Gukdoo!
Gukdoo...
Sorry. I got confused and pressed it.
-Are you okay?
-I'm fine.
-You can go. I'll take care of it.
-Okay, then.
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
I should have taken you home.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Are you okay?
What do you mean?
I pushed you.
What about it?
You worry too much, little one. Go home.
I'm the one that got beaten up.
What the heck?
I only suppressed an attempt to assault.
We'll talk in the station.
You were caught in the act.
She beat me.
Come with me!
-She beat me!
-Sir, wait!
I'm not that old! I'm not even married!
Your cane.
-What?
-Come with me.
You crazy...
Go home quickly!
-Hey!
-She's crazy.
You just wait!
Hey, Do Bongsoon!
Oh?
Lie low from now on, okay?
I didn't do anything.
I was just walking. He came at me.
You make me worry.
But what are you doing
in my neighborhood?
I came to get a walnut pie.
Oh.
The world got too dangerous.
It's so difficult for weak women
and powerless people to live.
-Bongsoon.
-I won't tolerate it anymore!
Bongsoon! Come to my office tomorrow.
Bye!
I'll file a report to
the Ministry of Labor!
-What? Who, me?
-Yes!
-Why?
-You promised me...
...you'll let me work in the development
team if I catch the blackmailer.
You say one thing and do another.
I didn't promise that I'll...
-I did.
-You did.
Who says I won't keep my promise?
But look, Bongsoon.
Yes, you caught the man
that was blackmailing me...
...but the killer
is still out there, right?
If you catch him, then you can work
in the development team.
-Until then, I'll stay with you.
-That has nothing to do with it.
See? See?
You never wanted me to work
in that team, did you?
That's not true! I swear to you.
I'm going to quit!
You are so dirty and cheap!
Cool your jets and think.
I am on your side!
I'll help you.
I mean it.
-Really?
-Yes.
Then I'm joining the development team.
Of course!
-No more excuses.
-I promise.
No, we're making
pinky promises too often.
Why do you want to work in
the development team so much?
I want to develop a game.
Then do it while you're with me.
We can work together.
-No, thank you!
-Why?
I want to officially go to work,
get approvals on my ideas...
...and put on my employee card.
Gosh. I want to be part of
Ainsoft's development team.
I really don't get it.
What is wrong with you?
Getting obsessed about nothing.
That's not it.
I'm just responsible and punctual.
Anyway, bye.
Gosh. Do Bongsoon.
Bye!
Goodnight!
Name?
Kim Kwangbok.
I should have arrested you last time.
The victim didn't want a punishment.
She forgave you.
Why did you try to kidnap her?
I don't believe this.
"Forgive"? "Kidnap"? "Victim"?
Listen. All this time
I was in the hospital.
These teeth are new implants.
They are not my natural teeth.
My goodness. Get it back in.
Put it back quickly.
Say ah. Say eeh.
Do they fit well?
Yes, they do. Perfectly.
Sir, my entire body's a mess.
My arm...
...won't move more than this.
I need a bidet to clean myself
after I go number two.
My goodness.
People will treat me like
a loser if they find out...
...that I got beaten up by a woman.
So I just let it slide.
I wasn't even paid for the injuries.
But...
...it's just so humiliating!
So, Do Bongsoon did hit you that day...
...and you lost four teeth and
seven ribs were fractured? Right?
Poor you.
I can hardly breathe.
-My ribs...
-I can see that.
I can't even chew my favorite food, squid.
Because my jaw got so weak.
-All I can eat is tofu.
-Because a woman beat you?
Yes, a woman beat me!
This is so humiliating.
It must have been so traumatic.
Wipe your face.
Thank you.
Gosh.
Do Bongsoon is not a woman.
You wouldn't know unless
you get beaten up by her.
So you wanted to beat her?
I wanted to have a proper fight.
Hey, hey. Calm down.
-My head was ringing.
-Okay, okay.
Okay, it's ringing.
He's under stress. Be gentle.
-I'm the victim.
-Okay, okay.
-Come here.
-I'm the victim, really. I got hit.
I am the victim!
We live in a democratic country!
You can't force an investigation!
-Open the door quickly.
-I'm not getting in there.
You can't do this to me.
My teeth! My teeth!
-Wait! My teeth!
-Get him in.
-Stay there and calm down.
-It's not me!
It's not me! I'm the victim!
This isn't democracy!
I am the victim!
Did you get home safely?
-How dare you touch her!
-Gukdoo!
Are you crazy?
He's pretending to be only friends.
I don't like it.
I'm so glad that Kyungsim is okay.
That man is really a psycho.
How can he go back there?
Is my pretty girl upset because
she missed the criminal?
Why doesn't life work out as I plan it?
Why wasn't I good at studying?
Why is nothing I do right?
Why can't I be open
with the man I like? Why?
-What are you talking about?
-What's wrong, sweetie?
-Bongsoon.
-I can't even do things my way at work.
I bought this for you. It's your favorite.
-What's this?
-What is it?
Spicy chicken feet! Bongsoon's favorite.
-It's spicy chicken feet.
-They're so plump. Look!
Bongsoon, have some.
I bought your favorite.
-Come on.
-Let me try one.
Let's eat.
-Let me see.
-It's good!
Why am I so simple-minded?
Kyungsim, did you sleep well?
Don't worry, my friend.
I got your back.
I have never felt this confused
in my life before.
I wanted a permanent job
at Ainsoft so much...
Now I want to catch
that killer more than ever.
I heard your transfer to
the development team was put off.
So it seems.
Gosh, Mr. An...
Doing this in the morning
brings me good luck.
Gosh.
Wow, you are amazing.
You caught the blackmailer.
Yes, I'm very good at what I have to do.
I was really surprised.
The culprit was a total stranger.
Just a psycho.
I thought it was
one of Mr. An's brothers.
He's not here yet.
Oh? What's this?
What's this?
What's this? I guess this is not mine.
That shocked me.
Good morning!
Hello, Mr. An.
Did you sleep well?
Sorry?
-Yes.
-I slept well, too.
Is this laptop for me?
Yes, you wanted to work
in the development team.
You should start working on
a presentation for a new game.
Work on that while you're here.
Everything you need is installed.
Can I use this anyway I want to?
It's yours. No need to ask.
Thank you.
Open it.
Okay.
If you ever go near her again...
...not only won't you be able to chew
squid, but you won't be able to drink...
...or even walk again.
No, I'll make sure you
can't use your legs. Got it?
Don't forget that.
Oh my...
It's fake.
The case of missing women
in Dobong-dong...
...took a new turn with another victim.
To prevent more incidents
and speed up the investigation...
...the police will conduct
an open investigation.
-It'll be an open investigation!
-What?
The police are questioning suspects
based on the footprints he left.
They're also gathering information
on the missing women.
Criminal profilers say it's
a typical misogynistic crime.
The Dobong-dong kidnapping
recalls one particular case.
Recently, in UK, a movement against
misogyny called "Reclaim The Internet"...
...has become a huge interest.
This movement is actually based
on another movement that was active...
...during the 1970s when 13 women
became victims of a serial murder.
Women demanded to walk the streets
at night without fear of crimes..
...hence, the movement was called
"Reclaim The Night."
Times might have changed, but
crimes against women are still committed.
Violent acts of the strong
against the weak.
The survival of the fittest might be
the rule in the animal world...
...but power should not be used
to oppress the weak in our world.
It should not! It can never be allowed!
What is she working on so hard?
Jo Insung?
Perfect. My gosh! Who's that?
Sir, your father wants
to see you right now.
-Now?
-Yes.
I don't want more scandals
before the shareholder meeting.
There won't be.
I'll cover it up.
I believe in you
and I respect your decision.
If the board finds out that it
was a fight between brothers...
...it won't be of any good for us.
Announce an official engagement
before the shareholders' meeting.
And bring that girl home.
I want to get to know her.
The faster, the better.
Yes, father.
Where is he?
Oh, my goodness! What did he do? Jeez!
Gosh. Insung.
There.
Should I take a break?
Oh?
"Fourth Victim of the Dobong-dong Case"
That son of a...
"Emergency Conference,
Seoul Metropolitan Police Agency"
-Another victim.
-He's not just another criminal.
Let's think about what we can do
to protect our neighborhood.
The criminal is after skinny women
weighing between 40 kg to 48 kg.
-Why skinny women?
-Skinny women are his type?
We can't eliminate the possibility
of his liking for such women.
-Do you think they're alive?
-Yes, they're alive.
We found no bodies of the victims so far.
-What about the first victim?
-Why was she killed?
As you can see, she resisted violently.
He didn't mean to kill her.
It was an accident.
She was also very skinny.
Yes, she was like the others.
Gukdoo's mom said
there's a play similar to this case.
This is the poster of a play
performed in Daehak-ro.
A man kidnaps and breeds seven women.
-Seven?
-To have a group marriage.
We tracked down the footprints
the suspect left in the scene...
...and found that they came
from the male lead.
He's claiming he lost his shoes,
but we have many doubts.
So, we're investigating him right now.
There's a fourth victim.
Pull out of this case!
Send the special investigation unit
to the neighborhood's precinct.
The special investigation unit
will go to the neighborhood.
What? What do you mean?
We have to catch the criminal...
...to clear Gukdoo of the deferred
disciplinary action against him.
Then let's catch him.
Before the special unit does.
You scared me.
What are you doing?
-Nothing much. Let's go.
-Where?
I'm going to catch him myself.
I won't leave it to the police.
Let's go!
Today you'll learn defensive skills.
-The best defense is...
-A good offense.
Exactly. Attack me.
I'll show you the best defense.
-Can I?
-Yes.
Then your neck breaks.
Come on.
Then you're dead already.
-I can use this arm.
-Then I'll do this.
You can't use your arm.
-You can't move.
-Yes.
Gosh.
Get up.
Now I'll attack you,
so you protect yourself.
Here I go.
Wait!
Hey.
Jiu-jitsu. Go!
What on earth?
You are firing me up.
It's not too hard.
You're driving me nuts. Okay, Jiu-jitsu.
Jiu-jitsu starts like this.
Hey, that's...
Oh, yeah!
Here.
Hydrate yourself.
Open it for me.
There.
One, two! One, two!
You're getting faster.
-Of course.
-Good!
-Knees up to your chest!
-Gosh.
-Lift them up!
-Stop doing that!
Good. That's it.
Duck down. All the way.
Become one with the jump rope.
There must be a reason
I was given this power.
A world where the powerful
abuse their power. Oh, no!
I will use my power to punish them!
I'm the strong woman,
Do Bongsoon! Here I go!
Pick it up quickly.
It got nice and clean.
Pick that up.
Good job.
What?
Hey! You can't throw
cigarette butts here!
-Then you pick it up.
-You threw it, you pick it up!
Don't talk back, you're still
wet behind the ears. Get lost!
Leave him alone.
You guys are good boys picking up garbage.
As punishment from school, right?
No, to keep our neighborhood clean.
I don't like the way you look at me.
And I think a beating will fix that.
You little brat. Eyes down.
You want a piece of me?
-You punk.
-Oh! Bro!
Who's your leader? It's not your teacher
who is watching your back.
-What gang?
-How dare you glare at me?
I'll show him whose turf it is.
-I'm not telling you!
-You're not telling us what?
Call your boss. Now!
Boss, we need you here.
Say what? Hey!
We got beaten up. Come quickly.
What the heck?
I told them to pick up garbage
and they got in trouble anyway.
-You want some?
-I can starve to death.
-We'll never eat that!
-Never!
I shouldn't have been nice to you.
You little brats.
Hey. What are you doing here?
-Boss!
-You're dead now!
Boss!
Isn't that Do Bongsoon?
What are you doing to these minors?
Did you beat them?
-How can you do this?
-She's Do Bongsoon.
Oh, so you're the famous Do Bongsoon?
Let the kids go. We should have a talk.
Can't you see this?
We're guarding the neighborhood.
I'm sorry but we have to
protect the ladies.
I should just...
If you're guarding
the neighborhood do just that.
What are you doing? Go home.
-Boss!
-Who said you can go home?
We asked them to not throw
cigarette butts, but they did.
What? Gross!
-Clean that up!
-You clean it up, crazy woman!
-Clean it up!
-Come on. Hit me.
You have to hit us first
to start a fight.
Or the kids will say
we hit the lady first.
-So come on. Hit me.
-Then don't whine later.
Of course!
Don't ever touch the kids again!
-Yes!
She's awesome!
What? Do Bongsoon again?
Why does she stand in our way?
What gang is she in?
Do we have any information?
I think she's working freelance.
Some say it's a Taiwanese gang from China.
Others say she's being
trained by the Triad, sir.
Darn! It's so humiliating!
My pride is crumbling!
Do Bongsoon is no longer a woman!
She is our enemy! Understood?
-Yes, sir!
Okay, I got it.
Someone help him.
Are you doing that on purpose?
Okay, it's fine. It's fine.
Okay, I got it. Now sit.
Okay, okay.
Someone help him!
But how do we crush her?
Ah, my head!
I don't think it'll be easy, sir.
You think I don't know that?
Who said it'll be easy?
-Someone help him.
-I can't chew.
I got it.
Why didn't you get him softer tofu?
So I can eat with a straw.
Okay, okay. I'm sorry.
Darn it. Okay, okay.
So you're not staying
at your boss's anymore?
I'm not. I'm going to
protect Dobong-dong.
Wow.
You can go home now.
I'm getting sick of this hospital.
Thanks for recovering
so quickly, Kyungsim.
Hey. But you're not putting
much strength in your grip.
Yes. Now I can control my strength.
I have more skills now.
I'm a new Do Bongsoon.
Kyungsim, Bonggi's seeing
Gukdoo's girlfriend.
-What do I do?
-Is it a love triangle?
Isn't she really mean?
How can she do that to Gukdoo?
Why not? Bonggi is a cool guy.
I'd date Bonggi even if
I were dating Gukdoo.
-What? You can't be serious.
-I am serious.
You can't break a promise so easily.
If you decided to date someone
and give him your heart...
...you stay with him.
Why do you hesitate?
Love changes.
Love is like a seesaw,
it goes up and down.
Like a swing, it goes up and down.
It moves. You never know.
-You might end up liking Mr. An.
-What?
That's how love is.
You really don't get it.
Heeji!
I've been thinking about it.
And I think it's my fault.
Well, my friend told me this.
Women waver endlessly
if her man doesn't give her...
...the confidence she deserves.
I'm sorry.
No, it's not like that.
But... I couldn't help it.
Because...
...I always had
someone else in my heart.
I think I've liked someone
for a long time.
And I realized that just now.
Have you been seeing someone else?
No.
I'd nag at her all the time.
I've been so harsh on her.
She does such stupid things.
And I got angry every time I saw her.
Because I didn't want her to get hurt
or feel pain.
I felt like I'd lose my mind
if people treated her badly.
You do like her.
And very much.
I'm sorry.
So don't feel guilty.
Hey, stay in bed until
you're fully recovered.
Don't take a step out of this house.
Okay. The police gave me this.
And don't trust in that too much.
As soon as your treatment is over,
go to Busan and stay there, okay?
And this... Ta-da.
-A present to welcome you.
-What is it?
It's shampoo with perfume
of natural ingredients.
It'll help you relax.
-It smells nice.
-It does.
Thanks.
Are you sleeping?
Yes.
Then wake up.
I don't want to.
There's somewhere we need to go.
I'm going to sleep.
I'll pay you double for overtime.
I'll go and pick you up now.
Wear clean clothes, wash your hair,
and wait for me looking decent.
Where are we going?
To my parents'.
Why should I go there?
I'm leaving now. Get ready!
-He's coming now?
-Who?
-My boss.
-What?
Don't move.
Bongsoon, let's go to the temple.
Let's go and say hello to Buddha
or he might forget us.
-I can't. I'm going out.
-Where?
-I don't know.
-Mr. An is coming.
What?
-Oh, my. Oh, my.
-Mom!
Like he's so important.
Jump!
Mr. An! Hello.
Bongsoon isn't ready yet.
Wait inside.
I'm sorry for making her
work on a weekend.
Oh, don't worry.
She can work her all the day
throughout the year.
Come in and wait inside. It's okay.
Be quiet!
-But I...
-Make yourself at home.
But I...
Mom!
We were having breakfast.
Come and join us.
What is she doing?
No, I'm fine.
Don't tell me you're picky with food.
Do you only eat high-quality food
at fancy places?
Of course not.
I'm never picky with food.
-Then join us for breakfast.
-I'll just...
Okay. Thank you.
This is our usual breakfast.
Okay, let's eat.
There are so many new dishes
in our usual breakfast today.
He's too busy in the hospital
so he can hardly come home.
Who makes so many dishes
for breakfast? We're leaving.
Bongsoon, that's not how I taught you.
Didn’t I tell you this all the time?
Never let a guest leave without eating
if he comes at mealtime.
-Enjoy it.
-Thanks.
Eat up!
-Okay.
-Enjoy.
-You don't have to.
Don't feel too pressured.
No, I'll enjoy it. Thanks.
-Dad, I want chives kimchi.
-Okay. Here it is.
Have some more.
There's japchae, too. Take it.
-Bongsoon, eat this.
-This is good.
-You eat well.
-Have some meat.
Have this.
Oh, thanks.
-They're so small.
-They're baby crabs.
Son of a crab.
All you have to do is act like
you're my fiancé.
Double isn't enough. Double the double.
You could have told me
it was a breakfast gathering.
When was I supposed to tell you?
What do you like so much about Minhyuk?
Sorry? Well, he's...
He's...
He's handsome.
Well, and he has a great personality.
Actually...
...he's nuts.
-What? He's nuts?
-Yes.
And not just nuts.
He's ultra-super nuts.
Yes, he's nuts. He is!
Sometimes he makes me wonder
if he's really in his sane mind.
That's right! He's nuts!
Your father knows.
This looks great! Let's eat.
I was worried about the rumors.
Now that I see you I can rest at peace.
I sent him abroad to study
as soon as his mother died.
While he was overseas,
he met too many women...
...that I was very worried.
But suddenly he stopped meeting women.
Then I heard about this absurd rumor.
Gosh. No, I've sinned a lot.
Anyway, please take good care of him.
He's not gay. I'm sure he's not.
He's not gay. Wake up!
Your vocabulary improved a lot.
"Ultra-super nuts"?
See? Education works.
You improved because you look
at the dictionary I gave you.
Sorry.
You should buckle it
as soon as you get in the car.
Where are we going now?
I bought your time today, remember?
Where are we going?
To meet the woman I loved the most.
Hi, mom.
I came with someone I wanted you to meet.
There's an old movie called
"When Harry Met Sally."
It was my mom's favorite.
And in that movie,
there's a line that goes...
"No man can be friends with
a woman that he finds attractive."
Then I guess no one finds me attractive.
Men are friends with me.
I don't think so.
Your friend likes you.
And very much.
Having you as a friend...
...is very difficult.
Especially for a man.
Your friend is lying.
Or he might have you as a friend
so he doesn't lose you.
No, we're just friends.
I'm sure about that.
It's very simple to become
lovers from friends.
One of the two has to
take one step closer.
This one step is enough
to change the relationship.
Like this.
One step.
No one took that one step
between Gukdoo and I.
But that day...
...he came one step closer to me.
"Special Investigations Unit"
The special unit took the case,
but we're not giving up.
We'll keep investigating
behind closed doors.
They won't share important
information with us.
-We have to investigate on our own.
-Chin up, everyone.
This is a famous line of the 86th
episode of "Chief Investigator."
"The criminal lets himself be caught
if the police tries hard enough."
Sir! I reached the owner of
the dash cam and got it.
So this is the street that
leads to a national highway.
But the byway...
Wait!
It smelled like gasoline.
It's the smell of asphalt.
Sorry. I'll be right back.
What? Where are you going?
He doesn't understand
the concept of teamwork.
It's an individual combat from now on.
You mean we won't share information?
That's not what I meant!
The play actor is here.
All the actors went out
for dinner that day.
You can confirm that with
the director and the company.
I was performing a night play.
It's been quite long
since I lost those shoes.
-Anyone you have in mind?
-I'm not sure.
There have been theft cases
in the dressing rooms...
...but there are no CCTVs.
Seriously. I never imagined someone
would steal my shoes.
Excuse me.
Where is the owner?
-He's abroad on a business trip.
-Where?
To Sudan to sell car parts
from scrapped cars.
Korean car parts are popular
in Africa these days.
-When did he go?
-Last week.
-Does he go abroad very often?
-Yes.
The price of scrap iron
is too low these days.
So we make a living out of
exporting car parts from scrapped cars.
That's why he goes often.
I see. Thanks.
Wait for me!
Oh, gosh!
-Come home early.
-Okay.
Sir, we confirmed the alibi of the actor.
He's certainly not the one.
Spectacles, you investigate further
with the other actors and staff.
Same old, same old.
Yeah, you know. My wife cooks for me.
I have to work late again. I'm so tired.
-Excuse me.
-Okay.
Hold on. How can I help you?
I was told to come and give
my statement as witness.
I'll call you back.
Come with me.
-Gukdoo must be so busy.
-I'm worried.
I regret sending him
to the police academy.
-Law school would have been better.
-What are you talking about?
Someone like Gukdoo
must be a policeman...
...so we have a brighter future.
Alain De Botton,
a writer that I like said...
"Earning a lot of money
and holding a high position..."
"...doesn't mean success."
"It has to be success defined
by yourself, not by others."
Gukdoo probably thinks he's successful.
Of course he is.
Here it is. Enjoy it.
The pastry chef apron
looks so good on you.
Thank you! Do you mean it?
Thank you!
How can you laugh when
the neighborhood is in trouble?
What did Gukdoo do while
the case became so serious?
Jinyi, don't try to tick me off
with absurd comments.
So many people are dying of cancer.
-What is Bonggi doing?
-What?
Bonggi is an orthopedist.
I can't talk to you.
Yes, don't talk to her.
Please get going.
Anyway, I'll get going.
-Bye. Goodbye.
-Bye.
-Can't you be more civilized?
-What?
How can you say that
after you heard what she said?
What does cancer have to do with Bonggi?
She's a writer and she makes
such ignorant comments!
You started it!
She's already worried about Gukdoo!
How can you ask her what he's doing?
What? Why do you smile like
an idiot when you're with her?
-I did not smile like an idiot!
-You can't look more like an idiot!
You give her everything, don't you?
You might even give her
all your entrails!
When? When? Watch your mouth!
-You got quite daring.
-I won't tolerate it anymore!
Where are you going?
Alain De Ron?
Alain De Ton?
Where did Jinyi go
after she beat her husband?
To the hospital to give Bonggi
some clothes to change.
He got so beaten up.
Poor man.
I feel so bad for him.
It makes me want to treat him
to some hot soup and rice.
I feel pity for him.
-Alain De Botton.
-Look at this eye.
Will it stay red for long?
"Baek Tak Industries Development"
I thank Mr. Beak and
everyone for coming...
...despite your busy schedule
to this countermeasure meeting.
Charles Go, the brain of
Baek Tak developments...
...holds the MBA degree
of Harvard University.
He's written...
"Economy of the 22nd Century!
No Worries, We'll Be Dead by Then"
He'll come out to give
a presentation on our business.
Please welcome him with
a big round of applause.
Now let's call him out.
Charles Go!
Hello, I'm Charles Go.
Baek Tak Developments is facing
a very important time.
It's the right time to
expand our business!
But due to various
unwanted accidents, I know that...
...our CEO and many employees
are very concerned.
The fate of a company
depends on its people!
It depends on how and when
you allocate your resources.
This is a report of the damages
our people suffered recently.
First, the redevelopment site
in Dobong-dong, Dobong-Gu.
Seven men, including Kim Kwangbok.
Second, three men
in Dobong-dong, Dobong-Gu.
Third, two men in the house
of Ainsoft's CEO, An Minhyuk.
Fourth, three men in the playground
near Dobong High School.
Surprisingly, they were attacked
by a woman called Do Bongsoon...
...aged 27 and of very small size.
But these men were not
beaten by Do Bongsoon.
It was Kang Banggu, aged 76.
She's an old woman that lives
in Goejeon-dong, Daegu.
But Kang Banggu turned out to be
Do Bongsoon's grandmother.
-What?
-Surprising?
We were attacked by a family.
It is a very scary organization.
Now let me brief you about the damages.
A total of 15 men were injured.
Forty percent of them must be
treated for 28 weeks at a hospital.
Six teeth were lost
and faces were crushed.
Optic nerves damaged,
hearing was impaired!
Ribs and femurs got fractured!
Na Seonggi, who is the eldest son
of a family with few men...
...got injured in his testicles
that represent manliness!
The most serious aftereffect
they suffer are...
...loss of confidence, anxiousness,
and fear of being attacked again!
Psychological trauma of women!
Above all, the urge to avenge oneself!
Cheolsoo!
-That's enough.
-It's Charles.
Forget it! That's enough!
Tell us what we can do!
We all know what happened!
There is...
...a way.
We'll take our revenge.
-We'll defeat Do Bongsoon...
-That jerk.
...and clear our name from
bad rumors and reputation.
Hey, hey! Stop! Stop!
So how do you suggest we defeat her?
We were beaten up,
we will rise up to beat up.
That is a gang fight!
The last resort!
Gang to gang fight!
So we all beat her up together?
No, no, no.
It'll be a one-on-one fight.
We live in a time where
the fist is stronger than the law.
We must build up our power
again on that basis!
Okay, I get the logic.
How do we get Do Bongsoon here?
She won't just come!
There is a way.
That will be voice phishing.
Amazing! Yes, that's it!
Why didn't we think of that?
He trained abroad, all right.
So I have...
...invited some specialists in the area.
-Come out!
-Specialists! It's different!
What?
Aren't they...
-Aren't they comedians?
-Pull up your pants.
Hello!
-Hello.
Did he kidnap them?
They're comedians.
How much do we pay them?
-Hey, hey.
-What?
-Do we upload it in YouTube?
-What? No, never!
The boss won't like it.
She wants a quiet life,
so we'll help her have it.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
Though...
Punch! Kick!
Do you have a death wish?
I think it won't be bad that
we let people know...
...who's watching our back
and what she can do.
What do you think?
Let's do it!
What are you doing here?
You're working on weekends
so I came to visit you.
-Wow!
-Here.
-What's this?
-I got my salary.
I bought mom and dad a present,
but I want you to have it in cash.
Whoa!
Awesome!
-You must be busy. I'm off.
-Bongsoon.
I like her, too.
I'd like to meet her,
but I shouldn't, right?
Of course you shouldn't.
That's not fair play, so don't.
You're all grown up now,
getting into a love triangle.
-I'm off.
-Oh, come on.
Good luck to you, too!
-For what?
-Go on a date.
-With who?
-An Minhyuk.
I think he's a nice guy.
As a doctor, I can say
he's not gay, at least.
I think mom brainwashed you.
I'm off!
I'm on duty tonight.
I won't go home.
I know!
-Pick up your tools.
-Get ready!
We're fighting against Do Bongsoon.
She is not an easy opponent.
Poke her, roll her, beat her...
What are you doing?
-Sir!
You'll go armed to fight a girl?
I'm afraid someone might find out!
Sir, it's Do Bongsoon.
She might kill all of us.
You stay here!
I'm ashamed of you.
Stay home.
Put that down and come.
-Yes, sir!
-Yes!
Don't just leave it there.
-Bongsoon! Bongsoon!
-Dad!
Dad, are you so happy
that mom is gone on a trip?
I feel great!
-Why are you so happy?
-Wait. One, two...!
-Hello?
-We have training today.
-I know.
-I'm in your neighborhood. Come out.
Right away.
To Bongsoon
To my pretty granddaughter Bongsoon.
The little kid has now become a lady.
You even got a job.
You don't know how proud I'm of you.
I know you can't lead
a normal life like the others.
People might ask why be
ashamed of being strong.
But the world isn't so easy.
They backbite and bully you
if you're different to them.
Bongsoon, I always told you to hide...
...but don't ever be
ashamed of your strength.
Because it is a gift from heaven
that we must be used for the good.
I love you, my sweetie.
From your granny.
Just do it. What's the problem?
Do it like you do it on TV.
It's all set up. Go ahead.
Sit.
We'll get arrested
if it's real voice phishing.
-Do we look like we're lawful?
-We never succeeded.
So put your mind to
make it happen this time.
Call this number. Plug it in.
They'll do a good job
if they want their limbs intact.
It doesn't fit.
-Hello?
-I said I'm coming.
She's coming.
-Hello?
-Bongsoon, help!
They kidnapped me!
Did you hear that?
We kidnapped your mom.
-What?
-So come to that address quickly.
If you call the police...
...your mom dies!
-Kyungsim, mom got kidnapped!
-What?
-Try calling Mom.
-Hey! We should call the police.
No, we can't call the police.
-Mom!
-Hey!
Sir!
See? They're professionals.
Why isn't she picking up?
Please, pick up.
She doesn't pick up?
Why do you keep calling me?
-Were you not kidnapped?
-Kidnapped?
Why would anyone kidnap me?
It'll only make their lives miserable.
But what are you talking about?
Oh, never mind.
Have a lot of fun on your trip.
Bye.
-She didn't get kidnapped.
-Then what happened?
-Voice phishing!
-What?
-What do we do?
-Voice phishing?
How did they know she got paid?
Mom!
-Hello?
-Where are you?
I'll deduct 100,000 won for every
ten minutes you're late.
Mr. An, my mom got kidnapped.
-What?
-Mom!
Where are you? Do Bongsoon.
-Bongsoon!
Gukdoo, it's Bongsoon's dad.
Yes, sir.
What? I'll look into that.
Hello, Control Team?
Please locate Do Bongsoon.
Locate Do Bongsoon.
Mom!
Mom...
Hey.
Where's my mom?
What? Your mom?
Hello?
Bongsoon, where are you?
Your mom's fine.
I think it was voice phishing.
Yes, I think so.
Okay, don't worry. Bye.
Ms. Do Bongsoon.
The reputation of our organization
got dumped into a poop bucket!
So let's have a fight.
Oh, wait. Before we do,
get on your knees...
...and beg for forgiveness
so we can film a video.
Okay.
-Let's do that.
-What?
-Really?
But you'll get on your knees, not me.
Me? Me?
On my knees?
What's that?
Walnuts?
Come at me.
Let's begin.
"Strong Woman Do Bongsoon"
Oh, yes! Yes, yes, yes!
-Are you okay?
-She fainted!
You have to look happy.
You're happy.
You're eating with Bongsoon.
It's okay.
Rich and flawless guys don't exist.
Sorry. I won't look at her.
Do as I say.
Okay.
Are you okay?
We should put a computer generated halo.
-Your lines.
-You have to do this...
-I don't have lines here.
-But to do this...
You have to come closer
and I should see your face.
That's how it works.
-No, that can't be.
-What can't be?
If I thought he was a man,
I wouldn't come at night...
...and stay up all night.
What am I saying?
What are you saying?
You can see us all!
Cut!