(In her heart,)
(there is a garden.)
(A ray of light.)
(Doors leading to a palace.)
(A lovely, obscure place.)
(Meanwhile, I am dressed in rags, filthy.)
(A man convulsing in pain.)
(It just so happened
that I was unambiguously prohibited)
(from entering that area.)
[Building a world-class resort]
[13th District Marina Bay Investment Agreement]
(It's right ahead.)
(I've prepared)
(your favorite wine.)
(Let's drink while we chat.)
(Okay, we'll drink and chat.)
[Pei Group, Sunshine Fund]
[Enlightening Reading Investment Agreement]
[Sunshine Fund]
(Pei Su.)
(I love you.)
(I'm a monster.)
(But)
(I love you.)
(I'm shameless.)
(Brutal.)
(And et cetera.)
(Many times, I knew how you felt.)
[Lolita]
(And knowing that)
(is insufferable.)
[Missed Call: Philosopher]
[Justice in the Dark]
[Episode 7]
Search the premise thoroughly, got it?
Then compare these two fingerprints.
Let me know soonest possible.
Okay.
All right.
And verify
the victim and the others.
Got it.
Send me anything useful.
Okay.
And these two as well.
Captain Luo.
What's happened?
Xinzhou Kangxin High School
organized a field trip
to the aboriginal heritage park in Xiling
this afternoon.
They were kidnapped halfway.
By tracking one of the children's phone GPS,
we followed the bus's route to the crime scene.
The culprit has been shot dead.
So the case has been resolved.
Why did Qiao ask me to come so urgently then?
To help clean up?
It's because one of the children
is missing.
Check the surroundings again.
Okay.
-Captain Luo.
This was taken during the visit today.
The missing girl is called Qu Tong.
Fifteen years old from Xiling.
When the bus was ambushed,
Qu Tong jumped out of the window
as the teacher was fighting off the culprit.
Have you initiated the Feiling Alert?
Yes. It's been four hours.
The Patrol Detachment
has combed through a radius
of ten kilometers.
At last, the clues ended
at the side of a dirt trail
about five kilometers from here.
Qiao is already on her way there.
The first 24 hours of a child going missing
is crucial.
Xiao Hanyang, report to the department.
Get them to send search and rescue dogs.
Yes, sir.
Wu.
Keep in touch with the Patrol Detachment.
Notify me immediately if there's news.
Get Qiao to send me the location of the dirt trail.
I'll head there now.
Got it.
You're funny.
Right.
Pei Su?
Do you guys come here often?
Yes, we hang out here often.
Mainly because Donglan invited us.
It's quite a nice place.
Captain Luo.
How come you're involved in this?
A child has gone missing.
We're taking over the case.
What are you doing here?
Rubbernecking?
You weren't here, Captain Luo.
What happened just now was too scary.
If our fleet
hadn't taken action there
and hadn't run circles around the criminal,
turning it into a cat-and-mouse,
hunter-turned-prey situation,
the incident today
would've ended badly.
Please explain.
We have a sports car club
on a mountaintop in Xiling.
The excursion just started today.
Who knew we'd come across such a thing?
Since the officers requested our help, so...
We played along accordingly.
So you happened to mislead the kidnapper
while out racing.
Should I prepare a stack of medals
to thank you?
There's no need.
Captain Luo.
No need to be so courteous.
The three of us are close.
A family.
Your matter is my matter.
I haven't had the chance to thank you for last time.
Anything else you need from us?
Just say it.
Who's one family with you?
Donglan.
I just heard from an officer
that there's a girl still missing.
A child is missing?
Yes.
Is that so?
Then I'll have to do my part.
I might not have the smarts,
but I can help out physically.
Might as well make use of our fleet of cars.
Right, Captain Luo?
A girl is missing.
Shouldn't we help search?
-Yes, she has to be found.
-Yeah, search.
We'll search.
All right.
Yes, a girl is missing from the bus.
I'll send the photo to Pei Su.
Forward it to me.
Captain Luo and Mr. Pei's business
is our business.
Search for her like it's your own kid.
-Move out!
-Okay.
-All right.
-Let's go.
-Go, go.
I can give you a ride.
Wear your shirt properly.
I'm truly middle-aged.
I no longer understand
the emptiness youngsters in Xinzhou
like you all feel.
Emptiness is better than weakness.
What happened to your hand?
Who hurt you?
Your brother.
The stray cat you dumped to Tao Ze.
Did you forget it?
Little punk.
Always looking for novelty.
Other people have to clean up your mess after.
What?
Touched by my kindness?
It's been a long time.
You're raising it still?
If not?
-You want it?
-You...
Take it if you want it.
Do I need to be vaccinated?
You suddenly being so thoughtful
has caught me off guard.
Being considerate of the elderly
is everyone's duty.
That nice?
Okay.
Next time, when it's the festivities,
don't forget to bring sweets and fruits
to pay me, your old man, a visit.
No problem.
I'll make sure to make an offering
at the altar for you too.
[Do not enter]
I thought you adored the cat back then.
Why did you give it up?
I don't like keeping pets.
It's too troublesome.
Besides,
you guys made a summary.
The three signs of an Apath.
Wetting the bed, setting fires,
abusing little animals.
I worried that I wouldn't be able
to control myself.
Captain Luo.
Is the explanation
reasonable?
Captain Luo!
Over here!
Sir, take a look over there.
Here.
We showed it to the parents.
They confirmed the shoelace
came from Qu Tong's sandals.
(Qu Tong ran all the way here
after escaping from the bus.)
(She tripped on a tree branch and fell.)
(The branch cut her ankle.)
(A person stood in front of her.)
(An adult.)
(She left with them.)
Looking at the scene,
someone must have passed through here
and saved Qu Tong.
Sir, that's good news, right?
After all, it was raining.
And we're on the mountain.
Loose soil can be a safety hazard.
Someone passed by
and saved the girl.
At least tonight,
she wouldn't be out in the wilderness.
Did she go willingly, or was she forced?
We don't know that yet.
Are you saying...
Don't assume.
Get the forensic team to come take a look.
See if they're able to discern from the traces
whether the girl left willingly or not.
Look out for any reports nearby
regarding a found child.
Also,
get in touch
with the heritage park the kids visited today.
Check the visitor list for today.
And get access to the surveillance cameras
around the area.
Check and see
what other vehicles passed through.
Keep a lookout
for a solo male driver.
Increase search efforts.
Remember, time is of the essence.
Yes, sir.
Captain Luo.
When the girl went missing,
was she also wearing a floral dress?
(Recently,)
(a teenage girl went missing
in the mountains of Xiling.)
(The missing girl, surnamed Qu,)
(is a Year 10 student at Kangxin High School.)
(After SID took over the case,)
(an emergency plan was immediately initiated.)
(With Xiling as the center,
a joint task force was formed)
(with the Patrol Detachments
of the nearby three districts.)
(A missive has been issued to go down the streets)
(and investigate even the smallest unit,)
(a joint online and offline operation.)
(Presently, Qu has been missing)
(for over 24 hours.)
(As we all know,)
(the first 24 hours)
(are crucial in finding a missing person.)
(Every minute saved)
(means a higher chance of survival for the child.)
[16-year-old girl missing in Xiling. A 200-strong
search party, 25 hours later, still no news]
[Missing person]
[16-year-old girl missing in Xiling]
I don't know who left it there.
Nor when it was left there.
I found it in our milk crate.
Our child has gone missing.
[Qu Tong's father]
This was the least of our concerns.
Today, when the milkman knocked at our door,
I opened the crate,
and this fell out.
What's in it?
It...
It's an audio recording.
We don't have much to go on right now.
I don't want to think too much,
but after listening to Yang droning on
about Lotus Hill's Case,
it's practically etched in my mind.
That's why I'm here to confirm it with you.
The missing girl, Qu Tong,
has a lot of similarities
to the victim of Lotus Hill's Case.
They were both wearing floral dresses
when they went missing.
There were no calls asking for ransom.
Rather, we got suspicious audio recordings.
You mean this recording?
Yes.
Qu Tong's parents submitted it.
A case that happened 16 years ago.
We only ever heard about it.
But you experienced it personally.
After you heard this recording,
do you think
it sounds like
the call the kidnapper
made to the families back then?
Lotus Hill's Case
was a high-profile one.
Even now, you can easily find
a multitude of newspaper reports on the case.
However,
there was one detail
we never revealed to the outside.
I remember the first missing girl,
the one where your mentor received the call.
During the investigation,
the victim's parent
mentioned one thing.
During the call,
I heard the sound of jingle bells
from my daughter's pencil case.
It must have been the kidnapper.
Could you have heard it wrong?
No way!
Don't get so worked up. Tell me slowly.
Ling...
She collected colorful jingle bells
(and placed them in the pencil case.)
(When she was bored,)
(she'd shake the pencil case like a shaker.)
She is my daughter.
I wouldn't have heard wrong.
(The parent firmly believed)
that it was his daughter in the recording.
Of course.
That was just a small detail.
We didn't keep any audio records.
There's only the testimony from the parent.
No wonder.
My mentor didn't mention it in his notes either.
There was no reason for SID
to reveal a dubious detail like that
to the public.
Could it be the wrong person was killed
in the old case?
The culprit
is back at it again
after over a decade.
A serial killer
wouldn't just halt his desire to kill
without any reason.
If they had indeed gotten the wrong person,
the culprit could've killed
thousands of people during this time.
So I'm pretty sure
he is an Apath.
Chief Du.
What was the ultimate factor
determining Wu Guangchang
as the suspect in the serial kidnappings?
Was it because he had
a few pieces of bloodied children's clothing?
No.
Apart from the shredded pieces of clothing,
the main reason
Wu Guangchang was ascertained
as the main suspect
was that there was a seventh girl.
We found
signs of abuse on her body.
When she woke up,
she quickly identified Wu Guangchang.
The girl was called... What was it...
Su... Su something.
Su Lingnai?
Yes, that's her name.
It's been too long.
I've forgotten many things.
Go and retrieve the case file.
I'll go to the archive right away.
Mr. Du.
Here's what I think.
Currently, the investigation on Qu Tong
has come to a bottleneck.
Whether you follow the trail
of the audio recording,
search the school buses, or track the vehicles,
it's basically like finding a needle
in a haystack.
My idea
is we switch up our train of thought.
Start with the case from 16 years ago.
A merged investigation.
Do you mean
we should reopen the case?
But that case was concluded long ago.
Although the suspect is dead,
the missing girls were never found.
We can't conclude the case is closed
just based on one survivor's testimony.
Whereas the current case,
it not only has
highly similar characteristics to the suspect,
but the detail of the jingle bells
in the pencil case also happened.
If it weren't someone involved in the case
or a participant in it,
they wouldn't have known such details.
Based on what we have so far,
the missing person case in the Xiling mountains
is definitely not a coincidence.
The person who kidnapped Qu Tong
could very well be
an Apath that we failed to capture back then.
Weizhao.
The expectation the whole of Xinzhou
has on SID,
you know it, right?
Once the old case is reopened,
whether it turns out right or wrong,
SID's reputation
will be on the line.
If it fails...
We will not fail.
Fine.
I will brief the Ministry of Supervision.
Weizhao.
It's your world in the future.
We are old.
Some have left, and some have passed on.
I'm the only one left to lead you bunch of monkeys.
It won't be long before I retire.
Isn't that a good thing?
I can only dream of the day when I retire.
Being able to wake up when you feel like it.
I can go on a trip around the world with my spouse.
When taking the subway,
youngsters have to give up their seats for me.
Dream on.
You don't even have a love interest.
Get lost if you're not going to talk seriously.
Yes, sir.
I'll get lost.
Little monkey.
[The ID "Janitor" you follow has a new update]
(Good day to everyone listening in.)
(Up next, we're bringing you)
(Classics Appreciation
by Enlightening Reading.)
(Broadcasted by Janitor.)
(She can fade away.)
(She can wilt.)
(Anything is fine.)
(But so long as I catch a glimpse of her,)
(a surge of tenderness rushes over me.)
(No matter how hard Humbert)
(tried to be charming,)
(still,)
(a sin is forever a sin.)
So... Sorry.
What's the matter?
There... There was a weird man.
Where? I don't see anybody.
Thank you.
It's fine.
Mister.
Do you sell drinks?
Take it yourself.
The rain is a little heavy.
Don't mind me taking cover here.
Sit down.
The rain's not going to stop any time soon.
What do you do?
SID.
[Guo Shinan]
Mr. Guo.
I'd like to talk to you
about Guo Feiling's case from 16 years ago.
She's been dead for 16 years.
I sent the perpetrator to the underworld
with my own hands.
I was sentenced. I served my time.
What is there to talk about?
Mr. Guo.
I didn't come
to pick on old wounds for no reason.
We're currently working on a case.
It's also a missing teenage girl.
It's the one you just read on the paper.
You saw it wrong. I didn't read it.
Mr. Guo.
There's evidence to show that this case
is possibly related to what happened back then.
Related, how?
The girls were both wearing floral dresses.
Children go missing all the time.
What has it got to do with me?
Three days after,
the culprit sent an audio recording
to the child's parents.
Aside from the girl's cries,
we also hear a noise.
Something like a tin case with bells inside.
Mr. Guo, this is
exactly like what happened to Ling.
That can't be true.
I had killed him.
This girl
is Qu Tong.
She's a sensible child.
Today is the fifth day since she went missing.
Mr. Guo.
The six girls from Lotus Hill's Case are dead.
But this girl
could still be alive.
Please help us find her.
Let Ling
and the other girls
whose bodies weren't even found
rest in peace.
I just have a few questions.
I'll leave right after.
I won't bother you any longer.
Mr. Guo.
The detail about the bells
placed inside a pencil case.
Did you tell anyone about it?
Yes.
Can you give me a name list?
Ling's homeroom teacher.
A relative who was working
at the telecommunications bureau.
The one that called.
The cleaners who worked
near the garbage dump.
They heard bits and pieces.
It was a blur.
Some stuff,
I repeated to many people many times.
I don't quite recall now.
There was also the officer in charge.
Officer Yang.
Yang Zhengfeng.
He knows
the ins and outs the best.
You can ask him.
He was my mentor.
He died in the line of duty.
Let's keep to the timeline.
When did you start investigating?
How did you end up with Wu Guangchang?
At the time,
SID was making no progress.
I was anxious.
I couldn't wait,
so I started investigating myself.
(The garbage disposal site
the culprit mentioned in the call)
[Garbage Disposal Station]
was the only clue I had.
(So I wondered)
(if the person who kidnapped my daughter)
(was perhaps someone who came out of town.)
(Because there's a road
connecting Lotus Island to the city.)
(To avoid the hill,)
(it has to pass by the garbage disposal station.)
Who is it?
Who are you looking for?
Have you seen my daughter?
No.
(I didn't have time to be sad.)
(I knew,)
(the sooner I found clues,)
(the safer Ling would be.)
You mean,
Guo Feiling's kidnapper
took her and left Lotus Hill.
But for some reason,
he stopped his car
before going onto the expressway.
He then took the girl to the nearby garbage dump
and made the call.
Why would he do that?
It doesn't make sense.
He kidnapped a teenager.
Not a small, lightweight toddler.
He ditched his car on the expressway
and brought a grown child
to an unfamiliar place
and assaulted her.
That was much too risky.
Your mentor said the same thing.
The case later
turned into a cross-district serial crime.
They were investigating multiple cases at once.
I couldn't wait.
I couldn't even wait one more day.
So I followed the clue
of it possibly being an outsider.
I checked all the hotels and inns
near Ling's school.
At last,
I found Wu Guangchang.
Yes, Wu Guangchang wasn't a Xinzhou local.
But I heard
he was an inpatient at the nearby hospital.
Why did you think it was him?
A nurse saw
a girl going to see him.
Do you understand?
If you had a teenage daughter
and she suddenly disappeared,
you'd become sensitive
to whatever you saw.
So I followed him.
I didn't see any girl.
But I saw a boy dressed in a school uniform.
The boy was secretly following him.
He claimed a girl from his class
had been skipping class.
He was the class monitor.
The homeroom teacher had told him
to find out what had happened.
The girl who played truant didn't go home.
After school, he said he saw the Wu dude there
to pick someone up.
But when he went to question him,
Wu denied it.
What happened next?
One day,
the boy suddenly called me.
When I rushed there,
I found Wu Guangchang
with a girl.
The girl was fighting him off.
But he forcefully pulled her away.
You mean Su Lingnai?
I told the boy who tipped me off to leave first.
I followed Wu Guangchang back to his house.
(I saw the bastard)
pulling the girl back with him.
I...
Who is it?
Here for the electricity payment.
Come another day.
What are you doing?
Get out!
Mr. Guo.
In your opinion,
did Wu Guangchang
seem like an Apath?
I don't think so.
One last question.
Do you still remember the name of the boy?
The surname is Xu.
I think it was...
Xu Dongyu.
Captain Luo, that's weight-loss tea I just made.
I didn't find
anything special in Xu Dongyu's data.
Second-generation migrant. Came from Yashima.
His family is wealthy.
He currently works as a freelance photographer.
[Xu Dongyu]
What about Su Lingnai?
[Photographer's Certificate]
She's gone.
[Xu Dongyu]
Gone?
She left Xinzhou and went back to her hometown?
Yes.
But not back to Yashima.
It's the home up there.
She's dead.
How old was she when she died?
After the incident, she became a wreck.
Her dance career got nowhere.
And her results were bad.
She somehow managed to get a certificate
from a community college.
With her being young and pretty,
she hung around rich people.
Her life was pretty much a mess,
and she got herself sick.
[Medical Death Certificate]
She died two months ago.
[Su Lingnai]
This is how it ended for the last survivor.
Everything is in one thin file.
Looks like everything
points back to Xu Dongyu.
Relax.
We mean no harm.
We'd just like you to help us
remember some things.
Okay.
[Xu Dongyu]
Did you go to Pingzhao High School?
Yes.
Do you remember a student
named Su Lingnai?
Yes.
Can you tell us about her?
She...
We haven't kept in touch for many years.
She
was a very cheerful girl.
She liked to wear all sorts
of floral dresses.
You summoned me here
because of the case about the girl
aired on the radio, right?
I heard about it on the way.
Then, I'll just get straight to the point.
Regarding the old case
of Wu Guangchang's kidnapping and murder,
how much do you know?
Well...
Not a lot.
Because I was only a kid back then.
The adults
wouldn't let a kid know so much about such a thing.
But a victim's father from back then
said he once met you.
Su Lingnai was saved in time
because you
had tipped off the authorities.
That
happened more than ten years ago. I...
I really don't remember.
When the serial kidnappings
and murders happened,
one of the victims' fathers
went to Pingzhao High School to investigate.
He chanced upon you
who were secretly tailing Wu Guangchang.
So he approached you.
You two suspected
that Wu Guangchang was up to no good.
So you tailed him together.
Remember?
I think...
Yes, that probably happened.
I really don't remember the details.
This guy seems to be tripping over his own words.
Why is he so obtuse?
Sir, do you think he's suspicious?
Just because he mentioned the floral dress?
That's not enough.
Pingzhao High School is a private school.
The students wear school uniforms.
They have strict rules.
Probably only a handful of special students
get exempted from following them
due to personal image requirements.
He remembers Su Lingnai
because she was the only special one in the class.
That's normal.
But...
But
I find it strange.
Back then, Wu Guangchang's case
was the talk of the town.
How come you,
who were personally involved,
couldn't remember?
It's like this.
I...
I fell really sick
in high school one time.
High fever.
It wouldn't come down.
I guess
it wrecked my brain a little.
The thing is, after that ordeal,
my memory deteriorated.
My reaction is a little slow too.
Sorry about that.
Are you married, Mr. Xu?
Where were you on the night
of the 27th?
At home.
By yourself?
I'm single. Of course I was by myself.
What did you do at home?
I read a book.
A book on photography skills.
Mr. Xu.
For the sake of the investigation,
can we check your dashcam?
Sure.
My car is right outside.
Any other questions, officers?
If not,
am I allowed to leave now?
See, I have a job tomorrow.
I have to make preparations.
(Let him go.)
(I've made arrangements.)
(He will be put on)
(24-hour surveillance after he leaves.)
All right.
Thanks for your cooperation.
Thank you.
Please sign your consent.
I heard Pingzhao High School
has strict management.
That's right.
They're always in your face about studying hard.
But it wasn't so bad once you got used to it.
Thanks.
That would probably mean there's no time
for puppy love, huh?
All the teachers would be watching you
when you attempted to speak to a girl.
You'd have to keep your crush secret.
Yes.
Did you have a girl you liked
at the time, Mr. Xu?
A special student like Su Lingnai
must stand out in class, no?
Young boys like pretty girls, yes.
She's already gone.
There's no point talking about this now.
Please.
I'll be off then.
You don't have to walk me out.
Goodbye.
[Monitoring Room]
I only found out that Su Lingnai had died
when I tried calling her in.
Up till this moment,
I've not told him about it.
So...
For Xu Dongyu,
who hadn't kept in touch with her in years,
did he hear about the news
from a zealous friend,
or...
Watch him.
We'll know the answer then.
Okay.
I was just saying the traffic seemed good.
I celebrated too soon.
Looks pretty bad.
-Is the driver hurt?
-No idea.
Has anyone called 120?
Is he all right?
[Emergency]
Are you done?
Mr. Pei.
This is not the way.
It's clear you don't have a healthy daily routine.
Young people nowadays
are night owls.
And they don't like to exercise.
No matter where they are,
they dive into video games
whenever they have a break.
That's no good.
How do you expect your body to heal?
Don't take your young age for granted.
Plenty of people in their 20s and 30s
suffer from osteoporosis nowadays.
Doctor.
A playboy like him
doesn't play video games.
They're too busy socializing.
Look at his face. Pale as a ghost.
It's proof of his corrupt life.
Quite so.
Fortunately, you only suffered
a minor dislocation this time.
I'll set it back in place.
You can come back
and remove the sling in a few days.
But bear in mind.
No smoking, drinking, and women.
Also,
increase your calcium intake.
Otherwise, Mr. Pei,
you'll break at the slightest touch
after ten years.
Thanks, doctor.
You're welcome.
[Ms. Bai, something came up.
I'll see you another time. Apologies.]
Break at the slightest touch.
Take the next exit...
You missed it.
Don't you know how to use the navigator, old man?
Mind your words.
I had to cancel the appointment with my superior,
so I could look after you injured rascal.
Besides, did I say I was driving you home?
I'm actually going to sell you off.
I already have a buyer.
Let's go.
The buyer is waiting to check the goods.
Can I trouble you
to dress me up nicer before selling me off?
Go and get the buyer here.
I can't walk.
(I stepped on the gas instead of the brake.)
(I misread the sign.)
(It was an accident!)
It's just a birthday cake.
No need to hide.
The cake won't assault you.
What's the matter?
Did I remember wrong?
Or do you have other plans tonight?
The doctor said so.
That you should quit smoking, drinking, and women.
Your arm is in a sling.
Better give your daily excursions
a rest tonight.
Instead, enjoy some peace and contentment
[Start navigation]
with me, the middle-aged man.
(Destination, home.)
(Continue on the highlighted route.)
[Justice in the Dark]
Not a single soul in the underworld
Putting on my mask before I leave
In a constant battle with my inner demon
When the dark desire spawns,
I linger before the gate of the abyss
Let me indulge in the freedom to do what I want
Why are you staying silent?
You don't need to save me
I have no empathy,
but I wait for you to knock on my door
They are reading the desires out loud
Envying the others for following their heart
Sorry that you need to save me so
Please don't let go of me
I left the crowd all bloodied
And closed the door to my heart
I maintain my body temperature
Because I was born a human
I don't want to idle alone until you say
That you'll accompany me
however deep the abyss is
How many times do I have to tear my soul apart
To unlock your heart?
How many times do I have to try
To understand the look in your eyes?
I don't want to defend justice until you say
That you'll accompany me
however deep the abyss is
I left the crowd all bloodied
And closed the door to my heart
I maintain my body temperature
Because I was born a human
I don't want to idle alone until you say
That you'll accompany me
however deep the abyss is
How many times do I have to tear my soul apart
To unlock your heart?
How many times do I have to try
To understand the look in your eyes?
I don't want to defend justice until you say
That you'll accompany me
however deep the abyss is