[Justice in the Dark]
[Episode 2]
Father.
Do you know who can dictate life?
[This is a prop bird.
No animals were harmed during the shooting.]
Us,
the ones who are chosen by Heaven.
[Chengguang Club, Shizi Road East Junction]
(Excuse me.)
(Do you know)
(where Chengguang Club is?)
(Chengguang Club is a private club
located at the back.)
What? Are they recruiting deliverymen too?
Hello, we're from the SID.
We have several questions for you.
All right, got it. I'll be there immediately.
You came to work on time again.
Are you heading to Xiaxi District?
Yeah.
Xiao Hanyang interrogated
Miao Xiaowei again this morning.
He got an important lead from it.
What is it?
Miao Xiaowei said
He Zongyi said that his phone
was given to him by his fellow townsman.
Fellow townsman?
Back then, I thought it was strange too.
It's because I didn't hear
that he knew someone from here.
But that phone was too expensive for him.
Only then did he tell me
that during one of his deliveries,
he got into a fight with someone.
He was beaten up.
After that, I didn't know
if the other party regretted his action or what,
but they bought that phone to make it up to him.
Don't you think it's strange too?
If Miao Xiaowei was speaking the truth,
He Zongyi would have had no need to hide the fact
that he got into a fight with someone.
And all of them were staying together.
If the others had no idea,
that means he wasn't seriously injured.
If so, did the other party
need to buy him something that expensive
to make it up to him?
And
I rechecked the evidence yesterday.
Come with me.
Look.
Not only is this suit expensive,
but it's also a traditional suit.
If he was meeting a fellow townsman his age,
He Zongyi could've used the money
[Money Lender, one hundred thousand]
to rent a modern suit.
So, in my opinion,
if he wasn't seeing an elder,
that means...
He was seeing someone powerful.
You're right.
That's what I mean.
You arrived at the same conclusion as I did.
Seems like our hearts are interconnected.
It wasn't me.
Don't tell me it's him.
Tao Ze, I told you before.
Our case details shouldn't be...
I know.
It was purely an accident yesterday.
And don't worry.
We didn't go against the regulations.
What else did he say?
Sticking a note on the victim's head
can be seen as an elder
trying to teach a junior a lesson
or as an act of bullying.
And the culprit
has a narcissistic personality disorder.
So you think
that the person He Zongyi was going to meet
and the person who bought him the phone,
or even
-the 100,000 yuan...
-They're the same person.
We have no evidence.
That's right.
That's why I wish to investigate it further.
All right.
We'll proceed with that.
Tao Ze.
You know what I think about Pei Su.
People who suffer from empathy deficit disorder
are the most dangerous bunch
among Apaths.
They understand fear
and guilt.
However, they have no empathy.
They take themselves to the top of society
and manipulate other people's lives
for pleasure and enjoyment.
And, regarding how those people end up,
I'm sure you've seen plenty of it by now.
Pei Su...
Maybe he's...
It's because you didn't witness it yourself.
Do not let Pei Su get a hold of our case details.
Do not let him turn into someone like that.
We made that promise before.
And even if Pei Su is sensitive to crimes,
those are just his speculations.
You cannot use them as leads.
Just like what our mentor kept telling us.
That's we need to do things based on evidence.
Go now.
[He Zongyi]
Is this the person?
Yes.
Hello, Captain Luo?
Understood.
I'll see if there are any witnesses.
Excuse me. When He Zongyi
was delivering the goods,
have you ever seen
or heard
that he got into a fight?
A fight?
Does it count if he was beaten up?
It happened at that door.
Do you have surveillance cameras here?
We do.
Captain Luo, I told Wu to do
an investigation just now.
The guy who beat up He Zongyi
is called Zhang Donglan.
He's the son of Zhaonan Group's CEO.
That means...
He's Chief Zhang's nephew.
That's right.
Did you find out why he beat him up?
No.
They said they had no idea
why they got into a fight.
However, He Zongyi didn't retaliate.
So the fight didn't last long.
He was fine in the end.
And the fight was over.
On the day the crime happened,
did the staff who saw He Zongyi say
that they witnessed
any abnormal behaviors from He Zongyi?
They said he was acting normally.
However, one of them said
that He Zongyi tried
to inquire about a private club
on the day the crime happened.
Find out where it is.
I need to know its name.
This club is crucial to our investigation.
Please wait a moment. I'll ask them right now.
Hello?
Luo,
Miao Xiaowei dropped another important lead.
What is it?
We followed the lead,
which was He Zongyi's suit,
and inquired about the meeting from him.
He said he had never heard He Zongyi mention
that he knew any elders
or powerful figures in Xinzhou.
But on that day,
He Zongyi inquired about a place from him.
What place?
Captain Luo, I got the name.
The place is called...
-Chengguang Club.
Tao Ze,
do you miss me already?
Were you at Chengguang Club
two nights ago?
I was.
What's the matter?
Were you together with someone
named Zhang Donglan?
Yes.
Captain Luo, how did it go?
Have you confirmed that it was the suspect?
Yes.
The Chengguang Club you found
was actually a private club
that Zhang Donglan designated.
And during the day the crime happened,
Zhang Donglan was at Chengguang Club.
Did you bring that person back?
The guys at Xiaxi District
didn't obstruct you, did they?
They didn't.
This case
has implicated the SID.
But now,
we do have a solid reason to bring him back now.
The guys at Xiaxi District were happy
to let him go
when they heard that he's Chief Zhang's nephew.
That's why we brought him back.
However,
he's a tough nut to crack.
[Zhang Donglan, Nephew of Zhang Zhaojin]
Yes.
I might have beaten him up before.
So?
What's wrong with that?
I've beaten up plenty of people.
However, this truly has nothing to do with me.
You can ask Pei Su if you don't believe me.
Didn't I tell you already?
I was together with him on that day.
Officer Tao,
listen up.
If it weren't for Mr. Pei,
do you know what I would do
if you detained me like this?
I guess Mr. Tao will have a hard time.
Captain Luo,
a person with the surname Pei
wants to see Mr. Tao.
A person with the surname Pei?
Is it him again?
Please have a seat.
You really take this place as your home, huh?
Where's Tao Ze?
He's busy.
Officer Luo,
the coffee you have here
has a strange fragrance.
Do you need me to bring you guys
some top-quality coffee?
On the night of the third,
which was two nights ago,
where were you,
who were you together with,
and what did you do
between 8 to 11 PM?
Think twice before answering me.
Are you guys in charge of the case now?
If so, you should treat me better.
I would have no obligation
to answer your questions
if no one requested your interference.
I can leave at any time
if you upset me.
So, I have to please you?
Fine.
Tell me then.
How can I please you?
Do you want me to sing you a song?
Or do you want me to buy you some candy?
I'm sorry. I do mind it.
I have
pharyngitis.
World peace would dawn upon us
if you became mute.
I can't stand that.
Have you seen this person before?
I have.
Tell me the time and location.
I saw him two nights ago
at the entrance of a cafe in Xindong.
You remember him this clearly
even though you only saw him once?
The features on his forehead
are too obvious to forget.
You know this too.
I've been like this since I was young.
I'll remember something for the entire month
once I see it.
Have you been
to Chengguang Club two nights ago
between 8 to 11 PM?
Can you testify for Zhang Donglan?
Around 8:30 PM,
he received me at the entrance
of Chengguang Club.
I left the place around midnight.
I did greet him
at these two time slots.
Are those two the only time slots?
There was three and a half hour
between our meetings.
Officer, I'm sure you wouldn't believe me
if I said I was together with him
for the entire period.
That means
you cannot prove
that he had no time to commit the crime that night.
I cannot.
But someone else can.
If it's necessary,
I can make everyone
who got into contact with him on that night
come here within two hours.
Are you hinting at me
that you guys are planning
to forge false evidence
using your money and intimacy?
What?
Even so, it'll only involve
several models from the club.
Captain Luo, even a person like you is afraid
that you cannot find out the truth?
No.
I'll tell you
why it's impossible for Zhang Donglan
to be the culprit.
If it was him,
he would not need to kill him personally.
He could have hired someone
and kidnapped the victim for him.
The population of Xiaxi
consists of a floating population
from all islands.
People disappear every day.
No one will notice
when a single person is missing.
Killers are usually irrational
when they commit a crime.
Are you saying
that it's a crime of passion then?
If so, Officer Luo,
besides the blow
that knocked out the victim,
were there any other blunt force injuries
on the victim's body?
Who's doing the interrogation now?
Sounds like it's a no to me.
If so, I suggest you focus
on the victim's relatives and friends.
This might be an inside job.
They might have gone way back with each other.
Are you trying to clear Zhang Donglan's name now?
I'm just taking the matter on its merits.
A crime of passion is defined
as a murder committed by the culprit by accident
or someone unknown to the victim
when they lose their rationality
in a short period of time.
If so, the culprit did it out of spite.
Their rage will reach its peak in a short period.
After that, they'll vent it in an extreme way.
Facing a helpless victim
who was knocked unconscious,
I think the victim's head
would've been bashed in.
However,
if it were someone I longed to kill,
I would choose...
Strangulation.
Strangling a victim
is a type
of prolonged murder that's truly enjoyable.
Sometimes, it might
even turn people on.
Do you think a person who's dying of thirst
has the time to sit down and enjoy tea?
In my opinion,
this process is unnatural.
So, you're saying
that killing people is just like enjoying tea?
It's just a metaphor.
Don't split hairs.
I'm saying
that Zhang Donglan isn't the culprit.
If he did kill him,
he would not dispose of his corpse.
If he did try to dispose of his corpse,
he wouldn't dispose of it in an alley in Xiaxi,
which was unfamiliar territory to him.
I'm speaking from a rational perspective.
According to my hunch,
Zhang Donglan's father,
Zhang Zhaolin,
is the CEO of the famous Zhaonan Group.
And his uncle is the chief of SID.
Moreover, he has been pampered all his life.
And he's a good-for-nothing.
Even if he's angry, at most, he'll insult you.
Even if committing heinous crimes isn't illegal,
I assume he doesn't have the guts to do so.
So, Captain Luo,
can I go now?
Sign here.
Confirm your statement.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Don't mention it.
I did it for Tao Ze.
This is standard procedure.
I wasn't sincere in thanking you.
Captain Luo,
don't you think there's a bigger doubt
you need to investigate?
Why is the SID
involved in this case?
This case of yours
has attracted public attention
for no reason
from the start.
And it's a serial killing from the get-go.
That's why you guys were involved.
Normally,
after a short period of abnormal attention,
people will lose interest.
But at this moment,
Zhang Donglan had to intervene in the fray.
If it was him,
to the SID,
which people refer
to as the last hope of Xinzhou,
it would be a huge scandal.
Is this merely a coincidence?
Or is there
a mastermind behind it?
This is normal, anyway.
It's just like that saying.
What was it again?
There's nothing new
in Xinzhou anyway.
The surveillance footage from cameras
outside Chengguang Club and on Shizi Road,
and the pictures.
I've sent all of them to your phone.
I might be a little nosy here.
[Crossroad Surveillance Camera Footage]
Since you guys have found Chengguang Club,
I believe you guys will find this too.
Just treat it
as if a normal civilian
is providing you guys with some leads.
Pei Su.
It's next week, right?
It's been seven years.
Are you still dwelling on it?
Big-Eyed Lan, what's the matter?
The guys at Xiaxi District
arrested Miao Xiaowei.
What?
[Trial Room]
How did it go?
That brat said
he might have drunk a little that night.
He saw someone pestering his sister.
He thought it was a hooligan.
That's why he beat him up on impulse.
After that, he forgot about the person
he had beaten up.
I showed him a picture of the victim.
He only said that he kind of remembers him.
And, according to him,
he never apologized to anyone
or bought anyone a phone.
I think he was speaking the truth.
Even now, he doesn't realize
that he's in the wrong for beating someone up.
Maybe it was someone else.
It's hard to say.
Have you told someone
to investigate Zhang Donglan's alibi?
I told Qiao to retrieve the surveillance footage
in Chengguang Club.
By the way,
was Pei Su here just now?
He left long ago.
Listen, that brat
is crossing the line here.
I told you not to let him get his way, right?
Look at how arrogant he is right now.
Pei Su said
that Zhang Donglan
was flirting with girls
when he wasn't beside him.
He should have been in Chengguang Club
for the entire duration.
If Zhang Donglan has no time to commit the crime,
at least the SID's name is clear.
That doesn't matter
right now.
Why?
Just now, Xiao Hanyang called us
and said that Cui Hongliang
had arrested Miao Xiaowei.
And Cui Hongliang
identified him as a major suspect.
What?
What's the evidence?
It was He Zongyi's phone.
Wu and the rest located his phone
using GPS.
The phone buyer confessed immediately.
He said Miao Xiaowei was the one
who sold the phone to him.
After that, Xiaxi District Patrol Detachment
found the fingerprints of Miao Xiaowei
and the victim on the phone.
The chain of evidence isn't complete
with just a phone.
This can only prove that Miao Xiaowei
stole He Zongyi's phone.
It's not enough to prove that he's the culprit.
He gave them his statement too.
When they interrogated him
and asked him where he got his phone,
he paused for a second
and said that he picked it up at the crime scene
after he heard that someone is having a fight.
It's like he's turning himself in.
Yeah.
It's been many years
since we encountered such an honest culprit.
There's even more.
They even discovered track marks
on Miao Xiaowei's arms.
He's a drug addict too?
Don't you think
it's too much of a coincidence?
This is unbelievable.
Initially, it was a kill-and-dump.
But now, it's involving the Zhaonan Group
and a drug crime.
Oh, yeah.
What did Chief Zhang
think about our interrogation
of Zhang Donglan?
He didn't comment on it to avoid suspicion.
What?
Du Yuliang, Acting Chief of SID]
Chief Du?
Chief Du.
What are you doing here in person?
You already brought Zhang Donglan here.
Of course I have to be here.
I'm doing it for Chief Zhang's sake.
If we detain Zhang Donglan,
other people won't be able
to get the goods on the SID.
Brat,
you're afraid that people might stir up
a commotion over their relationship.
You think I don't know that?
This case involves Chief Zhang.
The Ministry of Supervision
is paying much attention to it.
Zhang wants to avoid suspicion,
so I shall take over his position
for the time being.
It's that serious?
Come with me.
Captain Luo,
what about He Zongyi's call history
and the surveillance footage
of Chengguang Club?
I'll take care of the call history.
You can take the footage.
Continue your investigation.
There's no overtime pay here.
Okay.
Big-Eyed Lan, time to work overtime.
Are you saying
that the place of disposal
has something special about it?
Yes.
We checked the soles of the victim's shoes.
They're clean
even though the crime scene
is filled with mud and garbage.
And Miao Xiaowei has confirmed
that He Zongyi did wear that pair of shoes
when he went outside.
Basically, we can eliminate the possibility
of the culprit changing the victim's shoes.
If the culprit intended to go to another place
to commit the crime,
why would he choose a risky place like that
to dispose of the victim's body?
Unless...
Continue.
Unless that place
has something that people dare not talk about
even if they see them.
When Miao Xiaowei was interrogated,
he said
that he heard someone fighting
near the crime scene.
But when we asked him
what he saw after heading downstairs,
he hesitated to speak.
That means
certain events
will happen in that place frequently,
which people dare not talk about.
Luo Weizhao,
what are you trying to say?
Chief Du,
at first, I only had my doubts.
But when Chief Zhang told me about it,
I knew
the fugitive was just an excuse
to get us involved in the case.
I'm afraid the drug overdose cases
that happened in Xiaxi a few months ago
are the cases
we should pay attention to.
Just now, Qiao told me
that they discovered
track marks on Miao Xiaowei's arms.
That's how I was able to confirm my speculation.
This is a file containing reports
from anonymous individuals.
It contains the three cases
you mentioned just now.
Deputy Director Cui Hongliang,
who is in command of Xiaxi District,
is the drug syndicate's protective umbrella.
What's your evidence?
Just like what you've noticed,
the crime scenes of the three cases
are in the same area.
All of them are in the same area
where He Zongyi's body was disposed to?
But these are just speculations.
We lack conclusive evidence.
That's why Chief Zhang
wants us to get involved.
The leads are many and complicated.
Many things aren't as simple as they seem.
That's why
I didn't show it to you before this.
If these reports are valid,
we'll know why his body was disposed of.
And we'll know why everyone
wasn't willing to talk about it.
As for He Zongyi,
it's either he was colluding
with the drug traffickers,
or the culprit moved his body there
because the culprit
knew some inside information.
The culprit wants those drug traffickers
to pay for the victim's life.
These doubts alone
are not enough.
We still lack conclusive evidence.
Otherwise, the SID still has no right
to join the investigation officially
without it.
Tell Tao Ze and the rest
to continue investigating the leads
Zhang Donglan provides.
As Chief Zhang is involved,
it concerns the SID.
As for the other lead,
you can investigate it alone.
Do not alert the guys at Xiaxi District for now.
Report to me immediately if there's any update.
Yes, sir.
We'll investigate both leads.
I'll request an official intervention
when I find conclusive evidence.
All right, resume your work.
Weizhao,
Xiaxi District is a complicated place.
Many drug traffickers aren't afraid of death.
Don't forget about your mentor's instructions.
Do not act recklessly.
Don't worry about me, Du.
Mr. Tao, I've reviewed all of them.
I think I'm going blind.
How did it go?
Zhang Donglan exited the place
four times in total.
The total time he spent was 40 minutes.
However, each exit was short.
At around 9 PM,
the dinner in Chengguang Club was over.
Zhang Donglan left the room,
and, for the first time, his face was caught
by the surveillance camera in the courtyard.
He spent some time in the courtyard.
After that, he went back inside.
At 9:45 PM,
he was seen in the courtyard again.
He went to the courtyard with a girl,
and they spoke for a while.
After that, they walked into the forest.
That makes sense.
The surveillance camera outside the hotel
recorded Zhang Donglan
coming out of the forest with a girl.
Since his schedule was so packed,
it seemed like
he had no time to commit the crime.
Did the surveillance camera record He Zongyi?
There are too many cameras outside.
I'm reviewing them one by one.
Captain Luo said
that we could try checking out
the surveillance camera on Shizi Road.
Shizi Road?
Why?
I don't know.
But I think
Pei Su said it.
Pei Su?
Mr. Tao,
actually, I've wanted
to ask you this for a long time.
Can I ask you now?
Is it about Pei Su?
Who exactly is Pei Su?
Why does Captain Luo
still value his suggestions
even though he treats him like his sworn enemy?
And what do they mean by seven years?
What happened seven years ago?
Seven years ago?
Who did you hear that from?
I heard Captain Luo saying that
when I was at the entrance.
But I wasn't eavesdropping on them.
So,
what exactly is going on?
Pei Su reported a suicide case
when Weizhao and I
were handling a case.
It was seven years ago.
Weizhao and I just graduated
from university back then.
You know this too.
He was born in Xinzhou, and he had good grades.
And there were not many people
who were more capable than him.
That's why
when we first started patrolling the community,
Weizhao tried his best
to save everyone from everything.
When they told him
to mediate a community conflict,
he turned it into a fight instead.
However, there weren't many cases
we could investigate in the community.
The first and only case
we received
was Pei Su's.
Mom?
[Seven years ago]
(According to our investigation,)
(all evidence led to suicide.)
(However, Pei Su never believed it.)
-(He was very agitated.)
-No.
My father is an Apath.
I'm sure he killed my mother.
It's impossible for my mother
to take her own life.
It's my father.
(He insisted that his father)
(was related to his mother's death.)
It's impossible for my mother
to take her own life.
to take her own life!
That's impossible!
Mr. Pei,
although we've revoked the case,
there are still
some procedures we need to go through.
Please cooperate with us.
Okay.
Sorry for the trouble.
Wait!
Officer Luo,
is there anything else?
There are still some doubts about this case.
Don't tell me Captain Luo
went against the rules
and helped him investigate the case?
That's impossible. That's not how he works.
Technically, it's not an investigation.
Back then, there was conclusive evidence
for the case.
So we had nothing to investigate.
Although his father, Pei Chengyu,
didn't pay enough attention to his family,
he had no motive to murder his mother.
If so, Pei Su must be...
In the end,
Weizhao was the one who broke the news to him.
(I don't know what Weizhao told him back then.)
(But since then,)
(they've been at odds with each other.)
(We thought that Pei Su wasn't able)
(to get over his mother's death)
because his subconscious mind
might be resenting his mother
for abandoning him.
However,
he never listens to us.
(Although we had taken care of him for seven years,)
(one)
(was rash)
(and unrestrained,)
(while the other was meticulous)
(and aloof.)
(When they're together,)
(they'll argue non-stop)
(over something silly.)
(They've been contacting each other less and less)
(since Pei Su inherited
his father's inheritance.)
(I think it might be because...)
[Letter of Report]
(they still haven't let go of the past.)
If so, why did he insist
that his father was the one who killed his mother?
His father, Pei Chengyu,
is the CEO of Pei Group.
He's a talented businessman.
He doesn't spend time with his family usually.
I guess Pei Su firmly believes
that his father's absence
was related to his mother's suicide.
It's pretty cruel
to a child.
If so, has his relationship
with his father gotten any better?
His father was caught in a traffic accident
three years ago.
He is in a persistent vegetative state now.
Don't tell me
both of them are Apaths.
Although we couldn't find anything conclusive,
Weizhao held a grudge against him.
He said he found out
that this child has a special talent.
What talent?
He's a genius at committing crimes.
(His memories)
(are cruel.)
(They resurface, detail by detail,)
(recalling the scene that happened that night.)
[Du Jia]
Mr. Pei, what's the matter?
I have an update.
What is it about this time?
It's about Julien.
[8th March, with my little brother, Chen Zhen]
8th March?
Little brother?
Shoo, Frying Pan!
Get off.
[The trade location has been changed
to the vacant land at Golden Triangle]
The vacant land at Golden Triangle?
Hello, Tao Ze. Go ahead.
Captain Luo, we found something.
Around 8:50 PM,
He Zongyi appeared at Shizi Road,
which was nearby Chengguang Club,
with a kraft paper bag.
Kraft paper bag?
That's right.
The kraft paper bag
[Chengguang Club, Shizi Road East Junction]
didn't appear at the crime scene.
But we suspect
the "one hundred thousand" note
taped on the victim's forehead
was torn down from this kraft paper bag.
If so, that means He Zongyi
met the money lender last night.
That's right.
Judging from the shape of the kraft paper parcel,
it should contain the 100,000 yuan.
What else is there?
He Zongyi smoked a cigarette
under the street lamp for a moment.
He answered a phone call too. He left at 9:30 PM.
[Twelve seconds]
9:30 PM?
That number doesn't exist either.
Either?
Is there anyone else besides him?
It's nothing.
Did you find out where he went?
I did.
When he left,
he wasn't heading toward Chengguang Club.
He headed in another direction.
There was a bus stop over there.
Lan Qiao and I retrieved the road camera footage.
We did locate He Zongyi.
He got on Trolleybus Route 34.
And he got off the trolleybus
at Wenchang Junction Stop at around 10 PM.
If that's the case,
that means Miao Xiaowei's testimony
doesn't add up.
It's impossible for He Zongyi
to be in Xiaxi District at this time.
That's right.
Good job.
Gather all of our men.
Search the entire Wenchang Road tomorrow.
Yes, sir.
Pei Su,
why are you here again?
Are you here to deliver some warmth to us again?
All right, don't be anxious.
I'll notify them for you later.
I'll ask them to give you a stack of VIP fines, okay?
Do I have to be fined
even when I'm accompanying my friend's sister
to cooperate with your investigation?
Captain Luo,
don't you think you're being too harsh
on a normal civilian?
Zhang Ying?
[Zhang Ying, Zhang Donglan's younger sister]
Let's cut it short.
Do you know this guy?
Can't you treat a lady nicer?
It's fine. Don't be afraid.
Miss Zhang,
this is the reception room,
not the interrogation room.
Your brother is a major suspect now.
This concerns a homicide.
Every single word you utter
is of utmost importance.
Understood?
It's fine.
Just tell him the truth.
Captain Luo arrived at the same conclusion as me.
We both believe
that it's impossible for your brother
to be related to this case.
I saw that guy before.
Back then, I was doing my internship
at a trading company.
I was working overtime that day.
I wanted to buy some coffee as I felt sleepy.
But for some reason,
one guy kept following me.
He kept mumbling.
He asked me if I knew a guy called Feng Nian
or Feng Nianguo.
His surname is Feng?
Is it Nianguo or Nian?
I don't know.
Anyway, that sounded like what he uttered.
He doesn't seem like he's from Xinzhou.
He spoke with an accent.
I didn't know which word he was uttering.
I don't know
if it was a nickname
or his true name.
I was so afraid back then.
I wanted to avoid him.
When did that happen?
It's been some time.
After that?
Did he retaliate?
No.
He was just dodging while protecting his face.
Only then did I find out
that he was pretty young.
I thought I misunderstood him.
I dragged my brother immediately.
I told him to stop.
Who else was there back then?
My boyfriend was there too.
My brother was drunk that day.
So my boyfriend drove.
They went there together.
Seems like all nice girls
already have boyfriends, huh?
Who was it? He was pretty quick.
It's Rongshun's Zhou Hongchuan.
We met each other at Chengguang Club.
So it's the law firm
that Pei Group employed, right?
Captain Luo, you're pretty resourceful, aren't you?
What happened after that?
Did you see He Zongyi after that?
Captain Luo,
my brother will never kill anyone.
He Zongyi's dormmate said
He Zongyi brought a new phone back to the dorm
and said the other party compensated him with it
after he got involved in a fight.
Did you know about that?
I didn't.
My brother told me nothing.
I don't think that'd be the case either.
My brother only punched him
because he wanted to stand up for me.
After that,
we never saw him again.
My brother will never kill a person
because of a trivial matter like this.
It's impossible for him to kill anyone.
Captain Luo,
please trust me, okay?
Okay.
Don't worry.
Since your brother didn't kill anyone,
he'll be fine here.
Zhang.
Yes, sir?
Sorry about that.
There's a procedure we need to go through.
Please follow my colleague
and give
your statement.
It'll be fine.
Go now. Don't be afraid.
I'll wait here for you.
Goodbye, Captain Luo.
Where's Tao Ze?
Thanks to the lead provided
by a civilian who's eager to help,
he's rushing off his feet in the city
to investigate the case.
He hasn't found it yet?
Pei Su,
don't you think you're too concerned
about this case?
I remember someone once telling me
that everything that happens in the world
will leave traces behind.
And these traces
are the only evidence
that can prove our subjective will.
They're very important.
Where's the badge?
(Everything that happens in the world)
(will leave traces behind.)
(And these traces are the only evidence)
(that can prove our subjective will.)
The door and windows were locked.
There were no signs of a break-in.
The security system in the house,
which was considered
the most advanced back then,
was untouched.
She put on makeup,
changed into a dress,
and even played music.
There was a sense of ceremony to it.
And a written will was on the table.
After verification,
we determined that the handwriting
belonged to the victim.
The person who wrote the letter
was obviously depressed.
She was an adult.
There were no signs
of drugs in her body.
There was no wound on her body either.
Those were all the pieces of evidence
we gathered back then.
You were the one who reported the case.
You reached the crime scene earlier than we did.
Unless you tell me
that you were hiding some sort of evidence,
it was most certainly suicide.
Back then, I told you
everything that happens in the world
leaves traces behind,
only if they're true events.
Pei Su,
you might have a special hunch.
You might be good at digging out
people's true feelings.
However, we can't solve cases with hunches alone.
Fine.
Speaking about psychology,
I don't know
if you have heard of this foreign theory before.
According to the theory,
if someone wishes to take their life,
they might suddenly confess
their feelings to their family members
in a certain way.
You heard
what she said back then too.
When I am down
And oh, my soul, so weary
When troubles come
And my heart burdened be
Then, I am still
She's been dead for seven years.
The case was closed long ago.
Evidence that was related to the case is gone too.
You can choose to remember her
as a sort of emotional sustenance.
However, it's meaningless
for you to dwell on the past.
I do not accept your conclusion,
Officer Luo.
[Justice in the Dark]
Not a single soul in the underworld
Putting on my mask before I leave
In a constant battle with my inner demon
When the dark desire spawns,
I linger before the gate of the abyss
Let me indulge in the freedom to do what I want
Why are you staying silent?
You don't need to save me
I have no empathy,
but I wait for you to knock on my door
They are reading the desires out loud
Envying the others for following their heart
Sorry that you need to save me so
Please don't let go of me
I left the crowd all bloodied
And closed the door to my heart
I maintain my body temperature
Because I was born a human
I don't want to idle alone until you say
That you'll accompany me
however deep the abyss is
How many times do I have to tear my soul apart
To unlock your heart?
How many times do I have to try
To understand the look in your eyes?
I don't want to defend justice until you say
That you'll accompany me
however deep the abyss is
I left the crowd all bloodied
And closed the door to my heart
I maintain my body temperature
Because I was born a human
I don't want to idle alone until you say
That you'll accompany me
however deep the abyss is
How many times do I have to tear my soul apart
To unlock your heart?
How many times do I have to try
To understand the look in your eyes?
I don't want to defend justice until you say
That you'll accompany me
however deep the abyss is