(Episode 4)
I kept on investigating the case,
and it looks like Yang Chul Ki is definitely the murderer.
The evidence is clear as day.
Someone definitely helped him out in the process.
- Mr. Nam. - Yes?
On the day of the Ahyeon-dong Murder Case,
a delivery man was apparently there as well.
Could you check it out?
A delivery man?
Since it's been seven years,
I doubt there would be any documents or CCTV footages.
But please look into it just in case.
Check if he met anyone...
on his way home...
from the crime scene...
or stopped by anywhere. Look for everything.
But I don't get the correlation between that delivery man...
and the murder case...
He doesn't reply back when I talk.
My gosh.
- Hello, sir. - Hello.
How many CCTV cameras do you have in this building?
I'm not sure about that.
(13:05pm to 14:00pm, November 21, 2012,)
(deliveries in the direction of Star Hostel)
There are three outside...
- and one inside, right? - That's correct.
- Is that one for the elevator? - Yes.
For how many years are the archives stored?
They're not in chronological order...
since he's stored all the records from the past decade.
The dates aren't marked, so it'll be difficult.
That's fine.
Thank you.
There are two CCTV cameras.
(Fax, lamination, copy)
All right.
Oh, my. This is no joke.
What?
What? Hold on.
I recognize that face.
Give me a minute.
Wait, look at her.
Do you recognize her?
It's her.
She's the one from the trial.
Don't we have the same one from a different angle?
From where she was walking from?
Yes, we do.
Hold on.
Isn't that Yang Chul Ki?
Do you have her number?
Go in. Bye.
I have one question.
You know Yang Chul Ki, don't you?
You've met this delivery man seven years ago.
The delivery man gave you a parcel, and you handed it to Yang Chul Ki.
Why did you meet him on that day?
I don't remember.
This is very important to me, so please answer.
- What was inside the parcel? - Why should I tell you?
It may be important to you, but what does it have to do with me?
I'll pay you handsomely.
Get lost.
Why did you meet Yang Chul Ki?
Just tell me that.
If you're dying to know, ask him yourself.
And don't you dare come see me ever again.
You scumbag.
A lawyer who's famous is different, indeed.
Thanks to you, I get to come here.
You must want to know something,
seeing how you're here this late at night.
If I don't get you out of prison,
what do you think Prosecutor Seo would do to you?
Would she be able to find evidence for the murder or not?
I'm curious.
What did that crazy wench tell you?
You're right. Prosecutor Seo is one crazy wench, isn't she?
By the way, on the day of the murder,
you met with Jang Young Mi.
So what?
She also met someone else apart from you.
I have no idea what you're blabbering on about.
Is that right?
If that's the case, don't you worry.
You can take your time remembering what happened...
while rotting in prison.
Chairman Song would want you to take me out of here.
Why did you meet her on that day? Tell me.
And what was in the parcel that the delivery man gave?
I'm not sure.
Being imprisoned for too long has failed my memory.
I can't remember.
(Court of Criminal Division 3)
Defendant Yang Chul Ki has committed similar assaults...
2 years ago and 6 months ago as well.
His reason was that the laborers didn't give...
the right amount of commission.
It's highly unlikely that he was trying to protect...
the laborers as their team leader.
I hope you acknowledge that this is...
a habitual special assault case committed by a thug...
with seven previous convictions...
because of privilege on a construction company.
That is all.
Defense?
Proceed.
I will not...
make any counter-argument.
What are you trying to get at?
Do I have to tell the prosecutor about my strategy?
You're not going to get Yang Chul Ki out, right?
I'm sure the murder case is related to your brother's...
Stop paying attention to my brother's case.
I don't plan on getting you involved. And this case...
is an assault case, not a murder case.
Then, defend him only for the assault case.
I will look into the murder case.
(Restricted Number)
I guess your memory is coming back to you now.
How are they related?
The girl who died in Ahyeon-dong.
And the delivery man who died in a car accident.
Are you curious...
about how your little brother died?
What do you mean?
I asked you a question, you jerk.
I can't believe...
the Almighty Lee Tae Kyung is all worked up.
What is it?
I thought it didn't matter.
How are you involved in my brother's case?
I'm not involved at all.
I couldn't care less about how a mere delivery man...
died.
I'm pretty sure you will rot here...
for the rest of your life.
Come on.
You will have to get me out of here...
no matter what.
Will Lee Tae Kyung get Yang Chul Ki out?
Once he finds out everything...
I knew that he was a tiger cub when I took him in.
The wind is bound to shake things up.
I can't defy nature.
You crazy jerk. This is too expensive.
Stop acting like a country boy.
You're going to be a fancy lawyer.
You should act like one.
Once you become a lawyer,
you should suit up.
Don't you know that a good tie completes a suit?
Goodness. You don't know anything.
I didn't pass the third round yet.
Well, you'll pass...
as long as you don't curse out the interviewer.
No?
Open it up.
- Why? - Do you see the clover there?
The designer who made ties for Hiddink came up with that tie.
It's a lucky tie.
You never listen, do you?
Just make sure you put that on.
I got it.
(Lee Tae Ju)
When you graduate, you should go study abroad.
You said that all those famous chefs went abroad to study.
Forget it.
I don't have to because I'm already that good.
Starting now, I'm the breadwinner.
I will get you back to school, send you abroad,
and marry you off. I'll take care of everything.
Are you kidding me?
Who are you to tell me what to do with my life?
You should quit your job right now.
Once I attend the Judicial Research and Training Institute,
I'll get a regular paycheck.
So you just need to focus on going back to school, okay?
Once I go back to school,
I'm going to start dating first.
Like a player.
You might end up becoming an uncle next year.
Will that be okay for you?
What's that on your hair? Come here.
What is it?
I've been too nice to you lately.
Come on, use your words.
Come here.
- No, wait. - I've been too nice.
Mr. Lawyer.
You won't listen when I talk nicely to you.
You come here.
- Come here. - Mr. Lawyer.
Come here. Should I go to you? Or will you come to me?
- Did you just kick at me? - I have a knife too!
- You squirrel. - Bring it on.
You'll be sorry. I'm serious.
- Hold on. - My gosh.
Wait!
Are you curious about how your little brother died?
The chairman is doing well, right?
What chairman?
Darn you.
This is getting interesting.
Lee Tae Kyung...
found out about Jang Young Mi.
Don't make mistakes.
Mistakes?
That reminds me.
I think you might have to...
give me a bit more than what was promised.
I shouldn't make mistakes.
You know?
Mr. Guk, this jerk, Yang Chul Ki...
Prosecutor Seo, we have a problem.
Please explain why the prosecutor in charge has changed.
It's my way of telling you to focus on the investigation.
You can let another prosecutor take care of the trial.
It's only an assault case of a thug. I don't need that much support.
I don't understand...
why you had to change the prosecutor in charge.
You.
You have an ulterior agenda behind this case.
You interrogated Yang Chul Ki about a murder case.
It was a simple interrogation regarding the assault case.
I was just checking his previous convictions.
Why did you want this case even if you had to take it...
from the previous prosecutor in charge?
Because of this,
it is my judgment and decision as your supervisor...
that you've lost your impartiality.
The trial is right around the corner. How can...
the new prosecutor take over the trial with just a few papers?
This is outside pressure.
Seo Yeon Ah.
Is our organization a joke to you?
No.
I'm doing this because I want to prevent that from happening.
I will not let someone else take over my trial.
If that happens,
I'll jump in with a bomb.
Bomb?
Goodness. She's making a royal mess here.
What is it?
Why is...
the organization trying so hard to cover up...
You think you're all grown up.
Since when did you ask me why?
Just follow my orders.
Why is it so hard for you to follow my orders?
Is it because you didn't go to college in Seoul?
This is exactly why I didn't work with prosecutors...
who didn't go to colleges in Seoul.
If you do this, I have nothing to say to my junior...
Will they promote you to the Assistant Prosecutor General?
If you have no connections, you must do everything to get some.
Why are you so dense?
Make sure you deal with Prosecutor Seo.
You'll be reappointed after this case is over.
Let's not lose something big over something petty.
Okay?
Woo Yong, should I just...
let Yang Chul Ki get released and kill him?
The more I dig it up, the weirder it is.
Seven years ago,
he was definitely involved with Tae Ju too.
Don't you think he's the guy who killed my brother?
Let's get him out of there and find out what happened.
No, I don't think we should let this guy go.
Prosecutor Seo has been replaced.
Yang Chul Ki is...
definitely not alone.
If it doesn't feel right, don't let him out.
A guy like him is nothing.
I'll manage.
Therefore, this was a case of mild violence...
in the process of a fight for a privilege...
which broke out in the midst of a reconstruction process.
There was only mild violence involved.
However, Yang Chul Ki, the defendant,
already had seven previous charges of violence.
Well, despite that, he used violence once again,
so the nature of his crime is...
very serious.
However, this case is an accidental homicide...
that broke out as he was working on duty...
as a team leader of laborers.
Therefore, the prosecution demands...
10 months of imprisonment...
and 2 years in probation to Yang Chul Ki,
according to Article 286 of the Criminal Code,
negligence in the conduct of business.
He is a murder suspect.
I'm the prosecutor who investigated this case.
I would like to explain the parts that were left out.
I request the right to speak.
I will dismiss the request as it was not previously agreed on.
Defense? Make your final statement.
The defendant, Yang Chul Ki,
is a key suspect of a murder case.
(Court)
The defendant, Yang Chul Ki,
is a key suspect of a murder case.
To be more exact,
he is under suspicion of the prosecution as a culprit...
of an unresolved murder case from seven years ago.
However, we aren't holding this trial for that unresolved case.
We're here to deal with an assault case...
which broke out on May 30, 2019, at a construction site...
in Nonhyeon-dong.
If the prosecution believes the defendant is...
a suspect of that murder, they should bring in evidence...
to indict him again for the murder,
and judge him after going through the proper procedures.
Of course, he deserves to be criticized...
for using violence again when he has previous charges.
But he deeply regrets what he has done,
he settled the case with the victim,
and the victim does not want him to be punished.
Above all, please take into consideration...
that he ended up using violence to protect the livelihood...
of other laborers on the site. That's all.
Do you know what you have done?
He's a murderer.
This was an assault case.
He's a key suspect of a murder.
We don't know who else could die if he gets released.
This isn't the end. Several people have died.
Then find the evidence and indict him for murder.
You couldn't even prove a simple assault.
Stop whining and claiming he's a murderer without evidence.
Why have you changed so much?
Everyone changes.
You have wrinkles next to your eyes.
You should go get some facials.
Is your paycheck not much? But your father is rich.
You still have your darned way with words.
You know, the tongue is a muscle. You can develop it by working out.
The court isn't a cheap soap opera.
Cheap soap operas get the best ratings.
I hope you won't get any uglier than this.
I mean it.
(Court)
(Seoul Detention Center)
Hey, thug.
Are you here for me?
(True correction, bright future)
You need to keep your promise.
Of course.
But I can't do it today.
Do you seriously want to die?
Come on, you're scaring me.
My wife is pregnant,
and she's getting birth pains.
Goodness, you lack originality.
Goodness, you're so inhumane.
Hey, I may be a scumbag,
but I wouldn't lie about my kid.
You would. You're a thug.
But let me ask you one question.
Who's behind you?
You killed the detective and changed the prosecutor.
You didn't do that alone.
Goodness, I didn't kill anyone.
You're saying scary things, sir.
What I have to give to you is at home anyway.
That thing is...
an important piece of evidence for your brother's death.
Let's meet again tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Okay, let's go.
You ended up making Lee Tae Kyung get Yang Chul Ki out of there.
The most foolish desire of a human soul is...
the desire to find the truth.
Lee Tae Kyung is too dangerous.
Do you know why I like Tae Kyung?
He still has something called a soul.
I am going to turn his life...
even fancier than what it is now.
(Noodles, dumplings, rice cake soup, chopped noodles)
Woo Yong, I think Yang Chul Ki ran away.
I'll look for him. Don't worry about it.
I told you to wait.
The prosecution kept on going behind my back,
and Lee Tae Kyung was such a nuisance.
I was about to go insane from fear.
It'll be over once you leave to the Philippines in two days.
If you didn't use his brother as bait,
he would have gone all the way without releasing me.
Right?
No one is smarter than you, Chairman Song.
Is there something else you want?
Yes.
I don't want to go to the Philippines.
Either Australia or somewhere more developed.
It's good for my child's education.
The good nature of a person...
comes out when they are faced with fear.
- Dad! - Hey.
Is this your friend's house?
The house is awesome.
I had a lot of great food too.
What's your name?
I'm Yang Seung Il.
Yang...
Seung...
Il.
Come here.
You can get something delicious.
Thank you.
Good boy.
Good for you.
Your dad's...
tough days are over.
Darn it, why is it suddenly pouring?
You're here.
Woo Yong, I can't get a hold of that jerk, Yang Chul Ki.
Where do you think he is?
(Special thanks to Lee Dae Yeon for his cameo performance.)
(Justice)
You can do it with me.
That cooperative investigation or something.
A million dollars. Bring me whatever you have.
The better the information is, the more I'll bet.
This is why people should prepare for their future.
I thought it could come in handy, so I kept this around.
What do you want?
What was it? That delivery man died.
I just took it and handed it over.
- That USB. - USB?
Jang In Tae. A trainee.
A person died as soon as Yang Chul Ki got out.
Someone in the same agency as the girl who died seven years ago,
and the crime method is similar too.
Yes, but I'm not the real culprit who killed your brother.
The real culprit is someone else!