Grandma often insulted me for behaving like my mom.
I just came to realize that.
Mom she talked about is the one who gave birth to me.
Excuse me, I'll reserve it now.
You're like my hero.
I don't want others to look down on us again.
Got it?
Hey! What are you doing?!
Let go of me!
Who hurt my son!?
Mrs. Venus, please help me!
(Mr. Kul, please pay the down payment now.)
Hello? Kong.
Where is Max?
Bastard!
What right do you have to hurt other people?
Can't you see how much he hurt Top?
I don't trust Max
since I've found out he works for your mom
to spy on us and Kanya.
How could you do this to me?
I've always treated you well.
Recent hot news reveals about Mrs. Venus, the owner of Youth Club,
The insider spills the tea
that the man with her in the car is not just her friend.
Who can I trust from now on?
But now, all of you, get out.
Get out!
Please make yourselves at home.
Jate.
Please take a picture for us.
Sure.
This is Jate,
my wife's friend.
He's also our family's photographer.
1... 2...
Done.
Nus, this is Mr. Manop.
He'll be co-investing with us.
I asked Mr. Manop and his family to join us for a meal
so that we'd get closer.
It's my pleasure.
It's a beautiful house you have.
It's Nus' family villa.
We usually come here for vacation.
Oh, Kong. Come here.
Is this your son?
He's my middle child, Kong.
Is this Copter?
Yes.
They're probably the same age.
What about you guys go and play together?
- Want to ask your friend to play together?
- Yes.
Okay, then take care of your friend.
Go play with your friend, Copter.
Don't be naughty.
Then you guys better take care of the guests,
I will take care of the children.
I'll leave it to you.
Sure.
This is great.
So the children would become closer.
Maybe they could work together when they grow up.
That'd be great.
Please go ahead.
Copter!
You murderer!
I can assure you.
Kong didn't mean it.
It was an accident.
But their son's dead.
If it wasn't Kong,
then who's the culprit?
Wat!
How can you say he's the culprit when he didn't do anything?
I will never invest in anything with you ever again.
We shall never work together in this lifetime!
You see?
Everything is ruined because of him.
I'll never accept you as my son.
(V Construction's trying their best to go on despite -39% margin, signaling a tremendous loss.) -
(Thachai's ready to take his first year of office after a landslide win, devoted to helping the people.)
If you agree to the deal I offer,
we can work together.
I'm willing to accept any offer.
Thank you so much for helping.
One more condition.
The issue about your son.
End things swiftly.
Make sure no news is leaking.
I don't like it when people dig up scandalous things
that could ruin our business.
You have my words.
I'll make sure he has no presence.
One more picture.
1... 2... 3...
(Wait for me, Kong.)
(I'll find a way to fix this someday.)
OHM PAWAT CHITTSAWANGDEE
NANI HIRUNKIT CHANGKHAM
PHUWIN PHUWIN TANGSAKYUEN
SATANG KITTIPHOP SEREEVICHAYASAWAT
KAY KAY LERTSITTICHAI
FILM RACHANUN MAHAWAN
PIPLOY KANYARAT RUANGRUNG
DIRECTED BY CHAINARONG TAMPONG
On the topic of the morality of this election's candidate,
Mrs. Venus' case has been widely brought to attention.
The instance of scandal between her and her male friend
seems to signal a romantic affair.
As well as, the student under her support resorting to violence.
I think this has a negative impact on our team.
We might have to postpone the publicity of Mrs. Venus' candidacy.
Isn't that just running away from the problem?
No, it's not.
We have to step back and prove ourselves.
Otherwise, all the things we have been building will end up in ruins.
I have resigned from the university to prove my innocence.
I was planning to fully support Mrs. Venus up.
But when the game gets dirty like this,
I don't think we can use the conventional way to get back at them.
That's only when we have enough evidence.
Just wait a little longer.
There will be enough evidence.
If we're not going to start clean,
then we have to take it all the way.
We don't have that much spare time for waiting.
Thank you so much for visiting my grandma.
But you should go home and rest.
I know that you're going through a lot on your own.
Even though I can't help,
I'm rooting for you.
And for your sister too.
It's totally fine.
You can cry if you're sad.
Who do you like then?
Tell me who.
Pali.
Is it okay for me to visit?
Why wouldn't it be?
I was afraid
that you'd still hate me.
I don't hate anyone.
Nor am I still angry at anyone.
There have been things that were beyond my control.
So I just let it be.
I want to move on already.
You're so strong.
We're all going through a lot.
Let's support each other
and get through it together instead.
I've heard from May
that you want to meet your real mother.
So...
I and Kanya want to help you out.
So we did some research.
Maybe it would make you feel better.
Thank you so much.
That handsome boy's friend, May,
just transferred me some money again.
For having him sing here?
If I really helped draw people into your place.
Then I'm glad.
Then you would have me here for a long time.
Well, as long as that person's willing to cover your pay.
It's nice to be handsome.
People even pay you to be hired.
Hey, Peem. You're early.
I heard everything.
So what?
I quit.
Why are you being so dramatic?
I didn't pass the audition by myself.
I got this job because someone bribed you.
I want to take responsibility.
Do you feel that guilty?
I do.
Let's do this.
Play me a song, any song.
Huh?
Just do it.
Just one song.
I want to hear.
Go on, Peem.
You didn't bring your car, did you?
Then let's take Tam home first.
Yeah.
If you like her, you should just tell her.
Not everything can wait.
How did you know?
I'm your friend.
What sort of friend are you?
Did you just realize it now?
A bad friend, perhaps.
I'm worried that she might feel bad.
Because you used to be in the talking stage with her.
And if I happen to tell Tam how I feel.
Tam might think that I and you are fooling around with her.
Honestly,
if you're really sincere about your feelings for her,
then the past isn't a problem.
I think
you should let Tam be the one to judge.
I'm just...
I'm just afraid.
I'm afraid to lose a friend.
Just like how you did.
Don't be afraid.
Sometimes if you don't say anything,
you might end up losing everything.
I'll take my leave.
You can go wherever you want.
Just get here on time.
What?
Let me tell you what.
I hire you because you're good at playing the instrument
and at singing.
Haven't you heard your own voice before?
But the tips she gave me,
I consider that my tips.
Am I guilty of that?
I'm just taking the tips from your friend.
Would that be okay?
Of course it is.
Why are you so worked up about it?
Are you embarrassed to have someone paying for you?
Let me tell you something.
First off, you should be proud of your skills
because you're good with your instrument and singing.
Second, you should say thank you to the person giving you the money.
Your friend, that is.
For me,
I'd call her a true friend.
Seriously.
Kong.
Come on, let's go.
What?
Where are we going, Gun?
Why are people in this house acting all mysterious?
It's suffocating, you know?
Kong.
This is not the time to be all curious.
Let's go.
What the heck?
Gun.
Let's talk about it later.
What's going on?
Let's get out and talk.
What the heck?
Where are you taking me?
We're meeting Mom at our countryside villa.
Good.
I want to talk it out with Mom too.
I can't stand this situation anymore.
I don't even know what others are thinking of our family right now.
Stop.
You guys listen to me.
Our family's situation is not in a normal state right now.
The one who caused Mom's accident
is our very own Father.
How can that be?
Listen.
Our parents parted ways long ago.
They meet occasionally
to maintain their social status.
So Dad would seem like a famous businessman
who lives a conventional life.
But the one who has to bear all the unconventionals
is mom.
We can no longer run away from the truth.
Dad is ruining everything.
In a time like this, can I ask you...
Can I ask you guys to be on Mom's side with me?
I'm ready.
We should get going.
Hey.
What are you doing in my room?
Grabbing my stuff.
I made up my mind.
I'm planning to donate the stuff I don't need anymore.
But I think I'll keep these,
my dad's bracelets.
And I'm here to talk to my dad.
What?
Talk to your dad?
Your dad
isn't here anymore, is he?
Yeah.
My dad passed away.
In this very room, actually.
At first when I let you stay here,
I want to feel like
there is someone still living here.
To hear some sounds.
But I'm just lying to myself that my dad's still here.
But I'm glad that it's you who live here now.
And I'm sure my dad's glad too.
No need to be scared.
My dad would love you too.
Trust me.
Thank you so much.
For everything.
For the things you told me and things you never told me.
Thank you so much, really.
Don't be so sentimental.
I don't like it.
Then
I have a question.
What's the scariest type of money?
Money shortage.
Oh?
Wrong.
But I'd consider it an interesting answer.
Then try telling me the right answer.
I want to know what you're going to say.
Money cut.
Ouch!
Cut my butt.
Are you cussing at me or Karn?
At you!
By the way.
I think we should let Mink come back and stay here.
Karn doesn't know this place.
And on that day,
I'll be the one to lure Karn out of the house.
Why did you decide to take me here?
Seems fun, isn't it?
I'm excited every time I see you.
You would be more excited than ever this time.
Then you go get the stuff.
You know,
I'm the goddess of this place's favorite.
Whenever I invite anyone here, no one agrees to come.
There's only you
who let me do whatever I want.
Let's see
who would be the luckier one
between me and you.
The CCTV at Karn's place should all be gone already.
Just like what Mink said.
The key is on the lamp at the entrance.
Damn it.
I feel like I'm going to war.
It's similar, actually.
It's similar in the fact that
you can really die from it.
Yes!
Perhaps today's not your day.
You should go ahead into the bedroom.
There's one drawer by the bed.
I keep the important stuff in there.
Where are you going?
Suddenly quitting is pretty rude.
I don't find it fun anymore.
Here.
Take a sip to cool your head.
I want to go home already.
Why don't you try one more time?
You're definitely winning this time.
The goddess was just teasing you just now.
That'd be a waste of time.
My luck is not here.
If you're bored,
we can go somewhere else first.
Can we go to your place?
I've never been there before.
I don't think that's a good idea.
I'm not comfortable with that.
My dad's there.
I went through your Instagram.
Didn't your dad pass away?
The ghost of my dad.
He's very vicious.
Then let's go somewhere else.
Where shall we go?
To my house.
It's much more fun there.
My luck's there.
Let's go.
Get up.
Quick.
Is there anywhere else where the stuff would be kept?
(Go check the drawers downstairs.)
(The one at the bookcase.)
Who are you texting?
No one.
Password?
Anywhere else?
I've been looking all over.
He must be coming back.
(Can you try looking in my bedroom one more time?)
Okay.
Karn!
Stay still.
What are you doing?
Stay still!
Hey!
Still!
Karn!
You bastard!
Hey!
Stop right there!
Hey, May.
Where are you?
I'm in my house.
Watching your kiddy game.
It's pretty simple. I saw right through it.
One problem, though.
That fox, your friend,
might be getting burned by the sun in the car.
Let go of me!
Karn!
You bastard, Karn!
That's loud!
Karn.
Karn!
Hey!
Do you want me to call the police?
Damn it!
I sent someone over to get the stuff.
The plate is 3571.
You can hand it over to him.
It's for everyone's safety.
Here it is.
Thank you.
May!
Let's go.
Before he drives after us.
He wouldn't be able to use his car for a while.
Damn it!
The shop is closed.
Karn.
Why are you here?
To see Mink.
You know she doesn't usually come home.
Why are you looking for her here?
What are you guys on about?
You really don't know your sister.
Including your friends.
What sort of friends are you?
They are ganging up together.
Ganging up together doing what?
What are they up to?
Stealing.
Both your sister and your friends
are about to be in trouble.
Go tell them to return all the stuff to me.
I'm giving you two days.
And I mean, all the stuff.
You tell your sister, she knows.
Where's Mink?
I'm asking you where Mink is.
What rights have you to meddle with my sister?
And what the hell is wrong with you?
Don't you know what your sister's facing?
How can your family let her get hunted down and hurt like this?
Huh?
Do you even know that she needs to fight for
her life to get the evidence for the lawsuit?
Why does a girl have to go through all these damn things on her own?
Mink?
Getting hurt?
Getting hunted?
What the hell?
There you go.
You never cared about your sister.
Mink.
Don't stick your nose in.
Come out, let's talk.
Guys.
Mink's gone.
My dad's bracelets are gone too.
Have we ever been here before, Gun?
Of course, we have.
When we were very young.
Let's go.
Mom.
Is there anything I can do to make you hate me less?
Mom!
Mom.
(No!)
(Let me play with you!)
What's going on, Mom?
(No!)
Why do I feel like it happened before?
(Let me play with you.)
(Copter!)
It's like I was the reason someone fell down the stairs.
At this place.
How can you say that to our son?
Why not?
He's the culprit.
- Did you see with your eyes that he did it?
- It's okay, Kong.
This has nothing to do with you.
Murderer!
It's a long time ago, Kong.
I wanted you to forget about it.
But it has become the reason you're being forgotten.
I made the wrong choice, Kong.
Where is your middle child, by the way?
I don't want Kong to be on any media.
I want him to feel safe.
Because perhaps
someone might want to use his past against him.
Even though he didn't do it,
I'm worried for my child.
All the evidence I have
should probably be enough.
Ever since what happened to Kong,
Dad decided to go on another path entirely.
He doesn't care about anything but money.
So I decided to leave the business we built together
for my own safety.
So I wouldn't have anything to do with the dirty businesses.
And after that,
it's all about gathering the evidence.
There's only Gun
who's working with Dad and helping me from afar.
There is a lot more dirty business Dad's doing with Thachai.
Thank you, Gun, for doing the right thing
even though you must be in a tough spot.
Mom.
Does Dad have to go to this extent with us?
He can do much more than this.
He's trying to pair up Kanya with Top, Thachai's son.
The reason why I'm trying to quickly send Kanya to the States
is not because of Pali.
But because of this.
Then why do you have Max reporting to you about me and Kanya?
Because I know I can't get close to you and your sister.
So I need someone to look out in my stead.
And I thought having Max watching over you
isn't like you're being trailed or anything.
It's for everyone's safety.
The first day of your party
when someone barged in and wrecked it,
those were your Dad's people.
He meant to play me over
ever since I announced that I'd become Thachai's competitor.
He believed that the party was actually Youth Club's event.
That means.
Max's incident is what ticks them off.
Since our people hurt his son.
That's the spark to all the fires.
He just wanted to win at first.
But now,
I believe they're planning to do anything to destroy us.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Thing is
I've always thought the world was such a nasty place all along.
I've only looked at things from my perspective
so I've never noticed other people's problems before.
I'm really sorry, Mom.
I needed time
and a lot of patience for this day.
To bargain with someone of power,
we need power ourselves.
But for Max's case,
whether he's to be proven right or wrong,
we need someone to help him out.
He's in danger.
Throw away the stuff you don't need.
We don't have that much space.
(I'll give up the house.)
(I don't think I'll be signing the contract anymore.)
Hello?
Top.
How are you doing?
Kul.
Do you love me?
Of course, I do.
If you really love me,
you have to help me destroy Max.
I never want to see his face ever again.
Do we have to go to that length?
We can just throw him in jail.
That's not enough.
If I'm in pain,
he shall be in more pain than I do.
But that's...
But what?
You do what I say.
Do you think I don't have a video of you?
The one you were sleeping with me.
If you don't help me,
you're the one who'll also get in trouble.
From what happened,
the university's come to a conclusion to have you suspended
until the case is completely investigated.
Professor.
If I'm not guilty,
do I still have to lose years of my life?
I think the penalty you get is already very light.
(This is obviously intended murder.)
(What he did to Top is just too much.)
(Men can't be trusted. He seems quiet
but has got more anger than we think.)
(The penalty's too light. Maybe he's got a powerful backup.)
Luang Por.
What do I do?
If my future has to end this way,
how can I go on living?
Will anyone believe me
that what I did
was a self-defense?
Will there be any sacred being to save me?
Let it be.
We have to own up to what we did.
The problem is right in front of me.
How can I let it be?
If I don't fight,
I die.
That's the truth.
My world and yours are different.
We can't use the same solution.
Do you understand me?
I have a problem.
This minute,
I don't want anything else.
I just need someone
who would stand by my side.
Just that my only father, would embrace me,
would embrace me,
console me,
and tell me we'd get through this together.
But I can't even have that.
You've never been anything for me.
(This is the devil in human form.)
(He's like this at this age, what would he become when he grows up?)
(Why not just give him a death sentence?)
Yes, Top?
Have you met Max, your best friend?
No, I don't see him.
He probably wouldn't come back here anymore.
I'll look for him somewhere else.
Is that so?
It's fine.
If you don't see him,
my guys must have already seen him.
They're quite impatient.
Let go!
Hey!
Stop kicking!
Let go!
Let go of me!
DIRECTED BY CHAINARONG TAMPONG
Top wouldn't let Max slide.
He wanted me to help destroy Max.
But I didn't want to.
Stop the car!
But you're not fond of Max.
Why would you help him?
I'm not fond of him
doesn't mean I want him to die.
You're calling me a thief?
And when you're defending her,
how much do you think you know about her?
Had your share of fun?
It's nice to be you.
To be able to meet your family.
You have no idea what I did.
I made a lot of mistakes.