What on earth are you doing?
Are you stealing?
Thanks for letting me live with you.
I can tell even when I was on stage.
You almost ate Kong up alive.
Just keep going.
I'll help you.
Kanya!
Maybe this is how we're supposed to part.
Why don't we get to know each other better?
Tam and I have decided.
We're going to try learning more about each other.
Why does it have to be Tam?
I'm scared you would be a jerk to Tam.
Like how you did to other girls.
But if you break Tam's heart this time,
I'm not going to let it slide.
Come on, Mom.
I swept the floor
and filled up water bottles already.
Why do you want me to do so many things?
Will you be away for many days?
(After making merit, )
(I'll drive your grandma home)
(and stay overnight there.)
What?
You told me you'd hurry back, didn't you?
You left me here.
Mink and Pan always got to go with you.
Whenever a boy comes, he gets noisy.
(Stay there.)
(Buy your dad some food.)
He's not usually home.
(Well, go see him now.)
(Let him know you're home.)
Okay.
I'll tell him later.
(Later again?)
(Go now.)
(You keep saying this.)
(You won't do it in the end.)
Fine.
Mom, turn on your camera
so you will stop nagging.
Let's get it over with, okay?
Look.
Dad, show your face to assure Mom you're really here.
(How could you do this to me?!)
(You asshole!)
You scumbag child!
You have always been a jinx since you were born.
You'll see.
One day, your life will be f*cked up like mine!
OHM PAWAT CHITTSAWANGDEE
NANI HIRUNKIT CHANGKHAM
PHUWIN PHUWIN TANGSAKYUEN
SATANG KITTIPHOP SEREEVICHAYASAWAT
KAY KAY LERTSITTICHAI
FILM RACHANUN MAHAWAN
PIPLOY KANYARAT RUANGRUNG
DIRECTED BY CHAINARONG TAMPONG
Hey, take it.
Thanks.
Tam gave it to me.
Tam and I have decided.
We're going to try learning more about each other.
Kong, if you want to date someone,
can I be one of your choices?
What makes you clean the house late at night?
What made you came downstairs and saw me?
I'm hungry.
We don't have any food today.
Here it is.
Oh, I see.
You're her dearest kid.
Of course, there must be special food for you.
Why?
What did you argue with Mom about this time?
I forgot you two are always arguing.
Or you must be heartbroken.
I was guessing randomly but I was right.
Do you want to vent?
To your mind, what makes people like each other?
What a tricky question.
You're the one who should give me some advice on that.
I asked
because I know you once liked him that much.
So, I want to know if everyone likes someone like Pali.
Someone fell for him?
Nope.
I was giving an example.
Hey, if you eat this much,
you'll get fat.
You said you didn't want to get fat, didn't you?
Just tell me if you want to eat some.
Wait.
You're putting it too much.
It totally ruins the taste.
Eat.
Open your mouth now
before it drops.
That's why I enjoy eating it.
People won't know if we're really bearing spiciness
or actually crying.
Well,
Pali asked me to return the bracelet to you.
But if you don't want to see it,
let me know.
I'll throw it away.
It's alright.
Please put it in my room.
You're getting fat.
This way, please, Luang Por.
I remember Mom told me she wanted to eat pizza.
Enjoy it in heaven, Mom.
(blessing)
Max, you have to practice today, right?
Be patient and work hard.
I hope you can get the important opportunity.
I'll do my best, Luang Por.
The 8th place goes to Mr. Worawat Ruengwattanakit,
the business owner of a famous real estate company. (10 Richest Business Owners in Thailand.)
Why isn't Top's family included?
I think they're even richer than No.1.
They only rank business owners.
A politician doesn't count.
Kong's mom is becoming a politician, too, isn't she?
Do you think it's possible for her to even beat Top's dad?
Hello, Senior Top.
Hello.
Nobody taught you
how a junior must treat me?
I'm Max, first-year.
All of us here are professionals.
I'm serious about it, too.
I want to be a national-level athlete.
National level?
Then, your first goal is to bring me down.
That's already difficult enough.
What are you guys doing, huh?
Help me warm up.
Sure.
Would you like to do some stretching first?
Why did you even ask?
It's your duty.
Sure.
I'll do that for you.
Hey, Kul?
You know him?
I know you must feel tired,
so I bought something for you to eat.
Come on, Kul, our dearest bro.
You came to work on time.
You know well I don't think of it as work.
I'm doing this with my heart.
Thanks.
Let me keep it for you.
The picture frame is used to tell a story about what's in it.
What we can see is what you intend to present.
What can you see in my frame?
Value, perhaps.
Your outfit, watch, shoes, and car key
altogether cost several millions.
How about your frame?
Professor, we call him a third wheel.
Kong is sitting between a couple.
Mr. Kong, what do you think?
This frame is handsome and warm-hearted.
We'd better call him untrustworthy.
That isn't wrong
because what's inside the frame is
what we choose to reveal to others.
People won't know other related stories about it
that make the truth not always being told.
This could be similar to how you view me, Mr.Kong.
Hey, I'll go to our club this evening.
Join me if you're free.
Do you want to come with me now?
I'm not going.
I'm not free today.
Hey.
But let me see your watch.
Wow.
Stunning.
Can I take a photo?
(I've finished my class. Where should I go?)
Happy Birthday!
Surprise!
That's your present.
What are you guys playing?
Stop pretending, okay?
Go ahead.
Show us what you've got.
Happy Birthday, Dream.
I'll give you the best service tonight.
Why haven't we met before?
Your schedule is tight, right?
Not at all.
Others aren't that interested in someone like me.
Come on.
Who wouldn't be interested in the top tier like you?
What?
Why?
Hello.
Yam, that client can't touch me like that.
Why are you suddenly becoming reserved, huh?
I'm not.
But if she wants to go this far,
I can't accept this rate.
Don't tell me they paid the full amount,
but you took a lot of commission and left me with so little?
Stop. I'll handle it for you.
How?
The only acceptable way for me is to see the transfer slip.
(10,000 THB successfully transferred to your account)
I like it if you're this nice.
I don't like someone so mindful about skinship
because when I spend money,
I'm never mindful.
How kind you are, Dream.
If a person like me likes someone,
I can give him everything.
What if I happen to say I want a car?
You'll get it.
These days, many young people can afford to buy cars.
They make good money.
Luckily, I'm hard-working.
How talented you are.
You can afford to pay this high monthly installment.
I bet you're earning a high income.
Here you are.
Give me a second.
Hello, everyone.
Now, we're looking at
my new car.
Stay tuned for the next clip
to see where I'll take you on a trip with this new car.
It's as much as 300 THB?
Can you give me a discount?
Just think of it as joining me in making merit.
I can't.
These are large fish.
They give you as much merit as their sizes.
Is that so?
Auntie, do you know that
if you do meritable things for a twin,
your good deed will be doubled?
That's true.
Many of our previous customers came back here to thank us.
Alright. I'll take it.
Thank you.
Is that dude in your gang, too?
He looks so damn rich.
Should we just release all the fish we caught?
To have a good life in our next life, you know.
Thank you.
Asshole.
If we had hoped for merit,
we wouldn't have caught them to sell in the first place.
It's money that matters.
If we can earn, we'll have a good life in this life.
He seems rich,
but he really looks down on others.
May and Kong look rich,
but they aren't behaving like that.
By the way, you stayed overnight at their place.
Did you take any of their stuff?
What the hell are you talking about?
What?
I'm not a thief.
I stayed overnight
because I just wanted to sleep in a room with air conditioning.
Damn.
I had such a comfy sleep and felt as if I hadn't slept for many years.
Will you go there again today?
I think I won't go there anymore.
What?
I'm too different from them. I don't belong there at all.
Just forget about it.
I'll work hard and earn money to pay the tuition fee.
As you wish.
(Youth Club is ready to provide you with education funds.)
(Just submit your application for this project.)
Is that Kong's mom?
They're one of the richest families on the rank.
I think
if her son could only give you pizza,
you'd better rely on her instead.
Trust me.
There's an influencer flaunting his riches, right?
You'd better show off your poverty.
That's a new type, you know.
Then, join this project
and ask to be funded.
(Youth Club goes all out, )
(providing the funds to support talented teens.)
I guess they will like you.
True.
You're already living a dog's life.
To the max.
They probably like you a lot.
He's thinking about it.
He's thinking hard.
Will you really allow me to do anything I want?
Of course.
I'll do as I said.
Can you tell me already what you're taking me to do?
You'll find out soon.
Will I hit something?
You won't.
A few steps more.
You're almost there.
We've arrived.
Peekaboo.
I have wanted to do this for so long.
Okay. Sure.
Who will ride first?
I want to ride pillion.
Here.
This is a popular photo spot people post on IG.
Stand here.
I want that fountain in the photo, too.
Smile.
One, two.
One more.
Smile.
One, two.
You aren't enjoying it, right?
It's not like that.
It's just that I haven't done something like this often.
But you aren't enjoying it, right?
Come on, Tam.
Let's be frank with each other.
I don't want us to not tell each other
if there's something we don't enjoy doing together.
It could turn into a long-term problem.
Honestly, this activity isn't bad at all.
It's just that I'm tired.
Going on a date doesn't mean
we have to create a romantic scene.
Just being together
and living our lives as usual can be adorable
and make us happy already.
I think I expected something too dreamlike.
I'm probably too into those IG posts.
Don't worry.
Just forget about it.
From knowing him,
what kind of person do you think Pali is?
He seems to enjoy freedom
and loves himself a lot.
Can someone who loves himself so much
really love someone else?
Hey. Don't be demanding yet.
If you want to go ahead,
you should try giving him love first.
How about this?
Take me to do what you enjoy doing.
I also want to get into your world, Pali.
This is my regular table.
I miss you.
This is Tam.
Your friend?
We're in talking stage.
I forgot that you're good at talking.
Well, let me order some food.
Go ahead.
I'm not disturbing you anyway.
Would you like your regular order?
How did you two get to know each other?
At which party?
We go to the same university.
Did you make the first move?
I'm just asking, you know.
I don't usually see Pali hitting on someone seriously.
Have you ever counted how many?
As many as 100?
Why do we have to talk about this, Aeko?
Can I just stay with her alone?
I took her here.
Are you guys on a date?
But you chose your regular place?
How could you not meet someone you know here, Pali?
If we count how many,
I guess that number can make a Chinese dinner.
I'll go back now.
My grandma called.
Tam.
There's really nothing in it.
I already cleared things up with them.
I just wanted to show I'm honest with you, letting you know everything,
but I didn't expect she would bug us this much.
Or else, I wouldn't dare to take you here, Tam.
Be honest with me.
What kind of person are you, Pali?
Are you a playboy?
How many girls have you met?
Am I here to be a funny one?
But can you give it a try?
Try trusting me
that I'm not like that anymore.
Tam,
we've talked about this already
that we'll keep trying together.
I admit
that I'm sensitive about something like this.
I'm not strong enough to handle things.
I can go back myself, actually.
I told you we'd stay together today.
I definitely won't break the promise.
Before you go home,
do you want to chill out at my place first?
Let's not do that now.
I want to take it slow.
Sure.
Tam, don't worry at all.
I really understand you.
I want to make sure you're really okay with it.
Tam.
(You weren't being yourself at all.)
(Let's meet if you're lonely.)
(You know I know well what you like.)
Are you surprised to see me?
I didn't think anyone would come here.
It seems nobody is that interested in it.
I'm interested.
I bought some food for you.
I don't want to eat alone.
Is the light bulb too loose?
I'll try fixing it.
Hey, let me do it.
But even I can't reach it, May.
Of course, I will
if you help me.
Why are you so surprised?
Carry me so I can reach it.
It's this easy.
Am I still a kind person to you?
I have something to consult with you.
I want this relationship to last.
Can you give me some advice?
Honestly, Pali has been hurt because of love so many times.
I think he himself still can't handle some issues that properly.
He seems like someone in error.
Just make everything simple, as Pali told you.
Just live your lives together.
Actually,
though Pali enjoys hanging out,
he's actually a homebody.
If there's no errand,
he buries himself in his room all the time.
(Pali) He says his bedroom is his safe zone.
So he invited me to his place
because he wanted to take me to his safe zone, right?
He's a lot more sensitive than we think
though he looks like such a playboy.
Pali.
Tam!
Tam, I didn't do anything.
She came herself
and tried to do everything.
Now that I saw everything,
you're still denying it?
Pali, why?
Just because I don't sleep with you,
you slept with someone else?
Tam.
There's really nothing between that girl and me.
As I told you, I rejected her.
She's angry,
so she's trying to approach me.
She's trying to do everything to get me back.
But that will never happen.
I ended everything already.
What if I didn't come today?
Would you tell me about it?
It's because I don't have anything to tell.
What's the point of arguing?
I told you already to be frank with me.
Even if the more I say, the more things get screwed up?
Do we have to go that far?
Tam.
What shit did you do again?
If you want to curse me, do that later.
Help me first.
(I screwed it up again.)
Are you surprised
I returned earlier than expected?
Not really.
You always do something I can't predict, don't you?
It's good we're all here.
I told Kanya I have something to talk to her about.
What is it, Mom?
I'll send you to study in the USA.
Your mom is so good at planning life, you know,
whether it be about work or her kids.
Without her,
I would end up in trouble for sure.
Thank you so much for trusting me.
As for your study in the USA,
you can go this month.
You don't have to wait until you finish high school.
You promised you wouldn't hurt Tam, didn't you?
I can't erase the mistakes I made in the past.
You know, I made a lot.
I don't know if there will be any other problem that will hurt Tam.
How will you take responsibility for her feelings?
Think, okay?
Pull yourself together.
If you still can't move on about Kanya
and aren't ready to start a new relationship, just don't do it.
Be decisive, okay?
Nobody deserves to be a victim of your sensitive emotions anymore.
Your alcohol level exceeds the limit.
It's you again, as always.
Did you call someone to bail you out?
(Mink)
Don't be angry with me, Kanya.
Kanya.
Pali,
I've made up my mind already.
I won't let Mom control my life anymore.
Let's go through this together one more time.
Tomorrow morning, I'll hurry to the court.
Don't worry.
What about us?
Can we really get back together, Kanya?
If the problem we had back then doesn't count,
we still love each other.
Do we?
I have to clear up something about myself first.
I don't know how much time we have left
about us.
If you're thinking about doing something,
do it real soon.
(Tam: I'm ready to talk now.)
Hello, Mr. Kanin.
Today, we'll discuss finding a representative to present about Youth Club.
We need someone with a clear image.
Or else Youth Club won't yet be recognized widely.
Yes.
Mrs. Venus!
You aren't allowed inside.
Please book an appointment queue in advance.
But I'm Kong's friend.
Are you his friend at the university?
Yes.
May I ask
if you were also at the event that night?
Yes.
Well, I want to apply for funding.
I'm a swimmer
but haven't got any medal from any big competition as a guarantee yet.
If you really want to be funded,
a medal is a must.
Or else we can't find a reason for funding you.
The committee could object to it.
Can being poor be a reason?
Do I have to only be talented to get support
and opportunities?
It's alright.
I understand.
I'm bringing a Buddhist amulet as a gift for you.
I hope sacred power will protect someone generous like you.
May I ask
if you know all of Kong's friends?
I do,
but I think I won't join them anymore
because I'm too different from them.
I feel embarrassed.
I think I can help you with the funds,
but can you do something for me?
Go back there,
be friends with Kong and other members.
Just keep me updated on everything going on there.
From today, I'll make you someone
who won't feel embarrassed about that anymore.
DIRECTED BY CHAINARONG TAMPONG
I've seen many friends ask for loans to pay their tuition fees.
But Youth Club offered me help.
Are you angry with me
that I joined your mom's project?
Just make sure she's not using you.
He still didn't agree to clear things up with you?
I called, but he didn't pick up.
He didn't reply to my messages either.
I don't know what to do now.
You like him a lot, don't you?
That's why it hurts you this much.
Who's that?
Mink?
Can you not mess with me now?
Who could give you this much, Kul?
This makes me lose face.
If you're this spendy,
how about spending some on me?
I can do anything.
Thank you for accepting my invitation.
May.
We've met again.
You like to miss strangers, don't you?
Can you help me now?
I don't want to be alone anymore.
What the hell?
Mink got abused by her ex-husband.
Do you know who Mink's troublesome husband is?