(When people come together, no matter the reason,)
(I think that turns them into acquaintances,)
(and a bond is then created.)
(What holds them together could be the word "friends",)
(but that means they must have mutual acceptance.)
Stop!
Let go!
How could you do this to me?
(But if they don't,)
(Because society needs a "brave person")
(Venus Pongsawarin, the leader of Brave Power party)
(they probably meet)
(only to make a turning point in life.)
(It could be either a small change)
(or a significant one, including death.)
(It's fine if we don't think of each other as friends,)
(but I never regret that at least we have met)
(though we almost had no good story to remember.)
OHM PAWAT CHITTSAWANGDEE
NANI HIRUNKIT CHANGKHAM
PHUWIN PHUWIN TANGSAKYUEN
SATANG KITTIPHOP SEREEVICHAYASAWAT
KAY KAY LERTSITTICHAI
FILM RACHANUN MAHAWAN
PIPLOY KANYARAT RUANGRUNG
DIRECTED BY CHAINARONG TAMPONG
6 MONTHS AGO
Hello, Mrs. Venus.
Hello.
May I interview you for further information, please?
Sure.
We've heard that you resigned from every position
at your husband, Mr.Worawat's company.
Is this true?
Mrs. Venus,
please answer the questions naturally.
This is the introductory interview of yourself.
Our team would like to focus on you
looking more mature than your actual age
and warm-hearted.
I think you're shaped by these personalities.
What if they ask about my personal matters?
Please answer only what you can confirm for now
to ensure our safety.
As for the company,
I think it isn't completely correct to call it Worawat's
because this business was started by our family.
Regarding my resignation,
I want to confirm that it's true I resigned from every position
and sold all the stocks I held.
It seems you want to start everything anew.
Yes.
I don't want to build constructions anymore.
If I have to build something from now,
I'd better create people with feelings and hearts.
That sounds like you want to continue in the field of politics.
Is that your plan?
Thank you.
Mrs. Venus, you seem to be the mother who understands teens best.
That's why you're launching this project.
Where is your middle child, by the way?
(Fulfill your vow at 09.09 AM.)
(It's indeed a super sacred time. Don't cheat.)
Listen.
This is my very last time trusting you.
Damn it.
It's always me who fixes everything in the end.
What's up?
(You started running already, right?)
(Stop by at the condo next to the park.)
Why must I trust you?
(If you don't come here now,)
(I'm surely done for.)
Hey, you slept with my wife?
You're done for!
Kong.
Hey, just jump.
You son of a bitch!
Run!
Hey, where are you going?!
Where are you running away to, huh?
Why are you so fast?
Hey, you brats!
My husband's towels!
Stop!
Pali, what the hell is this?
That woman said she likes me.
You can't just fall for any woman who likes you, okay?
Shit. She said she had already broken up with her boyfriend
but didn't tell me that guy would come back and make up with her.
Damn it. When he opened the door,
I was reaching the climax part.
Hey.
You asked your friend to help?
I'll trample you both.
Asshole, you slept with my wife.
How do I have something to do with this?
Just do, okay?
Lord, please hear my voice.
I'm fulfilling my vow now.
I promised that we would both run naked
if we got accepted into the same university.
I'm going now.
- Hey, won't the sacred power think you're cheating? - Trust me. They understand.
Hey, where are you running to?
Hey, stop.
Stop right there.
Why are you guys running naked?
Come with us.
What?
Are you running away, huh?
- What a chicken. - You're in for it.
Just wait till it's my turn!
Why are you naked in public?
Hey, bring it on.
Stop.
Please sign here.
Go in quickly.
Pali?
What's going on?
Hey, wait.
What's between you two?
She's my friend.
What were you charged with?
Committing an indecent act in public.
Have you called someone to bail you out?
Can I pay the fine for them?
Hey, it's alright.
I already phoned my family.
Take it.
You must feel so cold.
How kindhearted you are.
Kindhearted?
Nobody has complimented me like this for ages.
You should have given me that.
Kong, if your mom sees us like this,
won't she tear me off a strip?
Now, I'm unsure
what makes my mom angry first.
Because we're looking like this and here in this place?
Or because we're going to jail?
There he is.
Your dad is here.
He's not my dad.
(This project we're working on is called Youth Club.)
(We'll take care of them, listen to them,)
(and help solve problems)
(for kids and teens with nobody supporting them.)
She's afraid this will affect her reputation, right?
That's why she didn't come here herself.
She must feel ashamed having a son like me,
so she's treating me as if I didn't even exist.
Kong, don't be pessimistic about everything.
But it's always true.
She didn't even ask me to join
when her kids gathered for a family photo.
Take some rest.
I'll handle this.
Do you need a lift?
No, thanks.
See you around.
Well, today's atmosphere is kind of unusual.
If you don't want to go home now,
come with me.
Come on.
Don't say no to me, okay?
You know we only have each other.
Deal.
Lend me your tee.
Honestly,
I thought we wouldn't get to come back here.
Why?
Your mom would cut me out of your life, too?
Don't forget that I'm still mad at you.
Let's put it this way then.
Take this as my 2000th apology.
What's this?
Shit.
I'd never found this before when I cleaned my room.
Don't go too far hooking up with girls, okay?
I know you're being sensitive now,
but if you remain a player like this,
I think you will end up in trouble.
Nope. I didn't bring any girl here.
This belongs to Kanya.
I think she dropped it long ago.
Return it to her for me.
I won't argue with you about my sister anymore.
I know you already paid for it as much as you could.
I won't add insult to injury then.
I'm fine.
Though I look like I'm dying,
I'm still okay.
Forget about it.
But the new semester starts tomorrow.
I think we'll face lots of new stories.
We already fulfilled the vow.
Now, we only have to survive studying.
Do you think anyone wants to be friends with us?
Who would want to befriend troublemakers like us?
Damn it. Who knows?
There are still many more troublemakers out there.
Lots of them.
Well said.
From now on,
everything about you will no longer be private.
What we should be careful about is taking care of those around you
and family members
because whenever they face problems,
you also do, Mrs. Venus.
Yes.
Kong.
Yes?
Won't you tell me what trouble you caused again today?
It's really not a big deal.
It won't ruin your reputation.
You already knew?
It was a grand opening, wasn't it?
You also looked happy, Mom,
while your son was standing naked inside the police station.
Wait.
Okay.
I won't ask what you did today.
But I asked you to work for me.
Can you give me your answer now?
(Damn it. Who knows?)
(There are still many more troublemakers out there.)
The more, the better, I guess,
because my mom asked me to help find teens our age
to join her project.
We'll listen to and help them.
She probably wants to create an angle-look image for herself by helping the public.
You mean that Youth Club?
Damn it. The name sounds so weird.
Yeah.
It's everyone's ideal club,
ready to help solve teens' problems.
She's unbelievable.
She's ready to understand everyone but me.
Do you think you can do it?
Of course.
But I'll handle it my way.
I think I've just come up with something fun.
Sure.
I'll help you, Mom.
(NO VIOLENCE FOR FRESHY WELCOMING ACTIVITY)
No freshy welcoming activity! (NO VIOLENCE FOR FRESHY WELCOMING ACTIVITY)
No freshy welcoming activity!
(WE WANT FREEDOM OF DRESS CODE.) No freshy welcoming activity!
(WE WANT FREEDOM OF DRESS CODE.)
We want freedom of dress code! (WE WANT FREEDOM OF DRESS CODE.)
We want freedom of dress code!
No freshy welcoming activity!
Hey? Pali?
I knew you got accepted into this university
but didn't know we're in the same faculty.
You too, Kong?
We meet again.
Ouch.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
You're bringing so many things.
Are you selling them?
Well,
I'm bringing them just to boost my confidence.
Hey, take it.
(Aren)
It already belongs to someone, doesn't it?
It doesn't.
It's just that I like naming stuff.
Huh?
You named this inhaler?
Yeah.
I named everything.
Thanks.
How cute.
I'm meeting a kindhearted person again.
Kong.
Yeah?
Don't forget to return the tee I lent you that day.
Oh, okay.
I'm sorry. I didn't know I'd meet you today.
Why is he here?
Welcome all the first-year students of the Faculty of Fine and Applied Arts.
I wondered why Mom wanted me to study here that much.
I got it now. She sent him to report her about my behaviors.
We're glad to share this same moment with you all,
and we will grow together.
Our university believes that
what suits our students best is
being supported by someone ready to help.
That's why we are now in partnership with Youth Club
to create and offer help.
We'll introduce this project to everyone this evening.
Are they tricking us into direct selling or what?
Or is it a creed or something?
I think this sounds interesting.
Something good is probably waiting for us.
I think
it's time for some fun.
Hi, Dad.
When will you pick me up to live with you?
(Did you ask your mom about it?)
You know what?
I asked her, and she told me to ask you.
Now that I'm asking you,
you're saying this to me.
What should I do then?
Why do you want to move there that much?
Staying here is already good.
Why can't you wait until you graduate?
I'll hang up, Dad.
Yes.
You also said the same thing when I was in middle school.
Now I've finished high school
but haven't got to move anywhere yet.
Grandma, do I have to wait until I graduate?
You keep being obsessed with other things.
You don't do what you're really supposed to do.
You never pay attention to it.
You forgot to buy green onion, didn't you?
Oh, my bad.
You're always behaving like this.
But for something like green onion,
I guess people won't even care if you don't put it in.
While eating, they get rid of it anyway.
An unwanted thing, you know.
You're being rhetorical.
How was your first day at the university, by the way?
It was nice.
There's one project at the university
I want to join.
After I'm done with this, please let me join.
What project? Huh?
Don't use it as an excuse.
It's only your first day at the university,
but you've already turned promiscuous?
Grandma, don't be too hard on me.
Finally, the day has arrived.
When a daughter has grown up,
she always causes trouble.
Grandma, why are you saying this to me?
I haven't done anything terrible.
What's with your disrespectful voice just now?
You think you're mature enough
to say anything you want?
You believe whatever you think or do is right, don't you?
Grandma, relax.
There's nothing bad at all.
You've seen me your entire life.
Have I been such a worry to you?
Please trust me, Grandma.
Finish this.
Get home safe.
Is this your car?
Wow.
This is my dream car.
You can take a look inside.
No, thank you.
But if you're free,
I want to meet you often.
Don't forget to miss me sometimes.
I have so many guys to miss.
What should I do to miss you, Kul?
Will this help?
Give me a call.
Shit.
I did this much, but you only gave me 500 THB?
Foolish.
You took more money!
It was my idea!
That's not the point.
I'm the one who worked!
- So what? - What? Huh?
Hey, what the hell is wrong with you two?
Chao claimed that he's older,
and he took more coffin donation money,
while it was actually my idea.
You keep saying you're younger.
You just sat there and watched me work,
but now you want more money, huh?
The money...
Stop already.
If Luang Por knows you're fighting because of this,
you'll be kicked out of the temple.
That's good
so he will finally learn that
we brothers must earn money this hard
because the money to cover temple expenses
and my meals was used up for your tuition fee already!
Be frank with me.
What right do you have to use the temple's money?
I told you already.
I borrowed it for this first semester only.
I didn't just take it.
The semester has started already, right?
Ask your new and rich friends to help you then.
Or does nobody at the university talk to you?
Tell me.
But I kind of sympathize with you, you know.
Look at you.
You'll see.
I'll make good
and rich friends,
so I can finally get away from this kind of life.
I think she didn't mean to do it.
She's this little.
She wouldn't want to be a thief.
Do you think that her innocence could make her sneak to the cashier,
open the cash drawer,
and take all the money?
It's your fault, Peem.
How could this have something to do with me?
It's your fault, indeed,
because you're too soft-hearted.
You want to be a good person so much that you're brainless.
I told you already
not to allow others to sell inside our store.
Won't you give others a chance at all?
I gave you once, didn't I?
Now what?
Instead of helping me,
you end up sympathizing with a thief.
See?
Got it now?
I'll think that you conspired with her.
Take it.
Now, get lost.
You insulted me that I never give anyone a chance, right?
Fine. You're right.
You're fired!
(Landlord: If you still can't pay the rent this month,)
(I'll ask you to move out.)
Damn it.
What a lousy day.
Shit!
Everyone, thanks for coming.
Welcome to the club.
It's alright.
We're just starting.
I think I was too careless this time.
I believed everything would be easy and go as expected.
But I think I made the wrong plan.
The first group of people we have to fight with are those
we want to take our side.
Jate, can you really help me work on this?
I'm seriously doing that for you now.
You know that, don't you?
When is he coming back?
Soon.
But he has probably found out about this whole thing.
He can handle things a lot faster than we expect.
As things have turned out this way,
I'm kind of worried now.
Hey, you enjoy pranking others that much?
You're deceiving us, aren't you?
You claimed that this is about Youth Club.
This is totally unfair for those who really want to join.
I do apologize for distressing you all.
I've heard that many don't really trust that club
as they aren't sure of what they will be asked to do.
So, I've just come up with an idea that
if there's a space where everyone can gather
to have fun while also trusting each other,
it's better, isn't it?
But can we trust you then?
If you really want to listen to that project,
I can give you the location.
It's not far from here.
Damn. What the hell?
What a waste of time.
If all of us use this one space
to try doing whatever we want to
and being whoever we want to
without being judged by anyone,
it's a good idea, isn't it?
Just form our own club.
Whatever you think is best.
Actually, this club is just one of your options.
Feel free to either stay or leave.
Let's go.
What's the point of staying?
Damn.What a waste of time.
Here we go.
Why go to other clubs?
This place sounds like a lot of fun.
I'm Tam.
I'm Kong.
What do you think about this?
I'm a bit worried
because I told Grandma I'd join a university event.
Now, it looks like I lied to her.
But we're all your university friends.
It's not different from what your grandma probably imagines.
Well, I'll give it a try then.
I hope you won't disappoint me.
Or probably someone has sent them to be our friends?
So, we only have all of you left.
Nope. I mean,
you all have been selected.
Let's get to know each other more, shall we?
Let's play a game.
Drink if you're single.
That easy?
Why not?
Say anything you want.
Ask any question if you like.
Alright.
My turn.
Who has more than 50K followers?
Whoa.
What a celebrity.
You're an influencer, aren't you?
I have fewer than 300 followers.
Does that really matter?
I'm not that surprised.
Tam, you've stayed quiet for too long.
It's your turn now.
Me?
Who got an average o-net score of more than 80?
Is that really your question?
- Why? I couldn't come up with anything else. - Wait.
- I'm smart, you know. - Your score was below that.
You just got 62.
Hey.
Yours was 50. I remember that.
Does this sound too nerdy?
Same here.
I don't drink.
I have to get up early tomorrow.
Isn't that because you're a noob?
Hey. My turn.
Mine is a lonely vibe.
Who is living alone?
Hey. Are you serious?
Is there any room available at your place?
Can I rent a small corner to live in?
Are you serious?
Yeah.
I can't afford to pay the rent anymore.
Wait.
You two discuss that later, okay?
Who hasn't spoken yet?
You.
Wait.
You haven't asked a question yet.
Don't you want to find someone with something in common?
Playing a game won't help.
Just surviving another day is already worth celebrating.
Don't you think?
Cheers.
Last person.
My turn.
I'll make it easy.
Any middle child here?
Come on.
Seriously?
So we're a gang of troublemakers now.
Troublemakers? No.
You know how glad I am seeing you all gather here.
Making new friends at the university isn't easy.
Are we friends now?
Yeah. Can't we?
Any rules for our friendship?
Not treating each other like crap is enough, I guess.
What other rules do you want?
No romantic relationship.
No sex.
Or else we'll be screwed.
Alright then.
I'll give you the passcode to enter this place.
I want to make it everyone's space.
Do anything you want.
Talk about anything you want.
If you have any problem, just come and stay here.
I think we must name our gang.
Make it as weird as Youth Club is.
Well then,
cheers to the opening of Wednesday Club,
everyone's safe zone.
Damn cool.
Cheers.
Kong, I think Youth Club sent someone to handle us.
If they know you're with me here, I'm done for.
Why are you running away?
We aren't doing anything wrong.
You can't imagine what my mom can do.
How does your mom have something to do with this?
The Youth Club we're playing with is owned by Kong's mom.
She's the owner?
Yeah.
Run!
Now.
Well, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to make things turn out this way.
Let me know what I can do to compensate for this.
I really didn't know this would happen.
Don't get mad.
No worries.
I think it's fun.
It's enjoyable facing this kind of thing sometimes.
Or else I wouldn't get to stay here with you, Kong.
Do you know
you're the reason I decided to come today?
Let's change from compensating for this
to getting to know each other better.
(Youth Club's grand opening was a phenomenon,)
(but their first activity was totally a flop.)
(An empty club nobody pays attention to.)
(What a shattered dream for Mrs. Venus of Gen X)
(as no students joined her.)
(Was the party just their gimmick?)
(Does Youth Club really exist?)
(Nobody went there.)
(The leaked photo just shows a party.)
(What a liar.)
(Kanin)
Hello.
(Don't post anything)
(or respond to any comments)
(because people will misinterpret them.)
(The PR team will handle it for you.)
From now on, if I want to do anything,
I have to get approval from the team first, right?
(Please trust us, Mrs.Venus.)
(We can handle this better.)
Okay.
What did you do, Mom?
I'm supposed to ask you that, Kong.
Why did you send your men to barge in my place?
Are you a mafia already?
Why have you gone this far?
Are you taking revenge on me?
What revenge are you talking about?
You were mad at me
because I convinced your targets to join me.
But I didn't force them.
They made their own choices.
Kong, stop.
I have nothing to do with what you said.
Someone broke in?
What happened?
Kong, what did you do?
What event did you host last night?
What you did is already wrong in the first place.
Don't count my issue in.
Just forget about it.
Everything is already ruined anyway.
Who did that to you?
Did you see their faces?
Kong.
I think there's one thing I should let you know.
From now on, you must be careful
when you make friends or meet someone new
because I'm not sure anymore
what else our family will have to go through.
So you're planning to go into politics as rumored, aren't you?
Why do you risk your family members as hostages in your game?
You'll find out soon.
Why do you keep saying this to me?
Do you think I'm that young?
Why can't you tell me what you're doing?
Mom, you know what?
You can't do it.
You're still cutting those you dislike out of your life.
How can you open up your mind to help others?
I think it's already safe in here.
This was my mom's house
when she was a kid
before my grandpa became rich.
My brother once used this house as a store,
and Mom asked him to close it down.
Luckily,
there's plenty of stuff left to use.
But your mom seems to know nothing about what happened last night.
Honestly, I would have believed what she said
if she hadn't treated us three kids like that.
Why are you laughing?
I'm laughing in tears.
Honestly,
I think your mom just probably wants to handle me,
separating us from each other for good,
like how she did to Kanya and me.
Shit. What the hell?
Pali.
Now, think carefully.
Did you sleep with someone's wife again?
Her husband is probably here to make you pay for it.
Nonsense.
I haven't slept with anyone anymore.
This has nothing to do with me.
From now on, you must be careful
when you make friends or meet someone new
(because I'm not sure anymore)
(what else our family will have to go through.)
DIRECTED BY CHAINARONG TAMPONG
Men and women can never be friends.
They can, actually,
if they don't think of each other that way.
Are you stealing?
I bought it to share with everyone.
Thanks for letting me move here.
You know well what I want.
Women and men can really be friends.
I will return the best favor
to make it worth your generosity.
I'll help you.
Don't you know Tam has a crush on you?
Are you hiding something from us?
Just say it.
Don't make it such a big deal.
Why does it have to be Tam?
She likes me.
Perfect.
Kong, if you want to date someone,
can I be one of your choices?
You guys are breaking the first rule so soon.
I'm sure this will be fun.