=Bloom in Turmoil=
=Episode 8=
Zhaoyang, I love someone else.
I cannot marry you.
I hope you can understand.
Shiqi.
Xinnian.
It really is you.
I'm not dreaming, right?
You're not dreaming.
It really is me.
Xinnian, I love you.
You came back
because you love me too, right?
Yes.
I love you.
Don't you have anything to say?
About my family.
Lu Shiqi's power is growing day by day.
He's losing all respect for you.
He openly defies you at court
and even challenges you for the girl.
Shiqi forged evidence
of the Lu family's treason.
He is currently the Emperor's favorite.
He framed the Lu family
to win the Emperor's favor.
That ungrateful wretch
betrayed the family who raised him.
My Lord, you must plan ahead.
(Forging evidence.)
(So it was you who made
my family bear the infamy.)
And that letter.
I believe Lu Shiqi must have made
a secret deal with the North Land.
Even you have been deceived by him.
My Lord, General Lu's procession
has arrived.
The bridal sedan is waiting outside.
Let's go.
(I still held onto illusions about you.)
(Lu Shiqi, you deserve to die.)
I thought
you slaughtered my family
because I betrayed you.
But I never imagined you would forge
evidence of my grandfather's treason,
making my family bear eternal infamy.
We treated you well.
Why did you do this?
True or not, I don't care.
Just give me your word...
I'm so foolish.
I held onto a sliver of hope about you.
You watched me every day searching
for the truth like a headless chicken,
while you hid everything from me
in the name of love.
Lu Shiqi.
Is this what you call love?
I truly did love you.
But now,
I truly hate you.
General.
Shijiu, step back.
She wants to kill me.
Then let her.
Lady Lu, the general was forced.
If you kill him, you'll regret it.
For the rest of your life.
Silence!
Yunhe, come out.
Lu Shiqi, hand Yunhe over to me.
Xinnian.
Don't be afraid.
Wait for me in my room.
Shijiu, take good care of Xinnian.
Greetings, My Lord.
You brought so many people.
Want to ruin my wedding night?
Lu Shiqi, hand over Yunhe.
Yunhe?
How could Yunhe be here?
She took the gold
and chose such a charming man.
Then have Zhaoyang come out and see me.
How unlucky.
My wife has just gone to bed.
Wife?
Is the person inside really your wife?
My sister?
Of course.
You personally witnessed
Zhaoyang enter the bridal sedan.
Our time is too precious
for interruption.
Don't think I don't know who is inside.
I won't leave today
until I see Zhaoyang.
I'm afraid you will be
disappointed today.
I must see Yunhe.
Alive or dead,
I must see her.
Men!
What do we do?
Shijiu, what did you mean earlier?
Lady Lu, if you want to know,
save our general.
He is a lord with no real power.
He can't do anything to the general.
Refusing an imperial decree
to marry is a capital offense.
Lady Lu, you cannot go out.
If you go out,
everything the general did
for you will be in vain.
If you insist on barging in today,
you'll have to step over my corpse.
Do you think I won't?
Brother.
What did you call me?
Thank you for finding me
such a good match.
General Shiqi treats me very well.
Do you take me for a fool?
How could you be Zhaoyang?
You are clearly...
Brother.
It was you who watched me
enter the bridal sedan chair
and marry him with great fanfare.
Or you think it'd have been better
if your sister had eloped on the way
and defied the Emperor's decree?
What are you saying?
You must be joking.
My Lord, a word in private?
General Lu, do you think
such petty tricks
can stop me?
My Lord, Zhaoyang has a secret lover.
If this dirty little secret leaks out,
your noble name will be utterly shamed.
I will eliminate them from this world
to uphold our family honor.
My Lord, this is not merely
a family matter.
Zhaoyang defying the decree
is a capital offense.
Surely, you cannot emerge unscathed.
Why not let this woman take her place?
Consider this a favor to me.
What if I refuse?
Don't push me too far.
We know each other's secrets
far too well.
Do not let a woman
destroy your years of planning.
Report! Urgent military news
from the North Land!
The enemy has invaded.
Cities have fallen.
My Lord, General,
His Majesty summons you.
The realm or a woman,
which weighs more heavily?
Surely, you have your own resolution.
After you.
We shall discuss
countermeasures with His Majesty.
Good.
Very good.
Let's go.
(Bloom Pavilion)
Strike.
Master, I beg you for mercy.
Yunhe only did it
to overturn the Lu family's case.
What does it have to do with the lord?
I already showed mercy when she
approached the lord without permission.
But playing the bride
to get back into the Lu Manor?
Does she have any idea
who the lord is?
You're right.
I accept punishment.
The lord is of the most noble birth.
And you played him
for a fool repeatedly!
That's unforgivable.
Master.
Yunhe was trained by me.
I'm responsible for her mistakes.
Let me take the remaining punishment.
Fanghua.
I have vital information.
Please dismiss the others.
Leave us.
I did this to spare you heartache.
What did you say?
I can't destroy the bond
between you and the lord,
so I must leave the lord's mansion.
I can see
your deep affection for the lord.
How did you know of my feelings for him?
The look in one's eyes when they
love someone cannot be hidden.
I once had it,
so I know.
Master.
(Fanghua, the Emperor has ordered me
to the North Land for peace talks.)
(I must leave at one.)
(Take care of yourself.)
(I'll return soon.)
(Lu Shiqi is ruthless and vindictive.)
(He must die.)
Yunhe, since you've already impersonated
Lady Zhaoyang to marry Lu Shiqi,
use that to kill him.
♪The moon kisses the blossom♪
♪Red beans bloom in stealth♪
♪Black hair entwined♪
♪Bound half a life to fate♪
♪The undone chess game♪
♪Is set up anew♪
♪Pieces clatter against the cliff♪
♪Longing shatters in my heart♪
♪A cold blade sunders every vow♪
♪In memory's abyss♪
♪How can regrets be filled?♪
♪When the wind blows♪
♪Candle shadows lean♪
♪A silhouette burns my eyes♪
♪Even if I crush mountains,
rivers run dry♪
♪Just to undo the knot inside♪
♪Even if true hearts
are buried in eternal night♪
♪I'd still wish to dwell
in memories bright♪
♪Shadows in the game♪
♪Truth's hard to tame♪
♪Wanting closeness,
kept apart by worlds between♪
♪Wanting to forget,
but memories replay their sting♪
♪A tear of hatred♪
♪Falls onto fingertip near♪
♪With obsession♪
♪I mend the world's♪
♪Ever-changing cracks♪