I love you.
Takumi.
I know.
Stop it. Look forward.
Forward.
What's wrong? Don't you believe me?
- That I'm in love with Takumi.
- That's not it!
Hey, Saki Giichi!
What are you whispering about with your neighbor?
Stand up.
Yes.
Saki.
What is the population of Moscow?
I've never been to Moscow, so I wouldn't know.
Oh, is that so?
Then what places do you know?
Well...
United States, Japan, UK, France, Ireland, Austria,
Switzerland, Italy, Spain, Sri Lanka.
And...
You may sit down.
But be quiet.
Yes.
Now then.
Regarding population migration after World War II...
It can be broadly divided into
migration to the Americas and to Russia.
Of these, immigration to Russia...
because Russia shares a land border
with many European countries...
the circumstances were rather unique.
(Mouthing) I love you.
This school, nestled deep in the mountains...
is an isolated, all-boys boarding school.
Its name is Shido Gakuin High School.
The school was founded...
in the early Showa period.
I hear that it once only admitted...
the sons of prominent families.
But now, even boys from ordinary families...
study here side by side.
Hey, Takabayashi.
This is for the exhibition.
Ah, thanks.
Yeah, it looks pretty good.
(Student Council Room)
Compared to when it was first established...
its aristocratic atmosphere...
has faded considerably.
However...
among them...
is a transfer student from the United States.
An extraordinarily wealthy young man.
Saki Giichi.
Known as...
Gii.
That Genda...
he always has it out for me.
He calls on me at least once every class.
Well, maybe you shouldn't do things
that make the teacher mad.
But I just want to tell you I love you, Takumi.
You say it so often...
it sounds like you're kidding.
Takumi.
I'm serious.
I know.
Then right here...
kiss me.
Huh?!
Well?
Go on.
I don't want to die yet.
Why would you die?
Gii has absolutely no idea.
My high school life...
has already been turned completely upside down.
That's right.
It all started on that day.
When I became a second-year...
the dorm roommate assignments were posted.
Huh?
What am I going to do?
Just by being Gii's roommate...
I'm already getting a ton of unwanted attention.
And on top of that...
if people find out that Gii and I are a couple...
Hey, if you don't hurry,
we'll lose our seats in the cafeteria.
You're right, Akaike-kun!
Let's go.
- Hey! Wait up, Takumi!
- Don't run.
Let's go, Takumi! Hurry!
I told you, don't run.
"Takumi-kun series -Drama-"
(Episode 1)
This is rare.
You're not with Gii.
Well...
Gii and Akaike-kun are still...
You're as predictable as ever.
Never mind that.
You'd better not get too close to Gii.
Otherwise, people might get the wrong idea
about your "relationship."
"The wrong idea?"
Friends with benefits.
You know, sex partners.
Friends with...
You've got to be kidding me.
Gii and I just happen to be roommates,
and happen to be the class and vice class presidents.
But you and Gii are alone in your room every night.
There's no way people will believe nothing's happening.
If you fooled around with every roommate you had,
things would be a total mess.
Gii is different.
Huh?
Don't tell me...
Nogawa-kun.
You have a thing for Gii?
That's not what I said.
Hayama.
Sorry for the wait.
Oh.
Here, this is for you, Takumi.
Thanks.
Thanks for the food.
Gii and I...
are friends with benefits...
Is that what everyone thinks of us?
Come in.
Excuse me.
Not you again, Shingyoji.
Working late, Arata-san.
I don't recall giving you permission to enter.
Stay back.
I can't let you see these documents.
Sorry.
Working overtime again?
It's routine.
The student council has a ton of work.
The other members already went home for the day.
Oh, I see.
Arata-san.
Any plans for Golden Week?
Didn't you hear me?
I probably can't go home.
You too, right?
Yes.
I have to train hard for the summer tournament.
The main players are second and third-years,
but first-years still have a shot.
Don't get discouraged. Keep it up.
- Yes! I'll do my best!
- Stop.
Do not come within two meters of me.
Ah.
Sorry...
Wait for me, Arata-san!
Arata-san! Arata-san!
Please don't ignore me, Arata-san!
Let's go back to the dorm together!
Stop.
Listen up.
From now on, do not invade my personal space. Ever.
Goodbye.
That's so harsh...
Arata-san.
By the way, what's "personal space"...?
Ah.
Hello.
I remember...
That boy...
He's a first-year...
Takumi.
Toshihisa.
I've been worried about you.
We were roommates during our first year,
so I could still look out for you.
Yeah.
I'm grateful.
You were the only one, Toshihisa,
who treated me kindly.
You were in pretty bad shape
during your first year, Takumi.
You would go ages without saying a word.
And you got all those weird nicknames.
Emotionless.
Apathetic.
Cold-blooded.
Even human-hater and germaphobe, right?
Yeah.
Ah, sorry.
That was a bit blunt of me.
Bringing up things you're sensitive about.
It's the truth, though.
But you know...
when I heard who your roommate was this year...
that it was Gii...
I thought it was going to be a disaster.
But now, I'm actually relieved.
Huh?
Because...
with someone like Gii...
I doubt he'd be swayed by any rumors.
And I feel like he's someone
who can really understand you.
So, how is it?
Are you and Gii getting along?
Yeah.
I guess...
it's going okay.
That's a relief.
Takumi, aren't you going to take a shower?
Oh, um...
I still have a little homework left.
I want to finish it up.
Homework?
We have homework?
Oh...
An English essay.
You're so lucky your English is good, Gii.
I was in the US until I was 15,
so of course it is.
Can I borrow your pen?
Sure.
Here.
Let's see...
This sentence is really well-written.
But a different word might work better here.
For example...
Instead of "uncleanly"...
try something like "dirty."
Hey, aren't you going to bed?
Hmm...
Pretty soon.
Let's get some sleep.
Just a little longer.
I've been letting my schoolwork slide
because of club activities.
Well then...
I'm going to head to bed first.
Okay.
Yeah, you go ahead.
Oh, sorry.
You won't be able to sleep with the light on.
There's still some time before lights out.
I'll go work in the common room.
Good night.
What's his deal?
Yoshizawa, you idiot.
Morning.
Good... morning.
Hey, wait up.
You're...
You're Hayama Takumi, aren't you?
Yes.
And you know who I am, right?
No...
I'm sorry.
Well, I can't let you go
until you get to know me.
Whoa, hold on...
Relax, I'm not gonna bite.
See? I just wanted to ask you out.
It's an invitation to a date.
I appreciate the offer, but...
I'm not interested.
Come on, wait.
Hey, Takumi!
What's going on?
Oh.
Gii.
I'll ask you out again later!
That guy...
The captain of the third-year basketball team...
Nozaki.
(Disciplinary Committee Room)
Excuse me.
Oh, Akaike.
Sorry for calling you in during your lunch break.
It's no problem.
So, what did you need to see me about?
It's about our first meeting.
As the committee chairman, I'd like to make a list
of things we need to do beforehand.
Have a seat.
Oh, pardon me.
Could you give me a hand with that?
Of course.
Ever since last year...
I guess I'm the only weirdo willing to do a thankless job
like the Disciplinary Committee two years in a row.
I suppose so.
Well then, let's make that list.
Let's see...
First off...
We should probably put together
an agenda for the meeting.
Right.
What else?
For the school rule patrols, we go in pairs.
- Right.
- It might be a good idea to decide on the pairings beforehand.
- I see.
- Yes.
Takumi.
Pass me another roll.
Sure.
That's your fourth one, you know.
Thanks.
That guy Genda...
He seems to be holding a grudge,
ordering me around all the time.
I'm starving because of him.
Do you want this one?
I've already started it, though.
You're the best!
Ah...
Finally, I'm full.
Hey, Takumi...
Yeah?
Let me rest my head on your lap.
Huh?
I just want to rest a bit.
Wait, Gii...
- Wait a minute.
- I'm not asking for a kiss.
We're a couple, aren't we?
What's the big deal
about me resting my head on your lap?
Huh...
Just this is more than enough for me...
Mm.
Thanks.
Gii...
For so, so long...
I always felt like
he was from a world completely out of my reach...
For us to be like this...
How long can it possibly last?
Being a couple...
means that one day...
we'll surely take the next step...
Huh?
Takumi...
Oh, is lunch break over?
No...
That was...
the bell for the end of fifth period.
Oh no, fifth period was English.
I'm already so bad at it.
If the teacher gets on my case again...
What am I gonna do...?
Takumi.
In that case, let's just skip sixth period too.
Don't be ridiculous.
We have to go back.
Everyone's probably talking about us by now.
Talking about what...?
Isn't it obvious?
Us disappearing together for an hour.
About what Takumi...
and I were doing.
Oh...
- We should go back separately.
- That'll just look more suspicious.
Then what are we supposed to do?
Good question.
Instead of letting them make things up...
why don't we give them something real to talk about?
What do you mean by that...?
Let's enjoy ourselves so much we lose all track of time.
See ya, Gii!
You've got some nerve, Hayama.
Grades aside...
I never thought someone as serious
and straight-laced as you would skip class.
No, it's just that...
By the way, where's Gii?
He was with you, wasn't he?
No, he wasn't.
Hmm.
So, where were you?
Uh, I accidentally fell asleep in the courtyard.
I see.
In that case...
I'll be sure to confirm that with Gii later.
I completely fell for Akaike-kun's leading questions.
Akaike-kun...
Just how much does he know about us?
In any case, from now on...
I have to be more careful.
Past tense...
Past perfect.
What does that even mean?
It's better to use "used to" here.
Huh?
Oh...
I see.
You've got a scientific mind, Takumi.
Because you're such a purist, you can't be satisfied
unless there's only one right answer.
- That's not true...
- Yes, it is.
You can't help but put a label on everyone.
"This guy is just a classmate..."
"This one is just an acquaintance..."
"And this guy is just my roommate."
When it comes to how other people's feelings might change...
you choose to ignore it, don't you?
Gii, what are you talking about...?
Because your own feelings never change, Takumi,
you just assume no one else's do either.
Gii...
Like what happened today...
You hated the idea of people thinking we were together.
That's why you ran away, isn't it?
Because I do hate being misunderstood!
Don't be an idiot! I'm in love with you, Takumi!
What man in this world...
can stay indifferent to the person he loves?
Have you ever once stopped to think about how I feel?
I'm sorry... Gii.
If "sorry" is all you can say...
Takumi...
Gii?!
I love you.
Takumi.
Stop it, Gii!
Gii is always true to his own heart.
But I...
I don't even understand my own feelings.
Why...
Takumi...
Besides...
there's a reason...
why I can't...
move forward.