YoYo English Channel YouTube
You told me that you were sick and couldn't go to the army.
I'm sick, too.
I'm not happy to go to the Alliance.
Isn't it a bad omen?
It makes sense.
You came to see me for...
Know yourself, know your enemy.
You can't fight without a fight.
You're still so vigilant.
I don't expect them to have any interest in me.
What about you?
Why don't you go to Zheng Qi Hall?
I'm not from the Alliance.
I'm not going to have fun.
Here it comes.
Welcome the one who has the honor of the sword of the Xuan Tian Gate.
Please.
I heard that the Xuan Tian Gate is hard-working and determined.
The heart of the cultivation can remove the demon and turn to darkness.
Do you think they will find the demon in my body?
You have my spirit ink on you.
It won't be found under normal circumstances.
What about the unusual situation?
It depends on whether you are lucky or not.
But I don't want to see him more than the Xuan Tian Gate.
Welcome Princess Su from Jing Hua Palace.
Please.
It's been proven that the Yuan family always shows up.
Back then in the Ming Yue Villa, you and Gao Xiu had an affair.
Oh no!
Sang Qi's army is attacking the village. Run!
Change the clothes on the big lady and her clothes.
The big lady is so beautiful.
You can die for her.
It's the greatest honor of your sword-slaying.
It's just some old stories about the evil master and the sword-slayer.
The South Prince is so generous and generous.
He is so kind.
You don't have to listen to such a dirty thing.
I have also seen it once.
The past days of Miss Mu were so bitter.
Stop it.
Don't pity me.
No need.
I don't want to pity Miss Mu.
If you can't kill me, just stand up.
Stand up and take back everything.
This is the truth of the world.
Chief Cang.
Chief He.
Last time you left, you were so handsome.
Chief Cang, how are you?
Please.
The leader of the neighboring island, He Xianwu,
looks like a carefree person.
I heard that he loves to adopt spiritual beasts.
Then he and Su Ning Zhen will meet.
They shouldn't fight.
In this case, it's not a big deal.
That's a good feeling.
Su Ning Zhen looks so fierce.
Someone has to stop him.
I'm going to kill him.
The sky in Bixiao Palace is really full of wealth.
Vice Princess Duan.
Welcome.
Please.
I heard that Fu Yuan Ting and Duan Xiaorong
are so rich.
This way, please.
Look at that.
He's wearing clothes from head to toe.
He's not a genius.
He's walking alone.
Everyone wants to go up and grab him.
He's Princess Fu Lansheng of Bixiao Palace.
Mother.
I'm going to play.
Go.
There's no better name than the world.
Nan Xu.
Vice Princess.
I heard that you came to Yongxue City, too.
So I came with you.
The beauty next to you is a stranger.
The new disciple of Yongxue City, Mu Xuan Ling.
This is Vice Princess.
Hello, Miss Mu.
I thought it was Gao Xiu Shi.
You said Gao Xiu Shi.
Could it be...
The first beauty in the fairy tale.
She's a fan of the Palace of Pure Flower.
It's hard to imagine that she's even more beautiful than you.
They're all beautiful.
Different styles.
Are you a cultivator?
Yes.
Can't you tell?
I'm a gold-billed spirit.
If you're in trouble,
you can ask me for help.
Is Nan Shiyue's friend my friend?
We met for the first time.
Maybe there's no gift.
These are the magic weapons I found a few days ago.
They're all for women.
Do you like them?
These are all the magic weapons of the heaven.
What's the big deal?
I have more.
Bixiao Palace is rich in the world.
Princess Fushao is the richest person in the world.
Since she insisted on giving them to you,
I'll take them.
Take them.
Father.
What's that sound?
My...my spirit beast.
What's the spirit beast's name?
It's father.
Are you my father?
Come out.
Let him out.
Father.
Are you my father?
He...his father is missing.
I think it's obvious that I'm a person.
Mother said that father is the richest person in the world.
But my money was also given by father and mother.
So, the richest person in the world should be my father.
Brother.
There are many people who call me brother.
Count your voice.
Come on.
Brother gave you some gifts.
These are all for the spirit tribe.
How can you have a magic weapon for the spirit tribe?
I have three thousand spirit tribes.
You have three thousand spirit slaves?
No, no, no.
They are all good friends to me.
We often play together.
Little thing.
What's your father's name?
I'll go back and ask you.
Fu Cang Li.
This name is indeed from our Bixiao Palace.
I will pay attention to it.
I'll go first.
Two.
Three.
Goodbye.
I won't see you off.
I know.
You just wanted to say that he is the world's number one leader.
Right?
Excuse me.
Leader, you are inside.
Thank you.
It seems that this is the master of the spirit tribe.
He is really handsome and elegant.
He is not far from Miss Mu.
He is so quiet and dignified.
He is indeed a good match for Young Master Xie.
Why does he always look at me?
He doesn't need to be so exaggerated when he sees a beauty.
He is just a little girl.
Forget it.
I'll go out and represent the Jin Hua Palace.
I won't bother him.
He is really elegant.
He really has the temperament of the Young City Leader's wife.
Thank you, Young City Leader.
I wonder if you have something important to call us to come to Snow City.
Why don't you see the leader?
Senior.
Snow City is in a mess.
The leader is in danger.
How could this be?
Who did this?
It must be Sang Qi and Xiu Xian Ge.
Xiu Xian Ge?
Xiu Xian Ge and Sang Qi are together.
The jade seal of the Jin Hua Palace was stolen by them.
The leader was killed because of this.
They are taking all the jade seals.
I wonder if there is anything strange in your family today?
I haven't found anything strange.
May I ask where the jade seal of Snow City is now?
The enemy hasn't won.
The jade seal is still in my Snow City.
I told you earlier that you should attack Dark Citadel first.
And kill all those dirty things.
The Dark Clan will not die.
I'm afraid it's hard to go there without permission.
Yes, we should be cautious.
It's not right to lose our alliance.
Sang Qi came back to take the Soul Bead.
And open the barrier of the Immortal Formation.
The priority now is to select the new leader.
And give the Soul Bead to him.
Thank you, Young Master.
Thank you, City Leader.
You are the best leader of the current Alliance.
I think you can take the Soul Bead.
I was in Mount Liangjie.
I was attacked by the Immortal Formation.
I was trapped for seven days.
I was badly injured.
I can't recover my spiritual power.
Now the situation is critical.
I'm afraid I can't take the Soul Bead.
As long as you say something,
I will ask the world to cure you.
Besides, I have a lot of people in the world
who have the safest gold warehouse in the world.
It's enough to keep the Soul Bead.
Now the situation is critical.
How can we afford to delay it?
Besides,
when did you really think about the great cause of the Alliance?
Sun Ning Zhen, if you really want to be the leader,
just say it.
Why are you here to say that?
It doesn't matter.
I have been guarding the two mountains
and fighting against the enemies.
I'm the only one who can do it.
You saved the jade seal.
You are also in the Palace of Pure Flower.
If you become the leader,
I'm afraid you can't protect anything.
He Xiang Wu, you always fight against the spiritual clan.
I'm afraid you've forgotten your identity.
Two, don't talk.
Calm down.
I'll beat you to death.
The one who sent the sword
is like the one who was in the Palace of Pure Flower.
I had to do it.
Since the one who sent the sword said it,
then I won't say any more big truth.
Six thousand years ago,
the Qian Guang Army first established the Alliance
to unite the people and fight against the enemies.
Now that the leader Xie's bones are not yet cold,
the enemy is still in a lot of confusion.
You have to separate yourself?
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
It seems like theA да,
in the past days,
please consider the party leader positions in the city.
You are selected the day after tomorrow.
I was the most proud of Dao City among the Alliance.
Now that he's gone, I've lost a lot of friends.
I think that Xue Chen is suspicious.
That's why he didn't say anything
and brought us to Yongxue City.
Then the man that Master Xie suspected
naturally included you.
Now that he's the City Leader, no one can trust him.
That's what I should do.
If Dao City sees it, they'll be relieved.
Then why don't you fight for the position of the Leader?
How can you let Su Ning Zhen be arrogant?
The old Crown Prince and the Leader
are fighting for the position of the Leader.
What's the Leader doing here?
I don't want to be troubled by these things.
I don't know why he's fighting for the position of the Leader.
This way, please.
Su Ning Zhen
Princess Su and the rest of the members are resting in this courtyard.
This way, please.
Qiu Ming
Master
What's the matter?
I just didn't expect that the leader of Xie was killed by a thief.
A lot of things have happened during this time.
How can the young princess of Jing Hua Palace be so afraid of the world?
Qiu Ming, you need to practice more than martial arts and mind.
I understand, Master.
When I become the Leader,
you must be able to inherit Jing Hua Palace.
I'm sorry, Father.
I have to leave now.
I don't want you to worry about me.
I'm just going to leave.
I'll go with you.
I'm going with you.
I won't be afraid of you anymore.
I'll go with you.
Now, everything is just a dream.
How can it be so absurd?
You didn't join the dream because of this reason?
This is the difference between us.
For the matter of Yan Fan,
I can be a guard.
But you always think about saving him.
So I can be free in Yun Xiu Villa.
But you are trapped in the seven winds and the bitter snow.
You are all alone.
Chief Xie is the mirror of the magic.
The person who can kill him should be among them.
You want to pretend that your spirit energy hasn't recovered yet.
But that inner world may not be able to write.
In these days,
there should be a time of self-killing.
I'll wait.
When can you think about your own life?
If you die,
I may be sad.
I'll try my best not to die.
Senior,
what do you think about this?
You should have done it long ago.
Senior, even for the sake of the world,
you should be the leader.
I'm not as good as Chief Xie in terms of Taoism.
In terms of cultivation,
I'm even worse than him.
How can you be worse than him if you haven't fought before?
Even though Chief Xie is born with a strong body,
he is still so young.
Can he be compared with Senior's cultivation?
Chief Xie is pure and pure.
But I have a bad feeling.
I don't deserve to be the leader.
Senior.
Chief, you must be tired.
Let him rest.
Xuan Xin, you call me Master.
Do you always help the leader?
You shouldn't have pulled me, you should have persuaded him.
The leader has his own idea.
Others shouldn't force his will.
Others?
Your master, I'm an outsider?
Yes, I'm an outsider too.
You...
I shouldn't have picked you up back then.
I don't want you to be angry with me now.
It's hard to get rich if you're soaked in the mud.
Master, you're too late to regret.
I wanted to come to Yongxue City to play.
But I didn't expect that the leader would be left in the crisis.
This thief is really bold.
He came to Yongxue City to fight.
If I catch him, I will...
What's wrong with you?
You can't be the hero now.
Before the
promotion, you must save my life.
You must know that your battlefield is a hundred years away.
You will be the leader of the Alliance.
Mother, you look down on me.
What am I?
Master Xie is a man of the heaven.
He's a strong man.
No one can be of any help in the past hundred years.
Even if he's not the leader, he'll be the next one.
Besides, he's still young.
He can be the leader for at least a few hundred years.
You know nothing.
Although the statue is a thousand years old,
how many people can really be treated with respect?
Besides, Xie Xuechen's sword is the best in the world.
I don't have it.
It's a sword that doesn't leave a trace.
It's very durable.
Maybe, as long as you can live for a long time,
you don't have to fight.
Even Hao killed those opponents.
I'm so tired.
Look at what you said.
Is my greatest value just living?
I don't agree.
You're still reliable.
Son, your greatest value is to give Bixiao a young lady who has the right and the right to hold the factory.
Only then can Bixiao continue to grow.
Father.
Fu Yanting.
You said you used these scourges on me.
You want to ruin my son?
I'm ruined?
No.
Didn't you choose me as your husband because you wanted to have a handsome son?
You and I are not on the same level.
Don't talk about anyone.
But if I had known that your beautiful and beautiful beauty was so short,
I would have been better off looking for someone else.
Look.
You finally said it.
Do you still think about that person?
Who?
Who else can I think of?
It's none of your business if you don't want to think about it.
I'm almost out of my mind.
It's none of my business.
Father.
I'm still here.
Go away.
Young princess, you...
The late He Tianyu?
That...
The princess and the elder are currently studying the future development of Bixiao Palace.
Just do what you should do.
It's fine.
This couple is so similar.
They are so hard to get along with.
To get married?
Only fools can get married.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Are you a fan of Hungry давай就운
I can't calm down any more.
You are so cool.
You...
beepin' in the middle of the night
You're too aggressive
Your bed's crumbling
Your friend
You're scary
You
No need to chase her. Let her go back and report to the police.
This is your plan with Nan Xun Yue.
You are the enemy of Ruo Yi.
You are really despicable.
You should let me participate in it.
You should just forget it.
You are too good at this kind of despicable thing.
You are back in Yong Xue City and you are at your own home.
You are being attacked.
How is it?
I was lucky to be here in time.
The imperial edict has not arrived yet.
They won't kill me now.
They are just here to see how much my spiritual power has recovered.
I should be the one who is in charge.
If I hadn't come just now,
how are you planning to end this assassination?
According to the plan, I will get hurt.
Then I will send out a signal to the players.
I will bring the elders and the disciples to come and kill them.
This is another way to kill yourself.
Where is the sword I gave you?
I didn't say that you are going to be an ordinary person.
Why are you still wearing a waistcoat?
Thank you, City Leader.
My sword skills are very bad.
If I brought a sword to save you,
I would be laughing to death.
Also, your calculation is too fast.
Then I should thank you.
Can you calculate after you finish?
What are you afraid of me doing in the middle of the night?
In terms of lying,
isn't your progress a bit too fast?
Although the City Leader is busy with his affairs,
he doesn't even have time to teach his disciples to wield swords.
But as a disciple of Snowblade City,
protecting the City Leader is an honor.
Why are you so suspicious?
Stop looking at me like that.
You are guilty.
You are right.
There are many bad things that I want to do.
But tonight...
Tonight, I just want to suddenly come and see you.
Xie Xue Chen,
I haven't seen you for a day.
I miss you.
Thank you, City Leader.
Am I pretty?
The color is like a fake.
It's been a hundred years.
I think in your eyes,
you are the most beautiful person in the world.
there is only a difference between good and evil and strength.
Do you know in my eyes,
what is the difference between people?
Except for Xie Xue Chen,
there are other people.
How dare you, Mu Xuan Ling!
You didn't get up and stayed up all night, but you sneaked out!
You disturbed City Leader.
You are so ridiculous.
You even affected City Leader's rest with other colleagues.
You even brought bad luck.
Do you know your crime?
I know.
I will go back and think about it.
City Leader, your bed is too easy to break.
Next time, you should change to a solid one.
You are so rude!
Mu Xuan Ling!
You...
City Leader.
Xue Chen, you and him...
You can't stand it if you are too strong.
You should change to a solid one.
I...
It's late.
Elder, go to sleep.
Brother Dao Cheng,
I was unlucky to use Xue Meng Chen.
It's my fault for not controlling it.
Honorable Superior.
Do you think that I am a good person?
What do you think of the mortal world?
The mortal world seems to be meaningless compared to the dark realm.
The new demon, the holy one, is far more powerful than the dark realm.
Even you can feel it.
Why can't he see it clearly?
Are you talking about the holy one?
He has spent too much time on the human clan.
The Xiu Xian Ge has been sent.
Xue Chen's spiritual power hasn't recovered yet.
Go to Snowblade City and take the Soul Bead.
Hand it over to me.
If anyone is in the way, kill him.
Yes.
I'll go.
Who is Mr. Nan talking to?
Which lady is she?
If Feng Yao knows that someone calls her a lady,
she will be upset.
I told Feng Yao to investigate the Xiu Xian Ge.
After the chaos in the Jing Hua Palace, they disappeared.
That's not strange.
But they have been in the mortal world.
They have taken in many human and spiritual clans.
It seems that someone will notice them.
That's right.
Feng Yao has found a spiritual clan near the city of Bixiao Palace.
She claims to have seen the Xiu Xian Ge.
She said that the leader is a young man over the age of twenty.
He is a gentleman with a good manner.
The other is a dark-skinned man.
But he can hear that he is a young man.
He calls the leader as the leader.
Dark-skinned?
That means he doesn't want people to know his real identity.
Then why does the leader dare to show his true face?
Maybe he is afraid of nothing.
He has been in the mortal world for so many years.
I'm afraid that it's not the right time to completely eliminate him.
The Xiu Xian Ge is not eliminated yet.
Sang Qi should be released from the coffin.
What will he do next?
The Dark Clan's flag.
I didn't expect that there are so many people who miss the Alliance.
That's great.
This is a waste of time.
It's time to choose another better puppet.
Sister.
What's wrong, A Bao?
There is something scary around here.
It's like the place where the Dark Clan was.
The Dark Clan?
Which direction?
East... East South.
Watch A Bao for me.
He is timid.
He might be scared when he sees the Dark Clan.
I'll go and check.
Are you alone?
That's enough.
I think you've already felt it.
I'll go to see the City Leader Xie.
Xuan Xin, you take the disciples to set up the formation.
We must find the Dark Clan and get rid of them.
Yes.
It's been a long time since we met.
The Saint of Sand is still so heavy.
I don't know which one is stronger.
I think it's the Dark Clan.
It's you, Chi Ying.
You've been fighting for so many years.
It's not the first time you've been killed by me.
Just get used to it.
The Saint ordered me to say something to the Saintess.
Good people play for a long time.
Do you really forget who you are?
The Saintess came with the task of the Saint.
But she didn't act.
The Saint had to suspect that you were trying to do something.
Since the Master told you everything,
you should know that I have my own plan.
I hate it when people talk nonsense when I'm working.
If Master doesn't like it, you're not qualified.
Stop!
You're really not a good person.
How dare you hurt the innocent?
Please save me, Master.
I found her magic.
She wants to kill me.
Gao Qiuming, are you stupid?
She's been revived by the Dark Clan.
Youxue City has a protective barrier.
How could the Dark Clan come in?
Get out of here.
I shouldn't have hidden it from you.
The Dark Clan is really not a good thing.
Gao Qiuming, the Alliance is full of fools.
You're one of them.
The Alliance is full of fools.
What are you going to do?
Gao Qiuming, I'll settle the score today.
Yan Zheng?
Is there really a case?
I was so smart.
I shouldn't have blamed him.
I'll take care of it.
The Dark Clan is full of fools.
It seems that I can't escape from the Dark Clan
as long as I practice the Dark Palace.
I found it.
I won.
You killed your fellow clan
and stepped on their bodies and blood
to get here.
If they don't die, I'll die.
Since only one person can live,
it can only be me.
Not bad.
It's very exciting.
My good disciple told me
that you'd rather die than live.
You want to kill me?
I'm not afraid of you.
What are you laughing at?
I want revenge.
They killed the only person in this world
who treated me well
and gave me warmth.
I want power.
I want the power to make you revenge.
I want revenge.
Remember, the more painful you are,
the stronger you will be.
You won.
From now on,
you are not only my disciple,
but also the saintess of Dark Yu.
I'm sorry.