The
I'm not a low-level spy.
But since you're here,
you should trap Xie Xue Chen first.
I'll save him at the most critical moment.
In this way,
he owes me another life.
But to be honest,
the greed of the world
often escapes from the heart.
I'm afraid that
the greed of the world
often escapes from the heart.
I'm a little curious
what the greed of the world
will be.
Miao Miao.
Miao Miao, where are you?
Where are you?
Miao Miao.
Miao Miao, come out.
Miao Miao, I brought you a little fish cake.
Pick up the sword.
Father.
You can't throw your sword away
at any time.
I know I was wrong.
Are you looking for that little snow cat?
It won't come to ask for snow.
I'll kill it.
Why?
What's that look on your face?
Father, although the snow cat is a monster,
it doesn't harm people.
Why did you kill it?
It's my new cat.
You can't be kind to a person who has a heart.
Did you forget?
No, I don't understand.
Mother said that
you can't be kind to a person who has a heart.
Why can't you be kind?
You can save people with your heart.
Is this your way of doing things?
Answer me.
Yes.
Okay, if so,
you should break your love.
If you have a bias,
how can you tolerate people with great love?
If one day you have a choice,
one side is love, the other side is the world.
Can you give up your love
to save people?
Why can only choose one?
Life is short,
and it's more rare.
Xue Chen,
you will never change.
You will be the king of the human world,
and the king of the three realms.
Until that day,
the fate of the world's people
will be in your hands.
Love will only become your weakness,
and it will also make the world's people
in danger.
Since you have the right to be a king,
and your heart is devoted to the people,
then your heart will be
free from all evil and die.
You shouldn't choose to love only one person
or one thing
including yourself.
Why is Xie Xue Chen's greed and desire cage
different from others?
Because he has no greed and desire.
No greed and desire?
How is that possible?
He has the highest level of cultivation.
He is the best in the world.
He has been forced to cultivate
the path of heartlessness since he was a child.
A person who doesn't even care
about his own life,
what kind of greed and desire can he have?
Yu Ying,
can your greed and desire cage
still see more memories?
For example, what he went through
ten years ago?
Saintess,
I am in the greed and desire cage.
What has nothing to do with greed and desire
can't be looked back.
If that's the case,
it's useless for you.
Saintess,
what do you mean?
It's so obvious.
Can't you see it?
You want to kill me?
We can just
play a show for Xie Xue Chen.
You don't have to kill me.
If you kill me,
my body will know.
It seems that you don't know
that there is a flaw in the painting list.
What flaw?
When you die,
you will know.
You really betrayed An Yu.
I will kill you.
I didn't expect that
our Xie Shao Sect Leader,
a master of the magic mirror,
would take away
my weak girl's power.
That's not kind.
Weak girl?
When you threatened me,
why didn't you think
if you were thick-headed?
Fine.
I'll give it to you.
From now on,
as long as it's mine,
you can keep it if you want.
You're dead.
You're the one who's dead.
How did you die?
How would I know?
You don't know?
Why would she know?
No.
She died and she didn't know.
How would you know?
It's obvious that
there's a flaw in the painting list.
The body can only sense
the death of the projection.
But it doesn't know
what happened before the projection.
It doesn't know who killed the projection.
If I knew
which idiot
made the list,
I would have to
take him down.
Enough.
Stop talking about the painting.
Before you left,
you called a man
who was so powerful
and powerful
that he would catch the Saintess
and Xie Xuechen back.
What happened?
You're good.
Go ahead.
When I train the projection,
you don't have to...
Although I don't know
whether the projection was killed by Xie Xuechen
or by the Saintess,
I can be sure that
someone killed them.
Then when we meet again,
there won't be any more surprises.
Aren't you afraid that
after he wakes up,
he will remember what happened just now?
What if an ordinary human
goes crazy?
No.
After he was resurrected by the Dark Clan,
he doesn't know anything when he wakes up.
Even if someone tells him,
even if he wants to ask a thousand times,
he can't remember.
You know it so well.
Did you
get resurrected by the Dark Clan?
Young Master Xie,
I just blocked one arrow for you.
Even if it's a sword from the illusion,
it's painful to be stabbed.
Why don't you care about me?
How about
you eat the demon elixir
that you just turned into?
I can also increase my power.
What's the benefit
of God's increase of power?
Hey,
can you find a reason?
Where are you going?
Yunxiu Manor, right?
There are only two places
closest to this place.
One is Jinghua Palace.
The second is Yunxiu Manor.
Although Jinghua Palace
is one of the five sects of the Alliance,
now you're not sure
who the traitor is.
Of course you won't go there rashly.
Although Yunxiu Manor
is not in the list of the Alliance,
it is known to the world
by its clever formation.
It's said that
the owner of Yunxiu Manor
has developed a conveyor belt.
It can transport people
up to ten thousand miles in a flash.
You want to use the conveyor belt
to return to Yongxue City as soon as possible,
right?
Miss Mu,
I'm not a person who doesn't know kindness.
You saved me.
An Li said I should thank you.
But we're not on the same path.
You follow me like this.
When my spiritual power is restored,
we will meet again.
Why don't we start from now
and go our separate ways?
You should know that
there is a word
called a book and a map.
If there is a way to stop me,
I will make all the way.
Isn't that good?
Why do you have to follow me?
What do you want to do?
What if I say
I want to give up my life to vote for you?
I don't want to.
What?
I want to give up my life
to vote for you.
I don't want to.
I have to.
You think
it's fun to be with Sang Qi?
Most of the spiritual clans
are driven by human clans.
I'm only forced to obey him.
Actually, I didn't want to
I'm also quite good at it.
Then you can just destroy the Demon Palace and become an ordinary person.
My spiritual bridge is broken.
I can't repair my spiritual power.
The Demon Palace
is the path I take to live and die.
But Xie Xue Chen,
if I'm willing to destroy the Demon Palace
for you
and become an ordinary person,
will you protect me?
Yes.
You think I'll believe you?
It doesn't matter if you believe me or not.
You can't resist it anyway.
I have my own answer.
Before I find it,
please stay by my side
Thank you, Young Sect Leader.
They have the phantom elixir.
We also have the shadow-shadowing elixir.
The jade shadow has been trained to cast shadows.
I think it will be faster to eat and drink.
It will be even harder to walk.
If you want to avoid the search for the new demon,
you can't just rely on the shadow to hide.
The shadow-shadowing elixir can help people to hide their appearance.
When others see your face,
they will only think that your appearance is ordinary and ordinary.
They will be over-expected.
Will you kill me
or only do the work when others see your face?
Do whatever little sign you dare.
I also want it.
Ahh, right,
help me add it up.
Stupid.
How many dark clans have you killed?
Eight hundred without a thousand.
Then you killed less than me.
What are you remembering?
I'm remembering your wishes.
I heard that
two people can spend their lives together
only when they are of the same mind.
Why are you so alert to me?
I've been helping you
since we met.
You are so close to each other.
Then?
Go away.
The heart of a Taoist
is so powerful that it can kill hundreds of people.
But once it is attracted to the devil,
it is no different from mortals.
In the dark clans,
even if you have a spiritual power,
you will be like a snake.
Or,
this is what Miss Mu wants?
What do I want?
Don't you know?
We've been meeting for so long.
Why don't you ask
what kind of spiritual clan I am?
Don't you really want
to know more about me?
I don't ask.
You will tell me even if you don't.
I'm Teng Ling.
When I was a kid,
half of my face was
a demon's tattoo like a ten-fingered.
This is the monitor.
It's very big.
It's very awake.
People who have seen it before
will be able to see it.
You really don't remember at all.
I don't remember anything.
I just remember that
you really don't remember anything.
What did you say?
Nothing.
You're so arrogant.
It's getting late.
We should find a place to rest.
If you don't rest,
Ma Er will rest too.
People are all the same.
Ma Er is also in it.
Thank you, Chen.
I'm also in it.
Coming.
Another bottle of wine.
Okay.
Here's your wine.
Boss, the hotel.
Sir, I'm really sorry.
There are too many guests today.
Now,
only one room is left.
How about you and your servant
share a room?
No need.
Then you can live with my colleagues.
Very good.
What's good?
What are you looking at?
He's my husband.
I'm so rude.
I'm sorry.
Waiter.
Please come in.
Okay.
This way, please.
This way.
Those two seem to be strange.
They seem to be willing to do whatever they want.
Could they be kidnapped?
They seem to be very familiar.
I think so.
That man seems to be a good seller,
but he's not a common man.
Although he's not a good man,
he should be a good master.
That woman seems to be an ordinary person,
but she doesn't have the ability to kidnap others.
I heard there are many demons nearby.
Could it be...
Brother, you're thinking too much.
Those two are just ordinary people,
but they don't have the spirit of demons.
I heard that the people here are very generous.
There are often women who are very rich and force men to be rich.
That woman seems to be from a rich family.
Although the man is ordinary,
he has long waist and long legs.
He has a good sense of humor.
He must have something special.
Brother, you're more knowledgeable.
Thank you, Young Master.
I do have something special.
Take care, everyone.
You two, your rooms.
Room No. 1, Tianzi.
This way, please.
Looking at the embroidery on the clothes of the embroidery artists,
it should be the embroidery of the Palace of Pure Flower.
What are they doing here?
Could it be that there are high-class embroidery artists in the Palace of Pure Flower here?
Does Young Master Xie want to be a star?
What do you want?
Are you worried that I will kill someone and silence him?
Could it be that you won't?
Maybe I will. Maybe I won't.
But you're right to be worried.
I'm not a good person.
You're not a person.
There's a demon aura.
I've hidden the aura for a long time.
Sir, please take care.
Sir, this way, please.
Master Gao.
It's been a long time.
Please sit down.
It's him.
I...
Please enjoy.
Thank you.
Senior, you're finally back.
Junior Brother Lu and I have checked the east side.
We didn't find anything.
What's going on over there?
Senior Song, you don't know.
Senior and I were attacked by the forest tribe.
What kind of forest tribe? Did you get hurt?
Senior Gao is a genius and has a high level of cultivation.
With our senior, of course we won't get hurt.
Oh, right.
It's this little demon beast with the eyes of a tiger.
Senior said that this is one of the ten great beasts, the Tartar.
Tartar?
His hearing and smell are all the best.
Where are the treasures?
They know best.
Give it to me.
Here.
Senior and I just ran into him.
I wonder where this little guy stole so many treasures.
Wow, they're all good treasures.
Yeah.
You, the Tartar, stole so many treasures.
If you're caught by the forest tribe,
I won't forgive you.
Senior, you seem to be very fond of this Tartar.
You don't want to train him into a spirit beast, do you?
Although the Tartar is a beast,
it looks very weak.
It's no match for the enemy.
I'm afraid it's not suitable to be a spirit beast.
I can fight against the enemy myself.
Why do you need the spirit beast to help?
Senior is right.
I heard that the Xie Young Master of the Snow City
is also a one-man show,
and never sees the spirit beast.
Senior Gao and the Xie Young Master are both talented people.
How can we compare?
That's right.
Okay, we still have a mission to do here.
Take a rest and keep looking.
Yes.
Your little mouse has golden ears.
It's cute.
The little mouse is timid.
It will be scared and even die of cowardice.
Look at its ears.
The more it rips, the brighter it is.
It looks pretty, but it's a brave battle.
Who is it?
Who?
There.
What are you doing?
They are coming to us for trouble.
That's your trouble.
It's already at this time.
Why are you still separating us?
What are you doing?
Cooperate with me.
Who are you?
Why did you break in?
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Get out.
Go.
Close the door.
They don't have the spirit beast's breath.
Get up.
I don't...
What if they are still eavesdropping at the door?
The show is over anyway.
How about we pretend to be real?
Let me go.
Have you had enough?
No.
You three search around today.
Who are you?
You are the one who is the most dangerous.
You are the most dangerous.
You three search around today.
Maybe there will be a spirit beast's breath at night.
Tomorrow morning, we will continue to find the spirit beast.
Okay.
Go.
So they are here to find you.
Now, in the Palace of Pure Flower, there is only one girl with a super position and a high gender.
That is the Miss of the Mingyue Villa.
Now, the disciple of the Princess of the Palace of Pure Flower, Gao Qiuming.
So what?
I heard that she is engaged to you.
She is in bed with me in front of the fiancee.
Is it exciting?
She is not my fiancee.
Are you afraid that I will misunderstand you and explain it to me?
Xie Xuechen, you should marry me.
I love people more than her.
I love you.
I have never seen a shameless person like you.
You are half right.
I am not a human.
But I am shameless.
Some?
The heart of the young master Xie is a little bit confused.
Is it because of me?
Do you fall in love with me?
Yes.
Kill the heart.
Good.
Kill the heart is also a heart.
At least you can remember me.
What I am most afraid of is that you don't remember me.
I am afraid that you will forget me.
Bursing sweet potatoes.
Didn't you run away just now?
What else do you come back for?
Did you sew on my body and have a baby?
Sister.
You can speak?
Will you turn into a human?
I can bring savory and refreshing
I won't hurt you
I... I just came out to find my father
I didn't do anything bad
Don't send me to the palace
Mom said that father is the richest embroidery master in the world
Those treasures are all from my father
I really didn't steal anything
Really
The richest clan in the world is Bixiao Palace
Is your father Princess Bixiao Palace?
Don't guess
What's your father's name?
Fu... Fu Canglin
Brother, do you know my father?
Princess Bixiao Palace is indeed blessed
But I've never heard that Bixiao Palace has a person named Fu Canglin
What's your name?
A... A'bao
You didn't go to the temple to get in?
Mom said that if you go to the temple
You will be caught by them
And be controlled by the human clan
You have to be a slave for your whole life
Mom said that it shouldn't be like this
I heard that Xie Shao has been in seclusion for many years
He rarely goes out of Yongxue City
It seems that he doesn't know the situation of the human clan
The human clan's oppression of the human clan is much worse than before
If the human clan goes to the temple to get in
They will become human clan's slaves
They can fight, scold, kill
They can also do business
They can't be free for life
But if they don't go to the temple to get in
They will have no status as good or evil
They can be killed regardless of their good or evil
This is the rule set by the human clan
The more domineering, the more shameless
Do you want to be sent home?
My baby is gone
I lost all my father's baby
I don't dare to go home
Okay, okay
Don't cry
I will help you get it back
Gao Qiangming is a good fighter
Don't make trouble
It's Gao Qiangming who took A'bao's baby first
It's a good thing that I helped him get it back
Since it's a misunderstanding
I will explain it clearly
Do you think they will believe it?
They will hand A'bao to the sword spirit department?
Young master Xie is a human
He will speak for people
But I am a human
I will stand up for the human
You are right
I don't want to convince you
Just leave me alone
Where is he?
Senior sister
I always think something is wrong
No one wears shoes in the same room
It's obviously a blind test
Fortunately, Senior sister Gao is smart
She can see your abnormality
Senior sister, you are so smart
I told you not to be so anxious
You should take off my shoes first
Then take off my clothes
Look
People misunderstand
You should remember next time
The flower of a man should be slowly coming
But
I like it
You are so talkative
I won't believe it
Today I will catch you and the
You
Who is it? It's so late
You are still sleeping
Sorry to bother you
You are so evil
Chase
One is a human and the other is a demon
If you collude with each other, you will be heartless
Today I will take your hand
We are not evil
Stop talking
No
Is there anyone who is asking questions?
Why do you call πά bom
time goes by so fast
She is so good
The artwork photo
What are you talking about
Just tell me
AH
ishna
You're so evil.
You're so disgusting.
How dare you come out and scare me?
Steward.
Go.
Get him a mask.
Don't scare him again.
Yes.
Hurry.
Give her clothes and her clothes back.
Let me go.
She's a daughter of a rich man.
You're not going to die for her.
It's the greatest honor in your life.
Brother.
You stopped me.
You've won.
Let them go.
What if I can't?
I won't let you kill anyone.
Go.
They wanted to kill you.
I protected you.
They have no power to fight back.
You don't have to kill him.
Why do you insist on fighting?
I'm a man like this.
Why would he want to kill me?
I can't kill him.
Is it worth protecting
if you're the only one who wants to protect him?
It's right to think you're right.
Let's run, Shijian.
But it's not good for us to see him die.
We can't save him here.
Since he's a different monster,
he must be a little bit confident.
Let's go back to the gate and report it.
Hurry.
You used blood as a sword.
You protected him like this?
I said
I wouldn't let you kill anyone.
You don't have any power now.
Even if you use your blood,
I have a hundred ways
to defeat you easily.
You're not going to die.
The Blood Sword is fake.
The Love Formation is real.
Your fake sword is with me.
In fact, the blood is the shadow,
so the Love Formation is set.
The blood from the Fàxiangxiu
is the soul of Zhichun.
I think you're just
overacting with me.
Wipe the blood out.
The blood from the Fàxiangxiu
is the soul of Zhichun.
and blood spilling out
Gradually forming this maze
I was weak on the way
You've been patient with me for so long
Just for this moment?
You can set up a killing formation
What's the point of setting up this trap?
You saved me
It's a return for not killing you
Then I have to thank you
for your kindness
Why didn't you use the devil's bow just now?
If you had the devil's bow
you would have died
You were badly injured
You didn't have the power to protect yourself
You couldn't stop my devil's bow
You hurt people with the devil's bow
I used the blood to protect them
I lost my life after all
Let's end this game here
I killed people with the devil's bow
You killed people with the sword
What's the difference between
the devil's bow and the sword?
If I really wanted to kill you
you would have died
You just can't bear to do it
Xie Xuechen
You really left?
I
I have something important
to tell you
Come back
Yaonan
Sister
rib
Tied, killed, attacked
A magic formation has four power, the stronger the power, the weaker the power
The four power of the ten thousand-monger Cuihua formation are all strong
It's easier to break
And this Linglong family is the first trapped formation in the world
It's harder to break if you're trapped
What if the people from the Swordless Realm come?
Sister, A'bao, A'bao is going to find someone to save you
I've observed that the Linglong family is built by the Tuluo tree
It's so hard to break
A'bao, A'bao
Is he really going to find someone?
Yes
Xie Xuechen
You protect him like this
Just because he's a human?
Is it the Human or the Spirit?
Can I decide?
What a couple, I don't like them
I don't like them
Young Master, we're here
But why are you here?
I'm here to save you
I know that I'll meet an old friend here today
But I don't know if he remembers me
I'm here to save you
A dream is like a dream, but it's no longer real
I have no wish in this life, I'm by your side
Translated by Hua Chenyu English Subs