The Taoism Grandmaster
Episode 5
Is this true?
We once loved Sang Qi.
He was forced to marry his father for the Winyang Soul Bead.
Qiu Min.
You heard it.
But you forgot it.
Go back.
The Taoism Grandmaster
They say that a little girl is too excited.
Anyway, you set a barrier outside.
No one can come in.
Why don't you come in?
Why don't you...
You've been away for a long time.
I couldn't wait for you.
I wanted to sleep first.
Since you're back,
what do you want to do?
Continue?
I have a lot of things to do.
I can't protect you all the time.
I'll send you back to Snowblade City first.
Snowblade City?
What?
Are you going to lock me up in the prison again?
No.
No one can lock you up in the prison.
No one can.
But Xie Xue Chen,
Sang Qi forced me to help him find the Soul Bead.
Go back to Snowblade City with me first.
I'll figure out a way to unlock the spiritual energy.
I'll go with you.
Go.
Chief Xie,
you'd better not force him to go to Snowblade City.
Otherwise,
the spiritual energy that Zun Shang left in his soul
will take his life at any moment.
I can still train my head.
Do you think
he will come?
Why did Master change his plan?
The sword power of Xie Xue Chen
is really not good enough for Xiao Qu.
I finally got the head shadow.
It took only one shot to fly away.
What a pity!
The head shadow.
The stupid head shadow
locked me in the prison.
This is the prison of Xie Xue Chen.
Why would I enter his prison?
You're really the master of Snowblade City.
You've been thinking about this mountain.
Forget it.
He's already here.
Let's see what his current greed is.
Stop.
Father.
I give you ten thousand people
to protect you
and the world with my sword.
You disappointed me.
I let you close the gate of Snowblade City
and erase your thoughts.
You disappointed me again.
Do you still remember
how you told me back then?
I'm grateful
for not being able to go down the mountain.
Since you know your mistake, why didn't you change it?
The previous people
didn't have the God's Cauldron.
We couldn't cultivate our spiritual power.
We could only look up to the gods in the sky
and beg for their help.
The God's Cauldron is the gift of the gods.
You were born with the right way of life.
You're loyal to the heaven and earth.
But you're distracted by your own personal feelings
and are disheartened.
I don't understand.
Father.
I really don't understand.
I can die for the people of the world.
I can protect the people of the world for a hundred years and a thousand years.
Why can't I die for the people of the world?
You can't save the demons.
He is your desire
and your heart.
Kill him.
It's just a fantasy.
Can't you bear to kill him?
Or
do you want to stay in this fantasy?
No.
I won't kill him.
Since I can't let him go,
I won't let him go.
He has never been my enemy.
It's not my desire for justice.
So
I'm your heart demon?
Yes.
It's always you.
You're here.
Does it mean
that I'm also your desire cage?
Then
I'm also your heart demon?
I remember
only two people protect each other
to enter the same desire cage.
Is it true?
Xie Xue Chen
is also my heart demon.
Mu Xuan Ling
It's not true.
Let's talk about it again.
I'm not going to kill you.
We're on two mountains.
This is a fantasy.
I'll take you out.
Go.
I felt a spiritual wave just now.
What happened?
The projection of the jade shadow just now came.
It mentioned that Sang Qi
planted spiritual energy in Mu Xuan Ling's soul.
After we got out of the desire cage,
she looked like this.
I tried to send the spiritual energy
but it didn't work.
The soul of the soul?
Sang Jie planted the spiritual energy
in the dark jade before.
It was in the position of the heart.
Now it seems
the position has changed.
You're the same as her.
Try to find it in her spiritual stage.
See if there's anything that doesn't coordinate.
I'll find it.
It's done.
She doesn't have the spiritual energy.
Spiritual energy is too important to her.
I dare not force her to leave.
I have to seal it temporarily.
If I hadn't let Sang Qi take her away,
she wouldn't have suffered this torture.
The ashes on her face
are also the signs of the soul.
Is there anything else on her?
No.
My head is dead.
I'm sorry.
I just don't understand
why you ordered me
to lock the Saintess in there.
Because they
will be in the same prison.
I want Xie Xue Chen
to know this.
So,
the Saintess also loves Xie Xue Chen.
But why did she...
Why did she turn out to be Scholar Xie?
Even if you remember anything,
you will still gotต bones.
You will be hurt again and
forget all your feelings again.
Xie Xue Chen, who he loves
and Scholar Xie's Meng Xuan Ling,
good student.
I...
Xie Xue Chen.
Get out of my way.
Mu Xue Ling.
Xie Xue Chen.
It's okay.
I'm not ready yet.
How can I be?
The seal has been sealed.
It's okay.
My life is a flop.
You owe someone the seal.
Since I have a relationship with Xie Xue Chen,
I don't think it's a good idea
to step into the trap quickly.
Perhaps Lord Nan loves you that way?
It's so strange.
Every time I feel that lying to you
is harder than lying to Xie Xue Chen.
You can even suffer from the pain of chasing your heart
for lying to him.
As long as I can lie to Xie Xue Chen,
the pain of chasing my heart is nothing.
But I didn't expect that the jade shadow would come.
Maybe Master is afraid that I didn't play it well enough.
If I can suffer from this pain,
Xie Xue Chen will not leave me alone.
If not,
he will definitely send me back to Yongxue City.
This is not within my plan.
You look a bit strange
now.
I am the real me now.
The one before was just a disguise.
And now you only want this paper.
Help me wash up and sleep.
You lied to me
and you didn't tell him.
I was very moved.
In my eyes,
Xie Xue Chen was just a central key to eureka pearl.
And you are different from others.
I thought you were a threat when we first met.
But now,
my thoughts have changed.
Maybe,
we can be friends who are closer.
Right?
You removed the barrier
because you trust her completely.
I know.
She is different from before.
She is suspicious.
But I want to believe her.
What if she makes trouble again?
If she can make trouble in front of me,
I will be so grateful.
You are the same as your sword.
You are so unyielding.
It seems that you can't afford to bear any result.
I should go.
But Mu Xuan Ling is...
Don't worry about her.
I will take care of her.
I see.
I should go.
Master is so strange.
He must have more secrets.
I'm afraid it's related to the Soul Bead.
I should tell Xie Xue Chen as soon as possible.
Go.
Hold on.
No.
If Ji Hua Palace's disciples see us,
they will report to Master.
What's so funny?
Didn't you go back to the dark domain with Sang Qi?
My friends and lovers are all in the mortal world.
I will come back.
How could Sang Qi let you come back so easily?
I don't believe it.
Of course I'm so eager to Xie Xue Chen
that I ran back.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't expect you to be my friend.
You don't trust me at all.
Friend?
At most, we are
friends who can say hello to each other.
I'm so happy to give you some of my love.
I overreacted.
If you want to be my friend,
I won't stop you.
But I'm telling you.
Don't play tricks on me.
Or I'll punch you
into pieces.
Then Xie Xue Chen is leaving. Hurry up.
No.
Wait.
I can't go there.
If Ji Hua Palace finds me,
Master won't forgive me.
Please.
Ji Hua Palace's people
are all out there.
Otherwise, why am I here?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Xie Xue Chen.
Gao Xiu came here by chance.
I'm afraid you can't go back.
I'm sure she found out something.
Come with me.
This should be related to
Master Miao Hua.
That is to say,
the previous princess of Ji Hua Palace,
Master Miao Hua,
had an agreement with Master Gao.
Master Miao Hua forced your mother
to marry Master Gao
and use her body
to keep the Soul Bead.
But they didn't say
that Master Miao Hua
replaced the real Soul Bead.
Yes.
If the Soul Bead
is not in the hands of Ji Hua Palace,
how could Su Ning Zhen
send the Soul Bead to the young princess?
Could it be
that Master Xie scared her?
But
they did mention the real Soul Bead.
But they didn't mention it.
I came out of the palace
and went to find Master Miao Hua overnight.
I heard that Master Miao Hua
wandered around the world after taking the princess's place.
No one has seen her again.
So she is still in Ji Hua Palace.
When I was a child,
I secretly followed Master
to the forest near Ji Hua Palace.
There was a cave there.
Master found me
and was very worried.
He took me away immediately.
Later, Master told me
that Miao Hua lived there.
Back then, he was very vicious.
After he passed the princess's place to my master,
he hid there.
Hiding these news
didn't want anyone to bother him.
But
I went to the mountain to find out
that Master lied to me
after I went to the cave.
You...
Master.
I am Qiu Min.
Gao Qiu Min.
Back then, you and Master
brought me back from the Mingyue Villa.
It was that child.
You...
What's going on?
Of course, it was made by my good disciple.
When my sister died,
my grandfather had a nightmare.
He couldn't sleep.
He came to see me
to soothe his mind.
You know what?
Why did you come?
I want to ask where the Soul Bead is.
At the moment of the Snowblade City,
no one found out that it was fake.
No wonder he didn't want to tell me.
He wanted to tell me
that he was going to kill me.
He wanted to pass the message to you.
You hid the Soul Bead?
Where is the Soul Bead now?
No one hid the Soul Bead.
No one could find it.
What does it mean?
I don't know.
I've never seen Master
hide anything.
Maybe the Soul Bead is not in the Palace of Pure Flower.
During the discussion between you and the elder,
I mentioned the clues of the Mingyue Villa.
Since they didn't want others to know the truth,
in the past,
they might have hidden the key to finding the Soul Bead.
I was still young at that time.
I couldn't remember everything.
And my father never allowed me to go to my mother's room.
Then we can only go to the Mingyue Villa to investigate.
We have to hurry up.
I sneaked out of the Palace of Pure Flower.
If Master finds it,
he will send someone to find me.
You don't need to...
I will go to the Mingyue Villa with you.
Maybe it's dangerous.
I don't know if there will be any changes in the Soul Bead in your body.
The Soul Bead has been sealed.
Besides, I've learned the Yuchue Skill.
If there's any danger,
I should fight with you.
Besides, Nan Xun Yue is not here now.
If anything happens to the Soul Bead,
who can control me except you?
I'm sorry.
You don't want me to cause more trouble, right?
Let's go.
What's going on?
When did Mu Xuan Ling learn the Yuchue Skill?
Isn't that Xie Xue Chen's skill?
And what's the danger of the Soul Bead?
Wait for me.
Can't you explain it to me?
Brother, can you hurry up?
Hurry up.
A'bao, I've been eating for days.
Can I have a rest?
But I haven't seen my father for a long time.
I've forgotten his face after I eat.
Didn't you say you haven't seen your father?
Okay, okay, okay.
A'bao, don't cry.
I'll help you find him, okay?
Next one.
I'm hungry.
Brother, can you help me find my father?
A'bao, look.
I've been looking for him every night.
Bi Xiao Kong didn't hide you.
Where's my father?
I want to find my father.
A'bao, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I want to find my father.
A'bao, listen to me.
Can you help me find my father?
A'bao.
I want to find my father.
Or there's another way.
Father, I'm begging you.
Just give me the snow sword.
I'll return it to you after I find A'bao.
You don't care about the business in the family.
You don't practice hard.
You're the young master of Yi Gong.
You surround this girl every day.
How ungrateful.
A'bao is a little girl.
She came all the way to find her father.
I promised her.
I must do it.
What's wrong with finding your father?
She even came to my Bi Xiao Kong.
Really.
Her father is Fu Cang Li.
He's the richest man in the world.
I think he might have something to do with our Bi Xiao Kong.
What's his father's name?
Fu Cang Li.
Father, do you know him?
No.
I've never heard of him.
You've been reading the ancestral books and the list recently.
You're looking for his father again?
That girl is from the Lin family.
Her father is Ren Xiu.
Apparently, she married a Lin family's wife.
Do you know where their family lives?
How would I know?
I didn't ask that much.
A'bao said his father had been gone for years.
He hasn't been home.
So, father, we have to help him.
We can't find Bi Xiao Kong.
Then you give me the snow sword. I'll go out and find him.
No.
Why not?
It's just a snow sword.
I'll borrow it.
Yes.
Madam.
Take it out.
Snow sword.
Thank you, mother.
You know how to love someone.
This way.
How is it?
Is it comfortable?
I'll teach you again.
Snow sword.
Thank you.
A'bao.
Madam.
Why did you borrow it from him?
You used the snow sword too.
Except for what Lan Shen saw,
he couldn't see anything else.
The snow sword
needs to be made of pure blood.
So, this fate,
if you can't find it, you can't find it.
What should come back
is destined to be unstoppable.
Let them go.
Maybe
there will be a result.
My dear.
Really help me find my father?
This mirror is called a snow sword.
My father got it from a evil monk.
The evil monk studied the books of blood.
He used his blood as a shadow.
After someone else drank it,
he could use the snow sword
to get the feeling of being connected with his blood.
He can see what he sees.
I was curious before.
I dropped my blood.
Then I found it.
Then I saw what my mother saw.
Then I dropped my blood.
Can I see my father?
No.
You can only see what he is looking at.
Come on.
Who are the three of them?
I can't see clearly.
Why do I feel like I'm losing?
So I think...
Your father doesn't want to follow them, right?
Does he want to get the Tao?
My father has many treasures.
How can he get the Tao?
This kind of forest grass is not common.
I heard that it's only near the Mingyue Villa.
I don't know why.
Mingyue Villa?
Take the blood sword.
Let's go and see your father.
We're selling vegetables.
Bun.
It wasn't this quiet before.
Hot buns.
Sir.
I want to ask
why the town is so quiet?
Do you know that there was a Mingyue Villa here?
It's said that in the past,
there were a group of demons
who cleaned up the entire village.
The repairmen there were all dead.
The town was also affected.
Everyone said that this was an ominous place.
Too many people died.
No one will come to protect us anymore.
If we can leave, we'll leave.
Sir.
Why are you still staying here?
I was born here.
Where can I go if I want to leave?
Give me some.
No need.
Okay.
Take care.
After my master was taken away,
I never came back here.
I didn't expect...
You didn't kill him.
You should take revenge, not be sad.
He's comforting me.
It's a waste of time to be sad.
Let's go.
Let's go to the Mingyue Villa first.
Three of you.
Sister.
Long time no see.
The repairman.
Fu Lanshou.
Sister.
I miss you so much.
You're finally back.
Sister.
I miss you too.
It would be better if you could show us where the chaos is.
Why does the repairman know we're here?
He's not saying anything.
Brother, I found something.
Come here.
We found that A'bao's father was following you with the blood sword.
So we came with you.
Why did A'bao's father follow us?
We don't know.
We couldn't see anything with the blood sword.
I guess he used some method to block the investigation of the magic weapon.
Your father is quite mysterious.
So what's your plan next?
We can't use the blood sword.
We can only follow you and find A'bao's father.
You haven't found him yet?
No.
I've asked them to send more people
to search along the path to the Mingyue Villa.
If I knew it,
I should have locked him in the room.
Can you lock him to death?
Once he's dead, he won't be at peace.
I went to the back hill.
The villagers have seen Miao Hua.
He's been more disobedient lately.
Let him see her.
The most important thing for a woman is to be in the palace.
She won't tell him anything.
The most important thing now is not to find the villagers.
Forget it.
We can't stay there.
Send someone to take the magic weapon to the Mingyue Villa.
Destroy the whole house where my sister lived.
Okay.
Why do you have to be curious about the past?
There are things
that shouldn't be rebuilt.
Go.
Go!
Gao Shun Shi.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
I just thought about some things from the past.
Let's go to my mother's room.
There might be a clue there.
I didn't expect it to be like this.
You've also experienced the past.
Aren't you afraid of seeing these?
I can't remember
the past.
You can't remember?
You used to be very worried about it.
Isn't it good
that you can't remember?
This is my mother's room.
This is my first time
coming to my mother's room.
A'bao,
this is the reception area.
Please wait a moment.
I'll go and check.
Okay.
A'bao,
it's a big room.
Please wait for me outside.
Okay.
Let's split up.
It's strange.
It doesn't look like
someone has lived here.
Could it be that someone
has kept your mother's things?
Impossible.
When I was little,
my father always stayed here all afternoon.
He never let anyone
come close to my mother's room.
This magic array was built by everyone.
We, Bixiao Palace,
also have similar mirror system
to protect
precious magic weapons and spiritual medicine.
Unless we know how to
break this mirror system,
otherwise,
it's impossible to open the gate.
I...
I don't know.
Move aside.
I...
The secret is right in front of us.
Let's go and check it.
My mother hid a secret path
so deep under the room.
Let's go.
The secret is right in front of us.
I'm willing to stay by your side.
The flowers are blooming,