YoYo English Channel YouTube
Xie Yuchen, Xie Yuchen
Why are you staring at me like this
Yueling
I won't let you be in any danger
I don't want to lose you anymore
Xie Yuchen, what's wrong with you
What happened
I'm the chief of the Xiu Xing Ge
He is going to destroy Wen Xian Town in secret
What
How do you know
It's too late to explain
I have to send it over immediately
Should I call you Chief He or Chief Xiu Xing Ge
If I remember correctly
You only saw my face once
Did I make any mistakes
Or who told you
You are a quiet and calm person
It's not a crime of youth
There are many Taoists in the world
Except for Yi Rong Shu
Only you can change the form and change the skin
Who are you
I asked you but you didn't answer
But I want to ask from me
It doesn't matter
Whether you answer or not
I won't kill you today
Just happen to have this intention
In a short time
Xie Sheng's main force has greatly improved
And the audience is looking forward to it
I really hope he can succeed
That will prove that he is the one I am waiting for
Give me a little more time
One day is enough
Why at this time
Can it be changed
It's still a failure
Did I succeed
It's a pity that the reality hasn't changed
The person you love didn't come back to life
I'm sorry
I didn't expect you to be so kind
It can be changed
It's just a little bit different
Just give me a little more time
Can stop the core
You promised to help me go back to the past
Change his fate
Why at a critical moment
Suddenly brought me back to reality
You misunderstood me
I didn't mean to bring you back to reality
But the time and space are unstable
Every time you stay, there is a limit
When the time comes, you will be forced to return to reality
How long can I stay
At most, only one day
Just one day
One day is already the limit
As long as I can save him
I can bear all the pain
The damage of the spirit body is irreversible
Every time the wheel is
I have thought about it
Only one night
Must use this night
Take Ling'er away from the dark cloud
As long as she is no longer the holy daughter of the dark cloud
You can live in peace
No need to get involved in the things that happened later
I am still asking for blood
Can't let anyone see me go down the mountain
Fortunately, I learned from Ling'er
The way to cover the shadow
Can cover the face
Good wine
Haven't eaten such a tender spirit body
Get out
You are stupid dark clan
Big brother saved me in front of the sky
I can't die here like this
Big sister
Don't be afraid little sister
Sister is not an enemy
Look at this little poor thing
But your performance is still very outstanding
You can survive in so many dark tribes' pursuit
You saw me being chased and killed
But you didn't help me
At least we are not friends
I made a bet with Chiying
I bet that the tribes that Honorable Superior brought back
Which one of them can survive till the end
I told him it was you
He didn't believe me
But now the other tribes are dead
You survived
You are the strongest one
I admire you
Then
What made you have such a strong desire to survive
The money that you have accumulated
Or the unneeded treasure
Or the most delicate fragrance
Or the supreme power
I don't like what you said
Then what else in this world
Is worth your longing
I don't have any longing
But I don't allow myself to die like this
Interesting. Why
It has nothing to do with you
Do you think
Our dark tribe is very bad
Very disgusting
You don't want to say a word to me
Isn't it
You are so unreasonable
You should be glad
Because of the dark tribe
You can survive in the dark
The most obvious dark tribe that Prince Yu showed
Is the best to be used
Actually, the human race is also like this
You shouldn't have a competition for desire
But to use it
This can control the dark tribe
And control the human heart
I don't want to be like you
Want to survive in the bad guys
You have to become a bad person first
Only to be the ultimate bad
You can fight against the bad
Remember?
Think about it
Why you came to the dark tribe
And why you live
The important thing is
To know what you want
To achieve your goal
You are right
Now like this
Is it like a bad guy
I believe we will meet again
Finally found
Why someone is at the door of his house
Make such a trap
I will go to the door
Fortunately, I brought this
You shameless dark tribe
You bullied me to come out
And harass me
Luckily, I fell asleep in advance
I just passed by
You are a fool
Why should I lie to you
When I passed by
I saw the flowers in the forest
I was curious and got closer
I didn't expect to be fooled by you
You are a little mysterious
Well
Are there many dark tribes bullying you?
You know it well
You dark tribe don't have a good thing
Especially the one called Chiying
Always looking for trouble
And make trouble with me
When I become the most powerful mushroom
I will defeat all dark tribes
I must make him kneel down
And laugh at me
Can't let him go on like this
Otherwise, he will go to the trap of the base
Do you want to learn powerful martial arts?
I teach you
Just you
Even my trap is heavy
You want to teach me?
How is it?
Is it powerful?
Yes, brother
I recognize you
Let's go, brother
Let's go back
Be gentle
I only saw him in front of the dark tribe
Look like a man
But I didn't expect he just came to the dark tribe
So reckless
He said
He had a demon on his face when he was a kid
But I didn't see it
Come on, brother
Drink tea
What powerful martial arts do you have?
Teach me
I want to be more like the dark tribe
It's not a good thing to be like the dark tribe
Why not?
Yu Ying said
If the evil team
Becomes more powerful than the evil
The destruction of the human race
Is another step closer
Why do you hate the human race so much?
Don't be blinded by hatred
And don't self-revenge yourself
Do you know?
Although there are many bad people in this world
But there are also good people like big brother
If he is still here
He must want you to be like an ordinary person
Live happily
How do you know about big brother?
Don't use those
Outwardly written martial arts
To steal my heart
I just don't want you to force yourself
To become another person
I didn't force myself
I just want to be as powerful as the dark tribe
No
I want to be stronger than all the dark tribes
All of them
But you
As a dark tribe
You are not like the dark tribe
If I say I'm not the dark tribe
Will you go with me?
I will take you to a place without conflict
Where there is no pain
Let you spend your life in peace
No
I want to avenge big brother
Stay in the dark
To become stronger
Is big brother so important to you?
Even if you are bullied by the dark tribe
You will live in the fear of pain
Even if you will lose your life
You have to stay in the dark
To me
Big brother is the most important person
For big brother
I can suffer any pain
I'm willing to do anything
Time is running out
Come with me
What are you doing?
You have to leave me
I said I'm not leaving
This is the signal bomb of the dark tribe
Once fired
The whole dark tribe will be alerted
Sang Qi will immediately come to the dark tribe to chase you
You can't leave then
I don't care who you are
What purpose you have
I can not expose you
But you have to leave my house now
Ying'er
I'll shoot if you don't come
It's getting dawn
We have to hurry back to the dark tribe before it's too late
Otherwise, everything will be in chaos
Go
Hurry up
This time I still didn't grab the time
But fortunately
I'm still alive
I still have a chance
I'm here
I've been in the secluded place of the Snow Tower for a long time
The snow has been falling
The night is still young
Who is in my place?
I always thought
When Mingyue was in the mountain villa
Father was completely disappointed in me
He didn't want to see me again
That day he asked me to go down the mountain
He also performed so well
But why
If the leader of the Alliance is still here
He must want to tell you this
Xue Chen
So many years
Father has always treated you very harshly
But in fact, father always knew
How hard it is for you
But even if he died
It's impossible to get out of the Dragon Snow City
Remember
Don't try to change other people's fate
And don't let people know your existence
Otherwise, your father will not be able to bear the cost
There will be countless people who will become the victims of fate
The worst possibility
Is that the whole world will be destroyed
And there will be no more suffering
If one day in the future
My life and this world
Put it in the right place
You don't have to worry
You must choose the latter firmly
Don't be blinded by hatred
And don't be self-pitying
Do you know
Although there are many bad people in this world
But there are also good people like big brother
If he is still here
He must hope that you are like an ordinary person
Live happily
If it's big brother
I will be happy
But what do I want to do?
Time is up
Ding'er
I'm back
I have nothing to fear
I have no regrets in this life
I will be by your side
Li'er
You finally wake up
It's so good to see you
Li'er
This time
We will never separate
Ok
Now the war of human and spirit has ended
Wan Xianzhen is repaired
The world is peaceful
You promised me to go to the mortal world
Don't play tricks
Take me to the mortal world now, ok?
Ok
Li'er
Don't be so rude
Rude
You are awake
You are weak now
Don't be so arrogant
I am not
How is she?
There is no change in this world
There is one thing
I am a little confused
Li'er said
She has a big face of a demon
But I saw it
She has no demon on her face
Why?
I can't give you the answer
But you need to find out for yourself
I will try again
Your spirit is seriously damaged
If you force yourself to travel through time and space
You may not have any regrets
Even if it's the last hope
I will try
She is still waiting for me
You are so lazy
Listen
Tonight is the birthday of the big lady
Be more careful
And
Don't go to the front yard to bump into your guests
You are all traitors
The water is not full
Who is responsible?
Lingling is responsible
It's cold these days
The river is frozen
We need to break the ice to make the water
I am not
Good
You are lazy again
What time is it?
You didn't even jump the water in the house
You can even jump the water
I think you are playing tricks on purpose
Sir
I have been jumping the water all night
I can't eat anything
I am so weak
You dare to joke with me
I am not joking
I am so weak
You dare to joke with me
I am strong
I was the one who picked you up from the tree
And fed you
You are so arrogant
You are so low-key
The water is frozen
I am not joking
I am so weak
Don't be afraid
Are you cold?
I am a slave
Sun Huan said
I won't be cold
Are you feeling better?
Shen Lang
How dare you hit me?
Do you know who I am?
Please spare me
I am wrong
Although he is not dead
He left with Lin in Sang Qi's blood
Before Mingyue Villa
So that he can get rid of Lin Lu's identity
And live well
Killing a person who has nothing to do with the police
Can only be a moment of relief
But it may lead to a bad ending
Please spare me
Go
Will you go with me?
Are you a guest in the villa?
I am Lin Lu
I want to listen to the director's orders
You are not Lin Lu
Haven't you eaten yet?
I have to pick up all the water tanks in the villa
To eat
I'll take you to eat
I am sorry
You don't have to say you are not sick anymore
I won't let you get hurt again
Sir, your dishes.
Thank you.
Sir, enjoy.
You don't eat that much.
Why are you only eating?
I'm not eating.
I'm just eating.
Why are you only drinking porridge?
I can eat enough porridge.
I used to drink porridge all the time.
So this is the taste of the dessert.
It's so delicious.
It's not convenient for you to eat with a mask.
Take it off.
No, no.
I have a mosquito on my face.
It's ugly.
I'm afraid I'll scare you.
No.
I saw your eyes.
I knew you must be beautiful.
This is the
Rosalina Route.
Please don't go.
How beautiful the scenery!
Come on.
This dessert is really delicious.
Why do you treat me so well?
Or do you want me to do something?
You don't need to do anything.
I just want you.
Are you my 13th father?
You hope so?
It's good.
Why?
You will take me away, right?
You have left me for so many years.
You will compensate me, right?
How can I compensate you?
I want to wear beautiful clothes, eat delicious food,
and live in a big house.
I can sleep for two hours every day.
Okay, I promise you.
I will take you to buy clothes later, okay?
Okay, father.
Don't call me father.
If you don't tell me your name,
what should I call you?
If you know my name,
we will have a future together.
You have done so much for me.
I don't want to see you sacrifice yourself for me.
I just hope you can live well.
Even if you don't love me anymore.
Anyway, don't call me father.
Then...
call me your big brother, okay?
Okay.
What did you say?
Big brother.
You have never been me for thousands of years.
He is my big brother.
He gave me my life.
Big brother.
You like to eat snacks so much.
Back then,
the first thing big brother took me to eat
was snacks.
I see.
He mentioned big brother every time.
It was me.
The clues have been revealed.
It's so obvious.
But I was so obsessed with it.
I just found it out now.
What's wrong with you?
Did I make you unhappy by calling you big brother?
No.
Then can I call you big brother?
Okay.
Big brother.
Li'er.
Thank you for taking me to the hospital to heal.
And bought me new clothes.
The clothes are beautiful.
I like it.
It's good that you like it.
Today is the Fourth Day of the Spring.
It is said that
this festival was set for the chaos pearl.
They said that 6,000 years ago,
it was the power of the chaos pearl that
established the Immortality Formation.
That's why the human world
is not attacked by the Dark Clan.
But actually,
the Human Clan never asked the will of the chaos pearl.
Never asked if it would be sacrificed.
Chaos pearl.
Isn't it a pearl?
Will it talk?
Big brother.
What's wrong with you?
Are you sad?
As long as you are happy,
I won't be sad.
If the Fourth Day of the Spring
can see fireworks together like this,
it will be great.
Calm down.
Let us go together.
Crowded.
Mmmm.
Fall in love with you all the time.
You can see the brilliant fireworks.
Really?
Thank you, big brother.
Li'er.
I'm sorry.
It's two different things to take you with you.
If you stay with Xie Xuesheng,
there will still be unknown risks.
I will take you with me.
But in the future,
you must be alone.
Forget me.
Live well.
Although I want to take you away now,
the soul-searching ring on your feet
limits your range of activity.
If we leave forcibly,
it will endanger your life.
Although there is only one day,
I am already very happy.
So, big brother,
you don't have to lie to me.
Even if you really can't take me away,
I won't blame you.
I didn't lie to you.
I really want to take you away.
So I'm going to find the High Master
and let him untie the soul-searching ring for you.
Really?
But the Master is a magic mirror.
He's amazing.
If it really doesn't work,
don't force yourself.
Don't worry.
I will take you away.
Master,
Young Master of Snow Tower wants to see you.
Xie Xuechen?
Why did he come here all of a sudden?
Ask him in.
Yes.
I envy you, Miss.
You have a big feast every year.
But you have to make us suffer.
For this day,
you have to be busy from morning to night.
I'm busy.
Enough.
Our clan is a low-ranking clan.
At least we can have a meal at the Mingyue Villa.
When Sang Qi was blood-sweeping at the Mingyue Villa,
it was in the high mountain town.
Is it today?
Sang Qi has been planning for this battle for many years.
It's impossible to stop him.
Feng Xiang's past is in front of her eyes.
The wheel is also told repeatedly
not to change the past.
As long as we can take Ling'er away before the incident,
we can't let her fall into Sang Qi's hands.
We have achieved our goal.
He has done so many dirty things.
He is very rich.
We need to be experienced in front of him.
We can't let him find out that Ling'er is the Soul-guarding Bead.
I'm sorry.