[English subtitles are available]
[Under The Skin]
[Episode 15]
Hu Zhifeng.
Who are you?
In May 2017,
someone pretended
to be the son of Zhang Jianguo.
He asked the old man
to transfer RMB500,000 to pay his debt.
One year later,
the old man died as he had no money
to treat his illness.
What does it have to do with me?
In January 2018,
someone pretended to be Mei Chaoying's
long-lost son
and conned her out of RMB300,000.
In October,
he cheated Zhou Guangnan
out of his pension.
The old man starved to death at home.
Last September,
someone used face-swapping technology
to impersonate Xu Siwen.
He tricked Xu Yiduo
out of his life savings.
Four days ago,
he committed suicide.
It was you.
Who the heck are you?
The one who will send you to hell.
Don't move!
[Police]
Stop taking pictures!
Move backward.
Stop filming.
Put your phone down.
Don't push me.
Put your phone away.
All right.
Everyone, please leave.
Stop filming.
Put your phone away.
Stop filming. Come.
Move backward.
-Move backward.
-You are rash.
-What if he stabbed you?
Stop taking pictures.
Please cooperate with us.
Shen Yi was right.
The resemblance between this couple is uncanny.
Yeah, they look like each other.
I know, right?
Why do they like
someone who looks like them?
It's annoying.
Isn't it?
Yes.
Do you know why couples look alike?
-Is it backed by any scientific evidence?
-I've heard of it.
Is it?
[S.engine]
Really?
Two people
who spend a lot of time together
will change each other's habits.
Over time,
their catchphrases
and expressions
will be more similar.
These habits
also affect their facial muscles
and figures.
Their appearance and temperament
will become particularly similar.
This
is why couples look alike.
Zhang Xiaoxue
looks like that man
[S.engine]
but not in terms of features.
It's...
Do you know what it is?
What is it?
I don't know.
The similarity lies in the movements of facial expression
and mien.
Got it? A round of applause,
please.
You are impressive, Jiang Feng.
[Couple look]
You have profound knowledge.
Here you go.
Peach Oolong flavor.
This is just the basics.
If you
build your knowledge,
you can do it too.
Let's have a tea latte.
It tastes good.
Thank you.
Hu Zhifeng has pleaded guilty.
He also confessed to the location of his accomplice.
Contact each sub-bureau now.
Catch him!
Yes, sir.
[Beijiang Interpol Team]
[Try pressing the green button on the remote control when the TV has no signal]
[The fruitcake girl in the alleyway across the street is called Huanhuan]
[My husband's name is Xu Yiduo]
[The old man holding a Pom and wearing heavy clothes is Professor Li. Greet him.]
[Siwen likes your red braised pork belly the most]
We caught the man
who impersonated you.
But they are gone.
If I didn't have a row with them...
If I
often phoned home,
maybe they wouldn't be conned.
Shen Yi.
I would like to keep a portrait of my father.
Is it too late?
It is not.
If you
met your teacher that day,
and he asked you to go back,
what would you choose?
I would tell him
that I wanted to stay
and continue as a portraitist.
It would still be your choice
if you got such an opportunity?
The police force
would do just fine without me.
But here,
my portraits can save countless people
and fight evil.
I can do
much more
than just draw.
No regret?
No regret.
[Floor Information]
Good morning, Captain Cheng.
Hello?
[Cheng.]
I'm not going.
[I have yet to say anything.]
Banquet, buffet,
dinner, and party.
What else could it be?
[You have guessed it, again.]
[Tomorrow, there will be a...]
I'm not free.
[Jiang Feng told me]
[that it's your time off tomorrow.]
I already told you
-that I'm not interested.
-Good morning, Captain Cheng.
[You will see all industry leaders in Beijiang.]
All right, I got here.
I've got to go.
Good morning, Fei.
Good morning.
I've been waiting for you.
What's the matter?
Let's talk in the room.
All right, please come in.
[Meeting Room]
What is it, Fei?
My friend's cousin's
daughter's best friend
is extremely beautiful.
But she is always single.
That's why
I've decided to introduce her
to the finest male police officer
in our sub-bureau.
I think you are the right man.
Thank you, Fei.
I don't think I'm the finest.
You must be the finest.
You look debonair and handsome.
You are the visual
of our sub-bureau.
That's settled then.
Tomorrow morning, ten o'clock.
Fei.
Well...
Unfortunately, I
have a class tomorrow morning.
What about the afternoon?
Don't turn down Fei's offer,
the visual of the sub-bureau.
Fei.
Captain Cheng is off tomorrow.
So...
Du!
Fei.
I am miles and miles from being the finest.
Look, I'm not fine.
You must be the finest.
Look at you.
You look debonair and handsome.
You are
the visual of our sub-bureau.
Fei, no.
Don't turn down Fei's offer.
That's settled then.
Her address, name, and phone number
are written clearly.
For the glory of our sub-bureau.
For the glory.
Don't be late.
[Interpol Team Timetable]
Good morning.
[Learning and Education]
I heard you're going on a blind date.
Fei told me.
Good luck.
Good morning, class.
Good morning.
Where is Zhao Xiaoxu?
Please come up with your painting tools.
I'd like to ask you
to wear headphones.
While listening to the melody in the headphones,
you begin to imagine
and paint a landscape.
This is Zhao Xiaoxu's
graduation project of landscape painting.
In the students' mutual evaluation
and assessment,
he came last.
11 students in the class
gave him a score
below the passing rate.
Next,
I would like to read
some noteworthy comments.
"This painting
makes me
uneasy."
"It is too invasive."
"Paintings live."
"I think
someone capable of drawing up this
must be mad."
This is William Hogarth's notable work,
"A Rake's Progress In The Madhouse."
Can anybody tell me
who is the madman
among them?
Who is the painter?
I think all of them.
I think the two women
in the back of the painting
are not mad.
Why?
They dress in theatrical clothes and look respectable.
And they hold a hand fan.
They look at the others
with curiosity and disapproval.
They are more like outsiders.
Correct.
These two noble ladies
were visiting the madhouse.
At that time,
madhouses charged their visitors
to sustain
their operations.
Were they mad? Who would visit a madhouse?
Mr Shen.
Who is she? I haven't seen her before.
Me too.
Please.
I'm sure
the man without clothes
in the middle of the painting
is not mad.
Why?
You said this painting is called
"A Rake's Progress In The Madhouse."
This man
is in the middle of the painting.
I think he is the rake,
not a madman.
You are right.
He is
the central figure of the painting.
"A Rake's Progress In The Madhouse."
During college,
he unexpectedly inherited a legacy.
But he blew it all on gambling.
On the day he went bankrupt,
he had a mental breakdown and attempted suicide.
Then he was sent to the madhouse.
It's inhumane.
He was locked up just because he attempted suicide.
Well said. I would like to ask.
Is everyone in a madhouse
mad?
Hogarth wanted
to tell future people
that sanity and insanity
are defined by society.
A conservative and domineering society
will portray a sane person as a madman.
Who is the madman?
The jurisdiction
is in the hands of us.
And each of us
is also judged
by our own kind at all times.
Tell me.
What did you see?
What did you hear?
It's the serenade by Schubert.
I saw someone punting.
The oar pushed the water lilies away.
Now,
does anybody define him that way?
Sorry.
I'm a police officer.
Because of
my work,
there are times where I can't go home
for weeks.
I don't think we are suitable for each other.
Du Cheng, right?
I'm Xiao Shan.
Sorry for being late.
You must've been waiting for long.
It's okay, I
just arrived.
There was a sprinkler truck on the road.
And I didn't manage to avoid it.
Waiter.
Please get me a dry towel.
Thank you.
Mr Shen, see you.
See you.
You look alike.
Who?
Du Cheng.
He has your eyes
and your temper.
You must be Du Qing.
Brilliant!
I read the news about you.
The Crime-hunting Detective of Beijiang Sub-Bureau.
But when you stood with the police
in the news,
you looked like
a cat among the wolves.
On the podium today,
you looked like
a fighter among the painters.
How is it?
Am I right?
What color is it?
Royal blue.
What about now?
It seems to be darker.
The same pen
will show different colors
in different environments.
But the pen has not changed.
Same goes to me.
I am a portraitist.
Whatever environment I'm in,
I remain a portraitist.
Now I see
why my brother appreciates you
and insists on working with you.
Is this your first blind date?
I'm a police officer.
I know.
The police are cool.
Cool?
No way.
It's all go.
We have to work overtime
and travel all day.
Being a model is the same.
We fly everywhere.
We are similar in some ways.
Did you drive?
Well...
Run me up to my company later.
My clothes are soaked.
This is inconvenient. I've got to get changed.
It's inconvenient for you, isn't it?
Then I'll sit here and wait.
I'll stay until the clothes are dry.
It's pretty cold.
Where is your company?
It's pretty close.
Cheng was like them when he was young.
He colored his hair.
He fought.
He did everything
a teenage rebel did.
Back then,
my parents were busy
and had no time for us.
They thought Cheng was a lost cause.
He once
smashed the headmaster's car at school.
The headmaster
wanted to talk to my parents.
Did you know what he told me?
He said,
"That's great.
I can finally
talk to Dad alone."
Only then did I realize that
he did these things
to talk a bit more
to our father.
Did he get his way?
My father
still sent his assistant.
Why are you telling me this?
Can you tell Cheng
not to be a police officer anymore?
Why?
He wanted to enter the police academy since childhood.
My parents disapproved.
He was rebellious.
My parents' disapproval
only gave further sustenance to him.
He doesn't really want
to be a police officer.
He just wants
our attention.
I think Du Cheng chooses to be a police officer
just for himself
and nobody else.
Du Cheng
is a man of great faith.
He believes
in his intuition and judgment.
He is uncompromising once he sets his mind.
No one
can manipulate his choice.
It's his nature
that made him a policeman.
I've lived with him
for thirty years,
but I don't know him any better.
Perhaps
the depth of understanding
is not determined
by the length of time.
Do you want to drop in?
If you have anything to say,
say it.
The temperature of the coffee shop
was 25 degrees Celsius.
It was not that cold.
You brought me here on purpose.
I guess you're not directing at me
but
at my position as a police officer.
I hate to trouble you.
However, no one
but you
can help me now.
What is this?
There is a Xinshan Art Garden that just opened.
Did you know that?
An exhibition
was held there recently.
It was an exhibition of art
by the top photographer, Mandy.
I fought for the opportunity
of a photoshoot with him.
And it came to this?
On the day of the exhibition opening,
we walked into the pavilion
just to find that my head
was cut off in all the photos.
When did it happen?
Evening three days ago.
The exhibition has been called off now.
Did you call the police?
I did.
I did so that evening.
But Xinshan is a new region.
There is no security camera inside.
We can't find this person.
This pavilion
is locked at night.
So the person
should have entered
before midnight.
Cutting off your head in the photos
means beheading.
This person has a spite
at you.
No real damage
is caused yet.
But if you can't find the person,
it is likely to turn into
actual bodily harm.
Do you have a feud with anyone recently?
Shu Qianqian.
Ever since she found out
about me working with Mandy,
she has been targeting me for everything.
I don't know why.
Xiao Shan.
We're going to work.
Why are you here?
I've heard about
the photographic exhibition.
Don't worry so much.
Two of us are the only models
in Mandy's photographic exhibition.
My photos have been removed now.
Only yours are left.
Are you saying
your photos
were tampered with by me?
Calm down.
Who are you?
I...
He is my friend.
We just want
to know the score.
What were you doing
the evening before the incident?
I had a show from seven to ten
that evening.
FLY Studio's Spring Fashion Show.
After ten,
I went to the celebratory dinner.
I didn't go home until the early morning.
Can anyone testify
what you said?
Excuse me.
Who are you?
Police?
I think
it's not good for anyone
if the case is reported.
Everyone on the show
can testify for me.
And
after the event,
Mr Zhang asked his driver
to drive me home personally.
Qianqian.
Do you want...
Mr Lei.
I'm so sorry.
I forgot about
our shooting.
Could you wait a moment?
I'll wait outside.
All right, I'll be there in a minute.
You've wasted my time.
Xiao Shan, you saw it too.
Mr Lei
will be
my personal photographer from now on.
You were lucky.
He made you a star.
But who would have thought
you were soon abandoned?
I was the one terminating
my contract with him.
It must be Shu Qianqian.
Who else would be so twisted
to do this to me?
Are there
other unusual things around you?
Or someone who makes you feel threatened?
Follow me.
Don't look back.
Who is following us?
Presumably, it is the one who cut your photos.
Be yourself.
So that I can catch him.
Why are you following us?
Who are you?
You...
[Police]
Why are you following Xiao Shan?
What's the matter? I didn't break the law!
Invasion of privacy is a crime.
I like her so much.
She is my ideal type.
But she has an offensive air of superiority.
Every time I went to the airport to meet her,
she just brushed me off.
I spend so much money on her.
Why doesn't she belong to me?
I feel bitter!
All right.
Last week,
she was involved in a photographic exhibition.
Did you know?
Yes.
Did you know the exhibition has been called off?
Did you know why?
Yes.
No.
Because her head
was cut off in the photos.
You did it, right?
It was not me!
It was
absolutely not me.
What's wrong
with liking someone?
What is my offense?
Xiao Shan, I love you!
Xiao Shan!
Officer Du, you are awesome.
So he is the pervert.
Not him.
He is just your fanatical fan.
Fan?
The day before the exhibition,
he followed you to a party.
He couldn't make it to the exhibition hall.
When did you
start drawing?
Since I was small.
I scribbled.
Then I met my teacher,
I...
Officer Du.
What are we going to do now?
No fingerprints and evidence.
And no injuries.
I can't enter the evidence management system.
What's wrong?
This person went so far.
You must be hated.
I don't know.
You also think
it's an expression of hatred?
This person even cut off her head.
Is it not hatred?
The edge is smooth.
Do you think it was cut
with hatred?
Do you
notice something again?
I'd like four salads,
with one of them being meat salad.
Okay.
Thank you.
Can I get you anything else?
No.
Do you want anything else?
Please wait a moment.
No, thanks.
Why were you with my sister?
She sat in on my class.
I have to
give a warning to you.
She always wants
to plant a spy on me.
Don't listen to her.
This paragraph is interesting.
I'll check them out.
"Artists cut photos
not just for collection.
They also make collages
to add new value
or emotional expression."
[Hockney's Pictures]
There you go.
It's too much.
Just eat.
Tell me if you want anything else.
Isn't it interesting?
What?
What's interesting?
Thank you.
[Jingxiang House]
Shen Yi.
Why don't you come with me...
I'm off today.
Don't make him work.
I'm taking him out.
Where to?
Party.
Since you're not going with me,
he should go with me.
I...
Let's go.
Officer Du.
What do you think about this matter?
Are there
artists around you?
Take it easy. Don't worry.
Many of them are my friends.
Come.
Mr Chen and Mr Wang!
Hi.
Long time no see.
Yeah.
I hope your business is going well.
You are getting more and more beautiful.
You are so sweet.
Lady, would you like a drink?
Okay, thanks.
Thank you.
Take it easy.
Didn't you say
you're a portraitist anywhere you are?
Just be yourself.
I'll socialize with them.
You get familiar with the environment.
I'll be right back.
All right, I'll leave you to it.
Miss Du.
Mr Wang.
Hi.
Come.
Long time no see.
-How's business?
-Hi.
Not bad.
-It's been a while since you came to my company.
-Long time no see.
Do pay me a visit next time.
All right, sure.
[Actually, those photos...]
It's not good
for such a handsome guy
to be on the phone by yourself.
Let me
introduce my friends.
See, the man
in a black suit over there.
He is the water industry chief
of Xincheng.
Look at that one.
The one in a plaid suit.
He is the boss of a biotechnology company.
Recently he is having a deal
with the government about health databases.
These are the people
who control the entire
urban system of Beijiang.
Together with him.
The future
of the Internet in Beijiang
is in their hands.
Mr Chen.
Sorry.
All right.
Thank you.
Talk to you later.
Long time no see, Miss Du.
Long time no see.
Let me introduce you.
This is my handsome brother.
Shen Yi of Beijiang Sub-Bureau.
He is a genius portraitist.
Hi.
This is
the boss who has the power
over the future of the Internet
in Beijiang.
Mr Chen Zhou.
I'm not that good, Miss Du.
-Hi, Mr Chen.
-Nice to meet you.
Hi, Mr Chen.
I will leave you two to it.
I'm going to talk to some old friends.
Shen Yi.
Officer Shen.
I've heard of you.
But when I see you today,
you're younger than I thought.
You flatter me.
By the way,
there was a case,
and your company
helped a great deal.
It's no bother.
Recently, Cyber City
is developing
a new security system.
I hope that
we can help with
your composite drawing
in the future.
Thank you.
I think it's a good thing.
Who is it?
Mr Lei.
What's the matter?
I'd like to ask you some questions.
Have you been to
the Xinshan Exhibition Hall four days ago?
Lei Hao, speak up!
Yes.
Why did you do that?
Because he admires you.
Admires me?
What would you have done
when you see your page
in a magazine?
I'll tear it out
and keep it.
You must be careful when you do that, right?
I'll lay a pad
and cut it down
inch by inch with a paper knife.
The same goes for
the photo cutouts.
The person who damaged the photos
didn't mean any harm.
He really liked them,
so he wanted to keep them.
He cut the photos
and pieced them together.
He made it into
what he really wanted.
Mr Lei.
If you admire me,
why did you cancel the contract with me?
When I first saw you,
you had me
riveted
with your cynicism.
You have been my source of inspiration.
But I didn't expect you
to enter into the showbiz industry
to gain more popularity.
You began to please
and entertain the public.
You no longer
dress up and make-up
in your old ways.
Your beauty
died away.
I brought
these photos back
because I want to tell you
that there's one man
who devoutly likes
the old you.
I will treasure
my muse forever.
Hello?
How are things at your end?
Is it not over yet?
[Almost.]
The photos were not cut out
for venting or threatening.
It's an appreciation.
[And...]
[Cheng!]
[You are drunk.]
Come over here!
Hurry.
Stop talking to him.
Let's have a drink.
Officer Du.
Thanks for your help today.
Let me treat you to dinner.
No need.
I'm glad it's resolved.
I've got things to do.
Goodbye.
Hi.
Come.
Thanks.
Would you two raise a toast?
Don't just look after your own interests.
Please look after my company.
All right?
All right.
Are you drunk?
Don't drink if it isn't for you.
You took longer than I thought.
You had noticed it, right?
He didn't cut out the photos
because of hatred.
You always
believe the worst.
That's why it took you so long.
I can't help it.
I'm used to being a policeman.
It is an old bad habit,
isn't it?
What do you mean?
I mean,
you did everything to gain attention
in the worst way.
For example...
For...
For example,
you smashed the headmaster's car.
How did you...
Cheers!
I wish you a prosperous business.
Come.
My sister told you that?
Don't believe her cock-and-bull story.
Don't believe her
just because
she treats you well.
She wants to know
everything about me.
So she tries hard
to sweet-talk my friends.
Jiang Feng and others fall for this.
Are we friends?
Your sister is tough.
She deals with every situation
as if she's at home.
She is good at everything,
except that she is too caring to me.
As a child, I was fearless.
I feared no one but her.
Not just me.
I remember there was a time
we children threw down the gauntlet.
Many people came.
When they heard that my sister was Du Qing,
they cursed and pulled back.
They said I was lucky.
Isn't it exasperating?
You are showing off.
But you are really fortunate.
Not everyone
has someone
he is committed to.
Indeed.
Besides my sister,
I still have Jiang Feng, Li Han,
He Rongyue, Yan,
Bureau Chief Zhang...
And you.
We are all friends
and mates.