(heartbeat)
(footsteps)
(ominous music swell)
(scary wooshes)
(heartbeat continues)
(solemn orchestral music)
(diamonds clattering)
(solemn orchestral
music continues)
(cicadas chirping)
(gentle orchestral music)
(wolf howling)
(wings fluttering)
(gentle orchestral music)
(sudden ominous music)
(guard grunting)
(dagger thudding)
(soft tense music)
(helmet clunking)
(tense orchestral music)
(tense orchestral
music continues)
(door clanking)
(door creaking)
(soft tense orchestral music)
Huntsman Kaiser?
(door thudding)
What are you doing?
(lock clanking)
(soft tense music)
(soft tense music continues)
(handmaiden breathing heavily)
(gentle tense music)
(gentle tense music continues)
(sudden ominous music)
(witch reciting spell in Latin)
(dramatic orchestral
music) (handmaiden gagging)
(handmaiden screaming)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(witch reciting spell in Latin)
(soft intense music)
(spear thudding)
(dramatic orchestral music)
Nuts.
(guard grunting)
(magic whooshing)
(magic crackling)
(soft orchestral music)
(soft tense orchestral music)
(soft tense orchestral
music continues)
(sudden ominous music)
(dagger thudding)
(tense orchestral music)
-Hurry!
She's losing her breath.
You must save her.
Quickly, the vials.
(tense orchestral music)
It is worse than I feared, but
she's been poisoned, my King.
It is not enough to kill her,
but more than enough
to take the child.
Find the old woman
responsible for this.
(dramatic orchestral music)
(gentle tense music)
(magic cracking)
(door thudding)
(rat squeaking)
[Guard] Where is she?
(sudden ominous music)
(guards roaring)
(sword thudding)
(guard roaring)
(flesh thudding)
(sword clanking) (guard
gasping fearfully)
(witch reciting spell in Latin)
(magic whooshing)
(guard choking)
(soft intense music)
(sword thudding)
(guard thudding)
(armor clanking)
(soft tense orchestral music)
Please, save my child.
I cannot lose you, my love.
Our love will never
be lost, my King.
It will live on
through our child.
(Queen screaming)
(soft tense orchestral music)
(gentle piano music)
It's beautiful.
What is?
The snow.
(light orchestral music)
It's like a million dancing
stars falling to the earth,
bringing light and
purity to the world.
It's the most beautiful
thing I have witnessed.
And I am blessed that it will
be the last sight I will see.
(King sobbing) (light
orchestral music)
Huntsman Gunnar.
Promise me you will always keep
my child safe and protected
as if it were your own.
(soft orchestral music)
Please go now.
Please go, my love,
so that this sight is not
your last memory of me.
(soft orchestral music)
(melodic orchestral music)
(nurse sobbing)
(melancholic orchestral music)
(melancholic orchestral
music continues)
(Queen sobbing)
(soft tense orchestral music)
(soft tense orchestral
music continues)
(weapons clanking)
You again.
(soft tense music)
(guard roaring)
(magic whooshing)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(singers vocalizing gruffly)
(sword thudding)
(witch grunting)
(witch reciting spell in Latin)
(guard groaning)
(dramatic orchestral
music) (singers vocalizing)
(blows thudding)
(witch grunting)
(sword whooshing)
(sword thudding)
(guard grunting)
(guard coughing)
(soft tense orchestral music)
(soft tense music)
(baby crying briefly)
(gentle melancholic music)
(gentle melancholic
music continues)
(blood dripping)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
[Villagers] Kill him,
kill him, kill him!
Kill him, kill him, kill him!
Kill him, kill him Kill him!
(tense orchestral music)
[Villagers] Kill him,
kill him, kill him!
Kill him, kill him, kill him!
(Kenneth grunting)
Kill him, kill him,
kill him, kill him!
Attention!
I, Gerald Schultz of Meltonbury
hereby sentence
Kenneth Slatag to death
for the crimes of theft,
(villager laughing)
Witchcraft,
vagrancy,
treason,
public intoxication,
(soft melodic music)
Arson,
heresy,
murder,
pirating.
(villagers laughing)
Urinating in a jar.
Forgive me for that one, Lord.
And a litany of other crimes-
(ax thudding) (guillotine
blade thudding)
(blood spattering)
(crowd gasping)
(soft melodic music)
(background people chattering)
(villagers gasping)
Hey!
Oi!
(villagers cheering)
Thank you to Snow White, our
Princess of the Peasants.
It's nice to see some royalty
come down from the castle
to fill our hearts and not
just their own pockets.
(villagers laughing)
(cheerful accordion music)
That was amazing. Did you
see his head fall off?
Yes, yes, it was great.
The guillotine was nothing
but a parlor trick.
Oh, I know, let's
go to the aviary.
Again? We were just
there this morning.
[Yvonne] Yeah, what's
got you so flustered?
No, no, no, nothing
is wrong, I just,
I just love the birds, you know.
The birds?
Yes, the birds.
Come on, let's go.
Snow, no. (cheerful
accordion music)
Don't look now.
Oh, I know.
Oh, I see.
I think I'd rather
skip the aviary
and stay here and
watch the lovebirds.
(all laughing)
-You behave this time.
Always.
(cheerful accordion music)
Looks like we missed it.
Missed what?
Only the best part of the faire.
How will I find inspiration
for my writing
without the execution?
The beheading, the decapitation.
The old neck hole and head roll.
The blade drop and head pop.
The hatchet and head basket.
Come on, you're a Prince,
make them do it again.
That old trick, to
entertain nursery children
and simple-minded travelers?
Wait, we're not travelers.
Just talk to him already.
I couldn't, you saw me up there.
And what if I'm not his type?
Snow, you do this every time.
You are a beautiful
Princess, Snow.
You are quite literally
everyone's type.
Come on, you've known him
nearly your entire life.
Plus we've all seen the
way you look at him.
And he looks at you.
I don't look at him.
Oh, you definitely look at him.
We all do.
You've got this.
(laughing) That's disgusting.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
Is that awkward lady trying
to avoid your attention?
Oh, Jacob, that is
no ordinary lady,
that is the Princess, Snow
White, right, my Lord?
The Prince says-
[Florizel] I told you
not to call me that.
Princess? No, I
called her a Princess.
No, my Lord.
I'm not your Lord,
the Prince is my Lord.
No, I'm your friend,
not your Lord.
What do you think
they're talking about?
My guess is they're
debating the finer nuances
of how to properly
scratch their knackers
during a public event.
Oh.
I'm sure it's very regal,
very important things.
Ruling kingdoms,
political status,
heroic battle
stories and strategy.
If my Lord requests we
do not call him my Lord,
we do not call him my Lord.
Well, I'm certainly not
going to call him Florizel.
And why would you call him that?
That is his name,
right, my Lord?
Is that your name? Why
didn't I know this?
Well, I knew it.
My Lord!
Florizel.
[Florizel] I must talk to her.
That you must.
Must he though?
Ignore him.
You have been dreaming
of this girl for ages.
Ages?
All the appropriate
ages. Don't be weird.
I can't, not today, I'm not
even dressed for the occasion.
Come now, Snow,
you look radiant.
I wouldn't change a thing.
Well, if I knew I was going
to see a Prince today,
I would've worn something
a bit more revealing.
Revealing? That's not like you.
Well, yes, you know,
just something to catch
the Prince's attention.
Well, I think you've already
caught his attention.
(playful orchestral music)
Oh, hello there, I
don't believe we've met.
I'm Snow White. You are?
Oh, I'm sure we
have met in person
and 1,000 times in my dreams.
He's good.
Hm.
Have we?
Hm, I simply don't recall.
Oh, I recall you speaking
about me just moments ago.
You? Oh no, I was talking
about another Prince.
There's another Prince here?
Well, if there is, then I'd
better sweep you off your feet
before he lays eyes on you
and falls as hard as I have.
Well, I would watch
where you fall.
There have been a
lot of livestock
traveling through here today.
Well then, perhaps you and
your friends can join me
and ensure I remain upright?
Well, making sure a
Prince does not fall
into a pile of manure sounds
like a wonderful time.
We had plans to go
to the aviary, right?
No, we don't.
We would love to join you.
Great.
Shall we?
Yes.
(soft ominous music)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
(Evil Queen groaning)
(corset creaking)
My Queen.
You-you wanted the results
of the skin treatment
with the arsenic.
(gentle tense music)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
Well?
Though the skin
does appear lighter
a-and more youthful, I would
not recommend ingesting it.
And the belladonna in the eyes?
The pupils did
enlargen, my Queen.
(gentle tense music)
Have it ready for
me in my chambers.
Give her the mercury next.
(gentle tense music)
(corset creaking)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
Why do I hate them
so? (corset creaking)
Why is their laughter like
glass shards in my lungs?
Tighter.
My Queen, I fear it is causing
undue harm to thy body.
I said tighter.
(corset creaking)
(Evil Queen grunting)
Why does my blood burn with
hatred to see her smile,
or the smallest glint of
happiness in her eyes?
[Mirror Demons] Because
you are jealous.
I am not jealous.
I am the Queen.
[Mirror Demons] You want her
youth, her beauty, her joy.
I cannot be seen like this,
waist growing larger by the day,
flesh beginning to fold.
Once I have it all back,
I will marry into a larger,
more powerful kingdom,
and then burn this
useless one to the ground
with Snow White and her
nasty peasants in it.
[Mirror Demons] After you
have her heart, of course.
(laughing) Yes.
A beautiful beating heart.
Oh, Huntsman.
Gunnar?
I'd say we've known
each other long enough
for me to call you
that, don't you think?
Tell me, who is the fairest,
most beautiful woman of all?
(light melodic music)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
Always
and only you, my Queen.
(soft cello music)
(hand slapping)
Good, I'm glad I can
still catch your eye,
while you still have
them, of course.
(hand thudding)
(birds chirping)
(soft melodic music)
(background people chattering)
So what do you think?
[Snow White] Hm.
Are you the Princess?
Why, yes, I am.
And who is your little friend?
[Felix] This is Diamond.
Diamond is very pretty.
And your name, my good sir?
Felix.
I am so sorry, please
accept my sincere apologies
and forgive my son, he
does not understand.
No, no, it is an honor
to meet you, sir.
There was nothing
to be sorry for.
Father, may I have a shield?
[Felix's Father] I wish I could.
With your mother
falling ill, I-I...
(coins clinking)
-For the shield,
and may the rest
help with your wife.
This is too much.
No. Felix, may I help
you choose the shield?
How about
this one?
Here, I will even mark it
with a kiss for protection.
(soft melodic music)
Now what do we say to your
father for this lovely gift?
Thank you, Daddy.
Thank you. Thank you
1,000 times, Princess.
I will never forget
your kindness.
(soft melodic music)
That was very sweet of you.
How so?
I did see you give
that man your coin.
Give him?
Oh, I'm sure he
worked much harder
for those coins
than I ever have.
You really are Princess
of the People, aren't you?
I don't know about all that.
I was offered the gift of being
able to help and I took it.
The pleasure was mine.
And what are you
going to do with that?
I thought I might
buy it for myself,
should I find the need to
run it through your heart?
You've already pierced
my heart, Princess.
Then I shall keep
it at the ready,
should you be so
callous with mine.
Oh, I assure you,
I hold your heart
in the highest
treasure over any.
I would hope so,
as it appears you keep
trying to steal it.
Oh, certainly not,
a stolen heart will
not truly belong to me.
And I do pray that one
day, I am worthy enough
for you to give it yourself.
You think you're so charming.
You have been my longest quest.
Have I? I bet you say that
to all the other Princesses.
(soft orchestral music)
(sheath clicking)
(coins clinking)
(soft orchestral music)
(gentle tense music)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
(Evil Queen groaning)
(gentle tense music)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
She's probably down
there right now
covered in muck,
smelling of the stables,
just like the company she keeps.
Why is she like this?
I raised her to be a proper
Princess in my image.
Careful.
(gentle tense music)
(Evil Queen reciting
spell in Latin)
(soft orchestral music)
(liquid hissing)
Huntsman, I've lost
far too much blood.
Bring me a peasant girl.
Bring me one of Snow
White's little friends.
We shall see how quickly
that pretty smile fades.
(intense orchestral music)
(birds chirping)
You know, I was a
champion jouster myself.
Of course you would be.
But you know, you could
get yourself hurt.
Hurt, have you suddenly found
a care for me after all?
Well, it is just
that when I dreamt
of a Prince falling for me,
it didn't involve you
falling off your horse.
Oh, but it did include me?
That is not what I meant.
(both laughing)
That looks amazing.
Come on.
(soft orchestral music)
Well, they look like they're
having a wonderful time.
What about you?
Me? It's all right.
Just all right?
If you like that sort of thing.
Well, do you, like
this sort of thing?
I could get used to it.
Well, what do you like?
I like you.
Snow, they're playing
our favorite song!
Oh!
(cheerful melodic music)
(cheerful melodic
music continues)
(hammer clanking)
(cheerful melodic music)
You're mine.
(villager laughing)
You did it, didn't you?
(cheerful melodic music)
(cheerful melodic
music continues)
I want to show you something.
All right.
Yeah. (laughing)
(villagers cheering)
(tense melodic music)
What are the huntsmen
doing out here?
(tense melodic music)
(gentle tense music)
Is he pointing at us?
I don't know why he would be,
unless, what did you boys do?
(soft tense music)
He's not looking at us.
He's definitely looking at you.
Well then, we should go.
We can't get in
trouble again. Come on.
(tense orchestral music)
(light tinkly music)
(soft orchestral music)
This place is amazing.
What is this place?
How did you find it?
My father used to bring
me here before he died.
We would talk to my mother.
Your mother, and
did she ever answer?
Oh no,
but I could feel her.
There are times I swear
I could almost see her.
Every time I come here,
I feel reborn, more alive.
When my time here
comes to an end,
I'd like my final
breath to be here.
(soft orchestral music)
Well, let's hope that
that time doesn't come.
(tense melodic music)
Do you see them?
What do you think they want?
I don't know, but it
doesn't look good.
Will you boys please
take Sofia home?
(soft tense orchestral music)
Meet me at the aviary.
Okay. Please be careful.
You too.
(tense orchestral music)
(tense orchestral
music continues)
(gentle tense music)
(gentle tense music continues)
(chains rattling)
(gentle tense music)
No, please, I'm a
friend of the Princess.
We're just having a bit of fun.
(gentle tense music)
Are you are going to hurt me?
Oh, God.
Please help!
Help! (tense orchestral music)
(chains rattling)
Please, someone help me!
(intense orchestral music)
(soft orchestral music)
Is everything all right?
Yes, everything is
perfect, actually.
(soft orchestral music)
Oh, you're gonna run
that through my heart?
No, giving you mine,
for you to remember me by
and to give you
strength on your quest.
You're not one to
forget, Princess.
I'll hold onto it but
not to remember you by,
but to have something to hold
in the moments you
are not in my arms,
and to use it on my own heart,
when the day comes that
you are no longer mine.
That got dark.
Well then, be my light.
(soft orchestral music)
(Inga screaming)
(soft ominous music)
That sounded like Inga.
Your friend?
Yes, we need to go help her.
Right. (dramatic
orchestral music)
(chains rattling)
-Help!
(dramatic orchestral music)
No!
No, no!
Unhand her!
(chains rattling)
(Inga sobbing)
It's locked.
-No!
Get back, stand back.
(dramatic orchestral music)
(mallet thudding)
(Florizel grunting)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(blow thudding)
Leave her alone!
(chain rattling)
-Please!
-Leave her alone!
Huntsman Kaiser?
(Huntsman Kaiser laughing)
I'm here by the
order of the Queen.
(sobbing) Please, no.
You entitled little wench.
The Queen should have killed you
the day she killed your mother.
Wait-wait.
Oh, Snow. (sobbing)
(mallet thudding)
What did you say?
(sword thudding)
(Inga shrieking)
(light melodic music)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
(sword whooshing)
(blood dripping)
(light melodic music)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
(Snow White sobbing)
(Snow White
screaming in anguish)
You'll pay for this!
Kill them, kill them both.
(light melodic music)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
(swords clanking)
(both grunting)
(light melodic music)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
(Florizel grunting)
(blow thudding)
-Snow, run!
I cannot leave you.
I'll find you.
(swords clanking)
(both grunting)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(dramatic orchestral
music continues)
Snow!
[Snow] Yvonne! (sobbing)
We are being
followed by huntsmen.
They killed Inga!
Where is Sofia?
I, I sent her home
with the boys.
Come on.
No, no! We have to
inform the Queen.
They are here by
order of the Queen!
What are we going to do?
(dramatic orchestral music)
Hide where they are
too afraid to look.
(dramatic orchestral music)
(swords clanking)
(both grunting)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(Huntsman roaring)
(blow thudding)
(Huntsman thudding)
(cicadas chirping)
(gentle tense music)
(sudden ominous music)
What are you doing? Who are you?
Huntsman Gunnar?
What, what are you...
(solemn orchestral music)
My Princess,
this was your father's.
It's made from dwarf bone.
It will keep you safe.
Now go.
(soft tense music)
Who was that? Did you find them?
Just a couple of vagrants.
Go search the faire.
(soft tense orchestral music)
(soft tense orchestral
music continues)
Snow White!
Have you seen Snow White?
No, Prince, I haven't.
Oi! Oi, Prince!
Are you having a
great time or what?
Yes, yes. Have you
seen Snow White?
[Gerald] Aye, we have!
Where?
We saw her run into
the woods with a girl.
A girl with a nice set of
healthy lungs on her too.
Stay here and find the others.
(gentle tense music)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
(door clanking)
(soft tense music)
Where on earth have you been?
I've nearly aged another
year in your absence.
The huntsmen found
issue, my Queen.
With a young girl? That
does not seem likely.
With Snow White.
Snow White?
What has she done?
She and the Prince saw
Huntsman Kaiser's face.
The Prince is
involved? Where is he?
(dramatic orchestral music)
My Queen! (spears clanking)
My Queen, open the door!
I have news about the
Princess, she's under attack!
Seems we found the Prince.
Yet Snow White is still missing.
She must be found alive or
I risk losing the throne.
It's only a matter of time.
(hand thudding)
(object clattering)
-Find her now!
She's fled into the Dark Forest.
You must send your army there
to find the Princess, please.
We will relay your message.
Now, go before we
must use force.
(tense orchestral music)
Fine, I'll do it myself.
She will not survive
the Dark Forest alone
and we cannot risk
sending my men out there.
Then you go find her now.
And you remember,
I need her alive!
Get on!
(solemn cello music)
(water sloshing)
(ax thudding)
-Oh! What was that?
(leaves rustling)
Maybe we should go back, Snow.
[Snow White] I
don't think we can.
(gentle tense music)
(creature howling)
(both gasping fearfully)
(gentle tense music)
Snow, what are we going to do?
I'm so sorry, Yvonne.
It's okay.
It's all right.
(gentle tense music)
(leaves rustling)
(creature snarling)
(both gasping fearfully)
(gentle tense music)
(leaves rustling)
[Snow White] I can't breathe.
Can you help me with this?
[Yvonne] Yes, give
me your dagger.
[Snow White] All right.
[Yvonne] Snow, we
should not be here.
(gentle tense music)
(corset rustling)
-Thank you.
(gentle tense music)
(leaves rustling)
Over there! (sudden
ominous music)
(creatures snarling)
(both shrieking)
They-they're surrounding us, oh!
Yvonne!
(tense orchestral music)
(sudden ominous music)
(Yvonne shrieking)
(tense orchestral
music) (both shrieking)
(intense orchestral music)
(Snow White screaming)
(creatures snarling)
(tense orchestral music)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
(intense orchestral music)
(gentle orchestral music)
Is this the Haunted Forest?
The Dark Forest.
But it is haunted?
Well, yes, but they don't
call it the Haunted Forest,
just the Dark Forest.
And why are we going in there?
To save Snow White.
Right, about that.
I have heard there are many
other Princesses around,
beautiful too, way less drama.
-Jacob.
-So why don't we just-
-Jacob!
-For Christ's sake, Jacob.
(sword whooshing)
For Snow White.
For Snow White!
[All] Snow White!
Yes, Snow White.
(dramatic orchestral music)
(dramatic orchestral
music continues)
(flesh squelching)
-Every breath she takes
feels as though she
steals from mine.
Every step she takes
marches across my very soul.
(gentle tense music)
Her heartbeat is like
the clanging of sword
on shield inside my
head, it won't stop.
[Mirror Demons] But
you want nothing more
than to see her dead.
'Tis not true, mirror.
(flesh squelching)
The death of Snow White
would cost me my throne.
She cannot die, I
cannot eat her heart
until I gain power
over another kingdom.
I need her.
[Mirror Demons] Need and want
are very different things.
You need the power she
brings with her bloodline.
You want the beauty
she effortlessly holds.
Mirror hanging on the wall,
I am the fairest of them all.
[Mirror Demons] Oh yes,
you are fair, it is true,
but power is not
beauty, my Queen.
Snow White has a pure heart,
a gentle soul
and a radiant face.
You have a dark heart
and a face marred by
envy, age and hate.
Snow White is more
beautiful than you.
No, she's just a
child, a nobody.
I am the Queen, the ruler,
the most powerful fairest
woman in all the kingdom.
[Mirror Demons] And what a small
insignificant kingdom it is.
Enough! I will not listen
to any more of your lies.
Snow White is nothing to me.
[Mirror Demons] You must take
her to the gates of death,
neither asleep nor awake,
in an eternal trance.
Only then can you
bathe in the blood
of her purest heart forever
without consuming her heart
and losing your throne.
(dramatic orchestral music)
And then...
[Evil Queen] I
shall have it all.
(soft ominous music)
(soft tense orchestral music)
(soft tense orchestral
music continues)
(ax thudding)
There she is. Get her!
(soft tense music)
No, no, no! I'm just
an ordinary girl!
We're here by order of the
Queen to bring you back safely.
If the Queen wanted you dead,
she would've left you here.
(soft tense orchestral music)
(soft ethereal music)
(gentle orchestral music)
(tense melodic music)
(singers vocalizing gruffly)
(tense orchestral music)
Leave us!
We are here by
orders of the Queen.
Let her go!
Or what?
Or I'll free your body from
that wart you call a head.
We're here by
orders of the Queen.
Your Queen has no power here.
(dramatic orchestral music)
And neither do you!
(singers vocalizing gruffly)
This is going to be easy.
(swords clanking)
(fighters grunting)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(singers vocalizing gruffly)
(Huntsman Merek gasping)
-Splitsies?
-Splitsies.
-Splitsies? (groaning)
(dramatic orchestral
music) (flesh tearing)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(singers vocalizing gruffly)
(swords clanking)
(fighters grunting)
That was quite the face-off.
(playful orchestral music)
(dramatic orchestral music)
No, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait!
What, we can't kill them now?
We'll send one back.
Remind the Queen she has no
power of jurisdiction here.
So we only need one?
(intense orchestral music)
(mallet thudding)
(flesh squelching)
(Tiny exhaling heavily)
(blood dripping)
Tell the Queen what you saw here
and remind her of her place.
(soft tense music)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
[Tiny] I got brain on me shield.
-Tiny.
-Yeah.
-We wrapped that up nicely.
-I've got a few secrets.
-Time for a bath.
-Yeah.
[Tiny] Awesome, can we keep her?
[Arsta] You forgot
to feed the last one.
(gentle orchestral music)
(singers vocalizing softly)
(soft orchestral music)
(gentle piano music)
Rar! (tankards clunking)
-To another victory!
-Yeah!
Yes, another one!
I can't remember what it's
called, glare-off! (laughing)
Of the head. (all laughing)
To our victory!
-Yeah!
-Victory!
(dwarves chattering)
Hello?
(playful orchestral music)
(dwarves chattering)
Hello.
(playful orchestral music)
(dwarves chattering)
Hello!
(playful orchestral music)
(dwarves chattering)
Men.
Men!
Hello.
How did you get down here?
Oh, I had her restrained.
I thought it was rude
to tie up a woman
without her knowing.
Uh-uh, here we go.
Besides,
what is she going to do?
Kill us in our
sleep, that's what.
I'd kill her in my
sleep if she tried.
(both laughing)
(tankards clanking)
Beautiful, we can't trust
her, she could be a killer.
She's too pretty to be a killer,
But so is that witch
that sits on the throne.
Are you talking about the Queen?
She's not my Queen.
Aye, nor mine.
But you know her?
Aye, she banished us.
Banished you?
Are you from the kingdom?
Aye, we were,
'til she imprisoned,
tortured and killed
our families. (sobbing)
(gentle melodic music)
The last of us that survived
just cast away.
We are all the
family we have now.
Lousy trade, if you ask me.
I'm so sorry.
I just learned today
that I lost my family
to the Queen as well.
Just today, she killed my friend
and sent huntsmen to kill me.
Oh wait!
What we doing?
She could be a spy.
(dwarves exclaiming)
Or a witch.
I'm not a witch nor a spy.
Hm, that's exactly
what a witch would say.
(tankards clanking)
-Aye.
If you thought I
was a danger to you,
then why would you
let me into your home?
Well, that's because...
(dwarves whispering)
Actually, how do you know
we are not murderers?
Wait, we're not?
I thought we were
quite good at that.
No, of course not.
I'd say we absolutely are.
I can see it in your eyes.
There is kindness in your souls.
You can see my soul?
Sounds like witchcraft.
[Dozer] She's being
hunted by the huntsmen.
Which means she's a thief.
[Grimwald] Or a witch
sent by the witch.
The witch sent the
huntsmen to hunt a witch,
but then she switched
from witch to killer,
then back to a witch.
Should that be the
witch's huntsmen
in the huntsmen's search
to find a killer witch?
Obviously.
-Oh, right, okay.
-I don't get it.
I know she's a witch,
she is a witch.
-That makes sense, don't it?
-Yeah, witch makes sense.
(soft melodic music)
(dwarves chattering)
We are the people of
the kingdom filled
We live by the crowning
glory of the cause
Righteousness we stand
against the darkness
That's our calling
on our hearts as well
(fists thudding rhythmically)
Brothers, stand
against evil fury
Fix the enemies
of the throne
We guard the castle,
every life is worthy
Protect our people
in the realm and home
(dwarves laughing)
(tankards clanking)
How do you know this song?
My father used to sing it to
me as a child before he died.
That very tapestry
hung in his quarters.
(light melodic music)
Snow?
Snow White, is it really you?
Yes.
Do I know you all?
I gave your father this dagger.
I was there when you were born.
Your father had watched
over us all the way up
until the witch killed
him and took over.
I was always told he
died by his heart,
and that my mother died in
childbirth during a siege.
It was his heart, a blade
that the witch ran through it.
And your mother,
your mother did not die from
the birth, my dear girl,
she was poisoned.
Can you tell me more
about my mother?
There was no kinder soul in
the kingdom than your mother.
Beautiful by all definitions.
I was their doctor.
You worked for them?
We all did. I'm called
Arsta, by the way.
You can call me Sunny.
I was the royal thespian.
He was a jester.
Hm.
I was the personal
night guard, Dozer.
My father was the Chamberlain.
He ensured that the
royal family was fit
and dressed properly.
I was to follow
in his footsteps.
Beauregard at your service.
Just call him Beau.
That is quite improper.
But you, you can call me
anything you like, my lady.
Undergarment sniffer.
Oh, stop it. Enough out of you.
I was their gardener
despite my allergies.
They called me Pollen,
which reminds me,
did you like your flowers?
They were a terrible idea.
Yes, the bed!
They were gorgeous.
-Oh.
Gorgeous? Well then, I
helped with them too.
You did? Are you a gardener too?
Absolutely not!
The only thing I can grow
is tired of their shit.
Language.
Huh!
I was an ambassador,
probably because of my
good nature with people.
I can tell.
What about him?
Who, Tiny?
He was my assistant.
(chair legs scraping)
(lamps rattling)
-Oh!
(all laughing) (playful
orchestral music)
Alchemist, apothecary, chemist.
I make the mead.
I provide the weed.
I make the dope, you
know, to help you cope.
Would you like some?
You're the dope.
(Tiny laughing)
-I am.
-No, thank you.
I meant that he, well,
just doesn't look
like the rest of you.
Hey, we don't dwarf shame here.
Even if they can be a
couple of twats sometimes.
-I am.
-Language.
I'm so sorry. I didn't
mean anything by it really.
Enough about us.
Tell us, how did you
get lost in the forest?
(gentle tense music)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
[Mirror Demons] You
saw that, didn't you?
(soft ominous music)
My Queen.
Is there art I can do for
thee, before I take my leave?
Ssh!
(soft tense music)
(Laira gasping)
Yes, this will do.
(claps) Handmaidens.
No, no.
Please, you don't
have to do this.
Please don't.
Please, no.
Please, please, please.
-Get on with it.
(soft tense music)
(Laira sobbing fearfully)
(soft ominous music)
Uh! (sobbing)
(soft tense music)
Yes, these will do quite nicely.
Take the rest.
(soft tense music)
(Laira groaning)
(tooth clattering)
(soft tense music)
You forget.
I can take everything from you.
(door clicking)
(tense melodic music)
(singers vocalizing gruffly)
Rise.
Did you find her?
Yes, we found her.
Then where is she?
We captured her, my Queen,
but we were ambushed.
Ambushed? You mean she got away?
(Laira screaming)
A dozen dwar-giants!
attacked us,
(Laira sobbing)
(tooth clattering)
Killed three of my men
and took her from us.
But spared your worthless life.
Why?
A message, I was to let you know
that you have no power
in the Dark Forest.
(tense melodic music)
(singers vocalizing gruffly)
(Laira screaming)
(Evil Queen laughing)
Is that so?
Tell me, huntsman,
which hand do you
wield your sword with?
The right? Well then, you
have no use for the other.
Huntsman Gunnar, I would
also like to send a message.
Now relieve this man
of his left hand.
My Queen, but this blade is
not meant to cut through bone.
Then put your back into it.
(tense melodic music)
(Laira sobbing)
(Laira screaming)
(soft intense music)
(blade thudding)
(flesh ripping)
(tense melodic music)
(singers vocalizing gruffly)
(Evil Queen laughing)
(soft tense music)
(intense orchestral music)
(Laira shrieking)
(soft tense music)
I would've taken your head,
but 'tis apparently useless.
I will do anything
to please you,
my Queen.
Of course you will, of course.
(severed hand thudding)
(gentle tense music)
(Laira sobbing)
Leave.
(gentle tense music)
(Laira sobbing)
Where do you think you're going?
(gentle tense music)
(soft intense music)
Prince.
Prince, come quick.
I found something.
(soft ominous music)
Yvonne!
(gasping) I'm so sorry.
My God, what happened here?
[Felix] Is that the
Princess, Daddy?
Felix, what are you doing here?
You're not supposed to be here.
It's okay, I have my shield.
I came to help
find the Princess.
We've come too far
to turn back now.
We're not safe here.
(gentle tense music)
What do you say?
I agree.
We must keep moving.
(creature screeching)
(broom sweeping)
(light melodic music)
You're doing it wrong.
Hey, that's not very nice.
Yeah, she's doing us a favor
I'd say she's even
sweeping us off our feet.
(all laughing)
Well, she should, otherwise
she'd be a freeloading witch.
We agreed to stop
calling her that.
(playful orchestral music)
Witch.
[Snow White] Shouldn't you
be out mining or something?
I was, I was minding my
own business until you-
Wait.
Do you feel that?
There's something
wrong with the forest.
(melodic orchestral music)
Hey, don't clean under my bed.
(playful orchestral music)
Or look in my trunk
or under my pillow.
Be safe.
Don't tell me what to do.
(playful orchestral music)
I think you're cute.
Scratch that.
(dramatic orchestral
music) (fighters grunting)
Put this in the book.
Not right now, Jacob.
(soft intense music)
(sword thudding)
(melodic orchestral music)
(soft orchestral music)
(sword thudding)
(villager thudding)
Oh, I liked her.
Huh?
(creatures snarling)
(soft ominous music)
(melodic orchestral
music) (blows thudding)
(light melodic music)
(creature snarling)
-Over here, please!
(dramatic orchestral music)
(singers vocalizing gruffly)
Tiny, inny-outy!
Inny-outy up!
(dart thudding)
(creature grunting)
(soft intense music)
(blood spattering)
(playful orchestral music)
Well, that was vile.
That's not going to wash out.
(soft ominous music)
Cover me.
(melodic harp music)
(gentle orchestral music)
Sorry, I've never
met a Queen before.
You called for me?
Yes, I need your help to
bring our Princess home.
Snow White?
Of course.
What can I do?
Well, your role would
be very important to me,
but would be difficult.
Of course, I'll do anything.
Oh dear, I'm so glad
to hear you say that.
My handmaidens will
prepare you now.
(soft tense music)
[Sofia] It was
lovely meeting you.
Charmed.
(gentle tense music)
Have her ready for my return.
(soft tense music)
(singer whispering)
If you want something right,
you must do it yourself.
Death delay, but
breath shall stay,
though blood be drained
and flesh decay.
(soft tense music)
(singer whispering)
Beauty is gone and
life is now taken,
slumber eternal
and never awaken.
Cursed in nightmare
unending damnation,
lest true love's kiss
comes sending salvation.
(tense orchestral music)
(blood dripping)
Rotten, spoiled,
wizened and vile,
this the blood from
the head of this child.
(soft tense music)
There you are, pretty girl.
(witch grunting)
Huntsman, help me.
(Evil Queen groaning)
(soft tense music)
Handmaiden,
fetch me the robes
of a peasant woman.
Now!
And get me my hair.
It's time for me to take
matters into my own hands.
Stop looking at me like that.
(soft ominous music)
(blow thudding)
That's right, run
away, you cunt!
Language.
(playful orchestral music)
Oh, my Lord!
My Lord! (panting)
Boy, what you doing here?
And who are you, bringing
these innocents here
to be slaughtered?
We're actually looking for
someone of great importance.
(sword whooshing)
My name's Prince Flo-
Oh, great, more royalty.
More? Have you
seen the Princess?
Told you she isn't a witch.
Wait a minute.
How do we know that she's
not hiding from you?
Aye.
She's not.
She's hiding from the huntsmen.
I've come to save her.
Works for me.
This forest is becoming
overpopulated, if you ask me.
My Lord!
My boy, Felix, he's missing!
(sudden ominous music)
(leaves rustling)
(distant creature howling)
(creature growling)
(soft tense orchestral music)
(soft tense orchestral
music continues)
[Felix] Father!
Father, help me!
I am lost!
Daddy!
Hello, child.
I've lost my father.
Come here.
I have come to help you.
No need to be scared.
Let's see if we can
find your father, eh?
Show me your fear!
(tense orchestral music)
The dwarves,
they are protecting her.
[Felix] Are we going
to find my father?
Ssh!
I will take your fear away.
(bones crunching)
(tense orchestral music)
(Evil Queen laughing)
[Tiny] Boy!
[Arsta] Felix, where are you?
Felix, come back!
[Florizel] Where
did they all go?
Who?
The dark creatures,
the evil spirits.
When we were banished and
cast away to the forest,
the spell that they used took
away their power over us.
Our very bones are
poison to them.
And Snow White, you're
sure she's safe?
(laughs) Safer where she
is than near that witch.
Witch?
The witch you call Queen,
that banished us
and cast the spell.
She's no Queen, she's a
right bitch, ain't she?
Now, now, the Queen is
the one after Snow White.
The Queen after Snow
White, are you sure?
Quite sure.
In trying to enlist the
Queen's aid to save Snow White,
I, I might have told her she
was hiding in the Dark Forest.
Split up, all of you.
Get back to the cottage.
The rest of us will
look for the boy.
(dramatic orchestral music)
(gentle orchestral music)
Do you like those
scratches, yeah?
You like little scratches, huh?
(soft orchestral music)
Where are you going?
Little friends? Where are
you going, little friends?
(birds chirping) (gentle
orchestral music)
Friends, where have you gone?
(sudden ominous music)
-Help!
Oh, my goodness, what
happened? Are you all right?
In the forest, please help!
It's all right, I have
you now, you're safe.
(soft tense music)
I've got you some water.
Now what were you
doing out there?
It can get quite dangerous.
I was merely gathering some food
when I was attacked
in the forest.
It was fortunate that
I was there to help.
Please,
take this.
(gentle tense music)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
Oh, I couldn't, food is so
scarce out here in the forest
and I am well fed here.
I cannot accept it.
No one has ever shown me
the kindness that you have.
I could not live with myself
if I did not pay it back.
But there is nothing
to repay, my lady.
Kindness should
not come at a cost.
Perhaps you can repay
me with a smile.
(soft tense music)
Your eyes.
You smile,
but there is deep sadness.
Something a bit familiar.
Eat it.
(gentle tense music)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
Eat it.
(soft ominous music)
(Snow White groaning)
Eat it.
(soft ominous music)
(Snow White groaning)
Oh, you're dead, Princess.
(soft tense orchestral music)
(Snow White thudding)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
(melodic harp music)
(haunting orchestral music)
(people shouting faintly)
Oh.
Snow!
(dramatic orchestral music)
Snow, where are you?
Snow.
(melodic harp music)
Inga.
Do you know her?
One of Snow's friends.
She was killed when the Queen
sent a huntsman after us.
She's not upstairs.
[Arsta] She's been poisoned.
Poisoned? How do you know?
I've seen this before.
The poison that killed
the Queen, Snow's mother.
No, the Queen died in
childbirth during the siege.
The Queen did die
during childbirth,
but the cause was
far more sinister.
(haunting orchestral music)
(dagger thudding)
(flesh ripping)
(Queen sobbing)
(haunting orchestral music)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
(gentle orchestral music)
(flesh ripping)
You have been poisoned by
a form of aero longbeng.
It was shared between you and
your child through your blood.
Can you save her?
The only antidote lies within
the magic that was crafted,
a life for a life, a sacrifice,
that can only be made
through true love.
How can I save her?
My Queen.
Please, please.
You must take her poison breath
from her lips to your own.
I cannot give you
the memory of me.
But take in its
place the knowledge
that I love you with
every part inside of me,
and my entire heart. (sobbing)
(soft orchestral music)
If only I could see the
woman you are to become.
(nurse sobbing)
(soft orchestral music)
(melodic orchestral music)
(soft orchestral
music) (baby crying)
(soft ominous music)
(Evil Queen laughing)
Sofia, darling, thank
you for your sacrifice
in my effort to
find the Princess.
I feel so much better
knowing you're happy to help.
(gentle tense music)
(fingers snapping)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
(blood dripping)
(gentle tense music)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
(dramatic orchestral music)
'Tis much better.
[Mirror Demons] Yes,
but surely, not enough.
I have found and
reclaimed my beauty.
[Mirror Demons] And yet
you want more, don't you?
Why, there she is, all
there for you to take.
Go ahead.
You have tasted her beauty.
Now take her heart
from her chest
and consume it all.
I cannot,
not yet.
[Mirror Demons] Eat her
heart and live immortal,
beautiful forever.
I cannot.
[Mirror Demons] Oh,
you know you can.
Handmaiden!
(solemn orchestral music)
(solemn orchestral
music continues)
You are a plague, child!
Even in sleeping death, you
bring me great suffering!
(melodic harp music)
Bring me the shears!
(haunting orchestral music)
Uh!
I do not have anything on
me anymore, Snow White.
You want me to do
your work for you?
No, my Queen.
(haunting orchestral music)
(Queen groaning)
(flesh ripping)
(Queen shrieking)
(tense orchestral music)
(flesh ripping)
(Queen shrieking)
Did you find the boy?
Aye, we did, but a bit
too late, I'm sad to say.
Did you find Snow?
Ah, the witch has taken her.
We are going to take her back.
Yes, about that,
what's the plan?
I just told you the plan.
The plan is we're
going to take her back.
Were you not listening?
Yeah, we're gonna
go save Snow White.
Right, so you're telling me
we just march in
there with no plan?
That is the plan.
What's with this cunt?
Language.
(playful orchestral music)
All right, all in.
[Tiny] Hey.
(Florizel sighing)
(melodic orchestral music)
(soft tense music)
(Queen groaning softly)
(soft tense music continues)
(shears snipping)
(soft tense music)
(soft tense music continues)
My hands, they're
showing far too much age.
Handmaiden, bring me a small
vessel of Snow White's blood.
My Queen.
In your own words, you said
you cannot harm Snow White.
Harm her?
I said no such thing.
I merely need her
alive and she will be,
just without a bit of
blood here and there.
Oh, she won't even miss it.
(blood dripping)
(haunting orchestral music)
(haunting orchestral
music continues)
(tense orchestral music)
All right, they have two
royal guards up ahead.
Killing them would be
treason. Have you any ideas?
Aye, we say bedtime.
Aye, let's put them to sleep.
All right.
I go to the right,
you go to the left.
(playful orchestral music)
No, I said treason.
What are you doing?
(blows thudding)
(royal guards grunting)
(royal guards thudding)
(armor clanking)
Oh god.
(playful orchestral music)
-There we go.
-I thought you said
you were gonna
put them to sleep.
Aye, I did.
Can't you hear them?
They're snoring.
(royal guard gurgling softly)
That's gurgling blood.
(gentle tense music)
Your Highness, I
have urgent news
of an attack on the castle.
An attack?
Who would be so foolish?
It appears that they
are dwarves, my Queen.
(Evil Queen scoffing)
The dwarves? Have
they all gone mad?
They do appear to be quite mad.
How long until they
reach the castle walls?
My Queen, they've
reached the outer walls.
(dramatic orchestral music)
Fuck!
(horses' hooves thudding)
(dramatic orchestral music)
Here they come!
(villagers grunting)
(swords clanking)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(guard thudding)
(swords clanking)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(blows thudding)
(guard groaning)
Is that one of our guys?
I don't know.
(swords clanking)
(dramatic orchestral music)
Think I could do that?
No.
(dramatic orchestral music)
(singers vocalizing gruffly)
(blow thudding) (Tiny roaring)
That's beautiful,
write that down.
Oh!
(guard groaning) (dramatic
orchestral music)
I'm a hero!
Put that in the book.
Fine.
(dramatic orchestral music)
(blow thudding)
(Tiny groaning)
It's a bit crowded in here.
It is a bit crowded.
(dramatic orchestral music)
(singers vocalizing gruffly)
Am I gonna live, boss?
I never got to be
the little spoon.
You're gonna live.
(tense orchestral music)
[Both] Poppers.
(Tiny grunting)
(dart thudding)
(tense orchestral music)
(guard exploding)
(blood spattering)
Do you think they're
doing this on purpose?
Do you think they know
we're doing this on purpose?
[Villager] A little
help would be nice
if it's not too much trouble!
(dramatic orchestral music)
(singers vocalizing gruffly)
(Tiny roaring)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(singers vocalizing gruffly)
(Tiny roaring)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(singers vocalizing gruffly)
(arrow thudding)
(Tiny groaning)
Come on, is that all you've got?
(arrow thudding)
(Tiny groaning)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(singers vocalizing gruffly)
(swords clanking)
(fighters grunting)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(singers vocalizing gruffly)
(Tiny groaning)
(door thudding)
(soft orchestral music)
(singers vocalizing softly)
Thank you, Tiny.
(soft orchestral music)
(singers vocalizing softly)
(tense orchestral music)
(door thudding)
I am beginning to lose
faith in your men!
You are safe, my Queen. There's
no way they could breach.
(door clicking)
(soft tense music)
(dramatic orchestral
music) (swords clanking)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
You kill her, you
lose the throne!
(dramatic orchestral
music) (swords clanking)
Fools, all of you!
(sword whooshing)
Your stupid mistake
in attacking me
has given me everything
I could want.
(gentle tense music)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
(tense orchestral music)
(sword thudding)
(gentle tense music)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
Uh!
(sword clanking)
(gentle tense music)
Save her!
(Evil Queen roaring)
Stupid fucking dwarf!
(Grimwald thudding)
(dramatic orchestral
music) (Evil Queen roaring)
No!
(dramatic orchestral
music) (Evil Queen roaring)
Traitor!
(dramatic orchestral music)
Your powers lie in the Dark
Forest, little dwarves.
(witch reciting spell in Latin)
(magic whooshing)
(solemn orchestral music)
(Dozer thudding)
(Sunny thudding)
(solemn orchestral music)
(dramatic orchestral music)
No!
(Evil Queen laughing)
(swords clanking)
(sword thudding)
(soft tense music)
(witch reciting spell in Latin)
(tense orchestral music)
(tense orchestral
music continues)
(dwarves thudding)
(soft orchestral music)
(singers vocalizing softly)
Here it is now.
We're finally alone
and you cannot hear
my heart beat for you.
For years, I have felt for you,
and always thought you would
be there when the time came.
But here it is and here you are,
and I am the one to be gone
without you knowing
my full heart.
(soft orchestral music)
For you to always remember
me by when I'm gone.
[Both] And to give you
strength in your quest.
(soft orchestral music)
If you can hear a single
word that I'm saying,
take them and hold them forever.
With all of my heart and the
brightest parts of my soul,
I truly do love you, Snow White.
(soft orchestral music)
(soft orchestral
music continues)
[Arsta] The only antidote
lies within the magic
that was crafted,
a life for a life, a sacrifice,
that can only be made
through true love.
(melodic orchestral music)
(singers vocalizing softly)
(soft tense music)
No, no, no, Princess,
you are not meant to come back.
(soft tense music)
I'm going to enjoy this
more than I should.
(soft intense music)
(dagger thudding) Uh!
(blood dripping)
(Huntsman Kaiser groaning)
(blade whooshing)
(blood dripping)
(Huntsman Kaiser groaning)
(Huntsman Kaiser thudding)
(Snow White breathing heavily)
(gentle tense music)
All your words were
not lost, My Prince.
(melancholic orchestral music)
(tense orchestral music)
(swords clanking)
(tense orchestral
music continues)
No.
(tense orchestral music)
Kill her!
Take her heart.
Wait.
Let her death be in my
hands as was her birth.
(soft orchestral music)
I am not one for
sentiment, Huntsman.
Take it now!
Stop this!
(gentle melodic music)
There is no reason
for any more violence.
There have been enough
lives lost in our names.
Take my heart you
so desperately seek,
so that it may spare
the lives of our people.
I will give you my life gladly
in return for the promise
that my death is the
last of this violence,
that the villagers and the
dwarves may all be free.
Do I have your promise?
That the villagers and the
dwarves will all be free.
(Evil Queen laughing)
(soft tense music)
(Evil Queen clapping)
(Evil Queen laughing)
(soft tense music)
Stupid little Princess!
I am the Queen.
Now give me your heart.
(gentle tense music)
You have my promise.
Just do it already!
My Queen.
(dagger thudding)
No!
(soft haunting music)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
(gasping) Yes.
Yes.
Bring it to me.
Bring it to me now.
(soft haunting music)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
It is still warm.
(soft haunting music)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
(soft tense music)
(soft tense music continues)
(soft ominous music)
(Evil Queen screaming)
(soft tense music)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
(magic whooshing)
(glass shattering)
(soft tense music)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
(soft orchestral music)
(witch reciting spell in Latin)
You will die today, Snow White!
And I will steal
your last breath!
(dramatic orchestral
music) (magic whooshing)
Enough! (reciting
spell in Latin)
(magic whooshing)
(soft tense music)
(singers vocalizing eerily)
(Evil Queen groaning)
You know what I'm thinking?
Aye, I do.
Let's kill this fucking witch.
I'll allow it.
(dramatic orchestral music)
(Evil Queen groaning)
Oi, cunt,
just so you know,
we call this one
the butterfly.
(ax thudding) (flesh ripping)
(soft tense orchestral
music) (Evil Queen groaning)
Help me.
Help me, Princess.
Mercy. (groaning)
Show me mer-mercy. (groaning)
[Mirror Demons] Look at you,
you are ugly, vile and aged.
Look what you truly are.
(sobbing) Please help me.
[Mirror Demons] You
have never compared
to the beauty of others.
You will never
find beauty again.
I would sacrifice
all I have
for all I love.
[Mirror Demons] You are ugly.
[Snow White] Even with
all that you've done.
-Vile.
-To my mother,
to my friends,
I would give it all
for you to feel peace.
Your mother's sacrifice
was wasted on you.
The world sees your beauty
and it means nothing to you.
[Mirror Demons] You
are hated by all.
But everything I see about you
is vile,
ugly.
(heart beating) (soft
orchestral music)
And I used to think
that you
were the fairest
woman in the world.
(heart beating) (soft
orchestral music)
You cannot say that, take
it back, you little whore.
Take it back.
[Mirror Demons] Snow White
has always been the fairest.
You will never
find beauty again.
(Evil Queen sobbing)
You are disgusting.
It is your time to die
and your people will
revel in your death.
I'm not supposed to die.
Snow White is supposed to die.
[Mirror Demons] You
have never compared
to the beauty of others.
No!
[Mirror Demons] So look
at you, look at yourself.
You are absolutely disgusting.
You'll continue to watch
in this life and the next,
and everyone will celebrate.
(heart beating) (soft
orchestral music)
I am sorry for your pain.
[Mirror Demons] Watch
as the flesh rots away
and falls from your bones.
You disgrace.
-No!
[Mirror Demons] You have
never been anything.
Shut up, shut up!
(tense melodic music)
(Mirror Demons laughing)
Don't say all
that, take it back.
(tense melodic music)
(Mirror Demons laughing)
(blood dripping)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(Mirror Demons laughing)
(soft orchestral music)
(soft orchestral
music continues)
(Gerald laughing)
(villagers cheering)
Our Princess of the People.
Now, the true Queen.
(Pollen sneezing)
Oh, my friends.
Oh, it warms my heart
that you all are here.
The flowers are beautiful.
Oh, it was our pleasure.
The dress is heavenly.
I wouldn't have
it any other way.
Your performance
was spectacular.
Role of a lifetime.
And I have never felt more
safe than with you by my side.
'Twas an honor.
It is good to be back in
the kingdom, my Queen.
Oh, please, you do not
need to call me that.
Call her what?
My Queen.
-But she is the Queen.
-Don't start that again.
Wilhelm and Jacob Grimm,
I'm grateful you're here.
As are we.
I know that our Lord
would be so proud.
It's Florizel.
Well, thank you both.
Are you sure you
won't reconsider
being a part of my council?
Oh, heavens, no, I'm
too smart for politics.
And besides,
writing is our life.
In fact, Jacob and I
have started a story
about these very events
titled, "Schneeviechen!"
We are still
work-shopping that title.
Well, I'm sure it
will be lovely.
Thank you all again for coming.
-I'm so proud of you.
-Yes.
(soft orchestral music)
[Snow White] Thank you.
Yeah.
Where's she going?
(soft orchestral
music) (birds chirping)
May I have this dance?
(soft orchestral music)
(melodic orchestral music)
(singers vocalizing softly)
(soft orchestral music)
(soft orchestral
music continues)
(soft piano music)
(soft piano music continues)
(soft orchestral music)
(soft orchestral
music continues)
(melodic orchestral music)
(soft orchestral music)
(soft orchestral
music continues)
(melodic orchestral music)
(melodic orchestral
music continues)
One, two, three.
(villagers gasping)
(villagers cheering)
(soft orchestral music)
Yoo hoo, I could use some help!
[Crew Member] I'll
put that around.
[Crew Member] That's it.
(soft orchestral music)
(crew chattering)
[Crew Member] Yeah,
there he is. (laughing)
(soft orchestral music)
I'm gonna throw it up.
(arrow thudding)
(soft orchestral music)
-Yeah, another day.
-Another day, another slay.
[Crew Member] There's
gonna be blood everywhere.
I'm gonna get it all over me.
[Crew Member] Oh, why did
they make him do that?
(crew members chattering)
-Like Photoshop it.
-Hey!
-Sorry, I got it.
-Whoo!
(soft orchestral music)
(actor grunting)
(crew members laughing)
(soft orchestral music)
The plan is to kill them all.
(laughing) We're not
doing the line anymore?
(soft orchestral music)
Sure, thank you.
[Director] Set, ready?
Yep.
[Director] One,
two, three, action.
(soft orchestral music)
Cut!
(crew members laughing)
How bad is it?
[Crew Member] I think it's,
I think it's gonna be okay.
That's good.
-Try not to have this.
-I love you.
I'm sorry you're miserable.
I'm not miserable,
you're miserable.
(all laughing)
[Crew Member] Evil Queen to set.
[Crew Member] One, two, three.
(swords clanking)
Four, five, six, seven,
eight, nine, ten.
(soft orchestral music)
-That's cool.
-Oh, yeah.
(melodic orchestral music)
(melodic orchestral
music continues)
Did I get everything?
No.
(melodic orchestral music)
(handmaidens laughing)
[Crew Member] Oh
yeah, there you go.
(melodic orchestral music)
(actors laughing)
[Crew Member] (laughing)
it's Like thriller.
(melodic orchestral music)
Yeah! Get it, girl.
Yeah!
(melodic orchestral music)
Aw!
Yeah.
(melodic orchestral music)
[Crew Member] Want everyone
moving at the same time.
The creature's
coming. (laughing)
(crew member laughing)
(melodic orchestral music)
[Director] Two, three, action.
-Horses.
(horse farting)
(actors laughing)
(crew members laughing)
(melodic orchestral music)