Boss
Don't you think
We should decorate this place a bit
Leave some traces that couples should have
Traces that couples should have
What specifically?
Well, for example
Couple photos
Sure
Let's take them now
So nervous
How can I be your little wifey like this
Can't you show some confidence
Mm
That's more like it
Your photo-taking skills are so straight guy
Let me see
Just now
When I was against your chest
I heard your heart beating so fast
Have you never hugged a man before?
Strictly speaking, not a woman either
So according to that
I'm actually your first love
You... you could say that
Then you need to practice more
Maybe in the future
It'll come in handy when dating
We'll see about that
How is it?
Things couples should do
What's next?
Next
Sharing a meal
These are all made according to your menu
All your favorites
Your cooking is quite good
Looks pretty decent
Try it
Is it terrible or just not to your taste?
No
It's just
It tastes like home
Like home
You
Haven't been home in a long time, have you?
Speaking of which
Between us two
How do we distinguish
Who's the top
Who's the bottom
I think
That should be obvious at a glance
I can't dance
I'll teach you
You'll have to teach me dancing from now on
Okay
So this is the next part
Yes
A couple must watch a romantic movie together
Alright
Let's start
Why are you sitting so far from me?
Not used to being too close
Hey
You're a professional actor
Too far away
We don't look like a couple at all
Okay okay come come come hug hug hug
(Movie dialogue) I'm still too shy
(Movie dialogue) This letter, I cannot send
This story
Is too sad
It's all fictional
Don't get so invested
I'm actually envious
That they can have
Such an unforgettable love
Mm
Everyone has their own destiny
You'll meet your own love eventually
Will I?
You will
Definitely