What do you think about Teo, love?
Kind of weird earlier
because he was calling me...
- Yana Kassir.
- Doppelgangers.
But don't worry.
I don't sense anything bad about him.
I need a favor.
Can you get
a death certificate or police report?
Anything that proves
that Yana is really dead.
The police found Yana's body.
- Papa!
- Why?
My passport is missing.
I have something to show you.
She was a terrible person.
I despise her, ma'am.
You should get rid of
all your memories of her.
That job that you gave him?
That was a huge blessing for us.
I hope we can find luck with you.
That is, if he does his job well.
I said, faster!
- Sir, this is dangerous.
- Don't stop.
- Overspeeding.
- Sorry for the trouble.
If you can't obey my orders,
then you're fired.
Ma'am!
What the hell is going on?
Ace! Ace!
Get him out of here!
- Ace, let me explain!
- Ace!
♪ Love is never gone... ♪
That lawyer is a jealous man, huh?
Goodness.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Yeah, that might be true,
but to him,
you were doing something wrong.
But don't worry, I got you.
I'll find you another job.
- Teo.
Pa?
You're looking for another job?
What happened to your face?
Didn't I tell you to keep your cool?
Sir Ace hit me.
He thought
I was taking advantage of his wife.
But that wasn't what happened.
He fired me on the spot.
- Hey, hey.
Oh?
It's Sir Steven,
the butler at the mansion.
Sir Ace wants to talk to me.
Probably to give me my job back.
There we go!
- I'll go get changed.
Good luck!
Sir...
Teo.
I'm sorry, I didn't have
the chance to explain.
I just went here to put something
in the storage room.
She walked in and slipped.
I caught her just as you walked in.
You know I wouldn't do that, sir.
I owe you a lot.
I can't afford to lose this job.
My family relies on me.
I've talked with Gem.
She told me the same thing.
I hope it doesn't happen again.
Otherwise...
you know me well.
Good.
Now, go back to work.
Thank you, sir.
I want to use this one. Get it ready.
Go on.
Feeling better?
Of course. Who wouldn't feel special?
I'm a walking 3.4-million woman today.
I already requested
the speedy release of your passport.
Papa talked to
the ambassador about your visas and all,
so, we're still able to go,
but with just a bit of delay.
Perfect.
Teo, has Steven handed you your salary?
Yes, sir. Thank you for the extra.
Go home early today.
Treat your family.
I'm taking my wife out tonight.
-
Just the two of us.
Where are we going?
Well, you know,
one of your favorite restaurants.
- Oh, that's so exciting.
I'm home, Pa.
Huh. That's a lot of stuff.
Well, it's my first salary anyway.
Save some for yourself.
I got the roof and the gutter fixed.
I'm sick of it raining inside the house.
Oh, thank God.
It's almost the rainy season, too.
Wow!
There's so many groceries!
How are your remedial classes?
I'm doing good.
I got perfect scores on my quizzes.
- Oh.
And to be honest,
I find our lessons easy.
It'll be a breeze to go back to school.
That's good.
- I'll be upstairs. Okay.
Okay, okay.
Pa, get dressed.
We're going to get you a prosthetic leg.
So, the first step is making the mold
with plasters or 3-D scans.
It's to get an exact fit for your socket.
Then, we're going to select the materials.
We have basic ones and advanced ones.
Next is the trial fitting.
There, we'll make adjustments
if necessary.
We're so close
to getting you a new leg, Pa.
- Papa?
Teo.
You're fired!
- But why, sir?
Pa, what's this?
I was able to obtain
his records from Morocco.
That man was convicted
of murder and robbery.
Pa! Let's not play around
with his employment.
You let a criminal into our home.
You put our family in danger!
Haven't you learned anything?
I knew Teo went to jail!
Teo submitted his
police clearance and other clearances.
He had a physical assault case,
but that was dropped.
I didn't tell you about Morocco,
'cause that was in the past!
He's a convict!
Haven't you learned anything
from our past traumas?
People deserve to have second chances, Pa!
As they say...
Every saint has a past,
and every sinner has a future.
Bullshit!
Justice without mercy is cruelty, Pa!
Jurisprudence is not measured
by merely passing the Bar,
but by presiding over it!
You still have a long way to go
before you attain judicial wisdom.
You have yet to prove yourself to me!
If it's not an issue with Ace...
So come on.
It's as if we don't employ people
with criminal records.
Maybe we could use him.
Use him for what?
He's got a criminal record.
He has nowhere to go.
I have a bad feeling about this.
People like that are treated as rejects.
Society despises them.
But if you're kind to them
and you treat them well...
they'll serve you with
a loyalty you'll never find anywhere else.
Come on, love.
Why did you lie to me?
Why didn't you tell me
about your other conviction?
I didn't mean to lie, sir.
I just forgot to tell you
about my case in Morocco.
Ah.
So, you're a lawyer now?
I just needed a job, sir.
When you made the offer,
I couldn't say no.
But wherever I go and whatever I do,
I know, and I'm confident
that now my conscience is clear.
They gave me a royal pardon.
They saw that my association
with the case wasn't that strong,
so they let me go.
But then again, I can't blame you, sir,
if you want to fire me for real.
That's right.
I should, and I will.
But I will not give my father
any satisfaction
that I was fooled by someone like you.
I don't lose, Teo.
Not to you,
not to anyone.
I was mistakenly charged
and convicted in Morocco.
I'm a victim, sir, not a criminal.
What else are you not telling me?
Nothing else, sir.
It's so good!
- Yeah?
- Yes. Thank you.
Boss, two kwek-kweks, please.
It's okay, huh?
Yes.
Stay in love.
Yes, Papa. And I'm sorry
I can't bring you to the airport today.
No problem.
Thanks. It's delicious.
Oh, thank God.
Thank you.
Boss, mind if I ask you something?
I'm looking for a foreigner.
I saw him buying here yesterday.
Well, a lot of foreigners buy here
every day.
He's Spanish. Jorge Ybañez.
This man.
Ah, yes.
He often buys here,
but I don't know his name.
He's Spanish, but he speaks Tagalog.
That building
where all the foreigners live,
that's where he stays.
Why do you ask?
I'm just looking for him
for some unpaid debt.
Don't tell him about this, would you?
He might run off again.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Cold drinks!
Hello, sir?
Where are you?
Go back to the office.
Sir Ace is about to leave.
Okay, sir. I'm on my way.
Hurry up.
Did Teo drive you here?
Yes, love.
Love, can you send him home?
I have my car.
I can drive you.
I just don't feel comfortable
around him.
And I don't think
you should be with him either.
- Do you want me to fire him?
- Yes, please!
Then go ahead.
You make all the decisions.
You're the one who knows better, right?
You think I didn't think this through
and decided that keeping him
was the better option?
I didn't mean it that way.
Let's not talk about him anymore.
I was trying not to linger
on this issue,
but you keep bringing it up.
Sorry.
Thank you.
Let's just eat.
Teo stays, okay?
I'm sorry.
Do you know what happens
if you end up in jail?
When you don't even know
if you'll make it out alive.
That quiet anger
that's building inside of you...
it changes you.
And that's what happened to Teo,
and I understand him.
Waiter?
Yes, sir?
It's dirty.
- I'll replace it, sir.
- You can use mine, love.
Replace everything!
Plates, glasses... everything! Now!
All right, sir.
Psst.
Talk about short notice.
Good thing I'm single,
or you'd have no one to bond with.
You're the one who won't stop bugging me.
I mean...
this job is seriously driving me crazy.
There are so many events!
The deliverables are making my head spin.
But it's exciting.
How about you?
I told you to just tell them
you were locked up in Morocco.
And now... the ex-judge
and Madam are fighting.
And then Miss Gem?
Well, they're packing now.
Their move to the States
is happening sooner.
When will they be leaving?
What will happen to me if they leave?
Well, that's going to be a problem.
You'd better clear that up with Sir.
All right, thank you.
No problem.
Maybe we're brought to the same place
so we can always...
look out for one another.
- Hey, Larajean.
- What?
Larajean. Mama is calling you.
Yes, Ma'am Gem.
- Ma'am.
- Excuse me, ma'am.
Do you need me
to take you somewhere?
Will we use this car or Sir Ace's?
I'll just use the other one.
I didn't realize
your father was still here, ma'am.
I actually saw him.
Didn't we just drop him off
at the airport the other day?
- What?
- Unit 1538.
Encina Heights, Los Olivos.
That's where I saw him.
What the hell are you talking about?
That I'm the girl that you're saying?
Why? Am I wrong?
You and your delusions.
I don't have anything
to prove to you, Teo.
You know what I feel for you?
Pity.
Because Ace hurt you,
and I feel guilty about it.
So, here.
My daughter! How are you?
Hello, Papa!
You called?
I am with your mother.
Can I talk to her?
She's sleeping.
We just came back from her dialysis.
How was your flight, Papa?
It was okay.
Your mom really liked your gift.
She hopes to see you soon.
Me too, Papa.
Glad to hear she likes it.
I'll just call back later. Love you, Papa.
Anger is like fire.
Wild, it burns everything.
But with purpose...
it becomes power.
Whatever it is you're talking about...
I don't care.
Don't wait for my pity to run out, Teo.
Obviously...
you're struggling.
And I know you're working for your family.
You're hanging by a thin rope.
One mistake and you're done.
If that happens,
you'll just be another loser.
Go slowly.
There we go.
Oops. Just remember that...
- This is great!
- ...you should balance first
before you take a step.
This'll only take a couple of sessions.
You'll get used to
being without your crutches soon.
Nice one, Uncle Alonzo.
You'll be the first one out
during a gambling raid!
Shut up!
You look more handsome, Pa!
Really?
You're walking straight again.
Teo.
Thank you very much.
I know...
you've got a lot of bills to pay.
And then there's me...
just adding to your burden.
You deserve it, Pa.
You can go out and have fun with us now.
I'd love to invite you
to Madam Katarina and Miss Gem's
new collection launch.
- I'm serious.
- Oh, no. No, thanks.
- Wait, you're there too?
- Yeah.
I might be there too!
They invited all of their scholars, so...
- I have to show up.
- Do you need to go?
Yes, Teo.
- Well, I didn't want to, but--
- Then don't go.
Tell them you're sick.
Don't go.
Uncle Alonzo...
Pa, I'll just pay for this.
Looks like that's going to take a while.
I'll just go to the bathroom.
I'll go with you, Teo.
- Adjust it, please. Larajean?
- Yes, Uncle Alonzo?
What's wrong?
You're working with Teo
at the mansion, right?
Is he telling you something
about a girl named "Yana"?
Yana?
The one who scammed him in Morocco?
Nothing, really. Why?
It's about...
Gem Verona.
Gem Verona. Sir Ace's wife.
Apparently, those two look identical.
- She transformed?
- Like a chameleon.
She's wealthy, refined, and modest.
I think Teo is still investigating it.
That's why he's always lost
in his own thoughts.
That's why he's always on edge.
If ever...
you hear something,
give me an update, all right?
Okay.
Ordonez.
You have a visitor.
Take a seat.
Attorney.
Why am I still stuck here?
The judge said...
he'd help me get out of here,
as long as I kept quiet.
I will be your lawyer.
I already have a lawyer.
The judge gave me one.
I will be your lawyer.
Why are you making it so hard
for me to get out of here?
Is this case even worth fighting?
Why don't you guys just pay them off?
Why don't you just pay them off?
Are you suggesting
I'm not capable of winning your case?
It's not like that, Attorney.
My life is in greater danger!
You'll be in more danger
if you talk, Daniela.
Remember.
We know where your family lives.
- Cheers!
- Cheers.
Congratulations, sir.
- Thank you.
- Another win.
Governor Guevarra sent you something.
A box of champagne.
Nice.
Send it home.
And don't forget
to send him the bill, all right?
Congratulations.
Thanks, Pa.
You're coming here more often.
I'm not visiting.
I decided to work again.
Effective today.
I'm getting bored playing golf. And...
I didn't want to be an ambassador,
so I figured...
I'll oversee the cases in my law firm.
Is there a problem?
I've been trying to catch you
at the right time.
Must be nice to be rich, huh?
I wonder...
will we be stuck like this forever?
- Why isn't anyone doing my touch-ups?
- As a servant? As a slave of some sort.
You know what?
I'm actually confused.
I don't know what my job here is.
All I know is I'm the madam's assistant.
But she's asking me to do so many things,
as if I'm one of her household staff.
You like that, don't you?
Besides, this is just for now
because of the event.
Raya, move forward.
Gem, kindly move forward too.
And pose.
Yeah, that's it. That's nice.
Gorgeous. I love it.
Hold on. Why do they
have instructions, and I don't?
Ma'am, you just have to sit there.
This is getting to be boring.
Let's take a break. Is the food ready?
Uh, yes, madam. Um...
Shrimp salad is ready, and soup.
- Oh, good.
- Oh, thank God!
- That's my favorite.
- Okay, let's go.
We'll also take your solo shots, ma'am.
- Seriously?
- Yes, ma'am.
Please, be seated.
Okay! It's my time to shine.
- Go, go, go!
- Take shots of her, okay?
Thank you.
Hey.
You've been staring at her
since earlier. Why?
Oh, come on.
You're locked in, Teo.
Don't even deny it.
- It's so damn obvious.
- Larajean!
What is it?
Is there something you're not telling me?
What do you know?
This is about Yana.
Let me guess, Papa told you
I suspect Gem and Yana
are the same person, huh?
Hey, of course not!
- I swear.
- Ronnie told me already.
You're busted. Don't deny it.
Larajean, Madam wants to see you.
- Yes, Madam?
- Larajean,
I'm just wondering,
what's my schedule next week?
- Okay, ma'am. Let me double-check.
- Okay.
Love?
Love, where are you?
I'm here.
Oh.
But why are you here already?
I thought you were coming home late?
I had to get out of the office.
Dad is suffocating me.
Self-proclaimed consultant
of our law firm?
Why can't Dad
just trust me for once?
Love, calm down.
We'll be leaving for the US soon.
You can put up your own law firm there.
No one's going to bother you.
It's Josie.
I have to go to the jewelry store.
Wait, love. Sit down first.
Can we just stay here?
Or should we leave already?
Get away from here.
Maybe if we get rid of our stress,
we can finally have a baby.
It's been three years now, love.
Love, I know.
But the doctors said
we're perfectly healthy.
And I'm sure we'll have a baby soon.
But for now,
we have to listen to Mama's demands.
Remember, she might launch a world war.
Is that what you want?
Okay.
Is there any food?
- Yeah.
- I'm getting hungry.
You've been avoiding me all day.
Why didn't you tell me
about your suspicions?
I could've helped you with your mission.
Psst! Hey!
Stop ignoring me!
I've done some research.
I've also asked around.
Yana died in Morocco a long time ago.
There you go.
The only way to be sure is
to get her biometrics or run a DNA test.
But you don't have a point of reference.
So, what are you obsessing over?
Nothing. Okay?
Larajean, I'm here to work.
To make a living.
That's all.
That stare said otherwise.
You know what I think?
Your plan smells like vengeance
with karma on the side to me, Teo.
Am I right?
No.
If I were to see Yana,
I don't want to get revenge on her,
I want justice.
That's all.
- Honk the horn.
- Yes, sir.
- Get out.
Wait for me here.
Sir?
Wait for me here!
Good evening, boss.
Bring out your passports.
Take their passports.
Put our operations on hold.
And ask them
if anyone knows Daniela Ordonez.
Maybe one of the recruits
is a friend of hers.
Hey!
What are you doing?
- I... I'm a reporter.
- Huh?
- I'm a reporter!
- Yeah, right.
Come with me!
- What the hell?
- Stop resisting!
- I told you, I'm a reporter!
- Guard!
- Guard, we have a thief!
- Check my ID!
I'm not a thief!
- Guard!
- I'm a reporter, not a thief.
What are you doing here?
Don't move!
- Call for backup.
- Okay.
- What was that?
- We have a problem outside.
Attorney Verona.
My name is Hans Ruiz.
I'm a reporter from Kidlat News.
Your new driver saw him climbing the wall.
Attorney? Attorney?
Attorney, Attorney.
Sir, I'm a reporter.
Please. If I disappear,
people will look for me.
That will only confirm the rumors
that you're a smuggler.
This is a private property.
My family is doing nothing wrong.
Take him down to the police station.
I'm suing you
for trespassing and defamation.
And if you dare report it,
I'll add libel and cyberlibel
to your charges.
I'll bury you in lawsuits.
Boss, is there anything else
I can do for you?
A lot of people are besmirching our name.
The people Papa defeated in court,
and now the ones I sent to jail,
are all joining our list of enemies.
Are you going to press charges
against that reporter?
Of course!
To teach him a lesson.
There's nothing wrong
with the charges I'm filing against him.
All right, you may go.
Okay, boss.
Ma'am Gem?
Oh, it is you. What are you doing here?
Getting some fresh air, obviously.
You can go ahead.
All right, ma'am.
You're 20 minutes late.
I had to meet my staff
about the new case, Pa.
You told me to prioritize the clients
before all else.
I know. I also know who it is.
Daniela Ordonez.
Drop the case.
The court has ordered Ordonez to show up
and appear in court.
And when that happens,
your brilliant son will defend her.
You're not handling this case.
I assigned it to another lawyer.
We can't get involved.
Exactly, Pa.
What if someone
convinces her to be a whistleblower?
I'll handle the case
so I can watch over it.
No.
We can't take risks.
Leave the case to me.
Oh, by the way,
I learned about what happened last night
with that snooping reporter.
It's a good thing Teo was there,
or something else might have happened.
Teo told you about that?
No.
The guards told me.
If that reporter is presumed missing,
we'll get in trouble.
He didn't see anything last night.
So don't worry, okay?
You take care of it.
That's your responsibility.
I'll have our operations transferred
since our location has been compromised.
You should go to the venue.
Your mom has been nagging me about you.
Let's have quality family time tonight.
- Mr. Gani. Take a break.
- Yeah?
Have some snacks first.
- Okay.
- Come on.
Let's eat.
Oh, that looks good.
- Divino.
- Hey! How are you?
- Thank you for coming.
- Katarina, hello.
Hi, Alberto!
Katarina, congratulations!
This is something else.
Thank you, Alberto.
And I love that you like it.
What are you doing here?
Were you invited, or are you gatecrashing?
Pretty, isn't it?
Does it suit me? Ma'am Gem gave it to me.
You know, I looked it up online
and a brand-new one costs 35,000 pesos!
This is an upgrade to my wardrobe.
- You talked to her?
- Yeah.
Why wouldn't I? We don't have any issues.
I believe she likes me.
So, uhm...
Are you ready? Shall we try again?
Open your heart to me.
You're just
putting yourself closer to her.
Slight.
But at least I get something from it.
And yes, I admit.
I want to know if you're right
that Gem is Yana.
Juicy.
Larajean, let me handle this.
Just tell me what I need to do
and I'll do it, okay?
You're so stubborn.
Thank you, Steven.
I thought
everything had been planned.
Why are you so anxious?
Because your son isn't here yet.
Excuse me, Madam, Sir.
They're on their way.
Oh, finally.
Thank you, Josie!
Well, here's one.
I think here's the waiter. Okay.
Finally, here they are!
Finally!
Oh, here they are, here they are.
Well, did you like it, Ma?
Well, it's...
breathtaking, I must say.
I know.
But honestly,
had I known you were going
to make a quick change, Gem,
I could've swung from the chandelier
for my entrance as well.
Just for you.
I agree, Mama. That would be entertaining.
And I promise, the next time,
I'll swing from the chandelier with you.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I've never been
to an event like this before.
Ronnie. Hey.
Are rich people really like this?
Are you really asking me that?
Let's eat.
- Let's eat, guys.
- Is this yours?
There's more here.
What are you doing here?
- I was invited.
- Why?
I am also a scholar of the Veronas,
so I was invited with them.
Oh well, it's nice to see you.
Enjoy. Enjoy, guys.
Let's go, Gracie.
Does my outfit look bad?
- It looks fine.
- Yeah.
Fruity taste, and I'm telling you,
no hangover.
- Teo.
- Sir.
You're here.
I need you to do something.
Go to Ma'am Gem's room
and get the champagne bottles.
Bring them down here.
Yes, sir.
- Here's the champagne.
- That was fast.
And here's the room key.
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
What's going on?
Do you really want to help me?
Of course.
Hey, Ronnie!
- Hi.
- So, you're a scholar
sponsored by Raya's family.
Such a small world.
Y-Yeah, not just me.
Those guys over there, too.
- Hi.
- Enjoying the night, Raya?
Pa.
And who's this?
Uh, Dad. This is Ronnie.
He's my schoolmate.
We're in the same year,
but he's taking Legal Management.
And also, he's one of our scholars.
Ronnie, meet my papa.
The... Judge Divino Verona.
Good evening, sir.
- Uh...
- T-This is mine, sir.
Yeah.
Behave.
You don't have to do that.
I can take care of myself.
Raya.
- Come.
- Ma.
Have you met Harvey?
- Hi.
- Hello.
Why don't you spend
some time together and bond?
Yes, Ma. I will.
Okay.
Ma'am Gem.
You looked so stunning
when you were making
your entrance earlier.
How much is that, ma'am?
It's my dream to have one.
I'll definitely save up for it,
no matter how expensive it is.
I'm determined to work hard
so I can successfully do
what you did earlier.
Actually, ma'am, here. Cheers.
Larajean!
I'm sorry, ma'am. I'm really sorry.
I'm so clumsy.
- Um...
- It's okay.
I'll take you to the bathroom.
No.
- It's okay.
- I'll fix it, ma'am.
It's okay.
Accidents happen.
I was going to change anyway.
I'm really sorry, ma'am.
"She's on her way there."
What the hell
are you doing in here, you creep?
I'll make sure they fire you after this.
Sure.
But before that happens,
I'm going to tell your husband
who you really are.
Yana Kassir.
Oh, right.
You aren't Yana either.
Because you only stole
that identity, right?
You're crazy.
And this?
This Gem Verona...
Whose identity did you steal this time?
How much did you pay Jorge Ybañez
to cover up all the evidence
proving that you're Yana?
What? Did you use
the money you stole in Morocco?
You actually made up a whole story, huh?
You really are crazy.
Help! Ace!
Ma, have you seen Gem?
- Gem?
- Yeah.
Oh, she's just around, mingling.
She was just there earlier.
Drop the act, Yana!
Don't touch me.
Teo, stop this.
It's all nonsense.
Nonsense?
Teo, stop! Stop!
This is all nonsense to you?
You think this is nonsense?
How about this one? Still nonsense?
I gave this to you back in Morocco.
When you manipulated me.
When you set me up
so I'd end up in prison.
You should've just died
so I could get my family's life
back in order.
You ruined our lives, Yana!
Seeing you right now...
you have no idea
how much pain you caused me!
How many times do I have to tell you
that I'm not that woman?
What do you really want? Money?
Money?
Oh, yeah.
You're loaded now,
living in the lap of luxury.
You've got everything you wanted.
Miss Nadia must be so proud of you.
Your Mama Nadia...
the only person you can be real with.
Don't you drag my mother into this.
But she is not your mother.
You aren't her daughter, are you?
You were a fake then,
and you're still fake now!
But your deceit ends here.
Because I will tell everyone the truth.
Wait... wait! What is it
that you really want, Teo?
An explanation.
Tell me the truth
before I drag you
to your husband and his family
and reveal your dirty secrets to them!
Better yet,
I'll just tell everyone downstairs.
No.
You won't do that.
Why not, huh?
Why not?
You think you can manipulate me again?
You think so low of me, huh?
Because life goes on, Teo.
But only one thing is true.
I had already dug my own grave...
just so you could get out of prison.
That was because of me.
I had to die...
so you could live.
Gem Verona
admitted that she is Yana.
- Then turn her in.
- What's that?
But what if everything we've heard
about the Veronas is true?
She's with their family now.
That'll put her in danger.
Teo, I hope
you don't throw your life away
now that you are free.
Like what you're doing?
If you still have feelings
for that Gem,
it will only complicate things.
The Veronas are unforgiving.
They'll make you pay
for the smallest mistake.