Mr. Perm loves you so much.
He can do everything in his power to make you happy.
He can't do everything.
If that so, is there anything I can do on his behalf?
You can let me know.
I will do it for you.
You can't do this for him.
Can you dance with my daughter?
With my pleasure, Your Highness.
I feel bad for her.
Her husband didn't even want to dance with her.
M.R. Anongnuch.
Can I have my husband back?
Where are your manners?
You should wait for me outside.
Ms. Shen, what happened? Where is Mr. Perm?
I think you should take me home.
This is your favorite dance. It's waltz.
Why don't you get back inside and dance for a song?
We can just dance here.
Shen?
Shen? Where are you?
I'm taking you to dance.
- Shen!
- Mr. Perm.
Are you looking for Ms. Shen?
Did you see her?
I saw her walking over there.
I can take you.
Wait.
What did you do?
Earlier…
I leaned against a tree to rest, sir.
I can take you to see her.
Maybe she went back to the party inside.
Where is she?
I'm right here.
What are you doing in the car like that?
Come on, let's go back to the party.
I don't think so.
I'm not in the moed to dance, I'd rather go home.
I introduced you in a big party
because I wanted you to start socializing.
Instead, you wanted to go home?
Let's get back inside with me.
I'm tired, I want to go home.
Suit yourself. Let's go.
Tone, let's go home.
Yes, sir.
How were the ladies that I introduced you to earlier?
Was it fun chatting with them?
Fine, I guess.
You need to socialize with others in the next event.
I saw you sitting by yourself, not talking to anyone.
Sure.
You haven't talked much to you, are you still mad at me?
Nope, just really tired.
Are you jealous of me and Nuch?
Whatever you say.
Nope, we can't do this.
No matter how mean my husband is to me,
I can't do this to him.
Shen?
- Shen? Where are you?
- Ms. Shen.
I'm taking you to dance.
- Shen!
- Shh!
Mr. Perm, are you looking for Ms. Shen?
Did you see her?
I saw her walking over there a few minutes ago.
You both disobeyed my orders last night.
You disrespected me
still you've got a nerve to sit with me for breakfast.
Mom,
nobody said bad thing about Shen's dress last night.
Prince Pin said that her dress was beautiful.
What more do you want from us?
How did you know that nobody say bad things about her dress?
A noble person won't say bad things about you right in front of you.
I guess we have become a talk of the town already,
they'd say that I didn't teach my daughter-in-law
how to dress appropriately.
I'm done eating. I need to get to work.
You should go out today,
don't get in her way or you two will fight again.
I'm so tired to intervene when the in-laws are fighting.
Perm! Perm!
What do you mean by that?
Are you berating me?
Are you happy now?
For causing an argument among a mother and her son.
I'm done eating too. Excuse me.
You can try avoiding me, Shen.
Are you looking for something, Ms. Shen?
I was just getting some fresh air.
Should we harvest flowers in the garden?
We can put them in a vase to brighten up the room.
Ms. Shen.
Why this pomegranate tree from your house
doesn't produce any fruits or flowers?
It can feel the different soil and air, I guess.
Let it adjust a little.
Fruits and flowers will flourish after.
Chan,
we need your help in the kitchen. Khunying keeps on complaining.
She is?
I'm sorry, Ms. Shen.
- It's okay.
- I'm going!
I really need to go.
I understand.
What are you trying to do?
- What is wrong with you?
- You're avoiding me.
I am not.
Why did you act like you didn't want to see me?
I have nothing to talk to you.
Ms. Shen,
are you mad at me about last night?
Stop saying that.
You need to forget about last night,
and don't talk about it anymore.
It never happened.
I'm sorry.
I didn't expect that you would be so upset about it.
I just feel bad for my husband.
What do you feel about me?
Come in.
Khunying asked to see you at the hall, ma'am.
I will be right there.
Rayrai!
Ms. Rayrai! Ms. Rayrai!
Call the doctor.
- Go!
- Yes, sir.
Ms. Rayrai!
How's my wife, Doc?
She is doing fine, just some bruises on her.
But her baby…
Rayrai! You should have been more careful.
What were you thinking, felling down the stairs like that.
Don't blame her. It's an accident.
Rayrai said that she slipped and fell.
Nobody never slipped on the stairs before.
Why did she slip all of a sudden?
Well, I…
I cleaned the stairs earlier
and I saw mashed pumpkin on the floor.
Why did the mashed pumpkin end up on the floor?
I didn't do it, honestly.
I went to feed Khunphra this morning.
If I really dropped the pumpkin,
I would clean it up immediately.
I wouldn't let the mess on the floor for so long.
That's right. That is how normal people would do.
When they make a mess, they need to clean it up.
Unless you have bad intentions, so you leave the mess like that.
There is no reason for me to do so.
Who would know?
You could have a fight with Rayrai earlier.
Mom, don't accuse her like that.
Shen wouldn't know when Rayrai would walk pass the area.
Even if she really dropped the pumpkin,
she did it intentionally
and Rayrai just happened to be there.
That's it.
Intentionally or not,
Shen is the one who caused Rayrai to fall down the stairs.
Will you admit it?
Why did you keep pushing it?
It is an accident.
It was my first baby.
If it was your own baby, would you be mad?
Come on, stop it!
Did you see that?
You caused the whole house to be mad at each other.
Fine. I am the one who dropped the pumpkin.
If it will make you all to be happier,
then I admit that I did it.
Are you all happier now?
Look! Look at what she just did.
I shouldn't have let that unlucky girl to live in the house.
She has caused all the problems.
You should rest.
The doctor said you need to rest more so your body could recover.
I couldn't sleep.
When I close my eyes, all I think about is the baby
Can you stay with me a little longer?
I can't, I only took half day off.
I will be back sooner this evening.
You should rest.
Shen,
I need to talk to you.
Why did you have to lock the door?
I don't want anyone to disturb us.
I need to talk to you about the baby.
It was my first baby.
It was supposed to be my parents' first grandchild.
Everybody was anticipated to see it.
It was gone
because of your carelessness.
I am sorry about that.
Don't you think it is too easy to say sorry?
I think you need to do more to own up for it.
What do you want me to do?
Have another baby for me.
Help! Help me! Help!
Help! Help!
Who is in there?
Shen? Is that you?
Shin, get the key.
Why are you interrupting me?
Do you have any idea what you just did?
She is your brother's wife.
Well, she flirted with me.
Not true, he's lying.
He is a liar.
You need to be quiet.
I don't know what the true story is.
But nobody can find out about this,
especially Perm and Rayrai.
I will take care of Term, you hear me?
DO YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
Sure.
Go! Get out of here.
Not so fast.
What? Nothing happened, okay?
You have never changed, not one bit.
I thought that marriage could fix you.
Instead, you're behaving worse
and you tried to rape your own sister-in-law.
This is my order.
You can't touch Shen ever again.
I don't want to see siblings killing one another because of a woman.
Fine, this is noted.
Are you done lecturing me?
Don't you forget that
we need to be grateful for Rayrai's father, a lot.
Keep that in mind.
Sure.
- Shin.
- Yes, ma'am.
You need to keep your mouth shut.
Don't say anything to anyone, ever.
Yes, ma'am.
I won't tell anyone about this scandal for sure.
Perm! Why are you keep staring at them?
- You're jealous?
- None of your business.
Why are you jealous of them? Your wife is way more beautiful.
- Stop talking already!
- Perm! Perm!
Calm down.
I don't know what the hell is wrong with him?
- Get inside.
- What?
I really want to talk to you all day.
I can't keep it by myself.
But you need to promise me
that you can't tell a single soul
after I tell you the secret.
If it is so confidential, then
I don't want to know about it.
No, you have to. I want to tell you even though
you don't want to hear it.
If I keep this to myself any longer,
I will be a dead man for sure.
Can you please listen to me?
Sure, spill.
Mr. Term tried to rape Ms. Shen this afternoon.
Ms. Shen.
How did you get here?
Your husband are at the party tonight, he isn't here yet.
Ms. Shen.
- You can't do this.
- I know.
But I am so worried about you.
I know what happened today.
About what?
- Nothing happened today.
- Ms. Shen.
Don't you lie to me.
How did Mr. Term hurt you?
I don't want to talk about it.
Don't you worry.
If he tries to do anything to you next time,
I will protect you.
I am worried about you.
It is not your job.
And our bedroom
is not your place either.
I am sorry.
I shouldn't have done anything that it wasn't place.
I am just a car driver.
But I really want you to know that
I will be by your side forever.
I am willing to do anything for you.
No need to.
I don't want it.
Shen! Open the door!
Shen!
Open the door!
Go!
Shen!
Why do you have to lock the door?
I was taking a bath so I locked the door.
Yeah?
Have you been drinking again?
None of your business.
Well…
- I should find a cold cloth for you…
- No need to.
I'm not that drunk.
Did you...
wear your shoes to the bedroom?
Huh?
After dinner, I went for a walk in the garden.
I saw that my shoes were muddy so I brought them here to clean.
It could be the stain.
I didn't expect such a long answer for a short question.
I am willing to do anything for you.
No need to.
I don't want it.
Come in.
Mr. Perm.
What's up?
I'd like to resign, sir.
I want to go back to Penang
and help out with my family business.
Why?
Is there any problem?
I think that I'm not the right man for this job,
the one that you assigned me to do.
Where is Tone? Why doesn't he show up for lunch?
That's right.
The car is still here.
I think he needs to talk to Mr. Perm in his office.
You can't resign.
I gave your family a lot of money,
otherwise your mom would have been paralyzed by now.
You still need to send money for her medical bills every month.
If you weren't working for me,
how would you manage to pay the bills?
You are the right man for this job.
It is not beyond your ability.
Tone.
- Mr. Perm.
- Wait, Tone.
You can't forget me when we're apart.
I won't forget you.
You will forever be my boss.
And you will forever be my friend.
When I grow up,
can I come back to work for you?
Promise?
We were lucky that he didn't question much last night.
Yes, ma'am.
I won't do that such thing again.
You can't be here me anymore.
When I am out or buying stuff,
you don't have to follow me around and carry stuff for me.
I'm married and I have a husband.
My husband is your boss.
What happened at the party the other night
was a mistake.
And it won't happen again.
Yes, ma'am.
- Ms. Sales Associate?
- Yes, ma'am?
I am looking for perfume for my husband, any suggestions?
Can you describe your husband for me?
I can pick the right scent for him.
He is 28 years old, tall,
good-looking man
and he works at the Ministry of Commerce.
I am buying him a gift.
What about this one? It is imported from France.
There are a few bottles available and this is the last one.
Please give me your wrist.
Do you like it?
Sales associate.
Khunying Anongnuch, hello.
I am looking for a male perfume.
I'd like to thank him for being my dance partner the other night.
Do you have any suggestions?
Just a moment, Khunying.
And this one.
This scent…
which one is it?
It is this one.
I like the smell, I will take this one.
But…the lady…
Hi, Shen.
How long have you been here?
I didn't see you here. Did you see her?
- Nope.
- No, I didn't.
- I'll take this one.
- Sure.
How could you?
Didn't you see that I bought it first?
How much?
85 baht, ma'am.
Put it in a bag.
I told you to put it in the bag.
Sure, ma'am.
You like it, don't you? Stealing from others.
Who did you just berate?
I didn't mean anyone in particular,
then someone jumped to conclusion.
I will buy some rice bran after this
to feed fish in the temple.
If you want to take some of them from me, you can follow me.
Hey!
- Shen, you bitch!
- That's enough.
Don't waste your energy on someone unworthy.
Ms. Shen?
- Go home.
- What happened?
None of your business.
Ms. Shen, please tell me.
I want to go home.
- But…
- Tone!
I told you that I needed to go home.
Tone,
you should take a break.
You've been working out for hours, you must be tired.
Come on.
You're so sweaty, so soaked up.
- Have some water.
- Thank you.
Hey! Stop disturbing him already.
Disturbing what?
We were just watching him box, that's it.
Tone is so strong, unlike someone.
Hey! What do you mean by that?
Are you picking a fight with me?
About what? I didn't mention anyone.
You didn't say the name but you looked at me.
Nobody wants to talk to you.
- You're so full of yourself.
- That's right.
Such a smart mouth.
You're so tiny. I can hang you like a punching bag
and punch you.
Where is Shen?
I asked where she is!
She is at the terrace.
Honey?
Come with me.
- Where to?
- What mess did you cause yesterday?
- About Khunying Anongnuch?
- Damn right!
People at the Ministry told me already. You need to apologize.
You're not going to listen to my side of the story?
There is nothing to hear. Let's go.
- What happened?
- None of your business.
Get in!
Duang, you need to drive fast.
- Yes, sir.
- Go!
Can you fix a better facial expression?
You're here to apologize to her.
Nuch,
I bring Shen here to apologize to you,
she realizes that what she did was wrong.
If I need to apologize for slapping your face,
you need to apologize to me too.
Because you slapped me first.
Shen!
Such a smart mouth.
My dad hasn't heard about any of this.
If you want me to apologize to you,
I think I need to discuss it with him first.
By that time,
you wouldn't be just apologizing to me
but my dad could do anything worse to you.
I'm not sure if any of this
could affect Perm's career.
Well,
it seems like my dad is looking for a new Permanent Secretary.
I heard that so many talented people catch his attention.
I'm not sure who will be the very first ones
to be eliminated.
I'm sorry.
You slapped me so hard
but this was how you apologized to me?
If you bow down to your knees,
that would be more appropriate.
Perm.
Come here and sit with me.
I bought you a perfume.
I spent such a long time selecting
the one that would suit you the most.
Do you want to sniff it? I'll spray some for you.
Sure.
It smells nice.
It smells really nice.
Perm, dear.
My dad won't be home tomorrow.
I will be so lonely.
Can you come to dinner with me?
Sure, I can.
And…
don't bring anyone with you.
What are you doing?
I am useless to you.
- Why do you still want me here?
- I want you as my wife.
You're precious to me, I still need you.
Precious?
And you acted so close and cozy to Nuch right in front of me.
- And I am precious to you?
- I see her as a sister.
She is a daughter of my boss.
What would happen if she decided to tell on you?
I did that because I was worried for you.
No, you were more worried about your career.
You took her side and I need to bow to her feet.
You didn't even ask me what happened.
You didn't even care how hurtful I was.
If you really needed to suck up that bitch
and you ignored my feelings like this,
you should just divorce me and marry her instead.
Stop talking to me like that.
I am your husband.
You need to respect me.
I am your wife.
You don't need to respect me
and you can abuse me all you want?
You spoke to me harshly first.
I needed to discipline you.
If abusing your wife
would make you feel proud of your masculinity,
Go ahead and slap me more!
Just slap me!
You challenged me?
You're right for slapping me.
Because I am a bad wife.
I keep on talking back to you.
Slap me more!
Slap me until I was injured and die! Do it!
- Slap me until I die!
- Enough!
Get out of my face.
Go away!
Go!
Tone,
take me to the cottage in the rice field.
Yes, ma'am.
Make love to me.
I am no different
than the little birth, Nualnoi, in a cage at the terrace.
Since my mom passed away,
my dad had shieled me from everything.
He didn't let me go anywhere.
When I got married,
I thought that
I would be free from that cage.
It turned out that
I was just moved to live in another cage.
Today,
you finally free me from the cage, Tone.
I told you already
that I can do anything for you, Ms. Shen.
Does it still hurt?
Ms. Shen,
please stop crying.
You still have me, I am right here.
Where have you been?
Why are you home so late.
I went home to see my dad.
I need a shower.
- Aunt Erb.
- Yes, sir?
I won't be home for dinner tonight.
I need to have dinner with Nuch.
Please tell mom for me.
Sure, sir.
He is not the same guy that I used to know.
As a matter of fact,
maybe I have never known him.
Please don't change, Tone.
Never,
I will never change.
I wish I had a superpower.
I want to freeze this moment.
I don't have any superpower
but I will love you
as long as you want.
I'm here to warn you about Tone.
I see that Shen is going out with him every day.
They both are young and it could lead to scandal.
Do you have anything to tell me?