[Characters, events, place names, and groups appearing in this drama are fiction.]
[The child actor was filmed under the supervision of a guardian.]
[The animal scenes were staged and filmed in compliance with animal welfare guidance, in collaboration with experts.]
[Episode 3]
Seoul men are all handsome and stylish.
Imagine how ashamed and embarrassed she was
that someone like me showed up.
Darn it!
Hey! You're not shameful or an embarrassment!
If that's true,
I'm ashamed to have accepted such behavior for over 10 years as the boss.
Hey, don't swear.
It's not Kang Hee's fault.
You accepted this, of all things, as a "gift"?
Hey, give it to me, it's mine.
My god! Idiot, simpleton.
Han Woo.
What?
- I've decided.
- On what?
I... am going to lose weight!
Fighting!
I can do it!
I'll lose weight, become handsome, and go to see Kang Hee again.
Yeon Soo, it seems this life is a mistake.
Until that day comes, no carbonated drinks whatsoever.
Gods, what a waste.
Not long ago, you said Kang Hee would kill you if you lost weight and ate ramen every night.
Didn't you recently eat ramen with sausages?
The Cheon Yeon Soo you knew is dead.
I will be reborn.
Seven, eight, nine,
ten, eleven…
Twelve…
No, no.
Three.
♫  ♫
Hey! Take it slow.
Hurry up!
I'm getting dizzy.
♫  ♫
One, two.
One, two, three, four.
- One, two.
- Faster, faster.
♫  ♫
My thighs are bursting.
- Hey, come quickly.
- Just get on quickly.
♫  ♫
Hey, Han Woo!
♫ Riding a sled through the white snow ♫
♫ Feeling refreshed as I race along ♫
♫  ♫
I'm Geum Seok Kyeong.
It's that man.
Please transfer ownership of Kang Hee to me.
I will take responsibility.
No.
- It's not this room.
- Excuse me?
Come out, quickly.
I'm sorry.
It's been a while.
Have we met before?
I said let's get out of here quickly.
Ten years ago, we met once.
If it was ten years ago…
When she was working at the convenience store, you recorded a video...
of the boss who didn't pay and verbally abused her.
That was you then, right?
I'm sorry.
See, I told you we definitely met before.
You knew all along, Ms. Ji Kang Hee.
Then why did you pretend not to know me?
When did I say anything about transferred ownership?
My ownership is mine. I won't give it to anyone.
Yes, this! This is the expression I fell for.
This look in your eyes, this hair color.
I'm telling you, this just can't be replicated.
I won't let you go until I hear an answer, so tell me.
Why did you pretend not to know me?
I don't like working with people from the past.
Oh, that's exciting.
I really like that answer.
Then let's talk about the future, not the past.
You're heading up, right?
I was on my way down.
I'm not going to the after-party.
I won't take you along. No need to ruin the mood there.
Let's work together.
[Heir Geum Seok Kyeong]
Please come to our hotel design team.
The door is closing.
What now?
- Merry Christmas.
- Going down.
The door is closing.
Ah, this is all because of that Chun Pil.
Oh, wonderful daughter, happy birthday.
Um, that is… I mean…
Yeon Soo had something to tell you, begging and pleading…
That's what I did…
Hello, are you listening?
Our last Christmas together,
just know that you blew it off splendidly.
I will never contact you again.
Take care and live well, Mr. Chun Pil.
Yeon Soo.
I wonder if Seoul is very cold too?
What if it's very cold?
If it's cold and tough,
come back anytime, Kang Hee.
I'll wait here.
Whenever that is, I'll just be waiting for you.
Kang Hee.
I'm cold.
Who told you to show up, out of the blue?
Sorry.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm not going to hurt you.
Do you care for any wine?
I'm cold.
Ah, right?
I'll get you something warm.
Do you have chamomile?
Yes, take a seat and wait a moment.
Thank you for coming that day.
Thanks to you, I bade my grandfather farewell.
I'm sure grandfather was happy that you came.
Do you think so?
All we ever did was fight.
It wasn't your fault.
- What happened?
- Huh?
Why are you here today?
It was your father's request.
That and... I've caught the first snow ten times.
Huh?
I said I'm ready.
Ready for what?
Anything.
You're saying you'll come to Seoul?
There's nothing I can't do.
Hey, aren't you a large animal veterinarian?
There are no cows in Seoul.
But you're here.
Purple Tok!
This?
It's the one you gave me, that day.
- Really?
- Yes.
Look at the expiration date.
This teddy bear…
No, you're not even a teddy bear anymore.
This is my favorite champagne.
Chun Pil gave it to me, saying it's a gift for you.
And you?
Don't you have a gift?
Surprise!
Lame...
Open it.
Isn't this something you should give to a girlfriend?
You know I don't have one.
How would I know? It's been 10 years.
You've changed so much.
I almost didn't recognize you.
I said I would wait.
For life.
I said I'd only like you.
Let me try this on.
How is it?
Kang Hee.
Be honest, did you not miss me?
Don't use that tone.
I really wanted to see you.
Don't smile like that.
I thought about you all month, even dreamed about you.
Don't joke like that, it makes my heart flutter.
Don't… Don't listen.
No, even if you heard it, pretend you didn't.
♫ Close your eyes and feel me here ♫
♫ What color is in your mind? ♫
♫ Blue, dark gray, calm and sweet ♫
♫ I can give you all ♫
♫ Please tell me if you're standing here for me ♫
♫ Far across the dream, just call my name ♫
♫ Who's standing over the river ♫
♫ Here I am ♫
Answer it.
I don't want to take it.
It keeps ringing.
[Mom]
Just a moment.
What's wrong, Mom? Are you okay?
Yeon Soo, here… it hurts.
Wait a moment.
Merry Christmas.
Her eyes are exactly like her mom's.
She'll hear you.
- That's fine.
- Her purse is obviously a fake.
She fled our town at night, just like her mom did.
To be honest, I pity her.
Her mutt gaze is just like it was before.
She was so obviously a mutt before,
but now that she's grown, you can't tell as easily.
The older she gets, the more she resembles her mom.
That's why Chun Ja or Chun Pil,
one of them should've left our town ages ago.
- Be quiet.
- What if she loses it again?
That's right. I told you it would be like this
Sorry, did you wait long?
I remembered everything.
What did you remember?
Why I left.
You...
and I…
Why it didn't work.
Why didn't it work?
Save this for your girlfriend.
Kang Hee.
Hey, Ji Kang Hee.
If you go now,
I won't wait anymore.
That's what I've been hoping for.
Our first love...
ends here.
The end.
Are you serious?
Let's live well separately.
Thank you for liking me all this time.
♫ I realized it as I stared into your bright eyes ♫
♫ My love for you, fearlessly, keeps growing ♫
♫ My confession that never reached you, I love you ♫
♫ Will a part of my sincerity reach you today? ♫
No, don't follow me.
I can't take responsibility for you.
♫ My clumsy confession to you ♫
♫ has grown even larger since yesterday ♫
♫ My shy, hesitant first words to you ♫
Making someone wait when you can't even take responsibility,
I have to stop.
Meet someone better than me.
Be happy.
Goodbye.
♫ But it was all love ♫
The man smashed everything up,
and the woman screamed.
I put up with it and when I finally went there,
this lady came out with her eyes this big.
Are you going to report the assault, ma'am?
Me? No, it wasn't me.
I just fell over.
No, I filed a report because of this condition.
Do you beat people up like that for filing a report, huh?
And in front of kids?
You admit it, right?
Oh, I don't remember.
Yes, I saw everything.
Sir, just once, please make an exception just once.
And you, ma'am, get a grip.
How much longer will you live like this, getting hit?
This man just did it in a moment of anger.
But deep down, he is really kind.
He is kind.
Sorry, but could I have a word alone with my mom?
- Yes.
- Just a moment.
Ah, I would also like to speak separately…
Sir, please sit down.
Take a seat.
- Sit down.
- No, I said sit down, quickly.
If there's a misunderstanding, solve it…
Sit down, sit down. Just sit down first.
Sit down and clear the misunderstanding.
No, I will sit.
Oh, it's cold.
- Mom.
- I need settlement money, Yeon Soo.
Did that rat hit you?
That rat?
Hey, watch your words, that's your father!
Your workshop salary,
you've saved some. Right? Lend me some, okay?
I'm asking you a question. Did you get hit?
Why can't you answer me? Why?
Yeon Soo.
What day is today?
Silent night, holy night.
On such a night, should loved ones part ways?
Let me stay with your dad for a while.
Okay? Please.
Ugh, it's cold.
Please.
Please, okay?
You don't have to do it.
Oh my, take care.
Thank you.
Yeon Soo!
Let it be, will you?
Go there and buy some udon or something…
Go eat… hey, you!
I just wanted you to get a bowl of udon.
Yeon Soo, thank you.
Let's go. Are you hungry? What shall we eat?
Oh my, what?
What should I do?
That's upsetting.
Now, let's start the 10-second countdown
to the New Year.
Ten, nine, eight,
seven, six, five, four,
- three, two, one.
- Three, two, one.
Happy day!
We've gotten a year older.
Happy 30th!
Today, you should avoid beef and just eat chicken.
Cheerful voices spread everywhere encouraging a powerful start for all our citizens…
[Motel California]
Thank you.
How about starting with a salary of 30 million won? (~$21,000)
But there will be incentives for each project.
Well, there's a chance I won't get incentives.
It doesn't matter. I've wanted to try working on
the hotels and commercials that you, Director, I mean, CEO mostly handled.
Ms. Kang Hee.
Do you know what "aesthetic disharmony" means?
Pardon?
It refers to the estrangement between feeling genuinely beautiful
- and being forced to feel that way.
- Yes?
To be honest, I've felt that disconnection for a long time,
due to aesthetic disharmony.
Which is why I now want to do what I like.
What do you like?
Trot music.
Trot music?
How should I put it?
If the hotel is classic music, then trot is a motel?
I will not do it.
Ms. Ji Kang Hee.
Yes, Mr. Hotel Heir?
This is Ji Kang Hee speaking.
Is the offer to work together still valid?
Hotels are okay, but motels aren't?
Was it all a scam, pretending to be a hotel heir?
You said so yourself.
Your ownership rights are yours, Ms. Ji Kang Hee.
After hearing that, I also came to claim my ownership. From my father.
I contacted you because I believed you were a hotel designer.
With the rapid growth of accommodation apps, the motel renovation market has expanded.
You can work much more dynamically and creatively than in hotels.
But after all, it's still a motel.
Why do you dislike motels so much?
- Because they are third-class.
- Pff!
Listen up, motel owners around the country…
Fine, let's say motels are third-class.
What's wrong with being third-class?
What would the son of a hotel owner know?
Unless you're the daughter of a motel owner, you wouldn't know.
You are the daughter of a motel owner?
Jackpot, Ms. Kang Hee.
That's really enviable.
If you live in a five-star hotel, do you think you'll become a five-star person?
I thought you had more than five-star charm, even if you were the daughter of a motel owner.
It's not that I'm the daughter of a motel owner, it's just that our home was a motel.
I was born in a motel, raised in a motel, all the way.
The way people stared at me while I was growing up.
Do you even know what I've been through?
When I was young, I didn't know any better and just… fell for my dad's words.
Nonsense.
- Dad?
- Yes?
The kids won't hang out with me. Is it because motels are bad?
What?
What, who? Your friends say that?
I see...
Okay, Dad will explain. You need to listen closely.
Where do people go when they're hungry?
- A restaurant.
- Exactly.
When people are in need of sleep, where do they go? To a motel.
Why? Because they need a comfortable place to rest, right?
So, what should we do when such people come?
In a motel, we provide blankets, pillows,
and we can tell them, "Have a comfortable stay," "Sweet dreams."
That's what a motel is all about.
Do you understand now?
Oh, that sounds good.
Yeah, do you know what the most exciting thing at Motel California is?
Ramen, of course.
Want to eat some ramen?
Let's go! Dad will cook it for you.
The best ramen! Let's go.
People don't come to the motel because they are sleepy, but just
to escape, to hide away.
In a word, it sucked.
Let's combine our efforts to change that perception.
For Ms. Kang Hee's father's sake, too.
My father passed away when I was ten.
So please, leave me out of it.
Ms. Kang Hee.
I'll make you an offer you can't refuse.
- I refuse.
- Okay.
Please open it.
What's the offer?
What's that?
[Deposit 50,000,000 won, from Geum Seok Kyeong]
[Seongok Goshiwon]
Bang, bang!
Father, why are you doing this all of a sudden?
That's really fast, that thing… Hey, come here, you.
Do you think I sold cattle and sent you to college for this?
I paid it all back, that thing.
Hey! If you're going to act all high and mighty, take the cattle you bought and get out.
No, please let me, Dad.
Ah, in the end… Won't you come here?
Go ahead and talk like that in front of Mom.
Oh, really, Dad.
- Come here!
- Testing. 1, 2.
What are you two doing, really?
- Why are you fighting out here, instead of under that nice roof of yours?
- Father, don't do it.
The cows want freedom, too.
I'm telling you to come here.
- Just over there…
- Come here, you.
Father, why are you really doing this?
I didn't do this for you to… come here!
♪ Let's leave this place, to go grab cattle ♪
Why are you doing this, really!
♪ Tier 3, Tier 3 beef ♪
(Korean Beef = hanwoo, this character's name)
Turn it off!
♪ My dear friend, let us catch cattle and enjoy a fancy meal ♪
I said, turn it off!
You didn't act like this when Han Woo first came back. Why the fuss now?
I thought if it was too hard, he would give up and drop out, so I watched.
But it's becoming more and more of a spectacle.
A pasture? Animal welfare?
Do you remember the neighborhood feast when I first entered college?
It was worth doing.
The first one from Hana-eup to pass into Seoul National University, and it was into the law school.
When I gave up the civil service exam to run an inn,
do you remember me getting chased out of my house?
I even gave you a ride to the temple.
I still wonder...
how things would've turned out if my mom just accepted it.
Are you mocking me right now?
Did Han Woo ask you to take his side?
Honestly,
I envy you, Deok Gu.
Oh dear, I...
live without even seeing my daughter's face.
Even though I want to take sides,
I can't win against my wife.
No, a guy who used to dress sharply and was successful in Seoul
is just shoveling cow dung all day long now.
If I don't chase that guy away, I'll be the one getting chased away.
So that's why you're shorter than me.
Let go of your greed.
The best thing in life is to have your child by your side.
Yeah, I'm short, so what? And?
You've all had a hard time.
- You've worked hard.
Oh, you two have done a great job.
Now, everyone have a cup of coffee.
- Thank you.
Right, right, right.
Senior, today is the last day.
Congratulations on your discharge.
I'll be doing what I always do anyway, so we'll see each other often.
You said you're running a clinic in town.
The hospital my grandfather used to run.
Huh? Soon Ja came to sell that?
- What?
- You didn't know?
She even brought a broker.
You're buying a really good building.
Oh my, thanks to the president, I'm buying the building at a good price.
Now, we just need your son to come.
- Yes.
- Oh, right.
What are you doing right now?
Yeon Soo!
Yeon Soo, say hello, here…
The person buying the building, President Kim.
All the contracts have been written up, you know?
You just need to stamp here. Is this Yeon Soo's?
I'm not selling the hospital, so everyone, please leave.
You said it was yours.
Yeon Soo!
It's only in your name, but it's as good as mine.
Didn't you hear?
I said please leave.
I'm sorry, there has been a misunderstanding…
No, I…
You figure it out. Okay?
Yeon Soo.
Mom, I made a promise to Grandfather,
that I would take care of this hospital.
I inherited the hospital, not just the building.
Why did you leave the house?
Hey, how can you live there after all that fuss? So embarrassing!
Then, at least with that money, you shouldn't have gone on a Mediterranean trip.
That… It's been my dream since I was young.
Mom!
So what am I supposed to do?
Should I just live out on the streets with your dad?
Just come live with me at my house.
Ugh, no way!
I'm a newlywed.
How can I live in the same house with a grown son?
I don't want to.
I'll leave.
You said it's yours.
You said it was yours!
Enjoy your meal.
Hello.
I heard about it, come on in.
And Mr. Chun Pil?
He's out, he will be back soon.
Yes.
It's my job.
Thank you.
Still handsome.
♪ Uncle's guitar ♪
♪ For the first time ♪
♪ I touch it, feels good ♪
♪ Uncle wouldn't know ♪
♪ It's thrilling to play secretly ♪
♪ Eolleli kkolle ♪
- Go on.
- You arrived?
No, no. It sounds nice. Why?
Oh, you're here?
What are you doing here?
I could say the same thing.
Say what?
Why are you here?
Why do you look like that?
Look at this one. I need to set him straight today.
Agree? Let's go.
Put your luggage there and follow me.
Uncle, did you see that?
Wow, amazing!
- Wow, it's a hit?
- Good! Good!
Cha Seung Eon did it.
- You've worked hard, Seung Eon.
- You've worked hard.
You've worked hard.
- How about more?
- No, it's fine. Sit down quickly.
Well, these are thugs.
Just like this, the guys who were like that...
- We've grown a lot, haven't we?
- Yes.
These brats used to not even know how to use a spoon. Now they do all sorts of stuff.
But you guys, just wait a minute…
"Gangs family," you guys don't have an older one?
You're not in touch? Try calling her.
Right now.
Were you cut off? You…
- I cut Kang Hee off.
- Which part? Your own body?
That could be… The leg might have been cut off.
But seeing how you can't call her, you got cut off again, didn't you?
Oh dear.
Sir, you were also cut off.
Probably living well, I guess.
Well, calling her is like…
Bottles up.
- Nana!
- Let's do well!
[Golden Gilt Studio]
Miss Kang Hee.
Please choose a wallpaper color.
The pink you chose last time, Miss Kang Hee.
The clouds were a huge hit.
Someone posted in the review.
They say you don't need that medicine if you just go in there.
That pink is a bit, sensual, isn't it?
Ah, it's strange.
The colors chosen by Miss Kang Hee
seem a bit tacky at first, but strangely they catch on.
The photo shoots are also amazing.
How about this color?
Mountain Moose.
It matches the furniture well, and it seems it would make the skin tone look prettier, too.
Wow, it's perfect!
Just a moment.
I'm going to upload this to the website. Please take a look at the photo.
I like it.
The angle is good, and it looks spacious.
It would be nice if the temperature were adjusted.
It would seem cozier if you made the tone a bit warmer.
Miss Kang Hee, site survey.
Yes.
It seems more spacious than we anticipated, doesn't it?
Yes, the space seems well captured.
It's hot. Is it not?
Turn up the air conditioner a bit.
Is the air conditioner working or not?
It's coming out.
Anyway, the primary option here is to make it a business motel that mainly serves business travelers.
Is it possible?
It seems possible to have an open-front design.
Dining room or laundry room.
And I'll check if there's space for luggage storage services.
Okay!
Spicy?
Slightly spicy? Tastily spicy?
What was there like that…
Aren't you getting off?
What are you looking at?
What's the matter?
Excuse me.
Who is that man?
A classmate from my hometown.
"She was seen going in and out of motels," "Ji Kang Hee was already half undressed."
The rumors will spread far and wide, won't they?
- Get off.
- Why?
It's not true, we have to stop it.
It doesn't matter.
I have no reason to go back to such a hometown.
Let's go.
I went to Seoul for fun today, and suddenly I got turned on.
So I went to a motel.
But guess who I ran into there?
Ji Kang Hee.
No, that girl…
She went to a motel with a man in broad daylight.
When the elevator doors opened,
a man and a woman were stuck together, just really.
That girl seemed to love it to death.
I knew this would happen.
This is why home education is important.
What would the daughter of a motel owner have seen growing up?
So what?
- What?
- And you? Didn't you go there, too?
Ha, you guys. Hey!
I'm telling you this because I care about our friendship.
Hey, Cheon Yeon Soo.
You're not still thinking of getting back with Ji Kang Hee, are you?
Wake up from your dream.
Hey!
Hey, listen carefully.
The moment you gossip again about Kang Hee,
especially if I hear something terrible, you're really going to die by my hands.
What's the matter, really? You want to get sued again?
Dude, why are you making a fuss? Hey, why is this guy like this?
Hey, Kim Heon Yeol.
You are really like the mad cow of our house, all hell breaks loose once you're let out.
It's cleaner to bury it with an excavator.
It's over with just one shovel.
Hey, if you guys get reported this time, I really can't handle it.
Ugh, look at that loser.
Anyhow, that really is bad luck.
That's really low quality, that one.
Hey, hey!
Let's have a drink.
Have a drink.
Kang Hee…
Did someone really come into her life?
- Ah, Seung Eon.
- Why?
Can't you just shut up for a moment, really?
What's that, why?
Hey, where are you going?
Where is he going?
Where are you going?
To console him, thanks to you.
You're talking such nonsense.
You pay and come out.
Why did you come? Stay with Seung Eon.
Are you okay?
No.
So you should meet someone else, punk.
It's not like that.
Thinking it must have been hard for Kang Hee.
I feel bad for wanting her to return. It was my selfishness.
Hey, if you're sorry, then listen to Kang Hee for once.
Hey, Ji Kang Hee said let's live well separately.
So let go of Kang Hee now, please?
What is it, you?
Why aren't you talking back?
I'm going in first.
I have a meeting.
What would have happened if I hadn't scouted Deputy Ji?
What? I was the one who made Ms. Kang Hee join.
I was the one who snapped her up from the field.
I was the one who picked Ms. Kang Hee's design.
No, it wasn't.
Ms. Kang Hee joined because of me.
Wanna bet?
Then, 100,000 won, even.
Take 100,000 won, and add another 100,000 won.
Are you joking?
All in!
If you're scared, go on in.
Shall we give it a try?
All-in!
We are in the midst of a stake fight right now, you know?
Kang Hee, please sort this out.
When I sent the 50 million won to you.
That swayed your heart, right?
Not a chance. It was the proposal I made when you came to return that money, wasn't it?
It was me who made the drastic proposal, wasn't it?
Thanks to Coach Esther.
You said you rejected the job offer, right?
If you've come to persuade me… you're wasting your time.
No? I came to commend you for doing well.
I'm an expert at this kind of thing.
Even when I started a business with Seok Kyeong, I was the one who secured all the investments.
I'd like to return the favor for the wedding gift… how about now?
What do you think
Kang Hee, would you like to comfortably talk about
the things you want to accomplish through work?
Someday,
I want to have my own company.
A company with my name on it.
And?
Near the company,
I want to have my own space.
Not a goshiwon or a semi-basement… but a space of my own.
A space of my own.
- And?
- What more could I ask for?
If it comes to that… I might as well sell my soul to the devil.
Would you perhaps be willing to receive an investment?
Who would invest in me?
When receiving an investment,
do you know what the hardest part is?
Finding someone who recognizes my value.
Kang Hee, you've already met them.
CEO Hwang Jeong Goo has a good reputation in the industry.
Geum Seok Kyeong, I vouch for him. He has ample financial resources. Above all,
it's a company that would believe in our potential.
Ji Kang Hee and I, together, hand in hand.
Let's join forces and conquer the motel industry once and for all.
You were behind all of that?
And you haven't said a word to me about it until now?
If you two are the Hwang-Geum line,
shall we say we're the Park-Ji line?
Let's split the dividends in half.
Now, having received the dividends, shall we get inspired to work?
What did you call me for?
Can you go as the site manager for our company's branding project?
Thank you!
I will really, really work hard.
Loyalty!
Where is the site?
You might not know it, it's called Hana-eup.
Where did you say?
Hana-eup.
- Just a little bit lower.
- Yes.
Okay, it seems like gastroenteritis.
The cause is often stress.
In the case of acute gastroenteritis, it could be due to eating something bad.
Director, a phone call.
Yes, sir.
Ah, is that so? Yes.
Yes, I will go right away.
Yes, please wait a moment.
- Ms. Yoon, I need to go to the birth of a calf.
- Yes.
You know the snacks we usually give animals.
Never share with this one from now on, okay?
Yes.
[Hana Veterinary Clinic]
Doctor, have a safe trip.
Will you stop avoiding me?
Avoiding? Since when did I do that?
I'll double the incentive if you go to Hana-eup.
I'll just take the penalty instead.
Are you really going to be like this? Let's talk.
I have a date, I need to go now.
I'll have my phone off, so don't look for me.
You know I'm on monthly leave from tomorrow, right?
I'm going.
Why is that?
She said it's a date.
- A date?
- Yes.
Ah Reum.
Hey!
How did you get here?
I will, I'll carry it for you. Just a moment.
Hello! Wow, you have a lot of luggage.
It so happens I have a cart in my car.
Please, wait a moment.
- Who is it?
- A company employee.
- Did you follow me?
- No.
I live next door.
You live next door?
Because it's the company dormitory.
Hey, dormitory? At such an expensive place?
Our company has a lot of money.
Hey, what does your company actually do?
What?
Wow, it's so beautiful!
Hey, what is this?
Oh, my! Wow, goodness!
Ah Reum, look at that.
I designed this. It's in the magazine.
Really? Wow, that's cool!
Is this a company business card?
Hgpj?
This J is for Ji Kang Hee's.
Hwang-Geum-Park-Ji.
Hwang Jeong Goo, Geum Seok Kyeong, Park Esther, Ji Kang Hee.
Hey, so this is your company?
You could say I'm sort of a founding member.
I have a small stake in it, too.
Goodness!
Wow, I think I'm really going to cry!
Just a moment.
Have this with your friend.
If you need anything else, just let me know.
If your friend wants to tour Seoul, my car…
We'll take good care of it.
- Just a second…
- Ah, thank you, take care.
- Aren't I going in?
- Ah, yes, yes.
- Your friend…
- Have a good day.
Hey, that guy likes you, right?
He likes me? Really?
Yeah.
I didn't know.
Hey!
Have you heard any rumors lately? About me.
What rumor?
Kim Heon Yeol didn't say anything?
That can't be right.
Disappointed? Want me to spread a rumor?
A fabulous guy lives next door to Kang Hee?
The guy next door is dying for Kang Hee?
Go ahead, spread it.
All right.
I'm not going back to that neighborhood anyway,
whether the rumor spreads or not.
It's a relief.
You and Yeon Soo both met nice people.
Yeon Soo...
met someone?
That…
A junior from the same school.
Ah.
It's looking like he'll get married soon.
I see...
Ah, that's right! I brought this.
My mom's homemade fresh kimchi.
Mom really said she wouldn't make it, but…
But when I told her it was for you, she made it right away.
Anyone want kimchi?
Me!
First, the seasoning will be really delicious.
Fresh leafy mustard goes in… either sand lance sauce or anchovy sauce.
Senior!
Oh, Ms. Yoon.
Uh, do you drive?
No, it's been a while since I got my license… I need to take the driving course again.
Oh, is that so?
While I'm not here, you might need to travel alone,
and there might be a lot of emergencies.
Take some training when you have time.
Can't you give me the driving training?
It would work if you train me.
Sorry, I don't have a car.
Oh, why not?
Why don't you train me? Please do it.
Please do it.
I'll do it, later. Later, right?
Okay, you're doing well.
But shall we speed up a bit?
- Speed?
- Yes.
- Just press it gently.
- Fast?
Yes, just a little.
Oh, but I see a car over there.
- What should I do?
- Oh, it's okay.
- Now, stay calm, and…
- Yes.
Tap the brake lightly and… just move a little to the right.
- Yes, lightly.
Brake! Brake!
No, you have to press the brake! What are you doing?
Brake, not the accelerator!
Right, right! Brake.
Brake, to the right!
Are you okay? You're not hurt, right?
The car is fine, so just stay put.
Don't get out.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Get in the passenger seat, I'll drive.
I can't get out, senior.
Okay.
Get out carefully.
Watch your step.
Be careful.
♫ What if I was wrong apart from my everything ♫
♫ Don't force me to hurt because of my feelings for you ♫
♫ Forgive me, my dear, for running into you for a while ♫
♫ You told me about your everything, your whispers are all my favorite thing ♫
♫ I think I fell in love with you ♫
♫ But how can I forget you? ♫
♫ You stayed close in the everyday ♫
The daughter of a motel owner came to renovate the motel.
My father was a motel owner.
Where does he run his motel?
I thought he passed away when you were ten.
This is the most important part. Please don't call me by my name.
- Dear owner.
- Excuse me?
- You're the owner of this project.
Ji Kang Hee got drunk drinking four bottles all by herself.
I don't deserve to come back to Yeon Soo...
- That teddy bear didn't keep any of the promises he made to me.
- Don't leave...