[THE DEVIL BETWEEN US]
[Episode 3]
[Nuanfeng Hengke]
[Accounting Department]
Wu.
Take a look at these for me.
These are invoices from
Public Relations Department.
When were they booked?
I don't remember.
These guys spent a lot of money.
Oh, I see.
Mr. Sun instructed that
these invoices don't comply with
the reimbursement regulations,
but their work is special,
so some costs can't be
claimed officially.
Just let it go.
We usually don't dig too deep into
public relations expenses.
But these past few months,
the amounts have been getting
higher and higher.
If this keeps up,
it's bound to get us into trouble.
What are you afraid of?
Even if the sky falls,
the tall ones will hold it up.
I’m just afraid the tall ones will duck,
and we'll get flattened.
Where are you going?
I'll ask Mr. Sun for his opinion.
See what we can do.
Ken.
Qiang.
Help me check it quickly.
Why haven't I got my salary this month?
Qiang.
Have a seat for a moment.
I have to handle something.
We'll talk when I get back.
No.
I need the money urgently.
Clear this up for me before you go.
Then I will tell you the truth.
I think you know
the reason clearly.
You violated
the workshop equipment regulations
and caused two production accidents.
Your salary for this month
has been deducted completely.
Since Hengke was established,
I've been here.
I've worked here for fifteen years.
I'm a veteran here, right?
Yes.
Then how can you just
deduct my salary like that?
Qiang.
If you weren't a veteran,
we would have
let you pay for the damages.
That's impossible.
You're being unreasonable.
I didn't break any rules.
It was a machine failure.
I'm going to see Mr. Sun.
Qiang.
Calm down.
You're retiring next year.
You're not in the right here.
Making a scene won't do you any good.
I see.
You're behind this,
right?
You just don't want to pay me, right?
No.
Am I right?
I'm just an accountant.
The money doesn't come out of my pocket.
I have no reason to target you.
Why are you explaining so much?
Leave now, or I'll call security.
Stop it.
Give me my money!
Qiang!
Don't do anything rash, Qiang!
I want my money!
Help!
Calm down.
I want my money!
Calm down!
Pay me my salary!
Help! Call the police!
Give me the money!
Qiang.
I know you want money.
Let's talk to Mr. Sun, okay?
Don't move!
Who dares come closer?
I'll stab him if you do!
Get back!
Qiang!
Back off!
Don't be rash, Qiang!
I'm walking.
I didn't...
Stay back!
Think of your wife and kids!
Qiang!
Wang Ping.
Wenjing,
why are you here?
What happened?
We got a report.
They said...
Protect the scene.
He walked me from
downstairs to the stairwell across.
Just like this,
we backed up the whole way.
He had me by the neck
and held scissors to my throat.
Once we got here,
he didn't allow anyone to come over
but stand there.
When we got here,
he pushed me away.
He muttered to himself,
and then jumped.
I didn't even touch him.
I really didn't push him.
He jumped on his own.
Wu and the others saw it.
Yes.
He jumped on his own.
Before he jumped,
what was he muttering about?
He said something like,
"I'm sorry to my wife and kids,"
and "I can't go on living like this."
He said these words.
Do you guys know
if he had any recent changes
in his life or work?
Changes?
He made two mistakes at work this month.
His entire salary was deducted.
But one month's salary isn't much.
It's not worth jumping over.
Ken.
Relax, don't be so nervous.
There are so many witnesses here.
You won't be wrongly accused.
I want to relax
but my...
My legs are still jelly.
It's okay. Don't be scared.
I'm just asking routine questions.
Think again.
Was there anything abnormal
about him lately?
Nothing abnormal.
He's a gentle person.
I don't know
why he suddenly went mad today.
I don't know if this counts.
The moment he pushed me away just now,
he whispered,
"Sorry, Ken."
He said it very calmly.
Just one sentence?
Yes.
Write that down.
Alright, we're done here.
Who is the factory director?
Anyway, if there's any news later,
please contact us.
Let's check the surveillance footage.
I'm leaving, bro.
Qiang.
What happened to you?
Master Liu.
Liu Qiang
is a veteran here.
His work used to be fine.
But this month,
he made two basic mistakes,
causing significant losses to the factory.
Since our factory
has always
had a people-oriented philosophy,
and he's a veteran,
we only symbolically docked his pay.
We didn't punish him severely.
We asked him to get a checkup,
but he refused.
Stop banging on the door.
Stop banging!
Quiet!
I'm hungry.
I know you're hungry. Sit down.
Sit down.
I bought groceries.
We'll have dinner soon.
Jiajia.
Wake up.
It's time to eat.
Look at the time.
Why are you still sleeping?
Aren't you going to sleep tonight?
Wake up.
Jiajia.
Jia.
I'm calling you.
I'm hungry.
I know. Sit down.
Sit down.
Kidney function should be maintained
to reduce the impact of uremia on
lung tissue.
Let's get her admitted first.
We'll use antibiotics
and nebulizer treatment
to see if we can
get the condition under control.
I'm counting on you, sir.
Don't worry.
Uremia complicated by lung infection
is a fairly common complication.
We have extensive experience treating it.
Jiajia's condition isn't too serious.
Go pay the fees.
Director, there's something else
I'd like to discuss.
She was supposed to
have the surgery last time.
But since
there was no kidney source,
she didn't have the surgery.
Can the cost of
hospitalization and treatment this time
be deducted from
the surgery fee I prepaid?
If it's not enough,
I'll
make up the difference.
These are two separate things.
The money you paid last time
has nothing to do with this.
Okay. I see.
How about this?
Go apply for a refund of the surgery fee.
The application takes a long time.
I will tell you the truth.
I don't have enough money now.
Don't go to the billing counter.
Go straight to the Accounting Department.
I'll call them
and explain your situation in detail.
They should be able to accommodate you.
Okay, okay.
Thank you, Director.
Go ahead.
69.
Have you done these questions before?
No.
Then how did your score go up again?
You didn't cheat, did you?
It's a mock exam for
the postgraduate entrance examination.
I did it for myself.
Is there any point in cheating?
I told you before that
what really matters
is finding the right method.
I'm on the right track now,
and I have endless energy.
What method?
I can't tell you.
We're not even applying to
the same school.
Do you really need to guard against me?
I'm not guarding against you.
I'm afraid you won't be able to
control yourself.
What do you mean?
I can only spare you three.
What's this?
I got these through a special channel.
To be honest,
they contain stimulants.
But you must control the dosage
because it's addictive.
Take at most one a day.
Stimulants?
Give them back if you don't want them.
We're classmates.
I don't want to harm you.
Taking too many isn't good.
Once your scores improve,
after two months at most,
you must quit.
And only those with
very strong willpower
can quit.
I've been taking the postgraduate exam
for three years.
I kept trying despite repeated failures.
Who has stronger willpower than me?
Isn't this just ordinary coffee candy?
Keep it in your mouth.
Wait until it melts,
and you'll understand.
Three for 300 yuan.
Pay me.
I have to pay?
Duh.
Give me a discount?
One pill a day.
You'll spend 3,000 yuan a month,
and only 6,000 yuan for two months.
It can help you
get into your dream college.
Is that expensive?
You're back.
Yes.
What are you smiling about?
Dinner is ready.
When we were messaging today,
an old colleague at my company...
I've been studying really well lately.
I'll definitely get an offer next year.
Really?
I've never seen you this confident.
By the way,
what were you saying just now?
What happened at your company?
Nothing.
As long as we get over
this hurdle smoothly,
life for the two of us
will definitely get better and better,
right?
Stop grinning like an idiot.
Wash your hands.
Sis.
Thanks for everything.
How much is this milk tea?
260 yuan.
What about the candy?
50 yuan a piece.
What a rip-off.
How many grams of drugs
are there in this candy?
About 100 micrograms.
One gram sells for 500,000 yuan.
What's the raw material cost?
Over 3,300 yuan.
That day at Black Forest,
how many did you want?
450 grams.
That's over 100 million yuan.
What good is all that money?
The contact got caught.
The police must have got the goods.
I followed Hu Wenjing that day.
I heard their words that
the suspect died
but the drugs weren't found.
Why didn't you tell me
this important information?
You didn't ask.
Forget it.
If the police can't even find it,
how are we supposed to?
I used a backup account
to buy some things online.
The address and phone number are fake.
It hasn't arrived yet.
When it arrives,
go pick it up for me.
I need to see Daquan as soon as possible.
Can I try this?
Sure.
Any side effects?
You'll die.
You must be joking.
So many people have drunk it.
Are they all dead?
Not if you don't overdose
in the short term.
But this hallucinogen is terrifying.
Different people
have different reactions.
At first, it brings
euphoria and confidence,
and even hallucinations.
Once you're addicted,
you'll suffer insomnia,
anorexia,
and weight loss.
It will make you lose your judgment,
change your brain structure,
distort your perception,
and ruin your personality
until you truly believe that
it's a good thing
and can never quit it.
In the end,
you'll suffocate,
go mad,
become depressed,
and have cardiac arrest.
Anyway,
I never take it.
If you don't believe me,
you can try it.
Liu Qiang committed suicide?
What...
How is that possible?
Look at the time.
Why are you still making noise?
Go to bed, now.
Liu Qiang committed suicide?
Is that true?
Yes.
When was the last time you saw him?
I...
I texted him a couple of days ago
about your blind date with his nephew.
I mean meeting in person.
Meeting him?
I haven't seen him for over a month.
When you last met him,
did you notice anything abnormal?
Nothing abnormal.
Before,
I used to ask him to go to
the foot massage parlor.
But the last few times I asked,
he didn't come out.
When you last saw him,
did you
notice any injuries on him,
or maybe needle marks?
You didn't pay attention to that, right?
I didn't pay attention to that.
I think there weren't any injuries.
Are your questions
related to Liu Qiang's death?
No, just curious.
I remembered you knew him,
so I'm just checking.
My god.
By the way, Dad.
It's not safe around here lately.
Don't eat anything when you're out.
If you need food or drinks,
go to big supermarkets.
If you're really not sure,
bring it back for me to check.
I can protect you now.
If anything happens, you must tell me.
Don't worry.
I know
what I shouldn't do.
That's right.
Don't leave.
You have to remember that
you have parents and kids
who are all waiting for you to come back.
I know.
Know your limits on your missions.
Don't push yourself so hard.
Whether you catch the criminal or not
isn't that important to us.
If you don't catch criminals this time,
you'll have the chance next time.
But do you know what matters most?
We all want you to come home safe,
my girl.
I see.
I know what I'm doing.
Don't worry.
Finish washing up and go to sleep.
Remember that.
Okay.
I'm going for a smoke.
Going for a smoke?
Not allowed in the ward.
In the corridor?
Okay.
Ma'am?
Please help keep an eye on my child
for a while.
Okay. Go ahead.
Hungry.
Xiaoyu is hungry.
I want to eat.
I'm hungry.
One, two, three, four, five.
Five!
I counted to five!
Jiajia.
I've been watching you two for a while.
Smoking isn't allowed in the hospital.
Okay.
Actually, I quit smoking years ago.
How old is your son?
Not yet ten.
How old is your daughter?
About the same.
She's nine.
What does she have?
Uremia
with a secondary lung infection.
Once the pneumonia is cured,
she just needs a kidney transplant
for the uremia, right?
Yes.
But
we need a donor kidney.
We're currently waiting for a match.
Why don't you and your wife have a try?
Direct relatives are usually good matches.
My wife passed away.
I have chronic glomerulonephritis.
I'll end up with uremia
sooner or later too.
What about your son?
What does he have?
Congenital heart disease.
He caught a cold a couple of days ago,
and we had to rush him to the ER.
Will surgery work?
The doctor said the cold caused
a severe lung infection.
He's not strong enough
for surgery right now.
They implied a few days ago
that my son
might die this time.
He'll recover slowly.
Yeah.
I probably shouldn't say this,
but sometimes I think
it might be better if he just passed away,
which can end his suffering.
Treating him these past two years
has wiped out our savings
and left us deep in debt.
They say there are no filial sons
at the bedside of the long-term sick.
Look at these two kids.
Both have lung infections.
Both are complications.
And they're in the same ward.
It's fate.
Yes.
If anything happens,
let's look out for each other.
Definitely.
Hello.
Is that Cheng Ken?
Yes.
I'm from the Neighborhood Committee.
Someone's been screaming
in your apartment.
Is a child trapped in the bathroom?
We are going to pry the door open.
No, no, no.
Don't pry it open.
That's my family.
Don't freak her out.
I'll be right back.
Bro, please keep an eye on
the child for me.
I have an emergency at home.
Okay, okay.
Don't worry.
Okay.
Letting her out.
It's troublesome.
Mrs. Wang,
Mrs. Zhang, I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Sorry for coming back late.
Cheng Ken.
Why is there a mental patient
living in your house?
It's my niece.
She just moved here.
I have to take care of her for a while.
Sorry.
Will
she come out and hurt others?
No, she won't.
She is young.
Only fifteen years old.
She's usually quiet.
I always kept a close watch on her.
I don't know what happened today.
I took Jiajia to the hospital just now.
It was urgent.
She might be hungry.
Sorry.
It won't happen again.
Sorry for the disturbance.
Please go home.
Okay. Let's go.
Sorry.
Stop knocking.
What are you screaming for?
Why are you screaming?
I'm hungry.
Stop screaming.
Shut up!
Scream again, and you will get no food!
I want meat.
Eat this first.
It's yummy.
Sit.
Sit down.
I'll get you some meat.
Do you like it?
Is it good?
You're back.
How is she?
Everything's fine.
Dr. Yang came by earlier.
He's my classmate.
He works here.
It's good to know people in the hospital.
Dr. Yang said
he had checked on Jiajia.
Her fever has gone down.
She's fine. Don't worry.
Okay.
Thank you.
No problem.
What should I call you?
My surname is Cheng.
Cheng Ken.
Cheng means a bright future.
Ken means diligence.
My surname is Xue.
Just call me Old Xue.
Mr. Xue.
Thanks.
Take a break.
Okay.
Dad.
Where have you been?
Xiaoyu is at home.
She was hungry.
So I got her something to eat.
It's okay. I'm not leaving.
I'll stay here with you.
Alright.
Get some sleep.
Her lungs are recovering fast.
She can be discharged
after this morning's IV drip.
Take the child home.
Come back if anything happens.
That way,
it can lighten your burden.
Director, I still want to ask about
the kidney transplant.
Roughly when
will it be our turn?
Haven't I explained this to you?
It's not up to the hospital.
I can't say for sure either.
I understand that.
But please understand me.
I don't want to keep bothering you.
But just waiting like this is torture.
I'm also afraid
that some complications might pop up.
Mentally
and financially,
I can't take it anymore.
But without a donated kidney,
I can't speed things up.
Didn't I tell you that
as long as there's a suitable kidney,
scheduling the surgery is easy?
Alright, relax.
Jiajia is already
at the top of our hospital's list.
Many patients
aren't even physically fit for surgery.
I understand.
Mrs. Xue.
You haven't had breakfast, right?
I bought some for you.
I already had breakfast.
No.
We can't accept this.
No, no.
Let me express my gratitude.
Mr. Xue helped me a lot.
It's just a small token.
Thank you.
How are things lately?
Let's check your blood pressure.
Same as always.
It takes time.
You have to take it slow.
Can I see his medical record?
Since Jiajia also has a lung infection,
I want to see what meds he's on.
Here you are.
All of these are his records.
Yeah.
So many medicines.
Yes.
But the two kids' conditions
are definitely different.
Yes.
Go wash up quickly.
It's not crowded now.
Mr. Xue.
Look,
Jiajia's father brought us breakfast.
Thanks.
It's okay.
It's just something simple.
Haven't you left yet?
What are you doing?
Jiajia is amazing.
You are going to leave here.
That's the way.
Go home when you're well.
No need to stay in the hospital
if you're not sick,
right?
I really envy you.
He'll get better in time.
Yes.
My boy will recover soon,
right?
By the way,
I'm going to get some food.
Can you keep an eye on my son for me?
Do you have time?
Yes. We're not leaving yet.
The Director wants to talk to me.
Okay, okay.
I'll come back quickly.
It's fine, no rush.
Jiang.
I come for dialysis every week.
I'll bring you something fun next week.
I have picture books at home.
You can use colored pens
to color the images in picture books.
Do you know how to play?
What is Huarong Path?
I'm not very good at it.
Hello, Uncle Yang.
Jiajia,
eat light meals when you get back.
Okay.
Light meals.
How are you feeling today, handsome?
Put your shoes on.
Come on.
I'm going to draw some blood
for a checkup.
Come here.
Are you scared of blood draws, Jiang?
Actually, a little bit.
A little bit, huh?
Xiaoyu.
What is Xiaoyu doing?
Dad bought me a new puzzle.
Let's put it together.
I will give it to Jiang when it's done.
Look.
This is a blueprint.
Thanks, Xiaoyu.
What's up?
Nie has already
finished Liu Qiang's autopsy report.
It's just as we guessed.
He did take hallucinogens.
And it's a new state-controlled substance.
Didn't the City Bureau say
what Ding Lai bought is
the new drug from the foreign lab?
Now everything matches up.
Okay.
Listen.
Don't report to Director Dai.
Let's go to Liu Qiang's home again
tomorrow
to see if we can find any other clues.
I just finished reporting to Director Dai.
Why are you so quick to talk?
Well,
Director Dai takes this case
very seriously.
He specifically told me
to notify him immediately
if there were any results.
Besides,
why don't you want me to tell him?
When Director Dai is informed,
he'll report it to the City Bureau.
Will we still get to keep this case then?
I think
sometimes we should
stick to the rules.
You're so timid.
What kind of cop are you?
You're not even as brave as my two sons.
Hang up now.
Don't waste my battery.
[Nuanfeng County Public Security
Bureau Committee]
Come on. Right here.
Stop what you're doing, everyone.
Let me introduce you.
This is Officer Jin Longzheng
from the Municipal Narcotics Unit.
Qin,
you two know each other, right?
You've worked on missions together.
That is Tan Jie,
Wang Guangming,
Li and Sun.
The City Bureau
takes this case very seriously.
They hope that through Liu Qiang's case,
we can uncover the drug dens in Nuanhai
and wipe them out in one go.
Then, for this case,
we're counting on you.
I hope that while ensuring your safety,
you can solve the case
as soon as possible.
Just in time.
Are you looking for me, Director Dai?
Let me introduce.
This is Officer Jin Longzheng
from the Municipal Narcotics Unit.
To solve the case quickly,
I specially allocated
other police forces to assist you.
This is Hu Wenjing from
our county Criminal Investigation Team.
She's a veteran detective.
Hope we can have great collaboration.
Come on.
Welcome.
I reviewed Liu Qiang's case.
I want to confirm a few things
and plan to visit his home now.
Okay.
Alright.
We'll go there right now.
Did you hear that?
Qin said
we'll go there right now.
You go and assist them,
showing them the way.
After all, no one is
more familiar with every area
of our county than you,
right?
Liu Qiang lived in Room 201, Unit 2.
Let's go.
Room 201, right?
Yes.
You don't need to come with us.
Why?
This is a narcotics case.
We won't trouble you.
Let me ask you.
You know nothing at all
about your husband Liu Qiang's drug use?
Stop asking.
I don't know anything.
She said
she doesn't know anything.
So you know something about that?
Yes.
Then tell me.
My uncle
committed suicide, right?
How did he become a suspect?
Who did he hurt?
Tell me.
Listen to me.
I am currently questioning
the suspect's family
on site in accordance with the law.
Do not interfere with our investigation.
And you are not
Liu Qiang's immediate family.
I'm asking you to
leave the inquiry scene now,
okay?
This is my uncle's house.
Why should I leave?
Leave.
I'll say it one more time.
I'm asking you to
leave the inquiry scene now.
If you don't follow my order,
I will take coercive measures against you.
Understood?
Coercive measures?
I... I'm telling you.
I doubt your identity.
I'm telling you.
Give me your badge number.
I'll call 110
to verify it.
I have shown you
my ID
and search warrant, haven't I?
Fake.
Couldn't they be fake?
There are so many scammers
and fraudsters nowadays.
You look scruffy.
You don't look like a good person.
I'm telling you.
You're just making trouble.
Jin.
Come here.
What are you doing?
Take him outside.
You want to hit me, right?
Come on.
Don't touch me.
Don't touch me!
What's wrong?
Yang Xinyu, come out for a second.
Let me talk to you.
This is the police.
Don't get excited. Just calm down.
My uncle committed suicide.
You came to search as soon as he died.
Can my aunt handle this?
Besides, if the neighbors see this,
they'll think my uncle did something
horrible and unforgivable.
How can my aunt live here?
I understand.
But your uncle used drugs.
It's not a small matter.
We know
what kind of person your uncle was.
Like my dad,
he was just an ordinary worker.
So who pushed him down this path?
Don't we need to find that out?
Only then can we
give your aunt an explanation.
I get that.
The point is that
this police officer has a bad attitude.
He was just following procedure.
Who knows
whether he just used drugs himself,
or he also sold drugs?
We can't say for sure yet.
Selling drugs?
Could he do that?
No way.
Is that even possible?
Whether it's possible or not,
we have to investigate thoroughly
to clear his name.
Right?
Think it over carefully.
See if you can remember
any valuable information
and tell us.
It's better for everyone
if we solve this case soon.
My uncle
didn't drink.
But recently,
he went to a bar
frequently.
What bar?
[Next Episode Preview]