[English subtitles are available]
[Lost in the Kunlun Mountains]
[Episode 5]
Ms. Fengling.
Hello, Yunqi.
We met in a hurry yesterday.
We didn't have chance to say hello.
So I invited you to come here
to have a chat.
I've ordered.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I'm talking about the thing happened last night.
It's over.
Don't mention it again.
You studied medicine in England?
Yes.
Sir, your coffee.
That's a good job.
I learned world history in America.
But I couldn't make any contributions when I came back.
How long
have you been back?
I just came back.
I know a few friends who're doctors of Western medicine.
Do you want to meet them?
Not for now.
I want to finish these chores
before handling work.
I can understand.
You...
You don't talk much.
No.
I just have many questions.
Do you think
we are friends now?
No.
The person who saved you can't be your friend either?
I can't say it.
It's complicated.
Okay.
I'll try to understand.
When you think we're friends,
I'll tell you everything.
I'll also give you
what you want.
This is my family's phone number.
[Chu Fengling]
I have a hospital event the day after tomorrow.
If you're willing to come with me,
you can call me.
You can have dinner at my place that night.
That's all for today.
The coffee here is authentic.
Don't you want to try it?
I only drink tea.
[STEPHEN]
Yunqi, my car is over there.
Do you need a ride?
[STEPHEN]
No, thanks.
-Bye. -Bye.
[STEPHEN]
Where did you go?
I was confined by my master.
How did you escape?
Who was that pretty girl?
Her name is Chu Fengling.
She saved me.
Is it sweet?
What are you holding?
The phone number of Luo's Mansion.
What is a phone?
A phone
is a phone.
I'll show it to you some other day.
Excuse me.
They are students.
What they're holding
are not weapons, right?
It's a western musical instrument, a violin.
You're smart. You know everything.
If you stay in Shanghai for a year,
you'll know everything.
People in Mound-digging don't talk about this.
What do people in Mound-digging talk about?
Weapons, martial arts sect, farming,
Master and seniors.
We also talked about business before.
Master runs business in many places.
But I don't like business.
Master didn't force me.
You are all orphans.
Yes. Master brought us back.
The first time I knew
there was a place like home in the world
was when I went to your home when I was a child.
My mother was gone at that time.
That wasn't home.
Why not?
It was quiet and comfortable.
You didn't worry about making mistakes.
Your father was solicitous.
That was great.
I didn't want my master to pick me up.
I wanted to stay at your home forever.
Did your master treat you badly?
No. My master is nice to me.
Yunqi, let's go over there.
Waixiangua Street.
They're at Lane Baiye now.
We should go back.
What's the rush?
It's rare to come out for a walk.
I'll show you something fun later.
Not that one.
Don't push me.
They're at Little East Gate.
They went back to Waixiangua Street.
Ask our people to leave.
How about...
Go now.
Yes, sir.
Look what this is.
I can see it.
You can see it?
This is so uncomfortable.
Let me tell you.
Our juniors' tracking ability
needs to be improved.
They'll be discovered if they stay so close.
How did you
help our master teach them?
No matter how well they performed,
they would still be discovered by you.
I just let them practice.
You're not confined?
Master asked me
to make amends.
What do you mean?
Did he ask you to take me back?
He was afraid something would happen to you,
so he asked me to help you at the critical moment.
Master is so nice.
You're nice too.
Of course.
All right.
I think there won't be any critical moments.
Young Master Ding has regained his freedom.
I'm going to report.
No.
Xuewen.
Please tell Master
I'll go back and be punished
when I get the dragon bone back.
Where will you go back?
Mound-digging.
You two are engaged.
From now on, you have to travel the martial artists community together.
Why are you going back to Mound-digging?
What?
Don't mention it.
What do you mean?
You want to be a matrilocal son-in-law?
No way.
That's impossible.
Think about it.
You two are always together.
What would other juniors and seniors think?
I'll talk to your master.
No need.
What?
Oh no.
What's wrong?
[Wealth Grain Shop]
[Taiyi Private Bank]
Let's go.
How could Luo Yunsong let you go?
I was saved.
Who saved you?
His family member.
Luo Yunsong caught you.
Then his family member released you.
Do you get along with his family member?
It's a long story.
Uncle, I'm here today
to talk about my engagement to Wu Shuang.
Come here.
Sit down.
This matter
shouldn't be discussed by you.
Well...
You're a young man of a new era.
Let's not talk about the rules.
Did you get the dragon bone back?
No, I didn't.
I didn't know the dragon bone could be
taken as the bride-price.
So this is a misunderstanding.
I want to explain it to you.
Misunderstanding?
What misunderstanding is it?
Marriages are serious.
Of course.
Yunqi.
You
are engaged abroad?
No.
No, then...
Wu Shuang's
appearance, personality
and martial arts
are the best.
Why she wasn't worthy of you?
That's not what I meant.
Give me a reason.
The reason is
I won't take over as Heaven Official.
You won't take over as Heaven Official?
I hope you can understand.
I don't understand.
I don't want to be the Heaven Official.
Uncle,
I don't want to join the Penta-sect either.
You know
the situation of the Penta-sect.
What your father did
can't let him stay in the martial artists community
and Penta-sect.
So,
for the dignity of the Ding family,
the responsibility of the Penta-sect
is on you now.
No matter for what reason,
you have to take over as Heaven Official.
You've known my father for so many years.
I believe you know my father well.
He's not a traitor.
You...
How long has it been since you last saw your father?
Six years.
It's possible for him to betray us six times
during the six years.
Yunqi.
You're too young.
You don't know people well.
Uncle,
my father even sacrificed my mother
for the sake of the Penta-sect.
I don't believe there's anyone who're more loyal than my father.
How can you explain what happened in the Kunlun Mountains?
The Kunlun Mountains
is the foundation of the Penta-sect.
It doesn't belong to the Ding family.
Your father has no right to give it to others.
When I find my father,
the truth will be revealed.
The Penta-sect has a thousand years of history.
It's a sect with foundation.
It can't be destroyed
by our generation.
Yes.
It can't be destroyed by you.
It can be destroyed by me.
There are many out-dated rules in the Penta-sect.
They're not worth being kept.
What did you say?
I said I want to disband the Penta-sect.
In this era,
there is no need for the Penta-sect
to exist.
Ding Yunqi!
Okay.
Yunqi.
If you take over as Heaven Official,
I'll promise you two things.
First,
I'll help you get the dragon bone back
and find your father.
Second,
when I find your father,
I won't kill him.
I'll only punish him.
I'll confine him in Mound-digging Region
for the rest of his life.
For the future of the Penta-sect,
I'll keep my promise.
Uncle,
I've told you many times.
My father is still alive.
He's the Heaven Official. I'm not the Heaven Official.
I don't want to be the Heaven Official.
Let me ask you again.
Are you going to take over as Heaven Official or not?
No.
Fine.
If so,
hand over dragon bones
and Dragon sceptres.
They belong to the Penta-sect,
not yours.
They're my father's belongings.
I have to keep them
before I find him.
You won't hand them over?
No.
Go and persuade him.
I can't
persuade both of them.
What should we do if they fight?
We can't stop Ding Yunqi.
Xuewen, I'm leaving.
If Master found me, I couldn't escape.
You can't run.
Ding Yunqi just said
your engagement is a misunderstanding.
I know what to do.
I'm leaving.
Don't go.
You rejected the engagement to Wu Shuang
and refused to be the Heaven Official
and hand over the things of the Penta-sect.
Ding Yunqi.
What do you want?
Do you take here as a place you can go freely?
Do you think no one in the Penta-sect can handle you?
Guys,
are you ready to set up a formation?
You don't have to die.
That day at the dock,
I let you off.
Do you really think you won?
It was a narrow escape.
If I won today,
Uncle,
would you disband the Penta-sect?
Of course not.
Look.
No matter who won,
we couldn't change our minds.
So,
you can't solve everything with force.
It can only solve temporary problems at most.
Since I came back to Shanghai,
I've never stopped fighting.
I'm tired.
Don't you want to find your father earlier?
You want to kill or confine him.
But I want to find him
and help him clear his name.
I don't need the kiss of death.
Uncle.
See you.
♫Close your eyes to realize♫
♫Wind and rain are actually gifts♫
♫The sky cleared with the help of light♫
♫It finally put together♫
♫A different rainbow puzzle♫
♫We promised♫
♫To be happy♫
♫I'll protect you♫
♫Unrestrained♫
♫We promised even if I had to give my all♫
♫I would♫
♫Go with you♫
You're back.
Wash your hands.
I don't know where San Jin is.
We really need someone to cook at home.
Where is the oil?
When will San Jin come back?
He left.
What do you mean?
Where did he go?
Luo Yunsong
said my father killed three of his family members.
He wanted my whole family to pay with our lives.
I was afraid he would count San Jin.
No way.
It's not easy for San Jin to survive.
I asked Brother to send him out of this city
and let him live a good life.
Did your father really kill three of Luo Yunsong's family members?
Do you believe it?
No, I don't.
When did you come back?
How did you win
the formation set up by my juniors?
We didn't fight.
I won the argument.
You won the argument?
No.
Ding Yunqi,
you won the argument?
You can win a fight, but you must lose an argument.
My master always says right.
Yes. Your master is always right.
Then why did you come to the bell tower
instead of listening to him?
You...
I...
You questioned me?
Remember, my master is always right.
Here.
Be careful.
Let's go.
Master.
How is it going inside?
The work inside went well.
And the location is very accurate. We didn't make a detour.
We took all valuable things.
Things with less value were not moved.
Get to the point.
Master.
It was found in the southeast corner of the tomb.
Also,
there was a clear spiral knife pattern in the tomb.
It should be...
Ghoul?
Ghoul has been changed to escort agency.
They haven't gone down to tombs for decades.
Why did they suddenly take action?
Look at the feng shui and the tomb.
It's not a high official.
There might not be
rare treasures inside.
He came all the way to Shanghai.
He still had time
to come here.
Master.
Sun Sanxuan broke the Xunfeng Formation
and ran away with Ding Yunqi's help.
I think
we should tell Luo Yunsong about this.
Then Hua Xingchen and Xiao Liuzi
can come back.
We can also kill Sun Sanxuan.
What are you talking about?
It's a legal clean-up.
Sun Sanxuan is a traitor.
But if you let him
become a scapegoat
and told the government about it,
what would be the difference
between you and Luo Yunsong?
Don't forget your origin.
You can't forget justice
because of personal grudges.
-Yes. -Yes, Master.
It's almost done. Let's eat.
Where are you going?
The last dish is ready.
Come on. Sit down.
It's time to eat.
Look.
They're good in color, aroma and taste.
This is my first time cooking.
You must be honored.
Here.
This
is your first time cooking?
So talented.
Try it.
Gosh.
I'm so talented.
The color looks light.
Isn't it good?
Yes.
Don't you have a strong taste?
So I added a lot of soy sauce.
Come on. Try the meat.
How is it?
Is it delicious and tender?
It's delicious.
Brother.
Is there Tush today?
What's wrong?
Are you still mad at me?
Didn't we make it clear?
Brother.
Show me your Certificate of Appointment given by Her Ladyship.
You knew it?
[Certificate of Appointment]
I appoint Chu Fengling
as a special member of the Secret Investigation Team of the Kunlun Mountains.
People in the Black Feather Team are members of the investigation team.
Officials at all levels should actively cooperate.
She can deploy the police when necessary.
Not bad.
Now you're your brother's superior.
Brother.
You didn't want to leave this morning
because you were waiting for it, right?
No.
I didn't expect
Her Ladyship would suddenly appoint me to this position.
Brother,
you don't believe me?
We have the same goal.
Let's work together.
We have different goals.
Your target is the Kunlun Mountains.
My target is
Ding Yuanshan.
Right.
Find Ding Yuanshan or Ding Yunqi
and then open the Kunlun Mountains.
No.
What's wrong?
Everything is wrong.
You are now
a special member of the Special Investigation Team of the Kunlun Mountains.
The Black Feather Team is under your control.
Why do you think it's right?
I've thought about it.
The Black Feather Team was incorporated
in a public institution.
Her Ladyship also promised to give the most advanced weapons
to the Black Feather Team.
Brother, I don't want the Black Feather Team.
That's your team.
I just wanted to take this opportunity
to give the Black Feather Team an identity.
I meant well.
I felt wronged.
[Yun Song.]
[The Kunlun Mountains is the wealth of the Kuomintang. No matter what your plan is, let me remind you.]
[You should focus on the interests of the Kuomintang. I'll leave this matter to Fengling. The Black Feather Team will be deployed by Fengling for the time being.]
[I'll also appoint Fengling as a secret investigator of the Kunlun Mountains. Please cooperate. Chen Yu.]
It's just a suggestion.
You are too sensitive.
Her Ladyship knows you're catching Ding Yuanshan,
so she wants us
to work together.
Fengling.
I
really don't want you to go into politics.
I want. I like it.
What should I do?
Brother,
I planned to discuss it with you
when I come back tonight.
I didn't expect Her Ladyship took action so fast.
She gave me the Certificate of Appointment as soon as we met.
Brother.
Don't be angry.
Does it hurt a lot?
Do you want to spit it out?
There are no doctors nearby.
What should we do?
Bring me the medicine box.
Right. I forgot you're a doctor.
Which one?
It's hot.
Seriously.
You shouldn't eat so much even if they were delicious.
Just stop here.
Okay.
[Zhu's Wonton]
Young Master, I'm back.
Ms. Wu Shuang.
You're back.
Young Master.
What...
What happened?
He's not feeling well.
Why?
Stomachache. He just took some medicine.
What did you have for dinner?
Dinner?
There's something left over there. I cooked dinner.
Do you want some? Look.
You let Young Master eat these tonight?
He ate a lot. He said they were delicious.
You cooked them?
Yes.
You haven't eaten, have you? I'll heat them up for you.
Stop!
You poisoned Young Master.
Do you know it?
Poison?
How can they be poisonous?
Nonsense! How can I be fine after eating them?
Don't you know Young Master is allergic to mushrooms?
Leave here.
This...
-How could they be poisonous? -Leave here.
They can't be poisonous.
Get out!
Stop!
Go back.
I want to get him a glass of water.
Don't come here again.
Is it really because of my food?
Of course.
As long as I left home,
you almost killed Young Master.
Can you live without me?
No. We need you.
Listen.
Don't cross this line again.
Don't touch the pots and pans again.
I won't touch them. I promise I won't touch them.
I'll listen to you.
Mother.
Young Master.
Yunqi.
Mother.
Yunqi, are you okay?
Young Master.
Yunqi.
Yunqi, wake up.
Young Master.
Why are you back?
I felt uneasy when I wasn't here.
Young Master, let me get you some water.
Where is it hidden?
Open your mouth.
Auntie Hei.
Where do you think my brother hid it?
Maybe
he really gave it to experts.
That's impossible. Look for it.
Who is it?
Jiutian.
You recognized me
by my butt?
What are you doing at Brother's room
at this time?
What are you doing here?
I...
I... I'm doing what you're doing.
We have the same goal.
Our goals are different.
The thing I'm looking for
is different
from what you're looking for.
What do you mean?
OK.
Go ahead. I'm done.
I'll go to the police station
and have some tea with Brother.
Brother,
if my brother knew about this,
he wouldn't do anything to me.
But if he knew
your matter,
you would be in big trouble.
What matter is it?
The ancient tomb of the Qing Dynasty.
What? What did you say?
I don't understand.
It's out. Here.
Take it.
I won't drink tea.
I couldn't sleep if I drank too much.
I need to find something to eat.
Go on with your work.
My hand is swollen.
My lady, should we continue looking for it?
Brother has searched everywhere.
It's not here.
Give my comb back to me.
What comb is it?
It's hanging on your neck.
I saw it.
Give it back to me.
It's mine.
It's yours?
Where did you get it?
I won't tell you.
Give it back to me.
[Taiyi Private Bank]
Sect Leader Zhou.
Your disciples have been questioned.
They have nothing to do with the case of the tomb of the Qing Dynasty.
I sent them back for you today.
You arrested them and released them
for no reason.
Isn't there any explanation?
We only arrest people.
We release some of them occasionally.
But it's our first time
sending people back.
If you want any explanations,
you can only talk to our director.
Okay.
We have plenty of time.
Tell your director
that he's on my mind.
OK.
I will tell him.
Thank you. See you.
Master.
I didn't embarrass you.
Xiao Liuzi couldn't stand it.
He cried.
Does it still hurt?
Master.
I embarrassed you.
I failed to protect you.
Fine.
I've
tried
all the methods.
They're useless.
I still can't find my father.
I don't have a clue now.
The dragon bone is still in Luo Yunsong's hands.
It's really hard.
Who was the masked man
that saved you at the dock that day?
I don't know.
Then why did Chu Fengling save you?
[Feng]
Chu Fengling?
Since she saved you,
why didn't she return the dragon bone?