[English subtitles are available]
[Lost in the Kunlun Mountains]
[Episode 36]
It's all settled.
Where's Wu Shuang? Why didn't she come back together?
Shijiu heard that he was leaving the cave
and cried her tears out.
Wu Shuang is with her
and will come back later.
Brother, is everything going well over there?
Yes.
Black Feather and ghouls
are getting ready.
They will pick up the Yu family tomorrow morning.
As you said, they'll send them out of the city.
With the ghouls and Black Feather Team,
I'm relieved.
You are hiding something from me.
What is it?
San Jin is gone.
Sanxuan go send Fingling and Biao off.
Black Feather Team and ghouls
go send the Yu family off.
That sounds right.
But...
No.
Tell me.
What are you hiding from me?
Brother.
Are you afraid that I'll run away too?
You will only send me and Wu Shuang away
and guard here by yourself.
Ding Yunqi.
Is that what you think?
You're fighting alone here,
risking your life for justice.
I'm telling you, no.
No way.
Zhou Qiuhai killed my father.
I must kill him myself.
Brother, you misunderstood me.
That's the only way.
Because I can't think of it.
Stop beating around the bush.
Tell me if you have a plan.
I've sent a message to Zhou Qiuhai and Her Ladyship.
Three days later,
I will open the Kunlun Mountains.
Because the tide rises in three days.
The tide will flood Dulong Cave again.
Even if Her Ladyship knows where the cave is,
she can't find the way in.
In this way, we can
work together against Zhou Qiuhai.
But there's always what-ifs.
So I asked Shiqi to put a wooden boat
at the entrance.
If we can go together,
that's the best.
But if the plan changes,
you must promise me
to escort Wu Shuang out safely.
[Chinese Post Office]
[Reply]
To Shanghai Shen Journal.
Where are you going?
Can you find the way back?
I'll go back to Young Master even if I can't.
What am I now?
I am a traitor.
You don’t listen to your Young Master?
He didn't stop me from going back.
You didn't allow me to go back
I have to cook for Young Master.
Yunqi wrote this. See for yourself.
Your Young Master
gave the Soul Pursuit Order
and the accusations against Her Ladyship
to you.
If something went wrong with the Soul Pursuit Order,
all his efforts
would be wasted.
Do you really think
your cooking is delicious?
I...
San Jin.
You're holding the life of the Penta-sect.
If you really want to help Yunqi,
do what he told you,
That's a great help to Yunqi.
Let's go.
We should go to the next stop.
We don't know how are
Young Master, Wu Shuang,
Luo and Brother San.
They...
Heaven helps the lucky ones.
Let's go.
Take your stuff.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Let's set up the formation today.
We don't have to bring so many things tomorrow.
Let's go.
Be careful.
Here.
Master.
Since we know
the entrance to the Kunlun Mountains,
why didn't we go in first
instead of letting them take the lead?
No hurry.
There are countless traps in the Kunlun Mountains.
Let Ding Yunqi open the way for us first.
Those behind, keep up. Don't fall behind.
Keep up.
What's wrong, Shijiu?
Someone is coming.
There are a lot of people.
Army!
Oh no!
It's Her Ladyship's army.
They came early.
Brother Ding and the others are in danger.
You send the Yu family out of the mountain.
We'll help them.
They have guns.
It's us who should go back.
Members of the Yu Family.
Yes.
Come with me.
Yu Shiqi.
Yu Shiqi, you can't leave.
The headquarters is in danger.
We must go back.
No one can stop us.
Yunqi said
your lives are more important than his.
You can only go forward. You can't go back.
Then kill me now
or hide away.
-You can't go. -Go back.
We have to go back to protect the headquarters.
Don't go!
You can't go.
Let's go.
Keep up.
Her Ladyship's army is early.
Master!
Oh no!
If Her Ladyship's army arrives first,
we'll be in trouble.
Hurry up.
-Yes, sir. -Yes.
So
Zhou Qiuhai will be here soon.
Wu Shuang.
Take Brother to the entrance to set the Crescent Moon Formation.
Then here...
Don't worry.
I can handle it myself.
Let's go, Wu Shuang.
If you don't go,
I can't set the formation.
Be careful.
Wu Shuang.
Over there.
Brother.
What is your plan?
I'll tell you later.
Go.
Drink some water.
Take a rest.
Be careful of the trap.
Be careful.
Go ahead. Be careful.
Brother.
Brother!
The Kunlun Mountains!
I finally see you.
Ding Yunqi.
Are you alone?
To deal with you,
only me is enough.
Fight with me?
Do you still want to fight?
Open the door.
Open the door!
Okay.
Open it.
Here.
Is this the Heaven Official's headquarters?
The Heaven Official is the last barrier.
Behind the first Heaven Officer
is the entrance to the Kunlun Mountains.
What are you waiting for?
Come.
Here.
Open it and let me see the treasures.
The Ding family has guarded the Kunlun Mountains for hundreds of years.
Today, I wasn't forced by force to open it.
I did it willingly.
Fine.
You can say whatever you want.
Just open it
and let me see the treasures.
Okay.
Kneel before my father
and ancestors of Penta-sect.
What?
Kneel.
Yes.
Yunqi.
Are you in position
to negotiate with me now?
Are you kneeling or not?
Just for the decency
of the Ding family?
It's not decency,
but dignity.
You don't understand.
Yunqi.
Dignity
is for the winner.
With your current condition,
you'll never able to enjoy it
in your life.
And you also humiliated your Ding Family of hundreds of years of history.
Zhou Qiuhai.
You have no right to talk about dignity with me,
nor to criticize my family.
Fine.
Good.
Yunqi.
Be good.
Okay?
As long as you open the Kunlun Mountains,
I guarantee your ancestral temple will not be destroyed.
I'll grant you the soul of the Ding family
and a place to live.
Don't be too willful, okay?
Yunqi.
If you don't kneel,
I'd rather the souls of the Ding Family
have no places to live
than open the passage for you.
Kill me.
Yunqi.
Stop worrying about decency and dignity, okay?
Kneel.
Yunqi.
Yunqi!
Don't challenge me.
Sir, we found it.
Yes.
Be quick.
Pick up some things
in case it's a waste of time.
Yes.
Let's go.
Keep up.
Kneel.
Okay.
I have been in Penta-sect
for decades.
Today,
this is the last time I worship the Heaven Official.
Kneel.
Bow.
Second bow.
Third bow.
Okay.
Is it open?
I'll take you to the Kunlun Mountains.
This...
Hurry.
What did you do?
You...
Ding Yunqi!
Brother.
Why am I here?
Why did I fall asleep?
Where's Dulong Cave?
The tide is rising
and flooded Dulong Cave.
What?
Then...
What about Yunqi?
♫Toss the coin into the blind box♫
Is Yunqi inside?
♫I won't tell which side is up♫
-Wu Shuang. -Yunqi!
Yunqi. Don't pull me.
-I'm going to find Yunqi. -You can't go.
♫Fear of spoilers will reveal the results♫
-Stop pulling me. -You can't go.
-Yunqi. -Wu Shuang!
You can't go!
♫Fear of being vulnerable♫
Be good.
You all lied to me.
♫Entanglement is the cocoon of confinement♫
Yunqi.
I can't live without Yunqi.
♫Intuition is the direction of courage♫
Why did you lie to me?
Why?
♫Not that I don't miss you♫
I promised Yunqi.
♫But it's time to let go♫
♫Not letting go will cause injury♫
♫Give me the strength to break free from the cocoon♫
♫Together we step towards the horizon for the sunset♫
♫No matter how much wind and sand I endure♫
♫To break the shackles of the net♫
♫Oh♫
I'm here to marry you.
♫I'll just spare a smile♫
I trust you.
I agree to any decision
you make.
You are my
pride.
Father.
I may not be able to protect Ding family's headquarters
or the Kunlun Mountains.
[Her Ladyship is greedy and plotted to possess the Kunlun Mountains. She uses all kinds of tricks to get money and kill people.]
[The treasures of the Kunlun Mountains has collapsed into a mystery.]
Take your medicine on time.
[Wu Shuang Clinic]
[Wu Shuang Clinic for free medical visits]
The ancestral temple of the Ding family
was completely buried at the bottom of the mountain.
I hope all greed and slaughter
can be buried together.
[Save lives and help the injured with dedication]
The Kunlun Mountains is still there.
Just like all our good wishes.
I will still
find it.
Remember to take your medicine on time.
Thank you, doctor.
Take care of yourself.
Okay.
[Wu Shuang Clinic]
Thank you, Dr. Ding.
Are you tired?
Young Master, Madam.
Brother sent a letter.
[Luo Yunsong]
Yunqi.
Wu Shuang.
How are you?
San and I are going to the front line
to fight with the Japanese.
We'll come back to see you when we win.
[Luo Yunsong, August 21, 27th year of the Republic of China]
Be well.