=Flower Sea=
=Episode 5=
Jing'an!
Niannian? Why are you here?
To watch someone catch a cheater.
Catch what?
Um…
Let me treat you to milk tea.
Great!
I'll have snow cap milk tea,
full sugar with bobas,
and extra ice cream.
Welcome!
I'll have snow cap milk tea,
full sugar with bobas
and extra ice cream.
Hello.
Attention, students.
Students.
The city's top high school leaders
have decided
that the monthly exam,
scheduled for the end of the month,
will be a nine-school joint exam.
In other words,
students from nine high schools
will have exams together.
The exam date
has been moved up.
The exam is approaching.
Students,
please prepare it thoroughly.
Study hard,
live up to your youth,
and live up to yourselves.
What? A joint exam? So soon?
This is too sudden.
That's not the point.
I studied sciences.
How do I handle
your liberal arts subjects?
I don't know either.
What do we do now?
Zhu Niannian,
the homeroom teacher asks for you.
Go ahead,
we'll talk later.
You've heard about
the exam being moved up
and changed to a joint test, right?
Your recent performance worries me.
I spoke with your mom earlier.
You promised her
you'd rank in the top 10 this time.
I'm glad you're determined,
but if you need any help
with studies
or anything else,
just tell me.
You'll get the support you need.
Top... 10?
Yeah.
What's wrong?
Didn't you promise this?
Ma'am,
do you really think I can make it?
Niannian,
you're a top student.
I've always had
high expectations for you.
Judging by
your past results,
I believe
if you study seriously,
you can make it.
The key is maintaining the right mindset.
Ma'am,
what if...
I don't...
make the top 10?
Niannian,
I have full confidence in you.
You need to believe in yourself too.
Understand?
Chen Jing'an.
You know,
the joint exam is coming up.
What about it?
Chen Jing'an,
let's make a deal, okay?
What kind of deal?
Well,
could you help me
with this exam?
No.
Why not?
We've worked together
pretty well before.
If I fail this time,
my mom will hunt me down again.
I'm your best buddy.
You wouldn't abandon me, right?
But I really can't help you this time.
Chen Jing'an,
I... I won't copy everything.
Just help me pass.
I truly can't.
Besides, this joint exam is different.
We'll have texts
in separate classrooms.
This time...
you'll have to rely on yourself.
I'm dead...
Study hard.
You might do well this time.
Letting you copy would just harm you.
Since when did you become
such a moralizer?
Don't give me that
"If you copy now,
whom will you copy from
during the college entrance exams?"
That's not what I meant.
I mean...
this time,
I'm not even confident in myself,
let alone able to help you.
Whatever.
Forget it.
That excuse is too lame.
I don't want to hear it.
Leave me alone.
Niannian,
was it the homeroom teacher?
What did she want?
She expects me to make the top 10.
How am I supposed to do that?
Top 10 in the grade...
It's not that hard, is it?
You're a great student.
You could easily rank top 10.
Don't stress.
Am I really that good?
Did you forget?
Last exam, you had a stomachache,
left early, and still got top 15.
This time,
just watch your diet,
and the top 10 is guaranteed.
(But I'm not Zhu Niannian...)
(My liberal arts skills are trash.)
Don't worry too much.
I can study with you.
Tomorrow is Saturday.
Let's go to the library.
You go ahead.
I've got stuff to do.
Really not going?
I heard Chen Changning
frequents the library on weekends.
You might even run into him.
Why would I want that?
Here's a secret.
I saw your sister
sneaking off to the rock garden.
Look, look.
Look.
See?
Could you make the top 10
in liberal arts?
If I try hard... maybe?
You could, but I can't.
I only told your mom I'd get top 10
to make her happy.
Now the teacher expects it too.
She's backing me into a corner.
I'm sorry.
My mom and the homeroom teacher
always expect a lot more of me.
Don't apologize.
I'm not blaming you.
But I'm really not good
at liberal arts.
Politics and history make my head ache.
We need to figure out how to handle it.
I don't know either.
My science grades are awful.
I checked online.
No meteor showers anytime soon.
I think
we should take the initiative.
Let's see
if there's another way
to switch back our bodies.
Do you want to switch back?
This isn't about wishes.
We can't handle the joint exam.
We have to switch back.
Do you have any leads?
Earlier you mentioned
magnetic fields
and time travel.
I really couldn't understand.
Let me think.
I remember Chen Changning
had a book in his room,
a rare edition
Aunt bought from abroad.
It's called...
"The Big Bang".
It mentioned
some foreign scientist
already conducting experiments on this.
I just skimmed it before.
The details are fuzzy.
Why don't you get that book
so we can study it?
Don't let Chen Changning find out.
Isn't that stealing?
Changning and I are family.
We're just borrowing it.
I'm worried you'll get caught
and told him the truth.
- But...
- No buts.
Friday afternoon,
his exam runs late.
That's your chance.
A last-ditch attempt.
It's our only way.
What are you doing here?
I...
I was just talking to Chen Jing'an.
No?
Hiding to talk?
Private chats require hiding.
Should I use a loudspeaker?
More importantly, Changning,
why are you here?
Don't tell me
you're playing love police again.
I was passing by
and saw you.
What a coincidence.
You police the skies, the earth,
and now girl talk thing too?
Chen Jing'an.
Stop laughing.
It's noisy.
You police the skies, the earth,
and now my laughter too?
Why are you staring at me?
Class is starting.
Aren't you going back?
Fine, bye.
Steal the book.
Time to eat.
What's the special occasion today?
Why'd you make so much good food?
Your mom
made all this to support your studies.
Oh, I heard
your monthly exam
got changed to a nine-school joint exam.
Yeah.
I was just about to tell you.
Listen,
you better study hard.
You promised me
top 10 in your grade.
I haven't forgotten.
Top 10...
Right.
I have to make the top 10.
(Screw top 10.)
(I'd rather die!)
What if...
Just hypothetically,
what if
I mess up
and don't make the top 10?
It's fine.
As long as
you tried your best
and have no regrets.
Top 10 means top 10.
Not even one place short.
Why're you back so early today?
I finished the test early.
Are you expecting me?
No.
Any plans for dinner?
Anything's fine.
Did you steal the book?
No.
Chen Changning came home early.
Hey.
Can you talk now?
Yes.
We can't wait any longer.
Your mom expects me to make the top 10.
How can I do that?
Figure something out.
We need to get that book.
But
what if I really steal it,
and Chen Changning notices it's gone?
He'll have more doubts, right?
Good point.
Then how about this?
You find a way
to lure Chen Changning out,
and I'll go check
the book myself.
I'll return it without anyone noticing,
and he won't suspect a thing.
Does that book
really have a way to switch us back?
I won't know until I read it.
Fine.
You looking at me?
Aren't you going to the library today?
Why would I go there?
I mean,
the joint exam is coming up.
You should focus on studying.
Since when do you care about my grades?
Isn't it normal
for me to care?
Alright.
Let's go together.
No, no.
I'll pass.
It's fine if I flunk,
but you've got that recommendation exam.
I heard
they consider your usual grades too.
Fine,
I'll go.
When will you be back?
I'll…
come back later.
Okay.
Then, take care.
Strange.
I swear it was right here.
Where is it?
It used to be in this spot.
Where'd it go?
Niannian, haven't you seen it?
No, I haven't.
Did Chen Changning take it just now?
It's fine.
Anyway, Chen Changning's books
are all about astrophysics
and black holes.
Since I'm here, let's look around.
You check these first.
If you find any useful research,
let me know.
Why are you in my room?
Niannian
came over to hang out.
Why are you back?
But why are you in my room?
I asked Chen Jing'an
to give me a room tour.
Who wouldn't want to see
a top student's room, right?
I was expecting more.
But it's not that special.
Let's go.
My parents.
We're home.
Mom, Dad,
this is my classmate, Zhu Niannian.
She's here to hang out.
Niannian.
Hello, Niannian.
Hi, sir, ma'am.
This is the first time
Jing'an's brought
a girlfriend home.
Stay for dinner.
Where's your brother?
In his room.
Alright.
You two go play.
We'll start cooking.
Mom, Dad, let me help.
No need.
Niannian's visiting
for the first time.
Go keep her company.
Go on.
Spend time with her.
Okay.
Well,
don't you think
Jing'an's acting strange today?
You noticed too?
It's like she's trying extra hard
to impress her friend
around us.
Isn't it?
How's this taste?
Too salty.
I'll fix that next time.
Less salt.
I'm allergic to chives.
Niannian, what's up?
I just remembered I'm allergic to chives.
To chive dumplings?
Why aren't you eating either?
You love chive dumplings.
It's fine, Mom.
Just...
not hungry today.
Not hungry?
Stomachache?
I'll get you some medicine.
No, Dad.
Let me check.
Stick out your tongue.
What?
I'm a doctor.
Tongue out. Now.
Now.
You're perfectly fine.
Probably ate too fast.
Slow down, understand?
Niannian,
don't mind us.
Doctors are just
like this.
Back then,
at our hospital,
there was a TCM intern.
He had a poor appetite,
so he tried acupuncture
to cure himself.
And then
guess what happened?
He looked like a hedgehog
with all those acupuncture needles.
What kind of lame joke is that?
Here, Jing'an.
Don't want the chive dumplings?
How about some fish?
Eat some fish.
Have some fish.
Fish is nutritious.
Here,
have this piece.
Thank you, Mom.
Eat up.
(They seem to)
(prefer Zhu Niannian as their daughter.)
Have more.
Kids,
time for fruit.
Here, Niannian,
have some fruit.
Changning,
Jing'an,
we need to talk.
Your father and I
have been too busy at the hospital,
with no time to care for you.
But once this busy period passes,
we'll try to stagger our shifts,
so at least
one of us can always be home.
Okay?
Okay.
Jing'an, happy about this?
Yes.
Really? So hesitant?
Ma'am, I should go now.
My dad's here to pick me up.
So soon?
Well then, Jing'an,
see your classmate out.
Look,
why is there a book in the cabinet?
Changning, is this yours?
What book?
(The Big Bang)
Yes.
But this book
was always in my room before.
I'll see Niannian out first.
Goodbye, sir, ma'am.
Bye, Niannian.
Goodbye, Niannian.
Come visit again sometime.
(The Big Bang)
No need to walk me out, go back.
Niannian,
did you have fun
at your classmate's?
Yes.
Niannian,
tell Dad the truth.
Is something bothering you?
No.
Really?
But I feel like
you seem unhappy.
I am happy.
I have such a great dad,
such a great mom.
Plus
endless dresses to wear,
endless delicious food.
And Dad drives me to school every day.
I'd wake up laughing from dreams.
How could I not be happy?
(The Big Bang)
Why is there a book in the cabinet?
Changning, is this yours?
I'll see Niannian out first.
(The Big Bang)
(Soul Exchange)
Chen Jing'an,
what do we do now?
(Niannian)
Niannian,
I don't want to switch back.
Chen Jing'an,
why are you suddenly saying that?
I just think
there's not much time left before exams.
Even if we find useful information,
there wouldn't be time to switch back.
Might as well spend time
on something more meaningful.
That makes sense.
Besides,
I haven't had enough of
being the campus belle yet.
Alright, I'll follow your lead.
What should we do next?
Don't ask me now. I need more time.
(Grade 11)
(Five Days Until Joint Exams)
"Alone I stand in the autumn cold,"
"On the tip of Orange Islet,"
"the Xiangjiang River flowing northward."
"All mountains had become red..."
My crush,
please bless me to pass the exam.
The activity period
is changed to history class.
Stand up.
Good morning, ma'am.
Good morning, class.
(Back in Class 1,)
(English and math
stole activity periods.)
(Now in Class 8,)
(even history takes them.)
The joint exams are coming.
Look at your attitudes,
do you look ready for exams?
Listen up,
this is
a nine-school joint exam.
You must focus
and study hard.
Give it your best shot.
Understood?
Understood.
Louder!
Understood!
Alright,
turn to page
fifteen.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Niannian,
I can tell Liu Xinyi
is determined to compete with you.
You have to beat her!
Have a seat.
Niannian,
let's sit over there.
You eat first. We need to talk.
Niannian...
Go ahead, eat.
I've been thinking all morning.
Since we can't
switch back right now,
we should quickly review
the subjects we're weak in
to at least handle the exam.
Your idea makes sense,
but the joint exams are just days away.
In such a short time,
there's no way we can catch up.
You're a science student.
You're good at logical thinking.
Liberal arts won't be hard for you.
Just memorize the key points,
and you'll manage the exams.
Sure,
you might not make the top 10,
but at least you won't fail miserably.
Are science students really that amazing?
Humanities materials
aren't easy to memorize.
I'm not a photocopier.
The joint exam
has a set scope.
Just memorize the key points
within that range.
I believe you can do it.
I'm really not being modest.
Those materials are too hard to memorize.
Well...
I'll try.
But for me,
physics and chemistry
might as well be gibberish.
There's no way I can digest them
in such a short time.
Hey,
don't lose heart yet.
Mastering science subjects
requires learning strategies.
Once you get the basics,
they're easy.
Here's an idea.
We can help each other.
You teach me humanities problem-solving,
and I'll teach you the strategies.
Perfect, right?
But
what if I do poorly?
Will Chen Changning get mad at me?
Don't worry.
My parents might, but...
Just do your best.
Ignore them.
- Okay.
- Eat.
(Cafeteria)
Niannian,
what were you two talking about?
You didn't even invite me.
Nothing much.
Well, I'll head out first.
Sure.
Oh, bring the practice tests after school.
The milk tea shop.
Niannian,
are you and Chen Jing'an
studying together after school?
Yeah.
Don't worry too much.
I can study with you too.
Tomorrow is Saturday.
Let's go to the library.
You go ahead.
I've got stuff to do.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
You can go first.
I'm going to study at the milk tea shop.
At a milk tea shop?
Are you using that as an excuse
to hang out?
I really am going to study.
The joint exams are just days away.
You're going alone?
With Zhu Niannian.
I'll head over first.
♪Sweetness flows like honey♪
♪Warm hugs rest on my chest♪
♪Running together toward wild happiness♪
♪Shining just like this♪
♪Every day is glowing♪
♪Your love makes me strong♪
♪With you in my future,
I'm not lost anymore♪
♪This is our paradise♪
♪Golden sunlight spills
on the windowsill♪
♪Your sweet smile is like frosting♪
♪Every time you're near, my heart races♪
♪Love drifts through the air♪
♪Holding hands,
strolling under starlight♪
♪Every moment is brilliant♪
♪Your tender gaze
is a precious treasure♪
♪I'll keep it for a lifetime♪
♪Sweetness flows like honey♪
♪Warm hugs rest on my chest♪
♪Running together toward wild happiness♪
♪Shining just like this♪
♪Every day is glowing♪
♪Your love makes me strong♪
♪With you in my future,
I'm not lost anymore♪
♪This is our paradise♪