=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
This week, our school is going to hold a drama competition.
I heard that Li Wei had invited Jiang Chen
=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
to star in 'Thunderstorm'.
Jiang Chen.
=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
Let's discuss the division of roles later,
is it okay?
=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
Chen Xiaoxi.
I'm here.
=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
You're in charge of the dubbing,
such as recording the sound of thunder.
=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
Why are you so serious?
Just play around.
=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
You don't understand,
I need to do it well.
=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
Why are you hiding here?
Bro.
=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
It's over?
I specially come back.
=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
Chen Xiaoxi.
You've made a fool of yourself today.
=Episode 6
It's no big deal.
Chen Xiaoxi.
You've made a fool of yourself today.
Xiaoxi.
- Take it easy. - Look at her...
Let's talk on the sofa.
Let's go.
Jiang Chen, how's it going recently?
Is your study tiring?
Just like that. I have to go to the class.
Alright.
Here's the thing.
Mom is now working on my transfer.
If they would allow my transfer,
then I could come back to Hangzhou.
Then our family could be together
Got it.
Yesterday, what did the teacher tell us?
So she's right to be in love now?
It's just a suspicion.
The teacher especially emphasized that
we parents needed to be patient with her at this point.
Let me tell you,
haven't you read it on TV or newspapers?
How fragile the youngsters are nowadays.
Didn't you notice how upset she was last night?
She's been crying in the room for all night.
Which means,
our kid has failed to be in love with someone.
That's right.
You see, our Xiaoxi is careless,
just like a boy.
Who would like her?
That's because they haven't discovered her merits!
Stop it.
Chen Xiaoxi hasn't come yet?
Come, come over here.
Where did you go yesterday?
Come on, let's go to the office.
Come on.
I know I'm wrong, teacher. I'm sorry.
You are not sorry to me.
You are sorry to yourself.
Look at you.
Don't you wanna go to a university?
I know at your age,
it's easy for you to have some thoughts,
which I can understand.
But Chen Xiaoxi,
is it now the right time to have this kind of thoughts?
Go back and think about it.
Which class are you in?
The bell has been ringing for a long time, can't you hear it?
Stop.
It has already passed for such a long time,
yet you're still wandering in the campus.
Let's go.
Take me to your class.
I'll emphasize this one last time.
There's only a month left before the final.
Don't waste your time on those stupid things.
It's time for you to think about
whether to choose liberal arts or science.
It's a great event in your life.
When you come back home,
discuss about it with your parents.
What's more,
The gap between your scores is too big.
So I've discussed with various teachers,
we decide to divide you into several study groups.
In each group, those who have good grades,
should help those who have bad grade.
I'll read the assignment to you.
Li Wei, Yu Tian and Liao Chenxuan are in the same group.
Jiang Chen, Lu Yang and Wang Songson are in the same group.
Lin Jingxiao, Chen Xiaoxi…
Teacher.
And you, are in the same group.
What do you want now?
That…
Chen Xiaoxi is here.
Get in.
Teacher Liu.
Your classmate Chen Xiaoxi is always making trouble.
The class has already begun for quite a while,
she's still wandering in the campus by herself.
Director Zhang,
sorry for the inconvenience.
Students like her,
just need some discipline.
You're right.
Take care, director Zhang.
Who dare to punish you, I'll deal with them.
Li Wei.
Put it on the wall at the back of the classroom.
Chen Xiaoxi.
Who is your crush?
Tell me about it.
Shut your mouth.
Jing.
Dazhuang bro.
What's up?
I need a sandbag to practice with recently.
I'm wrong.
Bro, I'm going to swim.
If anyone bullies you, let pigeon Xiaoyang tell me about it
Look at Chen Xiaoxi.
How humiliating she is.
If I were her, I would've transferred a long time ago.
Such a pachyderm.
Let's go. Let's get some water.
Are you okay?
What did the teacher say to you in the office?
Just those cliche.
That's right.
The teacher must have said something like,
being in love at such an early age is sorry to your classmates,
sorry to your patriarch,
and sorry to your parents those kind of words.
I wonder whether all these teachers' hobby,
is to break up affectionate couples.
Be careful.
I've got scalded.
Are you all right?
Sister Xi.
I've brought you some milk.
What do you want?
Here's the thing.
I want to exchange the study group with you.
Aren't you in the same group with Jiang Chen?
You've got help.
Jiang Chen is not good enough.
There's something wrong with his way of teaching homework.
His method is really bad.
And he is not patient.
You are better, right?
No matter who meets a person with your IQ,
he will be impatient.
I want to go to the bathroom.
If okay for you not to teach me the homework.
You can still drink my milk.
Piss off.
Chen Xiaoxi.
Miss Liu is asking for you.
Are you addicted to making trouble recently?
So you really plan to return home after you graduate from here?
Let me tell you.
Whether you can graduate from high school or not,
it's now hard to tell.
Look at your homework.
What are these?
All of your answers are wrong!
When I'm available,
I'll absolutely go to visit your parents
and talk to them about this.
Get out.
= See you at the library.
=A message from Lu Yang: Chen Xiaoxi, it's a trap! So it's a deal that we've exchanged our study group. Please do me a favor.
=If I and Lin Jingxiao had a child in the future, you could be his godmother.
Chen Xiaoxi.
Come here, sit with me.
Your auxiliary line is wrong
There's answer in the back.
I'll check it myself.
The answer of this problem is omitted.
Then I'll figure it out myself.
Chen Xiaoxi, are you alright?
Have you been scolded by the teacher too much?
Or…
Has she asked you about your crush intensely?
What are you talking about?
It's nonsense.
It's nonsense?
You are not going to study?
What's wrong with her?
Bro.
Where is your bike?
Let me take you there.
Still haven't found the key yet?
I don't where it is.
What are you doing?
Pick the lock.
There's no need to do so. I've got spare key at home.
Then let me take you home.
It's okay.
If you've got into trouble, just let me know.
You are my bro.
I'll beat the guy whoever bullies you.
Stop it, you'd better hurry home.
Got it.
Bye.
Give me your money.
I've only got 10 yuan.
Who are you going to fool?
That's all you've got?
It's even not enough for you to get that fat.
Lin Jingxiao, please bless me.
Stop it.
You're two sizes bigger than her,
don't you feel ashamed to hide behind her?
Don't you think it's humiliating for you to do so?
You've made a fool of yourself today.
So you are bullying people.
You think others won't feel upset?
I've always been so nice to you.
You not only don't appreciate it,
but also say that I'm humiliating.
Why is it humiliating to like someone?
Besides,
she's got a big face, so she can lose face whatever she wants.
It's none of your business
Can't you look after the dignity?
Xiaoxi, we don't have such a relationship.
And you don't need to speak it out about my big face.
Cut the crap.
Just give me your money.
So you are going to rob me?
How dare you say that you're in this business?
Don't you know whose territory it is?
Whose?
My boss's.
Jiang Chen.
Bro, something's wrong.
She's got someone to back her up.
We should leave.
She is calling someone.
You have guts. Watch out on your way to school.
Chen Xiaoxi.
Brother, you are finally back.
Mom's been waiting for you for a long time.
Jiang Chen, you are back.
Let me have a look.
I think you are taller
And you are more handsome.
The transfer has been settled.
So we come back in a hurry.
Tidy up. Let's have dinner
I bought all the dishes.
I'll heat them up again.
Come, have a seat.
Go.
Let's sit down and eat the dinner.
What are you doing?
Your brother hasn't started eating
how can you start eating by yourself?
Let's eat. Let's eat.
Don't you remember that
you were sent to hospital after eating shrimps last time?
I just want to eat a little bit.
No, don't eat it.
Give it to your brother.
Now,
your learning tasks are heavy,
the nutrition should keep up with them.
I hear that you've got the first place in the exams again?
Awesome.
Do you hear that?
Your brother has come first in the exams again.
You should learn from him.
Mom.
I'd like to drink some milk.
You shouldn't have any milk during your meal.
How could you eat your meal if you were full by drinking milk?
Jiang Chen.
Let me get you a cup of milk.
Nutrition is important. The milk's nutrition…
I'm full.
Mom, don't you remember that brother is allergic to milk?
Xiaoxi.
Studying.
48 points.
I want to tell you something.
Here's the thing.
This afternoon, your homeroom teacher called me again.
I've discussed with your mother,
we wonder if there's something wrong with your school.
Too many activities.
I want to find a more strict school for you.
Let's transfer to another school, okay?
Dad.
I don't want to transfer.
Look at you.
Look at your examination paper.
What is this?
Your teacher has told me that,
your score,
is only the odd
of the first one's score in your class.
Isn't it humiliating?
What are you doing?
We agreed to talk to her calmly,
why do you start yelling?
Have a seat.
Baby.
We think you are a good student,
except that your self-restraint ability is poor.
There's a boarding high school nearby,
which is more strict than Chenxi High School.
I and your dad,
both think it's suitable for you.
We don't want to force you to do anything.
It took you a lot of efforts to get into this high school.
But a year has passed,
your grade is getting worse and worse.
As for the boarding school,
We've had an inspection.
The enrollment rate of first-tier universities is 30%
We just need you to study hard for another two years.
Let's get into a good university.
Wu Bosong.
What's the matter? You still haven't found your key?
No.
I just don't want to ride bike.
No problem.
From now on, I will be your driver.
Bro.
Which one will you choose? Liberal arts or science?
I haven't…
It's okay. Take your time.
I'll choose the same as you.
Go ahead.
If I transferred to another school,
would you guys miss me?
Transfer?
To which school? I'll go with you.
Do they take sport-specialized students?
No, I mean what if.
I'm not leaving.
Then…
Let's go!
Everyone,
please write this down on your notebook.
It may come in handy in your exams.
Chen Xiaoxi.
Stand up.
Please tell us
the judgment method of the monotone interval of a function.
You don't understand it,
yet you're not listening to me carefully.
If you were a student in my class,
you would have been expelled a long time ago.
Teacher.
I'd like to go to the washroom.
Go ahead.
Where were we?
Your study attitude…
Teacher.
I'd like to go to the washroom too.
Go ahead.
Thank you, teacher.
Chen Xiaoxi, you…
Teacher.
Jiang Chen wants to solve the math problem on the blackboard.
Of course.
Come here.
Chen Xiaoxi.
It's okay, don't be afraid.
You've got us.
What you've written here is the knowledge of Senior two.
Why are you still standing?
Sit down and write the note down.
Not until I had come out did I realize that,
how can I use such a bad trick like you as a clever person.
I thought you'd tell her the answer.
I just suddenly forgot that I am a top-A student.
What's going on with my bro?
How can I know?
Where are you going?
I can't lie.
I need to go to the washroom sincerely.
Let me calculate this for you.
Never mind.
I can do it myself.
Except for the "Solution" is right,
others are all wrong.
I did that all by myself.
Don't you worry about that.
I think I want to do this?
It's the teacher's arrangement.
She's afraid your grades will become a drag on the whole class.
Jiang Chen, don't say that.
It sounds hurtful even to me.
Now that the moral model Jiang Chen has said that,
I'll leave now.
I won't be a drag on your great class eight.
I'll transfer to another school next semester.
Transfer?
Mind your step.
Alright.
Young girl,
why are you crying?
You've been bullied by someone?
Don't come over here.
If you get any closer, I will shout.
Just shout.
Your boss is Jiang Chen.
I'm so sacred.
Bro, don't be afraid.
That Jiang Chen is a counterfeit.
Get on.
So you are her boss?
She...
Is my boss.
So handsome.
Shut up.
Chase them.
Who is it this time?
I'm gonna kill you this time.
Why do you take me here?
I've promised to treat you to eat steak.
Are you better?
Then I'll take you to try something interesting.
I haven't finished eating yet.
Close your eyes
and count from 1 to 10.
What for?
Just trust me.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
How about counting to 100?
11, 12, 13, 14.
15, 16, 17.
Come here and have a try.
No.
I would tip over.
It will be okay. I will hold you.
Believe me, have a try.
How about this?
Don't you feel like you're in Maldives?
I feel like that you need to go to the doctor.
Don't be so negative.
Come.
Let's feel this positively.
Isn't it cool to sit on the water?
Yes.
Isn't it super cool?
Don't you think it's no big deal?
Yes.
If the answer is positive, then speak it out.
It's okay to transfer.
The whole world should piss off.
Chen Xiaoxi is the best, the smartest, the most beautiful.
Chen Xiaoxi is the best, who has enough to eat and wear.
It's no big deal!
What's going on?
Come up.
You are not new here in the swimming team.
You don't even remember these ground rules?
I'm so sorry, coach.
It's because I'm in a bad mood,
so Wu Bosong took me here.
Please don't punish him.
I'm educating my teammates.
You should leave here.
Go.
Nothing valuable,
just some specialties for you to eat.
Please excuse me for that.
Yanjun, it's good for you to come back,
you don't need to bring us anything.
During these years,
Jiang Chen has caused great inconvenience for you.
I feel quite sorry about that.
Jiang Chen is an obedient and intelligent boy.
He can take care of himself.
He didn't cause any inconvenience.
We haven't helped at all.
Stop complimenting him.
I know he makes people worry about him.
He makes people worry about him?
He's good at study and independent.
Xiaoxi makes us worry about her the most.
Xiaoxi is good.
Stop that, she's not good at all.
She's bad at study.
She couldn't catch up with the others,
yet is busy all the time.
I don't know why she is so busy.
She's just a kid who wants to play.
She just needs to make up the lessons she had missed.
No.
It's only a temporary solution.
These days,
Chen and I,
we plan to ask some acquaintances
to help her to transfer
to a boarding school.
She's going to transfer?
Yes.
These days, we are trying to persuade her.
Just now, I got her message.
Finally she's agreed.
You should have some too, they are sweet.
Five-hundred push-ups and five-kilometer swimming.
Who's that girl?
You don't wanna say, right?
You think you're amazing after getting a few champions?
So you can break the rules in the team?
You think no one can punish you, right?
She's my girlfriend.
What?
Girlfriend?
Five-hundred more.
She's my girlfriend.
So you think you're already in the national team?
How dare you fall in love with someone?
From now on, you are suspended.
You are not allowed to swim again.
Dad.
I don't want swimming to be the only thing in my life.
I've been swimming for ten years.
Since I was a boy,
I first joined the youth team,
then the city team, province team,
and I have to join the national team.
From then on, it's all about winning the championship.
Champions, champions
There you go.
If I don't push you hard now,
you'll regret for the rest of your life.
Let me tell you,
don't hang out with those disreputable girls.
She's not one of those disreputable girls.
Since I was a boy,
you've just arranged everything for me.
Did you ever ask if I really like swimming?
Did you ever ask if I have any friends?
I just keep swimming everyday.
I even don't have time to talk to my classmates at school.
She's my first friend.
I like her.
You…
I'll do it myself.
What happened?
I just got scratched.
Scratches are not like these.
You are not having a fight with the others?
If a man,
fights with someone,
it's either for money,
or for women.
What are you talking about?
Where did you learn those nonsense?
Brother.
It's for a woman, isn't it?
Go back to your room.
What is he talking about?
Nonsense.
Just tell me,
what exactly happened?
You did not really get into a fight?
I've already told you, I just got scratched.
=A message to Chen Xiaoxi: Hello.
=A message to Chen Xiaoxi: Chen Xiaoxi.
=A message to Chen Xiaoxi: You…
=Have you finished your homework?
Don't transfer.
Wu Bosong.
Are you all right yesterday?
I'm fine.
Everyone, write the question down.
It's important.
Chen Xiaoxi.
Why it is you again?
Come to my office.
Look at her.
She doesn't look like a student.
Her homework is a mess.
And she was in a daze and sleeping during the class.
I've never met a more unreasonable student.
Mr. Guo.
Although Chen Xiaoxi…
Miss Liu, don't persuade me.
I must scold her sharply today.
When her parents are here,
I'll talk to them.
Zero tolerance.
So you're Chen Xiaoxi's parents?
Come here, come here.
This way please.
Hello, Miss Liu.
Hello.
Have a seat.
So sorry to bother you to come here.
Not long ago, I told her that
I wanted to have a talk with you.
Xiaoxi, you've already told the teacher?
You'd better look at this first.
It's her math homework recently.
I know it may be a tough period for students.
But her study attitude recently
is indeed a problem.
She's either in a daze or sleeping during the class.
Teacher, I think I know the reason.
Recently,
we're preparing the transfer for her,
maybe she just hasn't adapted to that for the moment.
She may have a mood swing because of that.
That's right.
That's how all these happened.
Transfer?
We've been studying at Chenxi High School
for almost a year.
Her grades are getting worse and worse.
It's about her future.
We are worried.
So we want to change the environment for her.
It suddenly occurs to me that
I've still got some math test papers of class seven to correct.
What about you
talking to the parents first?
And I'll go to correct the test papers.
Go ahead.
Actually, Chen Xiaoxi
is a good student.
She really is.
You don't need to worry about it.
I think,
her senior one's grades,
can't represent her future grades,
also can't represent her grades of college entrance examination.
Some students are slow-type.
So it may take them longer to be enlightened.
When they are in senior two,
they just need to work a little bit harder,
then they can catch up with the others.
If you insist on that she should transfer,
it may take her some time
to adjust to the new environment.
Perhaps,
the loss will outweigh the gain.
Miss Liu,
what you said
sounds reasonable.
But her father has already settled everything.
Now we just need to do the transfer formalities.
I'm sorry.
I need to answer the phone.
That's okay.
Look at your scores.
This kid.
Really makes us angry.
Chen Xiaoxi is called into the office again.
This time, her parents are called here too.
How can she be so unlucky this week?
She is going to transfer.
Transfer?
No. What's going on?
No, no. Why?
But it seems that every teacher is aiming at her recently.
If I were her,
I couldn't stand it either.
But Liu Qingshan likes her very much.
Mr. Liu.
What's the matter?
That, we…
Don't falter. Go ahead.
That…
Let Jiang Chen tell you.
Jiang Chen, what's going on?
Do you know that Chen Xiaoxi is going to transfer?
Chen Xiaoxi?
Transfer?
That's right.
Let's find out.
Yes, that's right.
Jiang Chen is in my class.
No problem, I'll tell him.
Okay. Goodbye.
Miss Liu,
did you just mention Jiang Chen?
Yes.
What's wrong with him?
Here's the thing.
Jiang Chen lives in the building next to us.
And his mother is our good friend.
If there's something about him
that could use my help,
I can tell his mother.
Here's the thing.
Recently around our school,
there are a lot of unemployed youth
who specially blackmail the students.
Jiang Chen had saw some,
so he called the police,
and managed to stall them,
and helped the police catch them.
So the Public Security Bureau informed the Education Bureau.
And the Education Bureau specially called me to praise him.
Jiang Chen is such a good boy.
You see, students from our school,
are upright and smart.
If it's known by the public,
everyone would like to transfer to our school.
Who is going to transfer?
Mr. Liu.
Let me introduce to you.
This is our Chinese teacher.
his surname is also Liu.
They are Chen Xiaoxi's parents.
Hello.
Hello, Mr. Liu.
Please have a seat.
Have a seat.
- Let me say something. - Okay.
You always complain that Chen Xiaoxi is not good at studying.
And she is good at nothing.
I don't agree.
And I don't like it when you say these things.
It's not because she's not good,
but because you didn't see her merits.
First, Chen Xiaoxi has a talent for art.
Then look at her.
She is outgoing and kind.
What a good kid.
Yes.
That's right.
Her grades are not good now.
But I believe her.
=King Zhuang of Chu: A famous king in Chinese history.
King Zhuang of Chu hadn't achieved anything for three years.
But he finally made a great coup.
Mr. Liu, thank you, thank you.
Mr. Liu,
your words make sense.
But her school work is quite important after all.
All right.
We adults
should stop arguing.
Let's hear what she thinks.
Chen Xiaoxi.
Tell us.
Do you want to transfer?
I…
Mr. Liu.
You just now asked me to take the Chinese test papers.
Yes, right.
The papers are on the desk.
Take the composition notebooks too.
Oh, Chen Xiaoxi's composition is excellent this time.
She has made great progress.
Come, help me take the notebooks.
Xiaoxi,
we haven't finished talking, what are you doing?
=Jiang Chen=
Don't transfer.
Xiaoxi.
Xiaoxi, hurry up.
I won't transfer.
Our school is really good now,
teachers are really good.
And my friends are nice to me.
I decide to stay.
You've promised us!
Exactly.
Your grades are in a complete mess.
How can you not transfer?
Right.
I'll absolutely study hard in the future.
I will do well in the final.
I will get into…
Top 15 in my class.
Top 15?
You?
That's impossible.
How can it be possible?
If I got into the top 15 in my class,
do I still need to transfer?
Impossible.
Mom. Dad.
The point is, it's impossible.
Good girl.
You've got backbone.
I have faith in you.
Mom.
Chen Xiaoxi.
Walk faster.
Okay.
I heard that you'd helped the police catch the hooligans.
Did you do this because of me?
No.
I did that to eliminate the bad people and protect the good ones.
And I am the good one.
I feel like someone's following me recently.
It's you, right?
You must know that I've been bullied by hooligans,
so you just secretly protect me on my way home and way to school.
Right?
You imagination can be used to write a book.
Hurry up.
Then give me a ride.
No.
Why?
Because you're heavy.
That's because I am a sweet burden.
Chen Xiaoxi.
=In Chinese, you have no face means you are unabashed.
Where's your face?
I've sent it to you.
=Detailed study plan in high school=
# I like your eyes, your eyelashes and your coldness. #
# I like your dimples, your lips. #
A sad love story.
Broken.
It was Valentine's Day and Hu Jin had said…
# I like your shirt, your fingers and your smell. #
# I want to be your cotton-padded jacket, #
# your gloves and your heartbeat. #
# The whole world knows that I like you. #
# I'm suffering. #
# Don't be angry. #
# You'll find out how patient I am. #
# I like every moment and every second of you. #
# I like every place and every corner of you. #
# It has become a habit for me to like you, which is addictive. #
All the invigilators,
please check the test papers in front of students.
And open the test papers bag.
Check the number of the test papers.
And deliver them to students.
Students now can answer the questions.
# It has become a faith for me to like you, #
# which is hard to let go. #
# You'll know how much I like you. #
Excuse me, excuse me.
Excuse me, excuse me, excuse me.
# You'll know how much I like you. #
No.13 in the class.
Chen Xiaoxi.
Your identity as a top student is finally exposed.
I'll break relations with you.
Guys,
I'll substitute wine with milk,
Let's congratulate Chen Xiaoxi on becoming a top student.
Let's congratulate Jiang Chen
on winning the title of doing boldly what is righteous.
At the same time,
let's congratulate us
on choosing the difficult path of science.
Cheers.
It seems that I still like you very much.
Jiang Chen.
We thought you transferred.
What?
It's her.
She told us that you transferred to Changsha.
I transferred?
You didn't?
You tell me.
It seems that you didn't.
She wants to tell you something.
The class is about to begin.
It's okay.
Let's see if Hu Yitian of class six is there.
Let's go.