=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
- How did you come here? - Bitch.
My brother and  I are step siblings from different mothers.
=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
What do you think about Lin Daiyu?
These are things that I couldn't do.
=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
That's not my problem.
My parents quarreled again.
=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
I'm really worried that they're divorcing.
Don't talk nonsense.
=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
You can talk to me.
Send my regards to your wife.
=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
It seems I'm wrong.
=I like Xiaoxi.
=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
Congrats, you've won. Can you tell us how you feel about it?
What inspired you to win the race so easily?
=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
She did.
=Episode 8
Stay there, I'll come for you.
He had just won the champion, so, why did they punish him?
Because of the interview by the girl
=Wu Bosong is punished
1. Receiving a severe reprimand
They must be settling a score with him.
=Wu Bosong is punished
1. Receiving a severe reprimand
Bosong.
Why don't you go and apologize to the coach?
They care about you so much.
I go home now, buddy.
Dad, mom, I'm home.
Look, that date is ok, isn't it?
What're you doing?
Choose an lucky opening day for your mom's trotters shop.
Saturday is a lucky day.
let's see it.
Suitable for funeral and burying.
Funeral, nonsense. Stop interrupting.
- We're very busy. - Leave us.
They've just been so occupied with their stuff,
even forget their daughter's birthday.
No big deal even if becoming "King of Trotters".
Doctor, can the child whose father is Jiang Chen be saved?
You have to eat some snow lotus stewed for 49 days,
and drink a drop of blood from Kylin's heart,
in order to save your baby and yourself,
It sounds delicious, doesn't it?
- Why can't you play it seriously? - I'm hungry.
- I want to eat my birthday cake. - Enough.
You've reminded me a hundred times of your birthday,
and I've already got a good idea for you.
Chunchun will have her concert here on your birthday.
- I'll go there with you. - I...
want to spend my birthday...
with Jiang Chen.
You always take love more seriously than friendship.
- Forget it. - Manchester United's coming to Hangzhou for a game.
I want to watch it with Jiang Chen.
Are you going to buy the ticket for him?
- Yeah. - You don't know how expensive the ticket is.
You have to sell your internal organs to buy it.
And anyway, it's your birthday, not his.
Jiang Chen is a fan of MU which rarely come to Hangzhou.
It's nothing to do with birthday.
By the way...
whose slip did you get at that time?
I guess it's Lu Yang's, the writing is awful.
Do you know whose one I got?
Jiang Chen's?
Xiaoxi's birthday is coming, do something.
I know. She reminds me of it everyday.
Why doesn't she remind me?
She maybe worries that you could extravagantly buy her a yacht.
- So, what's your gift? - Nothing, she is only a kid.
Besides, Wu Bosong's here, so we don't have to give her gifts.
Are we all buddies?
Take it, my pocket money for this week.
You and I must help Xiaoxi.
She likes MU now, and wants to get game tickets.
Alright, I've got a buddy who can get tickets.
But, how could she suddenly be interested in MU?
Handsome players.
Bosong, what happened to you and your dad now?
- No big deal. - But you are kicked out of the house?
How do you know that?
He is "the Flower of School" who is also known as "Big Mouth".
- Stop it. - I'm going for water.
- So where will you sleep at night? - What about my house?
My mom is away for work.
I'm going to my grandma's house.
Come on.
- What? - I have a question.
Whose slip did you get at that time?
Lin jingxiao's.
- So the slip in my hand is really his. - What're you muttering?
Happiness comes to me so suddenly,
and it almost makes me cry.
"Mother", written by Luofu,
"Ah, mother!
Your greatness created my body,
Your greatness shaped my soul,
Your life is the voyage of love.
- Ah, mother!" - Wait, wait...
What's going on?
Mom, I'm asking for money.
- Mother... - Shut up.
Ok, I buy some quiet with money.
Stop bothering me.
- Please give me a little more. - How much?
- 500 yuan. - 500?
- Why do you want so much? - I want to see the soccer game.
MU's coming to Hangzhou.
It's maybe the only one chance to see them in my life.
I've never seen soccer game before, that's why I want to go.
You're a girl who doesn't like sports. Why go to soccer game?
You can watch it on TV if you like it.
=Good Opening
=Vacancies for Attendants to be Filled
Hourly Wage: 5 yuan
Boss!
Do you need a waitress?
The boss's out.
It's you!
Look, tell me the truth.
You said you'd go to your grandma's house.
- I'm afraid she'd have worried. - So, you plan to stay here.
Why do you come here, though?
I need money.
- To buy the game tickets? - How do you know?
Lin said you like MU recently because of...
their handsome players.
So, are there any vacancies here?
No, I'd have torn it off in the morning as the boss told me.
- Can we come in? - Welcome! Come in and take a seat.
- I have to go. - Bye.
Wait.
What did you write on the slip at that time?
"Huoguo". That's my favorite cuisine.
You like Huoguo? It'll be my treat!
As a swimmer, I can't eat anything at will.
Then, I'm gonna go.
Boss, is there any vacancy here?
- Boss, is there any vacancy here? - No.
- Boss, I want to be recruited. - All the vacancies are filled.
5 yuan per hour, but you must have the health certificate.
Thanks, boss.
Excuse me, is it the place for checkup...
before receiving the health certificate?
=Physical Examination
Yes, it is.
- Chen Xiaoxi. - I'm here.
Take off your trousers.
For anal examination!
Why keep your eyes on ground? Looking for money?
I'm sorry.
For what?
I can't give you what you want.
Is it right?
=Jiang Chen: Let's go out together on Saturday!
I always tell you,
you have to focus your attention on new words.
But, look at your faces now.
=We'll go out for a trip!
Is this sentence right?
- Obviously, there is a mistake here, isn't it? - Yes.
What is it?
=- We'll go out for a trip! - Ok.
When you do your homework after school,
everyone has to remember the new words. It's very important.
I'll dictate them next class.
Now I've got some good news to tell you.
Wu Bosong has won a national champion in the race.
Thank you, thank you.
Keep at it, Wu Bosong.
Now it's the time to replay the race on TV. Let's watch it.
Very intense. Wu Bosong is rushing to the finish line.
He's a step away from champion.
He is swimming excellently. Wu is the champion!
What inspired you to win the race so easily?
She did.
Wu Bosong, "she did".
- Wang Dazhuang! - Stop it!
You'd better go to the washroom before next class begins.
Let's go.
Awesome!
=News Conference on China Tour of Manchester United
Two Coaches Meeting
Have you got the ticket yet?
No, it's sold out.
Who's your favorite in MU?
Rooney
I like him, too.
Look, is that the girl Wu Bosong mentioned in TV?
- Chen Xiaoxi in Class 8? - I think it's her.
Little girl, are you Lu Yang's friend?
The jersey autographed by Rooney, 200 yuan.
Let me see it.
- Chinese writing? - Autographed it specially for Chinese fans.
- They're good at ingratiating themselves with fans. - So sweet.
Give me a discount.
Forget it, many people are waiting to buy it.
Wait, we buy it.
We buy it.
Why do you buy shirt for Jiang Chen?
I originally wanted to buy the ticket for him,
but that's too expensive, so, second best is OK.
Is she Wu Bosong's girlfriend?
A plain-looking girl in ugly clothes.
She doesn't deserve Wu Bosong, does she?
and isn't good at studying either.
Doesn't deserve?
Tell me why.
Yes, I certainly deserve him.
Hey, Jing, it's you.
They said I didn't deserve you.
I heard it's Wu Bosong.
We've just arrived.
What? Is he jealous?
He isn't.
But maybe he is.
The slip I got at the time was from Jiang Chen.
Then?
I'm probably going to...
What?
... fall in love.
What are you laughing at? Have you got the tickets?
No, my buddy said they're not available now.
It's very difficult to get them.
So...
- don't squander my money. - I'm not this kind of person.
What's more, the notes are probably not enough.
Maybe we have to pool money if the tickets are available.
So, it's better to give up.
Say it again! Say it again!
OK, OK, I'll call my buddy later.
Call him now! Go.
Hey,  Lu Yang.
Where are you recently?
- Still in Chenxi High School? - None of your business.
Lu Yang becomes a tough guy,
and it seems he's rich.
I just want to talk about old days with you,
- Remember that thing when we're kids? - Zhao Yue.
Shall I remind you?
What're you doing? I have no money.
Want to run away?
I have no money, Zhao Yue.
Hey, buddies,
help yourselves.
Are they delicious?
Bosong, are you living here?
Yeah, here is fine.
Earning money without spending it.
Why do you want to earn money?
You've already won lots of champions and rewards.
The rewards were absolutely in his dad's pocket, not his.
But why do you want to earn money?
- Buy MU game ticket. - The price is soaring.
It's probably not available even if you've got money.
In fact, I want you to ask the soccer team...
if they can get the tickets. You've got buddies there.
Since you ask me,
and invite us to have barbecue,
- I'll do it for you. - Thanks.
Help yourselves.
- You too. - Ok, drink it.
Chen Xiaoxi, Chen Xiaoxi.
Let me help you.
=Reading in School
Lu Yang, don't cover my bro's drawing with graffiti.
Look,
I've raised the ideological level of the bulletin.
A girl...
- is reading "yellow press". - Don't move, Xiaoxi.
Erase it.
Do you think Chen Xiaoxi and Wu Bosong are really in love?
Absolutely, they've already made it public.
Wait, Jiang Chen, we go home...
Give me a minute.
Bye.
I note a certain tension in the room.
- Are you mad at me? - Let me go.
Please don't.
I planned to give it to you on Saturday when we're out.
but... here you are.
- The jersey autographed by Rooney. - I don't want it.
- And I cancel the trip on Saturday. - Why?
We've got an agreement,
and it's very difficult for me to buy the jersey.
I wanted to work part-time to get ticket,
- but run into Wu Bosong there, so... - How much it cost?
200 yuan.
Enough?
Don't follow me all the time.
Is it necessary to treat me like this?
Is it because I like you,
- so you blow up at me at will? - Did I force you to like me?
No,
you didn't,
it's me who was too amorous.
That's right.
My whole life is too long and I wouldn't only like you.
Bro, may I do my homework in your room?
As you wish.
Bro,
tell you something,
A girl in my class said she liked me.
But...
next day, she was playing with another boy.
Did she go too far?
Cut the crap, do your homework.
Bro,
are you in a bad mood today?
Scratched by the puppy.
Why I've never met it before?
I'm really mad this time.
I'd rather be a dog than talking to him now.
But I'm scared he'd really be angry with me.
What if he never talk to me?
I mean, I'm always scared if someone brushes me off.
No, no, Jiang Chen is not someone.
I'm just more afraid of him than of anyone else.
What do you mean?
I mean...
his anger will make me more nervous than anyone's anger.
Because I don't know if he is angry,
so, I don't know if I should be nervous now.
Do you think I am a pussy.
How about the tickets?
I lost them.
Lost what?
I lost the notes.
- You deliberately lost them, didn't you? - No, Jing.
Do you know that's my breakfast money for several months?
- I buy breakfast for you. - No.
I...
- Hey, you should do exactly what you said. - Of course.
- Have you got tape? - I have.
But not for you.
Don't be messing around, do your job.
Chen Xiaoxi,
Liu Xinxia's calling you.
Jiang Chen,
Do you think Miss Liu called Xiaoxi...
because of something with Wu Bosong?
I don't care.
Yes, it's none of your business.
I care.
Then why you talked about it?
Just chatting between classmates.
If Chen Xiaoxi and Wu Bosong really fall in love,
at least we'll have a couple among us.
- There may be another couple. - Shut up.
Saturday is Xiaoxi's birthday.
If they have a date that day, maybe a relationship will start.
Recently, Xiaoxi's crazy for the soccer game ticket,
but I think it's hopeless.
Chunchun'll have a concert here that day.
If I give Wu Bosong a hint...
I can give him a hint.
and anyway, Wu is so sweet to Xiaoxi.
I don't care about the relationship,
Miss Liu,
Wu Bosong should go to the Olympics,
so he can't be distracted by these stuff.
I've sent for Xiaoxi and Bosong,
we'll ask them seriously when they come.
- Miss Liu, I'm here. - Come here.
This is Chen Xiaoxi, and he's Wu Bosong's dad.
- He's the coach. - And his dad.
- Where's Bosong? - Are you coming here to catch him?
- Is it discovered that he's living in the grill? - What?
Living in grill?
- I mean... - Xiaoxi, cut the crap, tell us the truth.
He's working in a grill and sleep there.
Idling all the day and not seeking advancement.
Uncle Wu, it's not the truth.
Bosong is excellent.
Everyone in our class adores him.
On the surface, he looks careless and indifferent,
but he's in fact no time to get on with us because of swimming,
- that's why he's apathetic. - He must focus on swimming.
He's been focusing on swimming.
Every time I see him,
he's either coming out of the natatorium,
or is going there with swim gear.
Once, we're playing together and everyone wrote their secret,
He wrote on the slip that he wanted to eat Huoguo.
We didn't get what he meant,
he said he couldn't eat anything at will as a swimmer.
So, he's not eaten Huoguo for years.
Maybe you think he should be like this,
and no big deal to give up Huoguo.
But, have you ever thought that...
he also needs friends and to play with them?
He's just a common high-school student.
As his teacher,
I too think swimming should not be his whole life.
Yes, he's not a fish.
Here you are.
Hi, what do you want?
=Send to Jiang Chen:
Jiang Chen, I want to forgive you first.
=Lu Yang
Hi, Lu Yang.
Do you know where I can get the ticket of the concert?
Take it.
A swimmer can't eat Huoguo in restaurants, can he?
Today, you can.
Can I use seasoning?
No races recently, of course you can.
Bosong,
Am I too strict with you?
When I was at your age,
I was always occupied with nothing, and didn't know what to do.
But, now,
I've just realized...
I should have put more efforts then.
Pushing you so hard,
because I don't want you to regret in the future.
Dad...
Drop it.
Enjoy.
Don't let the boys smell Huoguo when you go back,
their noses are as sharp as dogs'.
Especially my bro, like a sleuth.
- Chen. - What?
Is it possible our shop will open up branches in the future?
Stand a good chance.
There'll be a national chain,
So, our daughter will be the "princess of trotters".
- "Princess of trotters"? - Yeah.
Bull shit.
- Wait, What's the date of today? - 26.
Tomorrow is her birthday.
How do you forget all about it?
You forget it, too.
No wonder...
she asked for 500 yuan a few days ago.
She wanted to watch the soccer game of...
MU
- So, you have to buy the ticket quickly. - OK.
- I go there. - Quickly.
Xiaoxi.
Look what dad bought for you.
And...
there are two.
=The Asia Tour of Manchester United in 2006
Hangzhou, China
Whom do you want to go with?
Thank you, dad.
So...
- is your dad great? - Yes!
In fact, MU is my favorite soccer team.
Speaking of MU, it...
Still in "cold war"?
Jiang Chen, I've got a problem. Can you help me?
What problem?
The answer of this one is wrong.
No wonder I can't resolve it.
Suppose the iron chloride and ferrous chloride in the liquid...
as X and Y,
According to EC method, 3X+2Y=...
My gosh, what an easy problem she's asking!
Easy? I can't understand it at all.
Hi, Wu Bosong.
- Did you go home last night? - Yeah.
I met your dad yesterday,
and had a serious conversation with him.
He told me.
Can you help me? Jin's been brushing me off.
You deserve it.
How dared you squander her money?
Xiaoxi.
Xiaoxi, let's go out tomorrow.
- I'll... - Chen Xiaoxi,
I want to use your tape, OK?
OK, I'll find it.
- Xiaoxi... - Enough, I know.
I told you I know it. Don't bother me.
=Chunchun's Live Concert
Ticket Office
They're sold out.
=Chunchun's Live Concert
Ticket Office
Lu Yang,
can you get the tickets from your buddy?
They've been sold out in the ticket office.
Wait, someone just returned a ticket.
Only one, and the seat's not good. Do you want it?
Hi, Jiang Chen.
Meet at the gate of stadium at 7 next evening.
Chen Xiaoxi, Chen Xiaoxi.
Have you got the tickets?
They're difficult to buy, aren't they?
- Yeah, I've got only one. - It's OK, I've got tickets, too.
Xiaoxi, what's going on there?
You've stayed for a long time in the morning.
Come out quickly!
I'm washing my hair.
- You never wash your hair at weekend. - Just wash my fringe.
=The Asia Tour of Manchester United in 2006
Hangzhou, China
Why is he so late?
- Ask him. - I don't dare.
- He's handsome. - Yeah.
- Come here with your girl? - Maybe not. Go to ask him.
We go together.
Hi,
Do you come to the concert with your girlfriend?
Yeah.
Let's go.
When will it begin?
Where are you?
I'm at the stadium.
Why can't I see you?
- The game is about to kick off. - Game?
Yes, MU's game, which you want to watch.
I see. Stay there, I'll come for you.
You're here at last.
=Entrance
Little girl, your tickets are fakes, You were deceived.
- Many scalpers sell these fakes here. - Fakes?
How could it be false?
My dad got them with a lot of money.
- Can you check them again? - Not necessary.
No security threads, absolutely fakes.
- Check them again, please. - We can't.
Drop it.
Let's go.
Chen.
The tickets you bought for our daughter...
- are they expensive? - No.
I bought them from a scalper.
Guess how much?
150 yuan for each,
and buy-one-get-one-free.
- Get one free? - Yes.
That's cheap.
=The Asia Tour of Manchester United in 2006
Hangzhou, China
Drink?
But, wait, I want to burp.
OK.
Done.
Give it to me.
Pretty?
- Thanks for walking me home. - Never mind,
My home is here, too.
Happy birthday.
Jiang Chen.
"The Secrets Written Down on Slips"...
What did you write?
- It was secret. - But I can tell you mine first.
I wrote:
I like you.
You're thick-skinned.
So what's yours?
"I don't want to play this game."
=I don't want to play this game.
=I like Xiaoxi.
Jiang Chen,
I've got something to ask you,
and you must tell me the truth.
Don't lie to me because of face-saving.
Go ahead.
That day, after we quarreled...
and I threw away your notes,
did you go back to school and pick them up?
Did you?
No.
Must be picked up by someone on duty.
So you went back there for them that day...
even you're crying like that?
It's money, after all.
Where is the money?