Manchester united is coming to Hangzhou for a friendly match.
=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
I would like to go with Jiang Chen.
Chen Xiaoxi and Wu Bosong are really being dating?
=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
Jiang Chen, please wait.
You know,
=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
if Chen Xiaoxi and Wu Bosong are really being dating.
At least there is a couple between us, right?
=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
This is for you.
How much?
=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
For a lifetime,
you are not the only one I will love.
=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
I really got angry this time.
I am a puppy
=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
if I talk to him anymore.
Let's see what I've bought for you?
=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
Look.
=Manchester United Asia Tour 2006, Hangzhou Station.
=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
Wow.
=Manchester United Asia Tour 2006, Hangzhou Station.
=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
Wow.
Thank you, dad.
=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
The secret written on notes.
What did you write?
=Previously on "A Love So Beautiful"
=I don't wanna play this game.
=Episode 9
Please Attention, My Fellow Debaters.
=I am in love with someone. But I won't tell you.
=I love Xiaoxi.
=I don't want to play this game.
Good morning.
What a big periorbital dark circles.
Did you become a thief last night?
No. I didn't.
I studied until late last night.
So you don't have to copy my homework today.
No.
Absent again.
It's so good to be an athlete that you don't have to go to class.
Are you still angry at me?
Be quiet. I have something to tell you.
Some leaders will come to inspect our school next week.
We want to organize an activity
to show off everybody's talents.
I have no talents.
But you have.
No, I haven't.
But other activities
can be helpful for learning?
So I arranged a debate contest for you.
To exercise your critical thinking skills.
This will be put in the charge of the monitor for the time being.
Li Wei, have you already finished listing the participants?
Teacher, Qiao Lu and I are make sure to attend.
But I haven't asked Jiang Chen and Zhao Jinhan yet.
Jiang Chen. Zhao Jinhan.
You two go to communicate with Li Wei later.
Are there any others interested in it?
Join Jiang Chen's team. Hurry up.
Ok.
If anyone interested in it, just let Li Wei know.
You've been keep silent for the whole day.
It's unlike you, Chen Xiaoxi.
Failed in the weekend dating?
No.
Then for what?
I made a mistake.
What mistake?
I thought this note belonged to Jiang Chen.
But it belonged to Wu Bosong.
What?
It is so unexpected.
It made me so agonising.
Okay.
So what are you going to do?
I don't know.
Let me think about it.
What should you do?
What's wrong?
Don't look back.
Wu Bosong is there.
Are you gonna keep hiding from him all the time?
You are classmates.
Meet regularly or frequently.
How can you?
Besides, I don't think it's a good idea.
I know.
But if I speak frankly,
maybe we are not friend anymore.
Or else,
you can try to date with him.
Look at him.
He is a handsome boy.
And he also has a good body shape
with winning dozens of thousands yuan for a single competition.
You know what that means?
Almost can be a contractor of a store.
One competition for one store.
Do you think I am that kind of woman?
Countless stores.
Then let me think about it.
Screw you.
But in my mind, Liu Xinxia is a big supermarket.
Okay. Class is over.
Dismiss.
See you.
Let's go back home together.
Li Wei is waiting me in the lecture theatre.
We are going to discuss something about the debate competition.
Okay. Then I go back home first.
You don't know what I've given up for you.
Let's go. Go back home.
My supermarket is leaving with another one.
What a couple.
Don't you dare say it again.
The hostess of the supermarket has changed.
How dare you!
Bosong.
Why are you staying here everyday?
Did you have a fight with your little girlfriend?
See you.
- Jiang Chen. - You forgot your draft book there just now.
Thank you.
I think we should readjust the order of the debate.
Can we go to the lecture theatre for
further discussion after school?
Okay.
It has been so long time I haven't go back home with Jiang Chen.
Are you envious?
Just join the debate team.
How can I?
I even can not argue with others.
You can be a support crew.
Dealing with the water serving or something like that.
Make Jiang Chen can see you everywhere.
Do you need someone to help you
to do some notes as record,
to serve you water or something like that?
Don't bother.
Did I ask you?
Let Chen Xiaoxi join you.
She has never attended debate competitions before.
She is so curious about it.
Okay.
Is there any problems?
It's okay.
Zhao Jinhan.
Let Chen Xiaoxi join you to do some record.
Okay?
Okay.
Chen Xiaoxi.
Why don't you have a try?
Me?
How about this?
Let me start with my opinion.
We are arguing against this time.
My opinion is,
although the school record is very important to students.
But what more important is personal quality.
Just like our famous litterateur,
Qian Zhongshu.
He only scored 15 on his math test.
But he still becomes a great litterateur.
That's right.
For example,
the best Wu Bosong in our class.
He only scored 9 on his math test last time.
But he won the nationwide champion.
I think Chen Xiaoxi's point is good.
Continue.
And...
Now he becomes a nationwide champion.
It's already very successful.
It also means...
There is no need for him to worry about his life anymore.
It's not that he doesn't need to worry about it.
It is he's going to have a great career.
Because he has a good start.
A good start.
I'll go first.
Jiang Chen, wait for me.
See you.
Why did you suddenly say you wanted to go home?
Are you mad?
No.
Is it because I mentioned about Wu Bosong,
then you got mad?
No, I haven't.
Dad, here.
Have you ever attended debate competitions?
What?
Debate competitions.
Debate competitions?
To be frankly,
my eloquence is unexceptionable.
I did a great job all the time.
Do you have any key to success?
Stand up.
What happened? You can't find the TV remote?
Key to success. Firstly,
to take action at unawares.
What's wrong?
Key to success. Secondly,
overwhelming your fellow debaters with vigour.
Key to...
Don't go.
Mum.
Why my socks are not pairs?
None.
Hurry up!
You are going to be late.
Forget the socks.
Now I will play the positive side to open debate.
We think that...
The one and only task for students
is study.
Scores
is the only criterion for inspecting this task.
And also the most basic task.
Not go back home yet?
I am ready to go.
You wanna go back home on foot?
Yeah.
Do you want to go somewhere for a ride?
This is Jiang Rui's new bike.
I help him to try it.
I want to go to the riverside.
Let's go.
Will you go to the lecture theatre tomorrow?
No, I won't.
Why?
No reason.
Chen Xiaoxi.
Be careful.
Can you ride a bike by carrying people?
Yeah.
Let's change if you can.
Your legs are so long. It is hard to ride you.
Be careful.
Blue ocean. I am coming.
This is river.
What are you doing?
Taking off my shoes.
It must be very comfortable to get into the water.
What's wrong?
I think maybe it is not a good idea.
So I...
Why there's such a big hole on your sock?
I couldn't find my socks this morning.
I've already said it wasn't a good idea.
Hey! You're going too far.
Isn't it the time when a well-mannered boy
should give his coat to a girl?
Look, Jiang Chen.
I have no arms.
Jiang Chen.
Wait.
Wu Bosong.
Bosong.
Are you finding me?
Xiaoxi.
Are you okay?
Let me have a look.
Oh no.
I am not a doctor.
Let's go.
Let's go to the medical room.
It's okay.
Just a bruise.
It's not a big deal.
But he is going to run prizes few days later.
Is it okay?
Just a bruise on the forehead.
It's not a big deal.
You can back to the classroom later.
Excuse me, I still have something to deal with.
Wait.
I've seen the note you wrote.
Sorry, I am not into you.
I can understand if you hate me for this.
Please don't.
Do you take it seriously?
I just wrote it for fun.
Really?
No one will play such a silly game seriously.
Do you know how many gifts from girls I will receive
everytime I finish my competition?
You scared me out of my wits.
What?
Is it really so horrible?
Yes!
I will be ripped by your fans.
I guarantee that you won't be ripped by them.
Don't touch my hair.
Watch out my hair style.
Don't worry.
You will always be my bro.
See you.
Xiaoxi.
You mentioned about Wu Bosong last time.
I think that is a good point.
You are more familiar with him.
Could you please do me a favor?
To collect materials as much as you can.
Then we can get to this debating point much deeper.
Maybe it will be helpful in the competition.
Okay.
How about you and Wu Bosong?
We've talked about that. It's fine now.
That was a big mistake.
However, I feel something wrong about it.
What's wrong?
It's fine.
What do you think about Wu Bosong
as you two are deskmate?
I think...
Wu Bosong...
is very nice.
Why?
Because he doesn't need to attend classes.
As you sit in front of Wu Bosong,
what do you think about him?
The hero of youth. Starting from scratch.
How highly you think of him!
It's none of your business.
Shut up!
How dare you!
Lu Yang.
Wu Bosong is specialize in swimming.
And you?
Are you a coquettish cat?
Miaow.
Wu Bosong.
Come here.
Let me ask you some questions.
You start learning swimming when you are six, right?
Were you swimming by crying at that time?
Even couldn't confound water and tears.
No.
I felt comfortable in the water when I was a kid.
Maybe you were too young to remember at that time.
Were you broke your legs at ten?
And thought that you could no longer swim?
And then with your own perseverance,
you are back to the top.
No. I didn't break my legs before.
How about arms?
Have you ever suffered from phobia or something like that?
Feeling sick at the sight of water.
Or want to knock your head against walls when you hear a shot.
Bulimia.
Anorexia.
Yeah. Yeah.
Let me think about it.
Okay.
Hurry up!
I will get cramps if the water is too cold.
Well, I do not bother you.
I will be rooting for you.
Would you like some water?
Just put it there, thanks.
Yesterday, teacher said the topic of this debate is quite common.
She hoped we can prepare it from some new perspectives.
I think what Xiaoxi proposed last time...
the point about Wu Bosong is good.
He is famous in the national wide.
And he is also our classmate.
It's more closer to our lives.
So I asked Xiaoxi to prepare some materials.
Xiaoxi, have you prepared?
In my opinion,
it is better to take historical celebrities as example.
Wu Bosong can't even get there.
What?
Are you talking about historical celebrities?
Wu Bosong will be a historical celebrity
after a hundred year.
And you are just a name on a tombstone.
It's our debate competition. None of your business.
So what?
It's fine.
Let's hear more from everyone.
I think this point is quite good.
But we can take it from different perspectives.
Listing some historical celebrities as examples.
Then we can make a good comparison.
What's wrong? Collywobbles?
There is something wrong...
with this drink.
Stop drinking.
Xiaoxi, it was you!
I don't know what's going on.
It doesn't matter who bought these drinks.
Take her to the medical room.
Take her to the medical room first.
Chen Xiaoxi.
Take that bottle of drinks with you.
It's not your problem.
Qiao Lu asks for leave for poor health.
But the debate competition is coming tomorrow.
Which one can take Qiao Lu's place?
Chen Xiaoxi.
She helps them do the preparatory work all the time.
She can do it.
Okay, Chen Xiaoxi.
Get ready for it.
Jiang Chen.
You can coach her after classes.
Okay?
I will try my best, teacher.
Lu Yang.
What are you running for?
Come back!
You've learned how to run away now, Lu Bien.
Where's Da Lei?
You and Da Lei are no more friends now?
Zhao Yue.
I've gave you money already.
It was not enough.
You have to pay me more this time.
I have no money.
Are you kidding me?
Not enough.
Who's he?
Who are you?
I will show you who I am if you dare to come over.
I tell you what...
I never strike a woman.
I will let you leave today.
Let's go!
Hurry up! Let's go!
Lu Yang.
Give me a hand please.
Let's go.
You have to confess right now.
Yeah.
It's not a big deal.
There's no need to make everyone here.
Cut the crap.
I was in poor health when I was a child.
My mom wouldn't let me go out for fun.
Then I just played games at home by myself.
I liked Contra so much.
Like, I've played it again and again.
I was very thin and weak at that time.
And they always bullied me at school.
Zhao Yue was one of them.
I was so scared at that time.
Then I've got an idea.
There are two characters in Contra.
One is called Lu Bien.
And the other one is called Lei Ze.
And then I called myself as Lu Bien.
Lei Ze as Da Lei.
When Zhao Yue was bullying me,
I told him that Da Lei would get back at him.
I didn't know how Zhao Yue known that
Da Lei was a figment of my imagination.
And he always mock at me with this
by saying there was something wrong with my mind.
People were even less willing to play with me since then.
There once they took off my pants,
and threw me into ladies' room.
I just feel too embarrassed to tell you.
I didn't have many friends when I was a child.
But I am so happy that I can make friends with you now.
It's just a piece of cake.
Sounds like you've killed someone in your childhood.
Everyone has a friend from imagination when he was young.
I used to imagine Hua Lun was my boyfriend.
Bought me something delicious every day.
Yeah. I also had a fantasy that I was Bai Niangzi.
By sticking a broom on my butt as a tail.
And finally got a good beating by my dad.
By contrast, I'm so embarrassed.
My pants were taken off by others.
It's not a big deal.
Everybody has experienced that before.
Young man,
tell your story.
I was changing my clothes in the dressing room last year.
And went out for training.
And then...
I found out myself without swimming trunks.
Awesome.
And you?
It was a summer vacation in my childhood.
I drank my mother's osmanthus wine slinkingly.
And then I was drunk.
And rang neighbor's doorbell.
Stayed at their house by singing "Mr. Black" all day long.
Whose house?
Yours.
Why I wasn't at home?
What did you want to do if you were at home?
What did you want to do to our Jiang Chen?
Thank you.
Hello.
Curiosity kills the cat. Just one.
Here.
Thank you.
Hello.
Which movie did that boy choose?
Eh...
Here is the thing.
He is my big brother.
And his mental state is not so good recently.
My mom asked me to watch over him.
I can't...
Fine. Just choose a seat.
This one.
25 yuan.
Thank you.
You are so beautiful.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
I feel like vomiting
at the thought of going on stage this afternoon.
Don't worry.
I'll clap for everything you say.
Don't you have a competition this afternoon?
Yeah.
What's wrong with you today?
Your smile seems like you are going crazy.
I went for a date yesterday.
How about that?
Tell me about it.
What's wrong?
I am so nervous.
I want to pee.
Nervous for what?
You're not the ostrich.
Let's have a try.
The score only can prove that...
What's next?
I'm so nervous.
I want to pee.
Good job.
Hello, coach Wu.
We are reporters from Metro Sports.
We would like to do a interview with Bosong, is that okay?
Sorry, not today.
Dad, I gotta go.
I still failed to catch the competition.
Why are you here?
Are you okay?
Are you asking me?
It's all because of you.
Because you put diet pills in the drinks.
Be careful next time.
The other two arguing. Do you want to go to the college?
Do you need a good grade to go to college or not?
Have you prearrange that...
you will have a bright future if you go to college.
You will sure to succeed in the future.
We think...
go to college can not...
No.
It's hard to say go to college will be successful or not.
The people who obtained great achievement,
were always good in studying when they were young.
Such as the father of aviation in China, Qian Xuesen.
The father of cloning, Tong Dizhou.
And the founder of phenology, Zhu kezhen.
And so on.
They were all got high score in study when they were young.
So we can definitely figure out that,
One's school record is a great impetus to one's achievement.
Excuse me. The other two arguing,
what's your opinion about this?
We think...
=Wu Bosong
Let me give you an example.
My classmate, Wu Bosong.
I think everyone knows him.
What's the score does he usually get in the exam?
The math paper was just handed out this morning.
He only got 5 points.
But how about his score in the 100-meter freestyle?
Fifty second eighty-four.
How many national championships has he won?
27 times.
Compared with him,
all of you can get a higher score.
But who can say that...
I will be more successful than Wu Bosong in the future?
So...
Everyone has his strengths and weaknesses.
Judging someone by school records
is very...
one-sided.
It's very one-sided.
In our opinion,
school records can't decide
if you will be successful or not in the future.
Instead, the key point should be...
the students themselves.
Wu Bosong.
Have you won 27 times of national championships?
No, just 7 times.
Mr. Black.
Forester say hello to you.
Salute to you.
Your eyes are as wide as bells.
Your ears are like antennas.
Mr. Black.
What's going on?
He is so drunk.
Salute to you.