Try it.
Is this safe to drink?
It's clean.
It's rainwater.
It's not like the acid rain
we get in the city.
Where did you learn all this?
From my coach.
Miss Vinluan.
Help!
Yen, let's follow the sound.
The plane where my daughter
is on board crashed.
Maybe you can expedite
my release papers?
Did you know that Amanda
is getting released from jail?
The court approved her petition.
I want you to do something.
I want to take revenge
before she gets freed.
I'm glad to see you again,
Yenyen.
What about Raichu?
Did she survive too?
I haven't found her yet.
I'm here with Red.
Meet Red.
This is not going to be easy.
You must do the first aid
I taught you, okay?
Amanda, how did it go?
What did the warden say?
Are they going
to let you out sooner?
They can't let me go
without my release order.
Dindi, I want to look
for Eden myself.
I want to do something
to find her.
The days pass by without a word
about the investigation.
I feel like...
I feel like I'm dying
from fear and worry.
My daughter is missing.
And we can't do anything
but wait.
I want to find Eden.
Amanda, God has mercy.
Is that her?
Yes, that's her.
Okay, I'll take care of it.
Just give my family the money.
Make sure you do
what you set out to do.
I got it.
Okay, keep me updated.
Good!
Are you sure?
Very good.
Rina?
Who were you talking to?
Was that your brother?
He's just asking
how we're doing.
Why? What did he need this time?
Didn't I tell you not to talk
to him anymore?
He brings nothing but trouble.
Look, Victor. He's still family.
Okay? At least he can do things
you're not capable of doing.
What is that supposed to mean?
You know what I mean.
Rina, I'm warning you.
Your brother thinks
like a criminal.
Don't make our problems worse.
Our son is missing.
We have to prioritize him!
How dare you!
And what? You're blaming me?
Are you telling me that
I'm not thinking of our son?
Look, I love Red.
I can't bear to lose him too.
So do everything you can
to find our son!
Do everything in your power,
Victor!
I'm glad that we found my coach.
I'm not too worried anymore.
Someone is going to help us out.
She's a good motivator.
You're lucky to have her.
I owe everything to her.
I owe her all my achievements
in life.
Not only in sports
but in my private life as well.
Even my dream of being
with my mom again.
I nearly gave up several times.
But she's been reminding me
to keep fighting.
That's why I owe her a lot.
She always reminds me
that I can still be with my mom.
That all my dreams in life
will come true.
I heard they're going
to release you soon.
That's true.
You've been here
for a long time.
8 years...
for something I didn't do.
Are you still denying
what you did?
Do you need anything?
Yes.
I just want to cut your throat!
Don't try to fight me.
I just want to give you
a souvenir.
So you won't forget us.
You beast!
If you're trying to kill me,
you're wasting your time
because I've long been dead!
My daughter is my only life,
but they got me locked up here!
They separated me from her!
They took my rights
to care for my child!
I lost the small hope I had
of being with her again!
I don't know
if I'll ever see her again!
All of you are shameless!
All I need is my daughter!
I need my daughter!
I want to be with her!
I want to get out of here
to be with my daughter!
Hey! Stop this!
Why are you fighting?
How dare you!
- Give me that!
- Monsters!
Give me that!
Monster!
My daughter.
That's enough!
You're all evil!
My daughter!
Stop!
Let's go!
Get up!
Good job, guys.
Keep on working together.
Good thing that you're working
together to achieve your goals,
especially in this situation.
You really need
to work together.
Your presence
makes a difference.
I'm just here to give you
instructions.
You guys do the hard work.
But we have to build
our shelter for now.
The sun is about to set.
Go on, Red.
Okay, Coach.
Come on, Yen.
- Let's go, Red.
- Go.
Go, guys. Go.
You came here to tell me
that you failed?
I'm sorry, Rina.
I didn't know
that Amanda would fight back.
I underestimated her.
Why didn't you get an inmate
who could get things done?
Rina, I can try again.
I'll find someone else to do it.
What for?
What for? It's too late!
She's about to get released!
So annoying!
Why don't you just
get her killed?
No.
That will end her suffering.
I want her to pay.
I won't leave her alone.
Not until she regrets
everything she did to my family.
- Coach.
- How are you feeling?
- Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm doing fine.
I drink all our water, though.
It's okay, Coach. I'm glad
you're feeling better.
It looks like it's about
to rain.
Rain is essential.
You have to collect rainwater.
So we can have something
to drink.
But for now, you have
to finish building our shelter.
You can collect the rainwater
using the tarp.
- Go on, hurry up. Get to work.
- Okay.
Move.
- Let's go, Yen.
- Okay, Coach.
Coach!
Coach, we finished it!
- All right!
- Good job, guys.
Good job.
I'll be right back.
I'll get some bamboo sticks.
Coach, how are you feeling?
I'm okay.
Don't worry about me.
I'm doing fine.
I told you
I could get through this.
I got this.
I can't die here.
Coach.
I'm just like you, Yenyen.
We're the same.
I have a family to come back to.
My daughter.
My daughter, Yenyen.
I have to go back to Ana.
She'll be 18 next month.
I want to be there
on her birthday.
I want her to celebrate
her birthday with me.
It's going to happen.
You're right.
Just like how your long-time
dream will come true.
Your dream of reuniting
with your mom.
Yes, Coach.
Being your friend
is not a coincidence.
My daughter was separated
from me for a long time.
Long time.
Probably that's why God
got us together.
To help each other out.
You helped me when I was longing
for my daughter.
And I was there for you when
you were longing for your mom.
Coach, I'm so grateful
to have met you.
That's why we're going to fight.
- Yes, Coach.
- We will never give up.
We will get out of this island
alive.
Yes, Coach.
Yen! Look at this!
Hurry!
I'll be right back.
- Go on. Go to him.
- I won't take long.
- What is it?
- Look what I found!
Bamboo!
What is it for?
We're going to use this
to save the rainwater.
- Oh! You're good!
- Right?
But it's a little small.
We won't be able to save
a lot of water with this.
Wait. Wait here!
Here, balloons!
What are we going to do
- with that?
- To save water.
Hurry up. Lift it up.
All right!
You're great!
Okay, let's try that.
We don't have to think about...
There it is!
- It's raining!
- Yes! Just on time!
Hurry up, I'm parched!
Me, too!
Hold this.
Okay.
Let's fill this.
There you go.
They already have
my release order.
I can get out of jail now.
Have you packed your stuff?
I have your room ready.
I'm not sure if I want
to get out of here.
It's been days,
and we still haven't heard
about the plane crash.
And how Eden is doing.
Amanda.
She's the only reason
why I want to get out of here.
Why I want to continue living.
Where is she?
Do I still have someone
to go home to?
We have water now!
Yes! We have a water supply now!
- Finally!
- It's good now!
Is it?
Let's go!
Let's bring this to Coach.
Coach!
Coach, we have some water now.
- Coach.
Coach.
Coach!
- Coach!
Wake up!
What?
Coach, wake up!
Coach!
Coach! You said we'd go home
alive!
- Yen!
- Coach!
You said we'd all go home
together!
- Yen!
- Coach!
Right, Coach?
Coach!
Yen!
- Yen!
- Coach, you promised me!
Yen! Yen, that's enough. Yen!
Coach, you promised me!
Yen, she's gone.
Stop it.
Yen, stop.
Coach!
Coach, you said we'd all make it
back to our family.
Coach!
You said...
You said you'd be there
for your daughter's birthday.
Coach!
Coach, wake up!
- Wake up!
- Coach!
Wake up, Coach!
Don't leave me, Coach!
- Yen, that's enough.
- Coach!
Yen, stop.
Coach, wake up!
Yen, that's enough!
Coach!
Wake up!
Yen.
Coach!
Yen, that's enough!
Amanda, I prepared
your favorite food.
I'm sure you missed it.
Let's go.
I don't want to go home yet.
Why?
I want you to bring me
to someone
who can give me an update
about the search.
Okay.
Let's go.
It's a good thing that
you're aware of your mistakes.
Now, learn from it.
That's the difference
between winners and losers.
Losers cry their hearts out.
They drown themselves
in frustrations.
But winners know
how to get up...
and fight.
Why is this happening?
Why do I keep losing
the people I love?
When I was ten,
my mom was taken away from me.
And now,
my second mom...
is gone too.
Do you think we can get out
of this island?
We might die here too.
Don't think like that.
Why not?
Do you still think
someone will rescue us?
You keep telling me
that someone will rescue us.
But where are they?
We've been here for days!
And no one came to rescue us.
And if they will rescue us,
why...
wht not when my coach
needed help?
Red...
The world has forgotten
about us.
It's over.
We're going to die here.
We're going to die.
No!
No, we're not going to die.
I can't accept that!
Can't you see what's going on?
We have no hope!
We're helpless!
Maybe you're right!
Maybe we have a little chance
of survival.
But I won't give up no matter
how small our chances are.
I will keep fighting.
And we'll get out of this island
alive.
I will do everything I can.
Hopelessness is our enemy.
And we can't let that defeat us.
Think about someone
who's waiting for us.
Think about your mom.
My family.
I promise
that we'll make it home.
We can all celebrate together.
This is all Amanda's fault!
She ruined our family!
And I will never, ever,
forgive her!
You said you'd give me a call
for an update!
I've been instructed
to tell the passengers' families
that the longer
the search takes,
the smaller the chance
of finding them alive.
What?
If we get this done
and get to sail out,
what do you think
we'll see first?
A ship!
Help!
- Help!
- We're here!
Help!
- Help!
- We're here!