She's not like this before.
She loves our children so much.
That's why she's changed
into a horrible person
and taken revenge
because she's in pain.
But it's wrong to take it out
on someone innocent.
My sister didn't do
anything wrong.
- Mom!
- Aunt Amanda!
Get out of here!
You have to go,
or you'll get hurt too!
- Mom!
-No, Mom. We're not leaving you.
Get out of the way!
- Mom, you have to stop this!
- Get out of the way!
You have to stop!
Angelo won't like this!
Please, stop!
I won't let you be happy!
- You can't be happy!
- Stop!
Red! No!
No!
I'm sorry.
I had no idea about what
she's been doing.
What kind of husband am I?
Dad, don't be too hard
on yourself.
She's determined to hide
what she's been doing.
She doesn't want us to know.
Eden, we've done you a lot
of wrong things.
We took you away from your mom
and your child.
She lost a lot of blood.
She needs you right now.
You have to stay by her side.
She wants to talk to you.
Please forgive me, Amanda.
Red was right.
I looked for someone to blame.
I couldn't bear to lose my son.
I was blinded by my anger.
It's all my fault.
Amanda, I want to ask you
a favor.
Take care of our children,
Amanda.
- I will take care of them.
- Promise me...
You will take care of them.
Rina, all your pain will be
wiped away.
You can rest now.
I didn't get to protect your mom
against herself.
And she ended up hurting you
and Eden.
She's gone now.
I should have died too.
I don't deserve to be here.
- No, Dad.
- After I failed, Red.
- I failed.
- Dad, I don't want to lose you.
I need you.
Your grandchild needs you.
I was blinded by my anger
and pain, Amanda.
Please, forgive me.
Take care of our children,
Amanda.
You're more deserving
to be loved by our grandchild.
My mom is with my brother now.
Bye, Mom.
Bye, Angelo.
May you both be at peace.
Chloe's sleeping now.
Red...
I know you're still grieving.
I've been too busy
since we got Chloe back.
But I want you to know
I'm always here for you.
I'm still thinking about Mom.
I don't understand.
No matter how many times
she hurt us...
Even if she took our baby away
from us...
Even when she almost
killed us...
Red.
I still love her so much.
I miss her so much.
I wish that all of this
didn't happen.
I wish she learned to forgive.
I wish she had focused
on her love for me
instead of her anger.
If she did, we would have been
complete.
She would still be here with us.
Red...
Don't hide what you feel for
your mom from me.
I won't get mad.
I've forgiven her.
And it's not wrong
to love her still.
Because she's your mom.
And it only means
you're a good son.
And I know you will be
a great father to our daughter.
We can't change
what's been done.
And we can't bring back
the people we've lost.
But...
We can still make up for
everything we've been through.
As long we stay happy and heal
ourselves from all this pain.
While we're building
our own family.
I don't want to do anything else
but make you happy.
You and Chloe.
I will never forget
all the good things
you've done for me, Lucho.
You gave me a new life,
new strength, and new courage.
He's been generous to Red
and me, too.
Although he did some bad things,
he showed you how much
he love you, Amanda.
Thank you, Lucho.
Thank you so much
for loving me...
and my family.
I want to start a new life
with my family
that's been reunited
because of you.
Lucho...
You will always be in my heart,
even though you're already gone.
Chloe!
I need to check on Chloe.
Yen.
Chloe!
Red, I thought my dream
was real.
I thought someone
had taken Chloe from us.
Sometimes I can't
forgive myself.
I should have known
where she was.
I'm her mom.
I should have known what
was going on with her.
I shouldn't have given up on her
when they told me she was gone.
I should have kept looking.
You are her mother,
but you're not God.
I know you're trying
to handle everything.
But you will fail sometimes.
And that's okay.
It won't make you less
of a mother
because of a few mistakes.
Just like me,
I'm her parent too.
And I'm not perfect either.
That's why we're here.
To help each other.
So we could raise her properly.
Red, don't leave us, okay?
Never.
I know you will never
abandon our child, either.
As you said, we can't
take back the past.
But you know what, Yen?
I'm confident.
Now that we have Chloe back,
I know you will be
the best mom for her.
Aren't we going to lose her
again?
It won't happen again.
It's just a dream, okay?
Thank you, Red.
I can stare at her all day.
Me, too.
I want to wake her up
to see her beautiful eyes.
Don't wake her up!
She just fell asleep.
Don't bother her.
Don't worry.
We'll make up for all the times
she's not with us.
We'll fill her
with our love.
She'll forget all the days
we're not with her.
And we will never lose
her again.
Yen?
Mom.
Wow, you're smiling.
Of course, I'm so happy
right now.
Because we're complete now.
You, Red, and Chloe are here.
Amanda.
- Yes?
- The police officers are here.
What can I do for you?
We're investigating
your husband's illegal business.
And we're trying to find out
if you have something to do
with his criminal activities.
You have to come with us
to the precinct for questioning.
Okay, I'll go with you.
Stay here.
Everything's okay now.
What?
My lawyer accompanied me
to the precinct to explain
that I had nothing to do
with Lucho's illegal business.
Thank God.
I also told them I was willing
to help them
with the investigation.
So they won't have a reason
to suspect me.
Did Uncle Lucho hurt
a lot of people?
You know what, dear.
You're Uncle Lucho
has his own world.
And he hurt a lot of people.
But he...
He was good to me.
He helped me up,
so I wouldn't lose hope.
Especially when I'd already
given up on life.
I will be grateful to him
all my life. But...
I can't accept the money
he left me.
I can't use it.
What are you planning to do?
I'll try to help the family
that he hurt.
I will try to correct
all his wrongdoings,
even if he's already gone.
Just like you...
I also want to start a new life.
Who would have thought
I would meet the woman
I'd share the rest of my life
with on this island?
I survived this island
because you were with me.
And you taught me how to live.
The simple life
I've had with you
is the happiest moment
of my life.
We'd been through a lot
before we got to this point.
We had a lot of problems.
But with all those problems
we had,
I'm only sure of one thing.
I love you so much,
Eden Sta. Maria.
And I will love you for
the rest of my life.
Red, thank you,
because you changed my life.
I thought there was no place
for love in my life.
Because I had a lot
of things to do.
A lot of people depended on me.
But when I met you on this
island...
you taught me how to smile....
to laugh.
You gave me a reason
to be happy.
That's why I'm so grateful
to you, Red.
I love you so much, too.
Each day I spend with you
is like being in paradise.