Now you're saying you love
the son of that witch
who made my life miserable!
I will be in pain forever!
Mom, I love Yenyen.
What I feel for her is real.
Sorry, but I can't obey you
this time.
Red! Red!
Rina won't leave you alone!
She will take it out on you.
She will forever make you pay
for something that I didn't do!
She's not the one
who killed him.
She's still the reason
Angelo died.
Yenyen has nothing to do
with her mother's crime.
But still!
If you love Eden, you'll have
to love her family too.
And how can you love Amanda?
I'm perfectly fine.
- Really?
- It was just an act.
I convinced him, right?
See, he didn't leave.
So you were faking?
You weren't sick.
You lied to me.
Mom, I love you so much.
I'll be sad without you.
Mom, I need you.
Yen!
- Yen.
- Red, why are you here?
You didn't pick up your phone.
I was worried about you.
You should go.
My mom might wake up.
She'll be furious.
Yen, I'm not leaving, okay?
I'll talk to her.
I'll tell her
that we love each other.
And we shouldn't get involved
with their problem.
You can't do that.
They'll get hurt.
I love my mom.
Don't you love me?
Just leave, please.
I'm not going anywhere.
What is he doing here?
Mom, he's leaving.
You have the nerve to come here!
What do you want?
You want to poison
my daughter's head
to carry on this relationship?
No, Ma'am.
I came here to explain.
I don't need your explanation.
Just leave.
Mom, please stop.
I'm not going anywhere
until you hear my side.
Please hear us out.
I love your daughter so much.
And I can forget
everything that happened.
Oh, wow!
Let go of my daughter.
Go inside the house!
If you can forget everything,
well, I can't!
You should leave.
Hey! Go on while I can
still hold my temper!
I won't leave
even if you get mad.
Really? Are you that brave?
Are you a tough guy?
How about this?
Do you want this?
Are you leaving or not?
I'm leaving because I don't want
any trouble.
Not because I'm scared.
And I know you're not capable
of hurting anyone.
Yenyen told me
that you're a good person.
I don't believe
that you killed my brother.
Don't try to fool me.
You're just like your mom.
You all think
that I'm a criminal.
A murderer!
I don't believe that.
I don't believe
you're capable of doing that.
Get out of here.
Go!
Leave!
Eden, can you stay still?
I'm getting crossed-eyed
while looking at you.
I'm worried about mom and Red.
I don't know
what's going on downstairs.
I can't ask your mom
to come inside.
I don't think I have the right
to get involved.
I did her wrong.
So now she's mad at us.
I'm sorry, Auntie,
for dragging you into this mess.
I shouldn't have told you
about my relationship with Red.
What are you talking about?
Hello!
I'm your Aunt.
You shouldn't keep secrets
from me.
I was touched
when you told me your secret.
That's probably why your mom
got mad at me.
Because you told me your secret
and you kept it from her.
That's why she's giving us
the cold treatment.
But still...
I shouldn't have gotten you
involved.
Don't worry about it, Eden.
No matter what you go through
in life,
your mom and I
are always here for you.
And don't get upset with her,
okay?
It's only natural for her
to feel like that.
She was hurt.
But I know she will forgive you.
Okay?
I hope so.
How's Red?
Did he respond to your messages?
I'm calling him.
He's not answering his phone.
I'm sure he's with Eden
right now.
Don't try to control him
too much.
He might rebel against us.
You know how kids are nowadays.
They'll want to get away
if you try to control them.
Okay, I'll keep that in mind.
You should go.
You might get late
for your meeting.
Yes, Dear?
Auntie, I think you really need
to know about something.
Know about what?
It's about Red.
He went to see Eden.
How did you know that?
Get out of here!
I saw everything, Auntie.
And I saw what Eden's mom
did to him.
Mom...
I love him.
We love each other, Mom.
No.
That's not true.
Take back what you said.
Take it back.
It's not true.
Mom, I'm sorry.
Sorry, Mom.
Mom, how are you feeling?
I made you some coffee.
To ease your drunkenness.
I'm sorry, Mom.
I didn't expect Red
to come here.
Don't worry, I'll talk to him.
He'll listen to me.
Red is kind.
If he's really kind,
he'll stay away from you.
He'll listen to his parents.
He won't disobey them.
Red loves his parents so much.
When we were on the island,
we often talked
about our parents,
especially when we were sad...
when we were losing hope.
That's why I fell for him.
Because we both love
our parents.
And when I told him
that you were in jail,
he didn't judge me.
Who would have thought
that his parents were the ones
who put you in jail?
I'm having a hard time too.
I don't know what to do.
I'm so confused.
Mom...
I didn't betray you.
I just fell in love.
Who do you love more?
Is it me or Red?
Mom, I can love both of you.
No.
You can only choose one.
What?
Your mom is making you choose?
Yes, I don't know what to do
anymore.
Eden, I saw
how much you love Red.
You even had to fight Sabina
for him.
Are you going to give up now?
And you love each other.
I know.
But what am I going to do
with my mom?
You can only choose one.
If you choose him,
I will accept it.
Even if it kills me.
She told me she was hurting.
I can't blame her for it.
Red's family
made our life miserable.
There you go again!
It's his family.
Not him.
And it's a once-in-a-lifetime
chance to find the one.
I know.
But there's a problem.
Our parents are against
our relationship.
Eden...
Why don't you try to fight
for what you want this time?
They can't do anything about it
anyway.
Fight now, come what may later.
Something like that.
Miss Emma, where's my mom?
She left with your Uncle Zandro.
Did she say where she's going?
I heard her talking to Sabina
on the phone earlier.
She's going to...
Eden's house.
I think that's what she said.
And then she left.
Hey!
Who is that?
Who's throwing rocks
at our house?
Who...
You again?
You and your brother!
What do you want?
Do you think I don't know
what you did?
What?
You threaten to kill my son.
What a drama queen.
Threaten to kill him?
I just scared him off
so he'd stop
bothering my daughter!
You still threaten him.
Perhaps you want me
to make a threat.
Oh, aren't you doing it already?
What do you think you're doing?
You're throwing rocks
at our house.
That's nothing, Amanda.
- Zandro...
- Yes?
Show her what you're about
to throw at her house.
Did you like my bomb threat?
Both of you have the nerve
to do this.
You're going to involve
innocent people?
Why don't you get yourself
blown up too?
No. It's all your fault, Amanda.
I wouldn't be here
if you didn't do anything
to my son.
You know that I hate losing.
You killed my firstborn already,
and now you want to do it
to my other son too.
- I won't let you do that.
- You're annoying.
I'll kill you first.
Mom!
So she's here to the rescue
again.
What's going on here?
These two had lost their minds!
- What's that?
- Look at them.
Why is he holding a grenade?
- What is that for?
- I will shove it
in your sister's mouth!
Ma'am Rina, please stop.
You'll get other people hurt!
Are you going to kill
the whole village?
Why don't you just swallow
that thing?
It will fit your mouth better.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
Mom!
- Uncle Zandro.
- Red, please.
Stay out of this.
You'll get a lot of people hurt.
Stop this!
Why? What about what she did
to you?
Didn't she try to hurt you?
Miss Amanda didn't do anything.
She was just feeling
overwhelmed.
Let's just go home.
Put that away! Come on!
Red, relax.
It's just a toy. See?
You both are crazy!
Stop messing with us!
We'll call the police!
Next time, we won't just mess
with you!
I will bring the real thing!
- Oh, really?
- Mom.
- Mom, stop.
- You see that?
I'll get you, Amanda!
Amanda, time to eat.
Go ahead. I'm not hungry.
Amanda, I'm sorry for keeping
the truth from you.
I was really going to tell you
about it.
You just found out
before I get to tell you.
When I was still in jail,
I often thought of getting out.
Because I wanted to be with you,
especially my daughter.
I always thought...
that I'd finally have peace.
That I'd be happy with Eden.
But why is this happening?
It hurts, Dindi.
I wish I didn't get out of jail
if this is the life
I'll have out here.
No, Amanda!
Eden loves you.
She won't choose anyone
over you!
I don't believe that.
I'm prepared
for what's going to happen.
I know that Eden will choose Red
over me.
I will accept it,
even if it kills me.
Mom, why did you go there?
You and Uncle Zandro could get
in trouble because of that!
Amanda threatened to kill you.
What do you want me to do?
Just sit still?
Where did you hear that from?
Who told you?
It doesn't matter
how I found out.
I can't let Amanda mistreat you!
Look at what happened.
Was I wrong?
She can't do anything about it
now!
What are you two doing?
It's late at night,
and you're still arguing!
This is the only time
I will tell you this!
Stay away from Eden, or else!
Or else what?
You're going to disown me?
- Go ahead!
- Red! Red!
Don't talk to your mom
like that!
She's just concerned about you.
And to our whole family!
What would people think?
That we don't care
about your brother's death?
Why are you thinking
about what people might say?
That's not all!
We're hurt
because of what you are doing,
of your relationship with Eden.
So please, stop!
No!
I love her.
And I will fight for her.
And I don't care what you
or anyone says about it!
- What?
- Victor! Victor!
No, no!
Don't hurt him.
No, he's not our enemy here.
Raichu, I feel awful about this.
Is this what I'll give my mom
in return
after all her sacrifices?
I'm making her cry.
Eden...
She's hurting right now,
but it will pass.
Once she sees how happy you are
with Red, she'll be fine.
And most parents are like that,
anyway. Right?
I don't want to force her
to accept my relationship
with Red.
I don't want to hurt her.
I don't want to make things
worse for her.
Won't you regret letting Red go?
Remember, no parents would want
their kids to suffer.
You're right.
Hello, Red.
Yen.
How are you?
I'm sorry about what happened.
I'm sorry about what my mom did.
But that's not the only reason
I called.
Can I see you tomorrow?
Yen.
I'm sorry,
I just really missed you.
I want you to know that...
I'm not giving up
on our relationship.
No giving up, remember?
I don't care even if my parents
disown me.
Red, don't talk like that.
They're still our parents.
We owe them our life.
That's why we shouldn't hurt
them.
Yen, they want us to break up.
If we do what they want,
we'll end up hurting.
And we both know, that's...
That's unfair to us.
We don't deserve that.
They don't deserve to get hurt,
either.
No one does.
But they have sacrificed a lot
for us.
We should love them.
Can you be happy
while they're hurting?
Because I can't.
My mom has been through a lot.
I can sacrifice everything
for her,
even our relationship.
I heard you when you said
you wanted to meet with him.
Don't try to deny it.
I met with him
to break up with him.
I chose you, Mom.
I don't want to hurt you
anymore.
Are you happy now
that you broke up with Red?
See?
You're not happy.
Beat your record.
If you don't beat your record,
you and Red stay together.
- Eden!
- How are you feeling?
I'm okay.
When was your last menstruation?
You know the right girl
will come at the right time,
from the right family.
Eden is out of the list.
Eden, I hope there won't be
a second line.