Our baby's alive, Red!
I knew it.
Yen, I'm sorry.
Sorry for convincing
you to move on.
I thought our baby was gone.
We don't deserve this.
I wonder how Chloe's doing.
What are they feeding her?
What kind of milk are they
giving her?
She's been separated from us
for several months now.
I'm sure she's just like you.
What matters is that
we can get her back now.
She will be with you soon.
I hated you before because
I believed
that you were the reason
my daughter died.
That's the opportunity Rina
was waiting
to ruin our relationship.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Red, this is not the place
where they took me.
I asked around.
They said Thelma always
moves around.
This is where she lives now.
Mom!
Our baby's not here.
I want to stay hopeful.
But it seems so hard.
We can't give up, Yen.
For our child's sake.
For Chloe.
Hello?
It's Mom.
Mom, where's our baby?
Don't get too excited.
- My baby!
- Don't hurt her!
Rina, don't harm the baby!
Who is that?
Is that Amanda? Amanda?
Amanda, hello!
Don't hurt our baby!
Well, you know it's all up
to you, Eden.
I won't hurt your baby if you do
everything I say.
I will give you everything
you want.
Just don't hurt our baby!
Give her back!
Everything?
Do you promise?
Will you give me everything
I ask for?
Will you do everything I say?
Fine.
I will give your baby back if...
you give me your mother.
Give me Amanda in exchange
for your daughter.
Deal?
You're crazy!
You must be out of your mind
to think
that I will hand you my wife!
No way!
Oh, shut up, Lucho!
I have the upper hand
right now
because I have something
very valuable to you.
Mom...
Mom, please.
Please give us our baby back.
Don't you care about me anymore?
Is that why you're doing this
to me?
You too, Red!
Didn't you abandon me too?
You made me feel like
I'm worthless to you!
Rina, Rina.
Please, surrender.
We'll help you. I'll help you!
You, too!
You're a liar!
You abandoned me too!
So all of you will feel
my wrath!
Enough of this drama, please!
Okay?
Bring Amanda to me in exchange
of this baby.
And don't even try to call
the police.
Because I will find out.
You will be in more trouble.
So, bring Amanda here
to Zandro's hideout.
At 6 PM.
Baby and I will be waiting.
Please, leave the child out
of this.
Right, baby?
Shut up!
My baby, Red!
I said, shut up!
Shut up!
Are you hungry?
Are you tired, baby?
Well, I don't care.
They say you're my grandchild.
You have Amanda's blood!
You're worthless to me.
Do you understand?
Shut up.
Shut up, baby.
You're just a means to an end.
You're worthless to me.
I'm sorry the subscribers cannot
be reached.
Please try again later.
I can't contact her anymore.
We have no choice.
We have to alert the police.
You can't!
That's a good idea.
We should let the police deal
with your mom.
No! You can't report her
to the police!
She might hurt Chloe!
She's just saying that.
But once the police officers
get there,
she can't do anything anymore.
Your mom will be captured.
What if it doesn't end that way?
You heard her, right?
She seems out of her mind.
I don't want to upset her
any further.
She might harm the baby.
If we're not going to call
the police, what do we do then?
I'll handle it.
I'll talk to her.
I'm still her son.
She's mad at you, remember?
How can you be so sure
that she'll listen to you?
She might be mad at me
earlier over the phone.
But once she sees me in person,
she might change her mind.
Son, son.
Dindi's right.
At this state, she might not
listen to you.
I'm afraid of what she can do
to you.
I'll come with Red.
We'll talk to her.
You can't talk sense
into her anymore.
She chose to use violence.
We can do the same!
And then what?
Are we going to corner her?
What if she hurts the child?
We're not sure if she'll give us
the child.
What if she kills the baby
no matter what we do?
Please, don't talk like that!
Eden, I'm sorry. But I know
how she thinks.
Don't be like that.
Why are you making us lose hope?
We haven't seen Chloe yet.
I'm just being realistic.
Stop.
That's enough! You don't need
to argue.
There's only one solution
to this problem.
I will go to Rina.
We'll give her what she wants
in exchange for your child.
Mom, you don't need to do that.
It's the only way.
I won't let you do it.
Lucho.
Amanda, I can't let you
put yourself in danger.
He's right, Amanda.
And we all know what Rina
wants to do to you.
She's not doing this
so she can have a conversation
with you.
She will kill you!
Then she can go ahead
and kill me!
Mom!
Mom, don't talk like that.
Let's think of another way.
Not like this.
I don't want anyone to get hurt,
Mom.
But we can't find another way.
This is the only way.
This is the only way to get
your child back.
It's all my fault anyway.
This feud started because
I fought back with Rina.
This is our feud.
We started this.
So we have to end
this ourselves.
This wouldn't get this far
if I hadn't been so selfish...
if I didn't play her game...
if I didn't take revenge.
So let me do this.
Let me make up for what I did.
Mom!
I've made a decision.
You can't change my mind.
The two of you should prepare
because you're about to get your
baby back.
- Mom!
- Amanda.
Amanda.
Mom, I can't let you do this.
Mom! I can't let you do this!
I'm scared for your life.
I want us to be together.
I want to be with you,
with Red and baby Chloe.
I can't let you do this, Mom!
Yen, I'm sorry, it's my fault
that you don't have
a complete family.
No, Mom!
If only I'd forgiven Rina
and moved on with my life
with Lucho,
this wouldn't have happened.
Mom, it's Rina
who can't forgive.
Not you.
She might be acting like this
because I didn't ask her
for forgiveness.
Eden, even if I didn't kill
her son,
I failed to protect Angelo.
That's why Rina got hurt.
I will talk to her.
I'll talk to her and ask
for her forgiveness.
I'll ask her to stop
getting revenge.
So no one else can get hurt
anymore.
Mom, what if she doesn't listen
to you?
I'm willing to give my life
in exchange for your child.
Maybe that's what I need to do.
This is what I need to do
so we can all have peace.
Get my gun ready.
Yes, boss.
What are you planning to do?
Are you going to have
a gunfight with my mom?
What do you expect me to do?
Do you think I'll just let Rina
take my wife?
What if Chloe gets hurt?
Amanda is all I care about
right now!
I will kill for her!
You don't need to do that,
Lucho.
Amanda, you can't make me
useless.
I can't let you risk your life!
I need to protect you!
I know what you want to do.
You don't need to kill anyone
for me.
Lucho, I'm grateful to you.
For everything that you've
given me.
You've given me a new life.
You support everything
I want to do.
But that's enough.
Our revenge ends today.
We have to stop using violence.
It won't do us anything good.
Look at what happened.
The child's life is in danger.
So, what do you want to do?
Are you going to face Rina
alone?
Is that okay with you?
Do all of you think it's okay?!
You have to let me do this.
I will talk to Rina. I will ask
for her forgiveness.
I will come back to you if
God listens to my prayers.
I will come home to you.
We will have a complete family.
Red.
Have you talked
to your mom already?
I couldn't change her mind.
She said she would give her life
so our family could be together.
Do we need to get this far?
If only I could do it instead
of her.
I'm also willing to give my life
for our child.
Can't we get her back
without anyone getting hurt?
I only want simple things
in life.
I just want our family
to be together.
Why does it seem so hard to get?
We can't let Auntie Amanda
risk her life.
I will try to talk to my mom.
She thinks we abandoned her.
So if I have to kneel
in front of her
to ask for forgiveness, I will.
Red.
Yen, I don't want my mom
to become a murderer.
She's done a lot of bad things
already.
I don't want her to commit
more crimes.
Red, I know you want
to save your mom.
I know that you don't want her
to get hurt.
I understand.
I also don't want anything bad
to happen to her.
But we both know she has to pay
for everything she's done.
Mom, answer the phone, please.
I thought I was going die
on that island.
I thought I wouldn't
see you again.
No, don't say that, son.
You know...
God is so good.
He's so good.
He won't let that happen to us.
We still have a lot of plans
to travel abroad.
You still have a lot of dreams
to achieve.
We're always here for you, son.
I'm back!
My son!
I'm not going anywhere.
I'm not going to leave you
again.
I will continue my studies here.
A hundred percent! I will
take care of you.
I'm staying here. I'm not
going anywhere.
I'm not sick.
It will be better for you
to stay in the US.
No.
I'll stay here with you
and dad, okay?
You're so stubborn!
Of course, where do you think
I got it from?
I got it from you!
Now that I'm here...
I'm going to make you laugh
every day.
I'm going to make you happy.
I miss you, son.
I miss you so much.
There are a lot of women
out there.
Yenyen is just one of them.
You talked to Amanda,
didn't you?
She put those ideas
in your head!
Right? Am I right?
That woman was sentenced
to jail because she was guilty!
You're the child of the woman
who killed my son!
- Mom!
- You wench!
And now you're going
to take my other child!
Mom, stop!
- Stay away from my son!
- Mom!
- Stay away from him!
This is the only time
I will tell you this!
Stay away from Eden, or else!
Red?
I'm sorry.
I don't know how things ended up
this way.
Red.
I know she loved me.
She took care of me.
How could she hurt me like this?
I took her side, Yen.
I took her side.
She betrayed me.
How could she do this to me?
Why did she do this to me?
Red...
Lucho?
Where are you going?
Are you going somewhere?
I can't do it, Dindi.
I can't let Amanda deal
with that crazy woman alone.
You know what Rina did
to the midwife.
What else can she do once
she sees her mortal enemy?
But what about the baby?
She might get hurt
if you get involved.
What about Amanda?
She's my wife.
She's my only concern.
Lucho, please.
I love Amanda so much, Dindi.
I waited a long time for her.
I thought we would never
be together.
But fate made us cross paths
again.
I still can't believe
that she's my wife now.
That's why I will do everything
to defend her.
To protect her.
I can't lose her, Dindi.
I won't let that happen.
I don't want her to get hurt,
either.
Because she'd been through
so much to survive.
This can't end like this!
Go on.
Go and follow them.
But please, Lucho.
Bring my sister home alive.
Mom, no one should get hurt.
You can be free again.
No! Free?
Me?
I will have to run all my life.
Because the police will be
looking for me.
That's what's going
to happen to me.
But you know what,
I don't mind.
As long as I get my revenge
for Angelo.
I'm begging you.
Please save her again.
Save our family.
I won't let you win, Rina.
I can't let you have Amanda.
Run! Amanda!
Our baby!
Lucho!
The baby!