If Red is okay and nothing
terrible happened to him.
Red and I had an argument
because of that Amanda!
Because Amanda...
That's enough, Rina!
If there's anyone to blame here,
it's you!
If you only had left
Amanda alone,
she wouldn't have met our son.
You didn't see Eden there?
No. She wasn't there.
Eden!
Are you hurt? What happened
to you?
Yenyen is nothing but a bad
influence on him.
Even on the island, she was
always causing him trouble.
According to what
Sabina told me,
I don't think Yenyen is a good
influence on you.
Maybe we can still work on...
Sab, if you think that just
because Yenyen and I broke up
we can easily go back to how we
were now, you're mistaken.
I can only offer you friendship.
You must be forcing yourself
on him again.
You're making yourself
look dumb.
The nerve of you to call me
dumb.
When I'm one of the honor
students in this campus.
But you're just a good swimmer!
Haven't you learned your lesson?
You're doing the same thing
again and again.
You have to do a reality check,
Sabina.
It will be better if you tell
her the truth yourself.
I know your mom won't be able
to accept it right away.
But it will be more painful
if she finds the truth
from someone else.
You have to stop
before it's too late.
If you can't fight
for your relationship.
What are you doing here?
I saw you with Yenyen earlier.
It didn't seem like you were
trying to avoid her.
So what's the deal?
Were you lying to me?
I thought you didn't like liars?
Sab, whatever I have going on
with Yenyen,
you have nothing to do with it.
Stay out of it, please.
I have something to do with it.
Look, I really am curious
about this Yenyen girl.
Now Sabina has told me
a lot about her.
But then again, if she's the
girl you like, then so be it.
I won't stop you
from liking her.
What?
Look, Red.
I cannot control your feelings,
okay?
You are old enough to decide
who you want.
Just don't lie to me.
Now tell me, what is so special
about this Yenyen girl?
Do you need anything?
Mom...
Our tournament is about
to begin.
I might get busy, so I just want
to let you know.
I might come home late these
coming days.
Okay, I understand.
Be careful.
Eden...
I know we've been apart
for a long time.
And you became closer
with your Aunt Dindi.
Because...
you two were together
while I'm gone.
Eden, you sometimes feel
awkward around me, right?
But I'm your mom.
I'm here now.
I hope you won't feel
embarrassed to open up to me.
Don't hesitate to share
your secret with me
or any unpleasant feelings.
Okay?
This is your chance to tell me
the truth.
Nothing, Mom.
Well, we're still friends.
When she tripped at the gym,
I only helped her up...
like how she helped me
while we were on the island.
That's all there is to it.
But, why do I feel that...
Then you're wrong.
Yenyen and I are just friends.
Excuse me, guys. I'm tired.
I need to rest.
Okay.
Auntie, are you serious?
Are you going to push that
Yenyen to be with Red?
I cannot control his feelings.
If he likes her, then I can't do
anything about it.
Now, instead of wasting
your time hovering over him...
If you really want to do
something about it,
then do something about it.
So you can get back together.
Auntie, I'm doing everything
I can.
But it's not working.
Try harder.
Eden, someone's calling
your phone.
Eden, should I answer it?
It could be important.
Hello?
Who is this?
This is Eden's mom.
Hello?
Who is this?
What do you want
from my daughter?
Who is this?
Mom, who was that?
I don't know.
He didn't answer.
There's no name on the caller.
It's just a blue heart.
Who's that?
It's Blue, my classmate.
Maybe he's shy that's why
he didn't respond.
I'll just call her back.
Excuse me, Mom.
Hello?
Didn't I tell you to text me
first before calling?
My mom might recognize
your voice.
I'm sorry.
I just want to tell you that Sab
is spying on us.
You know, we really need to be
careful.
I just realized it earlier
while talking to my mom.
I tried to tell her the truth,
but I couldn't do it.
We just need to sacrifice
a little more.
We need to endure this, okay?
Red, I don't think
I can do this much longer.
I'm afraid of what could happen.
Do you want to meet tomorrow?
Let's talk about our plan.
Let's meet at Cafe Polca
around 2 pm?
I'll see you there?
Okay, see you.
Did Eden tell you something?
About what?
I don't know.
Didn't she say anything?
I just noticed that she's acting
weird lately.
Maybe you're just
not used to her yet.
She acts like that sometimes,
especially if she has a lot
of school activities.
Don't mind her.
Mom, I'll just ask permission.
I'm going somewhere.
It's Saturday.
Where are you going?
Raichu asked me to go with her
to buy swimwear.
Okay. Be safe.
Okay, Mom. Bye.
Bye, Auntie.
Stop, stop, stop.
Mister, follow that taxi.
She's on her way. She'll be here
in about five minutes.
Are you sure they have good
food here?
I need a distraction because
of what's happening
between Red and I. My God.
I'll just get whatever
you're getting.
Is that...
Is that Red?
What is he doing here?
Are you sure you didn't mess up?
He might tell the cops.
I don't want any trouble.
With all the beating
I gave that fool,
I'm sure he learned
his lesson by now.
He said he'd pay next week.
Well, he has to.
I don't want any trouble
with Mr. Akashi.
Yes, Sabina.
What can I do for you today?
Auntie, I'm in a restaurant
right now.
And guess what?
Red is here too.
And he's having
something set up.
I think he's doing this
for Yenyen.
Is it something like a date?
Are they on a date?
Yes, Auntie.
I know Red.
When he's having something
set up,
it means there's something
special.
Why don't you come here?
So you can meet Yenyen
once and for all.
Yenyen.
Red, what is this?
To welcome you back to Paradise.
Didn't you say you wanted to go
back to the island?
So I brought the island to you.
- Red.
- Yenyen,
no one will bother us here.
We'll be together.
And just be happy here.
Really?
I'm looking forward
to meeting her really.
I want to get to know
who this Yenyen is.
So they don't need to hide
their relationship from us.
Right?
They're hiding their
relationship.
I'm okay with it anyway.
Anything that will
make my son happy.
I just want to do something
special with you.
And I just want to thank you
for giving us a second chance.
And most especially, I want to
take away your stress.
I know how stressed you are.
We're going through a lot
because of our family.
By the way, this is for you.
Red, come on. You don't need
to do this.
You know...
every day that I'm with you
is always special.
Come on, let's eat.
Thank you, Red.
No problem, Yen.
There.
- That looks good.
- I hope you're hungry
because they have great food
here.
I'm really starving.
You might be hungry.
Is this your first time here?
Mister, can I ask you something?
What is it?
Can you tell me where you drop
off the young lady earlier?
Where did she get off?
Why? Who are you?
I'm her mom.
We have an emergency.
My phone is dead.
I can't contact her.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
I drop her off over there,
at Cafe Polca.
- Just straight ahead?
- Yes.
Okay, thank you.
How are you?
- Hi, Auntie.
- Hello.
I was right. Red and Yenyen
are here.
Fantastic.
Oh, there she is!
I'm finally going to meet
Red's girlfriend.
Are you for real?
Are you going to approve it?
Of course.
Whatever makes my son happy,
I'm happy.
Okay.
Let's go.
Miss!
Do you know where Cafe Polca is?
Over there. Go straight ahead.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you, Red.
You made me happy today.
I'll do everything
to make you happy, Yen.
You'd been texting me
that you were starving.
Red?
Mom, what are you doing here?
I'm here to meet Yenyen.
So, you're Yenyen?
Ma'am Rina...
Sir Victor.
I'm Eden.
I'm begging you.
Please don't put my mom in jail.
Remember this.
I will seek justice
for my son's death.
I will make sure your mom
will rot in jail.
I won't leave her alone.
Good afternoon, Ma'am.
I know you!
You're a criminal's daughter!
This must be your daughter.
Eden, right?
Eden?
You're Yenyen?
You're the daughter of the woman
who killed my son!
- Mom!
- My God!
- Mom! Mom stop!
- You monster!
- Now you're with my other son?
- Mom stop!
Get away from my son!
- Get away from him!
- Mom! Don't hurt her!
Get out of here!
Why are you hurting my daughter?
Get your daughter away from my
son!
Mom. Me and Yenyen love each
other.
What is this boy saying?
You two are in a relationship?
Mom...
Don't cry.
Answer me.
Red is my boyfriend, Mom.
Mom...
Come here.
- Come over here.
- Don't hurt her.
- Stay here.
- Stay out of this!
You too!
Get your daughter away from my
son! Get her away!
Stay out of our business!
Don't get involved!
What are we still doing here?
Let's go home.
You have a lot to explain
to your dad and me.
Mom, I can't leave her here.
What are you talking about?
Come on!
What don't you understand?
Mom, I love him.
We love each other, Mom.
No. That's not true.
You can't love him!
Her mom killed your brother!
Are you giving that woman
much importance?
There are plenty of women
out there!
Don't you get that I like her,
Mom?
When we were on the island,
I knew that I loved her!
- No!
- I hope you understand!
No!
You don't know the pain I felt
when your brother died.
Didn't you get hurt
when your brother died?
Why can't you understand?
She killed your brother!
Red!
I know!
I know, okay? I was in pain too!
You were not the only one
in pain, Mom!
And I'm sorry!
But are you sure?
Are you sure that
she's to blame?
We don't even know!
What are you talking about?
What do you mean by that?
That woman is guilty!
She was put behind bars!
What do you think?
Did you think the court
would lie?
But Mom, there's no evidence
against her!
No! That's enough!
I don't want to hear this
anymore, Red!
Let's go home.
Stop! This is enough!
Enough!
I feel like she loves Red
more than she loves me.
She didn't even think about
how I would feel.
But Amanda, you have to think
about her situation.
They were on that island alone.
And they fell for each other.
Not knowing that their parents
hate each other.
Why does it seem like
you know a lot?
I need to see Yenyen.
Her mom might be hurting her.
You will forget about her
eventually.
- It will pass.
- Of course not!
Sorry, but I can't let you
have your way this time.
Red!
Red...
Mom, I'm so sorry.
Mom, I will do anything
you want.
I'll do whatever it takes
to make you forgive me.
Stay away from Red.
Forget him.
Red, why are you here?
You have to go. My mom might
wake up.
She'll be mad.
What is this boy doing here?
Do you want some of this?
Are you going to leave or not?