Days pass by without
hearing anything about
the investigation.
I feel like dying
from fear and worry.
Is that her?
Yes, that's her.
Didn't I tell you to stop
talking to your brother?
He brings nothing
but trouble.
At least he can do the
thing you're not able to do.
I just want to
slit your throat!
Good job, guys.
Keep on working together.
It's good that you two
are getting along...
especially in
a circumstance like this.
You need to work together.
If you're trying to kill
me, then I'm not afraid!
Because I'm already dead!
You took my right to take
care of my daughter!
You took even the tiny
hope of being with her!
Why didn't you pick an inmate
who could get things done?
Someone who could
do what I want!
Rina, we can try again.
I'll find someone
else to do it.
What for?
It's too late!
They're going to release
that woman out of prison!
Bamboo.
What is it for?
We can collect
rainwater in this.
Coach!
We now have a
supply of water!
Coach, wake up!
- Coach!
We might die out here,
too, like my coach.
I can't let that happen.
Don't you see what's
going on, Red?
It's hopeless!
We might have a slight
chance of getting out of here.
But I'm not giving up,
even if it's a long shot.
I will find a way
to get out of here.
Hopelessness is our enemy.
I promise that we
will make it home.
We can celebrate together.
But how?
I don't know how.
We'll think of a way.
Right now, let's say
goodbye to coach first.
Coach,
I'm going to keep
your whistle for now.
Don't worry.
I'll give this back to your
daughter when we get to Manila.
I will tell her how kind
you've been to me...
how you helped us out
and gave us courage
while stranded here
on this island.
Even though you
were feeling weak.
I'll let her know...
how good her mother is.
Coach...
We will remember
everything you taught us
until we get back to Manila.
I hope you can ask God...
to help us.
We want to go home
to our family.
I pray...
that God will save us.
Why is this happening?
Several days have passed,
but they still couldn't locate
where the plane crashed.
Are they doing something
to find my daughter?
Are they doing their job?
Amanda, we were not the
only ones who were there.
All the passengers'
families were there too.
They said the same thing.
They still don't have any
information about the plane.
What do we do now?
Are we just going to wait?
Only God can help us now.
I want to see my daughter.
Amanda!
Amanda, are you okay?
Are you okay?
Victor, I can't
take this anymore.
Why can't we
just go to Davao?
Let's lead the search
and rescue operation.
Let them do their job, Rina.
They know what they're doing.
If they know what they're
doing, then where is my son?
Can you calm down?
Your rants are not
helping the situation.
Let's get you
something to drink.
No need.
Maybe I'm just stressed out.
I'm okay.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I'm okay.
I just want our son back.
I know.
Let's go home.
Wait.
That's Amanda!
So they really let that
witch out of prison!
Amanda!
- Hey! Amanda!
- Rina!
What are you doing?
Now is not the time, Rina!
Why?
Is there a right time to
confront the woman who
killed our son?
Rina! We came here for Red.
Learn to choose
your battles!
That's why I choose this!
I will fight for Angelo's
life as long as I live!
So let go of me because
they are getting away!
- Rina!
- Let go of me!
Amanda!
- Rina!
- Let go!
Amanda!
Amanda! Hey!
You heartless beast!
Monster! Amanda!
- Stop! Rina, stop!
- Let go of me!
Amanda!
You beast!
Will you let go of me?
That's Ma'am Rina
and Sir Victor.
What?
Your old employer?
I think so.
What are they doing here?
Perhaps they heard that they
released you from prison.
That's why they're
following you.
Gosh, they seem to be
losing their minds!
Maybe they
haven't moved on.
They're probably still blaming
you for what happened.
If we're not in this
situation, I will face them.
I will let them see
that I'm innocent.
And I proved my innocence
when I got acquitted.
But I have to think of Eden.
I can't waste my time on them.
All I care about is
finding my daughter.
What are you doing?
I'm going to make a raft.
What?
Raft.
We can use this to get
out of this island.
I saw a lot of wood out here.
Didn't you say you have a plan?
What's your plan?
Nothing.
I was planning to
make a fire again.
To signal the rescuers
that we're here.
Red.
We've been on this
island for days now.
If they had sent out rescuers,
they would have been
here by now.
Let's do something
to get out of here.
And you promised me that we'd
get out of this island.
You said we'd be with
our parents again.
So please, help me with this.
Okay.
Let's do this.
Okay, good.
Take care of this raft.
I need more wood, so I'm
going back to the forest.
I'll come with you.
Let's go.
I saw a lot of woods that way.
Which way is it?
Over there.
Hon,
breakfast is ready.
Are you still mad at me?
I would have confronted
Amanda if you didn't stop me!
I could have done
something to her!
That's the reason why
I stopped you.
I'm scared of what you can do
to her because of your anger.
Look, Hon, at this point,
I wouldn't put it past you
that you would hurt her
badly to get revenge.
And then what?
You will be a criminal?
Is that the kind
of justice you want?
Hon, let's try
to think about this.
Don't let our
anger take control.
Hasn't it crossed your mind?
The reason Red is missing
is for you to clear your mind.
And to get your mind
focused on Red alone?
So what are you
trying to say, huh?
That it's my fault
that Red is missing?
What? No!
What? That I'm getting
punished because I'm not
a good enough mother?
Is that it?
Amanda deserves to be punished!
Because she ruined our life!
She killed our firstborn child!
It's all Amanda's fault!
She ruined our family.
She ruined our life!
And I will never
ever forgive her!
You look tired.
Why don't you
get some rest?
No, I'm fine.
We'll get this done faster
if we help each other.
Ouch!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You're not being careful.
You're rushing it.
I'm trying to get this done.
I want to get out
of this island.
I don't want to stay
here another night.
I'm just worried
about you, Yen.
We need more strings
to tie this up.
I'm going to
gather more vines.
Hey.
See what I mean?
Come on, let's go
to our shelter.
Are you okay?
You must be dehydrated.
That's why you got dizzy.
Drink some water.
That's good.
I'm fine now.
I want to get
the raft done.
Yen!
Stay here for now.
Come sit down for now.
Come on.
I'll get the raft done.
I'll get it done
fast, I promise!
You must be getting
annoyed with me.
Yen,
I understand.
I know that you want
to get out of this island.
But it won't happen if one of us
gets injured or harmed.
So it's better if you stay
here and get your strength back.
Get some rest.
I'll get the raft done.
Okay? I got it.
You said you'd call me
to give an update
about the investigation.
You haven't contacted me.
I'm sorry, Ma'am.
But we still have no news.
They still can't pinpoint
the exact location
where the plane crashed.
So it's hard to do
search and rescue.
I've already heard that.
That's what you said before.
You should do your job better!
So you can find my daughter!
You have to find Eden!
Actually, I've been instructed
to tell the passengers' families
that the longer
the search takes,
the smaller chance
that they'll be found alive.
What did you say?
I'm sorry, Ma'am, but we only
want to prepare you
for what can happen.
Water?
Thank you.
I should be thanking you.
I got some rest
because of you.
Let me help you.
Let me see this.
I'm sorry I didn't
get a lot done.
I tied the wood together.
We'll be riding this, so we
should make it sturdy, right?
Are you disappointed?
You're doing it right.
It's just that...
What?
I just want to get
out of this island.
Right now!
I want to forget this nightmare!
Red,
I want to get out of here.
I want to forget everything
that's happening here.
Let's get this done!
No!
That's impossible to happen!
Do you know my daughter?
You don't know her!
She's courageous,
she's strong.
Eden is a survivor.
My daughter's been
through a lot.
She's been through
a lot because of me.
But she never gave
up, not even once!
She endured everything
without me.
So what you're
saying is impossible!
My daughter still has dreams!
She still has a long way to go.
She's not going to die.
My daughter's not going to die.
Amanda?
Amanda, what's going on?
Who are you talking to?
My god.
Amanda, what's wrong?
I don't want my daughter to die.
My god, my daughter can't die.
Everything you said earlier
will happen.
We're doing something
about it, right?
We'll get this raft done.
Even if we don't get
this done by tonight.
We'll go tomorrow.
We'll get this done.
We also need to
make paddles.
We need to make paddles
to get this thing going.
Actually, I'm excited.
If we get this to work,
we'll be out for an adventure.
It's like sailing.
I envy you.
You can stay positive
after all this.
Of course.
As athletes, we have to keep
a positive mindset, right?
It will keep us going
if we have a positive mindset.
We can envision our goals more.
That's it.
What about you?
Once we get this raft done
and get to sail out...
what do you think
we'll see first?
I think we'll find a place
with lots of people.
They will help us out.
And they will feed us
delicious seafood.
And more importantly, we'll have
a good reception there,
and we can contact our parents.
What about you? What do you
think we'll see first?
A ship!
A ship.
I hope it's a cruise ship
so we'll have a lot of food.
Red, I'm not just
dreaming about the ship!
There's a ship!
Help!
Yen! Wait!
Yen!
- Help!
- Yen, wait!
- Wait!
- Help!
- We're here!
Help!
- Help!
- We're here!
Help!
We're here!
- Help! We're here!
- Help!
Yen!
They won't hear us from here.
Let's go closer, then!
How?
Let's swim there!
Let's go!
What? Wait!
Do you realize what
you want to do?
What?
Yen! The ferry's way too far!
How are you going
to swim there?
Can we pull it off?
We'll never know
unless we try!
- Let's go!
- Wait.
Yen,
you have to think about this.
Okay?
I've been thinking for so long.
When we landed
on this island,
I had already been thinking
of a way to get out of here!
Now, we have the
opportunity!
Let's go!
Yen, wait.
I can't let this
opportunity pass.
Let's go.
Yen!
I won't force you to do
this if you don't want to!
Only one person has
to swim out there.
I'll ask the
rescuers to get you.
Wait, wait!
What are you doing?
Yen.
Okay.
If this is what you want,
we're gonna do this together.
No one will get
left behind.
Okay?
Here's the plan.
We're going to swim to them
so they can see us.
And then you'll blow the whistle
to get their attention.
- Okay.
- Okay?
Stay with me.
Don't let go.
Let's go.
Lord,
I trust in you.
I know that you'll take
care of my daughter.
Wherever she is,
please keep her safe.
Red, we have to make noise
so they can hear us.
Okay.
- Help!
Help!
Please keep my
daughter safe.
Please give
her back to me.
Please give her
back to me alive.
Help!
Keep on whistling!
Keep blowing the whistle!
- Help!
Red, we have to get closer!
Let's go.
We'll be safe now!
- We're going to be saved!
- We're here!
They've already found survivors
on an island near Davao.
They're checking who
survivors' identities.
They said there's a woman
as same as Yenyen's age.
Why the long face?
You know, you should be happy!
I have a very strong feeling
that Red is one
of the rescued survivors.
I just don't want us
to feel disappointed.
Especially you, Rina.
The recovered survivors
are still unconscious right now.
But requested videos
from the hospital
so you can check if your
relatives are one of them.
Are you following
me even here?
Why would we
follow you around?
I'm here to find
my daughter.
While you popped out of
nowhere to cause trouble.
Is she one of the passengers
of the plane that crashed?
Do you know someone
from that flight too?
Who is it?