Amanda wants to put
her past behind her.
She's now happy
with her life.
Blessing, my foot.
She can't fool me!
She can't one-up me.
I still have an ace against her.
Are you breaking
up with me again?
It's always like this.
You want to break up even
because of the small things.
We've been through a lot.
We've overcome a
lot of problems.
And in a snap, you
want to let go of me?
What is there to fight for?
Our baby's gone.
And we're always fighting, Red.
You know the Ramoses, right?
Her son, Red.
It seems that Red
is most wanted tonight.
His girlfriend asked me
where he was earlier.
His girlfriend is here?
I don't want you to
break up with my son.
Eden, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry if that's what you got
from everything I said.
I know that I have been harsh
to you and Red lately.
Maybe because I've been stressed
from the threats
I've been receiving.
You got your
enemies frightened.
Eden was here earlier.
It seems that she and Red
are having trouble
with their relationship.
But Amanda, it isn't time yet.
We have plans.
You can't be distracted.
I still love you so much.
I love you so much too.
I'm glad the two of you
have patched things up.
Thank you for letting me stay
even though our baby's gone.
We're going to let
your baby rest, Eden.
And when we bury her, you
should also bury your love left
for your mother.
Did you know what she's
going through right now?
Her baby died after
she gave birth.
What?
She said they got
into an accident
on their way to the hospital.
And she was brought
to a midwife.
Only one person can hurt
my daughter like this.
Probably she also had something
to do with the baby's death.
Sweetie...
we didn't meet,
but I'm bidding you goodbye.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I couldn't protect you
from the person who hurt you...
from your own grandmother.
I will never forget you.
And will never forget
the person who did this to you.
Because she killed you.
Our baby's gone, Red.
She was killed.
My mom killed her.
Don't worry, Yen.
Once we're both healed,
we can start a family again.
Thank you, Red,
for understanding
and for being patient with me.
I'm sure Baby
Chloe is now happy.
Because we're
still together.
We still love each other.
We love you, Yen.
Right, Mom, Dad?
Of course, Sweetheart.
Eden...
from now on, call me mom.
Okay?
Thank you, Mom.
Wait, before we leave...
I saw a restroom upstairs.
I'll go use it first.
I'll be right back, okay?
Okay.
Rina.
Amanda.
Did you also bury
someone here?
I can have you buried here.
It depends on your
answer to my question.
Why are you grumpy again?
I thought you had moved on.
Didn't you say, "I'm so
blessed to be stressed?"
Right?
What did you do
to Yenyen's child?
I knew it.
You had something to do
with her daughter's death.
I can't do that.
I can't hurt my grandchild.
Aren't you the child killer?
Not me.
You are so evil you
can do anything.
You're just putting on an act.
You want to exact revenge!
Anywhere and whoever
suffers, you don't care.
What did you do
to Yenyen's baby?
Why are you accusing me?
Didn't you curse them?
This is your fault.
That's not true.
What's wrong with you?
Amanda!
No! Amanda!
I knew it!
You still haven't changed!
You still behave
like a prisoner!
And you, you thought you're
better than me?
And you, you're wealthy,
but you have no manners!
Stop it!
Amanda!
Get off me, Amanda!
You deserve that!
What's taking your mom so long?
You know her.
I'll go check on her.
Something might have
happened to auntie...
I mean mom.
What time is it?
Gosh, long time.
Your mom's bladder
is something.
I'm hungry.
You all deserve that!
Get off her!
Are you okay, Mom?
Mom?
I won't let you
hurt my mom!
Mom?
Did you call her mom?
And why not?
I was with her
throughout her pregnancy.
And when the baby died,
I took care of her.
While you are busy
moving on with your life.
And didn't you say
that you're off to live
without your daughter?
So you won't
have any problem.
Did you say that, Mom?
You're brainwashing her.
How dare you.
Go on, Mom.
If you don't want to
care for me, it's okay.
Just forget about me.
Just leave the people who
care for me out of it.
Okay?
Sorry, Eden.
When will you move on, Mom?
I've lost a lot already.
You even got my baby involved.
I lost my baby, Mom!
I wasn't able to hold her.
To kiss her!
I wasn't even able to touch her!
Sorry.
Sorry?
Can your apology
bring back my child?
Mom, please.
Leave me alone!
Let go of your hatred.
I can't believe
Amanda came back.
And she hurt you again.
I should have confronted her.
There's no need for that.
Eden defended me.
I know it is hard for you,
but I'm glad you two have
already faced each other.
At least you were able to tell
everything you wanted.
Just consider this as a closure.
But why did she attack you?
I thought she didn't
hate you anymore?
She's just pretending!
During the party?
She was faking!
Party?
Was my mom there
the other night?
She was not just at the party.
She gave the party.
Lucho Madrigal is her husband.
She is Mrs. Madrigal.
Husband?
I'm sorry.
We don't want you to get
hurt, but your mom has moved on
since she married
that wealthy man.
She has forgotten about you.
She only remembered you
when she was threatening you.
Or when she wanted to hurt you
and our baby.
Leave her be, Red.
If she has forgotten about me,
maybe it's time for me
to forget my mom too.
So, the woman you wanted
to meet and impress so bad,
Mrs. Madrigal, is Amanda?
Will you shut up?
Fine!
She may have outsmarted me once.
But it will never happen again.
She may be powerful now
because she has money.
But I still have the most
powerful weapon against her.
Her daughter.
You really are something.
I know!
So you.
You should stop pestering me.
Find out who is sabotaging us.
I want to find out if he has
a connection with Amanda.
Yes, Rina. Actually I already
have a lead
on where the fake money
came from.
He will confess in no time.
Good.
It's our turn to take revenge.
Eden was just hurt too.
That's why she said that.
Your daughter loves
you so much, Amanda.
And she doesn't want
you to hate each other.
Or maybe she really
doesn't need me anymore.
Because she already
has her Mommy Rina.
So...
I'll talk to her.
You don't have to.
Rina has already
poisoned her mind.
That's why she's
so upset with me.
So, are you just going
to give up on Eden?
No.
I will never give
up on my daughter.
That's the reason
I came back...
for Yenyen.
We already have plans
on how to get her back.
Plans?
You don't need to
know every detail.
But rest assured,
that Eden will be with you
as soon as possible.
I heard you've met your mom.
Is it true that you told
her to forget about you?
Are you with her?
Yes, I'm here.
You should be here too.
I don't need
to be there, Auntie.
I don't want to mess
with her new life.
What are you saying?
What mess are you
talking about?
You are her daughter.
She only sees me as a burden.
That's what Mommy Rina told me.
Mom didn't deny it.
So I get it.
Please, don't force me, Auntie.
I'm okay being here.
And they treat me as family.
Yenyen...
Auntie?
Hello, Auntie?
Didn't I tell you
not to talk to her?
I'm just trying to convince her
to be with us.
It's not that easy.
I saw how Rina manipulates Eden.
Can you please avoid her?
You might tell her something
about our life here...
about our plans.
I don't know anything
about your plans.
And are you really going
to fight with Rina again?
Are you going to take
revenge once again?
Why not?
I've changed.
I'm no longer the poor
ex-convicted
they used to oppress.
Someone strong has
got my back now.
They can't bring me down.
Looks like your husband
has a bad influence on you.
Lucho saved me after Rina
tortured and threw me
in the garbage.
And after pushing
me to kill myself.
I almost got crazy.
But Lucho took care of me.
And he still supports
me up until now.
I didn't know that
you'd been through hell.
So I should take
revenge on Rina.
I will expose that woman.
So that Eden will
see her mistake.
I hope it's only Rina who will
get hurt by your plans.
What if Eden got involved?
She might stay away
instead of going back to us.
Just a bit more.
I might trip.
No.
Just close your eyes.
What have you got?
- What's your gimmick this time?
- You'll see.
You'll see.
- I'm nervous.
- We're almost there.
One more stop.
Surprise!
I want to make it up to you,
so I asked Emma for help.
We recreated what
you did for me.
Did you like it?
Of course.
But why do you look sad?
Sorry.
I really have plans
for our quality time, Red.
But Aunt Dindi called.
She's with my mom already.
I didn't want
to get affected, but...
No, I understand.
But I don't want
you to get sad.
Where's your killer smile?
I miss it.
There!
Silly.
That's the reason
I fell for you.
I sometimes miss the island.
It's so peaceful there.
We don't worry about
our problems here.
It's like we're not
in the real world.
I want to forget
all our problems.
Yen...
we don't need to be on the
island to forget our problems.
I'm here.
I'll help you forget.
Really?
I miss you so much.
I missed you too.
Wow!
Why you're so sweet.
What are you doing
here again, Sabina?
Come on, Yenyen.
Can't we be friends?
I'm here to invite you
to my birthday party.
Are you inviting me too?
Of course!
Red and I are friends.
So maybe we can
be friends too.
Right, Red?
Sab, I don't think
Yenyen is ready.
Why?
Don't tell me you're
still insecure with me?
- Sab...
- Yenyen, you already have Red.
No? Okay, fine.
I'm sorry.
Look, I'm just saying
congratulations.
Maybe you and Red are
meant for each other.
So maybe we can put
the past behind us?
Let's be friends, Yenyen.
Really?
Great! So come to my party.
So you'll have an
excuse to look good...
and dress up a little.
You know?
Once...
in a while.
I won't let them abuse me.
And I won't let them be part
of my and Eden's life forever.
So I will show Eden how
evil people they are.
Because once Eden gets hurt,
I'm sure she'll come back to me.
If you're not comfortable
going, we can just stay here.
But is it okay
if I give her a gift?
That's what you get.
You messed
with the wrong people.
Who bought that fake
money to pay me?
Is that Amanda Madrigal?
Answer me!
Can we bring Rina down sooner?
Before more people get involved.
She might hurt Eden too, and do
the exact revenge against me.
I want to take my daughter
back from that woman.
Don't worry.
We'll need to adjust the plan.