Our families are still enemies.
Isn't that enough reason for us
to stop whatever we have?
Why don't we just choose
for ourselves
and not for our families?
I hope our love for each other
overcomes everything.
Sorry, Red, but I don't want us
to ruin our relationship
with our families
by being selfish.
Yen!
It's about Red!
- Something happened to Red.
- What?
He got into an accident
with that girl.
She's at the hospital.
What?
She's at the hospital?
Why? What happened?
Red, I can't forgive myself if
something bad happens to you.
Red, please wake up.
Red, I'm going to talk to you.
No matter how hard
I deny my feelings,
my heart still says I love you
so much.
Really?
Please don't panic,
but something happened to Red.
What happened?
He got into an accident.
He was brought to the hospital.
Which hospital?
You again?
You're the one who keeps
following me.
You're like a magnet.
You stick with me.
You're like a yo-yo. No matter
how often I throw you out,
you keep coming back.
You said you would talk to me
if I woke up.
If it's true that you are here
for your daughter,
I hope she's in a grave
condition.
Aren't you going to stop?
- Oh my God, Auntie!
- Leave my daughter alone!
I will accept every
insult you give me.
But I will never let you do
anything against my daughter!
I won't move until you
talk to me.
Red, get back down!
It's dangerous!
Rina!
Stop!
Stop it, Red! Come on!
I want to be happy because
I listened to my heart.
But is it right to be happy
while our parents are in misery?
We'll find the perfect timing.
Once they've healed, we can tell
them the truth.
I cannot help it, Victor.
My hatred towards Amanda won't
go away just like that.
What do you take me for?
A balloon?
That once you pop,
everything disappears?
Especially now that she's
poisoning Red's mind.
I'd better not say anything,
Rina.
I'm tired.
What matters to me
now is Red's safety.
If something wrong
happened to Red,
that would be Amanda's fault.
Red and I had an argument
because of that woman!
Because Amanda...
That's enough!
If someone is at fault here,
it's you!
If you only left Amanda alone,
our son wouldn't have seen her!
She wouldn't have come near Red
to make us look bad!
This is your fault!
No, it's not, Victor!
Take back what you said!
I'm leaving.
I'm going to find Red
before he totally disappears.
Gosh!
Rina's always asking
for trouble!
She doesn't want to stop
bothering me.
But I won't back down!
You went there for Eden,
but you saw someone else.
You didn't see Eden, Auntie?
No.
She's not there.
Eden!
What hurts?
What happened to you?
Which hospital did you go to?
I went to the hospital
Raichu told me about,
but you weren't there.
I'm okay, Mom.
I just accompanied a friend.
That's right, Auntie.
Friend.
You were in a hurry.
I wasn't finished talking
yet when you left.
Who is that friend?
Our friend...
from swimming. Yes, swimming.
She's our teammate.
Your friend from
the swimming team?
Yes.
Why did you have to keep it
from me?
And why did Raichu have to lie
that you were in a meeting?
What?
It's okay, Amanda.
Let's just forget about it.
Nothing wrong happened
to Eden anyway.
I'm sorry, I panicked.
I got scared.
I don't know what to do
if something happens to you.
I have little savings.
I'll buy a cell phone.
So I can call you, okay?
I'm sorry, Mom.
Where's my phone?
Can I have my phone?
Here.
Pick up.
He's not answering.
He's not answering my calls!
Where's Red?
If Red was brought
to a different hospital,
I think it was Yenyen's
decision.
What made you say so?
How would you know?
The students who saw
the incident said
he was with Yenyen when it
happened.
Honestly, Yenyen is a bad
influence on Red.
Red often got harmed when
we were on the island
because of Yenyen.
I'm curious about Yenyen.
I want to meet her.
Auntie, she's a nobody.
That's why I won't be surprised
if, one day,
she'll use Red
to have a better life.
Then why does Red love
that Yenyen so much?
I don't know, Auntie.
I don't know what Red
saw in her.
Suddenly he's into her.
He's even neglecting his school
and other stuff
because of that woman.
- Red! Red!
- Red.
What happened to you?
Where did you get that wound?
It's nothing, Mom.
This isn't serious.
You got me worried, Red.
I know we had an argument
earlier on.
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry, Son.
No, Mom. I am sorry.
I shouldn't have talked back.
Sorry, I'm just confused.
Don't worry. From now on, I will
stay out of my brother's case.
I heard you were with Yenyen
when this happened.
Look.
I don't want to start anything
that we'll argue about.
But according to what Sabina
told me,
Yenyen isn't a good influence
on you.
Starting today, we decided
to end things.
We decided to part ways
and avoid each other.
You don't have to worry
about that anymore.
I was so nervous yesterday
because of what happened.
Your mom almost caught you.
Can you just avoid Red
next time?
I'm sorry, Auntie.
I can't do that anymore.
How come?
Red and I got back together.
Oh my God!
Do you know what you got
yourself into?
Your mom will get mad once
she finds out about it.
You know about your situation,
don't you?
I tried to avoid him, Auntie.
But he keeps coming back to me.
And he told me that her mom paid
someone off to expedite
my mom's case.
So he's now convinced
that my mom is innocent.
Is that the reason you got
back together?
- No.
- Then what?
I love Red.
That's why I went back to him.
I can't leave him.
What you want is impossible.
I don't think our families
will reconcile. You and Red.
And your mom and Rina.
It's the same as saying Ukraine
and Russia will reconcile.
Let's go.
- Hey! Wait!
- Mom?
I'm glad I caught you.
- What's that?
- That's for you.
Cell phone?
What?
This is just an expense.
It doesn't matter how I got it.
I won't worry anymore.
You need that.
I can call you, and you can
call me anytime, right?
You need that.
Thank you, Mom.
You're the best.
You're the best too.
Wow! She has a new cell phone!
Make sure you use it, okay?
Sabina's here.
She'll tell on us.
I'll go ahead.
Hi, Red!
Why were you talking to Yenyen?
It's nothing. She just asked me
something.
Are you sure?
And is it true that you're going
to avoid her?
You heard me last night.
Well, then...
Maybe we can still work on...
Sab.
Stop right there, Sab.
If you think that just because
me and Yeynyen broke up
we can easily go back
to how we were,
you're wrong.
We can only be friends.
Why is it so easy for you
to give me up?
You don't even want
to give me a chance
to improve myself for you.
Because our relationship
is impossible.
We really are not compatible.
And last night,
I know you're ruining Yenyen's
reputation with my mom.
Well, you don't have to do that
anymore.
Because we're over.
Red.
OMG, Friend!
I knew you couldn't just ignore
Red.
Family issues have no match
with Red's charm.
Recycled lover.
When love is biodegradable,
we can easily recycle it.
I have a hashtag for you.
#ReDenAgain!
You're so loud!
I told you it's a secret.
You're so stubborn.
Make sure you hold your tongue
when my mom is there.
I'm telling you.
Well, that's the problem.
I'm happy whenever I'm with Red.
But sometimes, when we're
together, I think of my mom.
I wonder what her reaction
will be if she sees me
with the son of the woman
who sent her to jail.
You know what?
I couldn't look my mom
in the eye last night.
I was afraid she'd know
I was lying.
You really are in a difficult
situation.
You didn't choose one.
You chose all of the above.
I love it.
Am I selfish?
I chose my happiness over
my mom's feelings.
Eden, it's not wrong
to be happy.
It's okay as long as you don't
hurt or trample anyone.
But in your case, it's like
choosing the one you love more.
Is it your mother or Red?
Can't I choose both?
I love my mom.
That's why I don't want her
to get hurt.
I also love Red.
That's why I don't want
to let him go.
I love them both.
So maybe we'll just take a risk.
And hope that our families'
situation will change.
I'll tweet that.
Your quotes are lovely.
I love Mom. I don't want her
to get hurt.
I love Red. I don't want
to let him go.
Beautiful.
Stop it.
That's so beautiful.
I'll tweet it.
It might go viral.
Yenyen.
Can I talk to you for a moment?
I saw you earlier with Red.
When you told me that you'd stay
away from him.
So what is it like that?
Why do you keep chasing him?
Sabina, I don't have to explain
myself to you.
I only came here because I
needed to retrieve some stuff.
So please just leave me alone.
Why don't you just admit
that you keep chasing Red?
That you still want to get back
with him.
Well, guess what?
He told me he'd stay away
from you.
So if I were you,
I would stop too.
He can avoid me.
There's no problem with that.
What are you so mad about?
Let me guess...
You're being like that because
even if Red and I are over,
he's still not coming back
to you.
You're pushing yourself
to him again.
You're making yourself
look like a fool again.
The nerve to call me a fool.
When I am one of the honor
students on campus.
While you are just good
at swimming.
Truth hurts, isn't it?
Sabina, haven't you learned
your lesson yet?
You're doing it again and again.
Just a reality check, Sabina.
How dare you!
Yenyen.
Oh my God, Yenyen!
- Yenyen.
- Are you okay?
What happened? Oh, no!
Sab, what is it this time?
What? I didn't do anything.
The balls fell on their own.
She's just dumb.
Are you okay?
I'll help you.
My foot hurts, Red.
It doesn't hurt that much now.
That's okay. Someone might
see us.
Don't worry if someone sees us.
I can't just leave you
like that.
Thank you.
Surprise!
Buffet!
There.
Yummy!
This is one of the moments
that I'd like to return
to the island.
I realized we have more freedom
there.
I thought everything
would be okay
when we're back to Manila.
But it's like we're imprisoned
in our families' past.
We have freedom on the island.
We're free to love.
If I am given a chance to return
to that island, I'll do it...
as long as you're with me.
You shouldn't have brought me
home.
What if my mom sees you?
Come on. It's okay. I can't let
you go home on your own.
My foot is okay now.
And I can handle myself.
Actually, you can drop me off
here.
People might see us.
Bye.
Be safe.
Yen!
You forgot your phone.
You shouldn't have
handed it to me.
My mom might see you.
Okay. I'll go ahead.
Hey.
Mom.
What are you doing here outside?
Eden and I almost came
at the same time.
There's a neighbor
who chatted with me.
That's why I stayed here a bit.
Eden!
Eden! Your mom is coming!
She'll see Red!
- You should hide!
- Hide! Hurry!
Whose car is that?
Our neighbor has a wealthy
suitor.
Amazing, right?
It's so flashy.
Come on, let's cook.
Our neighbor is unbelievable.
Dindi, can you take care
of the dishes?
I woke up early this morning.
- Sure.
- I'll get some rest now.
- I got this.
- Okay, thank you.
Eden, good night.
Good night, Mom.
Eden, I've been lying a lot to
your mom just to protect you.
Honestly, I'm scared
that Amanda will find out
I'm lying to her too.
Auntie, I'm not ready
to tell her yet.
And Red and I promised
that we would tell our parents
at the right time.
What if they find out
about it first?
What if they catch the two of
you before you can tell them?
It's okay to tell her
about it yourself.
I know your mother cannot
accept that right away.
But she will get hurt more if
she finds out from someone else.
If I were you, I'd stop before
it's too late...
if you can't commit to it.
Do you want to meet tomorrow?
Let's talk about
what we should do.
Okay. See you.
Mom, I'm going out.
I have to go somewhere.
It's Saturday.
Where are you going?
Raichu asked me to go with her
to buy swimwear.
Follow that taxi.
Is it something like a date?
Are they on a date?
Yes, Auntie.
Why don't you come here?
So that once and for all,
you're going to meet Yenyen.
I'm looking forward
to meeting her, really.
I want to know who Yenyen
really is.
Mom, what are you doing here?
I'm here to meet Yenyen.
Eden?