Why didn't you tell me Mom paid a visit?
I had things to think about.
"Think"? About what?
About whether you should really break up with me as Mom told you to?
No.
I should've watched more dramas.
Money envelopes and a glass of water to the face.
I thought I could handle those things like they do in dramas,
but I couldn't say a single word to her.
Did Mom speak harshly to you?
Yes.
She told me what we have isn't love.
What?
You don't know how much I regretted it all night.
Should I go to Seoul right now and tell her?
That I love you so much!
So, you're saying that you didn't tell her that, right?
What?
That's what my profound realization was about.
I love you!
I said I love you! I love you.
I love you.
I love you, Kim San Ha. I love you.
Welcome.
Have a seat.
Yes.
I told you I'd wait until you gave us your approval.
But I came because I couldn't wait.
Fine, go on.
I want to make sure Joo Won keeps smiling, eats well,
and stays happy.
When I left Haedong ten years ago,
I promised myself that when I was truly healed
and no longer needed to lean on Joo Won,
I would come back.
I missed her so much every day,
but I didn't have the courage to hide my pain...
so I couldn't come back.
I wanted to come back after becoming a true adult.
Is that why you endured it for 10 years and never once came back?
Yes.
But in the end, I couldn't endure it
and just came back.
Then I met Joo Won again,
came back to my family
and everything was better.
I truly won't worry Joo Won.
Joo Won and I will live ordinary lives like other people.
People's lives are pretty much the same.
What makes you different from other people?
Who in life can avoid difficult times?
I'll always be on Joo Won's side whenever it gets tough.
From now on
I won't be on your side.
Yes.
You know how scary I get when I'm angry, right?
I do.
That's enough, then.
Have you eaten?
No.
- Have a bowl of noodles before you go.
- Okay.
There's a tiny basketball class next to Haedong High.
I'm going to take it over.
"A basketball class"?
I played basketball in America, didn't I?
What about your dad? What does he say?
As for me, I support anything you want to do.
Dad does, too.
He's okay with anything I do.
Really?
Calling you Mom and Dad makes it feel like you really are my Mom and Dad.
Madam told me.
I heard you visited Dad's store yesterday.
Yes.
Since you're looking into moving into that neighbourhood,
I had a few things to ask him.
Is that right? Dad likes that neighborhood, too, right?
Yes.
He says you'll be at ease there.
All right.
I'll take care of it, then.
Madam's information is solid.
It seemed like that to me, too.
You know things don't just work themselves out, right?
Do you know what I've always regretted?
What?
That time I opposed Ahjumma, saying I didn’t need a mom.
I don't need a mommy! I only need an oppa!
Back then, I was too young.
I felt really bad because I felt like I wronged Dad, Ahjumma, and you.
You were seven years old at the time.
It's natural for a child to act like that.
Were you still consumed by that?
That's just how I felt.
Wow, Yoon Joo Won is all grown up.
So will it be Ahjumma or Dad?
It’s probably better to push Dad to take action, right?
Isn't there a natural way to do this?
By chance...
Let's tell him we are going to introduce Dae Wook Ahjusshi to her.
Are you crazy?
How messed up are you trying to make our family tree?
Is that too ridiculous?
I think it's all right.
Actually, the jealousy strategy...
doesn't seem like a bad idea.
Jae Eun set Dal up on a blind date.
I guess that's today.
- "Blind date"?
- Yes.
Since Dal's mom keeps arranging blind dates for her,
Jae Eun suggested we step in.
We gathered all our Haedong High alumni
and arranged a blind date with someone Dal's mom would approve of.
Did Dal agree to that?
She doesn't even like blind dates.
Yes.
Dal is not exactly in a position to disagree.
Since rumors about someone rejecting her have spread all over Haedong.
She didn't get rejected!
Thank you.
He's a catch.
What would you like to order?
What would you like?
Your most delicious menu item.
"Delicious"?
Why are you outside?
Someone just left.
Oh, they stopped by?
Who do you think it was?
There's nothing to be shy about.
Family should be understanding about these things.
I know everything.
Fine. There's no parent who can win against their child. I lost.
When I said I didn't approve of San Ha, you should've consoled the kids
and paid more attention to the family.
You were out of sight all this time.
But now that I've finally approved of San Ha,
you're absolutely ecstatic, aren't you?
I see, you've already approved of them.
"Already"? "Already"?
Gosh, Mr. Yoon.
Team Leader Kim came with a fruit basket to ask you to look favorably on San Ha.
Team Leader Kim was really concerned, too.
You should've told me, then. It's not like I'm God.
How would I have known?
Well...
How could I tell you when you were with her doing this?
"You're light."
What are you talking about?
And I didn't grab her back like that.
I just caught her before she fell and it happened that way.
- Is that so?
- Hey...
Now that I think about it, I had a lot of bread.
I can do without the noodles.
Team Leader, I'll head out first.
Okay, sure. I'm going to leave, too.
What?
There's food left over from San Ha's visit. Eat before you go.
What did you make for San Ha?
What did you make?
Joo Won.
Why?
She made this herself?
Yes, Joo Won made every one of them from scratch.
Hello.
- Is your elbow better?
- Doctor.
Hey, Dal. He came in to treat his elbow recently.
You remembered me right away.
I remember you were eager about treatment so you could play basketball.
Is it feeling better these days?
Are you still doing great at basketball?
Yes, of course. My club just can't run without me.
My buddy over there played basketball in America.
A former Haedong High player.
Oh, really? From America?
Hello.
It would be great if you guys had time to play a game.
I'm fine whenever.
Today works, too.
Then, shall we play a round?
Hurry, Babe.
Hurry over here.
The game that will decide Kang Hae Joon's life is about to begin.
Hurry up! Yes!
Oh, thank you.
What do you have planned?
The final victory.
Among men, it's over if you lose in a game.
What's this?
Why are you here?
Why? Can't I watch Kang Hae Joon play basketball?
I haven't been rejected yet.
Fighting.
You should reconsider.
You're too good for him.
She has a good eye for people.
Come on!
I'll be back.
Be careful.
All right, that's done.
The team that loses will pay for pork belly and soju.
- Sounds good.
- Why are you making such a big deal?
Just trust me.
I even got my girlfriend's father's approval.
What nonsense are you spewing?
Think about it while you do something you love.
Don't regret it.
Fighting.
You know I only settle for first place, right?
Just tighten your shoelaces.
- Let's go!
- Oppas, do your best!
- Fighting, Babe!
- Fighting, Kang Hae Joon!
Let's go.
Hurry and give it to me.
Hey, take him out of here.
I'll get it next time.
- Oh, hey!
- Pass!
Hey, pass!
- Hae Joon, let's do this.
- Crab! Crab!
- Hey, come fast!
- Go, first!
- Go long!
- Is that all you've got?
- Come here! Next to me.
- Okay.
You can do it.
Go, go!
♫  I begin to mirror your smile  ♫
- Kang Hae Joon!
- Nice!
- Here.
- Okay, I got this.
Nice!
♫  I am at my most beautiful when we are together  ♫
♫  So I keep searching for the me reflected in your eyes  ♫
Babe, fighting!
Nice!
♫  The fact that someone more precious to me than myself exists  ♫
♫  In this world that remains sorrowful  ♫
♫  It gives me reason to smile  ♫
I lost today, so I'll treat you to pork belly.
I don't need pork belly, but let me ask you for a favor.
You can ask me anything.
I'll take Dal...
with me today.
Pardon?
- Well...
- You don't have to say anything.
What?
Whatever you say, it doesn't matter to me.
No, I...
Let me talk first.
I like you, Sunbae.
No matter how stupid I am, I'm certain of that one thing.
I was told to study, so I did.
I was told to go to law school, so I did.
I was told to become a lawyer, so I did.
There's exactly one thing I did of my own accord.
That was coming down to live in Haedong.
But that wasn't because I love Haedong.
It was because Seoul was too difficult for me.
Throughout my life, there weren't many instances
where I thought, "I'll do it" or "I want it,"
just because I liked something.
In high school, you were the first.
The first time I liked anything.
But after today,
I realized I still like you.
So,
I like you.
"I like you, so what?"
That's what I'll tell you.
It's the first time I've ever told anyone I liked them.
But if I hide in embarrassment,
then I'll feel...
really pathetic.
Can I talk now?
Even in my sleep, I suddenly wake up.
And suddenly, while walking the streets,
I worry about you
and think about you.
You must not be a sister to me like Joo Won is.
It would be difficult
to call you a sister.
I don't feel as strongly as you do...
yet.
Pardon?
Do you want to date me?
Just say yes.
You say that well.
♫  Beyond the sunrise  ♫
Yes.
There's a reason you were good at studying.
I did that on purpose to make Kang Hae Joon stand out.
If that was acting, you could've been an actor.
Did you like guys who were good at basketball?
It's good to do well at anything.
What about soccer? I'm really good at soccer.
What can I do to make Yoon Joo Won fall for me?
How about we go camping since we got Ahjusshi's approval?
Should we go camping while we are on the subject?
The breezy beach
or the starry mountains?
What is it?
I wonder what kind of person you were originally.
If you didn't need to pretend to be okay,
I wonder what Kim San Ha would've been like.
If you didn't need to hide your feelings
and could talk about them instead,
I wonder how you would've turned out.
Whatever I may have been,
the fact that I like only Yoon Joo Won wouldn't change.
No, let's not think about it.
I think you would've been thick-faced, talkative,
cheesy, and a total playboy.
- "A playboy"?
- Yes.
- "Cheesy"?
- Am I cheesy?
- A bit?
"A bit"?
Shouldn't you renovate the house a bit?
That came out of nowhere. Is something broken?
Isn't Hae Joon's mom moving in with you?
What the heck are you talking about?
That's what Madam said earlier. That she's moving here.
Not this house.
She asked me to look in this neighborhood.
I didn't suggest it. Hae Joon did.
Hae Joon did!
Oh, is that so?
And stop making things uncomfortable like that.
Did someone say they were uncomfortable?
Hae Joon asked how I felt about moving to this neighborhood.
That's great! It would be convenient for the kids, and I could look out for you, too.
Why would you do that?
What am I to you, that you would look out for me?
Well, you're Hae Joon's mom and–
With a man I went on a blind date with once,
I left my child and didn't show up for 20 years.
I'll probably see you a few times because of Hae Joon,
but I feel uncomfortable with people looking at us weirdly.
She looks like she'd live however she wants,
without caring about what others think.
But when Hae Joon is involved, she won't allow even a single flaw
and won't do anything for her own comfort.
What kind of person is like that?
How long will she live like a sinner?
She's frustrating.
Yes, you're right.
I'm going up.
Why, already? There's plenty left.
Young, so young.
You're still in your youth.
Dad's youth.
He's the one who bought the alcohol.
- Are you going to work out?
- Yes.
What are you waiting in here for?
Oh, I'm going. I'm going now.
What should I wear?
Hey, Dal.
Are you going to work?
Hey.
It's Dal.
Dal, are you going to work?
- Did you sleep well?
- Yes.
How are you getting to work?
The bus.
Can I drop you off?
- Yes.
- Hurry up.
- Okay.
Did I say I wouldn't buy it for you?
I asked if you really had to buy it!
That's the same thing!
So I said just buy it if you want to!
How can I buy it when you have that unpleasant expression?
Forget it. I won't buy it.
Just buy it if you'll whine about not buying it! It's all right.
"Whine"?
You still complain even if I buy it for you. What do you want from me?
You should've bought it happily from the start!
Babe, why should I pay 50 million won for that tiny little thing...
Should we go and de-escalate things?
Getting involved is more dangerous.
Geez, you should live alone.
Living alone is the best.
You'd get in trouble if my wife heard that.
Team Leader, do you really not want to get remarried?
Aigoo! And go through that again?
I don't even have the energy anymore.
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry, Honey. I'm really sorry.
Should we go and buy your gift now? Okay? I'm sorry.
My mother told me everyone lives like that.
What is it?
Well, San Ha is seeing someone.
It's about time you told me.
You already knew?
So did you call to tell me not to oppose San Ha?
To just leave San Ha alone?
It'd be great if you could, since it's San Ha's business.
If San Ha gets married,
we will have things to discuss, too.
Even if they say divorced couples are worse than strangers,
you're still San Ha's mom.
So Hui wants to study in England.
What?
I'm going to focus more on So Hui.
I'm going to take her there.
San Ha's mom.
There's still some time before we leave.
I'll see San Ha before we go.
Of course, you should.
There's nothing I can help you with?
Are you happy I'm leaving?
I wished you a happy life even when you said you were getting remarried.
Put the past behind you
and live comfortably. Be at peace.
I'm hanging up. I'm busy.
Dr. Do Hui Joo?
Thank you.
Why did you disappear that day? I couldn't find you after the match.
I saw something I shouldn't have.
We really must be old now.
You know how to read the room now.
Forget it. Just buy me a drink.
- Should I?
- Really?
Yes, I'll go with Joo Won.
Gosh, you're so full of it.
I'm leaving.
Hey! Hey, hold on.
What do you think about Dal's blind date? I can hook you up.
Should I just throw a tantrum for Mom and Dad to marry?
No.
Look. Mr. Yoon needs to simmer for a while, like beef broth
before you can see his pearly feelings.
He hasn't simmered enough yet.
So should I just wait?
No.
You have to watch the fire and turn it low and high at the right times.
What are you telling me to do?
Madam.
Are you nagging Hae Joon again?
No, no.
There's no decent house in the neighborhood?
Yes, house prices have skyrocketed in this neighborhood.
After taking over the basketball class, I have some money–
I have none left.
Yes! I don't have money.
Gosh, I don't have money.
Why? Do you need money?
There's some money I saved up.
I was going to buy a store for you, but you're doing well on your own.
I planned to give it to you when you get married.
Then you shouldn't touch that money.
You shouldn't lay a finger on his wedding fund.
She's right. I need to get married.
Are you seeing someone right now?
You are.
Aigoo...
He's acting like this, so you and his mom settle down together.
Aigoo, this is too frustrating, I can't do this anymore.
What are you so focused on?
The rice cake shop owner out front told me this.
Hae Joon's aunt's company is supporting businesses in the neighborhood.
This is vital to small business owners like me.
I'm looking into it so I can apply.
Yoon Joo Won, you're quite the boss.
You just haven't seen it.
I paid back my loan within five years of opening the store.
Determined to pay back my loan within five years,
I never used a part-timer.
And I even baked my own cakes.
And I really paid off my loan on the five-year mark.
I cried so much that day.
The first few years, I was afraid I'd go bankrupt.
How come you never talked about it?
Never mind.
I should've known even if you didn't say anything.
It's okay.
I'm debt-free now and Daldal Bakery has many regulars.
It's only uphill from here.
It's totally an opportune life.
So I need to apply today for that opportunity.
Joo Won insisted she wouldn't go to college after graduating.
All the friends tried hard to change her mind.
- Is that right?
- She said she wanted to bake cakes
and applied to a baking academy during winter break.
I was surprised she was actually doing what she set her mind on.
Running a small business isn't easy.
Park Dal.
- Yes?
- Tell me something about yourself.
- Pardon?
- Do you have any struggles?
I don't.
If you're an attorney, are you ever in any dangerous situations?
I'm not trying to stop you or anything,
but if you ever end up having to defend
thugs, loan sharks, serial killers, and the like–
Sunbae, you watched too many dramas.
Sunbae, did I offend you?
I really asked out of worry.
- Sorry.
- Oh, it's okay.
I didn't mean to make you apologize.
By the way,  you laugh out loud like that?
It's very nice to hear.
Do you want to come out?
It's hot.
Let's go for a walk.
Okay.
Yoon Joo Won.
♫  Even if you don't say where it hurts  ♫
♫  I know  ♫
Joo Won.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
You couldn't even complain to our dads when you were having a hard time.
You must've worked so hard to grow up so well
on your own all this time.
Just how worried you must've been.
As for me, because coming back here was so difficult,
I couldn't think about you, who was struggling to protect this place.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
♫  My wish, as it's smaller than my height  ♫
You did great.
♫  I can't be the tree that you can take shelter under  ♫
What the heck? You said you'll wake me up in 10 minutes.
♫  Like the beautiful moon  ♫
♫  I will always, as I have always done, be with you  ♫
Where did you go so late last night?
A walk.
It was hot, so we took a walk around town.
Why go out when it's hot? You should stay home.
Can I also go on night walks with Joo Won?
Can I?
No way.
Why can't we go on walks?
What do you do on your walks?
That's enough.
By the way, Dal was so tired in the morning.
Did you walk about 5 km?
Gosh, that's enough!
Think about what to do about Mom and Dad.
You said you're going home today, right?
Go talk it out with Dad.
It's the adults' business. Don't be nosy.
It's because they're adults.
They probably can't do a thing because they're mindful of us.
Look at him. The young one does what he needs to do.
I told you to cut it out.
Help me.
- Hey, go easy on her.
- Save me...
Why didn't you help?
- You freed yourself.
- You still need to help.
I'm sorry.
You still need to save me!
- Okay, okay.
- Gosh, when will they grow up?
- Mercy.
- You promised.
- Hey, wait for me!
- Hurry up!
Do you still have things to take from here?
I was reminded of a book I used to read.
Hey... you heard Mom is going to England, right?
Yes.
She comes and goes, all as she pleases.
But I don't think that's the case this time.
Yes, I know.
I should've told you every time
why she was going and coming all those years.
My goodness.
I wasn't able to...
You stayed here, Dad.
You didn't go anywhere and stayed here.
Whether I go away or come back,
you're always here.
And that's why I was okay.
You're late. Hurry up and go now.
Go now.
By the way, Dad, aren't you interested in seeing anyone?
Aigoo, I'm fine. O-Once is enough for me.
Gosh, did I tell you to get married?
You could just have a girlfriend.
Come on...
What? You're telling me to meet someone to watch movies and have coffee together?
Yes. Do what you want to do.
Besides the police station, home, and family.
Think about those things.
How can there be such things? I don't have the time.
It's late. Hurry up and go now! Go on.
- I'll go now. See you next time.
- Okay.
Yes! It's so nice.
Aigoo, it's so nice!
Why are you telling me to do nothing?
Does Ahjusshi have feelings for Ahjumma or not?
- He does.
- Would Ahjumma not know when we know?
She probably does.
It shows quite a lot.
But if there hasn't been any progress so far, it means Ahjumma isn't ready.
But if we rush Ahjusshi altogether, how will he feel?
Will he be in a tough spot?
Embarrassed?
I know this because I experienced it.
The most frustrated one isn't us.
It's Ahjusshi.
I feel so sorry for my dad.
I was a pitiful one, too,
when you didn't accept me.
When did I ever say I wouldn't accept you?
You said you wouldn't give me a chance.
Don't you recall?
Gosh, you even hold grudges?
♫  Why am I like this?  ♫
Are you inside?
Yes, I'm here, too!
- Hey.
- Why are you here?
We were talking about Dad.
You can talk in the living room.
I'm going. I was about to go.
Bye.
What?
Gosh, do I really have to find a new place?
Hello.
Did you come because of your dad?
Yes.
You don't need to be mistaken.
I went to see him a few times because of Hae Joon.
Your dad and I don't have any other intention.
Back then...
when I said, I didn't need a mom.
I think I said that because you were pretty.
I have no memory of my mom, so I only know her from her pictures.
But my mom in her pictures is really pretty.
And when you showed up that day, Ahjumma,
you were really pretty.
I don't quite remember because I was too young.
But I remember I was mad because you were pretty...
and...
I remember I was mad because of the way Dad looked at you.
Reflecting on it after I grew up,
I don't think Dad ever looked at anyone the same way.
I probably won't ever get to have
a mom again in my life if it isn't you.
Could you be my mom, please?
I'll be a good daughter.
You'll ruin your shoulder like that.
Tiring your body out
just because your mind is cluttered is for when you're young.
You need to be wary of your age now, Mr. Yoon.
I think I'll do radish noodles this summer, too.
Last year, quite a lot of people were asking about it.
I won't do it.
You can hire someone,
or you can get married and make your wife do it.
But I won't do it.
Well, should I go on a blind date
and say that I need to get married because I need someone
to make summer radish kimchi for me?
What? Should I?
My goodness.
Madam, as I was saying, go to the marketplace
and check out the summer radish.
O-Oh, yes. Aigoo.
I'm not going.
I'm just going to go home.
Summer radish noodles?
Why don't you try?
- Take a seat.
- Yes.
What brings you here today?
Did Hae Joon say something again?
I don't know how to make summer radish kimchi.
Sorry?
But...
I'll still try to learn how.
What do you mean?
I'll try to learn
how to keep a home,
make noodles, and raise a daughter, too.
I asked you not to make things uncomfortable for me.
But I'm being too shameless, right?
I was always wayward with you, Jeong Jae.
I shouldn't have done that.
I'm sorry.
Y-You see...
You see, I had feelings for you from the first day you came here.
A single father having feelings isn't a big deal.
So I just put it aside and went on with life.
But those feelings returned after I saw you again.
I doubted my heart would race again at this age,
but it does indeed race.
Gosh, you know...
You don't need to learn how to make kimchi or do house chores.
Let's just...
laugh and cry together.
Let's just live like that.
Hey, let's turn it this way.
Lift it. One, two, three!
I mean, let's just put it back where it was.
Still, we should switch up the new sofa and the bed placement to
make it feel like a newlywed's home.
That's why we should redo the walls and get them new furniture.
Hey, I'll take care of it.
You should stop coming over!
Dad, just getting a new sofa won't make it feel like a newlywed's home.
That one.
That one lived in Haedong longer than Kim San Ha.
Reminds me of the old days. I like it.
Where did Ahjusshi go? Isn't it his day off?
♪ I love you ♪
♪ I love you so much ♪
Mr. Kim.
How is your singing so full of emotion?
It's Chief Kim, not Mr. Kim.
- He's the senior inspector of our town.
- Yes.
My gosh, how do you sing so well?
A-Aigoo, not at all.
- Please excuse me–
- Hold on.
We are getting some iced coffee right here. Join us.
Oh, my kids are waiting for me at home.
Aigoo, I'm sorry. Next time.
So he doesn't even go to singing classes anymore?
I mean, it's weird enough for me that Dad is singing in front of people.
You only went to the hiking club twice and stopped going.
Back then, I went because they said the makgeolli (rice wine) tasted great after hiking.
But the mountain was quite high.
Of course, a mountain is high. What will it be otherwise?
So, is your wedding all ready to go?
Gosh, don't call it a wedding.
We are just gathering for a meal.
He's just embarrassed.
Dad, so... what will you...
what will you do now? Hurry up and decide.
J-Just say the final verdict here.
How about aerobics? It's right around the corner.
Yes, that sounds great.
- I thought about it...
- Yes.
How does cooking sound?
- No way. Not at all.
- What?
- I-I can teach you.
- Don't you dare.
- I'm not doing it.
- You should stick to baking cakes.
I'm really good, though.
I'm not doing it.
- The cake store there disappeared?
- Yes.
I told you last time.
When?
Right after you came back to Haedong.
We were eating ice cream together.
You don't remember that?
You really must not listen to what I say.
Back then, I was a bit bewitched by someone.
Forget it.
- Let's go.
- Where?
I wanted to try this.
Do you even know how to do it?
It's my first time.
You don't even know how to do it.
- There you go.
- Yes.
- All right.
- Wh-Where?
No, it's not this. It's there.
Oh, it's there.
One, two, three.
Growl.
♫  In the breeze, in the moonlight, a softly whispered prayer is carried  ♫
- This one came out well.
- It did.
You look good with a crown.
You look too natural, though, Yoon Joo Won.
Because it's with you, Oppa.
It's pretty.
-  Oppa.
- Yes.
Did you think about it?
Is it really impossible?
I'm sorry. I'll be there in the fall.
Your school and accommodation are ready, so don't worry about them.
Yes. I'll see you at the airport.
When is she leaving?
Next week.
Will you be okay?
With what?
Are you really okay with not dropping her off?
So Hui's still young
and Ahjumma still has difficulty walking.
We need to prepare for the wedding, too.
I'm not okay with this.
It's obvious when you're worried, Oppa.
Take the trip. Okay?
If it bothers you, you can buy a gift on the way back.
"A gift"?
What will you buy?
- A toy.
- "A toy"?
Am I a baby?
A doll, then?
- "A doll"?
- Yes.
I arrived safely in one piece.
So Hui's really happy.
♫  I was filled with hopes about my dream  ♫
♫  That dream made me feel like I owned the world  ♫
Can you reach?
♫  My empty heart was filled with promises we made  ♫
♫  I didn’t even know it was cold  ♫
♫  I had nothing to envy  ♫
♫  Back then, we were the world  ♫
It's coffee.
♫  Like the sun in the clearest summer sky  ♫
♫  Those shattering days  ♫
♫  when we lived for each other  ♫
Gosh, I can't bear it anymore. Hurry up and come home.
Just hold on for 48 hours.
I mean...
why can't I reach him for the entire day?
There's still time until his flight.
Did something happen to him?
Gosh, he must be busy.
He said he'd arrive before the wedding, so I'm sure he will come.
He's not a kid. Stop worrying about him.
When are you going to be here?
I have to spend some more time here today.
When you come, can you bring the blue bag from my room?
I forgot to bring it with me.
What's in it?
The wedding ring.
What?
Why won't he answer his phone?
What are you doing?
Oppa.
Why are you here? Shouldn't you be at the bakery?
And why are you here? Shouldn't you be mid-flight?
I was going to surprise you, but it failed.
Surprise... "Surprise"?
I couldn't even reach you!
"Did something happen? What if he can't make it to the wedding?"
All sorts of things went through my head.
You should be glad to see me sooner than expected.
I was really worried, though.
I'm sorry.
I missed you.
Forget it.
Don't think you can win me over–
Don't think this can win me over–
I missed you so much.
Me, too.
You didn't really buy a doll, did you?
It's jelly, I think.
Am I still seven years old?
It was my wish.
"Your wish"?
Just like back then,
I wished you would smile all the time.
I wanted to see you smile all the time.
That was my wish.
Wow, you look really handsome, Dad.
Why isn't she coming, though?
Is she still sleeping because she was tired from prepping the store yesterday?
The phone is turned off. You'll be connected to the voicemail.
Hey, is Joo Won still sleeping?
Joo Won didn't come home last night.
- What?
- She wasn't at the store, either.
Didn't she come home?
What?
Why? What happened?
She said Joo Won wasn't home or at the store.
What?
When did you last talk to her?
I told her to go get the ring from my place.
"The ring"?
I told her to get the wedding ring.
Thank you Heartfelt Family Team! 🏠
Channel Managers: maria_lavendula_77 and deval_chloe
Thank you to our awesome Chief Segmenters:
baepsae29 and iamsolyne
Thank you to our amazing segmenters:
ts_lambrini, maria_lavendula_77, squirrelpants_73,
apatty69, manganese
Thank you to our amazing segmenters:
didi_dramas, joiicykalane_843, strongbird41_429, vivi_1485 and staycla
Our wonderful English editors: modestloving_147 (CE),
table122000, addictedtobooks, and matoon (GEs)
Our wonderful English editors: subwayhongsamkopiko,
vicky_daebak, and koriyan03 (TEs)
- Hey.
- What...
Long time no see.
You...
Wh-Why are you here?
J-Joo Won's missing right now, so...
What is it?
What?
It's nothing.
What is it?
Hyungnim.
Please have mercy.
You...
You crazy punk!
♪ Our meeting was not a coincidence ♪
♪ It was our most sincere wish ♪
♪ To forget... ♪
Thank you.
Watch what you say.
You just arrived in Haedong,
and you dozed in my room and overslept. Got it?
Yes.
You're the best, Hyungnim.
You're...
I'll see you after the wedding.
Save me.
Every man for himself.
♪ I love you ♪
The weather's nice today.
All right. Let me see you smile on the count of three.
Show me your teeth.
All right, here we go. One, two, three!
Come here. Let's take one together.
Joo Won and you two, come here.
We will take one together.
Yes, that's great. All right.
Please get closer.
All right. One, two, three.
♫  This cold, distant, indifferent star   ♫
♫  One that has always been wandering around lonely  ♫
One, two, three!
I got it!
I'm the one!
♫  Mirror your smile  ♫
♫  I finally become my true self when I'm by your side  ♫
♫  I am at my most beautiful when we are together  ♫
♫  So I keep searching for the me reflected in your eyes  ♫
♫  The fact that someone more precious to me than myself exists  ♫
♫  In this world that remains sorrowful  ♫
♫  It gives me reason to smile  ♫
♫  Though all the nights in the world fade into yesterday  ♫
♫  I promise that, for you, I will remain the same  ♫
♫  The world is busy trying to protect many things  ♫
♫  But there's only one I want to protect  ♫
♫  I'll make sure to protect "us" ♫