You're Mr. Yoon Jeong Jae, right?
Do you remember me?
P-Please give me a minute.
I'll call Hae Joon–
I hope to keep it a secret from Hae Joon that I'm here.
Sorry?
Have a seat.
Let's talk, just the two of us.
Don't you remember lending me money?
I remember lending it to you,
and I remember the exact amount.
But this is too much.
I put some more in there.
Why did you put more?
It must've cost a lot to raise Hae Joon.
It'll cost more for college.
Thank you for the coffee.
You're leaving?
This is so sudden...
Pardon...
Pardon me!
Wait a minute!
You came all the way here. Why won't you see Hae Joon?
What would be the point?
What do you mean? Well, of course...
It'd be nice to see him, even for a moment.
Why see him when I'm not here to take him with me?
Is it hard to tell him his mom paid her debt and left?
Just tell him it's great he doesn't have to pay you back.
That's not the issue. Your child would want to see you!
Do you know how long he waited for you?
How can I tell him you just came and left?
Don't be like this and–
Yes, fine.
If you insist, I'll accept only the money I lent you.
This leaves no resentment, right?
Take care.
Mr. Yoon Jeong Jae.
Why did you lend me money?
Excuse me?
No matter how I think about it, we were almost strangers.
You lent it too easily.
It wasn't easy for me,
and you must've had your reasons for asking when we were essentially strangers.
You seem to understand everyone's circumstances.
Yes, it's not that hard once you try to understand.
Just take it.
Wait, Ms. Seo Hyeon...
What am I supposed to tell him?
It's melting! Let's run!
H-Hey! Time out!
- Time out!
- Gosh.
- What?
- Pardon?
- Nothing. Let's go.
- Okay.
He never sleeps at night.
At least let him sleep during the day.
This has been ringing for a while.
Hello?
Put So Hui on the phone.
Why are you asking me for So Hui?
She told Ahjumma she was going to the restaurant to see you.
So Hui's gone?
Since when?
Welcome!
Ahjusshi, did So Hui come here?
- So Hui?
- Did So Hui not come?
Why? Is she gone?
Yes, I think she left by herself.
She didn't come to the restaurant.
You shouldn't be asking me that!
She might be on her way here. Please let me know if she comes.
Yes, all right. I'll do that.
I'll search nearby.
So Hui!
Aigoo, goodbye! Take care.
Take care! Goodbye!
If you wait a moment, the police will help find your mom.
I'm not looking for my mom. I'm looking for my oppa.
Over here! Over here!
Hello, we are from the Gangpyeong Police Station.
Is that her?
What's your name, Little Girl?
Where are your mom and dad?
She rode the taxi here by herself around 2:00 p.m.?
That's right. She said she came looking for her mom.
Where did she get in the taxi?
She didn't say.
Was there a report of a missing child?
Please hold.
When?
Off to the restaurant by herself?
Are you So Hui?
Oppa!
Where did you find her?
At a noodle shop in the next town.
I responded to a call and found her there.
How could you come here alone?
Thank goodness we found her, so all is good.
What if she does this again?
Do you think we will be lucky to find you again?
Oppa was just really worried about you, So Hui.
Really?
Jeong So Hui!
Who said you could leave home by yourself?
Do you know how worried I was?
Let's go.
Oppa.
Let's go!
You won't even greet me now?
Haven't you children learned you should greet your elders?
I did–
They did.
You're the one who didn't see because you ignored them.
They roamed for over an hour looking for So Hui.
So Hui has never left home by herself like this before.
You're the only oppa she has.
This wouldn't happen if you visited your sister first!
How is this San Ha's fault? What were you doing?
Do you expect me to monitor her continuously?
It hasn't been long since San Ha and the child first met.
They're not close enough for sudden visits.
Time is irrelevant. They're family!
Do you know how glad I was to see you after ten years?
"My son has grown so much since I last saw him."
"So Hui would love to live with her oppa."
"Fine, I should try."
"I should try to forgive you."
I said I don't need your forgiveness.
You never contacted me when you got remarried or had So Hui. Why now, suddenly?
- That's why I'm doing this at least now–
- That's why!
Please...
Please stop trying.
How could you...
Shouldn't I be the one saying such words?
Shouldn't you have begged for forgiveness before I tried to forgive you?
Whose fault is this?
- Please stop!
- Why should I stop?
Why are you yelling at me when it was your fault?
It was your fault.
- It was all your fault!
- Stop!
- She died because of you!
- Enough!
Come out.
Come out!
It's okay. Don't cry.
It's okay.
Where are you going?
Wait for us.
Give him some time to resolve his thoughts.
He didn't look back once.
He doesn't want to show us his face.
Where are you taking me?
That's right.
Before you left ten years ago, I blamed you.
I thought it was all your fault.
What are you saying?
You're a weak person.
I'm well aware you're not strong enough to admit your mistakes,
so I didn't want to remind you that it was your fault.
What are you talking about?
You're not the one who should be doing the forgiving!
I even gave you a divorce so you hurt less.
I did everything you wanted.
You "gave me a divorce"?
Jeong Hui.
I loved you that much.
How about me? Do you think I didn't?
Do you think I was a cold-blooded person?
Did I go crazy?
Why do you think I married a lowly civil servant with nothing to his name?
What? "Love"?
When I said I was depressed after spending my youth having two children,
did you even pretend to hear me?
You obsessed over your work performance!
What did you say when you finally came home?
"I think I'll be able to catch him. I just need a little more time."
You didn't care how lonely and miserable I was.
You're right.
- Everything you said is true, but–
- That day,
you weren't home either.
Was I the only one not at home?
Were you the only one free to go after criminals?
How are you the only one who is always righteous and dignified?
Right.
After my child died,
forget justice and dignity. Nothing mattered anymore!
But what about San Ha?
Is San Ha not our child?
Don't you feel sorry for him?
That little boy watched his younger sister suffocate to death!
Have you ever thought about the emotional state he has been in?
He was alone with So Jeong.
What was he doing then?
Didn't you ever think about that?
Have you never thought that before?
To forgive you.
I'm going to try to forgive you.
Shouldn't you have begged for forgiveness before I tried to forgive you?
It was your fault. It was all your fault!
She died because of you!
How about an adult? Is there an adult with you?
No one's here. No one...
When Ahjumma left this place,
do you know how cold she was to Kim San Ha?
She told me to "keep him," as if he were some object.
She never once held his hand.
And now, she wants to "forgive him"?
Why are you silent? Am I wrong?
Not too long ago...
In this world, toxic families also exist.
My mom and I are like that.
At the time, I couldn't understand how he could say something so harsh.
But I think I can understand now.
I've told you all this time how scary Ahjumma is!
How was I supposed to know with just that?
I can only understand if I know more.
He sneaks into his room at the mention of his mom.
It's because he's trying to hold back.
Why?
When? At what time?
Did he not even eat breakfast?
Aigoo, Joo Won is the only one who cares about San Ha.
Ahjusshi.
I told Ahjumma not to contact San Ha for the time being.
His grandmother is in Japan with his uncle, so he'll hear less from her, too.
Don't worry about it.
"For the time being"?
From when to when specifically?
Well... The soup tastes great.
You're not sure, are you?
He probably couldn't sleep before going to school.
Dad, don't you have anything better than jujube tea?
Something like king jujube tea or emperor jujube tea?
I'll check in the marketplace.
You both finish your breakfast before going.
I'll pack you some cherry tomatoes and apples.
Take them to San Ha later.
Will cherry tomatoes be enough?
Wait, why won't he eat breakfast?
You ought to eat, no matter what,
or you'll suffer all day at school.
Don't wake him up. Let's just go to the snack bar.
Did Oppa leave already?
- I don't know.
- He said he was going to the library.
Did he?
- Hey, move aside!
- Let's go!
We all ate our dinner.
Okay.
How much longer will you keep this up?
Isn't this enough?
As you said, we might just be motherless children in other people's eyes,
but you still live with Ahjusshi.
Look at me.
Whom do I have?
See? You pity me more, too.
Who says pity is relative?
My mom said she'd return after making money.
I gradually stopped believing it in middle school.
But you had to bring it up and rub salt in my wound. How mean.
But did I ever skip meals because I was embarrassed?
Being embarrassed is one thing; eating is another.
Will you skip tomorrow's breakfast, too?
Yes.
My goodness, when will he grow up?
Are you going through puberty?
It's much too late!
What's up with her?
I told you not to greet her.
I didn't even realize I was doing it.
But why the lunchbox these past few days?
Is he skipping school lunch?
It's not lunch. It's breakfast.
Kim San Ha has been skipping breakfast the last few days.
He must be busy studying.
It's not that.
Are you worried about Kim San Ha right now?
I'm not!
What do you mean?
You!
Were your feelings for Kang Hae Joon that fleeting–
I just have a favor to ask of him.
Why did you pack so much?
There's so much.
What are you trying to do?
Just this...
Hey, about that. Your–
I know who brought it.
Eat!
You're eating, right?
You can choose any menu item.
If you're eating, send a sign.
Eat and feel better. Fighting!
Welcome.
You don't have umbrellas?
It started pouring suddenly, so we are sold out.
As it rains harder, there will be more than 120 mm (4.5 in) of strong rain overnight.
As it rains, you'll see strong winds in some areas.
The Southern region, particularly near Jeju, will be issued strong wind advisories...
The call is not going through–
Dad, did you put tofu in the soybean paste stew?
N-No, not yet.
Don't add the tofu yet and wait.
Sure.
Did you eat?
What are you doing here?
What do you mean?
It's because you keep skipping meals.
Why did you turn your phone off?
It ran out of battery.
Charge your phone more often.
What are you doing? It's soybean paste stew tonight.
I'm not hungry. It's fine.
I didn't ask if you're fine or not.
You clearly don't look fine, so why bother asking?
It's pointless.
Don't you know why I'm avoiding you?
Why?
It's because I'm embarrassed.
I'm embarrassed I had a fight with my mom in front of you all.
It's considerate to leave me alone at times like this.
I said to come eat. Why the overreaction?
What are you doing? Come on.
Gosh, it's so cold.
So cold.
- Oh, you're back?
- Yes.
Your socks. Take your socks off before sitting down.
There we go.
She spent more than an hour looking for you.
She went back and forth from home to the bus stop.
Shut it.
Eat first, then wash up.
Since you haven't joined us for a while, I'll let you have all the tofu.
In return, the fried eggs are mine.
Let's be clear about that.
- Is it that good?
- You can't handle not getting to eat these, right?
Hey, this is salted mackerel.
Aigoo.
She's the fried egg monster.
Seriously.
It's not like you're Humpty Dumpty. Why do you like fried eggs so much?
- You can have mine.
- I ate it just in case.
You eat three dozen eggs a month.
I'll grow up and...
Dad was so relieved to see you eat.
Skipping meals is also being unfilial.
Sorry.
In that respect, I'm such a great daughter, right?
I miss her.
Miss who?
So Jeong.
I was just saying I do. Just saying.
I miss my mom, too.
You don't know what your mom looks like, though.
I saw her pictures, but also want to see her in person.
You never said anything like that.
Because if I say I miss her, my dad will be sad.
Do you think my dad misses So Jeong, too?
Does he have to point it out for you?
Right? It's a given.
I miss my mom, too.
Of course, I do.
19-year-old Kang Hae Joon still misses his mother.
Why do you always pick on me? Why?
- Whenever he thinks of his mother, Hae Joon gets teary.
- I said stop! Stop!
Do you understand Korean–
Dad!
Kim San Ha has a fever.
Since when?
He barely ate anything and got soaked in the rain.
This is no surprise.
Did you give him medicine?
I gave him those.
Let's leave him to rest.
Let's all go out now.
♫  One day, a precious memory  ♫
♫  Entered my small heart the day you smiled brightly  ♫
♫  And another day  ♫
♫  The memory of you holding me  ♫
♫  The day I wept freely, surrendering all my pain and struggles  ♫
♫  We loved all those days  ♫
Don't come.
So Jeong, don't come...
You'll catch my cold...
Why did you come back?
I don't care if you believe me or not,
but I came back for San Ha's sake.
Didn't you realize anything after meeting So Hui?
What about So Hui?
She resembles her.
To San Ha, So Hui is his second chance.
He can try to push her away all he wants.
He can't ignore So Hui forever.
I want to see the siblings get along again.
Is that so wrong?
♫  We just believed  ♫
♫  we didn't want to let go of each other  ♫
♫  While carrying the warmth of our memories in our hearts  ♫
Are you going somewhere?
How do you feel?
I feel better. The fever has come down, too.
Get dressed, then. Wear something nice.
It has been a while.
Is that so?
Dad...
I'm okay now.
The things Mom said...
don't bother me anymore.
How can it not bother you?
Even lies can convince you to doubt yourself the more you listen to them.
Even more so when it's your mom's words.
That's why...
I'm also...
going to use my words.
So Jeong's death...
isn't your fault.
It didn't happen because you two were together.
It happened because we left you two alone.
So you don't need to feel apologetic to anyone,
and you don't need to push So Hui away.
Nor must you try harder to be good to her.
She's your younger sister, after all.
Just do as your heart leads you.
Yes.
When I get my driver's license next year,
let's come here more often.
Don't come here alone, Dad.
Sure, let's do that.
Food is ready!
- What?
- Dad.
This is great news! Finally!
- Aigoo!
- So cute.
Isn't she a beauty?
She's so small!
Is that tiny thing her ear? When can we visit?
Auntie said she'd call me when she's ready.
You're so lucky.
Well, it's not today, right?
What are you doing after school today?
Let's eat steak!
- "Steak"?
- Yes.
Dal's mom said she'll treat us to steak.
Why would your friend's mom treat me when she isn't even my friend?
My friend is your friend, Oppa.
Not true. Ordinary people don't think that way.
It's a new place downtown,
and it's apparently very famous in Seoul, too.
Dal's mom is making a big gesture by treating us.
The students who've been there said there's no need to chew the meat.
When you place it in your mouth, it melts.
It just melts on your tongue.
Nothing is free.
- You're going, right?
- Let's go.
So it's just us two?
Then meet me after school in front of the main entrance.
Why is she treating us, though?
Let's hear that first.
To be honest...
I just...
have...
a favor to ask him.
Your grade in math is three?
Sure, grades drop sometimes.
Rather than getting this result in Grade 12,
it's better to face it now and be prepared.
Okay.
Didn't you say you got notes from Joo Won's oppa?
Did you get them or not?
Not yet.
You're too shy.
Can't you even ask your friend's brother for a simple favor?
I was going to ask when we got closer.
Should I meet Joo Won's brother?
Yes! I'll treat him to something tasty, so tell him to come with Joo Won.
If that's the case, aren't I the only one invited?
You two don't really need to be here, do you?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Delicious food is even more delicious when you eat it together.
- Welcome.
- Welcome!
Have a seat.
CSAT is approaching.
I hope I'm not taking too much of your time.
Oh, you're not.
We should order the 4-person set.
We have two boys here. Order the 6-person set.
Oh, then...
What do you want to eat? Is there anything you want to eat?
We've never been to a place like this, so we don't know.
- Right?
- Yes.
Have you never tried this in Seoul?
Oh, then the 6-person set–
- Excuse me!
- Yes?
We'd like the steak and rib-eye from the 6-person set cooked well done.
And please add a salad and cream pasta.
All of us will have a Coke.
- All right?
- Yes.
Pardon me.
Enjoy.
Thank you for the food.
You can't even order from the menu on your own.
I don't know how you'll become a lawyer at this rate.
Am I counting my eggs before they hatch?
Dal messed up in math this time.
I'm starting to lose hope.
Gosh, there you go again, you clumsy girl.
All she does is study, so she's lacking in many ways.
It's draining to maintain good math grades from the first year.
If she concentrates on it during the break,
she'll improve drastically compared to other subjects.
You shouldn't worry.
Really?
But that's only for smart children like you.
Our Dal has to work hard. I'm not sure if she can handle it.
Gosh, she just works hard without any strategy.
Eat. Eat up.
Why are you here and not eating with them?
Well...
Mom, I know I can't even choose from the menu
and I messed up on math,
but I wish you wouldn't treat me like I'm stupid in front of my peers.
It's fine when it's just the two of us at home–
Then, should I say my daughter is a distinguished person?
People get annoyed when smart people are praised.
That's just how people sympathize.
People are more likely to help if you seem to lack a little.
You need his notes.
I don't need his notes.
I'm not saying I want to act like I'm extraordinary.
I just don't want to look like a fool in front of my friends.
Why are you crying?
What did I say to make you cry?
I look so stupid.
I think she cried.
- She cried.
- Smile.
- I can't smile.
- Me, either.
Then should we tell Dal to her face that her mom is too much?
- Farewell.
- Thank you for the food.
- What?
- Goodness!
Do you have a bad relationship with your mom?
Ignore him.
Our relationship is fine.
Let's go to the beach!
We just have to walk a little.
Let's go.
Be careful!
Is this all you really need?
Thank you.
It is.
I'll show it to my mom and return it right away.
You should join them, too.
We came here to make you feel better.
I feel fine, though.
She was just acting like that in front of you guys.
She's not like that when we are alone.
And she's not exactly wrong.
Do you remember how you and Joo Won became friends?
Probably when I called Sunbae Hae Joon over when she got dragged to the incinerating facility.
Joo Won told me you ran without even realizing your shoe had fallen off.
That's right.
Lawyers aren't people who simply speak well.
Shouldn't they be like you, who spends time taking care of
others' business like it's your own?
Your mom's words weren't all true.
Just think of your mom as human, too.
Then you'll feel more at peace.
That's what I do.
Hey, look at this! Seaweed!
Do they grow it here?
Why are you laughing?
You know I'm astute, right?
Your friend likes Kim San Ha.
I'm positive! They look good together.
What the heck?
Something came over me.
It's Auntie!
Okay, okay!
- Auntie called. She said I could visit.
- O-Okay.
I'm off!
Hey!
My mom asked me when I'm coming, too.
Thank you.
Bye!
Where should we go now?
Should we just go home?
I still haven't digested that steak.
How do you feel?
I feel fine.
Auntie.
You're here.
He must be your nephew.
Yes.
Do you feel okay?
Did you see the baby?
She looks the same as her photo. She's so cute.
Your nephew must take after his maternal side.
He looks exactly like his mom and aunt.
What's the "maternal side"?
I'm saying you resemble your mom's family more than your dad's.
"Mom's family"?
What are you saying? He doesn't.
Wasn't the woman from a few days ago your older sister?
They look so similar. I could tell he was her son right away.
Mom was here?
Who was here?
Hae Joon's mom.
She came and left without seeing Hae Joon? Why?
Who knows?
Depositing this in the bank would feel like I'm getting rid of evidence,
but I can't exactly hide this large sum anywhere.
Gosh, I really don't know what to do.
What do you think?
You can use it for Hae Joon's college next year.
Don't say a word about it to Hae Joon.
She might have some circumstances.
What dire circumstance would stop her from seeing her child's face?
You don't have to feel guilty; this was your money to start with.
What's the problem with getting your money back?
Even so.
"Your mom paid her debt and left."
"She left without seeing you."
Can you tell him that?
She said she paid her debt before leaving.
So she said not to worry about the money.
I can repay the money later when I'm older.
I could have repaid it.
Did you give Dal your notes?
What do you think? Did she seem better?
Yes.
Anyway, why is Kang Hae Joon so dense?
You're the one Dal's mom wanted to see.
Why does he think I brought him along if he's not involved?
Wasn't that enough for most people to catch on?
Right?
Pardon?
You weren't listening.
I was.
What did I say?
That Kang Hae Joon is dense.
Do you know what he said to me earlier?
He said he's positive Dal has feelings for Kim San Ha.
He said he's astute.
Yeah, right.
What are you doing? You'll fall.
Wow, this feels nice.
Come up.
Grab on. It's dangerous.
Am I a child?
Doesn't he think about why Dal and I go to his basketball practice?
I don't even know basketball rules.
I'm just following Dal.
Exactly.
She always stops by the gym on her way to the academy.
Isn't that quite a blatant signal?
Was he always so dense?
Don't you agree?
You're dense, too.
Why am I–
♫  I keep rattling  ♫
♫  Like a broken doll  ♫
♫  I'm lost on every step  ♫
♫  I guess I'm locked away inside you  ♫
♫  I need an explanation  ♫
♫  My day is spent immersed in a dream  ♫
♫  I have a lot to say  ♫
♫  but I'm lost for words  ♫
♫  Why am I like this?  ♫
♫  Why am I always so excited like it's the first time?  ♫
♫  And remorseful like it's the last time?  ♫
♫  Again, I circle around you like I'm praying  ♫
♫  When our eyes meet  ♫
Doesn't Kim San Ha seem sensitive these days?
The CSAT is next week. I need to focus.
She should be more careful.
Boldly skip the questions you don't know.
If worst comes to worst, roll your pencil!
Congrats on finishing the CSAT!
If she left, she should've lived a good life. Why make him suffer?
Let go!
It's only been one day since you went to Seoul.
- Why does it seem so long ago?
- Oppa!
The time it takes to wake up from anesthesia varies for everyone,
but something feels off.
♫  These days...  ♫