"2 km SkyBike."
But will riding that make them reconcile?
Doing things together naturally develops friendship.
- Let go!
- Hey!
I said to make up. Why are you fighting again?
Hey, don't make up!
You're dead if you make up!
- Hang out with us.
- Gosh, I'm–
Please let go–
What the heck?
Aren't you Kang Hae Joon's younger sister?
What should we do? Is it heatstroke?
Should we call an ambulance?
Yoon Joo Won, wake up.
Where are they? How dare they hit a girl!
You!
- What?
You're Mr. Yoon Jeong Jae, right?
Don't you remember lending me money?
Why won't you see Hae Joon?
Is it hard to tell him his mom paid her debt and left?
What dire circumstance would stop her from seeing her child's face?
She said she paid her debt before leaving.
So she said not to worry about the money.
Anyway, why is Kang Hae Joon so dense?
You're the one Dal's mom wanted to see.
Why does he think I brought him along if he's not involved?
Wasn't that enough for most people to catch on?
Was he always so dense?
You're dense, too.
Why am I–
What I mean is...
So...
what I mean is...
I'm sharp.
What?
I said I was sharp.
Was I being dense today?
Tell me if I was.
Tell me.
Why are you laughing?
You said you were sharp.
Can't you tell why I'm laughing?
Why?
Why did you laugh?
It's Bus 900.
"Bus 900"?
Come on. Run!
We have to wait an hour if we miss that one. Hurry!
Ahjusshi!
Ahjusshi! Ahjusshi!
Come on.
Go to him.
Talk to Ahjusshi!
Thank you.
Imagine if we missed this one.
Forget one hour.
We might've had to wait two hours.
Can you use herb salt to banish a ghost?
Do you talk about this with your friends?
Yes. It's the hottest topic in our class.
You need to prove ghosts exist first.
After proving that, you can ask if salt can banish ghosts.
No, this isn't a matter of proving anything.
It's purely for fun.
Then herb salt should work since it has salt in it.
Since the main ingredient in herb salt is the salt, not the herb.
Okay, then. A hamster's feet sweat. Yes or no?
Hamsters are mammals, so they regulate their body temperature.
Of course, their feet sweat.
I'm an idiot for asking you.
My goodness!
What are you doing over there?
What took you guys so long?
What are you doing here instead of going home?
Didn't you visit Auntie?
Did something happen at the hospital?
Why? What happened?
Nothing. Auntie is fine.
Then who isn't fine?
Is it you?
Tell us what's wrong while I'm speaking nicely.
How much was it?
Twenty million won.
I knew because Auntie told me, but...
When did you find out she had borrowed money?
A long time ago.
When I first came here.
I wondered why she always made you walk on eggshells.
Auntie wasn't trying to be mean.
She just felt pressured, too.
She felt bad, too.
It's not Hae Joon's fault.
That's what I'm saying.
Why is he being cautious when it's not his fault?
Why feel sorry?
Well, she paid everything back, so it's settled.
You no longer have to feel pressured.
That's right.
I was going to pay it back.
If the money was the reason she couldn't contact me,
I could just pay it back.
But since she paid him back and just left...
I guess money wasn't the reason she didn't contact me.
It would've been nice if it was because of the money.
It would've been nice if she saw you before leaving.
Take it.
Here.
Eat it. I gave you one first.
Eat this, too.
I'm home.
Great. And Joo Won?
She needs something from Kim San Ha.
Okay...
I'm almost done. Go do what you need to do.
You should run the washing machine. Why do you always wash it by hand?
Do you see this? These areas must be washed by hand.
It's not even visible.
Even so.
It feels nice to go out in clean clothes in the morning.
About the money Mom paid you back...
What?
If we use that for my tuition next year,
I'll pay it all back by working.
How did you find out?
She visited Auntie.
Why did she see Auntie and not me?
Was she too busy?
If she comes back next time and looks for me,
tell her I don't want to see her anymore.
She probably won't return since she paid off her debt.
I'm going.
Hae Joon.
Don't say things like you'll pay me back.
You don't need to pay me back for anything.
Don't say anything Joo Won wouldn't say.
Kang Hae Joon told you he's aware his mom came, right?
There are no secrets here.
You should be glad he told you.
That's true.
I'll see you later.
One, ten, hundred, thousand, ten thousand...
I'm proud he's saying he'd do what he can to pay you back.
Making a child worry about money is nothing to brag about.
Did something good happen?
Why are you so happy?
San Ha's mom texted me earlier saying she's going to Seoul.
Will she not come here anymore?
It'll be hard to unless she is determined.
Seoul is across the country.
Did you tell San Ha as well?
Yes, as soon as I got the text.
She came out of nowhere and shook up the children.
But they all found their places in the end.
Now that I think about it,
Hae Joon's birth father has been quiet these days.
It looked like he'd sue right away.
Can you please just take one look at this?
Hey, do you know I was determined to go to America without you?
But I see you whenever I close my eyes.
And I'm reminded of you when I'm eating something delicious.
Don't you think that's what it means to be bound by blood?
You said similar stuff the first time you came, too.
Fool me twice, shame on me.
H-Hey, I'm not trying to fool you.
I'm totally serious right now.
You came to me out of worry that they'll take your assets away!
Well, that was before I met you.
Also, I'm your dad.
You abandoned us.
You abandoned Mom and me, and now you say what?
What now, then? What?
Should I beg? Should I?
If that's all, I'm leaving.
- Hey, hold on.
- Hae Joon!
What's taking you so long?
I told you to start without me.
We can't. He came all the way from Seoul to see you.
Tell the ones who want to go to college in Seoul to play.
Shut your trap. Hurry up.
"Seoul." "College"?
That's right. Okay.
Focus.
Is Number 10 Kang Hae Joon?
Yes. He's great at passing and just as great at shooting.
If his game management is that good, he can probably go to the pro league, too.
I can't tell since he's hiding in this rural town.
He'd be scouted right away if he went to Myungju University.
We know the limits of doing well without support.
Oh my, who are you?
I'm just a parent who was passing by.
By the way, Number 10 over there, he's good at this, right?
Is he really good?
Do I have to come back here in two weeks?
He keeps making me travel far.
San Ha.
Dad told me to wash the sheets.
I washed them yesterday.
- What?
- They're new.
Are they?
What?
I told you not to sit on my bed.
I'm lying down, though.
- Get out.
- Why?
Since I'm already here, let me stay a minute.
Don't come up to the third floor from now on.
- Why not?
- The CSAT is next week.
I need to focus. Hurry.
But why–
Come on.
She should be more careful.
Hey, mine, too. I forgot to put in my gym clothes.
These are almost done. Do them separately.
Here.
Why would you put something wet in there? Seriously.
Why are you so annoyed?
Doesn't Kim San Ha seem sensitive these days?
He has always been sensitive.
It's just a little worse since he became a 12th-grader.
Is that such a big deal?
The CSAT needs to be over soon.
"Your mind will be clear, and your stomach won't be upset."
"You'll easily solve problems you didn't know."
- Is someone taking the CSAT?
- My boyfriend.
Your boyfriend is in Grade 10, though.
I broke up with him ages ago.
He's a coward who ran away.
"Ran away"?
At the park last time.
Even so, aren't you moving on too fast?
All the important events in the world always occur suddenly.
Should I make one, too?
With red here?
No, it's purple.
Purple, purple...
I would love to have an oppa.
Do you want to take one?
Kang Hae Joon, if possible.
Come on.
Too weak. You need to hit it harder.
We are almost there. Keep it up!
♫  There was a time when I was filled with hopes about my dream  ♫
Five hundred won, a hundred won.
♫  That dream made me feel like I owned the world  ♫
♫  My empty heart was filled with promises we made  ♫
♫  I didn’t even know it was cold  ♫
Don't hold back on the rolled omelet.
Okay.
The doorsill! Don't step on the doorsill.
Stay right there.
The doorsill!
Be careful, or you'll lose good luck.
♫  We were dazzling and were united as one  ♫
- Dad, is it done?
- Yes, it is. All done.
- Take this.
- What?
Eat the chocolate when you're low on sugar.
What are you so nervous about?
I'm nervous for some reason.
I packed the stuff you usually eat.
But you don't have to eat it if you can't.
All right. Let's go. Let's go.
Fighting!
Boldly skip the questions you don't know.
If worst comes to worst, roll your pencil.
And don't miss the right answers.
Okay.
Today's dinner will be a special one, right?
Of course. I asked Madam to prepare the best meat she had.
- Yes.
- That's not it.
On days like this, you step back so they can have fun by themselves.
Mr. Yoon can grab one with me.
As if.
We should take care of the children who had a long day, not grab a drink.
Dad, do we still have the tent we used last year?
We do have the tent, but why?
Dad, you can go grab a drink with Ahjusshi.
I'll take care of things here.
Will you?
What will you do?
I'll have to invite Dal over, too.
It's generally said to be a bit harder compared to the mock exam,
but it's said to be a lot harder than last year's.
This year's Korean Language and Math were harder than last year's.
So it was said to have fulfilled the assessment function.
Yes, it's over!
- Gosh, I wrecked it.
- I'm doomed.
I'm done for.
Hey.
Which answer choice appeared the most?
- Which one did you choose?
- Number three.
Oh, number three did appear the most.
But you're in liberal arts.
It's different from mine.
Oh, you're right.
You got the message to wash your hands and go up to the rooftop, right?
Did they say they'll order chicken?
I don't know. Let's go.
What are you doing? Take a seat.
Did you also come?
How did you do on your exam?
Aigoo, you're supposed to take exams using your usual skills.
He's saying he didn't do well.
Who put up the tent?
Ahjusshi put up the tent.
Dad made the soybean paste stew and pork belly.
Dal brought the snacks.
- What about you?
- Me?
I showed up.
Anyhow.
Congrats on finishing the CSAT.
Did you both apply to Myungju University?
It's decided for Hae Joon, and I need to pass the admissions.
How great. You get to go to school together.
Our classes will be different. How can we go to school together?
Why can't you? You can just schedule...
Why aren't you careful?
You scared me.
Hey, your yelling scared me more.
I just got singed a bit.
You still need some ointment.
You two can keep eating.
I'll be right back.
Hey, it's fine. He won't be upset for too long.
He has never hurt anybody.
I see.
I'm fine, right?
It's nothing, right?
I thought you got seriously hurt.
The CSAT is over now, so stop being so sensitive.
Was I being sensitive?
You told me not to even come up to the third floor.
That's not necessarily because of the CSAT.
What, then?
It's fine. Go back up.
What?
Let's give those two some time alone.
This is long enough.
Here, eat this.
N-No, I'll do it myself.
Okay.
Hey, my mom was here.
Your mom?
Yes.
I thought I should at least tell you.
I'm glad.
Why couldn't she come all this time?
I don't know.
I couldn't even see her face.
She borrowed money from Dad ten years ago.
She only repaid him and left without seeing me.
Why?
I guess she didn't want to see me.
But you missed her.
You even looked for her in the streets.
Not at all. I hate her now.
She said she won't see me, so wh-what can I possibly...
I resent her.
But I also miss her.
I think I miss her even more.
I'm such a fool, right?
Do you want some onions? Should I grill them?
Onions? Hey, the onions...
Hey, why are you crying?
I always cry when someone else cries.
But I'm not crying.
You look like you are.
I mean, well... I do feel like crying.
But I know it, too.
You like San Ha, right?
Hey, don't worry. I didn't tell San Ha.
A third party shouldn't get involved in such things.
You should tell him yourself.
N-No, I don't.
I don't like San Ha Sunbae.
Oh, is that so?
I swear I really don't.
Of course, you'd say you don't.
I'll just say you don't.
Hey, I said I would grill it for you.
Spit it out. Spit it.
- It's spicy. Spit it out.
- He's shouting.
How many times did I say I really don't?
Hey, all right. I got it.
Let me tell you, just in case. San Ha doesn't like Hui Joo.
I'm certain about that, so don't worry.
I said I really don't.
What is she talking about?
Joo Won, did you put ointment on?
I should've done it instead of you.
No, I'm fine.
Isn't it about time for the last bus?
Your mom will worry if you stay out too late.
Walk her to the stop.
Excuse me?
You should walk her, Kang Hae Joon.
I'll...
walk her to the bus stop.
It's okay, right?
I'll come with you, then.
Do you want me to clean this up alone?
Text me when you get home.
- Make sure you see her get on the bus.
- Yes.
Let's go.
I'll go now.
Take care.
Can't you read the room?
Don't you know to stay out of it when you should?
Why?
Why is everyone telling me to catch on lately?
Why? Did Kim San Ha say he liked Dal?
Aigoo, you're seriously...
Hey, use your brain.
- He doesn't?
- He doesn't.
I thought it was about to get complicated.
Come on, clean up.
She doesn't even know her friend likes Kim San Ha.
He doesn't even know Dal likes him.
E-Excuse me.
I'm saying this not to be misunderstood...
but I don't have feelings for you, Sunbae.
I know. You like Kang Hae Joon.
Try to be understanding.
Kang Hae Joon is clueless in these matters.
He's the type to understand only if you're straightforward with him.
I'll never be able to get to him, then.
Why didn't you tell him?
It was great timing.
What if I never get to see him after?
Once I confess, I can never go back to before I confessed.
That's true.
He might say he'd never see you again.
I can just walk alone from here.
It must be hard to clean up by themselves. You should head back.
Joo Won told me to see you get on the bus.
Let's go.
Okay.
Why do you keep calling me?
If I didn't answer, just take that as an answer.
Oppa.
So Hui, it's you.
I told her you mistook her for someone else, but I don't think it worked.
She cried herself to sleep.
What did you think I'd say that you let So Hui call me?
I was sure it wouldn't be something nice.
Don't use So Hui as your shield.
I'll talk to So Hui myself next time.
Did you do well on the exam?
I called to ask about that.
Did you choose which college to apply to?
Not yet.
You must have a few options.
If you choose Seoul, we'll see each other often.
I need to know in advance to help you.
No. I'll be going to college here.
Will you live the rest of your life in that rural town?
Is that really all you're worth?
Yes. That's all I'm worth.
I'll have to be on my deathbed to see your face, won't I?
- Why do you talk like that–
- I'm hanging up.
Did you truly get only one wrong?
I guess that's my limit.
Who are you calling?
I need to ask the administration to get an estimate for a banner.
Did you tell your father you're applying for Seoul National University's medical school?
Hold on a minute.
What's your dad's phone number?
I've been telling you for a year that I'm going to Myungju University.
I said I would discuss this with your father.
Gosh, why bother leaving home to suffer?
Should I leave my warm home and warm meals?
Why? Why do you insist on going to Myungju University?
I mean, Myungju University is closest to home.
Hey, people wish to enroll at Yeonhui University, but they can't.
But what did you say? "It's closest to home"?
Do you have treasure hidden in your house?
Don't you aspire to play basketball where the big leagues are?
Why do you play basketball?
Because I take after my dad.
Anyway, I'll beat all the Seoul guys this time, Teacher.
I'll go to Myungju University and beat all the Seoul guys.
I'll just win against them all.
Why, you little.
Oh, really? Why, you little...
What? Hey, stay put.
You're fooling around again. Stay put.
I'm nervous.
Let's take it easy today.
Sure. They're nothing.
I'll just make ten three-pointers and sub out.
Jeong Hoon, you can beat him on your own. You know, right?
Hey, the game's starting soon!
Oh, San Ha.
Didn't you talk with Dad over the phone?
Your dad told me to go with whatever you want.
Are you laughing? Can you laugh right now?
When a person is born, he goes to Seoul.
When a horse is born, it goes to Jeju Island.
You were born in Seoul, so why won't you go to Seoul?
Look here now.
As one sows, so shall he reap.
However, if you reap what you didn't sow, then the seed
must return to where it was from. Don't you agree?
I don't even know if this will be of any use.
- Hurry up.
- There won't be any seats.
There won't be any seats. Hurry.
Hurry up and come.
We won't get a seat.
O-Over here!
Over here.
Nice seats.
Right?
I came a bit early to get the best seats.
- Do you like basketball?
- No.
I like you.
Why is he so bold?
I can never change my heart once it's set.
Just like a rock.
I can spend time with you throughout the game.
So would I miss this chance?
- Do you want to change seats?
- No.
Where's your sketchbook? Let's show some support.
If you also want to cheer, hold the other end.
I prepared my own.
No need to be intimidated. That Unni has nothing going on with Kang Hae Joon.
Yes, you're right.
Over here!
Here.
Why?
It's nothing. I must've been mistaken.
It's tight here.
There are no other seats.
The friendly match between the two schools known for their basketball teams,
Haedong High and Hwimyeong High will begin in five minutes.
- He's not a big deal.
- He's got nothing.
He can't even grab a ball properly.
Do you know him?
Well, he was here in Grade 10.
He lost the captain position to Hae Joon all the time.
I heard he's learning from a pro or something, but he just transferred to Seoul.
But why is he doing that?
Ignore him. Safety always comes first.
Long time no see.
Your dad still makes kalguksu, right?
Yes.
Aigoo, his business must be doing badly.
Those were on sale at the outlet.
Learn elite basketball today for free.
You can take notes, too.
And don't cry when you lose.
Guys,
tighten your shoelaces.
If I see anyone's feet stuck to the ground,
you're dead meat after the game.
One shot!
♫  There was a time when I was filled with hopes about my dream  ♫
♫  That dream made me feel like I owned the world  ♫
♫  My empty heart was filled with promises we made  ♫
♫  I didn’t even know it was cold  ♫
♫  I had nothing to envy  ♫
♫  Everything existed for us  ♫
♫  Like the sun in the clearest summer sky  ♫
♫  Those shattering days when we lived for each other  ♫
Well done!
Haedong!
♫  You are always my world  ♫
♫  And when we are together, the world sparkles  ♫
♫  Like the sun of each day that comes and goes  ♫
♫  May we shine brightly and may we last forever  ♫
- Don't, don't.
- Don't stop me!
When will you teach me some elite basketball?
Don't cry.
Darn, so annoying.
♫  I must finish the race without giving up  ♫
♫  I can't afford to get tired  ♫
♫  My dreams are watching me  ♫
It's okay! It's okay!
♫  It can't stop me  ♫
♫  Just wait and see how I overcome this path with passion  ♫
♫  I'll prove it to you without a doubt  ♫
Darn it.
Why are you here again?
Gosh, you scared me.
What? Can't a dad watch his son's basketball game?
What are you scheming?
Children should stay out of this.
The adults will take care of it.
That's because I made a great pass.
What are you saying? It's because I scored the basket.
Without my pass, you couldn't have scored.
What?
Oh, hey!
We have an afterparty to go to.
It'll be just a moment.
Hey, I'm hungry.
That man was just here.
Who?
Your birth dad.
And?
Did he leave?
I think he's on his way to Ahjusshi to discuss things.
Darn it.
Hey, come if you can, even if it's late! Got it?
- Let's just go.
- Let's go.
- Let's go eat without him.
- Forget him.
Dad, you could've come to watch if it weren't for the store.
I raised Kang Hae Joon well, didn't I?
That's great if he won.
Really?
Then I'll have dinner with Ahjusshi.
Okay. Call me if you'll be late.
All right.
What are you doing here?
This is my store.
You didn't even watch the game during such a historic victory.
Instead, you're carrying that stuff around?
My goodness. Get in the car.
I'm not getting in.
Aigoo, I knew this would happen.
The envelope got bigger.
This very famous school sent three students to prestigious universities last year.
Why didn't you tell me Hae Joon was great at basketball?
Did you hide it from me?
Why are you speaking informally?
I've heard parents go crazy when their children are lacking.
But who knew a parent could go crazy when their children are incredible, too?
Why go crazy when they're incredible?
I know Hae Joon is incredible,
but I haven't gone crazy.
That's what's driving me crazy.
You know it. You're well aware.
Then, you should've sent him to Seoul!
All the boys in the opposing team from Seoul learned from the pros.
How will he beat kids like them in this small town
without a proper director or coach? He's not a god!
How great would it have been to send him to a basketball class?
He would have had a notable title by now!
How will you raise him when he's so amazing?
If you can't, I'm telling you I will!
Why do you keep getting in his way?
You scum.
"In his way"? In whose way?
Don't.
Mr. Yoon opens the store at 5:00 a.m. and prepares the flour.
Then, he goes home at 7:00 a.m. to feed the kids breakfast.
For ten years straight.
He fed the child you abandoned like that for ten years straight. Got that?
I mean, feeding the children is a given.
Are there any children out there who starve these days?
And what I'm talking about is something on a higher level...
Seriously. Tragedy doesn't come after failure.
It starts with complacency.
What you're doing is setting up my son, Yang Hae Joon, for failure!
Hae Jon's last name is Kang.
Who are you to change his surname as you wish?
If anyone is sending him to America, it'll be me.
By what means?
That's for me to figure out.
The store is under my name, too.
"The store"? This store?
This store that has been around for ages?
This jerk! Where is the salt?
Darn. Fine. We will see.
That fool. Petty scum.
This jerk.
You scumbag.
He is Yang Hae Joon.
He's my son, no matter what anyone says.
Hey!
Wh-Who does he think he is?
Gosh, that jerk is really fast.
Why are you looking at these?
Let me just take a look.
It doesn't cost money to look.
Wow...
They have a real basketball team here.
I would've looked into these if only I had known.
Well, now you do. So will you let that man take him?
No way.
I won't.
I'm not someone who should be treated like this.
Why is he running like that?
Why did you visit Dad again?
What did you tell him?
Did that arrogant-looking boy tell on me?
Get in for now.
Do you want to talk in the middle of the street?
It has been over a year since I quit flour.
We aren't here to eat.
What did you tell Dad?
"Dad"?
We talked about America and basketball. All that I mentioned before.
I'm not going.
You have to.
I saw you play today.
I'm not going!
Go.
Why are you angry?
I'm the one who unfairly got rejected for offering to support you.
Honestly, your dad...
If that man wasn't lying about raising you like his own,
he would tell you to follow me.
If he stops you from going,
then you're just someone else's child to him.
Stop with the nonsense.
Why would he send his child away?
To prosper.
What parent would keep his child in this rural town
to block any chance of studying?
I can achieve everything I want to in Haedong.
That's that.
I'm leaving.
Hey.
What?
Do you...
think this world is easy for someone like me
to get a free pass in life?
What are you saying?
I'm saying I've had to cross the line at times in my life.
If I were to go astray in the slightest,
that small-town restaurant...
could disappear as soon as tomorrow.
Stop being ridiculous.
Feel free to resist me if you're curious.
I'm telling you loud and clear.
Don't mess with Dad.
If you want to see how I'll react,
feel free to challenge me.
Even when he throws a tantrum,
he's adorable.
If I were to go astray in the slightest,
that small-town restaurant
could disappear as soon as tomorrow.
Darn it!
Is the afterparty not over yet?
Come home and eat if you're still hungry.
Forget it.
I told him loud and clear.
I'll just tell him to leave again if he comes back.
Yes.
Did that ahjusshi come back? Why?
Probably to convince him to go to America with him.
But if he goes to America, he probably won't be able to come back.
What if Kang Hae Joon is unable to reject him again?
That won't happen.
He even plans to attend college nearby.
America?
No way.
That's true.
By the way, this is really good.
Stop eating.
You said it's good.
Restrain yourself so we can eat it with everyone at home.
Ahjusshi, give us one bag of red beans and one bag of Choux cream fillings.
All right, please wait a moment.
- Do you want me to carry it?
- No, it has to stay crispy.
Wait until we get home to eat it.
I thought you went to an afterparty? Did you not eat much?
Yes.
Sure.
Eat slowly.
Okay.
I'm asking you just in case.
I heard the Seoul team you beat today are actually really good players.
To have beaten that kind of team...
Do you want to play basketball at a higher level?
Why all of a sudden?
Did someone say something?
No, I just heard kids go to America to pursue basketball these days.
I haven't been able to watch your games these days because I'm so busy with the store.
The townspeople say it's a waste to let your skills rot in this town.
What townspeople?
What?
Just some townspeople.
It's not like Seoul or America is close by.
How can I live there alone?
I mean, you can still think about it.
This crab.
So he just left?
Yes.
I told him to leave and never come back.
Where did you buy this?
It's the best fish-shaped bun I've had recently.
Take your time eating it.
How can I eat any slower than this?
Who is it at this hour?
My mom.
Are you not answering it?
It's probably So Hui. I made a mistake last time.
You guys can keep eating.
- Okay.
Hello?
Sorry?
Dad!
I...
Mom... Mom was in an accident.
So Hui's dad, in the driver's seat...
passed away.
♫  One day  ♫
♫  A precious memory  ♫
♫  Entered my small heart the day you smiled brightly  ♫
♫  And another day  ♫
♫  The memory of you holding me  ♫
♫  The day I wept freely, surrendering all my pain and struggles  ♫
♫  We loved all those days  ♫