Why am I going through all this trouble?
(A man travels all around the world...)
I need to find something new.
(in search of a new flavor.)
You can find new ingredients
in a new place.
(JUNGLE BOB, a journey of 53,730km)
(Vanuatu)
(Palawan)
(Amazon)
(Andes)
(Pacific Ocean)
(He went around the world,)
(but his search for the taste didn't end.)
You can...
only meet new things far from home.
(the Caribbean Sea)
(The most beautiful sea on Earth)
I'm so excited.
("The most beautiful place
where a man can see")
(Christopher Colombus said it
after arriving in the Caribbean Sea.)
(It's always passionate
above the Caribbean Sea.)
(It's blessed with great weather
and abundant ingredients.)
(Where barbecue began)
(Barbacoa)
(Since Columbus' discovery in 1492,)
(it's where diverse food cultures
converged.)
(The center of Caribbean food)
(The biggest storage
of delicacies of Caribbean food)
(They head to the Dominican Republic.)
(The new journey begins.)
(The four BOB friends enter...)
(a new world of flavors.)
(Kim Ok Vin, Taste Navigator,
Ryu Su Young, Captain)
(Yun Nam No, Cooking Maniac,
Lee Joon, Passionate Maniac)
(Tasty Mission in the Caribbean Sea
begins.)
If we get to the end of the rainbow,
there'd be a pot of gold.
(We're here for a pot of flavors.)
(Ryu Su Young, Captain)
(The return of a true captain)
(And another companion on this journey)
(Kim Ok Vin, Taste Navigator)
(General Ok's amazing moments...)
(as she gets in her element)
(The Caribbean Sea is a stage for me.)
(Leave the undersea ingredients to me.)
(From General Ok of Peru
to a warrior of the Caribbean Sea)
(And the new BOB friend
who came to the Caribbean Sea)
(Ryu Su Young, 47 years old, captain)
(A cooking boy next to the captain)
I'm glad I've been cooking...
- for a long time.
- Why?
Because you're next to me cooking.
(They're both fascinated by each other.)
(A shy guy with a buzz cut)
(Let us tell you about this guy.)
(The moment he appeared,)
(he captured Choi Hyun Seok's eyes.)
(The Cooking Maniac is here.)
(Chef Yun Nam No)
(An eccentric maniac
who breaks the boundaries of cooking)
(Yun Nam No, Cooking Maniac)
(Any ingredient of the Caribbean Sea...)
(turns into Yun Nam No's dish.)
(A rising star chef
in the global spotlight)
(However, instead of delicacies,)
(he's practically living on junk food?)
You're quite something.
Why?
You ate three cup noodles
early in the morning.
- I had two. Not three.
- I thought it was three.
(Palm oil needs to be recharged
as much as he works.)
(He eats hard...)
(and works hard.)
(This man, right beside the chef
of "Culinary Class Wars")
(He's full of passion.)
(Lee Joon, Passionate Maniac)
(Boasting his passion)
(He's hyped energy comes out any time.)
(As his instinct leads him...)
(and as his body leads him)
(Somewhere between passion and madness)
(This madman with bright eyes...)
(has taken over the Caribbean Sea.)
(Embracing both day and night
of the Caribbean Sea,)
(an epic journey
of Caribbean food unfolds.)
The second journey, CARIB BOB, begins!
Yes!
(Among familiar faces)
Things change completely.
- It's totally different.
- It'll be a whole other vibe.
- Hello?
- Who are you?
I'm a new member.
- You are?
- Yes, I'm new.
Please introduce yourself.
Hello, I'm the new member
of CARIB BOB, Lee Joon.
Hello, I'm the kitchen guy
of CARIB BOB, Yun Nam No.
- "The kitchen guy?"
- Yes.
What about Cooking Maniac?
That sounds too provocative.
I can't wait to find out
the dishes you'll make.
We have high expectations.
I'm sure it'll satisfy your expectations.
- Really?
- I'm confident.
- My mouth is already watering.
- I'm excited...
because Chef Choi also
did an excellent job...
- in PERU BOB.
- Right.
He was exceptional.
And the Caribbean Sea has
an abundance of ingredients.
Just look at Nam No's build.
He makes generous servings for every dish.
- I love that.
- It's hearty.
I can't stand tiny portions,
even if I have to leave food.
You're not talking
about Hyun Seok, are you?
- Are you referring to him?
- Be careful with your words.
We just pursue different paths in cooking.
Joon had a shoot with me
right after he came back.
I asked him how the trip was,
and he said he was the life of the party.
- Meaning he took over the shoot?
- He said he did everything,
- and he was literally the main host.
- Hold on.
- He was the main host?
- I'm so excited to find out.
(That's new to hear.)
I mean, that happens...
when you try to be funny.
- Anyway, we'll see.
- I'll look forward to it.
- The main host, Lee Joon.
- He's the protagonist.
(What's the truth behind this rumor?)
(The Caribbean Sea)
(Beside the Caribbean Sea)
Dominican Republic.
It's located on the island of Hispaniola,
which Columbus discovered.
I see.
(They arrived at the Caribbean Sea
at 19:05.)
(Bayahibe, Dominican Republic)
- Hey.
- Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Hello, everyone.
- That was such a long trip.
- We've come a long way.
I'm happy to meet you all.
It's already so peaceful
from the beginning.
It feels like "Culinary Class Wars"
all over.
They're the tertiary judges.
It tastes really...
(Having a small talk
with someone particular in mind)
profound.
Who's older?
- I was born in 1990, and he's...
- I was born in 1988.
- So, you're the youngest.
- That's right.
- And you were born in 1988.
- Right.
- I was born in 1987.
- It's 1987, yes.
- I guess it's all set, then.
- Yes.
The first, second, third, and fourth.
- That's why I'm pouring the beer.
- The youngest.
I like how they have bright faces.
I feel so great right now.
- They're younger than me.
- You've got younger members.
- In Peru...
- Right.
- I was the young member.
- Hyun Seok was older than you.
Your face is glowing. It's so obvious.
- Look at that big smile.
- Since they're younger than me,
it's easier for me to ask them
to do things.
Did you forget about the Choi duo?
- I already forgot about them.
- That's right.
I can just tell she's completely
moved on from them.
(She can't stop laughing.)
It's nice to have younger members.
What do you need me to do?
There's nothing to do now. Relax.
- Thank you.
- You're going to be busy...
starting tomorrow.
You need to be careful
what you wish for here.
Or else you'll have to work your butt off
for the ingredient.
I should choose my words carefully.
Let's say you craved lobster.
Then, you have to get it yourself
in the water.
In fact...
I mean, I'm always ready to dive in.
We've got you a map.
This is just like "Jumanji."
- The map is awesome.
- But it's usually bad luck.
What is that?
- It's like a treasure hunt.
- I know.
Is this an actual map?
So what is it?
What kind of map is that?
(The map for Tasty Mission
in the Caribbean)
I see Mano Juan,
Santo Domingo,
Baní,
and San Rafael.
- I see a treasure chest.
- Yes, Eldorado.
- There are pictures of the ingredients.
- But...
- Crayfish and other things.
- There's even a blue marlin.
So, they are the ingredients
of each place.
I guess we're going all
across the southern Caribbean.
- Yes, in order.
- Right.
Goodness.
Look at that.
A feast is about to happen.
We're here right now,
so I guess we're going
to this island tomorrow.
Probably.
There's something I want to try here.
Do you know Sanji from "One Piece?"
He runs a restaurant on the sea.
- I'd like to achieve that dream.
- That's interesting.
(The cooking boy dreams
of comic-book fantasy.)
We'll be cooking a lot of seafood dishes.
I genuinely want my fantasy
from "One Piece" to come true.
- Cooking with Kraken, and...
- Kraken dish?
And huge sea creatures.
- How do you read this?
- Mano Juan.
- Yes, Mano Juan.
- We're here right now.
It's Mano Juan tomorrow.
- Gosh.
- My goodness.
Just look at the color of the ocean.
(To where the unknown ingredient lies)
I'm so excited.
- Look at the water.
- It's so clear.
I can see everything underwater.
It surely has the Caribbean vibe!
It's like "Pirates of the Caribbean!"
It's a real Caribbean bay,
not the water park!
You're right.
(Crossing the vast Caribbean)
- Let's go!
- Oh, my!
Awesome!
This is so much fun!
This is crazy.
(The BOB friends are taking
the first steps of their journey.)
This boat is so fast!
It's unbelievably fast.
I feel so refreshed!
(The best feeling ever)
This is...
Can you believe
the color of the water here?
It's unbelievable.
It's exquisitely beautiful.
It's so clear that you can see everything.
- Unbelievable.
- It's beautiful!
It doesn't feel...
like I'm on Earth.
It feels like I'm getting drawn
into a mystical world.
He sounds like he's had too much beer.
It feels surreal.
No, I was completely sober.
(Surprisingly sober)
Look, a rainbow!
- What?
- Really?
- That's incredible!
(A rainbow in the Caribbean?)
It's a rainbow!
- It's a real rainbow!
- A rainbow!
Look at that rainbow!
I can't believe it!
(A perfect rainbow has bloomed
in the sky.)
- How can that be?
- It's a rainbow!
- What?
- No way!
- Really?
- It's a rainbow!
(Everyone is excited here too.)
It looks like CGI!
- It doesn't look real!
- How can that be?
The rainbow is connected!
The rainbow!
I've never seen a full rainbow!
You're right.
This is the biggest rainbow I've seen.
It's a double rainbow!
Double rainbow!
- That has to be fake!
- It looks fake, right?
- How is that real?
- They were so clear.
They're the exact rainbows we imagine.
They're so vibrant!
I've never seen such vibrant rainbows.
How is that real?
- I've never seen anything like that.
- I've never seen such a perfect rainbow.
- Me neither.
- It's perfect.
- It's beautiful.
- I'm in awe.
(A vibrant seven-colored rainbow)
It's incredible.
(Even the Caribbean native is in awe.)
Captain!
She has a driving license.
- Really?
I get a dopamine rush in the ocean.
You know?
I live for the joy I get in the water.
I adore the ocean.
(Aqua Ok Vin loves water.)
I have driving licenses
for yachts and boats.
- You can drive a boat?
- That's so cool!
I'm also a certified safety guard
for water sports.
(Water sport safety guard course)
I have a permit for shellfish harvesting.
For bare-hand shellfish harvesting?
(She also has a free diving permit.)
That's incredible.
(The aqua woman has
all sorts of licenses.)
Come on!
- Okay.
- Me?
- You want me to drive?
- Yes.
- Come on!
- Really?
(Here comes Ok Sparrow.)
Let's go, Captain Ok Vin!
How can I drive it?
Okay.
(Ok Sparrow is taking the wheel...)
(without prior training.)
(Speeding up)
Let's go!
(You're the best!)
That's so cool.
Hold on!
- Let's go!
- Right on!
(Warrior Ok is taking over the Caribbean
with her wild driving.)
Your energy is different.
Even I can tell that.
You're like a different person.
I didn't know she was this kind of person!
And I've been watching her for six weeks!
(First time seeing her true self
in six weeks)
You're so cool!
You're incredibly cool!
(A thumbs-up from the captain)
This feels awesome!
(The refreshing sail
for the heart and the mind is...)
(making them feel the happiest.)
Right on!
Off to the ocean we go
You can tell he's genuinely excited.
- Definitely!
- It's so clear.
It takes a lot to sing that song.
(The former K-pop singer
with a booming voice is joining.)
You look like an old man!
Seriously!
(He can't hide his 70s and 80s vibe.)
Did you see that heart?
- Yes, the beer-induced heart!
- He's like a middle-aged manager.
He's an excited middle-aged manager.
The middle-aged manager is here.
(In the zone)
(The newbie is dazzled
by the middle-aged manager.)
(After a long sail full of laughter)
I see a village! Look at that.
- Finally!
- A village, at last!
Is that Mano Juan?
Yes, it is.
This is Mano Juan!
- We've arrived.
- Finally.
(Dominican Republic)
It's a village.
Finally!
(The first destination)
(Mano Juan)
I can't believe it!
(A paradise of nature)
It's dazzling.
It takes one hour by boat.
It's truly a hidden paradise.
I can't believe how beautiful it is.
(A tiny island village known
as the hidden gem)
Not many tourists come here.
I bet.
(The traditional fishing culture
has been preserved,)
(so the locals live in harmony
with the Caribbean.)
Unbelievable.
It's absolutely beautiful!
(A place to enjoy nature
in its natural habitat)
(The first journey starts in Mano Juan.)
Let's go!
(Getting off the boat after one hour)
It took an hour to get there.
(Everyone is getting off.)
It's so nice!
(Watch out, Ok Vin!)
Are you okay?
(The ocean almost swallowed Aqua Ok Vin.)
Watch out!
Oh, gosh!
There's a dip here.
Nice, Joon!
There was a cliff under our feet.
There's a big dip here!
- Is there?
- Yes.
- The water suddenly came up to my waist.
- You scared me!
I almost got sucked into the water!
No, Ok Vin!
I got her!
(A rough welcome, only for Ok Vin)
She still looks so happy.
Happier than she was in Peru!
You'll need to control yourself there.
(Embarrassed)
What a rough place.
I'm all torn apart!
Slapstick comedy is for Daniel, not me!
We've made it here!
(Entering Mano Juan)
Look at the clouds!
- I'm starving.
- Let's go there.
Wait.
First, we must find our house.
We need to find our house
to cook something.
- We hadn't eaten anything.
- We had to find our house first.
We hadn't eaten anything until then.
- It's the fourth house in Mano Juan.
- The fourth house.
- The fourth house in Mano Juan.
- Yes, the fourth house.
Why don't we look for a house
with number four on it?
Right.
Look for house number four in Mano Juan.
- Number four?
Does that mean...
every house in Mano Juan is numbered?
I guess so.
- I'm so hungry.
- House number four.
- Number four.
- The fourth house.
But these houses aren't numbered.
- Number four?
- How can we find it?
That was the start of our mental meltdown.
The palm trees are so short and cute.
Yes, they look so cool.
- It's not scary.
- No.
I feel so happy to be so far away.
Number 14!
- Number 14!
The houses are numbered!
(Have they found the numbers
on the houses?)
There's a number on it.
Really?
(The numbers are written on the posts!)
- If that's 14...
- We can find it in no time!
That's so easy!
That's the whole village.
- If we go straight...
- I'm sure we'll find it soon.
(The houses and stores are marked
with numbers.)
Number 13.
Numbers 17, 14, and 13.
The farther we go this way,
the shabbier the buildings get.
It feels like we're getting farther away
from civilization.
The houses are getting smaller!
Whatever.
- There's number six.
- Six.
(Getting closer to number four)
- We're almost there.
- Please be a good house!
Please!
- Five!
- Please!
Please!
That must be the fourth house, then.
Isn't this house number four?
- The next one...
- This one!
This is house number four?
- I knew it! It's number four!
- Is this the fourth house?
Come on!
I'll be really mad
if that's house number four!
There's no house.
- Are we camping?
- I got hopeful!
If this is house number four,
I'll be furious!
- It looks like a heritage site.
- Seriously!
No way. But that's house number five.
- Then, this is...
- Number four.
- This should be number four, then.
- Yes.
This can't be true.
- That's an abandoned building.
- It looks haunted.
- I can't believe it.
- This is going too far!
- It looks like a haunted house.
- It does!
Please!
- Could it be that one?
- Please!
(There has to be a different house!)
Could it be that one?
(Please!)
Four? Four!
(They've found house number four
with a solid red roof.)
- Right on!
- Perfect!
- I'm so glad!
- This is perfect!
- It looks so clean!
- Perfect!
- I love it.
- Come this way.
Amazing.
(Happily entering the house)
What a perfect home!
- Thank you!
- There's a kitchen!
- Perfect!
It's wonderful.
It's great!
(A clean kitchen and living room
in wood tones)
I love it here!
It's perfect.
- We even have fans.
- It's amazing.
There's an oven!
Nam No, we have an oven!
- We have a nice kitchen.
- Oh, my goodness.
Seriously?
What a nice place to stay.
- They need to get some proper rest.
- They really do.
- They worked so hard.
- The lodging is so nice.
What a beautiful place to stay.
(House Four with a red roof,
right on the Caribbean beach)
This place is even better than I expected.
- It's so nice. The inside...
- The kitchen is perfect for cooking.
(With the Caribbean Sea
in the background,)
(a new world of flavors begins.)
(A new symphony of Caribbean taste
starts soon.)
I learned something about Nam No
on this trip. When he's cooking,
- his eyes change.
- He becomes a different person.
He becomes a totally different person.
(They found the house.)
(But it's already lunchtime.)
They need to eat now.
I'm really hungry.
I think I've been really hungry
since I woke up at seven.
(Is there anything in the fridge?)
As expected, the fridge is empty.
(Nothing at all?)
I'm dying.
What should we do?
Joon really can't stay hungry.
The biggest problem with Joon is...
that he can't function without carbs.
- He completely shuts down.
- And he gets super sensitive?
He'd eat anything, even plain sugar.
- Really?
- I noticed...
that he couldn't stand up straight
when he was too hungry.
I'm serious.
- That's true.
- Really?
I was worried
when I heard he was going there.
I thought, "He can't survive
even a moment of hunger."
(Save Joon from hunger!)
I'm starving.
(They head out to find food.)
(His face looks awful from hunger.)
I don't mind losing sleep.
I'm fine with that.
But food?
When I'm hungry, I can't even talk.
- I have no energy.
- You're right.
I can't go anywhere
or do anything like this.
I think even his lips are turning blue.
(Please let there be a store nearby.)
How much farther...
Wait. Isn't that a store?
- Isn't this a place?
- Is it?
I think it is.
(They finally found a restaurant.)
- They sell food like that too.
- What's this?
It's street food.
What is this?
- Oh, it's an empanada.
- I see. Banana!
I think that's not it.
It's some sort of...
- It's Spanish...
- Did he mistake empanada for banana?
It's kind of like a fried dumpling.
It looks so good.
(After wrapping up various fillings...)
- It's similar to a dumpling.
- Right.
You can find empanadas easily
at Spanish restaurants in Seoul too.
It's really good.
Two of them?
(Smelling)
This is crazy!
He's losing it.
What is that smell? How is it this good?
(He's about to pass out.)
What's this?
What's this? I think it's pasta.
(It's the spaghetti we all know.)
I need it.
Gosh. The smell is amazing.
(Has he been starving for days?)
How can you look so miserable?
I'm desperate.
(Let me bag it for you.)
(They bought empanadas
and some spaghetti without hesitation.)
Oh, boy.
The pasta looks like
it's been sitting out for a while.
(They rushed back to the lodging.)
- Ok Vin?
- Please come out.
Great. Let's eat.
Come on and eat some.
Look at the food here. It looks rough.
Look at his face!
He's almost...
Ok Vin, it's banana.
I mean...
(It's an empanada, not a banana.)
I see.
- Thanks for the food. Is it good?
- Geez!
- I'm hungry.
- This is crazy good!
It's the best pasta I've ever had
in my life!
Is it that good?
I think hunger messed with his brain.
But it's so good!
It's insanely delicious!
(He keeps eating...)
(and eating.)
Honestly, that's better food
than what he usually gets at home.
- That's true.
- Right?
- What does he eat at home?
- Mostly just...
instant rice with some kimchi and laver.
That's it.
Do you know how harsh he is to me?
A few days ago,
he sent me a prison meal plan.
- A prison meal plan?
- He said inmates eat better than I do!
- I mean, their meals...
- Why would I eat like that?
But looking at it, I thought,
"It does look better than mine."
How good was the pasta, Nam No?
I just ate it because I was starving.
What did it taste like?
It was a basic tomato sauce one.
Edible, but...
I was honestly confused
seeing him praise it so much.
I wouldn't say I was inspired.
"How should I cook for someone
with that kind of palate?"
If he reacts the same way
to your cooking...
That means your dish is
as good as that pasta.
You can't really tell, right?
- It might actually hurt your feelings.
- Of course, it would.
I've made up my mind.
I'm going to move Joon with my cooking!
Now I'm really confident
after seeing how much he loved it.
I'm serious. This is the best so far.
For real.
(He's scraping up every last bit.)
He's so easy to impress.
Now that we're done,
we need to decide who's going fishing...
and who's getting other ingredients.
They're heading out right away.
- I'll go get some ingredients.
- Right.
- I'll check out what's in the water.
- In the water.
- Can you dive with her?
- Of course!
You can trust me.
I'll get everything!
(Team Divers: Ok Vin and Joon)
Nam No, you should ask around
if there's a grocery store nearby.
(Team Grocery: Nam No)
They have a small grocery store.
And I heard that they have
something special around here.
- What is it?
- Blue marlins.
- Blue marlins?
- Yes. Blue marlins.
Isn't that way too hard to catch?
He's going to catch one?
The big ones can weigh
anywhere from 450 to 900kg!
(Team Blue Marlins: Mr. Eo Nam Seon)
And you're planning to catch that
by yourself?
I think I can. Let me give it a shot.
- Let's get moving, shall we?
- Good.
- Let's go!
I've got a good feeling about this!
- I got excited!
- Me too!
Great.
- It's all about the spirit.
- It is.
(While Ok Vin gets changed in her room...)
What's that?
- What?
- Why is he coming out half-naked?
(He's putting on a changing show
on the street.)
Look at Joon's back! It looks so cool.
Geez. Look at those muscles.
What?
Is this for real?
As you can see,
he's got a lot of muscle mass.
Right.
(Envious looks)
But they're just beach muscles.
Right.
- He's not that strong.
- It's just between you and me!
- That's a secret!
- For photo shoots.
Why did you have to spill it?
- You're not that strong?
- Honestly, I'm not.
I look like a good diver,
but that's only in my head.
(In reality, he's just a newbie diver.)
(The newbie proudly shows off
his beach muscles.)
It looks like a commercial.
(I'm muscular but not strong.)
(But...)
How should I put this?
I've shown my upper body on TV a lot.
But this feels like
I'm revealing my lower body!
It feels really weird.
- Is it ripped here?
- It is.
It feels like I'm not wearing
anything down below.
Are you a flasher or something?
- Why does he keep showing...
- He needs medical help.
You look like a ballerino.
Let's strike a pose together.
I know.
Is this right?
I'm wearing a top, not a bottom.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
Ok Vin really looks like a pro.
She's got professional gear
and everything.
She's an amazing diver.
Be careful, okay?
- Watch out for the coral.
- All right.
I'll go first and board the fishing ship.
- Be safe.
- You got this.
Watch out
for the blue marlin's pointy nose.
- I'll break it and bring it back!
- That's it!
I'll grab it by the nose!
- See you.
- Let's go!
- You got this.
- Let's go too.
- Let's go!
- Go!
- You got this, Nam No.
- See you soon.
- Be safe.
- I'll get us about 20 fish.
- Twenty?
- Yes.
Don't worry. It's all about the spirit.
(Hunting is all about the spirit.)
You've spent a lot of time
underwater, right?
Yes, I have.
I love scuba diving,
so I've done it a lot.
Then you must not be scared at all.
But the ocean is the scariest place.
Because it's unpredictable?
It's unpredictable
and full of creatures below.
It's really scary.
Look at that!
That's incredible.
(Beneath the deep blue void,)
That's crazy!
Look at its eyes!
It's terrifying!
It's intimidating.
- How can they catch any of them?
- Are you serious?
(nature hides a treasure trove of food.)
(Mano Juan)
(To find the gem-like ingredients
hidden underwater,)
(they've arrived at El Dorado.)
The name is literally El Dorado.
(To the heart of El Dorado)
We need to be aggressive and catch a lot.
Sure.
- We only had pasta today.
- Yes.
So let's catch a lot for Nam No,
who can cook for us.
If I can't catch some here,
there's no reason for me to be here.
I'm not really good at anything
other than this.
If I had to dive there,
I could do it as long as I have equipment.
You might have to go a little deep.
About 25m.
- It's 25m?
- It's 25m.
- I can do free diving for that.
- That's really deep.
Ok Vin.
If it's 25m,
it's like going 7 to 8 stories down.
It can burst your eardrum.
She's a pro diver.
(Here comes Ok Vin, the ace diver.)
I'm happy to do anything to help...
since I'm a new member here.
Joon even got a certificate for this.
- He practiced a lot.
- Free diving?
- Yes.
- Yes, that's the one.
He's full of enthusiasm.
(Joon, the passionate diver,
is full of enthusiasm.)
(After a 50-minute sail, they've arrived
at El Dorado's treasure trove.)
(Getting ready to go with an odd tension)
(I must catch it.)
That's so cool.
(Ok Vin and Joon will dive
into the Caribbean.)
Off you go.
(Joon, the passionate diver,
will dive first.)
Let's do this!
(Here I go.)
(Diving in high spirits
without hesitation)
(Checking the depth of water
while steadying his breath)
(Ok Vin, the veteran diver,
gets ready to go too.)
I'm going in.
(Swish)
(Diving backward relaxedly)
(Where is Joon?)
(After checking where the other one is,)
(they move slowly
while getting warmed up.)
That's incredible.
(Starting their first Tasty Mission
in the Caribbean's golden spot)
(Shall I get started?)
(A swift dolphin kick)
- All the way down at once.
- She's holding her breath.
(Ok Vin, the ace diver,
has already reached the bottom.)
(feeling cozy)
Her movements are so light.
- She looks comfortable underwater.
- Right. She seems so relaxed.
(Ok Vin is gently flapping underwater.)
It doesn't feel
like she's holding her breath.
(Getting her breath back
while looking at the sea leisurely)
(But her eyes keep exploring
without a rest.)
(Let me look thoroughly this time.)
(Charging forward)
She's determined to do it.
(Swimming with ease...)
(and reaching the surface
of the water again)
(Searching through the gaps
between the rocks)
(As expected, the space between the rocks
is full of sea creatures.)
(Ok Vin is looking in the gaps.)
(Startled)
- It was just there.
- I ran into it on the way.
They can bite you.
(Something came out from the crack.)
I was so frightened.
(Startled, she heads out
of the water quickly.)
There's something in there.
What is it?
There's something,
but I'm scared because it's so big.
It's huge.
Of course, she'd be scared.
- I've never caught it before.
- Of course.
This is crazy.
(Suppressing her fear
and reentering cautiously)
(What was that?)
(Ok Vin's camera)
(This creature that is on full alert...)
Gosh. Look at that.
It's not easy to catch.
They must be delicious.
They're really good.
- The tail is filled with flesh.
- I know.
- It comes from the water.
- In the tail?
It's full of it.
(You can find this everywhere
in the Caribbean.)
- Look at how big it is.
- They're so fast.
How can you catch that?
- Goodness.
- Oh, my.
(Failing in her first attempt)
Look how fast it is.
They're faster than you think.
It's ready for an attack.
My gosh. Look. It's on alert.
(Furtively approaching from the back)
She's so brave.
It's trying to fight her.
(Screeching)
My goodness. She caught it.
Is it trying to escape from you?
- It's really strong.
- She's amazing.
(She captured the crayfish successfully.)
It's so scary.
She caught it.
She's like a female diver in Jeju.
Wasn't it scary?
It really was.
I've never seen this creature in my life,
but I had to grab it.
(It's the first one she caught
despite her fears.)
(XXXL size)
It's so big.
- Where do I put it?
- Over here.
I caught it!
(They acquired crayfish,
the second Tasty Mission ingredient.)
She had a really good start.
It's on the map too.
It's already amazing
from their first catch in the Caribbean.
(The first catch she bravely hunted)
I can't believe I caught it.
Nam No.
Su Young.
Wait for me.
I'll go and catch another one.
I'll get as many as I can.
She's amazing.
(Keeping up the momentum)
She seems to be more confident
after catching one.
(Be on your toes, crayfish.)
(Going round and round)
(Searching for food with a hawk eye)
(Check the location, then dive forward)
The gap between the rocks is
a treasure trove.
I can see that.
(Hide well, or I might spot your antenna.)
(They're hiding awfully well.)
(Stop hiding, guys...)
(because I'm coming to get you.)
(Between the rocks right next to her,)
(here's even bigger one.)
- What?
- Oh, my.
- It's insanely big.
(Slowly)
(Grabbing its antennae)
- She grabbed it by the antennae.
- So that's how you do it.
(No matter how hard she pulls,)
(it's crouching and won't let go.)
You can hold your breath for so long,
by the way.
(The standoff is continuing.)
(Screeching)
Look at it.
It sounds like an alien or something.
(Holding it down by the nape)
That's unbelievable.
Gosh. It's so strong.
It's very strong.
(Trying to hang on
and trying to get it out)
It's powerful.
She's like the natural enemy of crayfish.
(Getting crayfish twice in a row)
It's even bigger.
(Returning proudly)
(Here comes another one.)
(Big one after another big one)
What do I do?
This spot really is...
a treasure trove.
That must be why they put...
a treasure box on our map.
Seriously.
- You can't see it well from above.
- Why not?
You'll just see an antenna sticking out...
from between the rocks.
Did you catch all the crayfish
that day, Ok Vin?
(Remaining silent)
Where are you right now, Joon?
I must've been feeling anxious.
You're getting less air time than Daniel.
Come on.
- Seriously. I can't see you.
- What happened to "being the main host?"
How come I can't see you?
Where is the main host?
Why are they not showing me?
(Meanwhile, in the sea)
- Isn't that me?
- No.
- Do you wear a women's swimsuit?
- Of course not. It's not me.
(Ok Vin has gotten the hang of it,)
(and she dives back in.)
(Ok Vin's camera)
(She thoroughly combs through the rocks.)
(Under the rock right below her,)
(she found it.)
This is incredible.
(She lowers herself
so that it's easier to catch it...)
(and grabs it by the head.)
She's like one of those female divers
in Jeju.
Oh, like that?
She grabbed its head and pulled it.
(Now, she feels relaxed enough
to enjoy the process.)
(She elegantly swims back up
like a mermaid.)
(Screaming)
I caught it!
(She caught three crayfish in a row.)
We now have one crayfish...
per person!
"One crayfish per person."
If they're showing us this first,
it means the rest of them are
a complete mess.
- The rest of them...
- That's not true.
- They'll go, "On the other hand..."
- A total mess or completely edited out.
We don't even have footage of Joon
reacting?
(Were there any cameras filming him?)
I was doing my part somewhere.
- There he is.
There are waves,
so I can barely inhale before going in.
I can't even breathe from the start.
(The Caribbean current is
rougher than it seems.)
(The spirit wasn't good enough
to go right into the field.)
(I want to catch one, though.)
(Joon's camera)
(But I've come all this far.)
(He takes a breath...)
(and plucks up his courage
before he goes.)
(Flailing)
His leg movement already looks...
a bit clumsy.
He's such a rookie.
(He flounders like a rookie...)
(and takes his first dive.)
Look! Watch how cool he is.
- Okay.
- He'll be so cool now.
(Let's try catching anything.)
(Joon's camera)
(He looks around as he's floundering.)
What's that?
(He spots something.)
He's swimming down with some guts.
He is. That was pure strength.
(He gets as close to it as possible.)
(It's pointed, and it looks like a conch.)
He grabbed it!
- Oh, he dropped it.
- Did he drop it?
(He definitely grabbed it.)
Oh, no.
(It slips and goes back down.)
He can't go back now.
(But he's already out of breath.)
(Hurriedly swimming back up)
(Don't leave me here.)
(He tries to stay calm
and returns to the boat.)
I dropped it.
I'm going to go back for it.
I'll go back once I catch my breath.
Why is his face so pale?
(Meanwhile, Ok Vin stopped
where Joon was.)
(Looking around)
(It must be here somewhere.)
She's going in.
She's a total diver.
- Oh, it's the one he dropped.
- The one he dropped.
(The one that Joon dropped)
It was a gigantic conch.
- That would be enough for four people.
- Yes, it was huge.
It's as big as her face.
She's so relaxed,
even though she's holding her breath.
How does one do that?
- You look like an actual mermaid.
- She's so good.
You see people like her only in aquariums.
(She easily picks it up and swims up.)
That's the one!
- Wait.
- What?
That's the one!
She got it.
(Teary)
Yes, it was this guy.
Look.
(Fortunately,
Ok Vin retrieved his lost conch.)
It's the one
that Joon was trying to catch.
I still remember its taste.
It was so delicious.
- Was it?
- It was tasty.
- It was seriously good.
- It really was.
It has a fantastic texture.
(They acquired a lambi,
the second Tasty Mission ingredient.)
- It was upside down, right?
- Yes!
Just the way you dropped it.
(A near miss)
- This is good, though.
- Nice.
- Great job.
(We finally got the hang of it.)
We're going back in!
(Ok Vin and Joon set out to conquer
the treasure box of ingredients.)
Let's find the treasure.
(She slowly guides him
as he's new to this.)
- There's one.
- What?
There. Do you see it?
- Do you think you can dive in?
- Yes.
- There we go.
- Okay.
- Please catch one.
- He did really well.
(He snatches it faster than light...)
He's tired.
(and swims up.)
(He's become a skilled lambi hunter now.)
(Even when it's ten meters deep,
he dives in for lambis.)
He catches it right away and brings it up.
- He knows how to use his body.
- Exactly.
(Confident as ever)
(Everything he catches is...)
(extra large.)
Oh, I'm out of breath.
I almost missed it.
(In the meantime,
General Ok Vin is looking for crayfish.)
(One more, and she'll be able
to have one crayfish each.)
(But they're no longer to be seen.)
(She keeps searching.)
Word got out between the crayfish.
- They ran away?
- Yes, they're talking about you.
Like, "Watch out for that woman."
- Yes. "That woman..."
- "That woman?"
- "That woman..."
- "Watch out for her."
"She's hunting us, so watch out."
They're going, "She grabs you
by the head and pulls you out."
"She pulls your head out."
"She grabs you by the head
and pulls you out?"
(It's Crayfish and Ok Vin's
underwater battle.)
(Her search for crayfish gets longer.)
(She's starting to get exhausted
due to the long search.)
(She can't even go forward now.)
(For her,)
(Joon goes instead.)
I'm going!
- Look!
- Joon is going.
(He combs through the rocks...)
(to find the hidden crayfish.)
(He spots a long antenna under a rock.)
Could it be?
(He almost swam past it
without noticing it,)
(but he luckily found the crayfish.)
There you go.
(Snatching it from behind)
(Come here.)
(Joon caught the final crayfish...)
(to make it one crayfish per person.)
(We're proud of you, Joon.)
- He's done it.
- Well done.
(Covering his mouth
as he's still impressed)
Great job!
You did it!
(Panting)
It's like a movie scene.
(Although he's completely out of breath,)
(he can't let go of the one thing
that everyone wants.)
Joon made it!
(The passionate man has made it possible
for everyone to have one crayfish.)
- It's huge.
- It is big.
(The fourth crayfish)
(Joon's final effort made it possible...)
(for everyone
to have 1 crayfish and 1 lambi.)
- That's a lot.
- We have so much food.
I can't believe we caught all these.
(They're excited about today's harvest.)
- How did we catch so many?
- We have so many!
How come we have so many?
When I'm in the ocean,
I worry about what I should do
if I come across a great white shark.
But sharks don't attack you first.
But what if they do?
Then, you can shove its nose.
- Its nose?
- Yes.
(Then, you can shove the shark's nose.)
When you run into a shark,
shove its nose, and...
Are they usually that good-tempered?
- Because they have...
- Shove its nose, and you lose an arm.
(Shove its nose, and you lose an arm.)
After you push its nose...
After you push its nose,
- you're like this.
- "Where has it gone?"
Try to push it with the other arm, and...
- Do you think you can do it?
- They say that you should...
play dead when you run into a bear.
Apparently, you'll find yourself
in the sky when you open your eyes.
- As soon as it comes...
- Isn't that the same thing?
We'll keep that in mind.
You should, just in case you.
(We await anyone who can tell us a story
of surviving after shoving its nose.)
(Meanwhile, Nam No,
who was waiting on the island...)
Do they have a grocery store here?
There's a grocery store?
(He's looking everywhere
for a grocery store.)
(Cock-a-doodle-doo)
Where did that chicken crow?
Is that my game today?
He's like that jobless guy next door.
I miss my members. Where are they?
(Trudging)
When will they be back?
- Hello.
- What is that? Coconut?
- It is.
(Coconut is one of the top three crops.)
Coconut water.
(Do you want to see the inside?)
(His eyes are shining.)
So amazing.
Keep going.
He says to keep going.
I didn't know it was done by hand.
(He makes a hole and offers him a sip.)
He lets him try it.
- Can I try?
- It's coconut water.
What is it? Is it coconut water?
It's water.
(He didn't understand,
but he drank it anyway.)
It's amazing.
That was so good.
It's my first time seeing coconut.
It's so fascinating.
(The real coconut water amazed him.)
Gosh, it's delicious.
- I never tried it like this.
- What's so different?
Well...
It wasn't actually cold,
but it was so refreshing.
- Usually, it tastes pretty heavy.
- It was good.
People either love it or hate it.
My friend, where is a mart?
- A mart?
- That way.
- "Alli?"
- Yes, that way.
Do I turn right?
(It seems like there's a mart somewhere.)
- Okay, thank you.
- Okay.
(He goes toward the direction
he was told to.)
Do they have a mart here?
Hello.
(He's quite friendly.)
Nam No is pretty sociable.
Doesn't he look like a kid
running his mom's errands?
- That's a great way to put it.
- He's just saying hello.
- I'm on my way to get tofu.
- And it's his first time on that street.
Is there really a mart?
He's so cute.
Nam No is really cute.
- He looks like a cartoon character.
- His face is like an emoji all along.
It's somewhat lonely.
(I feel lonely.)
It looks like he's a resident there.
He's just adorable.
Can someone make a meme with that?
- He's like a cartoon character.
- Someone, please make emojis with that.
I can use that on a lot of occasions.
- It's perfect for an emoji.
- It should be called Caribbean Maniac.
"Caribbean Maniac?"
So cute.
(He goes as he's told for now.)
(What?)
(He manages to find a mart.)
Hello.
It's a local supermarket.
- Right.
- It's called "colmado."
That looks nice.
- It's really a small grocery store.
- Yes, it's small.
(Supplies are brought in
from the mainland twice a week.)
They source goods from the mainland.
Since it's an island,
most of them are canned food.
That looks good.
Things that don't rot.
- Because it's hard to store them.
- Right.
- Hello.
(Looking around)
His radar is on.
"What did Mommy tell me to get?"
(A giant baby is pondering.)
We need subtitles for that.
(If they come back with fish...)
I'll make broth first...
and put seafood in...
to cook spicy fish stew.
(Scanning ingredients for spicy fish stew)
He needs vegetables. There were none.
There were no onions, no garlic.
Onion and garlic.
(His eyes change.)
He instantly knows what he needs.
Yes, he has the whole recipe ready
in his brain.
(Onion and garlic)
What is this?
- It's pepper.
- Pepper?
(He gets a pepper and a paprika.)
That pepper is huge.
I need an eggplant.
(Carefully selecting the ingredients)
- I got everything.
- That's a lot.
I know.
What was this called?
Mama.
What is this?
In the Dominican Republic,
we call it "dallota."
"Dallota."
(It sounds like she's speaking Korean.)
It's sour?
(How is she speaking Korean?)
Do you speak Korean?
- How does she know Korean?
- She knows Korean?
(She was saying it was food,
but it made sense anyway.)
So...
I'll make fresh kimchi with that.
But if we don't get any seafood,
that's just a bunch of veggies.
(He scans for the ingredients
for when they failed fishing.)
This one... Hey, it's rice.
(He found rice.)
We need rice.
They only have this kind.
(He gets rice in case there's no seafood.)
Joon...
I think we need all of it to feed Joon.
(He even gets noodles.)
These noodles...
They have instant noodles?
Oh, I don't know. This should be good.
If they fail to catch anything at all,
it'll be a temple meal.
(Preparing temple food)
Thank you.
Nam No has a heart of a mother.
He wanted to feed us anyhow.
(Nam No returned from grocery shopping.)
I keep forgetting its name.
What was it called?
- I wonder how they taste.
- Me too.
A pepper should be really hot.
That pepper wasn't as hot as I thought.
Is that right?
(Heading out to the kitchen outside)
(Happy)
Shall we set the table?
Nam No, are you back from the market?
They're back.
(The diving team returns.)
She looks like a mom who's a fisherman.
"Hey, did you get anything?"
I see you have not much.
(Their hands seem pretty light.)
What is it?
What's this?
Is this like a local specialty?
I caught it.
I was too scared to go into the water.
He couldn't even get into the water.
Really? Why?
This really stresses me out.
What happened?
Should we pretend like
we didn't get anything?
- That's brilliant.
- You should...
(They suddenly plotted a prank.)
They were acting.
Let's improvise it as we go.
(These two actors have great teamwork.)
Su Young catches on fast,
so he would know,
- but Nam No would be fooled.
- You think so?
- I think he'll fall for it.
- Okay.
- Let's hide these.
- I can see him.
Put it away somewhere,
and don't look at him.
(The candid camera for Nam No is on.)
(They're acting with all their might.)
The current was too fast.
The boat just kept on rocking up and down.
- Really?
- When we got there,
we also were swayed along with it.
What should we do?
This is all we get for today.
I bought some vegetables...
so I could cook something up.
It's so frustrating.
- Seriously.
- Don't worry.
We can rely on Su Young, then.
He might catch something.
(The youngest is completely fooled.)
- He even stammers.
- He's so kind.
- That good boy.
- Right.
- He didn't want to hurt their feelings.
- He was trying so hard.
He's so kind.
- I couldn't even touch the water.
- Is that so?
Since I didn't witness it,
it sounds pretty scary.
Why would you do that?
He's really set out to tease him.
- I think I'm no good for this show.
- Oh, come on.
We need you to enjoy my food later on.
- He's so nice.
- You got something here.
- He's such an angel.
- What happened?
What even am I on this show?
No.
I can pull this off.
He's so cool.
- The equipment?
- Yes, we'll go get it.
I'll be here.
- We'll be back with equipment.
- Okay.
When you walked away,
I'm sure you thought, "We're screwed."
- I did.
- Did you?
I see.
- That was his first time cooking,
- I get him.
so of course, he'd feel so lost...
when they couldn't get anything
to cook with.
I wasn't mad at them or anything,
but I was annoyed in general.
- Oh, I get it.
- I had nothing to work with.
- He was annoyed by you guys.
- I wasn't annoyed at them.
No, I just said I wasn't.
I was upset that we had nothing to cook!
It'll be edited like you were mad at them.
I was mad because I couldn't feed them.
You can't set me up like that.
We just met, but you're pretty rude.
Being rude is what we do for a living.
- Please understand that.
- All right.
- This is how we get paid.
- It's our job.
Or else they won't pay us.
We can't do anything about it. I'm sorry.
What is wrong with him?
What is the matter with him?
- Joon.
- What are you doing?
His shoe even came off.
(It's also their job
to throw physical gags.)
That was hilarious.
- "Being rude was our job" was so funny.
- Gosh, it was so funny.
- They get paid when they are rude.
- It's their job.
We don't get paid if we're polite.
- Shall we go?
- Shall we?
- Let's go. In 1, 2, 3.
- In 1, 2, 3.
(Nam No, here come our ingredients.)
That's awesome.
- That should make a feast.
- Nam No is approaching.
- He missed us.
- He's going around the back.
- Should we hide?
- Don't let him see us.
(This poor thing doesn't know a thing.)
Nam No!
(Genuine shock)
That's a genuine reaction.
We caught something.
We got all of these.
That's really me. I had no idea.
(A feast of ingredients
that seems too good to be true)
How much would that cost in Korea?
- The crayfish?
- Yes.
A crayfish that big would cost
about 900 dollars.
About 900 dollars?
You were being so nice earlier.
- I knew he was disappointed.
- But he didn't show.
- He tried so hard.
- Yes.
Well, I had to feed you anyhow.
Do you like it?
- Isn't this amazing?
- It's big.
- Each of us...
- Look at that conch.
can have a crayfish for ourselves.
- I think it's still alive.
- This is crazy.
- That's huge.
- Gosh, look at that size.
It's so big.
I can't believe you fooled me.
- Ok Vin caught this one.
- It's huge.
- He looks so happy.
- Careful.
It's gigantic.
It's so big.
It's as big as a person's torso.
Why does its head...
Is this...
- Are more recipes coming to your mind?
- It's not that.
It's gotten more complicated.
I can't afford to cook poorly
now that you brought crayfish.
- Don't worry!
- No pressure. Do what you want.
- Do whatever you want.
- There's no pressure at all.
I think I should go
back to the grocery store.
Then...
- No, I'm sure we can enjoy anything.
- No. I've got this.
- We caught so much.
- I know.
They were talking about spicy fish stew
with lots of vegetables in it earlier.
- No wonder he's flustered...
- Exactly.
- to see crayfish.
- It changes the whole thing.
(In the open Caribbean sea at that moment)
Where's Su Young?
I can't wait to watch this.
I'm so curious.
My name is Eo Nam Seon.
(One man goes into a monologue.)
The Chinese character for "Eo" means fish.
(Watching the deep-blue Caribbean sea,)
(he brings up the mood.)
(Aquaman in the ocean)
("Eo" for fish, "Nam" for south,
and "Seon" for kind)
That's a cool name.
What's Eo Nam Seon, though?
- That's his name.
- My real name is Eo Nam Seon.
- You don't even know his name?
- You didn't know that?
- What?
- It's his real name.
- It's my real name.
- His name is Eo Nam Seon.
- I guess he didn't know.
- People call him Mr. Eo Nam Seon.
I thought that meant
"Last mister standing" in Korean.
- What are you talking about?
- What nonsense is that?
- His real name is Eo Nam Seon.
- That was new.
He's ridiculous.
- Su Young is his stage name.
- "Last mister standing?"
That's so funny.
Stop lying.
But I didn't know his real name either.
It's Eo Nam Seon.
I thought that was the name of that boat.
- What are you talking about?
- What?
- I'm serious.
- This is wild.
Why would they name a boat
Eo Nam Seon in the Caribbean?
- Do you think this is the East Sea?
- Exactly.
- He actually didn't know.
- It was true!
- What are you doing?
- Show me.
- It's Eo Nam Seon!
- After all this time...
Let me see it.
- It was true!
- After all this time?
- His last name is Eo!
- No way!
And the Chinese character
for "Eo" means fish.
- So, what I thought was wrong!
- It's "Eo" for fish.
- Of course.
- Seriously?
- Good luck, Nam Seon.
- Thank you.
(Take Two)
(Anyway, this ocean
that Nam Seon is in...)
- "Hemingway?"
- "The Old Man and the Sea."
(This is the backdrop
of "The Old Man and the Sea"...)
(by the great writer Ernest Hemingway.)
Swordfish?
That's every angler's dream catch.
- It shoots up like that.
- It springs up.
- It catches its prey by spearing it.
- Yes.
(It's got a bill that's like a sharp spear
and brutal aggression.)
- It can swim 80km per hour.
- Right.
- Underwater?
- Underwater.
It can spear through anything.
(This toughest fish to catch
weighs 0.5t when fully grown.)
When we talk about the Caribbean,
we always mention Hemingway.
"The Old Man and the Sea."
The lonesome struggle
in "The Old Man and the Sea."
Are we actually going fishing?
As a man, I have such a dream.
(This man has dreamed of this moment.)
(And his fishing guide in the Caribbean)
(Pedro with 25 years
of fishing experience)
Pedro?
He must be a veteran.
That's right. He's been fishing
for decades in that ocean.
That's reassuring.
- Is this bait?
- This is the bait.
(Even the bait is large.)
- What's the name of this?
- Even the bait is large.
This is Baho-ulo.
- Baho-ulo?
- It's a fillet of Baho-ulo.
- A fillet of Baho-ulo.
(They use raw bait to catch swordfish.)
I think it's the belly
of the fish called Baho-ulo.
He sewed the belly...
to make this bait.
That bait itself is a big fish.
(You use big fish to catch bigger fish.)
I'm going to catch a swordfish,
using Baho-ulo.
Okay. Let's get it started.
Let's go!
He's faking excitement again.
I need to catch one.
(Getting their fishing rods ready)
- That's...
- It needs to be strong.
Yes, they weigh 450kg.
- Look at the fishing line.
- That's so thick.
Bait thrown by Mr. Eo Nam Seon.
(Time to cast bait!)
Mr. Eo Nam Seon is throwing bait,
so help him catch a fish,
Kraken in the Caribbean.
- You shouldn't throw it so slowly.
- Slowly?
They're fed up with him already.
The Captain told him to throw it
because he kept talking.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Casting bait, expecting a big fish)
There's a huge rock attached to it.
It helps the bait go deeper.
(Loud noises come from the fishing rod.)
(Creaking)
- Listen to that noise!
- It must live really deep.
It's going all the way to the bottom.
(You can tell how deep it has gone...)
(from the color of the line.)
How deep is this sea?
It's 554m deep.
(The depth is
almost the height of Lotte World Tower.)
It's that deep?
They have to reel in the line
the height of Lotte World Tower?
With the fishing rod?
When the rock hits the bottom,
there's our bait.
So, we'll reel the bait in to lure it.
Then, I'm going to catch it!
Hit!
- No, I think he's actually excited.
- He's genuinely excited.
- I can tell that he's excited.
- He believes that he'll catch one.
Okay. I'll do that.
(He takes over the fishing rod.)
(He reels it in with full power
as he's desperate.)
(Working hard from the start
for the fish to bite)
(Su Young stops all of a sudden?)
It's too tight.
Hold on. It's too tight.
- It's too tight.
- Wait.
(Something big bit it!)
- Have we caught something?
- Already?
I got it!
(The first bite gives him
a dopamine rush.)
Let's go!
I got it!
(Blessing of fish
comes to those who are diligent.)
Look at his arms.
It's so pumped up.
It's here!
I didn't know fishing could look so cool.
- It's so manly.
- It is.
(The fierce battle between man and ocean)
(Something answers from under the sea?)
What is that?
Come on!
(With all his might)
I had been reeling it in nonstop.
I never stopped.
(The tension continues.)
(The relentless power struggle goes on
without either side backing down.)
(He let go of the rod for a second.)
(Stop.)
He told him to stop.
(Pedro checks the bait.)
What?
(He easily pulls up the line?)
(The tension is gone already.)
- It just came up.
- Is it gone?
I think so.
- It ran away with the bait, didn't it?
- It did.
- Many of them do.
- That looks too way too exhausting.
Now, we know that there's fish down there.
Yes. Right.
That was so hard.
(He lost the fish and his energy.)
(On top of that, the sun is sizzling.)
Did you feel how strong it was?
It was very tight.
Yes. I felt that moment.
- Do you want to try again?
- Yes.
- He's become eager again.
- Right.
I got motivated
when he told me there was fish.
(He casts the bait again and waits.)
I almost caught one.
(He's lost in thought without words
as he's tired.)
(The blue Caribbean reminds him
of one person.)
That's so picturesque! Look at the sky.
(What did Hemingway think about
in this ocean 70 years ago?)
He said, "The sea is..."
"the world,"
"and the fish is my desire."
Hemingway had caught
almost 1,000 tuna and swordfish.
(Is he emptying the desire inside him?)
(Things got busy on the boat
all of a sudden.)
What's going on?
What is it?
(Something bit the bait!)
It bit.
Look at how the fishing rod is bending.
It bends that much?
It's tighter than before.
It took the bait.
You can tell once it bites the bait.
You don't even need a bell.
You can tell easily.
(He reels it in more carefully
as he's lost one before.)
(It's incredibly tighter than before.)
(Bringing all his excitement)
Come on!
Come on up, swordfish!
- It's like watching an Olympic Games.
- I know.
- Okay.
- Okay?
He's going to put something on you.
Okay.
(He makes Su Young put something on.)
- What is he putting on?
- Sit down.
- What is that? A life vest?
- Out of the way.
What for? To go in and catch it?
Okay!
(The chair
that Su Young is sitting on is...)
(a symbol of big fish hunters,)
(the fighting chair!)
(An angler sits on it
for a long battle with a big fish)
It's to actually fight the fish.
- It's a fighting chair.
- To fight it.
- Do you have to fight?
- You have to.
If you just keep reeling it in,
the line will snap.
Even though it's very thick.
You have to reel it in
while controlling your power.
(Sitting on a fighting chair means
he'll have a 1-on-1 fight with a fish.)
Out of the way.
Move over, guys.
(They rush to give Su Young the rod too.)
All right!
- It's literally a 1-on-1 fight.
- Yes.
It's a 1-on-1 fight with the fish.
Yes, I can feel the fish.
It's so heavy.
I can't reel it in.
He doesn't keep reeling it in.
If I do that, the line will snap.
(It's vital to go back and forth,
winding and unwinding the line.)
(But Su Young can't even do it properly.)
Look how tight it is.
(It is rather pulling Su Young in.)
(He even put his sunglasses down.)
(But we still can't see it underwater.)
(He tries his utmost,
all the way down to his toes.)
It's hard just watching it.
(He's already in a groggy state.)
(Has he already reached his limit?)
(At that moment)
Nam Seon!
Yes! Let's go, Nam Seon!
- You can do it, Nam Seon!
- Nam Seon! Yes!
Let's go!
- Let's go!
- You got this!
(It turns out Pedro was
good at putting on enthusiasm.)
You can do it, man!
I'm sure it's there.
- A swordfish.
- A big swordfish.
Really?
It's amazing.
I could only do it
because he cheered for me.
He came to cheer for me
whenever I was struggling.
You would've given up otherwise.
(The original Mr. Fake Reaction
hangs in there, thanks to him.)
(But the effects of the cheering
didn't last long.)
It must be so tiring.
It really was.
(Getting his energy back up)
They poured water on me too.
(A cold shower just when you're tired)
- Don't stop, strongman.
- All right!
They're cheering him from the sides
like a coach.
- I know. Like a coach.
- Yes, they're encouraging him.
I got energized after a sip.
(He takes a sip of beer too.)
Come on. Don't give up.
(More fake enthusiasm by the Dominican)
(30 minutes into the confrontation)
(Under the hot Caribbean sun,)
(the big fish fighter is growing weary.)
(At that moment)
The line changed its color.
(The line turned black,
which means the fish is near.)
How much longer do I pull?
- We're 30m from there.
- It's 30m.
If the line changes in color,
it means you're almost there.
(There's only 30m left
until the fish comes up.)
I'm almost there.
(Loading up on energy again)
- He's almost there.
- I can feel it.
(He's about to conquer the swordfish.)
It feels different. It's so close.
(The black line is getting reeled in
more and more.)
(Is it coming into the frame now?)
- It looks like a shark to me.
- A shark?
Don't you think so?
You're almost there.
(He reels in the line
by straining all the muscles in his body.)
Come on.
(He only has a little more to go.)
- You've got this!
- Keep it up!
(He needs to go all out
for his last battle.)
(I will fight to the bitter end
with my name on the line.)
- It's coming up.
- Here I go.
(His hands get busy.)
- It's coming up.
- Here I go.
(Will Su Young make his dream
of a big catch come true?)
- Did he really catch it?
- For real?
It's out.
It's out of the water.
It's there.
(The ingredient expedition gets started.)
(The real hunting begins now.)
(We're going to get it, no matter what.)
(However,)
(they keep missing their ingredients.)
(Even the air container runs out of air.)
(What will be the fate
of Ok Vin and Joon?)
(We still have a trump card up our sleeve,
which is Nam No.)
(Even with super-sized ingredients
that he sees for the first time)
(Separating it at once)
(Will this be a legendary dish
by Nam No with the Midas touch?)
(And...)
My gosh. What is that?
(In the middle of the Caribbean,)
(they have
a once-in-a-lifetime encounter.)
This is unbelievable!
(They meet the legend of the Caribbean...)
(that could only be seen here.)
(What kind of magical things...)
(await the CARIB BOB expedition?)
(JUNGLE BOB 2, Caribbean BOB)