DOCTOR SLUMP
By the way, are you going to stay
at that apartment near the clinic?
-No, I'm going to move back here today.
-Really?
That way, I'll be able
to see you a bit more.
Right.
-Give me your phone.
-My phone?
-Yeah.
-Why?
Why do you think?
I'm going to change my name.
YEO JEONG-WOO
BOYFRIEND
SAVE
Here.
Give me yours too.
What? Are you gonna change mine too?
Yes. I'm going to change my name
and erase all the numbers of other women.
Be my guest.
There aren't many,
but erase all the ones you dislike.
I'll only change my name for today.
There. Let's end it here.
The phrase "Let's end it here"
is banned from now on.
-Why?
-That's what you said to break up with me.
"Let's end it here."
I've been traumatized by those words,
so please don't say them.
Why bring that up on such a good day?
This won't do. I'm too uneasy.
Write a promise saying you'll never ask
to break up for the next 100 years.
Let's get it notarized tomorrow.
I'll be at ease with the law's protection.
Fine. I won't say that ever again.
Do you mean that?
Promise me.
I promise.
You promised we'll be together forever.
All right.
By the way,
you're pretty handsome.
Did you know?
You're really beautiful.
You're the prettiest doctor I've seen.
You're the most handsome man
I've ever seen in my entire life.
You're the prettiest person I've ever met
and will meet for the rest of my life.
You are--
Will you just shut up?
He wasn't talking about us, was he?
No way. Of course not.
We didn't say anything wrong.
Right.
-Let's go.
What were we talking about again?
You said I was the prettiest person
you've ever met and will meet.
Right.
But back then,
you used to say I was obnoxious
and that I should've stayed in Busan.
I must've been insane back then.
But the things you did were
a little obnoxious. Just a little.
I thought you were pretty though.
-Really?
-Yes.
To be honest,
I didn't like your behavior either
but always thought you were cute.
I see.
Then, you can have this cute face.
-I can?
-Yes. Look at it all you want.
Someone might see us!
You're so cute!
You look so cute even when you're shy.
You're cuter.
You're the cutest person I've ever met.
You're the cutest in the world.
No, you're the cutest
and the most handsome.
You're cute and sexy.
I'm home.
-Hey.
-Hi, Ha-neul.
What? You're drinking beer without me?
You know I like beer.
Why didn't you text me?
You're so mean.
Should we say cheers?
What are you doing?
Is this a company dinner?
Are you going to make a toast?
Why can't I?
I wish you all good health and good luck
in all your future endeavors.
Cheers to this beautiful night.
Did you get some good news today?
Good news? No.
You look needlessly happy
for someone without good news.
Really?
Well, there's not much to being happy.
If you think you're happy,
then you are happy.
BOYFRIEND
I'll be in my room then.
Did she pick up a religion?
Or did she win the lottery?
It's neither. I think…
She has bipolar disorder.
You know. You keep flipping
between happy and depressed.
She's been depressed lately.
But now, she's suddenly happy?
I'm sure it's bipolar disorder.
Right? She has bipolar disorder.
Hey, Jeong-woo.
Of course, I got home safely.
Why are you so curious? You saw me go in.
Still, I wanted to know.
To be honest, I have so many things
I want to know about you.
Such as what time you go to bed,
how many cups of water you drink,
what kind of ice cream you like,
and whether you like it in cups or cones.
Then, should we talk
on the phone all night?
We can ask each other about everything.
Think you can handle it?
I've always been good
at burning the midnight oil.
How many hours do you normally sleep?
About five hours?
-Me too.
-Really?
We both don't sleep much.
You're right.
Maybe it's because I lack sleep,
but I hate it when people talk to me
when I'm about to go to bed.
Me too. I don't like when people
talk to me when I'm upset.
Me too.
I need time alone
to cool down when I'm upset.
I see.
Anything else?
There's one thing
I'm the most curious about.
How does it feel to get back together?
Well…
-It feels better.
-"Better"?
Yeah.
It's better than
when we first decided to date.
How do I put it?
Maybe it was because I still had
a lot of issues that weren't resolved,
but I wasn't sure
if I should've been dating.
But I've decided to conquer them now,
and I want to move on.
I have a different mindset now,
so I feel much more relieved and happier.
I'm glad to hear that.
I miss you.
Do you want to come up?
Right now?
Yeah. Let's have a midnight snack.
How about some fried chicken?
Or jjajang ramyeon?
Jjajang ramyeon sounds good.
Right. Mom made
green onion kimchi yesterday.
-Should I bring some over?
-Holy cow.
Those two go hand in hand.
Bring it right now.
Okay. Boil some water.
-I'll be there before it heats up.
-Got it.
Back then, I had no idea
that jjajang ramyeon
and green onion kimchi
could make one's heart race.
Since I'm in love, even little things
in life shine as bright as stars.
Why are you still up?
What are you doing with the kimchi?
I was craving some.
Goodness, you're eating it without rice?
This is delicious.
I'll eat this while reading dissertations.
Go to bed, Mom.
Eating kimchi while reading dissertations?
How strange.
Goodness. She didn't clean up.
Goodness.
That was close.
I was so scared that she'd catch me.
Good job sneaking up here.
-All right.
-Gosh, this looks good.
I've never had jjajang ramyeon
this late before.
By the way, it'd be best
to keep our relationship a secret, right?
Well…
At work, yes.
I don't know when I'll quit,
so I don't see the point of telling.
And our colleagues
could feel uncomfortable about it,
so let's keep it a secret.
Then, what about here?
I mean,
you'll be going to work from now on,
so they'll be curious
about where you're going every day.
And if you tell them you're helping me,
they might ask how that came to be.
I'm going to tell them the truth
and say we're dating.
Really?
Of course. Why can't I?
I mean, you did all you could
to sneak the kimchi up here.
So I thought you wanted to hide it.
That's because she suddenly appeared,
so I had to make something up.
Of course, I should tell them.
They'll love it.
They love you. Especially my mom.
Really?
What in the world?
My mother-in-law's cooking--
Your mother's cooking is the best.
It's perfect.
You're so silly.
-Eat up.
-Okay.
Jjajang ramyeon
and green onion kimchi go hand in hand.
It's perfect.
Are you cold? I opened the window
to air out the room. Should I close it?
No, it helps me stay awake.
I was full and feeling drowsy.
Are you sleepy?
Then, lie down.
What are you doing?
Why are you slapping the bed?
To show how firm it is?
You know that's not why!
Come here.
Come on. Stop telling me to lie down.
Just lie down for 30 minutes.
Fine.
Only 30 minutes, okay?
Okay.
What?
The door was stuffed with bills yesterday.
Where did they all go?
Goodness! Jeong-woo must be here!
Jeez, he slept with the window open.
He'll catch a cold.
Good morning, Ms. Kong.
I mean, morning. How have you been?
Good. I…
I wasn't meaning to look inside.
The window was open,
so I was going to close it and…
I can explain. You see…
This woman is actually--
What is it?
Okay. I'm leaving now.
Bye.
No, don't…
-Did she leave?
-We're done for.
Jeong-woo,
let's keep this a secret for now.
What?
That's not what you said last night.
I was going to tell her,
and all we did was sleep last night.
But she'll easily get the wrong idea
after seeing us like this.
She'll think we did something else.
Then, she'll suddenly get all nosy.
I won't be able to stand it.
Let's keep it quiet for now.
Then… What about my reputation?
She clearly knows we like each other.
But she'll think I've already moved on
to another woman and slept with her.
Will my reputation be okay?
No, it won't be.
What if she hates me?
That's… She'll find out the truth later.
-She'll realize it was a misunderstanding.
-What?
We're going to be late.
We'll talk again at the clinic. Bye.
Are you sure she'll understand?
I don't think she will.
Let me take a bottle of water.
I'll tell her I bought it
after working out.
Bye.
Ha-neul, I'm really scared.
Ha-neul.
No!
I have a bad feeling about this.
My goodness!
What's wrong? Why are you so upset?
Was the morning soap opera canceled?
I'm so dumbfounded right now!
I went to the rooftop garden
to get some lettuce.
Jeong-woo finally visited again.
But he wasn't alone.
He was with some girl.
What girl? Who was it?
How would I know?
The window was open, so I went to close it
and happened to look inside.
That's when I saw him
cuddling with some woman in bed!
Was she pretty?
How would I know?
Her entire face
was covered by the blanket!
-Maybe it was Ha-neul.
-Ha-neul?
You didn't see her face.
It could've been Ha-neul.
I'm home.
Where have you been?
I woke up early, so I went for a jog.
I'm so hungry. Mom, let's eat.
Okay.
-What?
-Gosh, I'm so hot.
She must've really gone for a jog.
Does this mean Jeong-woo
really is seeing someone else?
Damn it. That little scumbag!
-This is why you can't be nice to anyone!
-Mom.
Jeong-woo's not just anyone.
We know him pretty well.
That's not important!
What's important is that he betrayed her.
I'm going to cook him alive.
Meanwhile, on top
of having bipolar disorder,
Ha-neul's so out of her mind
she's eating green onion kimchi
while reading dissertations.
What am I going to do with that punk?
-I should throw him in boiling water!
-Oh, no.
Forget it.
Hello.
Hi. I guess you're going to work.
-Yes.
-You're even wearing a tie.
I'm only wearing this because the clinic
needs to upload my photo on their website.
I had no choice but to wear one.
-I didn't say anything.
-Right.
I'm truly happy that you're doing well.
Oh, no. Your tie is a little crooked.
-It is?
-Yes.
It should be fine.
Ms. Kong! Tap!
Goodness, your suit is so dusty.
It shouldn't be dusty at all.
Ms. Kong, not the elbow! Wait!
Ha…
Sorry!
Good luck at work.
BUSAN'S ORIGINAL MILMYEON
Have a nice day.
-Jin-woo, didn't we have fun?
-Yes.
It must've been hectic
these past few days.
Working and babysitting.
-Goodness.
-You had it worse, Mom.
You had to take care of your sister.
Jin-woo, have a safe trip.
Don't horse around or remove
your seat belt. Take it easy on Grandma.
I'm not a kid.
Right.
Here. It's a gift.
A gift? What is it?
It's for Mr. Bin.
I drew this to thank him
for catching those ants for me.
Really?
He'll love it.
This is him.
-This?
-Goodness.
He's going to be late for kindergarten.
We have to go now. Okay.
Let's go.
See you this weekend, Jin-woo.
-Bye, Mom.
-Bye.
You don't have to come out.
Let's go.
What did you want to give me
so early in the morning?
Jin-woo said to give this to you.
-It's a gift.
-A gift?
What is this?
He drew an ant, you, and himself.
I see.
-So this is the ant.
-No, that's you.
I see.
What a nice, cool drawing.
Right.
I bought some macarons on my way here.
You didn't have to.
I prefer soju.
You could've just bought me a drink later.
-Gosh.
-My goodness.
Why would I drink soju with you?
-This is for your daughter.
-It's for Eun-jeong?
Remember what you said last time?
You said she didn't like it
when you'd buy her taiyaki or egg bread.
Kids today are active on social media.
They like pretty, fancy, and cool snacks.
Ones they can take pictures of and upload.
So look it up on social media next time
and get her something pretty and fancy.
Okay.
LA BEAUTE PLASTIC SURGERY CLINIC
Do you want some coffee?
Should we get some downstairs?
Dr. Yeo, are you free to take
the photo for our website right now?
Yes, sure.
We're ready to take it
next to our clinic's logo.
I'll be there.
Let's have coffee next time.
Okay. Well…
Good luck on the photo.
Bye.
Mom, don't be shocked.
The woman you saw this morning was me.
No.
Let's try again.
I have something to tell you.
Jeong-woo and I are dating.
Dr. Yeo, you look so handsome!
You look like a celebrity!
This is insane. You look great.
Dr. Yeo, can you start your channel again
and show how handsome you are?
I'll subscribe and press like. Please?
-I'm not quite ready.
-One minute.
I think you'll look even better
with a bit more makeup.
-You already look good though.
-No, that's okay.
Come on.
You need to look good for the photo.
By the way, are you seeing anyone?
-Sorry?
-I'm just curious.
You don't have a girlfriend?
A girlfriend?
And our colleagues
could feel uncomfortable about it,
so let's keep it a secret.
Gosh, no.
A girlfriend? That's ridiculous.
So you're single too.
Of course, I am.
I don't have a girlfriend.
Dr. Yeo, what's your ideal type?
My ideal type?
Well…
Someone with long hair, big eyes,
and who cares about me more than I do.
Gosh. This is my first time here,
and their food is spicy and delicious.
I should bring Eun-jeong here
for her birthday next month.
She's going to scold you again.
Kids these days prefer food
like pizza and pasta.
You're right.
They like to post photos online.
Ms. Woo, I need you to consult someone
next Friday and book her for surgery.
My aunt's friend wants
an upper blepharoplasty
and a thread lift.
Give her a discount too.
Yes, sir.
You two must get
a lot of requests for discounts.
Don't get me started.
"How much is the discount?
How much work I need done?"
Without exaggerating,
I'm asked such questions every day.
They ask how much work they need too?
All the time.
If you become a plastic surgeon,
distant relatives,
former classmates, and even teachers
ask about how much work they need.
But you need to be cautious.
They might think we're judging them
and feel offended.
Still, can you tell me
how much work I need?
Come on.
Are you making me work while I'm eating?
Come on, do it for us
as a perk of working at a clinic.
I want to get an NI double eyelid surgery.
What do you think?
You're already so beautiful.
You are. But if you do get it,
then I think you could become
a little prettier. Just a bit.
What do you think?
I don't think she needs it.
Then, what about me?
What about a mouth corner lift?
Ms. Han, if you get it…
If you end up getting it,
I think you'll look slightly younger.
-I don't think she needs it.
-Really?
Dr. Nam, you're already perfect.
But some fillers in your brow…
So…
You look perfect in this natural state--
No, I think she could get some.
If she gets fillers in her brow…
This rolled omelette is good.
Dr. Yeo.
This is my piece.
This rolled omelette had eight pieces,
and there are four people at this table.
Then, the unwritten rule says
we each get two.
You already had your share,
so this is mine.
I'm sorry.
Let's not argue over food.
Ma'am, could we get…
an additional plate
of rolled omelettes for each table?
All right!
Dr. Bin, you should've
bought this coffee--
Come on.
What's the matter?
Do you really not know?
I'm really sorry.
It's like an occupational disease.
I only said you could get the fillers
because it wouldn't be bad.
But you don't need them.
You really don't,
but a lot of people get them nowadays.
Do you want get a beating?
It's an occupational disease? I work too.
You want me to put you to sleep?
Don't say such frightening things.
I mean, you're always scowling,
so I thought… I think it's rather cute.
But since you've always done that,
I guess I felt bad and blurted it out.
Forget it. Yesterday, you said
I was the prettiest person
you've ever met and will meet.
But now, you want me to get fillers.
I can't help but be disappointed
by all your fickle words.
"All"? Did I say something else wrong?
No, it wasn't wrong.
But it was disappointing.
When I asked you to erase the numbers
of other women on your phone,
you were fine with it.
So I thought you were the devoted type.
But you were having a blast
with our female colleagues,
getting your makeup done too.
And what? You don't have a girlfriend?
-Why are you making yourself available?
-What do you mean?
That's really unfair. I only said that
since you wanted it to be a secret.
No, that meant you should keep
our relationship a secret.
I didn't say
you should claim to be single.
You could've just said you were taken.
That hurt my feelings.
My feelings were hurt too, you know.
Remember how your mother choked me today?
And speaking of which,
you even ignored us when she elbowed me.
I thought you'd step in then
and say something.
Do you know how hurt I was?
I had no choice though.
She saw us cuddling in bed.
So how could I tell about that?
I wanted to wait
a few days before telling her.
-Is that so hard to understand?
-That's not what I mean.
I'm just hurt.
You can't even understand that?
You're hurt that I don't understand?
You can't understand that I'm…
What's your MBTI type?
That's such a random question.
Guys? Are you coming or what?
Yes, we're coming.
I'm definitely a thinker.
-Are you leaving?
-Am I not supposed to?
You're leaving just like that?
Then, what should I do?
Bye.
But…
Hey, wait up.
Gosh.
What in the world? Why did he follow me?
If you have something to say, then say it.
Where's the bus?
Jeez.
Should I talk first?
All right. It wasn't over
anything big anyway.
No!
I'm safe.
No, I wasn't trying to--
I thought he wanted to reconcile,
but he steals my seat?
He's still just as competitive
as he was back then.
What is this?
We should be going on dates
to places like these, but look at us.
Hey, welcome back. For a jobless person,
you were out a while.
What about you?
I bought some ingredients
for seaweed soup.
It's Mom's birthday tomorrow.
No way. Don't tell me you forgot.
Goodness. Look at you.
What's the point of having
a daughter who's a doctor
when I'm the one
who remembers her birthday?
What? What's this?
"Sky Lounge"?
So you did remember her birthday.
-What?
-Right. You've always had a good memory.
Yeah, good thinking.
Other daughters would take their mothers
to go shopping and eat good food.
But you were always too busy
to take her to a nice restaurant.
Did you book a reservation?
If not, then hurry.
Three people, including me.
No. With Uncle Tae-seon, it's four.
Hurry up.
Okay. I'll call them.
Ha-neul.
I'm really sorry about today.
I said your beautiful face needed fillers.
I tried to eat the last piece
of rolled omelette.
And I even said I was single.
I'm sorry for everything.
I'm terrible at relationships
and at being a good daughter.
However, what happened on the bus
was a misunderstanding.
I lost balance and fell forward.
What am I doing?
I'm like a kid
writing an apology letter. Come on!
Gosh.
Ha-neul, can I at least see
your face before going to bed?
I miss you.
I need time alone
to cool down when I'm upset.
Hi, Suk-ja. Why did you call
so early this morning?
Come on. A birthday isn't a big deal.
I'm just getting a year older.
Anyway, thank you for calling.
Right.
Is Ha-neul still unemployed?
Goodness. She should've treated
her blind date better!
Jeez. She has no job or boyfriend.
Goodness. It's your birthday today,
but I'm sorry you have
nothing to smile about.
Goodbye!
Her dad--
What? Did she hang up on me again?
Damn it. Did she call
to congratulate me or upset me?
What an annoying start to my day.
Ha-neul's going to meet someone
much better than that blind date guy.
Much better than him too.
I woke up early, so I went for a jog.
Every store sells that brand of water.
This is delicious.
I'll eat this while reading dissertations.
Go to bed, Mom.
It can't be.
Then, that woman from yesterday
was Ha-neul?
Hey, Jeong-woo.
Hello.
-Are you going to work?
-Yes, I am.
Goodbye, then.
What? Jeong-woo!
Jeong-woo, wait!
Jeong-woo, stop right there!
Ms. Kong!
Hold on!
Goodness, I see dust.
Jeong-woo.
I really like you.
-Sorry?
-I always have.
For Ha-neul's sake the other day,
I know you kept it a secret
and didn't tell me the truth.
That made me like you more.
You're qualified to be her boyfriend.
What do you mean?
That woman in your bed was Ha-neul, right?
No. It wasn't her. It was someone else.
GIRLFRIEND
Pick it up.
Hey.
Did you go to work?
I'm about to.
I see. Okay.
Have a good day.
Can I see you later at night?
Sure.
I'll call you later. Bye.
That must've been your girlfriend.
Her number looked very familiar though.
The last four digits were 0402.
Ms. Kong.
I assure you nothing happened that night.
Whether that's true or not,
it's not my business.
She must be too embarrassed to tell me.
I'll play dumb,
so I hope you two get along.
Goodness! How long were you
going to hide it?
You two sure make things complicated.
-Jeong-woo.
-Yes?
Did you know that it's my birthday today?
No, I didn't. Happy birthday, Ms. Kong.
Then, could you do me a favor
as a birthday present?
What is it?
This is amazing!
I can't believe you brought me here.
Thank you so much, Ha-neul.
Come on. You should thank me instead.
She just made
a reservation and paid for it.
I was the one
who said we should come here.
So you should thank me.
By the way,
what are you wearing?
I got this outfit as a gift
after finding Seok-won his bride.
Then, it's about 20 years old.
It's not as old as I thought.
I thought it was from the 1800s.
You want to get hit 1800 times?
Then, buy me some clothes.
Mom.
Hello. Did you make a reservation?
-Yes.
-It's under "Nam Ha-neul."
For three.
-This way, please.
-Okay.
What's with the Seoul accent?
You already know I can speak
in both Seoul and Busan dialects.
When I'm with women
or come to fancy places like this,
I use the Seoul dialect.
"I use."
The appetizers are apple tart
and rosemary crusted chicken.
The sweet flavor of the apples
will stimulate our appetites.
Right. Could you recommend
a nice bottle of champagne too?
We're celebrating today.
Sure, we'll prepare something
that pairs well with the steak.
You got to be kidding me.
What's wrong with you? You sound so gross.
-Tell me about it.
-What do you mean "gross"?
Busan girls love it
and say I sound intelligent and sweet.
This is why I'm popular.
I use the Busan dialect with Seoul girls
and the Seoul dialect with Busan girls.
I see. Good for you.
Excuse me.
We're expecting one more person.
Could we have another plate and glass?
Sure, I'll get them for you.
What?
We're expecting someone else? Who?
Who else? Probably Uncle Tae-seon.
Is he closing early?
Jeong-woo, why are you here?
Your mother invited me.
Happy birthday.
Thank you for coming.
What is this?
Did you forget he's our family's enemy?
You said he was in bed with another woman!
That woman was your sister.
Seriously?
I wasn't the one who told her.
That's right. We're dating.
He's my boyfriend.
Ba-da. Show him some respect.
You shouldn't bother him either, Mom.
I won't sit still if you elbow him again.
Share your good side dishes
and lower his maintenance fees.
-Treat him well.
-Of course. That won't be a problem.
-I won't charge rent either.
-That's okay.
Who charges their own family rent?
You're pretty much one of us now.
Hi, my brother-in-law.
Please treat Ha-neul well.
I thought she had bipolar disorder,
but she really was happy.
You made a great decision.
What is this? Some kind of huddle?
Are we playing for the World Cup?
Don't be so dramatic and sit down.
-We need to talk.
-What?
Okay.
What's going on?
Well, I ran into your mother this morning,
and she knew everything.
I wasn't going to tell her for your sake.
But you happened to call me right then.
I see. That's why you sounded so awkward.
You didn't sound too happy,
so I thought you were still upset.
Why would I be? It was my fault anyway.
Jeez. Then, why didn't you call me?
I wanted to.
I wanted to call you over a hundred times,
but I remembered you said
you needed time alone to cool down.
Hey.
That's when I'm upset about other things.
If it's about us,
I'd rather make up quickly.
Do you mean that?
Gosh. What was I doing yesterday?
I was too sad to sleep.
You didn't sleep?
Did you?
I sleep when I'm upset.
That's a good habit.
I'm sorry, Ha-neul.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
And I'm sorry about any fights
we'll have in the future.
-You don't know what we'll fight about.
-That doesn't matter.
Your mother must be waiting. Let's hurry.
Thank you for coming.
I was worried
you wouldn't be happy to see me.
So thank you.
Right.
But the bus incident
is a misunderstanding.
I lost balance and fell.
You saw me flying forward, right?
Fine. I'll believe you if you want.
What? No, that's not it.
-It's true.
-Back then, I had no idea.
I didn't know dating could be this hard.
I feel hurt, sorry, and grateful
on a whole different level.
All the most trivial things
feel so tremendous.
-Cheers.
-Bravo!
Bottoms up.
Okay.
You don't do that with champagne.
You shouldn't drink
since you're going back to work.
It's okay.
I didn't have any surgeries today,
so I took the afternoon off.
Well done.
-What a smart guy.
-Thank you.
Today, let's drink until we keel over.
-Yes, ma'am.
-How ridiculous.
Hey, that's too much--
She wants to give me a lot.
Please fill it to the brim.
-Thank you.
-Okay.
Take it easy.
You have surgery tomorrow morning.
You even know his schedule.
You're so obsessed.
No, I'm not. I know
because we're doing it together.
Do it together? Do what?
Well… To be honest,
I've been helping him out in the OR.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you sooner.
It's not permanent though.
I didn't want to stay home all the time.
I'm only helping him out briefly
while figuring out what to do.
Are you okay?
What? Did you expect her to return
to her hospital to become a professor?
Are you disappointed?
No, I'm not.
I'm just glad she's doing something again.
My daughter brought me
to a fancy restaurant like this,
and she's sitting next to her boyfriend.
She even got a job.
It truly feels like my birthday today.
I'm on cloud nine.
You should be smiling then, not crying.
All right.
Let's drink.
Whoever walks out of here sober
is a traitor.
-Yes, ma'am.
-What are you talking about?
Drink slowly or you'll get drunk.
Here!
Unbelievable!
Okay. Hang in there!
You're almost there!
We're here!
Goodness.
Jeez.
Here.
Gosh, I'm so exhausted.
What's wrong?
-There's a flower behind your ear.
-What?
When did she put this here?
Beats me.
Goodness.
Where are you, Ha-neul?
What are you doing?
Here.
-Let's go.
Are the macarons good?
Yes. It's unlike you
to buy something like this.
Well, my colleague--
No, someone I know--
A friend?
Who was it?
Anyway, someone wanted you to have them.
Want to try one?
How about this one? It's chocolate.
Gosh. How did you know I like chocolate?
-Not bad.
-It's good, right?
-Yeah.
-We're finally on the same page.
-You should buy more stuff like this.
-Okay.
What's gotten into her? She smiled.
Hong-ran, thank you for the macarons.
My daughter loves them.
Dad, my friends want to--
What is this? Isn't this blood?
Why do you have my underwear? Gross.
Bin Eun-jeong, tell me the truth.
Are you being bullied?
Did someone hit you?
What are you talking about?
I would've bled a lot more if I was hit.
Then, what is it? Why can't you tell me?
Darn it.
The wire from my bra
poked out and cut me, okay?
That happens?
Then, you should've told me about it.
How can I possibly ask you
to buy me a bra? It's embarrassing.
Wait, Eun-jeong.
BRAS FOR MIDDLE SCHOOL GIRLS
-What are you doing here?
-Hello.
"Bras for middle school girls"?
What?
They're… They're not for me.
Of course, they're not.
Right.
No, wait.
No!
It's for Eun-jeong.
I was looking it up for her.
That's true. If you wear
an old bra for too long,
the wire will poke out sometimes.
Goodness. Why do you think
she never told me about it?
Because you're her dad.
Girls her age are sensitive.
Give her your card
and tell her to buy a nice one.
I was going to,
but she stormed out
and won't read my texts.
You know that underwear store
near our clinic?
-Yes.
-I thought I'd buy something there.
But I don't know what to buy.
Then, want me to come with you?
Would you?
How's this one?
Good.
May I help you?
Is there anything you need?
Is this 100% cotton?
Is it sweat absorbing?
Of course.
It's wireless and perfect for students.
Then, I'd like three sets in nude,
and two shorts to wear under the uniform.
All right, then.
You're very caring parents.
It's rare for both parents
to shop for their daughter's underwear.
Right. Would you like me
to recommend one for you too?
This is a new design.
I'm not his wife.
We're not married.
I bought just a few,
so tell her to try them on.
Okay. Thank you.
And try to be more nonchalant
about sensitive matters.
She could feel more embarrassed
if you're awkward about it.
Okay.
Thank you for buying them for me
and giving me advice. Thank you so much.
Don't mention it.
You've helped me a lot too.
I should get going now.
Okay.
Good night.
Goodness.
Why did you have to drop them?
Jeez.
Thank you for today.
My mom is such an embarrassment.
No, she's not. She's great.
I'm so envious of your family.
When I look at you, I can tell your family
doted on you as you grew up.
I know their love and expectations
were a burden on you at times.
But I could feel how your family
truly cared about you,
and that often made me envious.
My family isn't like yours.
By the way, how come
you've never asked about my family?
-What?
-Well, they never came to my hearings.
I never mentioned
my parents to you either.
You could've found that strange.
But I was surprised how you never asked.
Right. About that…
Actually, I've seen your mother before.
Near the nurse's office
when we were seniors.
Sir.
I heard he's just anemic.
Fainting while studying isn't uncommon.
And you made me come here for this?
Not only are his grades falling
but he also ended up like that.
How could he not come
in first even in high school?
Then, you do know what my family is like.
You must've been surprised
since we're so different.
Rather than being surprised,
I just thought you'd be lonely.
What kind of people are your parents?
First, they're both
cardiothoracic surgeons.
My father is a professor
at a medical school in the US.
Recently, he became the first Asian chair
of the American Heart Association.
My mother's a researcher
at my father's school too.
They're incredible.
They are.
But because of that,
they always wanted me
to follow in their footsteps.
When I chose to study plastic surgery,
they were totally against it
when they found out.
They couldn't understand why
I didn't choose to support them
in researching the heart.
They scolded me
for taking a different path
than the one they paved for me.
Gosh. They just couldn't understand.
So? How did you convince them?
I didn't.
They still don't understand to this day.
I sometimes felt bad about it.
I always gave them
what they wanted in life,
so I regretted
not following in their footsteps.
But not too long ago,
you know I went through
some serious hardship.
My mother found out and called.
So I thought she was worried about me.
But guess what she said?
She told me to make sure
it wouldn't affect them.
When I heard that,
every ounce of regret I had
just disappeared.
I don't think they'll ever understand me.
We'll always be strangers.
-You must've been so lonely.
-I was.
But thankfully,
I quickly learned
how to fill that loneliness.
Everyone has
something they can never attain
no matter how much they try.
For me, I always thought
that was love from my parents.
But aside from that,
I had many other things.
So I tried to be grateful
and worked hard as I stayed focused.
Doing that seemed to make me feel better.
Then, there wasn't anyone else
you could talk about this with besides me?
Well…
Min Kyung-min?
We met when I was a senior,
and we were like brothers since then.
Then, was it my fault--
It's not your fault.
He's not a good person.
Look what he did to you.
But still.
Actually, I had a hunch.
I had a feeling
that maybe he wasn't a good person.
There were times when he seemed a bit odd.
"Director Min Kyung-min."
Gosh.
Professor Min-- Right.
Should I call you
Director Min from now on?
It's up to you.
Please sit down, sir.
You got a nice view here.
Right?
I was sad to see you go
as soon as you became a professor.
But now that I'm here, I get it.
I would've quit right away too.
You shouldn't quit.
-You're the backbone of the hospital.
-Please.
By the way, our department needs
a new pharmaceutical supplier.
As you already know, we spend
a hefty sum on medicine each year.
But it would be a shame
to give this opportunity
to people I'm not close with.
Then, may I take you up on that offer?
You know I always repay you
for your kindness.
How about we discuss the details
sometime soon over a round of golf?
You always pick up on things quickly.
You won't be disappointed.
Good. We're in the same boat anyway.
The numbers indicate you've improved.
How do you feel?
I've been trying
to put the past behind and move on.
I also realized I have
many people who care about me.
I'm also working again,
and it makes me feel important.
That's what we call self-esteem.
Self-esteem
is like a tower of pebbles
you stack every day.
It crumbles the moment you have doubts
and think, "What's the point?"
Have confidence, believe in yourself,
and continue to stack those pebbles up.
Then, before you know it,
you'll have a house or a sturdy castle.
I think we can lower your dosage now.
Okay.
I was getting stronger
than I'd been in the past.
Dr. Nam, I'll begin
the rib cartilage harvest.
Could you administer
some muscle relaxants?
Okay. I administered some 30 minutes ago,
so I'll administer
20 mg of rocuronium right now.
Thank you. Local anesthesia.
I was also proud of how well
Jeong-woo was holding up.
Hey, Jeong-woo.
Should we go to a bar
and have a glass of whiskey tonight?
Sure.
I'd love to,
but you could've just asked me
back in the office.
Well, colleagues who date each other
all seemed to meet up in the stairwell.
So…
I wanted to try it too.
Come on.
How silly.
Hello?
Today? No, I'm busy.
Maybe in two months?
We wanted to believe
that only good things awaited us.
Even if it wasn't astonishing,
we hoped to have a decent life.
We desperately prayed for this small wish.
We used to always drink beer and soju,
so now this whiskey is…
Is it too strong?
No, I love it.
By the way, about what you said last time…
You said Kyung-min seemed odd at times.
Can you tell me about that?
I think
he once spiked my drink.
What?
When I got into medical school,
he bought me a drink
for the first time to congratulate me.
But I ended up in the ER that day.
I think I'm too drunk.
Professor.
His blood alcohol level was high,
and we found traces of Ambien.
Ambien?
I heard he was taking medication
for his insomnia.
He shouldn't have had so much alcohol.
Why did you sweep that
under the rug instead of looking into it?
I wasn't sure whether what I saw
was real, a dream, or an illusion.
And objectively, it didn't make sense.
If he wanted to hurt me,
he would've used something stronger.
He wouldn't have used Ambien.
if it's mixed with alcohol,
that's still dangerous.
Your cognitive abilities drop,
and you become delirious.
You can't control your impulses,
so you could do something dangerous.
But what would he get
out of doing that to me?
How was he after that incident?
He was the same as always.
He was still just as friendly
and supported me all along like a brother.
Nothing like that ever happened again,
so I guess I forgot about it.
To be honest,
if there was even the tiniest possibility…
I wanted to believe him.
Because you relied on him a lot?
No.
For my sake.
If he really had done that…
I would've felt so pitiful.
I had forgotten about that incident.
But after learning what he did to you,
I'm starting to think
that maybe what I saw was real.
It scares me.
Yes, Professor Kim. I'll see you
this weekend on the golf course.
Okay.
Also, about your daughter's paintings
from her exhibition you mentioned…
Our company has decided
to purchase all of them.
It's my pleasure. I liked the drawings.
I'll see you this weekend.
Goodbye.
Come in.
What brings you here?
You need to keep your promise.
Are you okay?
I hope we weren't wrong
about things looking up.
DOCTOR SLUMP
Doesn't it feel
like we've gone back in time?
Stop right there!
Cheers!
I like how things are right now.
I hope this peace will continue to last.
Are you involved
in Jeong-woo's medical accident?
You're curious about many things.
Taking a stroll at night
without a care in the world.
Was wishing for such a day
asking for too much?
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim