DOCTOR SLUMP
Here's our next story.
It's been revealed that a Korean doctor
was involved in the shocking death
of a casino heiress
from Macau last spring.
Here's our reporter
Jeong Chae-hong with more.
It's been revealed that "A,"
an anesthesiologist and an executive
at a pharmaceutical company,
contributed to the death of Chang
by providing a gang from Macau with drugs,
such as heparin, in return for shares.
In addition, he paid large amounts
of kickbacks to a university hospital,
which has shocked the public.
But with A's death
from a car accident three weeks ago,
the charges and the case
have been dismissed.
The car accident before his death…
Why are you watching this?
It's nothing good.
Why not?
I have to know to see
if I need to console Ha-neul or not.
So Haesung Pharmaceutical
caused the car accident on purpose.
The police were closing in,
so they decided to kill him off.
Ha-neul could've been in huge danger.
It's awkward to see you
in normal clothes again.
Right.
What did your doctor say?
Are you doing better now?
Yeah, he said I'm progressing well
and to come in two weeks to check.
Goodness. Okay.
Good job. Let's go home.
I made some beef bone soup last night.
You can go first.
I have to stop by somewhere.
DAEHAN NATIONAL UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
Come in.
Dr. Nam.
-How have you been?
-Good.
-How about you?
-It's always the same for me.
-Sit down.
-Okay.
I quit so suddenly then
and didn't even get to
say goodbye. I'm sorry.
Don't be.
As the Chief of Anesthesiology,
I apologize for not knowing
what happened in our department.
He stole your dissertation and position.
In a way, your youth was stolen.
You must have suffered so much.
Dr. Nam. I'm truly sorry.
It's all right.
I know it's late, but you should return
to your rightful place.
You played a key role
in removing corruption from our hospital
and leading us in the right way.
Your return will help
both you and the hospital
in recovering lost reputations.
Seriously? They offered
a full-time assistant professor role?
Hey, Ha-neul!
Congratulations!
What's the matter?
You always said your ultimate goal in life
was to become a professor.
It's just feels
like I got rid of people
to get this position.
It feels wrong.
What are you talking about?
Those who did wrong were punished,
and you're taking your rightful place.
This was how it should've been.
But you just took a detour.
I'll be honest.
I'm not sure
if I can go back and do well…
or if I'm even completely better now.
This is tough.
Gosh, I'm hungry. What should we eat?
Cold noodles? Kongguksu?
Or spicy webfoot octopus
to relieve stress?
-Anything's--
-"Anything's fine."
Guys who say that are the most boring.
So pick. Cold noodles? Kongguksu?
Spicy webfoot octopus?
Or something else?
-Hey.
-What's wrong with you?
Lunch is on me!
-Coffee too!
-Jeez.
I'm sorry, but my schedule's empty
this afternoon. Can I go home early?
Of course, you can.
What? Is something up?
I think I have to hear
about what happened in person.
Please follow instructions
during your visit of inmates.
Giving inmates food or items
from the outside is prohibited.
Physical contact
with inmates is not allowed.
The case is closed,
but I came because I needed
to know something.
What was written on the note
you received from Kyung-min?
It said he had something to say…
about the medical accident.
I actually didn't know
Haesung was involved back then.
I was shocked that he knew about it,
so I decided to go talk to him.
He suggested we lower the heparin dosage.
He said the CCTV cameras would be broken,
which meant the surgery
wouldn't be recorded anyway.
He didn't want there to be
a fatal accident at your clinic.
MOM
Hello?
Why haven't you been picking up?
I've been worried sick.
I'm sorry.
I saw the news. I can't believe
you were close with that lowlife.
Being in pain because of him
is a waste of time.
I have a question.
What is it?
Right before my CSATs,
Kyung-min was sick and took time off.
Did you know
his father had… passed away?
I did.
I didn't tell you
so it wouldn't distract you.
I was so flustered that it happened
right before your exam.
Thank goodness you got into HNU.
I wouldn't have sat still
if you ruined your exam.
Right. Are you free on Saturday?
I've been meaning to visit,
but I've had no time.
We're coming to Seoul
for your father's conference.
I hope we can meet then.
I'm a bit busy, so I'll call you back.
I was only hospitalized for three weeks,
but the world had changed a lot.
It was almost the end of summer.
The air had become cool.
And now,
Kyung-min was gone.
Get in.
What if we hadn't met that night?
What if…
I had forgiven him then,
would things be better now?
Our what-if questions
continued to torment us.
-Did you just get off work?
-Yeah.
I was going to call you.
I'm sorry I wasn't there
when you were discharged.
Don't be. I'm not a kid.
Let's go.
How was your day?
It was okay.
How was yours?
Good. Nothing out of the ordinary.
We knew it'd be
too painful for each other,
so we each dealt with
our sadness on our own.
We never agreed to do it,
but we pretended to be okay
in front of each other.
We didn't know how to deal
with such immense sadness.
So we pretended like everything was fine.
DOCTOR SLUMP
Eat up. You too, Jeong-woo.
Okay. Thank you.
Your food is always so good,
so I can't help but eat a lot.
Especially the stir-fried fish cakes.
I'm amazed each time I eat them.
How are they so good?
There's a reason for that.
She used to run a fish cake factory.
Even though we had to close it
since popular brands took over,
she uses her expertise
to pick the best fish cakes.
Since you seem to love them,
I should buy a box of them
when I visit Busan this weekend.
-You're going to Busan this weekend?
-Yeah, on Saturday.
We always visit
around this time of the year.
It's not hot and there's a cool breeze.
The weather's perfect for going out.
We eat good food
and visit people we miss.
That's what we do.
Ha-neul is usually too busy.
So normally, it's just us
and Uncle Tae-seon.
I'm planning to go this time.
Goodness. Just stay here.
Your ribs are still healing.
What if you break them again?
They're held in place with metal plates.
When other patients are discharged,
they all take the train or fly home.
Still.
And…
I want to visit again.
Okay. Let's go.
Let's get some fresh air too.
In that case,
is it okay if I come too?
-You too?
Okay.
You're really going with us?
Why not? It's hot. I can't go?
Of course, you can.
Because of our uncle's shop,
it's only for a day. You'll be tired.
I'm okay. I didn't want to be in Seoul
this weekend, so things worked out.
What?
It's nothing.
How are Jeong-woo and Ha-neul doing?
I'm not sure.
I don't know if they're really okay
or just pretending to be.
Doesn't it seem like
they've bounced back pretty quickly?
They stayed in their rooms
for days after the funeral.
But they started talking
and laughing last week.
They look fine.
Who knows how they actually feel?
Anyway, since they both
want to visit Busan,
they must want some fresh air.
Let's use this chance to cheer them up.
Let's really relax and--
I'm home.
So tell me, Ba-da.
How much progress have you made?
Progress? With who?
So far, Se-a and I have kissed.
I wasn't asking about that.
I meant making milmyeon.
I already taught him
how to make the noodles. And so…
He'll learn how to make
the sauce properly tomorrow.
I'll be in my room then.
Okay.
You must be tired, so go and rest.
I put down a blanket for you.
What?
BUSAN'S ORIGINAL MILMYEON
I guess they're not out yet.
Hello, Father.
Yes, Mother told me already.
But I don't think I can make it today.
I forgot I had a conference too.
Have a good trip.
Goodbye.
Let's go!
-Did you bring everything?
-Of course.
-The lights and gas are off.
-And the charger?
I packed it.
And the car keys?
-I have them.
-All right.
Gosh. What's all this?
I steamed some corn
in case we get hungry on the way.
I also prepared some makgeolli bread
and monkfish jerky.
Basically, we brought our whole kitchen.
We're not going there to eat.
Eating is the most important part.
Okay, get in. We have a long way to go.
I'll drive, Ba-da.
No, I will. It's Ha-neul's car,
but I drive it more and know it well.
-But still--
-Goodness, it's fine.
Just sit back and enjoy the scenery.
You must be hurting after your ordeal.
Gosh, who cares who drives?
It's a long trip,
so we need to take turns.
-Go first, Ba-da. I'll take over later.
-Get in!
Okay.
Should we eat something?
-Sure.
-Already?
Still.
Each of you take one.
Thank you.
This's for you, Ha-neul.
-Give one to Ba-da.
-Okay.
And I steamed this myself.
-Gosh.
-I made it myself.
Thank you.
-Gosh. This is good while it's still hot.
-Okay.
Jeong-woo.
I packed some head cheese too. Try some.
Who eats head cheese in the car?
It's to eat with the alcohol.
Because I brought some makgeolli too.
Jeez, who eats makgeolli
and head cheese in the car?
Exactly. What is Jeong-woo
going to think about our family?
What's the matter?
This is what a fun trip is all about.
-Right, Jeong-woo?
-Of course.
All right, have a drink. Here.
All right.
Come on, Mom.
What?
It's nice to have a drink on a trip.
Of course. Please pour me a glass.
Okay. This will lift your mood right up.
-Here.
-Thank you.
No!
-Oh, no!
-Jeez.
-Do we have any towels?
-I'm okay.
I told you not to drink in the car!
-It's okay.
-Hey.
Here.
-Oh, no.
-Gosh.
-My goodness!
-I have some clothes in the trunk.
This girl I used to see
liked men who worked out.
So I used to work out
and put my clothes in the trunk.
-Do you want to wear those?
-I'd be grateful.
So you went to the gym? Is it a tracksuit?
I'm surprised
you didn't sell your uniform.
I could start up again, so I kept it.
Whatever. Don't eat anything
in the car from now on.
Goodness, you look great!
Since you're so tall and handsome,
everything looks great on you.
It looks better on me,
but you don't look too bad.
You look like you've done
kendo for 10 years.
Thanks. But I think
I should just wear my clothes.
You can't wear these. They reek.
I'll wash out the stains,
so wear them when they dry.
It won't take long since it's sunny.
Let's go to avoid the traffic.
But I…
I'm so sorry.
We're making memories. Don't you agree?
Let's go.
I purposely sat in the middle
so she wouldn't abuse you again.
Abuse? Not at all.
Why are we going so slow though?
It's taking ages. Step on it.
I'm trying to, but it's not working.
What's wrong with this?
Maybe it needs a tune up.
The car's inching along,
and it's dead silent inside.
Lighten up the mood.
Should we listen to some music as we go?
Sounds good!
Road trips and music go hand in hand.
Let's listen to my favorite song.
You are beautiful
You are trustworthy
Don't be shy
Jeong-woo!
Are you okay? I'm sorry.
Why can't you leave him alone?
No, I'm okay.
-I'm really okay.
-Okay.
-Jeez.
-What? The warning light turned on.
I think something's wrong with the car.
There's a nail stuck in the tire.
-Where?
-Over here.
Goodness.
Okay, please come
as soon as possible. Goodbye.
-What did they say? Are they coming soon?
-Well…
There's traffic on the highway,
so it'll take them an hour or two.
Why did you want to meet at the sauna?
I thought about it,
and there's a lot to do here.
There's table tennis
and a basketball hoop.
I can teach him sports
and we can bathe together too.
-It's perfect for Jin-woo, right?
-Yes, but…
-Jin-woo.
-Yes?
-Are you done eating?
-Yes.
Good, get up. We have lots to do.
You don't have to do that.
Don't ride his shoulders. Just walk.
No. Grandma has a weak neck.
Her older sister has a weak back.
And her younger sister has weak joints.
And you don't let me ride
because you're tired.
Then, when will I get the chance?
So I'll never get to try before I grow up?
Gosh, this just breaks my heart.
Just get me some pain patches later. Okay?
Hop on, Jin-woo.
Okay. One, two!
Okay! Good!
-Let's go!
-Jin-woo.
Jin-woo, focus.
Yes. That's it!
Go, Jin-woo.
-That's it! Here!
-You can do it!
Are you okay?
Oh, no. Are you okay?
My ear…
-Are you okay?
-There's a hole.
What are you doing?
That's so childish. Jeez.
-Wasn't that funny?
-Yes.
You have a good sense of humor.
High five! Okay!
Okay, go back to your side.
Jin-woo, aim at the circle on the monster.
Aim at the red.
You're doing so well. Nice.
Hong-ran, don't hold it with both hands.
Place one hand here.
By the way, are you two dating?
Are you Mom's boyfriend?
What? No, he's not.
He's not my boyfriend.
No way, Jin-woo.
EMERGENCY REPAIR
-Okay, it's all done.
-Thank you.
-Have a nice day.
-You too.
Let's buy Jeong-woo clothes first.
There's an outlet nearby.
We should hurry then.
We should see your dad before sundown.
Her dad?
This was my dad's favorite season.
So around this time of the year,
our family goes to Busan to see him
and the beach
where we used to walk together.
We can't be laughing
during his death anniversary,
so we just visit on another day
to reminisce about him.
I see.
I'm glad the sun's still up.
Me too.
Let's quickly greet him and go.
I'll wait here.
I don't want to be in the way.
Goodness, you're not.
You can come if you want.
He probably doesn't want to.
Who knows if they'll get married?
I bet he's uncomfortable.
No, that's not why.
I'm not sure if it's right
for me to be there.
Then, can you wait here for a bit?
I forgot to tell you
about this visit. I'm sorry.
Don't be. Go on then. You can go.
Okay. Just wait a little bit.
All right.
Let's go.
It's been a while, Dad.
You must be so surprised to see me.
He's probably surprised
to see how much you've aged.
You little…
He's probably more shocked
to see that you're still unemployed.
-Exactly.
-What?
I'm working hard
to make milmyeon these days.
Right, Uncle Tae-seon?
He does work hard.
I told you. I prayed all night
when Ha-neul was in surgery.
I promised to work hard
like people my age if surgery went well.
I prayed with all my heart.
Maybe my prayers were answered.
Thankfully, she recovered.
I almost flew to Greece to say thank you.
Why Greece?
Jesus.
He was Greek. He was born in Greece.
What? Am I wrong?
Of course, it's wrong. You fool.
Just go to Greece already.
Yes, please leave.
Come on. Don't be so harsh on him.
Gosh, you're so optimistic and kind.
So when are you leaving?
When are you-- Let go.
When should we send him off?
-Should we book the ticket?
-Should we?
Greece does sound good.
I'd love to visit.
SECOND GENERATION
SIXTY YEARS OF TRADITION
Gosh, long time no see.
-Goodness.
-This is on the house.
Eat up.
-Thank you.
Gosh, she gave us too much.
Unbelievable.
This place hasn't changed one bit.
It's the same.
-Did you come here often?
-Yeah.
Our dad enjoyed drinking soju here,
so we came often.
She drank soda
while solving math problems.
I remember we were drinking one time,
and he suddenly disappeared.
I looked everywhere for him,
and he was sprawled out on the beach.
Don't get me started.
He had sand in his ears for days.
To be honest, I resented him recently.
These two were in pain,
and he wasn't doing anything.
Come on.
What?
I did resent him.
But I mean now that I'm here,
it was good to see him.
It would've been nice
if you greeted him too.
You're right.
I thought you weren't supposed to,
but you were more cheerful than expected.
What I mean is
I've never lost a family member before,
so I thought the visit
would be very sad and gloomy.
That's why I thought
I should've stayed out.
There are many ways to miss someone.
A lot of time has passed for us,
so we only think of the good memories.
We still miss him, but we're not sad.
-Is Jin-woo asleep?
-Yes.
He played so much today
he was out as soon as he lied down.
I'm sorry you had to come all the way here
just because he wanted to play more.
Don't worry about it.
I agreed to play with him,
so I might as well use the whole day.
Right. Here.
You taught him some sports
and took him to the sauna.
Thank you.
I've used up all my SOS stickers now.
What a bummer.
Right. I should get going.
How about a cup of tea before you go?
We have tons of tea bags.
Really?
Well, having too many tea bags
is a huge problem.
Allow me to use some for you.
MOM
We're departing now.
Are you okay, Ms. Kong?
Of course, I am. I'm not drunk one bit.
Jeong-woo,
want to eat some ice cream?
You used to eat ice cream
after drinking with your husband, right?
How did you know?
I had a hunch.
Just as I thought, you're so smart.
I'm sorry you had to tag along
and have such a hard time.
Not at all.
I actually feel bad for tagging along.
I didn't know you were visiting him.
Gosh, it's nothing serious.
It's like I just told you.
We're no longer sad now.
We only remember the good times.
We're totally fine now,
aside from missing him at times.
How much time needs to pass
for things to feel okay like that?
I guess I'm not strong enough.
It's still really tough for me.
What's so tough?
Forget that bastard
and the pain he caused you.
It's hard to forget.
I'm such an idiot.
I can't forget how good he was to me.
I keep thinking about
how he was the only one
who showed up for my graduation.
I was never a priority to my parents.
And my graduation was no different.
Hey, Jeong-woo!
Kyung-min was the first person
who didn't forget about me.
Kyung-min!
Sorry for being so late. Congratulations.
Thanks.
Here.
Take it.
Is this the black suit?
Yes, take it.
Yes!
Thank you so much!
-You're the best!
-Are you that happy?
Yes.
-Congratulations.
-Let's go eat some tteokbokki.
Okay, let's go.
-Are you buying?
-Of course. Let's go.
I didn't know back then
that it had only been days
since his father had passed away.
I can't fathom how he must've felt
as he came to see me
with the suit he promised.
Ms. Kong.
I'm having a pretty tough time.
Yesterday, I was willing to forgive him.
But today, I don't want to.
I can't resent him.
But I can't understand him either.
It's too painful.
I don't know what to do.
Oh, dear.
You poor, sweet child.
You're too kind-hearted for this world.
Jeong-woo.
Someone once said
you forgive someone not for their sake
but for yours.
Hating someone is so exhausting.
It's painful, miserable, and upsetting.
Feeling that way towards someone
is hurting you too much.
But it would be too cruel
to tell you to forgive him.
After everything you've been through?
So for now,
let's wait.
Let's not try to forget anything.
Let's just wait.
Then, those memories
will become less painful and sad.
Let time heal us.
Goodness.
It's okay. You can cry.
It must've been so painful.
Why are you alone?
You couldn't find your mom and Jeong-woo?
I think they're getting some air.
It seemed like they need it,
so I just came back.
Is Jeong-woo going to dump you today?
Why would he?
Because we were such an embarrassment.
You sure were.
Yeah, this was a rough trip.
But in any case, what matters is
we got here safe and sound.
You got a text from Hong-ran.
She said you should accept
the assistant professor position.
Why did you look at my phone?
I wasn't meaning to.
Your phone was vibrating so much.
It was shaking the table,
and I ended up seeing it.
I saw the news.
All those bastards
who were connected to that guy were fired.
-Yeah.
-Is that why you got the offer?
But I don't know what to do.
It all happened because of me,
so I feel bad.
Ha-neul, I never thought
you'd study anesthesiology.
You know those doctors
who conduct surgeries in medical dramas?
I thought you'd do that instead.
But anesthesiology?
Well, it was really unexpected.
Really?
That's why I asked you
why you picked that department.
Do you remember what you said?
What did I say?
Your dad underwent countless surgeries
while he was sick those eight years.
When he had his final surgery,
you were crying outside
and didn't know what to do.
Then, a doctor approached you
and told you not to worry.
He said he'd do his best
to have your dad sleep peacefully
and have a nice dream.
You're right.
I didn't want to send him
into the OR by himself.
And I was worried
he'd be in a lot of pain.
But that's what
the anesthesiologist told me.
Right. You said that was
the reason why you chose that field.
That's when I realized
your dad's death hurt you deeply,
and it broke my heart.
But I also realized
you chose the perfect field.
Right, I did.
I wanted to comfort my patients
just like that anesthesiologist did.
Don't worry.
Once you wake up
from a nice nap, everything will be fine.
Pain is the worst feeling
a human could experience.
By administering strong analgesics
before they could feel pain,
so I enjoyed relieving their pain.
Some patients think anesthesiologists
leave the operating room afterwards.
But we change their blood bags
and administer more drugs.
We also maintain
their blood pressure and breathing.
We stay alert throughout surgery
and protect our unconscious patients.
Due to ruptured aortas,
falls, or car accidents,
we sometimes get patients
who are bleeding profusely.
At times, I'd worry those cases
would be challenging.
But when they would recover,
I'd simply be grateful they pulled through
and quietly cheered them on.
And I liked that.
You should go back to where you belong.
Go do your job before it's too late.
What in the world?
What's with this vibe?
Stop being so serious and let's have fun!
Okay. Three, six, nine!
Three, six, nine! One!
I'm glad I tagged along.
After all that you went through?
It was nothing.
Actually, I need to tell you something.
I know your parents are in Seoul.
-How?
-I heard you talking to them this morning.
I see.
That's why you wanted to leave, right?
You didn't want to see them yet.
Well…
Finding out my parents
hurt someone so deeply
was hard for me to accept.
Should I resent them
for driving him over the edge?
Or should I resent him
for doing the unthinkable?
I didn't know what to do.
But now, I think
I've sorted out my thoughts somewhat.
Whether it's resentment or understanding,
I'll do as my heart says.
I decided to let time pass.
Then after some time,
maybe I'll become okay one day
like your family.
So?
-Is that all you wanted to tell me?
-What?
You seemed concerned
about something lately.
Actually, I got an offer
to be an assistant professor.
Seriously? Why didn't you tell me?
You had a lot on your plate already,
so I couldn't tell you.
You shouldn't think that way.
You were in pain because of what happened,
but I was given
this position because of it.
I felt guilty
about being happy with the offer.
This is just
the result of all your hard work.
So don't feel guilty.
I'm truly happy for you.
Also,
I hope you accept the offer.
Okay?
My goodness!
Congratulations.
Thanks.
I'm so proud of you.
I can't believe this.
You're the best!
It's so pretty.
It really is.
The fireworks disappeared quickly.
But the display
continued to live in my memory.
The lights soared, shined, and dispersed.
They're shining so brightly.
And we realized
everything was bound to disappear
and the only things
that last are the memories.
We could let go
of things we wanted to forget
and hold on to memories we wanted to keep.
Just like the fireworks.
HANYANG HWARO
Cheers to Dr. Nam!
-Cheers!
Thank you.
-Congratulations.
Dr. Nam.
We just met but I can't believe
you're leaving us already.
I'm so happy for you.
Congratulations. You should hurry and go.
I'm sorry I have to leave so soon.
It was only going to be temporary anyway.
He's right. Don't feel bad and focus
on climbing the ladder, Professor Nam.
Eat up, Professor Nam.
I came here with Jeong-woo once,
and it was so good.
-That's why I booked this place.
-Thank you for the meal.
The restaurant is packed.
I wish our clinic was half as full.
Hey, you little…
Why would you bring that up?
I'll be back.
Hong-ran got a cake for our goodbye party
and wants me to pick it up.
She's my friend who works
at the OBGYN clinic across the hall.
We know her. Dr. Lee Hong-ran.
We're close with her nurses.
Right. I heard you two were best friends.
She should join us
if she hasn't eaten yet.
That's okay.
I'm already embarrassed about the cake,
but I'm accepting it for her sake.
But still, she came all the way here.
Wouldn't it be too cruel
to not invite her?
He's right. She should join us
if she's okay with it.
She'd probably feel too awkward to join.
Hello, I'm Ha-neul's friend.
-Do you mind if I join?
-You already have.
-We're glad you're here.
-Welcome.
-Have some.
-Thanks.
Dr. Yeo, you're so kind.
People might think you two were dating.
Since you're naturally so considerate,
you must be nice to everyone.
Could I have some too?
You don't have to pretend.
We all know they're dating.
Seriously?
You said it was a secret.
I thought it was, but they all caught on.
I never imagined
there would be a couple in our clinic.
-I was so surprised.
-Me too.
Hold on.
Maybe there's another couple in hiding.
To be honest, I've had my suspicions
about Dr. Bin and Nurse Do.
That's ridiculous.
We're like siblings.
She was my colleague at my previous job.
Then, I quit along with him.
That was only because I said
I'd pay you more.
Let's be honest.
Let's say we were on a deserted island.
We still wouldn't have
feelings for each other.
Why won't you answer me? It's true.
Who knows?
If it's only us two,
maybe we'd develop feelings then.
You're so mischievous today.
The meat's burning. Eat up, everyone.
That's still raw.
-What are you doing?
-What?
He's flustered.
There really must be something
going on between them.
Just be honest.
Come to think of it,
you look good together!
Hong-ran.
Why didn't you wait for me?
Jeez. My colleagues love to tease me.
Nurse Do and I really are like siblings,
so I don't know why
they'd say such things.
Who knows?
They must've based it
on things they've seen before.
And you two do seem pretty close.
Even on the rooftop last time, you were--
Wait.
Have you been keeping
an eye on me since then?
"Keeping an eye on you"?
I'm not a CCTV camera.
I'm just saying.
But…
You're the only one
I make time for on the weekends.
I'm curious and worried about.
And I didn't feel uncomfortable
when we shared that umbrella.
"I wish the rain won't stop."
You're the only one
who made me think like that.
What?
Take these.
Why?
Even without those,
I'll do whatever you ask me to do.
I don't think I'm seeing you
solely for the purpose
of helping each other out.
To be honest,
I was hurt when you told Jin-woo
I wasn't your boyfriend.
But I get that you had to lie to your son.
Now that he's not here,
let's have an honest talk.
Am I really…
not your boyfriend?
Well…
Because I…
Dr. Bin!
You forgot this.
What is this love triangle?
It seemed like Nurse Do
might have been interested too.
-Don't you think it's a love triangle?
-Perhaps.
I've never been this uninterested
in a relationship before.
Why not? I'm curious.
Hong-ran is interested in him too.
I wonder who'll end up with him.
But why him?
By the way,
aren't you tired after the party?
Your new job starts tomorrow.
I'm okay.
How does it feel to return
after a long time away?
Well…
I feel nervous, afraid,
and… excited as well.
Then, let me take
your nervousness and fear.
You can keep the excitement.
Okay.
-But I'm a bit sad too.
-Why?
We can't hold hands or have ice cream
after work like this anymore.
It's the end of our little happiness.
Your schedule will become hectic.
We won't be able to call each other often.
It'll be hard to meet up.
I'll be miserable missing you so much.
Then, I'll end up being lovesick.
You're so silly.
Gosh.
Don't worry.
I'm not going to
exhaust myself like I used to.
I'll still do my best,
but I'll take care of myself
and you.
Do you promise? You better keep your word.
-Okay.
-All right, then.
You got a text.
MS. KONG WOL-SEON
Ha-neul.
Tomorrow's your first day at work.
Hurry on home and rest.
Where are you?
What is this?
ANESTHESIOLOGIST NAM HA-NEUL
No way.
I should make that my profile picture too.
Don't.
Why not? You look so good.
I said don't.
Hold on.
-"Daehan National University Hospital."
-Stop.
-I'm going to hate it so much. Stop it!
-"Professor Nam Ha-neul!"
Where are you?
Give me your phone.
-Hold on.
-Give it to me.
Stop it.
Stay back. I'm warning you.
I'm leaving now.
Look at you.
All dressed up like a professor.
Have a good day, Professor Nam.
What's wrong with you guys? Bye.
Delete your profile picture.
BUSAN'S ORIGINAL MILMYEON
Ha-neul, your shoe.
-Bye, Uncle Tae-seon.
-Bye.
Gosh, here we go again.
After many ups and downs,
Ha-neul finally returned to her place.
Hello, I'll be her anesthesiologist today.
Hi, Se-mi.
Hello.
You're so energetic.
Which kindergarten do you go to?
Haenim Kindergarten.
What a pretty name.
You've run around
in kindergarten before, right?
Can you take deep breaths
like you were running?
Yes.
Then, can you come with me
and show me how to do it?
Okay. There's nothing to be afraid of.
I'll be by your side.
Okay.
Let's do our best.
-She tried so hard to come this far.
-You're so pretty.
So I hope she'll shine brightly.
The case we'll talk about today
is when anaphylactic shock
occurs during anesthesia.
Dr. Kim Seon-cheol
previously introduced this patient.
They had never undergone surgery before
and had no history of allergies.
I earnestly prayed
she would have big dreams and soar high
after all the pain and loss she suffered…
as I made dumplings.
Gosh, you're doing pretty well now.
You bet.
All right.
Since you're good with your hands,
you make good dumplings too.
Exactly. He's been making dumplings
every day while waiting for Ha-neul.
And now, he's become an expert.
Ha-neul said she'll be home early today.
Lucky you.
Ha-neul, are you on your way?
I see. It's an emergency.
No, it's okay.
Okay. Hang in there.
What's with the rage?
Don't take it out on the poor dough.
I'm okay.
I'm fine.
Darn it.
I thought I'd see her today,
so it makes me even sadder.
She promised to take care of me,
but she didn't keep her word.
No!
Don't be waiting for her, Jeong-woo.
Just take care of your own business.
Then, you won't feel so sad.
All right.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
BUSAN'S ORIGINAL MILMYEON
I wanted to have coffee with you
this morning, but I have a meeting.
You must be tired,
so have some. I miss you.
Me too.
Darn it.
I was awake until 3:00 a.m.
What time did she come home then?
Gosh.
Ha-neul…
Ha-neul?
ATTORNEY HAN JIN
Why do you look so down this morning?
Are you worried about something?
I'm sure you want me to ask you that,
but forget it. I can't be bothered.
You little brat.
Do you know how much pain I'm in?
In front of the woman I like,
I kissed another--
Never mind. I'm upset,
so let's get a drink later.
Okay. It'll be my treat.
I have some money now.
Money? From where?
Remember the penalties I paid
for the medical accident?
I got some of that back.
How much?
You don't have to know.
How much is it?
Why would you ask about that?
Tell me. I'm curious.
Jeez.
Two hundred million?
Two billion won?
Keep it down, will you?
I'm so jealous.
You got that money back
because you were proven innocent.
That is true.
In any case,
the incident hurt my reputation
and made me close down my clinic.
I didn't nitpick about who's fault it was.
I just settled and took the compensation.
Hey, let's go.
Let's go and spend that money.
Buy me a car.
What? Even I don't have one.
Then, let's go get you one.
Let's buy you a wallet and a belt.
And leave the 300,000-won-a-month rooftop.
It's actually 500,000 won.
I'm so jealous.
What will you do with that money?
I did give it some thought.
I'll spend it on something
to help Ha-neul and I be together.
Something to help you be together?
Do you mean…
Come in.
Jeong-woo. What are you doing here?
I've missed you.
Me too.
It was so hard to see you, so I came here.
I hope I'm not interrupting though.
No, not at all.
I was upset I couldn't see you
since I had so little free time.
Seeing you has made
all my fatigue disappear.
I'm the best energizer there is.
This room looks nice.
Gosh, you look so professional
in your own office.
Do you want some coffee?
Or should we go out to eat?
You see… I actually came by
to tell you something.
What is it?
Lately,
it's been really tough
since I haven't seen you.
So to be by your side,
I made a huge decision.
What kind of decision?
Who is this?
She's seven
and has microtia of the right ear.
I'm still in touch
with my old volunteer organization.
I asked if there was anyone
who needed my help.
I'd like to perform surgery on her.
But my clinic isn't fit
for this type of surgery.
So I just met
with a doctor from your hospital.
They're going to do
her reconstructive surgery here,
and I'll be helping them.
-Really?
-Yeah.
At first, I was only going to pay
for the surgery and do the checkup.
But since it meant I could be with you,
Dr. Nam, I wanted to…
I mean, Professor Nam.
I wanted to do
something meaningful together.
Would you be willing to join me?
If you look here…
Hello, I'll get right into the case.
This is seven-year-old Rhea.
She's set to receive surgery for microtia.
If you look at her right ear,
she has Grade 2A auricular hypoplasia
and aural atresia as well.
The pediatric genetic testing
showed no signs
of additional syndromes or deformities.
We plan to have a two-stage operation.
For the first operation,
we plan to do a rib cartilage harvest
from the left side
for reconstructive surgery of the auricle.
-Jeong-woo.
-Yes?
I'm really impressed by you.
In that case,
we should have a detailed discussion
regarding that topic.
How exactly do I impress you?
Explain it to me in detail.
You see…
A lot of people want to do
good things in life.
But it's not easy
to actually carry it out.
I respect you a lot for actually deciding
to do something like this.
It wasn't easy to get this money back.
So I wanted to use it
in a more meaningful way.
I see.
So I get that you're amazing.
But you should've just cut to the chase.
Why did you say you wanted to spend it
on something to help us be together?
You made me tense for no reason.
Tense?
Why?
Well…
I tend to get tense easily.
I see.
I'm a bit tired. Do you want some coffee?
I'm going to make some for myself.
Why did we both get texts?
Here are the photos
from our trip to Busan.
They're photos from Busan.
You don't have to look at the last photo.
-Why not?
-You don't have to know.
Holy cow!
This will be a great profile picture.
-I'm setting it as mine.
-No. Don't do that!
-You can't!
-Why not? It's my phone.
We don't have time for this.
I have a gift for--
Please don't do that!
Go back to work.
DOCTOR SLUMP
Should I give it to her like this?
Or like this?
Like this… Oh, no!
Forget her job. She's been single forever.
I need to be somewhere right now.
Could I see some bracelets?
From Ha-neul's standpoint,
she might still have doubts about you.
Necklaces. Can I see your necklaces?
Jeong-woo would be insane
to date that horrible Ha-neul.
You're so pretty.
Do you want to join my family?
This was the most touching proposal ever.
Tell her you have the night shift today.
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim