(Destiny and Saving)
(Episode 12)
Just checking her condition.
Why do we have to be kicked out?
The Young Sect Leader said
it's not good to disturb the Divine Healer
while he's checking her condition.
What are you complaining about?
Even I was kicked out.
What do you mean?
Are you someone special?
I'm the one who brought the Divine Healer here.
What kind of weird old man have you brought?
Looks like you've met your match.
What is Mo Xiao up to?
Divine Healer.
You can start now.
Well, I don't mind people being around
when I'm treating.
But it's better to send them out first.
Just prepare some wine for me.
Did you figure out what illness it is?
This young lady has an innate condition of extreme cold in her body.
No one can cure it.
Why did you specifically come to me, then?
Her cold condition is indeed difficult to cure.
But if I want to save her life,
only you can do it in this world.
Isn't that right?
I don't want that peach blossom wine.
You saved her life back then.
Are you going to ignore her now?
So, that day when you disappeared suddenly,
you went looking for the Divine Healer.
What else could I do?
Did you think I got cold feet?
You were gone for three days without a word.
I thought you had been kidnapped by those evil forces.
What?
You started to worry about me?
I was just worried
that
if the Phoenix-masked Woman shows up suddenly,
we naturally have one less helper
without you.
So you were just worried that no one would protect you.
I don't need your protection.
I was worried about Miss Wu Chen and Mo Xiao.
Of course.
Who could compare to your beloved
Mo Xiao?
Alright.
You're pretty good to.
To have found Shi Bujiu so quickly
and returned in time.
How did you do that?
Did you forget?
I had arranged to meet him before we came.
We agreed to meet at Peach Blossom Village in half a month.
I figured since we had a prior arrangement,
he should be nearby.
So I went to look for him,
and I found him.
However,
it's strange.
Our Uncle Master Xuan Zhen
is also a master of medicine.
Why didn't Mo Xiao
look for him
and instead had you prepare the peach blossom wine
and look for
this elusive old man,
Shi Bujiu?
Mo Xiao is always very calculated in his actions.
He must have his reasons for doing this.
You knew that Feng Xingtian had come to me?
When Feng Lixue was born,
the cold aura was so severe
and she almost died in infancy.
Feng Xingtian came to find you.
Although you couldn't cure the cold condition in her body,
you gave her an Ice silkworm cocoon
to protect herself from the cold aura.
This allowed her to be close to others,
to be fed,
and to grow up.
But if you knew I couldn't cure it,
why did you come to me again?
Divine Healer.
I invited you here
not just to treat her illness.
I wanted
to confirm something as well.
What do you want to confirm?
That young lady.
Is she the infant you saved years ago?
Is she Feng Lixue?
I've treated
countless people in my life,
and never failed.
Only for
her extraordinarily cold condition,
I was powerless to help.
I'm ashamed to mention it to the world.
At that time,
that infant
had unusual blood and meridians.
I will never forget it in my lifetime.
She
is undoubtedly Feng Lixue.
I'm Feng Lixue.
Then, Mo Xiao,
how exactly will you take me up the mountain?
I was born with a body of extreme cold.
No one could get close to me.
The white ice silkworm's cocoon is extremely cold.
It doesn't get wet in water, nor does it burn in fire.
Divine Healer, your appointment at Peach Blossom Village this time,
is also about the Tianxing Secret Treasury?
Ten years ago,
I learned that Feng Xingtian and his daughter
had both fallen off a cliff and died.
My precious Ice silkworm cocoon
disappeared without a trace.
I thought
perhaps that treasure
had been collected into the Tianxing Secret Treasury.
As the infant grows into an adult, the effect of Ice silkworm cocoon
has diminished.
But I
still want to find that treasure.
Haven't you ever considered thinking about
why the daughter of Feng Xingtian
would come back to life?
There are as many extraordinary people in this world.
If she can come back from the dead,
then it's her fate.
What does it have to do with me?
Mo Xiao,
you don't think
this is somehow connected to me, do you?
Other than you,
I can't think of anyone else in this world
who has such incredible power.
Mo Xiao.
You know
I only focus on treating patients.
I've never been involved in
matters of the martial world.
Please don't be hasty, Divine Healer.
I just have some doubts,
and hope you could give me some guidance.
As for the Tianxing Secret Treasury,
there are many rumors floating around.
So,
regarding the fact that Miss Wu Chen is Feng Lixue,
I hope you won't spread it around.
I haven't even mentioned you yet.
You're bringing up all sorts of nonsense
and now you're trying to restrict me.
You're a free spirit, a recluse beyond worldly affairs.
It was thoughtless of me.
A jar of fine wine, please.
Let it go.
The world is ever-changing,
and how is that my concern?
Prepare the wine for me.
I'm going to start working on the prescription.
After 10 years of diligent practice,
I must understand this cold syndrome this time,
and redeem my past failure.
The first step
is to infuse the blood and energy of a person with great cultivation
into her body,
to protect her heart veins from the cold poison.
The second step
is to use a thousand-year-old snow lotus in the medicine.
The cold aura in her body is too strong.
Only the thousand-year-old snow lotus
can help concentrate and control the cold aura inside her.
The thousand-year-old snow lotus?
Yes.
Isn't that a spiritual herb that grows in the desolate snowy mountain?
It's not easy to find at all.
I'll go.
You can't go.
You just transferred your spiritual power to Wu Chen.
Your body is so weak.
How can you go to such an extremely cold place?
I'll go.
Then I'll go too.
We'll go together.
That thousand-year-old snow lotus
possesses divine spiritual energy.
It roams the snow regions and its location is unpredictable.
If too many people go there,
I'm afraid it might startle the snow lotus
and it won't reveal itself.
I'll go alone.
♫A pale moon through the screen, your face so bright♫
♫Mist and clouds gather, I long for just one glance♫
♫Some find closure, some regret, for a thousand years♫
♫The bell and homing swallows stir my heartstrings♫
♫Fingers linger on those words once more♫
♫I know the lines, not the tone, leave it to fate♫
♫Parted, reunited, replayed in the wind♫
♫Vanished, reappeared, rising in dreams♫
♫A sword in the eyes, a thread in the heart, unbroken♫
♫Though the wind carries, with no return, drifting, echoes tense♫
Little girl,
you've already lost the third round.
♫Though the wind carries, with no return, drifting, echoes tense♫
♫Falling flowers rise, flowing water feels no weight♫
you've already lost the third round.
Drink it up, drink it all up!
♫Falling flowers rise, flowing water feels no weight♫
Hurry up.
Drink it up.
♫Gather a lifetime of blossoms, like dreams, like you♫
-Okay, let's continue.
-Come on.
♫Gather a lifetime of blossoms, like dreams, like you♫
-Good brothers.
-Three stars shine.
♫Gather a lifetime of blossoms, like dreams, like you♫
-Five champions.
You lost. You lost.
♫Gather a lifetime of blossoms, like dreams, like you♫
I won again, I won again.
♫Though just a moment, countless thoughts, unspoken, joy and grief entwined♫
I'm so happy.
Drink up, drink up.
♫Though just a moment, countless thoughts, unspoken, joy and grief entwined♫
You lost to me again.
♫Wipe away tears, never part, never leave♫
Let's go another round.
Come on, come on.
♫Wipe away tears, never part, never leave♫
♫Drenched in a lifetime of rain, waiting for the perfect line, and for you, for you♫
Come on, come on.
♫Wipe away tears, never part, never leave♫
♫Drenched in a lifetime of rain, waiting for the perfect line, and for you, for you♫
Drink it all. Drink it all up.
-Good brothers.
♫Drenched in a lifetime of rain, waiting for the perfect line, and for you, for you♫
-Three stars shine.
-Fortune in four seasons.
♫Drenched in a lifetime of rain, waiting for the perfect line, and for you, for you♫
Five...
You got it wrong again.
♫Drenched in a lifetime of rain, waiting for the perfect line, and for you, for you♫
Wrong again, wrong again.
Come on, come on.
♫Drenched in a lifetime of rain, waiting for the perfect line, and for you, for you♫
Let me pour for you.
I'll pour for you.
(Peach Blossom Wine)
♫Though the wind carries, with no return, drifting, echoes tense♫
♫Falling flowers rise, flowing water feels no weight♫
♫Gather a lifetime of blossoms, like dreams, like you♫
♫Though just a moment, countless thoughts, unspoken, joy and grief entwined♫
♫Wipe away tears, never part, never leave♫
♫Drenched in a lifetime of rain, waiting for the perfect line, and for you, for you♫
♫Though the wind carries, with no return, drifting, echoes tense♫
♫Falling flowers rise, flowing water feels no weight♫
♫Gather a lifetime of blossoms, like dreams, like you♫
You're cheating.
-No.
You've already drunk so much.
♫Though just a moment, countless thoughts, unspoken, joy and grief entwined♫
I haven't had a single sip yet.
-It's so good.
-Give it back.
♫Though just a moment, countless thoughts, unspoken, joy and grief entwined♫
-You can't drink alone.
-No cheating.
♫Though just a moment, countless thoughts, unspoken, joy and grief entwined♫
Give it to me.
♫Wipe away tears, never part, never leave♫
-No
-No way!
♫Wipe away tears, never part, never leave♫
No.
-No.
-No way!
♫Wipe away tears, never part, never leave♫
No, no, no.
♫Drenched in a lifetime of rain, waiting for the perfect line, and for you, for you♫
I haven't even tasted this good wine.
Look at him!
♫Drenched in a lifetime of rain, waiting for the perfect line, and for you, for you♫
No, no.
What are you doing?
♫Drenched in a lifetime of rain, waiting for the perfect line, and for you, for you♫
No, no.
Don't run.
♫Drenched in a lifetime of rain, waiting for the perfect line, and for you, for you♫
You've almost drunk it all.
I haven't had a single sip.
♫Drenched in a lifetime of rain, waiting for the perfect line, and for you, for you♫
-Give it to me!
-No, no, no.
♫Drenched in a lifetime of rain, waiting for the perfect line, and for you, for you♫
No, no, no.
Divine Healer. Divine Healer.
Divine Healer, wake up.
Divine Healer.
The thousand-year snow lotus.
You found it!
You really did find it.
My little treasure.
I need to hurry and use it in the medicine.
If I delay, it'll affect the effect of the medicine.
Found it, found it.
Finally found the snow lotus.
Do you have something to ask me?
Are you hiding something from me?
What makes you say that?
Mo Xiao.
You've always been calm and thoughtful,
but you've repeatedly taken risks for Wu Chen.
What exactly is she to you?
You've asked this question before.
But I think now
you must have a new answer.
You should at least let me know
why you're going to such lengths
for her.
Mo Xiao,
don't tell me you've really fallen for her.
You're the Young Sect Leader of the Shushan Sect,
the only successor of the Sword Sovereign Fengyue.
You're different from us.
If you've truly developed feelings for her,
what about the future of Shushan?
As a brother,
I really don't want to see you
ruin your bright future.
Lingyun.
Do you know why I asked you
to invite the Divine Healer Shi Bujiu?
I do.
To cure the cold poison in Wu Chen's body.
Wu Chen was born with this cold condition.
No one can cure it.
Actually,
it's not caused by the snow demon from the snow realm.
Then why did you ask me to...
Could she really be
Feng Lixue?
Then who is the Phoenix-masked Woman?
That's exactly the question I can't figure out.
This snow lotus elixir
is repelled by the cold aura in Wu Chen's body.
It can't be infused into her body.
I want revenge!
Lixue!
Lixue.
What's wrong with you?
Did you have a nightmare?
You're awake.
You just called out for Lixue.
Who is she?
She is the daughter
of the Heavenly Order Sect Leader, Feng Xingtian.
Phoenix-masked Woman.
Does she look like me?
Why
do you ask that?
Because
when I was in Shushan,
your Master locked me into the Demon Subduing Palace
and mentioned this name.
I've been hearing this name more and more lately.
Do I have any connection to her?
What are you thinking about?
(Peach Blossom Villa)
Zifeng.
Do you remember what the Sect Leader said back then
(Peach Blossom Villa)
when he selected the three of us from the Fengyu Branch,
Tielyv Branch,
and Baicao Branch
to be the
Guardian
of the Young Sect Leader?
As Guardian,
we are to help the Young Sect Leader avert disasters,
enhance his achievements,
honor the righteous path,
subdue demonic hearts,
guard the Young Sect Leader,
and defend the righteous path of the Shushan Sect.
That's correct.
That's our duty.
But
why are you asking this all of a sudden?
Are you feeling guilty because the Young Sect Leader
encountered difficulties after leaving Shushan?
Do you blame us for not protecting him well?
If the Young Sect Leader is tempted by the demonic heart,
should we help him subdue those evil thoughts?
What?
Don't talk nonsense!
I hope I'm just talking nonsense.
You've always taken the guardian duties most seriously since childhood.
Actually,
you don't need to put so much pressure on yourself.
Zimu and I are here too.
Zisu.
Did Mo Xiao send you to find me?
You've been hiding your identity
and staying close to the Young Sect Leader.
What exactly is your purpose?
Hiding my identity?
What identity?
The daughter of the Tianxing Sect leader,
Feng Lixue.
You're also saying I'm Feng Lixue?
Are you going to deny it?
I'm not denying it,
I just don't understand
why you all say I'm Feng Lixue,
but I have no memory of it myself.
You really don't know?
I don't know who I am.
It's ridiculous, isn't it?
Wu Chen.
I brought your favorite glutinous rice balls.
No matter who you are,
you'd better disappear on your own soon.
Young Master Jing.
What's wrong with Zisu?
She looks unhappy.
She's worried about me.
Worried about you?
But your cold syndrome has been
cured by the Divine Healer
Mo Xiao brought.
What is there to worry about?
Wu Chen,
you've made progress with your Ice Technique.
No,
I still haven't fully mastered it.
You've just recovered,
there's no need to rush practicing the Ice Technique.
No,
I still need to practice hard.
What's wrong?
Is it because so much has happened recently
and it scared you?
Don't worry,
we're here.
We won't let anything happen to you.
No,
I can't rely on you guys forever.
I have my own matters to take care of.
What matters?
Important matters.
Supreme Lord.
Mo Xiao
seems to have confirmed Wu Chen's identity.
Just based on Shi Bujiu's words?
No,
that will only make him more confused.
If he wants to find the answer,
he must go to Tongming Island.
However, Supreme Lord.
Wu Chen is starting to question
her background.
Since she has left Mang Mountain,
there are some questions
she must learn
to face on her own.
Great Guardian.
Will the Young Miss really appear here?
The Young Miss summoned us
with the Phoenix Feather Order.
So she'll certainly keep her word.
Those people are already eager
to head into the Myriad Isles Ice Lake to find Tongming Island.
I wonder when the Young Miss will open the Tianxing Secret Treasury.
The Young Miss surely has her own plans.
We
just need to do what we are supposed to.
Young Miss.
You haven't shown yourself for several days now.
I don't know what to do.
Please give me your instructions, Young Miss.
Three days later,
Tongming Island will appear.
Young Miss,
do you really intend to open the Tianxing Secret Treasury?
I'll follow your every command.
Then do what you're supposed to do.
Don't ask things
you shouldn't ask.
Great Guardian.
The Tianxing Secret Treasury
contains the treasures Master spent his whole life to find.
Does Young Miss
really want to reveal everything
and distribute all the rare treasures from the Treasury?
Indeed,
these are the fruits of our Master's lifelong efforts.
It's truly a pity
to give them away so easily.
The Young Miss is now the owner of the Tianxing Secret Treasury.
We'll follow
whatever she says.
But Great Guardian,
that day at the entrance of the Myriad Isles Ice Lake,
you saw it too.
The girl named Wu Chen beside Mo Xiao.
The cold aura she released was enough to freeze everything within a hundred steps.
Moreover,
you've also mentioned
that she has the Phoenix-shaped mark on her.
Great Guardian.
The Young Miss came so suddenly
and refused to tell us anything.
If something goes wrong,
we can't let the Tianxing Secret Treasury fall into trouble.
Indeed.
The seal at the entrance of the Tianxing Secret Treasury
was personally set by our Master.
From what we can see now,
it seems the only way
to know the truth is by activating it.
Only then
will we know who the real Young Miss is.
The Phoenix-masked Woman promised
to take us to the island.
When will she fulfill this promise?
The young mistress has given an order.
Three days from now, Tongming Island will appear.
At that time,
she will take you to the island.
Is that true?
I have the Token as proof.
Young Sect Leader.
Someone has already trespassed into the Myriad Isles Ice Lake to search for the Tianxing Secret Treasury.
As a result, all of their bodies were found floating on the surface of the water.
Greed blinds them.
If the Tianxing Secret Treasury truly contains
so many treasures,
how could they be so easily obtained?
There must be a conspiracy behind this.
Young Sect Leader, you have tried your best to stop them,
but you still couldn't prevent them from rushing to their deaths.
By the way,
is there any news from the Phoenix-masked Woman?
The Phoenix-masked Woman said that in three days,
Tongming Island will appear.
Once this news spread,
everyone is eager
to be the first to reach Tongming Island.
When that time comes,
it might turn into a fierce battle.
I understand.
Zifeng,
tell Young Master Xie
to prepare the peach blossom wine.
I want to invite the Divine Healer for a drink tonight.
Yes.
How could there possibly be two Feng Lixues in this world?
It's precisely because you don't understand.
That's why you're not worthy of being Feng Lixue.
You should have died along with Mo Xiao!
You've been hiding your identity
to stay by the Young Sect Leader's side.
What exactly is it for?
Hiding identity?
What identity?
The daughter of the Tianxing Sect leader,
Feng Lixue.
Why?
They all say I am Feng Lixue.
No, no.
We agreed on ten jars, why are there only five?
Why don't you check it first?
How is it?
Is it the authentic peach blossom wine?
It's authentic,
definitely authentic.
What about the other five jars?
And then
you pour the ten jars
into my wine gourd.
I'm leaving early tomorrow morning
to meet an old friend.
I'm going to drink and play chess with him.
With such good wine,
I'll have to ask him
to let me win a few more pieces this time.
Divine Healer, you cannot leave tomorrow.
What?
Why can't I leave?
The girl you asked me to treat
has been cured.
Once I finish my business, I can leave.
You need to accompany me to meet someone else tomorrow.
Another person?
Who?
I'll take you to meet him tomorrow.
No way.
We agreed to treat one person, and that's it.
How come there's suddenly another person?
I won't see her.
I won't see her no matter what you say.
Lingyun,
the five jars of peach blossom wine...
The five jars of peach blossom wine haven't arrived yet.
I'm worried they might have broken them
when they moved them off the boat.
What?
Broken?
How could you let this happen?
Such fine wine,
found only in heaven.
How could there be any in the mortal world?
You...
You actually broke it?
I'm furious!
Divine Healer, please don't worry.
Those five jars of peach blossom wine should still be on the boat.
If you agree to accompany me to meet that person tomorrow,
I'll make sure they handle the jars carefully
and not spill a drop,
pouring it all into your wine gourd.
Very well.
You...
Never mind.
I
have never been ordered around by anyone in my life.
But when it comes to this fine wine,
I'll bow my head and follow orders.
Master.
What are your orders?
Is there any news about Wu Chen's Master?
No.
Not a single piece of information.
The Dandelion System
has always been able to capture all the past information of the world
without missing anything.
Could it be that the Master mentioned by Miss Wu Chen
doesn't exist at all?
Or perhaps
her Master is not an ordinary mortal.
What about the Phoenix-masked Woman?
The Phoenix-masked Woman seemed to have been taken away by a mysterious person that day,
and finally disappeared at the boundary of Demon Sect's Mount Suyu.
No more information has been traced for now.
Mount Suyu.
It's indeed related to the Demon Sect.
I see.
Continue the investigation.
Yes.
Hopefully we can find the answer tomorrow.
Hey, kid.
Is the person you arranged to meet coming or not?
If she doesn't show up soon, I'll just leave.
Don't worry,
she will definitely come.
Great Guardian.
The Young Miss ordered us to keep an eye on
every move Mo Xiao makes.
But we're not allowed to act.
Why is that?
The Young Miss
must avenge her father's death herself.
Who's that person next to Mo Xiao?
He doesn't seem to be from the Shushan Sect.
The purple-gold gourd.
He is Shi Bujiu.
The Divine Healer Shi Bujiu.
He always carries a purple-gold wine gourd.
That's right, it's him.
Why would Mo Xiao bring Shi Bujiu here?
Is
he also suspecting the Young Miss's identity?
Before you came to Mang Mountain,
who were you?
Wu Chen.
What's wrong with you?
You're practicing so hard.
You've been out so early to practice.
Don't you want to eat breakfast?
I asked the inn
to make your favorite glutinous rice balls.
I'm not hungry.
I'll eat later.
What's been going on with you these past couple of days?
You've seemed so distracted.
If you have something on your mind, tell me.
Jing.
Does your father
love you?
Of course.
My father loves me the most.
Even though he's the Branch Leader of the Fengyu Branch,
and everyone in the sect fears him.
But,
he'll do anything
just to make me happy.
What does it feel like
to be loved by your father?
Let me think.
It feels like
you're not afraid of anything in the world.
Why do you suddenly ask this?
It's nothing.
Wu Chen.
Are you missing your parents?
No.
Since I can remember,
I've always lived in Mang Mountain.
I don't even know who they are.
Don't be sad.
Your parents
might have had some unavoidable reasons
for leaving you alone on Mang Mountain.
In this world,
there are no parents who don't love their children.
Even demons and monsters,
once they have children,
will give everything for them.
Just like Feng Xingtian, the owner of the Tianxing Secret Treasury.
His daughter also suffered from the extreme cold syndrome like you.
To save his daughter,
he gathered treasures from all over the world.
This love for his daughter is quite touching.
Feng Xingtian.
His daughter
is the Phoenix-masked Woman.
Yes.
She wants to open the Tianxing Secret Treasury,
causing all the sects in the martial arts world to scramble for it.
That's why Mo Xiao had to go and stop her.
Mo Xiao has gone to find the Phoenix-masked Woman?
Mo Xiao is worried that you might be in danger again,
so he told me not to tell you.
Don't be upset.
There's plenty of time ahead.
Who masters their martial arts in one go?
Actually,
you don't need to worry too much about your background.
Even though you're not exactly a pleasant person,
we've known each other for a while now,
and I consider us friends.
If you don't have any family,
at least know that you have us.
If you want to stay in the Shushan Sect,
after we resolve the crisis of the Tianxing Secret Treasury,
you can join the Shushan Sect
and become a disciple of the immortal sects.
Doesn't that sound good?
What do you think?
Am I right?
Wu Chen.
Wu Chen!
Running off again.
She's here.
Mo Xiao.
You summoned me with the Phoenix Feather Token.
Are you seeking death?
When you first released the Phoenix Feather Order, you promised that
the one who held the Phoenix Feather Token
could come to Tongming Island.
Now I have the Token in my hands,
yet you say the treasures in the Tianxing Secret Treasury
belong to everyone in the world.
What exactly do you mean?
I'm the one who can open the Tianxing Secret Treasury.
So I make the rules.
You go back on your word.
How can anyone trust you?
Who do I need to convince?
You want to enter the Tianxing Secret Treasury so badly
and brought helpers with you.
I don't want to go to the Tongming Island.
I'm not here to help either.
I'm just a doctor.
Shi Bujiu.
You brought Shi Bujiu here.
Are you doubting my identity?
You know me?
Of course.
If it wasn't
because you saved my life,
you can't cure my extreme cold syndrome.
How would my father have gone to Shushan
to participate in the Snow Peak event?
How would the lives of my father and me
have died there?
It looks like today is the day.
I'll take the lives
of all three of you.
Was Feng Xingtian's quest for the Millennium Token
really for his daughter?
Your father?
You are also Feng Lixue.
Indeed.
Divine Healer, be careful!
Tell me.
What is all this nonsense?
You want to die knowing the truth, don't you?
I'll grant you that wish.
Divine Healer, be careful!
Impossible.
How can this be possible?
How can there be two Feng Lixue?
It's impossible to distinguish between the real and the fake.
It's truly impossible to tell them apart.
How is it possible?
How can there be two Feng Lixue?