(Destiny and Saving)
(Episode 16)
My Lady, but...
ever since you woke up...
you've been preoccupied with worries.
Ten years ago...
Master Feng died after falling from the peak of Snowy Mountain.
As for the reason behind it,
we do not know.
Later,
I inherited my master's lifetime of cultivation...
and went into seclusion for ten years.
During those ten years,
my only wish
was to uncover the truth behind it all.
Young Miss.
No.
I've already taken my great revenge.
I have nothing weighing on my heart now.
Mo Xiao,
are you thirsty?
Shall I get you some water?
Lingyun!
The Love and Desire Valley is very peculiar.
We should be cautious.
Zifeng?
Zifeng!
That's Zifeng, right?
She can't recognize us?
It's not that she doesn't recognize us;
she simply doesn't know us at all.
Zisu?
Look what I brought you.
Mo Xiao.
You bought me white sugar sponge cakes?
Mo... Xiao?
Mo Xiao?
Who is Mo Xiao?
You bought me white sugar sponge cakes.
What's wrong with me?
What happened to me?
Young Sect Leader,
I will definitely complete
the task you've assigned to me today.
I will surely complete it well.
Please trust me.
Young Sect Leader,
I will definitely complete
the task you've assigned to me today.
Please trust me.
What exactly is wrong with your three guardians?
Why do I feel
like they're performing some kind of play?
Or as if they've lost their minds.
They seem to be under some sort of spell
or perhaps afflicted with gu poison.
Where's Jing?
Jing.
Lingyun...
Why are you only getting back now?
I've missed you.
Poisoned... she's been poisoned.
Since when have you become
so important to my sister?
Jing, Jing.
Wake up, Jing.
Jing?
Lingyun.
They don't recognize us at all now.
Don't frighten them.
How did all the people
from Tongming Island end up here?
What's going on with them?
This city in the valley is very strange.
There must be something unusual about it.
That's right.
Let's split up first
and investigate the situation in the city before we decide what to do next.
You really are one of Chongguang's minions.
So, you are the Phoenix-masked Woman.
Chongguang's scheming runs deep.
If I had known this earlier,
I wouldn't have thrown myself in so recklessly.
You say that my master has planned far ahead?
Ten years ago,
he took you, Feng Xingtian's daughter, as his disciple,
and only now has he retrieved the Stone of Insatiability.
Such patience and determination.
I can't help but admire him.
Otherwise, why would he specifically save your life...
and then
use your quest for revenge
to trick you into opening the Tianxing Secret Treasury?
It was only because he knew all along
that the Stone of Insatiability
was in your father's, Feng Xingtian's, hands.
Where is this stone now?
It's in the secret chamber of the Ancestral Hall,
where only the Star Lords of each palace can enter.
But since you're about to become the Star Lord of Shaohao,
it shouldn't be a problem for you to enter, right?
The Heavenly Demon Token has turned into Demon Stones.
Only someone with Yeyuan's bloodline can activate it.
How did Chongguang manage to do that?
Mother.
Are you suspecting...
Could it be that back then,
the child I gave birth to...
was harmed by him?
Yunchao,
investigate this matter secretly right away.
If it was really him
who harmed my child,
I will never let him off.
Yes.
It's my father's phoenix-shaped mark.
Guards!
Someone has broken into the secret chamber!
Hurry!
This way.
Put it back now.
Who are you really?
Why did you save me?
My name is Xuyuan Yunchao.
I saved you...
only because I didn't want you to fall into someone's trap.
You can control water.
You're from the Nüwa Clan.
So, you knew early on that someone wanted to scheme against me?
After being on Mount Suyu for so long,
people no longer bother hiding their true thoughts.
Everything is written plainly on their faces.
Hard not to notice.
So naturally, I can know a thing or two.
But sometimes,
knowing too much isn't a good thing either.
Like saving you today?
Of course.
This matter, for you,
is undoubtedly a trouble.
As for me,
I've never liked causing trouble for others.
If anything happens to you in the future,
remember to come to me for help.
Where are you going?
Find a quiet place to hide for a while.
Then, how can I find you if I'm in trouble?
Three days later,
I'll become the Star Lord of Shaohao here.
If our deductions are correct,
everyone in the City of Love and Desire has been poisoned with gu poison
and has lost their sanity.
Let's split up to find the source of the gu poison.
Why is there my father's mark
on that Stone of Insatiability?
Why has Master never mentioned to me
that my father had dealings with the Demon Sect?
Could everything that Mo Xiao said be true?
That I wrongly killed him?
Mo Xiao.
You're actually alive?
Feng Lixue...
How...
have you been?
You shouldn't have come here.
I came to find you.
To find me?
To kill me?
You're being used.
Just like everyone else in this city.
They're all controlled by some mysterious demonic power.
Perhaps the one who brought you back to life
might be tied to this power.
Lixue, tell me who he is.
Who is he?
I will find out
the truth myself.
But if you lie to me,
I will still kill you.
You've been standing outside for so long.
Why don't you come in?
Master.
You need something from me?
Nothing.
Just wanted to check in on you.
Are you comfortable living in the Shaohao Palace?
What?
You don't like it?
It's not that.
Master, whatever you ask me to do,
I will do it.
I picked up on it.
Something's on your mind.
Master.
I want to ask that...
now that we have retrieved the Sacred Stone,
what else do I need to do?
Be the Star Lord of the Shaohao Palace.
That's it?
That's it.
Whatever you wish me to do, Master,
I've had only one purpose for the past ten years:
to avenge my father.
I know.
And didn't I help you fulfill your wish?
But Mo Xiao is still alive.
You... have seen him?
Master, you've long known he's in the Love and Desire Valley, right?
You want to kill him
in the Love and Desire Valley?
Then, Master...
do you want me to kill him
or not kill him?
You know it.
That man
is still of use to me.
You can't kill him for now.
But I promise you,
in the future,
you will get your chance.
I'll wait for the chance you promised.
Supreme Lord,
Feng Lixue
is being far too arrogant and self-important about her achievements.
What she can do,
I can do as well.
Remember,
in this world,
there is only one person
who can lecture Feng Lixue,
and that person is me!
Now go,
deliver the ceremonial robes to the Star Lord of Shaohao.
Yes, Supreme Lord.
(Changhuan Palace)
Changhuan Palace?
That's right.
We guessed this should be where the city lord resides.
But there's a barrier at the entrance.
Neither Murong Ce nor I could open it.
We've already figured out
most of the situation in the city.
We likely entered the valley through the underground stream
beneath the city's waterfall.
The others who disappeared on Tongming Island
also entered the valley from that place.
But there's another exit in the west of the city.
There's another exit?
Yes.
It's the city gate.
However,
there's also a barrier.
Lingyun and I can still pass through it,
but the others in the valley can't get out at all.
We suspect
that this has something to do
with the demonic poison in their bodies.
This city appears very prosperous on the surface,
but beyond the barrier,
it's nothing but dense fog.
You can't see anything clearly.
Could this place be another demonic cave
hidden in the world?
You seem to dislike me very much.
That's right.
I don't like you.
If I remember correctly,
you used to be with the Dark Soul Palace
before switching loyalties to Master.
Shouldn't you be more... cautious with your words and actions?
Why are you becoming more and more unruly?
Life is unpredictable.
I've admired the Supreme Lord's grace and elegance for a long time.
Being able to serve under him,
I will give everything to serve him loyally.
And you?
Even your life was saved by him.
But ask yourself this—
is your devotion to him deeper than mine?
I can do anything for him,
yet you can't.
Then, I want to ask you,
why should I compare myself to you?
What?
You think
I'm not even worth comparing to?
Don't be so full of yourself.
You're nothing but a pawn of the Supreme Lord.
He's just using you to gather the three Sacred Stones.
Once his grand plan is complete,
you'll be discarded like the rest.
Three Sacred Stones?
The Supreme Lord favors you so much,
yet he hasn't told you about the plan for the three Sacred Stones?
He was originally the Demon Lord of Love and Desire.
He already possesses the Sacred Stone of Love and Desire.
This time, on Tongming Island,
you helped him retrieve the Stone of Insatiability.
If he gets the third one...
What happens if he finds
the third one?
The Supreme Lord's goal is to seize the Millennium Token
and overthrow the three realms.
Whether you're Wu Chen
or the Phoenix-masked Woman,
you're nothing more than pawns in someone else's game.
They exploited your hatred.
Don't be driven by karmic obstacles manipulated by others anymore.
Perhaps the one who brought you back to life
might be tied to this power.
In other words,
the Stone of Love and Desire in the Love and Desire Valley
can turn people into demons?
That's right.
Those people in Love and Desire Valley
have already been poisoned by Love and Desire Poison.
In seven days,
they will lose their sanity
and become the Supreme Lord's servants.
Why are you telling me all this?
Because I know
you're not absolutely loyal to the Supreme Lord.
And I want to prove to him
who is truly loyal.
(Changhuan Palace)
Those at the back, keep up.
Come here.
Next one, next one.
Hurry up, hurry up.
Those at the back, keep up.
Take them away.
Stop.
What's with these three?
They've only been here for three days, and you're sending them
to the Spirit Offering Pool already?
This one is affected a bit deeper.
When we first brought him back from Tongming Island,
he was already partially demonized.
These two younger ones are less affected.
They are from the immortal sects.
It's better to send them to the pool to offer their spirits sooner.
I'd feel more at ease.
I can't help but feel that something might go wrong.
No, no, that won't do.
This Spirit Offering Pool
has always required seven full days of demonization
before one can enter and offer their spirit to the Sacred Stone.
Take them back, take them back.
Senior Lu.
Senior Lu?
Senior Lu, wake up.
I'm here to get you out of here.
There's something wrong with this water.
Where is this heavy fog coming from?
Zimu?
Zimu.
Zimu!
Jing?
Jing.
Xie Lingyun, you...
Her condition is getting worse.
I'll seal her heart meridian first.
You hurry and go check on the others.
Jing,
hold on a little longer.
I'll definitely find a way to save you.
Zisu.
Zisu?
Are you alright?
Mo Xiao.
No.
Zifeng?
Senior Murong.
You're back.
Mo Xiao.
The fog here is poisonous.
Hurry up and put this on.
It's okay.
The source of the poison should be the river water.
We haven't drunk any water,
so we won't be affected by the poison
in the fog for now.
That's right.
There's something wrong with both the water and the poisonous fog.
Today, I followed that water truck
to investigate.
The river we entered this place through earlier
is called the Liruo River.
That's
where the poison originates.
After being catalyzed by this poisonous fog,
one's consciousness will gradually fade away.
No wonder Jing's symptoms
have worsened today.
The poison they've been infected with is Love and Desire Poison.
Love and Desire Poison?
What else did you discover?
I also found Senior Lu and the others.
Where are they?
They're in the Changhuan Palace.
The Changhuan Palace should be the city lord's residence.
He controls the entire Love and Desire Valley.
Senior Lu
has already lost his sanity now.
Senior Lu has been poisoned too?
It seems the poison has affected him even more seriously.
How is he now?
He's been imprisoned.
They say it only takes seven days from being infected with the poison
to completely transforming into a demon.
After seven days,
they'll be sent to offer their spirits.
Do you know how many days they've been here?
Four days.
What should we do now?
Starting from today,
don't let them drink water or eat anything.
Make sure they all wear veils
to prevent the poisonous fog from seeping in
and causing them to be poisoned even more severely.
Senior Lu is trapped in the Changhuan Palace
and has lost his sanity.
Jing and the Three Guardians are in the same condition.
We must figure out a way
to cure this poison, and fast.
That day at the Tianxing Secret Treasury,
there was a sudden, earth-shattering change.
I originally thought...
they had perished on Tongming Island.
Fortunately, we've found them now,
but I didn't expect...
they would be living in such a state.
Wait.
What did you just say?
The Tianxing Secret Treasury?
Yeah.
I know it now.
It's that demon stone.
Take good care of them.
What demon stone?
Mo Xiao!
You want to destroy the Stone of Love and Desire?
Looks like I guessed right.
All these strange things in the city
are indeed connected to this demon stone.
So, you think that destroying the Stone of Love and Desire
will save your fellow disciples?
What else could happen?
If it were that simple,
why would this Stone of Love and Desire
be left hanging out in the open without any protection?
What do you mean?
Everyone in this Love and Desire Valley
has all been infected with Love and Desire Poison.
They've lost their minds,
yet they rely on the demonic power of the stone to sustain their lives.
If you were to destroy the stone,
you'd cut off their source of life.
And they...
would die immediately.
I see.
No wonder the city lord has placed this demon stone
in such a conspicuous position.
He's certain that I wouldn't dare to destroy it.
Perhaps whether you destroy it or not
is all within his calculations.
Lixue.
Even now, you still won't tell me
who took you away back then?
Mo Xiao.
With your intelligence,
can't you figure it out?
Could it be the person who took you away on Tongming Island?
Your master?
That's right.
He is the lord of this city
and also the Demon Lord here,
Chongguang.
What?
Demon Lord Chongguang?
So...
your master is actually the Demon Lord?
Back then, for the sake of revenge,
I became his disciple.
Lixue, don't worry.
One day,
I will definitely uncover Chongguang's conspiracy.
When he brought you back to life at that time,
it must have had something to do with this demon stone.
Once I uncover the truth,
I will definitely clear your name
and that of
the Tianxing Sect.
By then, the Shushan Sect will no longer blame you.
And you can then be Feng Lixue again,
openly and proudly.
You and I are already on different paths—immortal and demon.
Please don't indulge in wishful thinking.
Tomorrow,
I will become the Star Lord of Shaohao here.
You'd...
better find a way to save your fellow disciples.
You are not a demoness. You're different from them.
You have kindness in your heart.
Listen to me.
Let me take you away from all of this.
I beg you.
Mo Xiao!
Listen carefully.
If the truth is not as you say,
I will still...
take your life.
Father,
the current situation
is roughly like this.
It's just that Jing's and the others' conditions...
Young Sect Leader.
-Young Sect Leader.
Mo Xiao.
Master Xuan Zhen,
what brings you here?
I sent a message back to the Shushan Sect,
informing them about the underground river passage leading into the valley.
The Sect Leader learned that you had entered the valley
and was very worried.
He was concerned that your young generation
doesn't know much about the Heavenly Demon Sect
and worried that you might stumble into trouble,
not only failing to rescue anyone
but also getting yourselves hurt.
So...
he sent me
to lend you a hand.
Master also knows about it too?
Three Demon Stones?
Master Xuan Zhen, you mean
that opening the Tianxing Secret Treasury on Tongming Island
was part of Demon Lord Chongguang's scheme
to find the Heavenly Demon Clan's three Demon Stones.
That's right.
Back then, Demon Lord Yeyuan
of the Heavenly Demon Sect
invaded Mount Buzhou
in order to seize the Millennium Token.
But...
he was utterly defeated by Sword Sovereign Fengyue.
At that time, the Heavenly Demon Token was shattered into three pieces,
turning into
the Stone of Love and Desire,
the Stone of Insatiability,
and the Stone of Asura.
If now
someone could gather those three Demon Stones,
they could restore the Heavenly Demon Token
and command 100,000 demon soldiers from the Demon Realm.
If that's the case,
Chongguang already has two of them.
The Demon Stone of Love and Desire
fell into his hands
after the battle at Mount Buzhou.
As for the Demon Stone of Insatiability,
it was in the possession of the Tianxing Sect Master, Feng Xingtian.
Now,
Feng Lixue has opened the Tianxing Secret Treasury.
It must be Chongguang plotting behind the scenes.
If Chongguang finds the third Demon Stone,
wouldn't he be like Yeyuan from back then,
leading a demon army of 100,000 to seize the Millennium Token?
That's right.
This Love and Desire Valley
is where Chongguang nurtures the Demon Stone of Love and Desire.
Those he captured on Tongming Island
have been secretly transported here via the underground river.
Those with extreme greed
will be sent directly to offer their spirits.
Now, all Chongguang needs to do
is wait patiently for the appearance of the third Demon Stone.
This is exactly what the Sect Leader is worried about.
The Sect Leader has ordered.
Demon Lord Chongguang has been plotting for a long time
to seize the three Demon Stones.
He must be seeking to once again invade Mount Buzhou
to seize the Millennium Token.
Now,
we not only need to rescue our fellow righteous cultivators in the city
but also prevent Chongguang
from activating the three Demon Stones.
-Understood.
Are you alright, Junior?
I'm fine.
Let's continue drinking.
Let's go.
So, you guys
couldn't find a way to break the Love and Desire Poison?
Since it's caused by the Demon Lord's Demon Stone,
why don't we just go and destroy it?
We can't.
Those who are poisoned are falling deeper into it.
If we rashly break the Demon Stone,
they might die.
Master Xuan Zhen,
every night in this Love and Desire Valley,
the stone releases a large amount of poisonous mist,
confusing people's minds.
How about this:
You and the fellow disciples
temporarily leave the valley
and set up camp outside,
waiting for Master Xie to arrive.
We'll stay behind to take care of Junior Jing
and look for a way to cure the poison.
Can't we just take them all out of the city now?
The underground river passage that Murong Ce led you through
only works in one direction.
The valley has its unique city gate barrier,
connected to Mount Suyu.
We've already tried.
Only those who haven't been demonized can pass through it.
That's why those poisoned in the city
remain addicted and unable to escape.
Uncle Master,
to avoid any complications,
let Lingyun escort you out of the city first.
Alright.
Then we'll leave the city first
and wait for your news.
However...
I'll leave Jing
in your care.
And where's that little girl from the Penglai Sect
gone off to?
Junior Yue Yao should have gone to find Senior Hao Tian.
Don't worry, Master Xuan Zhen.
I'll go find her.
Okay.
Hold on.
Supreme Lord,
our Heavenly Demon Sect has a rule
that those who trespass into the forbidden area of the Ancestral Hall
will be thrown into the Demon Prison.
Before Feng Lixue officially assumed the title of Star Lord of Shaohao,
she trespassed into the Ancestral Hall,
offending the divine authority of the Heavenly Demon Sect.
In light of this,
can she still be our sect's Star Lord?
Looks like...
you need to explain this to everyone.
I did indeed enter the secret chamber of the Ancestral Hall,
-but...
-I brought Star Lord Lixue inside.
Star Envoy Xuyuan has never been fond of speaking in public.
Today, however, you've surprised me.
Let him continue.
That day,
Miss Lixue heard from Star Lord Ji
that the Sacred Stone she had retrieved from the Tianxing Secret Treasury
was kept in the secret chamber of the Ancestral Hall.
Out of curiosity, she wanted to take a look,
but I stopped her at the entrance to the secret chamber.
I told her
that only the Star Lords of each palace
and the Star Envoy of the Ancestral Hall
could enter.
Fortunately,
I am the Star Envoy responsible for
the sacred scriptures and records in the Ancestral Hall.
Considering that she had already
been publicly appointed as the Star Lord of Shaohao by you, Supreme Lord,
I took her inside.
Xuyuan Yunchao,
do you know what you're saying?
Xuyuan Yunchao.
You should know
that bringing someone into the forbidden area of the Ancestral Hall
without permission is also punishable.
I
am willing to accept the punishment.
If that's the case,
the one who violated the rules of the Heavenly Demon Sect
is Star Envoy Xuyuan.
Master,
Star Envoy Xuyuan has nothing to do with this matter.
Star Lord Ji.
What do you think?
I leave it to your judgment, Supreme Lord.
Xuyuan Yunchao.
You knowingly violated the rules.
I hereby sentence you
to the Demon Prison.
Star Lord of Shaohao.
It's been clarified.
You were misled.
After all,
those who don't know are not at fault.
I remember
there's a rule in the Heavenly Demon Sect
that any newly appointed Star Lord
must visit the forbidden area of the Ancestral Hall to pay their respects
and commune with the star stone.
Then, let's say...
our Star Lord of Shaohao has completed this ritual in advance.
Star Lord Ji,
Star Lord Xuyuan,
Elder Minghuang,
are you
satisfied with my decision?
Star Envoy Xuyuan,
your mother has already left.
Why are you still kneeling here?
Hurry up and go to the Demon Prison to receive your punishment.
Yes, Supreme Lord.
You may leave too.
As expected of my Star Lord of Shaohao.
On the first day of taking office,
someone is already willing to step up for you.
I remember that this kid
rarely speaks up in situations like this.
Star Envoy Xuyuan is upright and straightforward.
It's your fortune, Master.
If you have nothing else, Master,
I'll take my leave.
Supreme Lord,
why did Xuyuan Yunchao
suddenly defend Miss Lixue today?
Could it be Xuyuan Wushuang?
No.
It's that boy
who has fallen for...
Star Lord of Shaohao.