Guess we’ll have to
pretend to date for now.
Then make him believe you're with a girl.
Why would she go that far?
Khun Ai planned it
so she’d be alone with you.
You don’t see through her games.
You don’t have to worry
about me all the time.
Does your dad even know
you came to see me?
Does he know you like girls?
You’ll find out I’ve got way
more tricks up my sleeve.
What are you doing?
Black Manhattan.
It’s for a classy girl...
sweet with a tangy twist...
but also mysterious.
Intriguing.
Me? Mysterious?
I’m pretty much an open book.
Not open enough.
I mean your heart.
Maybe someone just needs
to open it for you.
You.
Neither of us got what we wanted today.
Next time, then.
Let’s give it another shot.
Maple.
Yes, P'G.
Sorry for calling so early.
There’s an urgent doc you need to sign.
Will you come sign it at the office
or should I bring it to your place?
Um... I’ll head to the office.
Something urgent?
Yeah.
That’s a shame.
Last night we barely got started...
and you passed out
before anything happened.
Guess that Black Manhattan I made...
was a little too strong.
You’re really wearing that to the office?
Isn’t it a bit too sexy?
You can wear my clothes instead.
Borrow them or keep them,
I don’t mind.
Seriously.
Are you being nice to me...
or are you setting me
up to owe you again?
You can’t say “again.”
Because the last time I owed you...
you already got your payback.
With that kiss in the car.
Let’s just say I didn’t help you this time.
Call it a kind gesture instead.
A kind gesture worth tens
or hundreds of thousands?
Isn’t that a bit much
for someone you just met?
We just met, sure.
But you’re special.
No matter how much,
I’d still give it.
I’d rather not.
I’ll return it to you myself.
Since we’re going to see
each other again anyway.
I haven’t even gotten
the answer I want yet.
So, where’s the outfit?
Go take a shower and relax first.
Blow-dried like this...
Do you like it?
If you do, I can do it for you every day.
I really can.
And if you want to know if I mean it...
you’d have to move in with me.
Are you crazy?
Are you blushing?
Why would I blush?
They say women...
often say the opposite of what they feel.
I know...
right now you’re thinking about...
what it would really be like living with me.
Am I right?
Okay, I’ll stop teasing you.
You know what?
Normally, a workaholic like me...
wouldn’t waste time like this.
I even get my hair washed at the salon.
So you’re saying...
everything you said and did for me...
was because I’m that special to you?
Something like that.
You're quite the smooth talker.
So...
is the customer starting
to get interested yet?
No idea.
But I do know it’s time
for me to head to the office.
All done.
Hold on.
Your hair’s perfect.
Now your skin needs that dewy glow.
All done.
Thanks.
Someone told me...
you brought a girl into your room.
Who is she?
One of Dad’s spies, huh?
Who is it this time?
Which bodyguard?
Why is it that everyone around me...
is someone I can’t even trust?
Well, if you didn’t do anything...
then no one would
need to report back to me.
So?
Who did you bring here?
A friend.
A friend?
Which friend?
Do I know them?
How much can they be trusted?
You trusted them enough
to bring them here?
Why aren’t you answering?
It’s just a simple question.
No need for you to come
all the way here, Dad.
A phone call would’ve been enough.
I had to see it for myself.
So I know exactly...
what you’re really up to.
I wouldn’t do anything
to cause you trouble.
You don’t have to worry.
Worry about you?
I’m not worried about you.
I’m worried about the company.
About our reputation.
About my image...
that I’ve built my whole life.
This is my personal life.
Don’t you dare say that to me.
It reminds me of your mother.
You said you wouldn’t bring her up.
So why did you?
Then stop acting like her.
If you didn’t, I wouldn’t have.
Mark my words, Aiwarin.
I’ve already been let down
by your mother once.
Don’t make me disappointed in you too.
I don’t care that much...
about the filthy woman
you dragged into your bed.
But if one day...
news breaks out
that the heir of Orienna...
is acting out and being reckless...
I’ll cut you off for good.
Watch me.
Stay here for now.
Wait till he leaves.
Then you can go.
Okay.
Please prepare three sets of
the documents and cc the Chairman.
Khun Mae.
Go to your office right now.
What’s going on, P’G?
Don’t ask right now. Just go.
Okay.
Get me outfits like the ones
Maeveeka usually wears, ASAP.
Right now!
What’s this all about, P’G?
You told me not to worry.
So I tried not to worry.
But now you’ve gone and messed up.
The outfit you’re wearing is
from Andromeda’s new collection.
That collection hasn’t been released yet.
The only one who’s supposed
to have it right now...
is the brand ambassador, Aiwarin.
And she already wore
that outfit in a press interview.
Have you even thought
about what would happen...
if someone sees you in it
and posts it online?
I’m sorry, P'G.
Please be more careful next time.
Can you do that?
I won’t make the same mistake again.
I’ll end this as soon as I can.
Can I ask you one thing?
If you’re going to see her again...
let me come with you.
I’ll keep my distance.
Just in case something happens,
I’ll be there.
Someone told me...
you brought a girl into your room.
Who is she?
This is my personal life.
Don’t you dare say that to me.
It reminds me of your mother.
You said you wouldn’t bring her up.
Then stop acting like her.
If you didn’t, I wouldn’t have said it.
I’m sorry, Ai.
I really am.
But I have to go now.
Be a good girl, okay?
Yam, call an urgent team meeting.
I’ve read the
marketing analysis you sent over.
I think we need to talk.
Weren’t you taking today off?
I changed my mind.
Sitting around drives me crazy. I hate it.
Mae, may I come in?
I heard you went to a friend’s
party last night. Did you have fun?
It was nice, Dad.
I just want to remind you...
try to cut back on the partying for now.
Or better yet, put it on hold entirely.
At least until the bidding period is over.
I don’t want people saying...
you’re not serious about this competition.
Mae...
You haven’t forgotten, have you?
There are people waiting
to see us fall over this.
If we lose...
I haven’t forgotten, Dad.
I’ll do what you said.
Good.
Hearing that puts my mind at ease.
Now go get some rest.
Wait, Dad...
Would you feel terrible...
if,
What if I fail this project?
Failure isn’t even an option.
Because I believe in you.
You’ll succeed no matter what.
And I’m not the only one...
waiting to be proud of you.
Your mom’s waiting to see it too.
I’m sure of it.
Mae...
Before your mom passed away...
she entrusted you to me.
We both loved you...
and had the highest hopes for you.
And we both believe...
that you can do it.
Is this Maevika’s car?
She’s already gone. We should be
the first to get the bid envelope.
Take the stairs.
Who?
You.
I’m coming too.
Me too.
- Khun Maevika, may we have a quick interview?
- Hello.
How confident are you about this bidding?
100% confident.
Orienna seems pretty confident too.
Aren’t you feeling the pressure?
Today, it all comes down to the bidding.
Hurry! Maevika’s still giving an interview.
We still have a shot.
The representative from
Superior is the first to arrive.
Why aren’t you going in?
The first company to get the bid envelope...
gets a head start.
What kind of advantage?
Beats me.
But many companies believe in good omens.
They want to kick things off
on a winning note...
by being the very first to purchase
the bidding documents.
Maybe it’s so they can study
the TOR ahead of the others.
Just a few minutes earlier…
probably doesn’t make much difference.
Besides, making the first move...
doesn’t guarantee a win.
Orienna, feel free to go ahead.
I’m in no rush.
- Khun Maevika, over here.
- Please look toward this camera.
This camera too, please.
Good day, sir.
I really admire Superior...
for choosing someone young like you
to lead the bidding.
It doesn’t just add
excitement to the event,
but also pushes many companies
to reflect on themselves.
See what’s still stuck in the past.
It’s really nice to hear you say that.
Before this,
people kept doubting me,
saying I might be
the reason Superior loses.
I doubt they really meant it.
They were probably just trying
to mess with your head.
Don’t let it get to you.
Just focus on doing your part well.
Your work will speak
for itself soon enough.
Thank you.
Come on.
Let’s take a photo.
- Look this way.
- Over here, please.
Right this way.
Over here too, please.
And this camera, please.
Looking good.
Khun Rachen.
Good evening, Khun Maevika.
Khun Rachen, you're ignoring me.
Aren’t you stepping out of line a bit?
Sorry about that, it’s just that,
I noticed Direk
is heading the project,
so he’ll probably get
more time with the bidders.
But I’m just one of the small competitors.
It’s rare we get to meet.
So...
Please give me a chance.
Hello.
Khun Rachen.
Vice Chairman of Great & Glow Company,
a major importer of
consumer goods in Thailand.
Khun Mae, you seem
to know me quite well.
Well, there’s no one in the country
who doesn’t know you.
I know you like everybody else does.
In that case...
I hope it won’t be long
before we get to really know each other.
Come on, let’s take a picture.
This way, please.
Over here.
Nice.
- This camera too, please.
- Lovely. Beautiful.
- Yam.
- Yes?
Take the documents to the company first.
In case Dad asks.
I’ve got a headache.
I want to rest a bit.
I’ll catch up once I feel better.
Understood.
I'm taking the dress back to her car.
You don’t have to come, G.
Just wait here.
I'll call you once I’m done.
But,
It's just returning a dress. No big deal.
Hello, Khun Aiwarin.
Long time no see.
Yes.
Why wait till now to say hi?
You acted like
we didn’t know each other
back in the bidding room.
Or were you scared they'd find out
what you did to me?
If you’re trying to say
I did something,
you’ll need proof.
If you don’t have any,
then it never happened.
And I’ve got nothing to be afraid of.
The reason I didn’t greet you
is because someone else
caught my eye more.
That’s all.
If you plan to approach Maevika
the same way you once did with me,
then forget it.
Because that girl isn’t so easy to fool.
You sound like you know her well.
I don’t owe you an answer.
And I don’t have to listen to you.
You're hooked, aren’t you?
Sneaking around like this.
It’s kind of thrilling, huh?
I saw you talking to Rachen just now.
You two knew each other before?
And... back in the bidding room,
you seemed pretty close to Rachen.
Not just him, there's also Direk.
You’ve got quite the charm, don’t you?
Don’t change the subject.
I heard you two mention my name.
Well...
It’s nothing, really.
Just be careful with that guy.
As a rival...
and as a man.
Because he’s not like the others you’ve met.
Trust me.
I won’t, unless I know the reason why.
Fine, then.
My spare keycard to Orienna,
You can use it to get into my room.
And it’ll also give you
access to all VIP zones.
Meet me tonight at the floating pool.
We’ll talk about this then.
Mae.
Oh, G.
I was just about to call you.
Is something up?
You still haven’t returned the dress.
Let’s put that on hold for now.
There’s something more important.
We’re going to Orienna tonight.
Once we’re there, we’ll split up.
I’ll take the VIP entrance.
You go in through
the regular guest route, G.
Okay.
Wait, Mae.
This is a listening device.
It’s how we’ll dig secrets out of her.
Wanna come for a swim?
Maple.
I’m here about Rachen.
Aiwarin.
Just call me Ai. I prefer that.
It feels more like me.
It's about Rachen.
Alright then.
Rachen and I
met last year.
It was during the joint project
between Orienna and Great & Glow.
We were both invited to Boston for it.
Mr. Barry’s project was so exhausting.
We were lucky that
Great & Glow and Orienna
were the two Thai companies chosen
to manage the space together.
But I’ll be honest with you.
I’m not really a fan of working with others.
What are you trying to say?
I want Great & Glow to have full
control over the commercial area.
If you agree to withdraw from the project,
I'll compensate you
as much as you want.
Are you trying to bribe me?
Not at all.
Just making an offer.
I figured someone as smart as you, Aiwarin,
wouldn’t say no.
You're right.
I am smart enough to know better.
After that,
I was attacked two or three more times.
And every time...
It always happened when I was alone.
Luckily, I got out every time.
When I came back to Thailand,
everything just... stopped.
Then why didn’t you go to the police?
I had no evidence.
They didn’t leave a single trace.
That’s why I’m telling you,
you have to be careful.
We never know what
Rachen might do next.
I care about you.
But if you stay close to me,
I’ll keep you safe.
So...
are your doubts about Rachen gone now?
If so...
let’s figure out your answer next.
You still don’t have one, do you?
Yes.
Okay. I’m coming down now.
Can you check the
guest’s room number for me?
Please check this room number.
We’ll bring them a new keycard.
Did you see the woman when it dropped it?
He’s not sure.
Wait, hold on a second.
Is something going on?
I’ll come back and tell you, Yam.
I gotta run.
Hey! No, you can’t!
You have to tell me now!
So, What happened?
Spill everything.
Thanks for helping me out just now.
You saw that, huh?
And I’m sorry too.
About that day in the restroom,
I hurt you. I didn’t mean to.
So mysterious.
So intriguing.
Let’s stop here.
I think I have my answer.
Are you sure...
about the answer
you think you’ve found?
If so...
how about the two of us...
give this a try?
You’re the first person
who’s made me feel like
I want to take it seriously.
You,
But we’re rivals, remember?
-And then there’s that whole thing.
-I know.
I haven’t forgotten.
But do you remember
what I once told you?
If I wanted to follow my heart,
then I wouldn’t care
what happens after this.
I want to focus
on what’s right in front of me.
Okay.
I’ll be with you.
But...
you can’t let anyone know about this.
If you’re cool with that,
then I’m cool with it too.
Deal.
Ready to have fun with Khun Ai?
Let’s go!
Today was such a blast.
Khun Ai’s so glad to be dating Mae.
If Mae can bring
Andromeda onto our project,
when Khun Ai’s already
the brand ambassador,
it’d be like Superior
slapping Orienna in the face.
You,
Feeling smug now
that you’ve got the upper hand?
Come stand in the middle.
(Yam wanna be in it too!)
You little rascal.
I haven’t even clicked yet.
(Then strike a pose already.)
Oh, really?
(He’s being closely looked after.)
Feeling refreshed now?
Perfect.
(Let me try a sip too.)
(They’re getting ready for the next scene.)
(Teasing because it’s love.)
(That gaze is way too sweet.)