[English subtitles are available]
[The Girl Who Sees Smells]
[Episode 10]
[Taste Time Annda Group New Red Wine Event]
Thank you again for coming!
There is another important topic
in the event.
As we all know,
Burgundy in France
is one of the world's top ten places of production of red wine.
Next, let's warmly welcome
Mr. Phillip,
the spokesperson of Kaysersberg, the famous chateau of Burgundy,
to give us a speech.
Mr. Phillip,
your master class is full again this time.
Can you tell us whether you have a plan
to start a business in China?
The domestic market is getting better.
I'm willing to devote what I've learned
into the domestic market,
and I'll find more talents.
And Miss Lu Fenfen by my side
is the red wine genius I found here.
She will join me in the R&D of new red wine.
This is breaking news!
May I ask
what's your relationship
with Miss Lu Fenfen?
You're quite curious.
I'll keep it a secret.
[Anda Hotel]
Tianran?
Why don't you wear the flat shoes I gave you?
Why do you wear these high-heeled shoes?
Phillip gave them to me.
I'm wearing them because of work.
Look how swollen your feet are.
I'm fine.
It'll be bad if we're seen.
I'm really fine.
Let's go back.
Let's go home.
Okay.
Elder Brother!
You've changed?
You treat others better than your family now.
You've been back for so long.
But you haven't gone back home once.
You don't deserve to say the word family.
What did he just call you?
Elder Brother?
Elder Brother, about our relationship,
haven't you told Miss Lu?
You two are brothers?
You look younger than him.
Why did he call you elder brother?
You don't care about your family at all!
And about Lu Fenfen,
I hope you can remember her identity!
What identity?
I don't know.
Tell me.
She is my girlfriend
and your sister-in-law!
Tianran, don't act on impulse.
Elder Brother, I remember she's Xu Tianran's girlfriend.
And I'm Xu Tianran!
Brother Mingchen, am I?
He is Xu Tianran?
Who are you then?
He is Xu Mingchen.
He's the CEO of Xu's Group.
My biological elder brother.
Wait.
So, who is dating me?
It's Xu Tianran.
But he's the fake one.
He approached you using my identity.
Is it true?
Fenfen.
I can explain it to you.
People who lie
will cover up what he lied before
with another lie.
Trust me.
Fenfen, nice to meet you.
I'm Xu Qingran, the eldest sister of the Xu family.
Nice to meet you too, Sister.
Did you tell her?
You still play favorites.
Why can't I say what Xu Mingchen did?
Are you done?
Fenfen.
If I were your boyfriend,
I would never lie to you.
Just
ignore them.
Xu Tianran, what are you doing?
Xu Qingran, listen.
Things won't go as you wish.
And don't call me that name again.
Xu Tianran doesn't exist in the world.
But Phillip does.
I don't understand
why he hid his identity.
What do you think?
It's easy to toy with your feelings.
But,
why did he approach me?
I'm such an ordinary person.
You're not ordinary at all.
In my heart,
you are the most special.
I'm serious.
If you want to leave here,
I'll take you away immediately.
We will never come back.
Are you kidding me?
Your master class has just opened.
You still have so many...
I told you.
As long as you want,
nothing else matters.
Thank you.
But I still want to ask him about it.
Since I was little,
Xu Mingchen has always been one step ahead of me,
in terms of everything.
[Let bygones be bygones]
After my parents passed away,
he is the woman's favorite.
He got everything he wanted.
But I don't believe it.
I don't believe he can always win.
Can you give me a chance?
Don't worry.
I won't force you.
But I hope you can promise me
that you'll protect yourself
and stay away from the siblings.
They are not good people.
Why?
Did you go far away when you were 17
because of them?
What happened to your family?
Promise me.
Stay away from them, as far as possible.
You will get hurt.
Fenfen.
Fenfen, listen to me.
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
What were you doing earlier?
All this time, you've been lying to me.
I was fooled by you.
I've been dating you for so long,
but I don't even know who my boyfriend is.
Do you really think I'm an idiot?
No.
Fenfen, don't you know?
Mingchen is not feeling well.
He didn't mean to hide it from you.
You two can sit down and talk.
Fenfen.
Xu Mingchen is under great pressure
in his position.
When we first met you,
we were very grateful that you saved Xu Mingchen.
But later, we were indeed afraid
it could be bad for the company,
if the word that the CEO of the Anda Group
is not feeling well gets out.
So we deliberately
hid his real identity from you.
Fenfen.
I think what they said
makes sense.
Although it's wrong for Xu Mingchen to lie,
as the boss of a big company,
he must consider the interests
of the staff and the company.
Each of us has different positions,
which leads to different perspectives.
So, do you also think
I shouldn't blame him?
No.
Fenfen.
It's all my fault.
I shouldn't have lied to you.
Please forgive me.
But there's one thing I don't understand.
Xu Tianran is Phillip.
He's your younger brother.
But why do you look younger than him?
Because I'm ill.
What kind of illness it is? Is it serious?
He's sick with a very rare disease.
It's a long story.
Simply put,
it's a special kind of genetic inheritance.
He would look younger than his real age,
and would be younger and younger every year.
What will happen next?
It may...
It's nothing.
He just looks much younger.
Gosh!
That would be great.
[Anda Hotel]
You look quite handsome today.
This week's work plan is the same as last week's.
There's just a small adjustment.
Lu Fenfen is no longer in charge
of the godown entry of the lounge.
She only takes charge of management affairs of the lounge.
If anything happens,
you have to ask Lu Fenfen for instructions.
Understand?
Yes.
Fenfen.
It's my pleasure to work with you.
I'm in charge of the management affairs?
What's going on?
Okay.
The meeting is over.
Qiao Anna is quitting her job?
Yes.
That's true.
But there's nothing she can do.
Fenfen.
I didn't take good care of you
when you took office.
I didn't know at that time.
Please forgive me.
Don't take it to heart.
What do you know?
David. Fenfen is not like that.
Otherwise, with her identity,
she wouldn't have eaten in the canteen with us.
But Fenfen,
you shouldn't eat in the canteen with us anymore.
After all, you're the boss's girlfriend.
They are watching you.
Let's go.
CEO, I have something to tell you.
What's wrong?
Did you come to work with Lu Fenfen today?
Yes.
Lu Fenfen is my girlfriend.
Just deal with your management affairs normally.
It won't affect your work.
But Lu Fenfen has no educational background
or experience.
And she used to do odd jobs in a supermarket...
Enough. This is my personal affair.
If there's nothing else,
you can get back to work.
Okay.
Chairwoman,
I shouldn't have meddled in this matter.
But I think it's necessary
to let you know.
Go ahead.
This morning, I saw CEO
and a grassroots employee of our company,
called Lu Fenfen,
coming to work hand in hand.
Lu Fenfen...
They came to work hand in hand?
Yes!
I asked CEO.
He admitted it.
He told me that Lu Fenfen was...
I'm relieved that they made it public.
OK. Thank you, Bai Bing.
I'll hang up if there's nothing else.
Lu Fenfen.
What trick did you use
to bewitch the whole Xu family?
Wait and see.
I will reveal who you really are.
Mr. Xu.
What can I do for you?
Director Bai.
I heard that you had a hard time talking with Xu Mingchen,
because of Lu Fenfen.
Xu Mingchen hasn't come to the company lately.
I heard that he was hanging out
with Lu Fenfen.
That's impossible!
The CEO is not that kind of person.
You're too naive.
You don't know men well.
You've liked Xu Mingchen for so many years,
but he has never laid his eyes on you.
Now, Lu Fenfen
who is incompetent and not beautiful
is regarded as a precious girl by him.
It only shows that some men
are born with bad taste.
They're really not suitable to take responsibility.
Mr. Xu, as an employee of the company,
I don't want to hear you slandering the CEO.
You really don't know how to fight for yourself.
Xu Mingchen is a rich dandy now.
Only when he loses everything,
can he see you beside him
and understand your kindness.
And that moment
is the time when you can defeat Lu Fenfen.
Mr. Xu.
I will never betray
the CEO and Chairwoman.
I have something to do. I have to go.
The sales of the group in this quarter have fallen,
and Ding's Group is likely to come from behind.
Everyone is in a panic.
And the CEO hasn't shown up for a long time.
Mr. Xu Song secretly contacted the higher-ups of the company.
I'm afraid today is a trap.
Let's begin.
Chairwoman.
Is Mingchen not coming today?
The outside world is speculating
about his physical condition.
If he doesn't show up,
there would be trouble.
It's not a long-term solution
to make it not a trending topic.
You all have seen
the performance report, right?
For the first time in ten years,
Ding's Group has surpassed us.
A commander is indispensable to an army.
If Mingchen keeps being absent,
in addition to the speculation from the outside,
panic will be spread
within our group.
If Mingchen doesn't show up all the time,
what do you think we should do?
Chairwoman,
does Mingchen feel well?
I want to ask for your opinions.
We can only sacrifice the pawn to save the queen.
We should focus on the overall interests of the company
and select a new CEO.
In that case,
who do you think is suitable?
I suggest...
Excuse me!
I'm late.
How far are you guys going?
We haven't got to the point yet.
Mr. Xu is worried about your health.
Please rest assured.
My physical condition
is good.
[Xu Mingchen]
Hello.
You don't have to pick me up.
Why?
You have a special identity.
I don't want to be gossiped about.
I'll get you into trouble.
I don't think so.
You're a boss.
I'm just an employee.
How can others work normally
if you make me so special in work?
How can my leaders treat me?
Fenfen has grown up.
She would think about the company.
You are acting as a boss's wife.
Cut the crap!
I have work to do.
You don't have to pick me up.
Bye.
Oh no.
The bus is gone.
Why are you here?
I managed to make you my girlfriend.
Thinking twice,
I can't bear the fact that you may get hurt.
Thank you
for showing up when I need you the most.
Thank you for tolerating my willfulness.
Let's go home.
Be careful.
How about your legs?
They're fine.
Well. Qiao Yi isn't home today.
It's so late...
What do you want to say?
I want to say that you can stay here.
If I stay,
what can I do?
I want
to drink with you.
Okay, I'll go get some wine.
Cheers.
I...
I'm a little drunk.
Me too.
Fenfen.
Are you asleep?
What should we do?
Why is she back now?
How would I know?
She usually comes back late.
She's asleep.
Why are you being so rude?
What can I do?
It's okay.
Well...
Qiao Yi
will go back to her room after having instant noodles.
What should we do?
I can't take it anymore.
Don't say that.
I can't either.
How long will she be able to go back to her room?
Maybe... soon?
[I'm a donkey if I'm drunk!]