[English subtitles are available]
[The Girl Who Sees Smells]
[Episode 21]
It's so amazing.
Welcome, Miss Lu.
Mr. Xu told us
we only serve you today.
If you want to try on any dress,
just tell me.
We will do our best
to make you satisfied.
Where is he?
Mr. Xu said
he has something to deal with. He'll be here later.
Before he comes,
please enjoy yourself
in this wonderland.
Fine.
He did so much for me.
I can forgive him for being late.
Get up. Take a seat.
I want to eat wontons.
Okay, I'll buy wontons for you right now.
Bai Bing.
Don't be silly.
You hurt yourself for Mingchen.
But he won't know this at all.
He's getting married.
What can I do?
[He Le]
Hello?
Yijiang, where are you?
We've arrived.
I have something to deal with now. I'll be there later.
Are you going to congratulate him?
Go.
You know it.
Why did you hurt yourself
for someone who doesn't love you?
Have you forgotten
that you still have your family and me?
I'm your friend.
I will always be there for you.
And
you said you want to make wine.
Family?
My family abandoned me long ago.
They
just want my money.
Wine?
I worked so hard.
In the end,
I'm nothing
compared with Lu Fenfen.
Why?
Why can she
have the perfect sense of taste?
Why does Xu Mingchen love her so much?
Why is she always much luckier than me?
I don't want to argue with you here.
But you know what?
You look more like yourself now.
So beautiful.
Miss Lu, are you satisfied?
Yes.
I'm so jealous.
How about we get married again?
You want me to marry you twice?
Miss Lu, you are so beautiful.
And you have such a sweet boyfriend.
It makes me jealous too.
Miss Lu, is everything okay with this dress?
Yes.
Fenfen,
I used to worry that you
might pick a wrong guy to be your husband.
But now, you are getting married. How time flies.
What are you doing?
You are like my mom.
Don't say that. I am not like your mom.
No matter what happens,
you must live happily.
Don't worry.
My life will be very happy.
Don't be too sad.
Sometimes,
you just cannot get what you want.
I know.
I just cannot let it go.
Actually, there are many reasons
why Mingchen and Fenfen should be together.
It's their destiny.
If everything could start over,
Mingchen
might choose you.
What destiny?
I don't believe in destiny.
Jian Yijiang,
is there something you didn't tell me?
Tell me.
You shouldn't ask.
Don't do this.
Okay, I'll tell you.
When Fenfen gave artificial respiration
to Mingchen for the first time,
Mingchen's pain was alleviated.
What do you mean?
We did a lot of experiments
to find out whether this is true.
Our conclusion
is that in Fenfen's kiss,
there is a special bio-enzyme
which can balance
the growth hormones in Mingchen's body
alleviate his pain.
So Lu Fenfen's kiss
can help treat Mingchen's illness.
I've booked the ticket for you.
But Master,
is this your final decision?
I've made up my mind.
If you want to stay in China,
I can help you.
No, Master.
I'll always follow you.
Wherever you go, I'll go with you.
Tianran, I need to talk to you.
The formal invitation letters are being prepared.
I wrote this myself.
[Invitation]
[To Tianran: I'm glad to tell you I'm getting married to Fenfen. This is a special day for me.]
[Fenfen is the most important woman in my life. You are the family member that Fenfen and I value the most.]
I'm sorry.
I've booked a flight to France.
I can't make it.
You are my only brother.
I hope
you can attend my wedding.
Are you here to show off?
Tianran.
I'm very sick.
Does Fenfen know about this?
So this is the reason
why you rejected her proposal.
Yes.
I wanted to tell her everything,
but I was too afraid.
What are you going to do?
My happiness can only be short-lived.
I'll just take life as it comes.
Tianran.
I hope you can come back to the Group
and take over my position.
Don't worry.
I'll do my best to help you.
Da will also help you.
Some of the board of directors may oppose it,
but my sister and I will support you.
I've already...
Tianran.
Anda was founded by our father.
You don't want to see it ruined, do you?
I'll think about it.
I've investigated that car accident
and found something suspicious.
It was not just an accident.
What?
It's Xu Song.
He wanted to control the business
so he tried to kill us when we were travelling.
He did it so well
that we didn't suspect him.
After he betrayed the Group,
I investigated him and found out the truth.
Probably this is our fate.
Don't worry.
I've given the evidence to the police.
He will definitely be punished this time.
I haven't told Sister about this.
I'm afraid it's too much for her.
When everything is over,
we'll talk to her together.
-Thank you. -Come on, Fenfen.
Have a seat.
Sit.
Let me help you.
This place is good for taking photos.
Let me tell you.
Based on my experience in taking wedding photos,
I think you have to show
your slim figure.
Show the beauty of your sexy body.
I don't have a sexy body.
You have.
Come, sit down.
The weather is so hot. Sit down.
Have some water.
Here.
I don't think you should come here.
I'm here to send my best wishes to you.
Fenfen is very happy.
You've sent your wishes.
You can go now.
Fenfen.
I have something to tell you.
You will be interested in it.
Qiao Yi, this pair of shoes doesn't fit.
Find a new pair for me.
Fenfen.
It's okay.
Just a small problem. I can handle it.
Don't worry.
I warn you. Don't do anything that will hurt her.
Have a seat.
What happened to your hand?
It's just a small wound.
So what do you want to tell me?
Fenfen.
I really envy you.
You have such a happy life.
Thank you.
You will find your own happiness.
Do you really think everything just happened by coincidence?
Mingchen can't live without you.
He needs your kiss.
What do you mean?
It's true
that those who are naive are always the happiest.
You still can't let it go?
I don't want our relationship to be like this.
Even if we can't be friends,
we shouldn't be enemies.
You're so kind.
So what are you really trying to say?
Are you done?
Fenfen, try on the shoes first.
All right, I've sent my wishes.
I should go now.
I think Fenfen should know it now.
I'm the most honest person
you meet today.
Fenfen, what did she say to you?
I don't understand what she said.
I'm confused.
Alright, don't think too much.
Let's take the wedding photos first.
Xu Mingchen is dressed. He is waiting for you.
OK.
Two brides.
Fenfen.
You look so beautiful today.
Xu Mingchen,
Fenfen is the most important person
in my life.
If you dare to treat her badly,
I'll kill you.
Don't worry.
I'll hold her tight.
Okay.
Let's take photos.
I'll put you down.
Okay.
Done.
-What's wrong? -Are you okay?
Are you okay?
My foot.
Let me take you back first.
What's wrong?
She sprained her ankle.
Oh my god. Hurry up.
Sit here.
Here.
How did it happen?
Is it because of the shoes?
No.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
If this pair of shoes does not fit,
I'll get you another pair.
Okay.
It's true
that those who are naive are always the happiest.
Qiao Yi.
I'm hungry.
I want to eat the dumplings made by you.
Now?
Okay, let's go home and eat dumplings.
Okay.
To serve the bride first.
Let's go.
Be careful.
Slowly.
Qiao Yi.
I do not
feel good.
What's wrong?
I am thinking about
what Bai Bing said just now.
Don't do that.
Just remember
you are the bride.
Okay?
Okay, let's eat dumplings.
Okay.
Be careful.
Why do I feel so tired today?
You are tired today?
What about the wedding day? It will be more tiring.
Qiao Yi, you go back first.
I need to buy some vinegar.
Okay.
Go.
I gave him artificial respiration the first time I met him.
In the hospital, he forced me to kiss him.
He even wanted to make a contract to get my kisses.
Then he suddenly moved to my neighborhood
and we became neighbors.
The night when we were stuck in the elevator shaft,
he became so active after he kissed me.
And…
Lu Fenfen, don't think too much.
It must be a misunderstanding.
It's definitely not like that.
Sir, have you made up your mind?
The price will go up very soon.
Let me tell you.
We have several good apartments
in this neighborhood.
Rich people all like our apartments.
The price has increased again recently.
Yes, this is definitely
the lowest price I can offer.
I...
Listen.
If you don't believe me,
take a look at this apartment, 110.
Guess what?
It was sold at a price three times higher than the market price.
How is that possible?
I...
I'm serious.
Excuse me.
You said this apartment was sold at a price
three times higher than the market price?
Yes.
Miss, do you want to buy a apartment?
Let me tell you.
There is a long story
behind this apartment.
I received a call from a stranger
who said he wanted to buy this apartment.
I didn't give him my number before.
I don't how he got it.
I told him this apartment had been rented.
Guess what.
He said he had to move in that day
at any cost.
He said money was not a problem
and he would buy that apartment at any price.
Look.
He is really a super rich man.
After he hung up,
I got the deposit.
Girl, are you hired by him to ask the question?
The story is so false.
Sir, it's true.
You...
I'm not kidding.
Don't lie to me.
Shut up.
You can ask that person.
So everything was Mingchen's plan.
I really don't understand.
It's just a pair of shoes.
Why is she so sad?
I'm confused too.
After you took the wedding photos,
Qiao Yi became so strange.
She was furious.
Women
are so unpredictable.
You'll never know what she'll do next.
You are single. You know nothing.
I thought Fenfen is just not ready.
But look at her now.
If I
tell her the truth,
would she still love me?
You think too much.
She must have a fear of marriage.
She's just not fully prepared.
So simple?
Yes.
Don't think too much.
Prepare for your engagement party.
Really?
I must be right.
I have to go.
Qiao Yi said she will punish me.
Bye.
Mingchen.
If you really want to tell Fenfen about it,
just do it.
Cheers.
But don't you agree with He Le
that I should lie to Fenfen forever?
What's wrong with you today?
[Observation Room]
I already know everything about Xu Mingchen's disease.
I just want some money.
If you don't want this news to make the headlines,
come to Wangjiang Coffee House immediately.
How to Win Lu Fenfen's Heart
Dating Map.
Step One.
Amusement Park.
Girls' Favorites.
Candlelight Dinner.
The kissing scene is the most important.
[Good Pick-up Lines] [Growth Hormone Test Report]
Pick-up Lines.
Bai Bing was right.
From the very start,
he just wanted my kiss.
I need your kiss.
Not just one kiss.
I need to kiss you
every day.
We just moved in.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Lu Fenfen.
Nice to meet you, too.
Go out with me.
Lu Fefen.
Promise me
you will never leave me.
I need to see you whenever I want to.
I need to kiss you whenever I want to.
Do you really think everything just happened by coincidence?
Mingchen can't live without you.
He needs your kiss.
It's true
that those who are naive are always the happiest.
He Le knows. Yijiang knows.
Qingran knows.
Bai Bing knows.
Even Qiao Yi knows.
Everyone knows
but me.
It's true
that those who are naive are always the happiest.
I'm not a human.
I'm his medicine.
You look handsome.
Of course.
I'm thinking
whether you should put those candles
on the left or on the right.
Did you come to the place where Mingchen and Fenfen took wedding photos?
[Bai Bing]
Did you tell everything to Fenfen?
[Grandpa]
I'm too busy.
I cannot
come to your engagement party this time.
But I will definitely
attend your wedding ceremony.
I will bring you an amazing gift.
I'll make you proud.
What's wrong?
Grandpa, I'm so sad.
I think I'm going to say goodbye
to the biggest dream in my life.
A romantic relationship is not always a bed of roses.
If you feel tired and hurt,
just come back.
I'll always protect you.
In my eyes,
you are the most precious in the world.
Okay, Grandpa.
Remember to take good care of yourself.
Go to bed early.
You hang up first.
[Xu Mingchen]
[I'll sleep with Qiao Yi tonight.]
[Okay.]
Take good care of these flowers.
Let's see what kind of flower arrangements we need.
David, help me place those chairs.
Make sure everything is perfect.
Okay.
Keep an eye on them.
Put the chair here.
Fenfen.
Sister.
I wish you all the best.
But it's not an easy job
to be Mingchen's fiancée.
You still have a lot to learn.
After all,
Mingchen is the best man you can ever have.
Since there aren't that many guests here yet,
let's take a photo first.
Okay.
Sir, can you help take a photo of us?
Here.
Let me take a look.
Alright.
They're here.
Mingchen.
Congratulations.
Fenfen.
From now on,
you are Mingchen's wife.
If Mingchen treats you badly,
tell me.
I won't let him off easily.
Let's drink later.
Okay. That's for sure.
Mingchen.
Fenfen.
I sincerely wish you and Mingchen
can be happy forever.
Mingchen, I have something to tell you.
Mingchen.
Nana.
Is the chair
good now?
Mingchen.
I hope you can be happy in the future.
We are all here.
Qingran,
we are all here.
Let's take a photo together.
OK.
You two stand in the middle.
OK. OK.
Come on. Look at the camera.
Make a pose.
Let's give him a heart.
Okay.
-Make a heart. -Let's do it together.
Happy wedding.
Three, two, one.
How is the photo? Let me see.
Let me see.
Wait.
I'll take another photo with Fenfen.
Just me and Fenfen.
Okay.
I've never taken a photo with Fenfen.
One more. One more.
Let me take one.
I want one too.
I want to take a photo of me and Fenfen only.
Take photos for her.
Two of us.
Fenfen, look at the camera.
Mingchen, I have to tell you something.
Fenfen may know everything now.