It's suspicious for sure.
Can we check his Agucci purse?
-Give me this!
-Let's see what's inside.
Come on, you're jumping the gun.
MURDER ON THE HANGANG BRIDGE II
-What's that?
-What's in there?
A LETTER?
-Is there anything else?
-No.
The letter. That's most important.
Are you kidding me? Look at this.
What the heck?
Whose…
-That's the smoking gun.
-Whose…
There's a name on the back. "Buddy Jr."
"Buddy Jr."?
They even gave the baby a nickname.
The sonogram.
That freaked everyone out.
I figured he would've had
his one true love,
but I didn't have enough information
to pinpoint who the woman was.
Whose sonogram is this?
Who is it? Who wrote it?
Oh my gosh. Guys, don't be shocked.
I'll read this, so brace yourselves.
"To symbolize the time we spent together,
I gift you this watch."
"I hope you're not mad
that I splurged a little."
"That's just how much I love you."
"October 3, 2020."
You remember what happened then, right?
The car accident on the Hangang Bridge.
"Yours…
Second Marriage."
"…Second Marriage."
-What the…
-I knew it.
-Does this mean…
-Is it…
No way.
-I feel you. I would've killed him too.
-It can't be.
Lee Second Marriage, Yo-sep's second wife.
Fate must've been playing
a cruel joke on me
because she passed away
in the fire that followed the car crash.
Cho Yo-sep killed her
and staged it as an accident
to claim the insurance payout.
You're right.
The woman was pregnant with Buddy's child,
but Yo-sep killed her.
How did your friend
steal Second Marriage from you?
-He didn't steal her from me.
-Did you set them up?
I set them up on a blind date.
Why did you do that if you loved her?
-It wasn't like that.
-Then it was after you set them up.
It was indeed after that.
-One day,
-One day?
I was sick.
And she stopped by with homemade food.
That's when I fell for her.
It felt like I was seeing her
in a whole new light.
Gradually, something special
bloomed between us.
Hold on. What's this?
Is this the watch mentioned in the note?
-That must be it!
-That's…
That's Yo-sep's. He's wearing his watch.
"The gift you left behind."
-He wore the watch.
-That must be it.
-"October 12, 2020."
-The watch he's wearing
-was originally meant for Buddy.
-It's supposed to be yours, Buddy.
-"October 12, 2020." His blood would boil.
-Of course.
He posted that after killing her himself.
-Oh gosh, this is giving me a headache.
-I guess we'll wrap things up early today.
-Oh jeez.
-We won't have to search the river.
If Buddy hadn't killed him,
I would've ended him myself.
She was carrying his baby
he didn't know existed.
What he thought was an accidental death
turned out to be murder.
Yo-sep claimed the watch
Buddy's true love got for him.
His rage and sense of betrayal
would be unimaginable.
I assume there would be
a deep-seated grudge.
Let's go back to October 2020,
right after Second Marriage passed away.
Did you believe it was an accident then?
I did.
When did you find out
it wasn't an accident?
His wife's body wasn't even cold yet,
but the punk began
showing off his new watch.
Considering how both his marriages
ended in a similar way,
I began to suspect
it couldn't have been a coincidence.
Then I found out
he had collected huge insurance payouts
from the two incidents.
I thought that if he had been
behind Second Marriage's accident,
-I couldn't let it slide.
-Of course not.
That's why I deliberately set him up
with Park So-yun.
So that she could dig into him?
She wrote on the Big Score Community
that she was desperate
and willing to do anything.
-Was she after a big score?
-Yeah.
I asked her to find proof
that Yo-sep had killed his wives,
and So-yun said
she had found a document
that laid out Yo-sep's plan.
-That--
-Showing his plan to kill Second Marriage?
Yeah, his murder plan.
I was going to get that document
and have him thrown behind bars.
That was my plan.
So-yun said
she'd leave the garage door open
so I could come and get it.
-It was around 2:40.
-A.M.?
Yeah. I was at his place
looking for the document
when I came across that letter
among Second Marriage's belongings.
Not long after,
the guy who was supposed to
be working the night shift
came back home about five minutes later.
-He came home?
-What time did you call him?
Was it 2:40 a.m.?
After talking to Neighbor on the phone,
-Cho Yo-sep--
-We didn't talk.
I asked to speak to him.
Look, I called at 2:39 a.m.
I called, but they said he wasn't there.
That means Cho Yo-sep made his way home
to the garage during that time.
He asked what I was doing there so late.
I made up an excuse,
saying So-yun had asked me for a favor.
-That's very vague.
-Was it around 2:50 a.m.?
Yeah. And then I returned to the house.
You left when Yo-sep came home
but returned later on?
Yeah, because of that letter.
After reading about the watch,
I realized it was mine
and came back for it.
Was the car in the garage
when you returned?
I'm not sure. The front door was open,
so I entered that way.
-All right. Look, Detective.
-The front door was open.
Regardless of whether Buddy
just told us the truth,
someone drove the car,
be it Cho Yo-sep or Park So-yun,
all the way to the Hangang Bridge.
Here's what we need to note.
Park So-yun was in the passenger seat,
-and someone else was driving.
-Right.
-I don't think Yo-sep was the driver.
-Me neither.
Because he had to
have been hit by the car.
I'd actually like to check out the car
on the bridge again.
-I didn't get a good look at it.
-Let's go up there.
-Shall we?
-My hunches are good, you see.
There's blood here.
The car definitely hit someone.
-Did you see the bloodstains?
-I did.
-Hold on.
-What is it?
I see how it happened.
Yo-sep was standing there
when the car rammed into him.
Exactly. That's right.
I say that because I see blood
on that thing over there.
-The guardrail?
-Exactly.
There's blood on the guardrail too.
BLOOD ON THE FRONT BUMPER AND GUARDRAIL
The blood on the guardrail
suggests the body fell into the river.
A third person must've driven the car
in the first place
-with Park So-yun in the passenger seat.
-Right.
They killed two birds with one stone.
By ramming into the guardrail,
-Exactly.
-Cho Yo-sep, who was standing here,
gets hit by the car,
falls into the river, and dies.
Park So-yun,
who was in the passenger seat,
gets thrown out the windshield and dies.
As for the driver,
they likely went down the bridge
to hide Cho Yo-sep's body.
Cho Yo-sep's body had to be hidden
for the death to appear accidental.
Because the driver wanted to make it
look like one of his insurance scams.
THE PLAN WAS TO MAKE IT LOOK LIKE
A FAULTY AIRBAG AND SEAT BELT
CAUSED CHO YO-SEP'S INSURANCE SCAM
TO BACKFIRE ON HIM
So it has to be someone who knows
that Cho Yo-sep has been killing his wives
-to collect insurance payouts.
-Someone who knows about that, yes.
And someone close enough
to call him out over the phone.
And someone who's good enough at swimming
-To hide the body, yes.
-to go into the water and hide his body.
If the culprit had staged the scene
after being in the water,
that could explain the water
on the driver's seat.
-Right.
-However, the back seat is also wet.
I can't figure out
what they could've done back there.
They must've had a reason
to go back there.
-Hold on.
-Oh jeez, you startled me.
What's that?
-What's that?
-Isn't that Hubby?
A PUPPY KEYCHAIN?
ONE FROM MARRY'S SALON?
-Where did you find that?
-I swear I know nothing about it.
Look at this!
Where was it?
In the car!
-On the car floor?
-Right here!
-Hold on a second.
-Hold on.
Hubby, no!
-You can't deny that's not Hubby.
-Hubby, no!
-Hubby!
-Tell us the truth now.
I will, so please give him back.
-Start talking.
-Give him back.
Start talking first.
I'm an animal lover too.
I don't want to do this.
Yo-sep took me out
for a few drives before.
-I think that's when I dropped it.
-That's when you dropped it?
-In this car, huh?
-I had no idea it'd be here.
You didn't know?
-I didn't.
-Check her purse.
I think it fell off this purse.
Hold Hubby. He's our hostage.
Let me check your purse.
-Just let me take a look.
-Please give my Hubby back.
-With this box cutter…
-Give him to me.
Unbelievable.
-What is it?
-What's that?
A syringe?
Anesthetic for animals!
Anesthetic?
-Explain this.
-Take a look for yourself.
Did you just find a phone?
UNDER THE DRIVER'S SEAT
CHO YO-SEP'S PHONE
-Whose is it?
-Yo-sep's.
-Yo-sep's?
-We've hit the jackpot.
-Where was it?
-Here we go.
-Under the driver's seat.
-You're good at finding stuff.
-Let's check the call history.
Who's "Masery"?
-"Masery"?
-Let me see.
-Isn't it you?
-It's not me.
It's not me.
-It's you.
-You're Masery.
-Marry, Masery.
-Marry Zzong Zzong.
Only you don't get it.
-See? I knew something was off.
-Everyone here gets it but you!
Wait, the woman
who cut off the guy's feet?
-Like the character in Misery?
-Did you also…
-Did you also cripple Noh Two Feet?
-What?
-Did you injure him to wheel him around?
-Just a second.
-Not so fast.
-Noh Two Feet.
Are you saying I'm Masery?
-Masery.
-We all get it except you.
-Should we check her name tag?
-No way.
-Maybe she cuts off their feet
-when they try to leave her.
-My name's Marry.
Let's check his voicemails.
Voicemail box.
There's one. Turn the volume up.
FROM THE DAY BEFORE THE INCIDENT
I need to tell you something.
Come to the salon.
I'll be waiting.
-Come over here.
-Come here.
-Why?
-You called him to the salon on the 28th.
-To the salon, huh?
I had something to tell him.
Which was?
-Well…
-Did you meet up?
What did you say to him?
You know,
just the usual stuff between couples.
-Be straight with me.
-You sounded angry in the voicemail.
-Not at all. I just had something to say.
-Be straight with me.
-Look at what I'm holding.
-I had something to say.
You're acting suspicious, Masery.
Detective.
I secured a key witness statement.
-AD, what do you have for me?
-All of a sudden?
I have a witness statement
from Park So-yun's neighbor.
I see. Let's hear it.
-Park So-yun and Cho Yo-sep's car
-What about it?
was seen at around 3 a.m.
-Around 3 a.m.?
-Yes.
-Who was driving?
-Cho Yo-sep was behind the wheel.
And Park So-yun
was in the front passenger seat.
-At 3 a.m.?
-Yes. At 3 a.m.
Around 3 a.m.
That's around the time of the accident.
-Cho Yo-sep was driving?
-Yes, he was behind the wheel.
So that confirms Cho Yo-sep was driving.
That's right.
-They were both in the car?
-Yes.
-Was it just them in the car?
-Today's case is very puzzling.
-Cho Yo-sep was driving?
Cho Yo-sep was driving.
Hold on. Cho Yo-sep was behind the wheel?
Then the killer
wouldn't have walked to the bridge
or arrived in a different car.
I suppose the killer
could've been hiding in the car
and then appeared to strike.
-Can we open the trunk?
-Yeah, let's.
Sure.
HOW DID THE CULPRIT GET HERE?
To the left.
Was the trunk empty?
Yes, it was empty.
But there's dirt here.
-Not just there. There's dirt here too.
-Where?
Here.
-There's dirt here too.
-Yes, there is.
So, from the back…
There's a trail of dirt
leading to the trunk.
Could this be a possibility?
What if the killer was in the trunk?
-There's dirt here.
-Right.
What if three people were in the car?
There must've been
three passengers to begin with.
But how did the killer
get out of the trunk?
A SKI HATCH ACCESSIBLE FROM THE BACK SEAT
We open the hatch to fit the golf bags in.
-No one can fit through there.
-That's not possible.
Can't you open the trunk from the inside?
Why don't you go in?
-Me?
-Yes, get in there.
-I think it'll open if you pull this.
-Pull what?
-It's a task for our kind Mr. Neighbor.
-Okay, fine.
-You're practically an angel.
-Goodness.
-Watch your head.
-Slowly.
If he's the killer, it'll feel strange
since he'd be reenacting the murder.
Exactly. If he's the killer,
-he'd be retracing his steps from earlier.
-He must think he's screwed.
-Right, that he's doomed.
-I'm ready.
-I'll close it.
-We'll shut the trunk.
The key's still in the hole.
WELL?
-I can open it.
-It opens.
-See?
-It can be opened?
-The killer was in the trunk.
It opens from the inside.
I believe finding Cho Yo-sep's body
will give us some answers.
Why don't we look around?
Sure. I'll search the water down there.
Sounds good.
You can dive in, Mr. Neighbor.
THE MOST SUSPICIOUS ITEM: THE WATER TAXI
Can we catch a ride in the taxi?
The water taxi?
It's after hours, so I can't operate it.
-Should we look at the navigation system?
-Wasn't there a place he frequented?
Right, you said there was a place
he went often.
RECENT DESTINATIONS
WHILE THE WATER TAXI
IS BEING THOROUGHLY SEARCHED
KIM DETECTIVE SEARCHES
THE UNOCCUPIED HWANG BILLIONAIRE'S OFFICE
A DOCUMENT ENVELOPE?
Hwang Billionaire.
What did you have hidden so well?
Everyone, are you busy?
-Sorry?
-Let's all take a look
at what Mr. Billionaire has.
-Who?
-Mr. Billionaire.
-There hasn't been much evidence
-Mr. Billionaire, come on.
against him so far,
but I found three suspicious photos
and a contract.
3 PHOTOS AND A CONTRACT
Sure. Take a look.
This looks like the original copy
of the contract
Cho Yo-sep used
to blackmail Mr. Billionaire.
-It is.
-Right?
The contract signed by Cha Contract,
the person he hired
to stage a water rescue.
And these are photos
of the Hangang Bridge.
Who's this?
Is he Cha Contract?
And this here is a photo of you,
Mr. Billionaire.
That's obviously me.
Why are they all kneeling
on the exact same spot?
-They're tying their shoelaces.
-Why are they tying their shoelaces here?
-What do these photos mean?
-What do they mean?
I found these at the house.
-These photos?
-Yes.
-At whose house?
-Cho Yo-sep's.
You found these at Cho Yo-sep's house?
Yes.
Are you saying Cho Yo-sep took these?
He wouldn't stop threatening me,
but I couldn't keep paying him off.
So I went to his house
to get the original copy of the contract.
What time did you go to his house?
At 2:30 a.m.
When he wasn't home?
I knocked on the front door,
but no one seemed to be home.
I noticed that the garage door was open,
so I entered the house
through the side door by the car.
-The car was there, but no one was around?
-The car…
Was the car there?
The car was there,
but I was focused on getting
what I came for.
The two people
who could've gotten into the trunk
are Billionaire and Buddy.
-We know they were at the house.
-That's right.
When did you say you were
at the house again, Mr. Buddy?
I first went there at 2:40 a.m.
-Billionaire was there first. At 2:30 a.m.
-He went first. When did you go back?
A little after…
3:05 a.m.
-Maybe around 3:10 or 3:15 a.m.
-Is there nothing here?
-So, 2:30 a.m., 2:40 a.m., and 3:05 a.m.
-Right.
-Mr. Billionaire.
-Yes?
Could you give me the password for this?
I don't know what the password is.
-You don't?
-No, I don't.
-Really?
-I don't know what it is.
I'm afraid you'll have to find it.
HE'S NO PUSHOVER
What's this website? "Darkscene"?
The name alone is suspicious.
"Darkscene," huh?
He must be dealing something sketchy.
He won't tell me his password.
-Don't they keep it in places like this?
-Come on, don't be like that.
"Darkscene"?
-The password should be somewhere here.
-It should be written somewhere.
I wonder what the password is.
Mr. Hwang Billionaire.
What the…
-Unbelievable.
-For goodness' sake.
What's this?
THE BACK OF THE DISPLAY CABINET OPENS UP?
What the heck?
-What is it?
-What's going on?
IN THE DISPLAY CABINET
AT HWANG BILLIONAIRE'S OFFICE
What's this?
A HIDDEN SPACE
-What is it?
-What's going on?
HANDLE WITH CARE
HIGHLY TOXIC
Hwang Billionaire!
CLUE OVERLOAD
We got our guy!
-Hwang Billionaire's our bad guy!
-Oh, come on.
What's this?
-It's a chemical.
-What is it?
-No wonder.
-Formalin!
-I knew there had to be more to him.
-I know.
-We've got memory cards here.
-This explains the dark web.
What are these?
There's something written on these.
-Let's check them over there.
-Suspect me all you want.
-Wait, what the heck? This is a finger!
-What?
Suspect me all you want.
Wait, what the heck? This is a finger!
What?
These are all fingers!
-Is he insane?
-Are you serious? This is a finger.
-Do all tubes have a finger in them?
-They do.
-That lunatic.
-Wait…
Five fingers… No, ten.
A COLLECTION OF FINGERS
Remember the framed photo?
The one with just the hands.
Do you have a hand fetish or something?
-What's going on?
-Hold on.
What's your deal?
I'm not the only one
with a hobby like this.
You have your affairs and gambling habits,
so what's the big deal?
How is this the same as gambling?
-I'm not into anything bad.
-Fine.
I like collecting fingers.
-No way.
-Seriously?
The villains we have encountered so far
were nothing compared to this guy.
He had a bizarre and morbid fascination
with such a disturbing subject.
It never occurred to me
that he'd be a psychopath of this degree.
It was unexpected.
-What's this? "Exciting Screams."
-I mean, listen.
"Strong Old Man."
"Office Worker with Pretty Hands."
-Fine, keep going.
-"Giant Mole on the Back of the Hand."
"Muscular University Student."
-Shall we check one of the cards?
-"Midnight Swim."
-That's from 2021.
-"March 29, 2021."
-"Delivery Gone Wrong."
-"Delivery Gone Wrong"?
What's this?
A BROKEN GLASS TUBE?
What's this back here?
Right here, "g9v2…"
-The password!
-Is that the password?
-Nine.
-G, nine.
-What's after V?
-V, E.
Got it.
-M.
-M
-Seven.
-X.
-This is one complicated password. X.
-Tell me about it.
-Three.
-Q, one.
Z, eight.
-Eight.
-That's it.
He kept it deeply hidden.
-It worked.
-We're in.
CHAT HISTORY?
"Transaction request."
"Location, Hangang Bridge.
Price, 300 million won."
"Retrieval complete."
What's this?
What is this, you shady billionaire?
Do you have to ask?
I bought those fingers.
You bought fingers for 300 million won?
There were dates written on them.
Scroll down all the way to the bottom.
-March 29, 2021.
-March 29th.
"Arrived on time. Task complete."
-"Has the target arrived?"
-"One male adult."
"One male adult"?
"Excellent swimmer."
"Requesting a job on a specific target."
The target must be Cho Yo-sep!
"One male adult. 2 a.m.
Excellent swimmer."
Whoever this was arrived on time
and completed the task.
-Check if they match these dates.
-That was sent at 2:36 a.m.
-Look.
-March 29, 2021.
This was the most recent one.
Doesn't this mean
he only collected the finger?
Cho Yo-sep's body
is likely missing a finger.
-Right.
-One of his fingers is here instead.
-Right, if it's been chopped off.
-Did Billionaire have someone kill Yo-sep?
-"Squeaky Clean."
-I must admit
being ostracized within the company
really took a toll on me.
There's that moment
when people take their final breaths.
I feel a thrill in watching such moments.
See? I told you he was a psychopath.
-He's a psychopath.
-But as for these fingers,
-I didn't cut them myself.
-You keep them as souvenirs?
Yes, that's right.
I don't just keep the fingers.
There are videos as well.
You have recordings
of people's last moments?
-I keep snuff films with me.
-Snuff films.
-I keep them too.
-He's a complete nutjob.
HE COLLECTED FINGERS AS SOUVENIRS
AND FOOTAGE OF PEOPLE'S DYING MOMENTS
After hiring a hitman
to carry out a murder,
I go retrieve the souvenirs
from the storm drain.
The fingers and the snuff films.
The storm drain?
So the photo captured the hitman
placing them in the storm drain.
-They weren't tying their shoelaces.
-That was a cover.
Yes, while pretending to walk past it.
-You retrieved your souvenirs.
-That's how I collected them.
What's this about Squeaky Clean
completing a task?
Anyway, I wanted Cho Yo-sep dead.
So, I told him to meet me
at the Hangang River.
-I called him.
-On the 29th?
No, the day before.
We set a time and date.
But I didn't show up
-at the agreed time.
-Instead,
-you arranged for a hit on the dark web.
-That's right.
That way, I had time
to go find the contract.
-When was the time you agreed to meet?
-2:30 a.m.
I didn't think Cho Yo-sep had any idea
about this particular hobby of mine.
But he had evidence
of my ties with the contractor
and the collection I kept.
So it made me wonder
if he'd show if I called him up
when he was already aware
that I was working with a contractor
to collect such things.
But the hitman texted me,
saying that the task was completed.
ARRIVED ON TIME, TASK COMPLETE
After reading that,
I left for the Hangang River immediately
and waited near the Hangang Bridge.
Once I was notified
that the task was complete
and the goods were in the storm drain,
I picked up my souvenirs
and headed back to my office.
I got back, but here's the catch.
Yo-sep should've been
the victim of my arrangement, right?
-But it wasn't him who died.
-It wasn't?
-I ran into Yo-sep around that time.
-The photo from earlier. Look at it.
DELIVERY GONE WRONG
-Which one?
-This one, "Delivery Gone Wrong."
-This is from "Delivery Gone Wrong."
-Right.
Oh, someone else died.
I wanted Cho Yo-sep dead,
but I didn't get what I wanted.
-So I'm not the killer.
-Who did the hitman kill?
-Who did the hitman take out?
-Who did they kill?
I don't know either.
-Who in the world did they kill?
-I have no idea.
-I tried to have Yo-sep killed but failed.
-An innocent person died instead.
Did an innocent person die
instead of Cho Yo-sep?
-Anyway, a random man got murdered.
-He died, yes.
-And you have that random man's finger.
-That's right.
But seeing this still gave you a thrill.
I'd appreciate it
if you were gentle with that.
-Either way, you're off to prison.
-Right.
How so?
I'm not the one who killed Cho Yo-sep.
Soliciting murder is a serious felony.
You had nine people killed.
That's none of your concern.
I'll have my lawyers take care of it.
Then, Cho Yo-sep
must've been up on the bridge
looking for evidence in the storm drain
when the car rammed into him.
HIT WHILE CHECKING THE STORM DRAIN?
Maybe he was looking inside,
wondering what was in there.
-What time did you go to the storm drain?
-Where's this storm drain?
I came here at 3 a.m.
-Where?
-The bridge?
-Yes, where we agreed to meet.
-He was at the scene on the bridge then.
Had the car already crashed or not?
It hadn't.
-At 3 a.m.?
-That's right.
-I--
-You didn't see the car?
I took my souvenirs
and went straight back to my office.
-Think of the exact time.
-It was 3:10 a.m.
-Okay, 3:10 a.m.
-Yes.
So there was no car accident
until 3:10 a.m.
Yo-sep and So-yun's car
arrived on the Hangang Bridge
sometime after 3:10 a.m.
-Then, the incident occurred.
-Exactly.
Why did Cho Yo-sep drive to the bridge
sometime after 3:10 a.m.?
The car crashed into the guardrail
near the storm drain.
Those who knew the storm drain served
as a drop-off point for deals
are just Cho Yo-sep and Hwang Billionaire.
Billionaire admitted
that he wanted Yo-sep dead
and that he put a hit on him.
He then claimed that the contractor
ended up killing the wrong person.
That seems a little suspicious to me.
MEANWHILE, JANG NEIGHBOR
You minx.
I'm onto you.
AGGRESSIVELY SUSPECTING AN MARRY
You little minx.
You minx.
I knew it.
TWO ENVELOPES?
From An Marry to Noh Two Feet.
The letter was returned.
There are two.
Jeez, what now? Enough already.
What's wrong?
Look… Look at this!
-What now?
-Look at this.
This woman!
SEOUL DISTRICT COURT RULING
-This woman!
-We were right about Noh Two Feet!
Check this out.
"Two Feet, do you still flirt
with older ladies
while giving them swimming lessons?"
"You're the sexiest
when teaching the backstroke
thanks to your smooth armpits."
She has weird taste.
"Oh, right. You can't swim
with both feet anymore, can you?"
-"Why didn't you stay when I told you to?"
-No, not my precious hair.
Please let go.
"I didn't want to use the hammer on you."
"Don't resent me too much."
She's not a doe-eyed wacko
but a complete cuckoo.
She terrifies me!
-This is Misery in real life.
-Where's Ms. Marry?
The look in Masery's eyes has changed.
-Masery.
-What?
Even her walk has become more arrogant.
What did you do to Noh Two Feet?
-With a hammer…
-Did you kill him with a hammer?
Want me to snap your feet too?
Please. I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
-She's "Masery" for sure.
-What do you want?
This means that Noh Two Feet
wasn't born with his condition.
I made him like that.
He was "Two Feet" to begin with,
-I made him "Noh Two Feet."
-but you gave him a new surname.
-This is terrifying.
-Does this mean
she's the real-life version of Misery?
Yes, it's the same story.
What about it?
So what if I smashed the guy's feet
for not loving me?
-Sure, fine.
-What about the anesthetic?
What were you going to do with it?
What was it for?
I was going to smash his feet.
-After sedating him?
-Yeah.
-Once you lured him here?
-She's terrifying.
On the 29th…
This is important.
Kim Detective, listen up.
Hear me out, or I'll smash your feet.
-Sorry. What were you saying?
-On the 29th.
-I was patiently waiting.
-Okay.
-For Cho Yo-sep?
-Yes.
I just couldn't understand him.
He wanted to break up with me just because
I filled out the divorce papers for him.
-That made me furious.
-Okay.
He was refusing to accept my love
and crawled back
to that damned Park So-yun.
I waited for him, but he never showed up.
So I went to the Water Rescue Team
at 2:30 a.m. to find him.
-I took the anesthetic with me.
-At 2:30 a.m.?
I was going to sedate him
and break his feet.
-But he wasn't there.
-He wasn't?
At around 2:52 a.m., I went to his house
and found him there.
So I took the anesthetic and…
-Did you stick it in?
-I was about to,
but he overpowered me.
-He overpowered you?
-Yes.
-Cho Yo-sep stopped your hand like this?
-He was like, "What the hell?"
That's how I dropped the syringe.
-Park So-yun wasn't around, was she?
-It dropped.
I wouldn't know.
This happened at the front door.
-So?
-Is that when the plant got knocked over?
-Again, no idea. I was at the front door.
-What happened next?
At 2:54 a.m.,
I figured I should head back to my salon.
So I got back here at 3:05 a.m.
I haven't seen him since.
I was here all night.
After he overpowered you,
-you just gave up and returned here?
-Without a fight?
-Just like that?
-Without fighting back?
-I never wanted to kill him.
-When you break men's feet?
Was the syringe we found in your purse
one of the two you still had?
I lost one syringe, and I had one left.
So you had one out of two left?
Where's the other syringe?
Somewhere on the floor?
-That syringe…
-Maybe Cho Yo-sep took it.
That could explain why Park So-yun
has no other injuries.
Maybe she used it to kill Park So-yun.
Knowing Cho Yo-sep
wouldn't leave Park So-yun for her,
she could've killed her to claim him.
No way. I'll have him,
even if I have to break both his feet.
-I couldn't care less about Park So-yun.
-Really?
-You only wanted the guy?
-He's all I need.
Didn't you want to get back at her?
I approached him to get my revenge,
-but I ended up falling in love with him.
-Why in the world did Park So-yun die?
All the suspects
were linked to Cho Yo-sep,
not Park So-yun.
Why kill So-yun of all people?
And where's Cho Yo-sep?
Ultimately, the key to all this
is the culprit's movements.
The car was in the garage.
Here's what we're dealing with.
Three people have been confirmed
to have been in Cho Yo-sep's house.
-Marry, me, and Billionaire.
-Right.
-Marry wasn't in the house.
-I was only at the front door.
-Still, whatever.
-Sure.
But we still don't know
why the plant pot was knocked over.
You're right.
The dirt from the car
seems to have come from the plant pot.
-You're right.
-We could assume that.
It was also in the trunk.
So I was leaning toward Billionaire…
-The car was parked like this,
-Yeah.
and the culprit
must've gotten in the trunk.
-Exactly.
-With dirt from the pot on them!
Oh, from here?
-That's right.
-They got in the car, not realizing it.
What were they trying to find?
-What can you hide in a plant pot?
-It's not that.
They got flustered and knocked it over.
-They weren't looking for anything.
-It was by accident.
WAS THE KNOCKED-OVER PLANT POT
THE CULPRIT'S MISTAKE?
Is there anything here?
Couldn't the culprit
have left any traces behind?
I think they could've.
DID HE FIND SOMETHING?
Is that a zipper on the belt?
-Earlier…
-There's something here.
That's where he hid something?
"KCN"?
What's this?
-It's a drug.
-It's potassium cyanide.
-For real?
Isn't this a man's belt?
-Whose house are we in?
-It's Yo-sep's.
-Isn't it Yo-sep's?
-How do you know what KCN is?
-Why was this here?
-It's potassium cyanide.
-Yes?
And I heard about it from So-yun.
-What?
-And you're only telling us now?
-Why is this here?
-What did she tell you?
She thought that he was going to…
To kill her?
That's what she thought. This is crazy.
Let's say the killer planned
to get into the trunk and kill them both.
Then they must've been aware
of Cho Yo-sep's plan to kill his wife.
How else could they have made such a plan?
What the heck?
-No way.
-What's that?
A DOCUMENT ENVELOPE UNDER THE BELT BOX?
-You're good at finding stuff.
-Nice.
-I just lifted it and…
-Nicely done, psychopath.
-It's an insurance contract.
-"Insurance Contract."
-Let's read it.
-"Kim First Marriage, Cho Yo-sep."
"Accidental death, 500 million won."
-What did I tell you?
-Check the date.
-All right, here's the second page.
-The policy effective date.
UNDERWORLD LIFE INSURANCE
APPLICATION REVIEW FORM
-"Park So-yun."
-"Park So-yun. Cho Yo-sep."
One billion won for accidental death.
-One billion won?
-One billion won.
-500 million to 700 million to 1 billion.
-Hold on.
500 MILLION AND 700 MILLION
HAVE BEEN COLLECTED
He still had a debt
of a billion won to pay.
NEXT TARGET WAS THE 1 BILLION WON
INSURANCE PAYOUT FOR PARK SO-YUN'S DEATH
So that's why he insisted
on waiting six months.
-He signed up for the policy
-Does that mean I could've died too?
-On February 3, 2021.
-Of course.
-You were next.
-That crazy bastard.
She feared for her life
and wanted to run away from her husband.
She wouldn't have gotten
into the car with him willingly.
-No way.
-She wouldn't.
Seeing the cyanide made me wonder
if Cho Yo-sep had killed Park So-yun
before driving her to the Hangang River.
CHO YO-SEP
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO END THIS SOON
When Jang Buddy
was contacted by Park So-yun…
She had found a document
that laid out Yo-sep's plan.
He was told there was proof
of Cho Yo-sep's crimes.
She said she'd leave the garage open
so he could come in
and find the proof himself.
WHAT IS THE TRUTH BEHIND THE MURDER PLAN?
He's an alcoholic.
That's right.
(RUMMAGING)
Can you all please come here?
I found something.
-What did you find?
-Please take a look at it.
-Something went wrong.
-"Ddior."
-"Insurance… Cyanide."
-"Insurance payout period."
-"Cyanide. Risk of detection in autopsy."
-"Risk of detection in autopsy."
This answers all our questions.
-"Hangang Bridge."
-"Cyanide."
-"Cyanide, car accident, gas leak, fire."
-Was there a fire?
-A fire.
-The article said there had been a fire.
-"No coolant."
-"Idling, remote car start."
-The fire came
-after the crash.
-Hold on.
Was this note written by Yo-sep
and not you, Mr. Buddy?
That's his murder plan.
-So Yo-sep wrote it?
-I went back to his house after 3 a.m.
and found it by his pillow.
This breaks my heart.
IF HE BROUGHT THIS
FROM CHO YO-SEP'S HOUSE…
Is this everything?
Is the murder plan
all he took from the house?
Where?
Did you check everything in here?
PAPER CRANES FOLDED BY JANG BUDDY
-How many paper cranes are in here?
-I folded them while thinking
about Second Marriage.
Don't tell me there are 1,000 of them.
I folded them myself.
-Is there something inside?
-Where's that piece of paper?
There's something rattling inside.
-What the heck?
-The watch.
-What is it?
Of course.
It's that watch.
-Wait, you stole this from Cho Yo-sep!
-What? Why?
How is it stealing?
I only reclaimed what was mine.
Cho Yo-sep uploaded a photo of himself
wearing the watch on social media.
-He brought it home.
-I told you earlier that I did.
There's no way to tell if he took it
from the house or Cho Yo-sep.
-Off his dead body, right?
-There's no way of knowing that.
-Believe what you want.
-Hold on to that.
Unbelievable.
Do we really have to
go through all of these?
-What a hopeless romantic.
-Out of all these,
what do you think
was his plan for Park So-yun?
A car caught on fire
at the Hangang Bridge.
That was how Second Marriage died.
Right, and Park So-yun realized
he was going to kill her
by giving her cyanide.
That being said,
a car accident
couldn't have been his plan this time.
Hold on.
Without coolant, idling a car
would cause the engine to overheat.
He planned to knock her out with cyanide
and leave the car idling
long enough for it to combust.
That's not the point.
Cyanide is already lethal.
-But the fire would erase any trace of it.
-It was a cover-up.
Detective.
-He's here.
-What's that?
-We're here.
-AD, what do you have for me?
I have Park So-yun's autopsy report
from the National Forensic Service.
Listen up.
We have the victim's autopsy report.
All right.
"The subject's stomach contents
included cyanide and water."
"Toxicology results
confirmed cyanide poisoning."
"In conclusion, the cause of death
has been ruled as poisoning."
We can safely conclude
that Cho Yo-sep killed Park So-yun.
But afterward,
Cho Yo-sep was killed by a third person
while he was staging the car
to look like an accident.
Exactly.
Aren't we supposed to find out
who killed Park So-yun?
-No.
NO?
I couldn't tell
what the truth was anymore.
Cho Yo-sep was the one
who killed Park So-yun.
In that case…
Where could Yo-sep be?
Is he dead or alive?
At that point,
there was just one place left
that could help us move forward.
-Did you just grab the navigation system?
-I did.
"Favorites. Seongsan Bridge."
"North-end drainage channel, public pool."
"Hangang Bridge
north-end drainage channel."
Why would he go there so often?
Shouldn't we check the Hangang Bridge
north-end drainage channel?
-Yes, let's check it out.
-Seongsan Bridge…
The north-end drainage channel.
HANGANG BRIDGE
NORTH-END DRAINAGE CHANNEL?
We have a very capable AD who can help us.
AD!
Here he comes.
You ran? Shouldn't you have come by boat?
-No, sir.
-So tell me.
Is there a way for us
to search that reed field?
I'll get you a boat.
Okay. Make it quick, will you?
A FEW MOMENTS LATER…
Detective!
-What the heck?
-Detective!
Detective!
There's our boat.
Detective, could you lend me a hand?
-You're doing great.
-Good job, AD
Thanks for that.
How about we search
the reed field together?
Let's go.
I'll start rowing.
Off you go.
Hangang Express is leaving the station.
I never expected to row on this show.
-Oh dear.
-Look at us go!
-You're good at this.
-Head to the rock over there.
-Oh, this way.
-This is scary.
Hold on. I'll give you a hand.
-I'm scared. I'd rather grab the rope.
-I'll hold on so you can climb up.
But this is scary.
Will they be alone over there?
-Marry.
-Yes?
Kill him if you have to.
-If need be, I'll crush him with a hammer.
-Yeah.
We should…
Come closer to me.
-Goodness, Mom?
-Oh dear.
Mom, it's been so long.
I feel like I had a son like you
in a past life.
-My son! Let me see your face.
-Mom, I'm scared.
He's terrible at rowing.
There's water splashing everywhere.
Oh my. What are you two doing?
-Kara?
-This must be where I find love.
-Come on, Kara!
-Go on. I'll hold it steady.
Goodness.
Watch your step.
Push the boat for me, will you?
Push it hard.
A CLOSE CALL
(HOLDING TIGHT)
NEARLY HELD HIS BREATH
AND DIVED INTO THE HANGANG RIVER
I almost fell into the water.
Jeez, that was close.
We almost had a detective die
for the first time in this series.
THE MURDER OF DETECTIVE KIM?
I almost lost my love
shortly after meeting him.
Careful.
-Watch your step.
-Be careful.
-This is a dangerous place.
-Watch your step.
Wait, we can't lose the boat.
-Don't let it float away.
-That has to stay!
-Mister, be careful.
-We need it.
-Would this do?
-Tie it to something.
-Tie the rope to it.
-That was hilarious.
About three of us should've fallen in.
Over here. See these bloodstains?
-There's a heavy trail of blood.
-Trail of blood?
That's blood!
-Over here.
-There's blood everywhere!
So this is where they brought the body.
-It's here too.
-Let's follow the trail of blood.
-The blood trails down that way.
-Over there!
-Where?
-We found him.
What is it?
It's Cho Yo-sep
from the Water Rescue Team.
It's Yo-sep.
Yo-sep?
FOUND DEAD IN THE HANGANG RIVER
NORTH-END DRAINAGE CHANNEL
He's in his Water Rescue Team uniform.
Hey, Misery!
Yo-sep.
Misery did this.
-It wasn't.
-It was Misery.
-Is his leg injury just a coincidence?
-What the hell, Misery?
The legs…
-It wasn't me.
-That's so gross!
-So this is what you did to Noh Two Feet.
-It wasn't me.
-Wait, it looks like he was hit by a car.
-Yo-sep…
-Yo-sep.
-If you're hit here…
-He was hit by the car.
-Yes, it's from the car crash.
He was hit by the car.
The car hit him from behind,
nearly severing his legs
against the guardrail.
He then fell into the river and died.
We now know that Yo-sep
murdered Park So-yun with cyanide.
With that being said,
the key point for us now
is that this case has turned into
the murder of Cho Yo-sep.
Did he fall into the river
and get washed up here
through the drainage channel?
-There were blood trails.
-Or was he moved?
-Someone moved him.
-Yeah, I think he was moved.
Not many people would know
the geography of this place well enough
to consider it a good spot to dump a body.
-Him.
-The drainage channel!
GOTCHA, YOU PUNK!
He had this place marked as a favorite
on his navigation system!
The truth comes out at last.
You've been here twice, haven't you?
That's not it.
Look.
-The things here belong to the homeless.
-Exactly.
You're the only one with ties
to the homeless community.
-The homeless--
-Do you know who else has this cart?
-Jang Neighbor has the same one at home.
-Exactly.
Explain the drainage channel.
-Why have you been coming here?
-All right.
So, just as we've deduced so far,
Park So-yun died of cyanide poisoning.
The killer waited in the trunk
and then ran Cho Yo-sep over,
pushing him off the bridge.
Who had the means
to pull the body from the water?
-What's that?
This was in Cho Yo-sep's wallet.
It's from Underworld Life Insurance.
"Your insurance application was mistakenly
delivered to your neighbor."
"We sincerely apologize
for the inconvenience."
-The houses look identical.
-"To Ms. Park So-yun."
Neighbor received the insurance paperwork
for the policy Cho Yo-sep had taken out.
The houses look the same,
which caused the mix-up.
Yes, the form was delivered
to my house by mistake.
I realized it after opening it
and passed it on to him.
He threw a fit,
asking why I opened their mail.
-I didn't read it though.
-Did Park So-yun know about this?
After the insurance policy form
was mistakenly delivered,
Jang Neighbor likely became
somewhat aware of Cho Yo-sep's history
with insurance scams.
Given the situation,
Jang Neighbor has surpassed everyone else
and just became my prime suspect.
-What's this?
-Did Park So-yun know about this?
-What is it?
-Who knows?
He wired 300,000 won to Noh Homeless.
At around 10 p.m. last night,
Cho Yo-sep wired 300,000 won
to Noh Homeless.
You should know
as the captain of the homeless.
-What's this about?
-Why am I their captain?
-To a homeless person?
-300,000?
-As if you don't know.
-Wait, 300,000 won?
Why did he wire 300,000 won?
Does he have all his fingers?
-Any missing?
-His fingers?
-He has all five on this side.
-They're all intact.
So it was someone else's finger
that was cut off.
-This person…
-Park So-yun…
He sent someone else
to have his finger cut off.
He needed a decoy.
He hired a contract killer, remember?
Billionaire had planned
to kill Cho Yo-sep,
-but Yo-sep figured it out.
-Exactly, he figured it out.
Yo-sep needed someone to die in his stead,
so he paid Noh Homeless 300,000 won
to take his place.
That's how Noh Homeless
ended up dead instead.
-Then, he--
-Where did Cho Yo-sep go?
-To plan his wife's murder.
-To kill his wife.
If you remember, a neighbor saw
Cho Yo-sep driving the car at 3 a.m.
with Park So-yun in the passenger seat.
There's a reason why these three
didn't know where Park So-yun was.
It's highly likely that she had
probably died from cyanide poisoning
-by then.
-She was already dead.
She was probably dead
in the passenger seat.
-She was already dead?
-Or…
Why did Cho Yo-sep
take the car to the Hangang Bridge
with the dead Park So-yun inside?
Did someone force him to drive them there?
It's a bit crowded here,
so let's row back to the other side.
Come on.
Yo-sep…
Yo-sep.
Rest in peace.
-You're so fake.
-Yo-sep.
JANG NEIGHBOR IS NOW THE PRIME SUSPECT
Wait.
There's something here.
What the heck? There's something here.
A CELL PHONE?
Over here!
-What is it?
-I found something!
-What?
-What is that?
A phone?
-It's a phone.
-Bring it here.
Whose is it?
PHOTO1_STAGED_INCIDENT_CONTRACT.JPG
It's Yo-sep's phone.
-This is Yo-sep's phone.
-Yeah.
-Isn't this Yo-sep's phone?
-It is.
He must have two phones.
It's his burner phone.
-"Squeaky Clean."
-Wait, Squeaky Clean?
-How does he know Squeaky Clean?
-That's Hwang Billionaire's contractor.
Both Yo-sep and Billionaire
had dealings with Squeaky Clean.
Squeaky Clean contacted Cho Yo-sep
with a request of his own.
-"For an hour."
-"Skip patrol on the 24th for an hour,
and I'll wire you ten million won."
Thanks to his own deals
with Squeaky Clean,
he was able to figure out
what Squeaky Clean was up to.
Squeaky Clean had a job to do,
-so he cut a deal…
-With someone on the Water Rescue Team.
He requested that no one make rounds
during certain hours.
The times and dates perfectly coincided
with those in Hwang Billionaire's requests
to Squeaky Clean.
There must have been a moment
when Cho Yo-sep became aware of
Billionaire's dealings with Squeaky Clean.
-Check the dates.
-"Tomorrow from 2 to 3 a.m."
"One hour, same amount."
That was March 28th.
-The 28th. And the one above it?
-He knew someone was going to die.
-And also…
-What's this message from Buddy?
-"#Quiet, #mouse, #sneakers, KCN."
-"KCN."
I'll show you where I saw that.
JANG BUDDY'S SOCIAL MEDIA ACCOUNT
What's this?
"Men Breathe Loyalty."
Check out the Story Highlights.
"#Prim, #tears, #water spring, BNW."
"#Exhilarating, #tripe, #soft."
"#Offwork, #cuckoo, #funny."
"#Piano, #highlighter, #mischievous."
Jang Buddy posted those
and tagged Cho Yo-sep.
-What do these mean?
-But look.
-That matches what we just saw.
-"#Quiet, #mouse, #sneakers, KCN."
-What is this, Mr. Buddy?
-Huh?
"#Quiet, #mouse, #sneakers, KCN."
Why did you text him that?
-What do they mean?
We had…
something going.
-As in what?
-Just spill already.
We're not that easy to figure out.
-Unbelievable.
-Where's this?
-Could they lead to coordinates?
-"Quiet."
I mean the hashtags.
When you type in keywords,
the map app displays results.
-Can we type in words from the Highlight?
-The hashtags from his social media.
"#Prim, #tears, #water spring."
It's giving us something.
"Ripple Town, Calm District,
Incheon City."
"Incheon Port Terminal 2."
-The last one sounds like a car.
-A BNW.
-That's the car's make.
-Morsche, like Porsche.
-These just point to cars.
-Right.
-What about KCN?
-The codes
must be from their car smuggling days.
The tagged words indicate the location
where the car should be picked up.
COMMUNICATING THE LOCATION OF THE CAR
WITH THREE WORDS?
"#Quiet, #mouse, #sneakers, KCN."
Type in #quiet,
#mouse,
and #sneakers.
Hangang Bridge!
WHY DID THE HANGANG BRIDGE POP UP?
What the heck? Why did the bridge show up?
"#Quiet, #mouse, and #sneakers"?
He was setting up a meeting
at the Hangang Bridge.
-At 3:05 a.m.
-At what time?
-You're right.
This is the code calling him over
to the Hangang Bridge.
Why did you text Yo-sep
the coordinates at 3:05 a.m.?
I knew it would shake him.
It means I'm onto what he did
with the cyanide.
I wanted to lure Yo-sep out of the house,
so I could look for his murder plan.
Mr. Buddy was the one who lured Cho Yo-sep
to the Hangang Bridge.
If Mr. Buddy is indeed the killer,
perhaps he called Cho Yo-sep
to the Hangang Bridge,
where Yo-sep had killed
Buddy's beloved Second Marriage
to get his revenge.
Did you check everything here?
Jeez, the smell.
A FULL SEARCH OF JANG NEIGHBOR'S HOUSE
What now?
Are you kidding me?
What are you doing in my house?!
PANICKED
You can't do this in my house!
I just got the chills.
TA-DA
I knew it.
A BASEMENT AREA UNDER THE BED?
Move over.
HAS HE RESIGNED HIMSELF TO HIS FATE?
-How brave of her.
-We'll go in there and see.
Goodness gracious.
What is it?
BASEMENT OF JANG NEIGHBOR'S HOUSE
-"Did you really have to take everything?"
-"Really have to take everything?"
There's even a soccer ball here.
Something's fishy about this place.
But one thing's for sure.
He was actually praying.
-He was actually praying?
-I was praying.
-Jeez, you're such a weirdo.
-What's this?
-"Please forgive this one time."
-What are these marks on the floor?
-Beats me.
Look. Isn't this how the police
outline murder victims?
TRACES OF SOMEONE WHO DIED?
-Did you really have to
-What is it?
-take everything?
-Did you?
-What's in that thing?
-Oh, here.
-It's a phone.
-There's another phone in here.
Hold on.
"I'm so glad to be reunited
with the people who saved me."
"The man living next door."
"That Rescue Team member
who didn't save you back then
brought those gang members
from back in the day, so run for it."
Whoever it was,
they didn't get to send it.
Did this person die
before they could send this message?
I think another homeless person
was trying to warn Jang Neighbor.
Jang Neighbor has been
a true friend to the homeless.
I'll tell you everything.
Let's all head back up and hear him out.
So?
COMBINE THE CLUES
TO COMPLETE THE DEDUCTION
You see, like I said before,
I was living it up as the boss
of the Five-Star Gang.
But one day, I was ambushed
by a group of thugs
near the Hangang River.
Someone from the Rescue Team came to help,
and that someone was Cho Yo-sep.
Those who attacked me
paid him off,
-To look the other way?
-and he just left.
CHO YO-SEP TOOK A BRIBE
AND TURNED A BLIND EYE
But here's what upset me the most.
The people who attacked me
were my subordinates.
-Those I thought of as my family.
-Your brothers.
-The ones with stars on their foreheads?
-Yeah.
After doing a number on me,
they left me by the Hangang River.
The homeless came to my rescue.
Since then, I vowed to leave the gang life
and devote myself to helping the homeless.
I'm sorry I mistook you
for an organ smuggler.
I told you Mr. Neighbor was a good man.
-Finish your story.
-So, I thought about
what I could do to help them.
Since many of them
live by the Hangang River,
I scouted the areas
where the homeless usually stay
while operating a water taxi.
I'd sometimes bring them home,
but because of the neighbors' complaints,
I had them stay in the basement.
-You hid them in the basement?
-Yeah.
That's where I had them stay.
Three people saved my life back then,
and I had been searching for them
for quite some time now,
and I only managed to reunite
with them recently.
After reuniting with them,
I let them stay in my basement
while I searched for a better place
for them to stay.
But as I was coming home one day,
I saw my house burning.
I rushed in to put out the fire
and then went to check the basement.
-Two had died.
-Two were already dead.
Is that what the chalk outlines are?
Two had died from inhaling too much smoke,
but one was still alive.
As you saw in the text, my saviors
tried to tell me who the culprit was.
"The Rescue Team member
brought those gang members
from back in the day, so run for it."
And last night,
the sole survivor of the fire
passed away as well.
-At the hospital?
-She passed.
So that got me thinking that perhaps
I need to go back
to my Five-Star Gang days.
I was merciless back then.
Cho Yo-sep obviously couldn't be helped.
I decided that he had to die.
But the last surviving victim
always told me this.
-"Cleanse people of their sins."
-Forgive.
"Forgive." That's what she always said.
So, instead of killing Cho Yo-sep,
I decided to cleanse him of his sins.
I was going to
tie Cho Yo-sep to my water taxi
and drag him underwater
in the Hangang River.
That's why I keep a rope at the back
of the boat, near the life buoy.
So that's how you wanted to cleanse him.
Call it a harsh baptism.
I considered it the harshest punishment
I could give him.
I'd also be keeping the promise
I made to those who saved me.
That's pretty hard to believe.
I called his work for that reason.
I asked for Cho Yo-sep,
but they said he wasn't there.
Clearly, things weren't working out
as I had planned.
-So you prayed at home?
-Yeah.
For the peace of those who passed away
and for a chance to cleanse that sinner.
That day didn't work out,
so I wondered when I'd get my chance.
Either way, Cho Yo-sep deserved to die.
He wanted to cleanse Cho Yo-sep
by tying him to the back of a boat?
Is he out of his mind?
He held back the urge to kill
with prayers?
PLEASE FORGIVE THIS ONE TIME
Is that even possible?
I doubt he could hold back the urge.
That said…
We should discuss
why the drainage channel was used
to dump and hide the body.
By the drainage channel,
I found some items that suggested
it was a shelter for the homeless.
Cho Yo-sep killed the homeless people
Jang Neighbor was devoted to helping
by setting a fire,
letting them die a horrific death.
Killing him was the only fitting revenge.
The dead body
was then laid in a spot that served
as a makeshift shelter for the homeless.
Maybe it was to console their spirits.
Since he was an enemy of the homeless,
the body may have been left there
as a kind of battle trophy.
That's possible.
But the fact that
the killer hid the body over there
means they didn't want it
to be found anytime soon.
Anytime soon? More like forever.
The incident had to be written off
as a domestic case,
which is why the killer
staged the crime scene.
Let's not forget that this took place
on the Hangang Bridge.
The killer had to know Cho Yo-sep
would be there to kill him.
And Mr. Buddy was the only one
who could've lured Cho Yo-sep there.
He did send the text to get him there too.
Mr. Billionaire
also called him to the bridge.
I asked to meet at Honey Chestnut Island,
not the Hangang Bridge.
Billionaire was at the bridge at 3:10 a.m.
To collect the finger.
That's true.
-This is a hard case to crack.
-Here's what I think.
I'll lay out a scenario
where Jang Buddy is the killer.
He said he was at their garage.
I believe that's when he got
into the trunk.
So, he was already in the trunk.
Cho Yo-sep probably went to the bridge
because of Jang Buddy.
He had used the cyanide,
and someone who knew about it
called him to the bridge.
But today wasn't your typical day.
The fine dust level was very high,
and even though it was 4 a.m.,
there wasn't a single car on the road
-when the car suddenly accelerated.
-It was foggy too.
Yo-sep must've left the car
to look for Buddy.
I believe that's when Buddy left the trunk
and slipped in through the back door.
-Back door and not the front?
-The back door?
There's dirt on the back seat.
Let's say I did. What then?
You climbed into the driver's seat
from the back.
That makes sense, doesn't it?
That explains the dirt on the back seat.
It takes quite some time
to exit the trunk and get into the car.
In that time,
Cho Yo-sep might've spotted the killer,
despite the heavy fog.
How could the dirt have gotten in the car?
I get how it ended up in the trunk,
but how did it get on the seats?
I couldn't explain how the killer moved
from the trunk into the car.
-I believe Cho Yo-sep stopped the car.
-Can't really see, huh?
-That's what I think.
-He probably did.
-He stopped and got out.
-He stopped here and got out.
The car came to a stop.
Cho Yo-sep was out here looking for Buddy.
"What the hell? Where is he?"
"Jang Buddy told me to meet him here,
so where is he?"
RE-EXAMINING THE TRUNK
Right. Let's get back in here.
TRIES TO CHANNEL THE KILLER
There's a button.
I see.
IF YOU PULL THE LEVER
THE BACKREST FOLDS?
-Look.
-What?
What the heck?
-You can climb out.
The entire backrest folds.
Check this out.
-This is the only place my foot can go.
-Exactly.
-That must be it.
-By doing this,
you can move up to the front seat.
-You don't have to open any doors.
-Without being detected, that is.
-You can get to the driver's seat.
-That's why there's dirt on this.
Without getting out of the car,
the killer slipped into the driver's seat
-without Cho Yo-sep noticing.
-That's right.
The car suddenly accelerated
in both instances.
HOW CAN THE 2 SKID MARKS BE EXPLAINED?
Here. Imagine this is the car.
RECREATING THE CRIME SCENE
-Cho Yo-sep stopped the car here.
-Right.
-He got out and looked for his friend.
-He looked for Buddy.
-During that time, the killer moved up.
-The killer moved into the driver's seat.
The car launched at Cho Yo-sep,
hitting him once.
-The impact must've sent him flying.
-Right.
After Cho Yo-sep was hit,
he probably pulled himself back up.
Right after striking him with the car,
the driver backed it up.
The driver then launched
the car at him again from here.
ACCELERATED FROM A GREATER DISTANCE
AND HIT HIM A SECOND TIME
That's the second impact.
The only logical conclusion at this point
is that he was hit twice.
But even if this is exactly what happened,
I don't think how the killer did it
matters that much.
Who got in the trunk and why?
And why did Cho Yo-sep get out of the car?
Those are the questions
we need the answers to now.
Hold on.
Wouldn't he have checked the storm drain?
Yo-sep knew the storm drain
was Billionaire's drop-off spot.
Yo-sep knew that.
Mr. Billionaire had been taking things
from the storm drain,
and Yo-sep wanted to use that
as leverage to extort him.
He probably went to the Hangang Bridge
to see what was in the drain.
If Cho Yo-sep was the one
who first retrieved the finger and video
from the storm drain,
a certain someone would've felt
compelled to stop him.
Wouldn't Billionaire have killed him
to protect his future?
Detective, I think Neighbor is right
about what we should be focusing on.
The motive is what matters more right now
-than how the murder was committed.
-The technicalities matter less.
I've already identified
who the culprit is.
-You have?
-Yes.
I've been certain who the culprit is
for the past two hours.
IS HE GOING TO ARREST THE CULPRIT NOW?
Let me give you a hint.
I want you to mull over what I said today.
Think about who my suspicions
were mostly focused on.
Think that through.
I haven't been able to
put all the pieces together yet, but--
-We have no idea who you focused on.
-Wait, what?
-You don't?
-We haven't the faintest clue.
-The homeless.
-You only talked about the homeless.
Earlier, he demonstrated
how he got into the driver's seat.
When cornered,
people make extra effort
to present a plausible story
to escape suspicion.
People with limited knowledge
can be the most dangerous of all.
-You're way off.
-Are you talking about me?
-Yes.
-Was that about me?
-I didn't do it.
-You don't know much.
Just keep in mind that I learned a lot
from YouTube videos and TV.
-It wasn't me.
-Let's head back down.
ONLY THE LAST 3 MINUTES
AND THE FINAL VOTE REMAIN
All right.
Make way for Kim Detective,
the detective with the most swagger.
Today's culprit
had better brace themselves.
FINAL EXAMINATION OF SCENE AND VOTE
EACH GET 3 MINUTES TO EXAMINE THE SCENE
BEFORE CASTING THEIR FINAL VOTE
Get ready to be in the clink.
CAST YOUR VOTE BASED ON THE CLUES
"Underworld Life Insurance
Application Review Form."
To be the culprit in today's case,
they had to have known in detail
about the insurance scam
Cho Yo-sep was committing
by killing his wives.
That's why I thought
the prime suspects were Jang Buddy
and Hwang Billionaire.
However, my opinion changed after we found
the apology letter in Cho Yo-sep's wallet.
Jang Neighbor knew
that Cho Yo-sep had taken out
an insurance policy in his wife's name.
Also, Cho Yo-sep was the one
who put him in real danger
that could've cost him his life.
His life was saved back then
by the homeless people.
Simply put, the homeless
are the most significant part of his life.
He truly dedicated his life
to the homeless.
The thing that likely angered him most
was the fire started by Cho Yo-sep.
The homeless people
who once saved his life
lost theirs because of this lunatic.
"Did you really have to take everything?"
Cho Yo-sep!
Cho Yo-sep was more than
just someone he wanted to kill.
By leaving his dead body
in the drainage channel
where the homeless took shelter,
he was consoling the souls
of those unjustly killed.
I don't want to vote for you.
But I'm afraid I have no choice.
It was you.
KIM DETECTIVE AND JANG BUDDY
CHOSE JANG NEIGHBOR
What a shame. I'm sorry.
JANG NEIGHBOR: 2, JANG BUDDY: 1
I'm still on the fence.
Why did Cho Yo-sep
drive to the Hangang Bridge
and stop at that exact spot?
Why was the body dumped
at the drainage channel?
Why fish his wet body out of the water
just to leave it at the drainage channel?
While the killer
might've intended to hide the body,
I believe they needed to
find something Yo-sep was carrying.
What could be the thing that was missing?
Maybe it was the finger
he wanted to collect, but couldn't.
RE-EXAMINING THE GLASS TUBES
USED TO STORE THE FINGERS
Why is this cracked?
As I inspected the glass tubes
that housed the souvenirs,
I found that one of them was cracked.
The section of fabric under that tube
had faded to white,
probably because some liquid
had leaked from it.
Could this cracked glass tube
have been damaged during the car crash?
Could this be the item
he was trying to retrieve?
Hwang Billionaire
would've climbed out of the trunk
and used the car to run Yo-sep over,
pushing him into the river.
Then he would've checked the storm drain,
only to discover the finger wasn't there.
After a moment of panic,
he would've soon realized
that Cho Yo-sep must have it.
That's why he fished the body out,
brought it to the drainage channel,
and found the finger right then and there.
The finger belonging to Noh Homeless.
There's no escaping
my investigative skills.
My investigative skills
deserve five stars.
The culprit is…
you.
JANG NEIGHBOR AND PARK KARA
CHOSE HWANG BILLIONAIRE
JANG NEIGHBOR: 2,
JANG BUDDY: 1, HWANG BILLIONAIRE: 2
The watch.
What I find most suspicious
is the watch.
Was this watch…
Did he take it from Yo-sep's house,
or did he kill him first
and then retrieve it
from the drainage channel?
There's no way to tell.
Second Marriage was the love of his life
and the mother of his unborn child.
If he had found out the watch
she meant to give him
was in the hands of her killer,
he wouldn't have been in his right mind.
Fueled by rage,
Jang Buddy would've texted Cho Yo-sep,
hinting that he knew everything,
and lured him to the place
where Second Marriage had died.
He would've stayed hidden in the trunk,
moved up to the driver's seat,
and ran Cho Yo-sep over.
After hiding the body
at the fairly deserted drainage channel,
he would've taken back the watch
Second Marriage had meant to give him.
I believe Buddy Jang…
is the culprit.
HWANG BILLIONAIRE CHOSE BUDDY JANG
JANG NEIGHBOR: 2,
JANG BUDDY: 2, HWANG BILLIONAIRE: 2
WHO WILL AN MARRY CHOOSE?
All right. Let's do this.
-It was you.
FINAL VOTE COMPLETE
The third episode of the deduction game,
Crime Scene Zero.
The results of the nail-biting
deduction game to find the culprit
of the murder on the Hangang Bridge.
Let's see who received the most votes
as the real culprit.
We will now announce the results.
Let's do this.
-I hope you made the right choice.
-Please.
I hope you were paying attention
to my last remarks.
(A HALF-HEARTED NOD)
It was pretty obvious, if you ask me.
Don't you trust Kim Detective,
the detective with the most swagger?
-I don't.
-Come on now.
I think we're screwed.
First, we will announce
who was excluded
from the final list of suspects.
The results of the final vote
to determine the culprit are as follows.
With zero votes…
Park Kara
and An Marry,
you are excluded from the final lineup.
-Just the two of them?
-Are you serious?
Only two were excluded?
-Dang, we're definitely screwed.
-Only two?
And so,
Hwang Billionaire,
Jang Neighbor, and Jang Buddy
were identified as suspects.
Unbelievable.
Don't tell me two suspects
received the same number of votes.
The ultimate deduction game,
Crime Scene Zero.
The results of the final vote
of the murder on the Hangang Bridge.
The player who was ultimately identified
as the culprit is…
Please.
-In a three to two to two split…
-Three to two?
Three to two to two?
…the player with three votes is…
Jang Buddy.
No! We're screwed!
…Jang Buddy.
Wait, what? Did I hear that right?
Did you say Jang Buddy?
Jang Buddy, you've been identified
as the final suspect.
Please enter the jail.
You fools!
You're all so frustrating.
I practically spelled it out for you!
What's wrong?
-You…
-I…
-Who are you even talking about?
-Hold on.
A three to two to two split?
Which two people voted for him?
-Wait, a three to two to two split?
-Wait, what?
I can't believe this. Hold on.
-I can't believe you people. You idiots!
-What's going on?
Is it not him?
-Seriously.
-Today's a hot mess.
-Was it Mr. Five Viscera and Six Entrails?
-The real issue is that the culprit
-likely won the whole pot this time.
-You were all fooled.
Ten million won?
The players who voted for Jang Buddy,
Kim Detective,
An Marry,
and Hwang Billionaire,
please step forward.
I voted for him in the first round.
Marry, I have to ask,
so give it to me straight.
-Why do you think I did it?
-Just wait it out.
I'll explain my decision
once the culprit is revealed,
Mr. Buddy.
Wait, did you do it?
It's not you, is it?
If Jang Buddy is the real culprit,
An Marry and Hwang Billionaire
will each win two million won,
and Kim Detective
will win one million won.
-I refuse to take the money.
-This is better than the alternative.
If Jang Buddy is not the culprit,
the real killer will claim the prize money
of all other players,
a total of ten million won.
-I was fooled!
-Over my dead body.
-I'll steal the money.
-But it all fits.
-Detective, hand over your badge already.
-I'll kill them.
He has to be the culprit.
-The third episode
-I think it is Buddy.
of the ultimate deduction game,
Crime Scene Zero.
Jang Buddy has been voted as the culprit
in the murder on the Hangang Bridge.
Is he really the culprit
who killed Cho Yo-sep?
Mr. Jang Buddy.
Are you…
Come on, please.
…Cho Yo-sep's killer?
No, he's not!
I told you so!
You complete idiots!
-No, he's not!
-I told you so!
FIRST FAILED APPREHENSION
ON CRIME SCENE ZERO
You complete idiots!
I told you. I'm Kim Detective,
the detective with the most swagger.
-Seriously?
-Was my swagger too much for you to trust?
-I dropped plenty of hints!
-It was you, Mr. Billionaire.
Why would it be me?
It was Mr. Billionaire.
-It wasn't me.
-It was Mr. Billionaire.
-I dropped countless hints. You idiots!
-Why would it be me? It's not.
The culprit
-who masterfully deceived you all is…
-Was it Jang Neighbor?
-Hwang Billionaire!
-I told you so!
-…Hwang Billionaire!
No way.
Give up your badge right now.
No, wait! She's not done.
Surely there's more to the story.
-You don't deserve your badge.
-So what about Hwang Billionaire?
I feel so betrayed.
You've got to be kidding me.
As such, the real killer,
Mr. Hwang Billionaire,
claims the prize money
of all other players,
a total of ten million won.
HWANG BILLIONAIRE CLAIMS
THE PRIZE MONEY OF 10 MILLION WON
-This is crazy.
-Hold on. Did I hear that correctly?
He's a scary guy.
What was that?
He claims the prize money
of all other players.
-Are you sure you said that right?
-Thank you.
-You fool.
-Hold on.
-Wait.
-Mr. Jang Stone Bed.
-There's no way.
You killed him.
-Jeez, I can't believe you.
-Our detective is hopeless.
You killed him!
-You got me confused!
-You killed him!
This is all Kim Detective's fault.
All of this happened
because of Kim Detective.
IDIOT DETECTIVE
Confess already!
We'll now announce
-the key piece of evidence you missed.
-What could we have missed?
I'm dying to know.
-What was it?
-Out with it.
-The finger?
-His hand?
You didn't look closely enough.
-What is it?
-I checked everywhere.
You want us to continue investigating?
CHO YO-SEP'S BODY?
AND…
One's cracked.
Exactly. One of them is cracked.
The contents leaked
and whitened the fabric beneath.
You saw how all the fingers I had
were well preserved, right?
To keep them that way,
they need to be submerged in formalin
since it acts as a preservative.
THE LEAKED FORMALIN
CAUSED THE DISCOLORATION
Check his pocket.
-This one?
-Yes.
What about it?
THE LINING OF HIS POCKET
IS ALSO DISCOLORED
Does this mean Cho Yo-sep
had the tube in his pocket?
Yes, in this very pocket.
CHO YO-SEP TOOK THE GLASS TUBE
FROM THE STORM DRAIN
This is shocking.
No one picked up on that.
HWANG BILLIONAIRE COLLECTED IT
AFTER KILLING HIM
Man, you're something else.
IF ONLY WE HAD CHECKED HIS POCKET CLOSELY…
This was a tough case to crack.
How could you?
I'm retiring as a detective.
KIM DETECTIVE
IDIOT
The killer was impressive today.
-Lucky you.
-He did a solid job.
THE FULL STORY BEHIND
THE MURDER ON THE HANGANG BRIDGE
During his time with the Hangang River
Water Rescue Team,
Hwang Billionaire
often went on solo missions,
earning resentment
from his fellow team members.
Hidden beneath his headstrong behavior
was an ugly secret.
He was addicted
to a twisted hobby of finding thrill
in watching the life slip away
from drowning victims
as they struggled underwater.
Then one day,
he headed out on yet another
solo rescue mission,
following a report that a woman
had jumped into the river.
Just as he was about to watch her
take her final breath,
he saw a group of men
sprinting toward her to rescue her.
Reacting swiftly,
he saved the woman instead.
As it turned out,
she was the only daughter
of the Heaven Sent Group chaebol family.
In a stroke of luck, Hwang Billionaire
not only became a hero who saved her life
but also won her heart
and ended up marrying her.
This ultimately secured him
the vice presidency at Heaven Sent Group.
However,
his father-in-law's blatant disdain
for a son-in-law of such humble origins
placed Hwang Billionaire
under immense stress.
He decided to relieve himself
by embracing the hobby
he had long turned away from.
He hired a contract killer
to record snuff films of victims
and to cut off their fingers
that symbolize their final moments
before drowning.
They made a secret arrangement
where the contractor placed his souvenirs
in the storm drain at a designated time
and received payment
after Hwang Billionaire collected them.
While he endured
the ruthless life in the chaebol family
with the outlet he created,
a rumor began to circulate
about Heaven Sent Group's impending doom
due to the chairman's old age
and the company's declining business.
Hwang Billionaire viewed this
as a chance to secure his footing
in the company.
So he began posting vlogs of him
working as an honorary member
of the Water Rescue Team,
highlighting his heroic and humble image.
Aided by the overwhelming public support
the videos attracted,
he managed to win enough support
within the company as the future chairman.
Behind the success of his vlogs
was his junior colleague, Cho Yo-sep,
who had always treated him with respect
ever since his Water Rescue Team days
and helped film the videos
in any way he could.
Over time, Hwang Billionaire
came to trust Cho Yo-sep deeply.
But one day,
Hwang Billionaire
received a blackmail text.
To garner more views for the vlog,
they hired a temp worker
to pose as a drowning victim
under the false promise of promoting them
to a full-time position.
However, someone used
the secret contract as leverage
to extort money from Hwang Billionaire.
While silencing the blackmailer
with a payoff,
Hwang Billionaire had them tracked down.
His secretary found out
that Cho Yo-sep was the blackmailer.
It turned out Cho Yo-sep
owed billions in gambling debt
and was also suspected of killing
his two former wives
to claim their life insurance payouts
by staging their deaths as accidents.
Consumed by rage,
Hwang Billionaire decided to hire
a contract killer to eliminate Cho Yo-sep.
In the early morning of March 29th
when heavy fine dust and thick fog
kept people indoors,
Hwang Billionaire planned to lure
Cho Yo-sep to Honey Chestnut Island
for the contract killer to eliminate him.
And as per usual, he would be sent
a snuff film along with the finger
as evidence that the task was completed.
At 2:30 a.m.,
while Cho Yo-sep was being dealt with
by the contract killer,
Billionaire arrived at Cho Yo-sep's house
to locate and destroy
the original contract.
Seeing that the door was open,
he entered the garage.
There, he found Cho Yo-sep's wife,
Park So-yun, already cold to the touch.
Hwang Billionaire instinctively knew
she had been killed
like his two former wives
for a life insurance payout.
However, the envelope he found
in the house contained something
even more shocking than the contract
he had been searching for.
They were none other than
photos that exposed
the secret arrangement he had
with his contract killer,
which meant that Cho Yo-sep
could've realized
that he was being targeted.
Though his contract killer sent him a text
confirming that the job was done,
he couldn't shake off his anxiety.
Just then,
he heard a noise coming from the garage.
And what came next was Cho Yo-sep's voice.
As he suspected,
Cho Yo-sep was still alive.
Given how things turned out,
Hwang Billionaire decided that he had to
get rid of Cho Yo-sep himself.
Just as he grabbed a box cutter
from the garage,
he heard Cho Yo-sep approaching
and quickly hid inside the car trunk.
The car soon took off,
headed for its destination.
Moments later, he heard the car stop
and Cho Yo-sep get out.
He pulled the lever
and climbed out to the back seat.
The car was on the Hangang Bridge,
and Cho Yo-sep
was searching the storm drain
that held evidence of a murder.
Hwang Billionaire
moved to the driver's seat immediately
and drove the car
straight toward Cho Yo-sep.
Fallen over from the impact,
Cho Yo-sep tried to pull himself up
by grabbing the guardrail.
Hwang Billionaire then reversed the car
and launched it again,
hitting him even harder this time.
The force of the collision
deployed the airbag,
causing Hwang Billionaire
to briefly lose consciousness.
When he came to,
he saw that the car was sitting
on the edge of the bridge
while Park So-yun's body
in the passenger seat
was thrown out through the windshield.
He quickly got out of the car
to search the storm drain,
but there was nothing inside.
Down in the river,
he saw Park So-yun's body caught on a buoy
and Cho Yo-sep's body drifting away
with the current.
He quickly climbed down
the ladder on the bridge,
jumped into the river,
pulled Cho Yo-sep's body out,
and dragged it to the drainage channel
in the reed field.
From the pocket
of the deceased Cho Yo-sep,
he retrieved the glass tube
with the finger and the snuff film,
leaving the body concealed
in the drainage channel.
Then, he returned to the crash site
on the Hangang Bridge
and planned to make the crash appear
as another one of Cho Yo-sep's scams
to receive an insurance payout
by killing his wife, Park So-yun.
The thick fine dust and fog
would provide a plausible cover
for the scam to have gone fatally wrong.
Using the emergency hammer,
he smashed the windshield
on the driver's side
and ripped the airbag
with the box cutter from the garage,
staging the crash
to appear as a car defect.
He also tore the seat belt
to make it look like
it had been damaged in the accident.
After staging the crime scene,
Hwang Billionaire returned to his office.
He threw his wet clothes in a trash dump,
replaced the glass tube that had shattered
in the crash with a new one,
and stored the finger with the snuff film
in a hidden compartment in his cabinet,
all the while hoping
that his secret would be buried forever
along with Cho Yo-sep's death.
An Dancer…
How can a dancer be so bad at dancing?
My love for Gold Spoon is real.
I don't get why she keeps coming on to me.
Ms. Park Whole Chicken.
-How dare you?
-She's a bit rough.
-Please, not your right fist.
-Save it for later.
I found him very suspicious.
-Mr. Kim Club.
-I could just…
Why, you little! I didn't see anything.
He was even worse than I thought.
The person who surprised me the most
was Jang C-store.
Wait, you don't know?
He's 27.
-Stay out of this, will you?
-I don't know, you brat.
The grown-ups are talking!
Everyone seemed so suspicious.
That Mr. Gold Spoon's
being really sketchy.
Let me explain.
Explain what? Don't bother.
-We already know everything.
-We don't need it.
You can head down now. Let's go.
-Let's check someplace else.
-I'm disappointed.
We got it. We're good.
Subtitle translation by: Yenny Kang