♫ Raising the wine cup, I toast to the boundless sky ♫
♫ In talks and laughters are vast mountains and rivers. ♫
♫ Love and hate, debt and feuds, have all dissolved. ♫
♫ Where's my soul's hometown and my kindred spirits? ♫
♫ Seasons rolling by, we dream for harvest. ♫
♫ Warriors and warhorses howl across the sky. ♫
♫ If only I could turn into the wind, ♫
♫ to blow away all the pain in mortal coil. ♫
♫ I toast to the blue sky, to courage in solitude, ♫
♫ to migrating gooses, to boats heading home. ♫
♫ With even three thousand days and nights, ♫
♫ Will it be enough to drain this cup I toast to peace? ♫
[Swords into Plowshares]
[Episode 36]
Commander of the Imperial Guard, Qian Hongjun,
is appointed Military Governor of the Weiwu Army and Acting Grand Guardian,
overseeing all military affairs and concurrently
in charge of defending the Western Prefecture.
You will assist Minister Yuan in remaining at Hangzhou.
I obey.
Lord Hu,
you are appointed Commander of the Northern Jiangdong Campaign
and shall act as Deputy Marshal of all military forces.
I obey.
Chancellor Wu Cheng.
Yes.
You are appointed Inspector of
the Northern Jiangdong Campaign,
overseeing all provisions, armor, weapons, and supply logistics.
I obey.
Mobilize the Personal Guards, Imperial Guards,
Zhongzhi, Kuangwu  the Cifei, Left and Right Hall and other,
all twenty-three Companies to accompany my carriage.
I
will personally campaign north of the River.
All victories to the King!
What time is it now?
It is the hour of Zi.
Tea.
Lord Feng.
Tea helps to clear the eyes.
Lord, why must you torment yourself like this?
His Majesty's will is hard as steel.
He is no ordinary ruler content with mere preservation.
If he wishes to lead the campaign himself, then let him.
Why must you, Lord,
be so hard on your own health?
Ten years ago,
Shi Chonggui personally campaigned in Hebei.
Back then,
didn't you all think the same way?
That was completely different!
It is indeed different.
The Shi father and son, like the Zhu father and son and the Li father and son,
all of them,
seized their empire from the saddle.
They thought
that with their long spears and swords,
they could carve out an era of peace.
Fine words in a dream.
The Guo father and son,
were different from them.
They desired an era of peace for this entire realm.
That is why they took the throne.
Since I entered official service,
I have served ten emperors.
There were some like Emperor Li,
ambitious and heroic rulers of great vision.
There were also those like Shi Jingtang,
men of supreme cunning.
But only the Guo father and son
kept the words 'peace and prosperity' close to their hearts.
I
am old now.
I cannot stop His Majesty from
insisting on personally campaigning in Hedong.
But I can cling to life long enough
to guard Bianliang well for His Majesty.
I will stake this old body
and gamble one more time.
If I win this gamble,
I can then
close my eyes and pass away in peace.
If I am to lose the gamble,
it is nothing more than
this Central Plains getting another emperor
from a different family.
And it is nothing more than
me,
dying with my eyes open.
Lord!
Do your duties.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
Lord Feng is truly unwell.
He cannot bear the cold.
[Zhou's military camp in Bagongyuan, Luzhou]
Report!
Your Majesty!
The Southern Tang general Liu Renshan leads
a hundred thousand troops from Shouzhou to attack Huaibei.
Their spearhead points directly at Songzhou.
Lord Feng has issued a Hall Order. The capital is
under martial law, and all commercial travel is prohibited.
Your Majesty.
South of Songzhou, our army at Yingzhou and Suqian
has established two major Huaibei camps.
They are garrisoned with elite troops and
fine generals, commanded by my father
and the old Marshal Yao Yuanfu, who lead the defense.
It's absolutely impossible for the Southern Tang rebels to take Songzhou easily.
If Songzhou falls, my father and I, of the Zhao family,
are willing to accept capital punishment.
Good!
On your word alone,
if Songzhou does not fall this time,
I will grant this land to you and your father.
Thank you for your great grace.
This is where the Zhou army's Huaibei left camp
central command is stationed.
The defending general is named Zhao Hongyin.
He holds the titles of Yuezhou Defense Commissioner,
Right Company Commander of the Iron Cavalry,
and Commander of the Western Huainan Campaign.
He is fifty-four years old, from Zhuozhou, Hebei.
[Liu Renzhan, Military Governor of Qinghuai Army]
He's a tough rival, not easy to deal with.
This Zhao Hongyin has blocked the wells, destroyed the houses,
and set up camp here, blocking the main road.
This shows he is resolved to fight us to the death.
He seeks a noble death and shall have it.
We shall grant his wish.
The entire army will rest for three days.
In three days, we fight a decisive battle.
Yes, sir!
Report!
[Zhou's military camp in North Huai, Yingzhou]
Marshal, the enemy has retreated five li to make camp.
Leave.
Yes, sir!
Father-in-law,
[He Jingsi, Inspector of Western South Huai Campaign]
no, Marshal,
Liu Renshan is a renowned general.
Retreating five li to camp
means he intends to face us head-on
in a proper battle formation.
The enemy outnumbers us nine to one.
At most,
we can only hold out for a little over twenty days.
Liu Renshan
does not have twenty days.
[Southern Tang's military camp]
Bottoms up!
Come on!
Good wine!
Come on, eat up!
Come on!
What's that over there?
You must be desiring for women.
There's fog on the river.
A sow could look like a beauty through it.
You lot, what's all this noise about?
Head,
Squad Leader, head, look!
[King Qian of Kingdom of Wuyue,
Grand Marshal of All Armies and Secretariat Director]
[Southern Tang's camp in North Huai, Yingzhou]
In today's battle,
all troops must advance without retreat.
Advance, and you live.
Retreat, and you die.
Marshal!
This official has urgent news.
Speak.
The Qian of Wuyue has mobilized
its entire army against our border.
Runzhou is in peril.
The capital is in panic.
His Majesty has issued an edict, summoning you to withdraw
and return to court to repel the southern forces.
Academician, do you treat military affairs as child's play?
Marshal, please calm down.
Wuyue's army of over a hundred thousand has cut across
the Yangtze and attacks Runzhou fiercely.
Our southern front lacks troops; this is the true condition.
His Majesty
summoning you to withdraw is a last resort.
They are trying to besiege Runzhou to rescue Zhou.
The ministers in power are all wise men;
how could they be deceived by it?
Marshal,
the state's main forces
are all with you on the northern campaign.
The southern counties and prefectures garrison troops
number less than forty thousand.
It is truly
a case of no meal without rice.
I beg you, Marshal,
to obey the edict and withdraw.
Academician, you should know:
a general in the field may not always
obey his sovereign's command.
This is the golden token personally granted by His Majesty.
His Majesty decrees
that if you stubbornly refuse to obey the edict,
he commands me to use this golden token
to reclaim your seals for military authority.
Liu Renshan has withdrawn his troops?
I dare not lie.
We have verified it thoroughly.
All twenty-eight enemy encampments are now empty.
No baggage, cooking gear, or other items remain.
They have truly retreated.
This...
I told you
Liu Renshan would not have twenty days.
King Qian has sent his troops.
They have besieged Runzhou and cut off the Yangtze.
The Tang ruler urgently ordered Liu Renshan to turn back.
The threat to North Huai is over.
Lord Feng asks:
is there any military news from the Gaoping front?
The Liao commander of Yunzhong,
Yelü Dilu, leading thirty thousand cavalry,
arrived at Gaoping the day before yesterday
and joined the Northern Han ruler.
His Majesty's imperial camp forces number twenty thousand.
The enemy outnumbers us
three to one.
[Zhang Yongde]
Your Majesty,
He Hui and Fan Aineng, those two traitors,
forged Your Majesty's verbal order
and led the left and rear armies in retreat.
Before the battle even started, ten thousand of our twenty thousand fled.
One to three became one to six.
How do we fight this?
We should protect Your Majesty and retreat south
of Shengyuan Valley first.
If the main army retreats, the enemy will surely give chase.
Then no one will escape.
We must leave a force to cover the retreat.
I beg Your Majesty to take the center and
vanguard and retreat slowly.
I will lead the right army to hold the rear.
Even if I sacrifice this body,
I vow to keep the main Han forces pinned here.
Do you take me
for an emperor raised by women in a deep palace?
I would never.
You would sacrifice your body.
Do you think I have none to sacrifice?
Do you all
have no bodies to sacrifice?
You ask me to retreat.
Where should I retreat to?
Across the great river?
Back to the capital?
An emperor who abandons his comrades
on the battlefield and flees alone
is no emperor at all!
When I was in the capital,
I saw an emperor stripped bare, leading a sheep.
I also saw
a grandson who lived in abject survival
under the Khitans' iron heels.
I will not be that kind of emperor,
nor will I be that kind of grandson!
Zhao Kuangyin!
Yes!
Back on the walls of Bianliang,
facing the banner of the Khitan emperor Yelü Deguang,
were you afraid?
I was never afraid!
Nor was I ever afraid!
Before Emperor Taizong of Great Liao,
Kuangyin and I could stand tall and face him.
A mere Liu Chong,
a mere Yelü Dilu,
what are they?!
Do you think,
I should bow to them?
No!
Zhao Kuangyin!
Yes!
Bring me my sword!
I intend to take the old traitor Liu Chong's center.
Will you be my vanguard?
I would do it even at the cost of my life!
Your Majesty!
The two traitors, He Hui and Fan Aineng,
have been captured and returned to camp.
Please pass judgment, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty!
I lost my head and made a grave mistake.
I am willing to die in battle
[He Hui, Commander of Infantry]
to atone for my crime.
[Fan Aineng, Commander of Calvery]
Your Majesty!
I am also willing to die in battle,
to serve as your vanguard,
to recapture Taiyuan for you,
to atone for my crime.
Die in battle?
Serve as my vanguard?
Do you
deserve to?
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, have mercy!
Spare our lives!
Spare us!
Your Majesty, spare us!
If I spared you today,
how could I face these soldiers who died as my vanguard,
who sacrificed their bodies on the battlefield?
I am not afraid of Liu Chong, nor am I afraid of Yelü Dilu.
And I am even less afraid of you,
who for decades have let your troops wreak havoc,
you arrogant, domineering, unruly generals!
Drag them out and execute them!
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, spare us! Your Majesty!
Your Majesty...
The Khitan troops have really retreated?
Really retreated.
This Liu Chong,
collapsed too quickly.
And this Yelü Dilu, he simply didn't react in time.
He stood there dumbfounded,
watching the whole day's spectacle.
Liu Chong had many troops.
I had few.
He never imagined
that I could, in one battle, rout Liu Chong.
He was afraid I would die.
If I had died on the battlefield this time,
the Central Plains would, in less than a month,
install another emperor.
Who would be so bold?
Lord Feng.
He didn't want to let me lead the campaign
precisely because he feared my death at the front.
Then he would have to install another emperor.
The old man didn't want that.
Having watched for decades,
having seen nine rulers change,
he didn't want to change again.
Lord!
Lord, look!
Your Majesty has won, he's won!
At Gaoping, he killed Wang Tingsi, Northern Han's Chief of the Privy Council.
Liu Chong fled to Jinyang with only a few hundred men.
Lord!
Lord, your final memorial...
You speak a sentence, and I will write a sentence.
Honored Ministers,
my father says
this
is his final memorial.
[The census tally of households and population for
all prefectures and counties, Xiande First Year]
Lord...
Feng Dao died in the first year of the Xiande period,
at the age of seventy-three.
He served four dynasties and ten emperors,
holding the position of Chancellor for twenty-seven years.
He was a veritable political survivor of the Five Dynasties.
Amid the frequent regime changes and chaotic times,
Feng Dao's presence to a certain extent maintained
the stability of the ruling order
and the continuity of court decrees.
He was highly revered and respected by his contemporaries.
However,
later evaluations of him are polarized.
The Old History of the Five Dynasties questions:
"Serving four dynasties and six emperors as chancellor,
can he be considered loyal?"
Ouyang Xiu denounced him as "shameless."
Yet, thinkers like Li Zhi believed he "put the state first,"
saving the common people from turmoil.
Feng Dao's life experiences and
the mixed praise and criticism he later received
are precisely a true reflection of the tumultuous era
of the Five Dynasties and Ten Kingdoms.
Lord Feng, may your spirit return home.
We humbly request Your Majesty to return to the capital.
Kuangyin,
you and the Emperor may share a bond like brothers,
but the distinction between sovereign
and subject is now set.
You must not act as carelessly as before.
You must strictly uphold your duties as a subject.
Don't worry, Father.
I know what to do.
Currently,
the old Imperial Guards and
the Hedong military governors' elites,
have bloated ranks and
a chaotic military structure.
To dismiss redundant soldiers and train a new army,
we can only proceed gradually,
setting a ten-year time frame to progressively
dismiss and merge them.
Within three years,
this must be accomplished.
I intend to, establish another military administration office
in addition to the Imperial Guard Command.
It shall be called the Palace Guard Command.
Hear my decree:
I, having received the Mandate and the charts,
rule over this land, concerned with military affairs.
Now that the realm finds initial peace and
the provinces gradually prosper,
yet the malpractices in military administration,
long accumulated, remain unresolved.
Troop numbers are excessive, filled with the old and weak.
This is a true worry for the state.
Therefore, I specially establish the Palace Guards
to manage the new army.
I appoint Zhang Yongde as Inspector
and Zhao Kuangyin as Commander.
Dismiss the old and weak, inspect troop numbers,
rectify the ranks, select officers.
Ensure that the new army of the Palace Command
internally manages the guard,
serving as the personal guard of the court.
Externally defending the borders,
it shall be the pillar of the state,
mighty as thunder, imposing as bears and leopards.
All officers and soldiers must strictly obey this decree
without any disobedience.
Proclaim this to all,
so that all may hear it.
Who are you putting on this act for?
What?
Don't want to be the Commander?
I'm just a fighting man.
I only understand matters on the battlefield.
I'm afraid I won't do it well.
Are these words your own,
or is this your father's idea?
Rong,
they are my sincere words.
Get up.
The ground is cold.
The census tally of households and population for all prefectures and counties...
This?
This is Lord Feng's posthumous memorial.
The realm has been in chaos for too long,
so long that no one at court remembers
to conduct a proper census.
The last time
a census of households and adult males was taken
was before the Huang Chao Rebellion.
A hundred years ago.
It wasn't until last year that the late emperor
and Lord Feng deliberated
and initiated this effort again,
to conduct a census across the realm.
Kuangyin.
Do you know
in the fourth year of Qianfu,
how many people the Great Tang had?
No.
Four point nine six million households,
eleven million adult males,
twenty-five million total population.
Do you know how many there are now?
No.
Look.
Nine hundred sixty thousand households,
two point three eight million adult males,
four million, eight hundred sixty-eight thousand
total population.
So few?
The Imperial Guard stationed in the capital,
the Left and Right Wings of the Husheng Army,
the regional and garrison troops from various places,
plus the personal troops and retinues
of the military governors...
The total number of registered troops
is three hundred sixty-three thousand,
six hundred and sixty-eight.
That's one soldier drafted from every seven adult males.
Almost every household has to support one soldier.
They cannot afford it.
Tell me, in the Battle of Gaoping,
where we defeated Liu Chong,
how many troops from our entire army did we actually use?
After Generals He and Fan fled,
fewer than eleven thousand men remained.
And those who could truly fight to the death
numbered less than seven thousand.
The state supports eighty-eight thousand registered troops.
Even if I assume half are missing from the rolls,
that's forty-four thousand.
Yet in a time of crisis,
only seven thousand were usable.
Is this still a viable state?
This is clearly a volcano.
Ever since I inherited this mess,
I've realized how difficult it was for the late emperor
and Lord Feng those years.
Kuangyin,
are you willing to help me?
Within Bianliang, the Imperial Guard numbers
over two hundred thousand.
Add the Hedong garrison elites to that,
Each man must be supplied annually with one set of
summer clothes and one set of winter clothes.
Each month,
according to rank, they receive grain and pay.
A minimum of thirty thousand cash per month,
and fifteen dan of grain.
Many Imperial Guards have families with them,
incurring additional household expenses.
Just the expenditure on personnel and horses
alone is a burden the court can barely bear.
Not to mention the costs of military supplies and rewards,
among other various expenses.
Annual expenditures never fall below seven million strings of cash.
Therefore, the current priority is to reduce the army, not to expand it.
Since Emperor Taizu founded our state,
we have faced floods every year and wars every year.
The state's finances are strained.
I urge Your Majesty to cut military numbers
to nurture the people.
According to established custom,
when a new ruler ascends,
he should reward the armies to boost morale and unity.
How can one not reward but instead dismiss,
offend the military,
and cause resentment among the troops?
Moreover, the Palace Guard is newly established.
Its funding should be increased
to boost morale.
Even if we intend to reduce troop numbers,
now is not the time, is it?
Commander Zhao Kuangyin.
I'm here.
In your opinion,
should military expenditures
be increased
or decreased?
I believe
that the truly capable and combat-ready soldiers
do not care about such trivial matters.
What soldiers care about is only,
injustice.
That is all.
[Zhao Kuangyin's residence]
My master has prepared a modest gift.
Please, young man, pass it on for us.
Please pass it on for us.
This is a token of our regard for the Marshal. Please help us.
This is a humble gift from my superior. Please announce us.
Please do us this favor.
Gentlemen, gentlemen!
The Marshal has not yet returned to the residence.
Please return.
May I ask when the Marshal will return?
Let us see him.
I really don't know.
We will wait here for the Marshal.
Then please accept the gifts first.
Yes, yes, the gifts.
I truly cannot make that decision.
Brother.
In just half a day, the news of your promotion to Commander
[Zhao Kuangyi, Chief Palace Steward]
has spread throughout the city.
Those officers from various armies
[Zhao Kuangyi, Chief Palace Steward]
who are active in currying favor and seeking advancement
have completely filled the entire street in front of our gate.
Back then,
when Father was promoted to Commander of the Imperial Guard,
it wasn't as grand and glorious as this.
If Father heard what you just said,
he would surely slap your face.
In success,
do not become arrogant.
All the glory of today is sowing the seeds for future disaster.
Those people waiting outside the gate
are not here to congratulate you.
They are here to harm you.
Do you understand?
Don't worry, Father.
I know what I'm doing.
These people outside,
I can handle them.
Are you full, Father?
Kuangyin,
Kuangyi,
have your meal.
Kuangyin, now that you're in favor with the Emperor,
you can't forget us, your old comrades.
Kuangyin,
what exactly are the rules of this Palace Guard?
Does Marshal Zhang have the final say, or the Emperor himself?
Comrades in the army always side with kin, not reason.
Kuangyin,
just give us a clear word,
and we'll go through rivers and fire for you.
We, the scions of military families in the
Imperial Guard, have always been united.
We can't let those outsiders
from the regional garrisons take advantage.
A new army, a new atmosphere.
The monthly pay should be higher than that
of the Imperial Guard and other camps, right?
The Emperor's personal guard—
[Left: Liu Tingrang, West Palace Steward]
the selection and promotion of officers
[Middle: Wang Zhengzhong, Right Guard]
should naturally take precedence
[Right: Liu Shouzhong, Right Security Officer]
over other armies.
The Palace Guard Command is a new office.
Its rules are strict, its discipline severe.
The fifty-four capital offenses—
every single one will be strictly enforced.
There will be drills every five days, inspections every ten.
[Left: Yang Guangyi; Right: Shi Shouxin]
Anyone who violates regulations
will be dismissed and have their pay reduced.
[Left: Liu Qingyi, Left Guard]
[Right: Han Chongyun, Left Security Officer]
[Left: Li Jixun]
[Right: Wang Shenqi, Leader of the East and West Guard Squad]
If you want promotion, it must be discussed and agreed
by both the Eastern and Western Bureaus,
and finally submitted to His Majesty for personal approval.
Once selected,
without leave granted by the Emperor,
no one, no officer, is permitted to leave camp privately.
Even I,
the Commander in charge,
am no exception.
It cannot compare to
the carefree and easy life in the Imperial Guard.
Given these conditions,
gentlemen, do you still want to
break your heads trying to squeeze in?
It's not about breaking our heads to squeeze in,
but that even if we lose our heads,
we will loyally serve His Majesty to the death!
We stand with you, Kuangyin!
We stand with you!
Is this the Palace Guard Command?
Whose government office is so dilapidated, in such a wretched state?
Don't you all see it clearly?
Someone is trying to give Kuangyin a slap in the face!
What are you all standing around for?
Get to work!
Your Majesty, this is the draft regulations for
the Palace Command proposed by the two chancellors and I.
Additionally, here is the roster for the appointment and evaluation of officers at all levels.
Zhang Yongde.
Accompany me for a walk.
Bring the roster.
Yes.
I will not look at your draft regulations for now.
Your Majesty!
Think you're the most diligent, huh?
Am I not?
Kuangyin,
you have been wronged.
You honor me too much, Your Majesty.
Yang Guangyi,
I know you, lad.
Who are they?
Imperial Guard Officer, Li Jixun.
Leader of the East and West Squads, Wang Shenqi.
Left Secur Officer, Han Chongyun.
Imperial Guard, Deputy Commander of the Left Wing, Shi Shouxin.
Very good, very good.
Starting tomorrow, you will all report for duty at the Palace Command
and await Kuangyin's orders.
Yes, Your Majesty!
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Regarding cutting military expenditures:
The capital's Imperial Guard,
from seven million strings of cash reduced to five million.
The armies of each garrison,
from five hundred thousand reduced to three hundred thousand.
Those with less than three hundred thousand will not be reduced.
Approved.
The capital's Imperial Guard: five million strings.
The Palace Command: three million.
The Imperial Guard, two million.
Your Majesty!
In previous years, the Imperial Guard's expenses
were around seven million strings.
Now suddenly reduced to less than two million...
Even if we cut the troops by half, it would be unsustainable.
Morale will surely collapse.
I fear sudden calamities will arise within the capital.
Your Majesty, since the fall of the Tang,
generals and soldiers have grown increasingly arrogant.
Even if Your Majesty wishes to reform military affairs,
it should be done gradually.
Acting so hastily,
I fear there may be
another Xingjiaomen Incident.
I implore Your Majesty to consider carefully.
We implore Your Majesty to consider carefully!
Your Majesty,
when reducing troop numbers, it should
be done impartially, without favoring one over another.
Your Majesty,
military reform has always been a slow and meticulous process.
It should be carried out calmly and steadily.
One cannot expect immediate success;
it must not be rushed.
I ask you, my ministers,
to proclaim on my behalf to all the armies:
Tell those soldiers
that the current Emperor
is but a
commoner whose entire family was slaughtered,
a man with no father and no home.
If anyone wishes to rebel or start a revolt,
just come.
I will be sitting right here in the Daning Palace waiting.
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles
stretch towering mountains. ♫
run surging rivers. ♫
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles
cry warhorses. ♫
there are emotions unspoken. ♫
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles,
flowers are blooming along the road. ♫
gooses are returning to the north. ♫
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles,
we stand through storms. ♫
we hope for a safe return. ♫
♫ Tens of thousands of miles is not enough, ♫
♫ for a lifetime's sorrows and joys. ♫
♫ for the endless seas and rivers. ♫
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles, ♫
♫ love will overcome all barriers. ♫
♫ we are together in life and death. ♫
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles. ♫
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles, ♫
♫ the moon shines in the boundless world. ♫
♫ My heart has its hometown to return. ♫
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles, ♫
♫ who is the one crossing the waves with me, ♫
♫ with our hearts unrepentant,
through countless lifetimes. ♫
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles, ♫
♫ oceans and lands witness that♫
♫ the world will be safe and sound. ♫
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles, ♫
♫ my heart is unchanging. ♫