♫ Raising the wine cup, I toast to the boundless sky ♫
♫ In talks and laughters are vast mountains and rivers. ♫
♫ Love and hate, debt and feuds, have all dissolved. ♫
♫ Where's my soul's hometown and my kindred spirits? ♫
♫ Seasons rolling by, we dream for harvest. ♫
♫ Warriors and warhorses howl across the sky. ♫
♫ If only I could turn into the wind, ♫
♫ to blow away all the pain in mortal coil. ♫
♫ I toast to the blue sky, to courage in solitude, ♫
♫ to migrating gooses, to boats heading home. ♫
♫ With even three thousand days and nights, ♫
♫ Will it be enough to drain this cup I toast to peace? ♫
[Swords into Plowshares]
[Episode 23]
To establish the Trading Office in Taizhou？
What a pipe dream.
Not to mention a mere Prefect of Taizhou.
Even if he became the King of Wuyue, or the emperor, so what?
Those powerful families deeply entrenched and operating
for hundreds or thousands of years in the localities,
how could a young upstart like him shake them?
Since ancient times, saying goes that
a court lasts one century, a gentry clan last ten.
Even the emperor can do nothing about these deeply
rooted, powerful aristocratic families.
They have land and territory.
The court needs to collect taxes, needs to govern the people.
Every single matter cannot be done without them.
To be fair, what Hongchu is to do is indeed an important matter.
In five counties of Taizhou,
over a hundred thousand people crying for food.
If the spring plowing is missed, I'm afraid...
Spare me your grand principles!
What does that hundred thousand people
have to do with our family?
You care about their livelihood, but when events come,
how many of them will remember
our kindness of saving their lives today?
Back in the day,
your grandfather followed King Huang in rebellion.
He too was filled with fervor, determined to restore order,
to sweep away those powerful nobles and families
who fed on the flesh and blood of the nation and its people,
to rescue millions from suffering.
But in the end?
Were the people they wanted to save grateful to them?
After the defeat at Chenzhou, your grandfather led his
personal guards to break the siege and fought a way to Jingnan.
He was cornered on a mountain path
by the local soldiers of the Deng brothers.
Those were also poor men, scraping a living from the soil,
simple farming folk.
They were the very common people
King Huang's manifesto vowed to save.
Those people...
They all acted like madmen.
Swinging axes and knives, shouting slogans:
"Execute Huang Hao!"
"Punish the courtiers!"
"Welcome the imperial edicts!"
You may wish to save them,
but remember this:
one day, when you fall into misfortune,
do not imagine they will repay your kindness.
They will only take your head to
exchange for their wives' titles.
One day,
when you rule this island,
you can choose to serve whichever emperor or king you wish,
or indulge in indiscriminate charity,
saving millions of lives.
It will be up to you.
But as long as I, your mother, am alive,
on this island, I have the final say.
Five hundred thousand hu of grain—
I would rather scatter it to feed dogs.
Dogs have more conscience than people. They will not
bite the hand that feeds them after eating your food.
Elder Sister.
Elder Sister, I don't dare.
I will do it. What are you afraid of?
You know how much Uncle values rules.
This will be fed to the sharks.
If anyone is to be fed to the fish, it will be me.
You were coerced by me, innocent.
Sister.
You can't go there,
That place is the most crucial of all.
Everyone knows the rules.
If you take me with you, I can go in.
Elder Sister. Have you forgotten?
To enter there, you need at least Mother's and Uncle's tokens.
Otherwise, not even Brother can get in.
Go get a token for me.
I don't dare.
If Mother finds out, she will tear me apart.
You don't dare this, you don't dare that.
Come on, come with me.
Elder Sister.
Let's go.
Slow down, Elder Sister.
You!
Sister.
Mother, are you going to do something about this?
Sister!
What is going on? What's the matter?
Away from the island for these years,
even my household registration was canceled?
Taizhen, how can you speak to Mother like that?
Or perhaps, since I left the island,
I am no longer your daughter?
Now on this island, Brother is in charge,
and I, this younger sister, am an outsider.
Who upset you?
What's going on?
I was speaking with Mother,
why did Brother come and lecture me?
If you wanted to lecture me,
why didn't you do it before I was twelve?
This temper of yours is completely uncalled for.
The floor is cold, get up quickly.
Come on.
Did that Qian boy bully you?
If he dared bully me, I would deal with him myself.
There's no need to come to Mother
to complain about those grievances.
He came to the island to borrow grain from you.
If you're willing to lend it, lend it; if not, then don't.
What does that have to do with me?
Back then, when you gave me to him,
you didn't ask me if I was willing.
Now,
all these years later, it's because of him
that even I have become an outsider.
If you all treat him like a thief
to be guarded against, fine, so be it.
Or perhaps, in Mother and Uncle's hearts, I am a thief too?
If that's truly the case, then I won't stay here in your way.
I might as well leave the island, and from now on,
whether I live, die, or flee,
it will have nothing more to do with you.
What kind of madness is this?
This nonsense of yours, who told you such things?
Who said you were an outsider?
Who treats you like a thief to be guarded against?
What on earth is going on?
Elder Sister asked me to take her to Langya Pavilion,
but without Mother's and Uncle's permission, I dare not.
What do you want to do at Langya Pavilion?
Does one need a reason to go?
Must I have something specific to do?
Is that it?
Taizhen.
The rules of the island, you know them as well.
Langya Pavilion is a restricted area.
Without the token from us,
those who enter without permission shall die.
Right.
So,
Eldest Brother can enter, Chengyou can enter,
only I cannot enter.
I simply do not understand.
This temper of yours comes without any reason.
Could it be that because I refused to lend grain to that boy,
I am treating you as an outsider?
And so you must throw a fit to stand up for him?
Is it that I treat you as an outsider,
or is it that your heart turns outward and
treat your own mother as an outsider?
I lived on this island for twelve years.
If you all think that once I left home,
I became an outsider, then tell me directly.
I should not have come back in the first place.
There is no longer a room for me here,
nor any of my belongings, no place for me to stand.
Just say it clearly to me, that's all.
Taizhen, what do these words of yours
have to do with Langya Pavilion?
Uncle.
Just tell me, inside Langya Pavilion, are there any of my things?
Give me an answer and this matter ends here.
I, Taizhen will not say another word about it.
From now on, you will never hear the words
"Langya Pavilion" from my mouth again.
If I break this oath, may gods and men strike me down.
Langya Pavilion is the society's important treasury.
How could there be your...
Mother,
Uncle says there are none of my things inside.
Is that true?
After all this roundabout way, it's all for this matter?
Mother,
you just need to tell me the truth, that's all.
I know that I live too far away and
cannot fulfill my filial duties.
Although no ceremony was held, it's as if I'm married off.
A married woman is an outsider.
If there's nothing, then there's nothing.
I only beg you, Mother, for the sake of our mother-daughter bond,
to bestow upon me the gilded phoenix hairpin
Father left for me.
I will leave the island immediately, and from now on,
I will never worry you again.
What kind of nonsense are you talking about?
I am your birth mother.
You are flesh from my body.
Your matters— even no one else in the world cares about them,
how could I not think of them?
Taizhen, listen to me carefully.
Your elder sister has prepared a dowry for you,
a total of sixty-four loads.
Hairpins, ornaments, ceremonial robes,
cloud-patterned gowns, exquisite cosmetic towers—
just these wearables and accessories
fill a full twelve loads.
They follow the precedent of a princess's marriage.
Besides that, outside Hangzhou city, in your name,
one hundred mu of lakeside silt fields
were bought, and two manors were built.
Additionally, on Maxing Street in the city,
there's a cosmetics shop.
All these were prepared three years ago.
They are all stored in the Langya Pavilion,
and are tended to every few days.
Is Uncle telling the truth?
I'll take you there right now. You can see it with your own eyes.
Does Uncle want to take me to see the dowry,
or does he want to keep an eye on me?
Chengyou,
take the token and take your elder sister to Langya Pavilion.
Let her see whatever she wants.
Don't stop her from seeing anything.
Let her see it to her heart's content.
You!
Come on, go, go an see it!
I'll go take a look now.
Later, later I'll come back to apologize to Mother and Uncle.
How old is she now?
Such a temperament...
Maybe we should ask for less betrothal gifts.
I even feel a bit sorry for that boy.
Elder Sister, I've been asking for a long time,
but you still won't tell me.
What are you doing here?
What are you looking for?
What do you want this for?
Give me a hand.
Quick, help me tie it on.
I've gained a bit of weight lately.
Hurry up!
Alright, fine, fine, fine.
You two,
come here.
Come here!
Miss.
Sorry, you two.
Sister!
What are you looking at? Help out.
Find two sturdy ropes.
What are the ropes for?
To tie them up.
Tie them up?
Hurry up!
This is all we can take.
What is all this stuff?
Xue Wen, quick, move all this onto the boat.
This is...
Hurry up, what are you standing around for?
Move it!
Zhong Wu, Meng Qi, load the boat.
Hurry up, pack your belongs. Set sail tonight.
Sailing at night isn't safe. Better to leave tomorrow morning.
Tomorrow morning will be too late.
We won't be able to leave in another hour.
Sister,
go.
Go, go, go, hurry up, hurry up!
Let's go, pack up.
Sister, you...
Shut up!
What exactly did you steal?
Now is not the time to talk. Anyway, it's something useful.
Chengyou, you go back first.
He cannot go back.
He must come with us.
Leaving a witness behind after stealing things?
You are truly foolish.
Take the sword. Take the sword too.
Elder Sister!
Wait a moment. I suddenly thought of something.
There are still some matters. I'll go and come right back.
Alright. Just go back quickly.
Elder Sister.
Chengyou.
You... you be obedient.
I will take you to Taizhou.
We'll play for a few months, okay?
Okay.
Yes.
Play for a while.
Alright.
Let's go. Play for a few months. Let's go.
Even if you cut the ropes, this ship won't get far.
These warships are the foundation of
Huanglong Island's dominance at sea.
If this foundation is damaged,
it will be hard to ever return.
Elder Brother.
Are you going to stop us?
His father,
is my father.
My mother,
is your mother.
Tell me,
should I stop you?
Since you know what he intends to do,
you don't have to help him,
but I hope you won't ruin his plans.
If I wanted to ruin his plans,
I would have exposed you directly
in front of Mother and Uncle just now.
Thank you, brother.
No matter what you took from the Langya treasury,
it's not worth five hundred thousand hu of grain.
That is our own affair.
Since you do not wish to ruin his plans,
could you please,
let us go?
Leave quickly.
Don't let Hongchu
wait too long.
So slow.
Can't sit still anymore?
Then go take a look from the Wanghai Tower.
Accompanying this bratty girl in her mischief...
Isn't it exhausting?
Anyway, since childhood,
I've always been accompanying you in your mischief.
Now that I'm old,
accompanying Taizhen in her mischief is just the same.
If you,
insist on being a picky mother-in-law,
I'll just keep accompanying you then.
What do you think that wretched girl will take?
That depends on what she can carry.
After putting in so much effort,
if she only takes away worthless things,
then she's really losing out.
If she really takes away something worth
five hundred thousand hu of grain,
I'm afraid they won't finish moving it even in one night.
What is all this stuff?
This...
This is all of it?
The inspection is complete?
What is this?
The dowry has been collected.
The remaining sixty-four loads
are for Mother's remarriage dowry.
That wretched girl!
How dare she make fun of me!
What did she take?
She took sixteen double-dragon banners!
That's secret-color celadon from the Shanglin Lake kilns,
stock from the third year of Tianbao.
Be careful!
If sold on the market, it could buy ten whole qing of land.
A thief from within is hard to guard against.
I shouldn't have been so kind-hearted.
What else?
As a thief within, of course she knows what's valuable.
She didn't take a single valuable item.
Besides the banners, they also took the Yellow Dragon Token,
and Chengyou!
Pass on my order:
All ships on the island, regardless of size,
are to be dispatched.
Catch the two little thieves
and bring them back!
I'll have them sliced to pieces!
They've been gone for an hour already.
Where are you going to catch them?
We pay respect to Young Executive.
Summon all the Masters and ship-masters.
On January the Fifth, the Lantern Festival gathering
in Ninghai, Taizhou,
fifty thousand hu of grain can exchange
for one Double Dragon banner.
Dig it out!
Hurry up!
We respectfully obeys the order.
[Kaifeng Prefecture, Bianliang City]
[Liu Luojia, Guo Rong's wife]
Zongyi has gone to sleep?
She's asleep.
She waited for you until late in the Hai hour,
eyes could barely stay open.
He hasn't wet the bed for many days.
Zongyi was well-behaved today and
didn't join her Third Uncle's mischief.
She practiced calligraphy, and recited poems.
Mr. Wang praised two characters among the three she wrote.
She's finally fallen asleep. Don't wake her.
Luojia, I must leave the capital again tomorrow,
to inspect the river works.
It should take ten days or more.
So...
I likely won't return before New Year.
I'll go pack your luggage.
No need to hurry.
Come here.
When I left Jinyang last year,
I promised you both I'd return to celebrate New Year's with you.
But who could have known the capital would fall
into turmoil, separating us for over half a year.
I even made you and our children live in fear and anxiety.
During the Mid-Autumn Festival this year,
I promised Zongyi again
that during the seven-day holiday after New Year's Day,
I would take her to ride near Mount Yi.
It seems,
I must break my word again.
It's different from last year, after all.
A broken promise is just that.
She may be disappointed,
but we can make it up later.
At least,
you're not off risking your life again.
Chanzhou faces Yexia across the Yellow River.
Once the Shanghusao embankment section
is dredged and repaired,
the river's south bank will be secure
from flood threats for four to five years.
If we weather this year's summer floods,
and store the autumn harvest,
the court can finally catch its breath.
Your Majesty issued a clear edict last month,
exempting prefectures surrounding the capital
from taxes and corvee.
Launching river works will require conscripting laborers.
Court discussions may seesaw back and forth,
but the Emperor should not go back on his word.
It has been half a year since Your Majesty ascended the throne.
Prefectures and counties are now governing peacefully.
With taxes and grain levies remitted,
the over one hundred thousand refugees
gathered outside the South Gate have mostly dispersed.
Only seven or eight thousand remain.
Keeping these people in camps,
even on one meal of porridge a day, is a waste of grain.
Better to send them to the river works.
They'll get more substantial food to build strength.
If we promise to distribute the reclaimed land among them,
they are unlikely to be lazy.
That's wise.
With Zhang Yanze executed,
several thousand surrendered troops remain.
To disband them rashly risks,
leaving them without means to live,
they might harass and poison the localities.
To execute them all would damage imperial virtue.
Better to send them as well to the river works.
If they then grow lazy or cause trouble,
executing them could not be called inhumane.
This is Li Gu's idea, is it not?
Your Majesty's insight illuminates all.
Cheng Xun.
[Liu Chengxun, Liu Zhiyuan's eldest son]
Your Majesty.
Lord Feng and Chief Guo have deliberated thoroughly;
there is nothing improper.
I believe we must issue a clear edict restraining
the capital's nobles and garrison commanders,
barring them from buying land in Chanzhou.
The land reclaimed
from the river works
[Liu Chengyou, Liu Zhiyuan's second son]must be allocated directly
[Li Ye, Palatine Officer in charge of palace security]
to these refugees and surrendered soldiers.
Those with constant property have constant hearts.
Only thus can the capital region's stability be ensured.
Lord, what is your view?
Your Majesty,
these are words that plan for the state.
Left Guard General embodies benevolence and forbearance,
[Left Guard General refers to Liu Chengxun]
and understands affairs high and low.\
In employing men and handling matters,
he is thorough and appropriate.
This is a blessing to the court, and a blessing to the realm.
Chengyou, don't take this as criticism,
but as to palace affairs,
others may ignore, but you absolutely must not.
His Majesty's old comrades, his veteran ministers—
you should pay them visits, visit them often.
I'm not sure whether your Eldest Brother
knows how to handle affairs,
but he knows how to handle people.
In this alone,
you cannot match him.
Uncle, Elder Brother is the legitimate eldest;
his position was settled long ago.
All court officials, from Lord Feng and Chief Guo down,
see him as the heir apparent.
Even Father, soon after taking the throne,
gave him the post of Kaifeng Prefect.
His intent is clear without words.
How dare I compare myself to Elder Brother?
Chengyou,
you are mistaken here.
In this era,
what position is truly fixed?
If we speak of position,
His Majesty was a subject of the Shi family a year ago.
Your mother,
was merely a princess consort.
And now?
One is Emperor,
the other is Empress.
Was that achieved by discussing status?
Uncle, mind your words!
How can you say such nonsense— ?
That day, Shi Hongzhao— what did he say in court?
His Majesty holds the realm by long spears and swords.
And Lprd Feng— what did he do that day?
Rice and wheat, three hundred thousand hu each,
seed grain three hundred thousand hu,
could buy the Central Plains Emperor's throne.
With money and grain, troops and horses in hand,
and backing in court,
even if not the heir,
one still becomes Emperor.
This truth,
your Eldest Brother
understands far better than you.
This is how one survives in chaotic times;
it is a matter of life and death.
Uncle, do you think...
I still have a chance?
Whether a chance exists is one thing.
If a chance comes,
whether you can seize it,
is another matter entirely.
Opportunity,
is always reserved for those who are prepared.
What exactly is the Ninth Prince's plan?
Please, Deputy Prefect, enlighten us.
What is unclear?
Throughout the prefecture and counties,
which families have lent funds to the Taizhou Land Office,
or signed loan guarantees?
Before January the tenth,
bring the loan contracts or guarantees
to the Chief Clerk's office
for registration and verification.
If the contracts are genuine,
there will be a share of prosperity.
Inviting them into the jar?
Taizhou has no Zhou Xing,
and the Ninth Prince is no Lai Junchen.
This is not Wu Zetian's Zhou, but Wuyue.
May I ask, Deputy Prefect, what exactly is
this "prosperity" the Ninth Prince speaks of?
On the Lantern Festival, the fifteenth,
the Ninth Prince will host a banquet
at Zhang'an Port, Ninghai,
to entertain the prefecture's elders and gentry.
No invitation letter is needed, nor a calling card.
Your contract with the Land Office
is your credential for attendance.
This is hardly ‘inviting into a jar’.
This is clearly a poisoned chalice!
Assistant Wei.
The family heads who lent the money may choose to ignore it,
but you and I are prefectural officials.
Even knowing it's a trap,
how can we not go?
Assistant Wei, what do you mean?
Shen Yin only spoke a few words.
If this matter is resolved smoothly because of him,
in the future, within the five counties of Taizhou,
will there be any place left for you and me?
But... but he is after all...
Sit.
Sit down to listen.
Even the strongest can’t crush a native force.
Since the case in Taizhou was exposed,
these local magnates who made those loans
have been fish on the chopping block.
Shen Yin wants to use their heads as his proof of loyalty.
If you were a family head,
would you dare go?
But didn't Deputy Prefect Shen say...
What Shen Yin says is unimportant.
What matters is,
who they listen to and who they believe.
Even if it's a proof of loyalty,
it should be our proof of loyalty.
A proof of loyalty, eh?
With you gracing this remote place, Ninghai, Prince,
for local magnates, to offer some goods and gifts
is surely to be expected.
It hardly counts as a ‘proof’.
Just customary social courtesy.
Ninghai is a poor county.
Such ‘customary courtesy’ yields
thirty to fifty thousand in silver and silk.
Our Wuyue pays the Central Plains Emperor in ‘courtesy’
each year only two hundred thousand in silver and silk.
Add up the five counties of Taizhou,
and my ‘courtesy’ as Prefect might well surpass the Emperor's own.
How much is your courtesy?
I...
Your servant...
How much?
Prince,
I am but a minor functionary,
with no backing at court.
These local wealthy families...
how could they normally pay me any mind?
Even as social courtesy, the silver is
no more than thirty or fifty taels,
the silk no more than seven, eight bolts.
As for gold, pearls, valuables— even if offered,
I would absolutely never dare accept them. So...
That's too little.
I checked Gao Xu's confiscated property.
Here in Ninghai,
his annual ‘courtesy’ income might reach
over ten thousand at times, at least seven or eight thousand.
Yet yours is only thirty or fifty?
You lie to me.
Prince!
He...
He's a Prefect, he was a ‘Lord of a Hundred Li’,
a minor sovereign.
I am merely a lowly Assistant.
I'm...
To put it kindly,
I'm an official.
To be blunt,
within this county office, I'm just a senior clerk.
How could I possibly compare to Mr. Gao? I...
Fine.
You sound pitiful enough.
Very well,
I'll give you a chance to prosper.
From today,
you will act as the Prefect of Ninghai County.
This... I...
No... this...
First, register these and store them.
Then, pass on my word.
Pass... pass on... your word?
That Gao Xu was a mere minor lord,
yet his worth reached tens of thousands.
I,
am a former King's son,
the current King's own brother,
and royally appointed as master of Taizhou's five counties.
This trifling thirty or fifty thousand— who do they think I am?
The gifts,
I accept.
The gift lists,
send them back.
This...
Tell them to reconsider carefully,
and submit a new list properly.
This... this... I...
On the fifteenth, the Lantern Festival,
I will host a banquet at Zhang'an Port
to invite the gentry and nobles from the whole Taizhou
to feast and confer, to discuss shared prosperity.
Who is invited, who is not,
who may come, who may not—
all this will be decided by you,
the Prefect of Ninghai.
I...
This time, if you yourself do not collect an amount
equal to a year of Gao Xu's 'courtesy',
your term as prefect ends on the Lantern Festival.
Yes, my lord.
[Ge's State, Linhai County]
The Ninth Prince has arrived in Taizhou.
A new official, and a royal prince besides.
[Ge's State, Linhai County]
I wonder what his intentions are.
Only those with ill intent comes...
I recall last summer's Land Office tragedy.
Shen Congyue who served two terms as Prefect,
County Prefect Gao from a meritorious family—
both were ended by him.
Exactly.
Wasn't it said there's a gathering at Zhang'an on the fifteenth?
That is a trap.
To go is to risk losing your head.
Yes.
No. The Prince's blade may be swift,
but can he kill the innocent?
This Prince is the King's brother.
If he wishes to spare you, guilt becomes innocence.
[Ge Yanping, Literary Officer and Archivist of Taizhou]
If he wishes not,
innocence becomes guilt.
Officer Ge! Officer Ge!
Everyone, please, no formalities.
Please sit.
Gentlemen,
listen.
This Zhang'an gathering,
is Shen Yin's scheme.
This man holds a grudge against all Taizhou.
His motives,
are deeply suspect.
But do not worry.
Assistant Wei and I have a plan.
When the Lantern Festival comes,
we two will personally go to Zhang'an Port in Ninghai,
to pay our respects to the Prince.
First, to perform the rites due a superior.
Second, to sound out the situation for you all.
Officer Ge's high-mindedness fills me with gratitude.
With the Prince's arrival in Taizhou,
my humble family prepared a modest gift.
We must beg Officer Ge to present it to the Prince for us.
Of course.
I also have a gift list. Please present it for us, Officer Ge.
A paltry token of our respect.
This is mine.
Please rest assured, gentlemen.
Taizhou is still the King of Wuyue's land.
You are all subjects of the Qian family.
Even if the Prince has misunderstandings, I,
with Assistant Wei, will explain and resolve them for you.
We trouble you, Officer Ge.
It is my duty.
My duty.
[Gift List]
Commissioner.
The Archivist, Ge Yanping,
today gathered the heads of prominent local families
for a meeting at a country manor.
Carriages have clogged the roads outside the manor.
Many department adjutants, clerks, and subordinate officials
from the prefecture also attended.
Did Ge Qiang go?
He was not seen.
Go.
Keep watching closely.
Yes.
In the past,
the one who decided to expel Ge Qiang and his mother
was Ge Yanping's father.
Since the meeting was called by Ge Yanping,
needless to say, he wasn't invited.
Even if he were, he would never go.
Renji.
In your name,
invite this man to the county office to talk.
Can this man truly be trusted?
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles
stretch towering mountains. ♫
run surging rivers. ♫
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles
cry warhorses. ♫
there are emotions unspoken. ♫
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles,
flowers are blooming along the road. ♫
gooses are returning to the north. ♫
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles,
we stand through storms. ♫
we hope for a safe return. ♫
♫ Tens of thousands of miles is not enough, ♫
♫ for a lifetime's sorrows and joys. ♫
♫ for the endless seas and rivers. ♫
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles, ♫
♫ love will overcome all barriers. ♫
♫ we are together in life and death. ♫
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles. ♫
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles, ♫
♫ the moon shines in the boundless world. ♫
♫ My heart has its hometown to return. ♫
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles, ♫
♫ who is the one crossing the waves with me, ♫
♫ with our hearts unrepentant,
through countless lifetimes. ♫
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles, ♫
♫ oceans and lands witness that♫
♫ the world will be safe and sound. ♫
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles, ♫
♫ my heart is unchanging. ♫