♫ Raising the wine cup, I toast to the boundless sky ♫
♫ In talks and laughters are vast mountains and rivers. ♫
♫ Love and hate, debt and feuds, have all dissolved. ♫
♫ Where's my soul's hometown and my kindred spirits? ♫
♫ Seasons rolling by, we dream for harvest. ♫
♫ Warriors and warhorses howl across the sky. ♫
♫ If only I could turn into the wind, ♫
♫ to blow away all the pain in mortal coil. ♫
♫ I toast to the blue sky, to courage in solitude, ♫
♫ to migrating gooses, to boats heading home. ♫
♫ With even three thousand days and nights, ♫
♫ Will it be enough to drain this cup I toast to peace? ♫
[Swords into Plowshares]
[Episode 27]
Seventh Prince is appointed as Regent of the Two Armies,
in charge of both internal and external military affairs.
The elder brother passes, the younger succeeds?
Having a mature ruler on the throne is a blessing for Wuyue.
But…
There is a decree.
Summon Ninth Prince back
to the capital to participate in state governance.
What does Uncle mean by this?
I marry your elder sister,
and they give me three warships?
Brother‑in‑law, these are not for you.
They are an extra dowry for Sister.
Who adds warships to a dowry?
Are you afraid that your sister and I won’t start fighting?
Even if we do fight, and your sister wants to deal with me,
can she,
bombard me with warships?
It’s like this.
When Mother and Uncle left, they left a message.
They said you are a prince,
a member of the royal clan.
Usually, encountering some minor troubles
or difficulties is no big deal.
As long as your life is not harmed,
hen everything is fine.
But if you truly encounter a major trouble,
a great disaster, that endangers your life,
these three warships can ensure you
escape from Wuyue with Elder Sister,
return to Huanglong Island, and become a live‑in son‑in‑law.
So Mother‑in‑law and Uncle‑in‑law
are practically cursing me.
Prince!
You wretch, why are you in such a sorry state?
The prefecture has received an imperial decree
from the capital.
The Great King
has passed away.
In domestic governance, affection overrides righteousness.
In external governance, righteousness severs affection.
Serving the ruler is based on serving the father,
and the reverence is the same.
Honoring the noble and respecting the respected
are the primary aspects of righteousness.
Therefore, for the ruler, one also wears
the coarsest mourning for three years,
governed by righteousness.
Prince.
The ships are ready.
We can depart at dawn.
Understood.
You may leave.
If you want to cry,
then cry it out.
I don’t want to cry.
I just feel some regret.
When I was young,
I always thought he was a bit rigid.
He would put on a stern face whenever he spoke.
Although we were blood brothers,
we were never close.
Later he became the Great King.
I still often quarreled with him.
Over the past year or so,
I’ve come to understand many things,
and learned the etiquette between ruler and subject.
But that has distanced our brotherly bond.
Taizhou has only five counties,
yet there is so much endless work.
Over a dozen prefectures, more than seventy counties,
the heavy burden of millions of soldiers and civilians
rested on his shoulders alone,
for a full six years.
I’m afraid his heart’s blood was nearly exhausted.
In this world,
no one lives an easy life.
He didn't have it easy.
You didn't have it easy either.
Ge, your official career has been frustrated for years.
You've only recently seen some improvement.
To give it up so easily is truly a pity.
Please reconsider.
No need to reconsider.
Just a seventh-rank Administrative Officer.
If I resign, then I resign.
I am a rough and careless person who has languished
in low positions for years.
It was only by Prince's grace that I obtained this
green robe, the grievances of this lifetime settled.
My master is not the King of Wuyue,
but the Ninth Prince.
When the master worries, the subject feels shame.
When the master is shamed, the subject should die.
Now that Prince is in trouble,
how can I,
stand idly by?
Ge.
Renji.
Everyone has their own aspirations.
The Great King has passed away.
A new ruler has ascended.
The hearts of men in the capital are unpredictable.
Wuyue is in a time of life and death.
After returning to Hangzhou,
everything must be handled with care.
I must entrust this to you, Mr. Ge.
If our master faces peril, how dare I not give my utmost?
[Kaifeng Prefecture, Bianliang City]
Change shifts!
This afternoon, Prince of Zhou and Chancellor Yang
requested an audience.
Inside the main hall, they talked for nearly half an hour.
Liu Tingrang was on duty, who overheard everything.
Prince sets his sights on the Grand Marshal.
He wants to transfer the him to
patrol the borders at Hezhong Prefecture.
He also incited censors to submit memorials,
saying that you and your farther guarding the palace together
violates regulations and you should recuse yourselves.
His Majesty did not agree to his face,
saying, "Go discuss it with Lord Feng."
Move!
Father!
When exactly did you offend Prince of Zhou?
It wasn't me.
It was you.
Me?
I…
I have had no dealings with Prince of Zhou.
We've barely even met a few times.
I haven't even spoken a single word to him.
Prince of Zhou hasn't,
but Prince of Wei has.
Before Prince of Wei passed away,
you went to see him
and delivered a letter from Guo Rong to him.
He even promised you in person the future position
of Commander of the Personal Guards.
Now,
Prince of Wei is dead.
These matters
cannot be hidden from others.
What's this called? "When the city gate catches fire,
the fish in the moat suffer."
Enough.
I won't wait for him to make a move.
Tomorrow, I will submit a memorial,
volunteering to leave the capital.
That makes no sense.
Father. Since Prince of Zhou's apprehension is towards me,
if anyone should resign, it should be me, your son, who resigns.
Your weight is too light.
You understand?
I have been in charge of the Imperial Guard
for seven or eight years.
With the new dynasty established, it is only right
to step aside for the more capable.
Being appointed as an inspector or prefect
is entirely reasonable.
Kuangyin,
your official rank is too low.
Even if you were to be posted outside the capital,
there are no suitable vacancies.
Given your seniority, once you leave the capital,
I'm afraid you wouldn't even qualify
for a county military officer's position.
If I'm not even qualified to be a county military officer,
I might as well resign altogether.
Rash.
Father, even if Prince of Zhou were to grant me
a county military officer post,
what would become of the Zhao family's dignity?
Rather than wait for him to make a move,
I should simply resign from the position
and leave the capital.
As long as he doesn't see me,
he naturally won't go too far.
Father,
a son making way for his father is only right and proper.
[Western Court, Hangzhou]
Every New Year's Day, it is customary to reward the armies.
This is a long‑standing tradition in our Wuyue.
King Wusu could bestow rewards,
King Wenmu could bestow rewards,
and the late king could also bestow rewards.
Why can't I?
Regent, you are not yet the King of Wuyue,
so you should not bestow rewards.
Until the imperial court grants the formal investiture,
the Regent is not the King of Wuyue for a single day.
Grand Marshal,
rewards were given in previous years.
This year, I…
This year, it is my turn to serve as Regent,
yet there are no rewards.
I fear the officers and soldiers in the army will
harbor resentment, and unforeseen troubles may arise.
You worry too much.
Military discipline is strict.
I have received the grace of three generations of
previous kings, commanding the armies.
If any petty troublemakers violate military law,
I will execute them myself,
to reassure the Regent, and to repay the previous kings.
Clearly, bestowing a small amount of silver would
stabilize the morale and eliminate chaos.
Why must you insist on killing, Marshal?
You have never led troops,
and do not understand military affairs.
In the army, rewards and punishments are of utmost importance.
All rewards and punishments must have a proper reason,
and must follow established rules.
Indiscriminate rewarding and punishing
is a path to disaster.
I have already explained clearly, that
this is New Year's reward that should be given every year.
There is a reason and established precedent.
How can it be considered indiscriminate?
It is true that it is given every year.
What the armies receive are all rewards from the Great King.
Now, the Regent is not yet the King of Wuyue,
therefore, you should not give rewards.
What if I
insist on giving the reward?
Regent,
the army does not accept unreasonable orders.
This man treats the royal court with contempt.
If this can be tolerated, what cannot?
Regent,
what the Grand Marshal says is the truth.
Minister Yuan,
why do you also speak like this?
Before the imperial court bestows the title,
the Regent is not yet the King,
naturally you cannot carry out the King's rewards.
This is propriety.
Wuyue established its state here,
serving the Central Plains court well,
and upholds the principle of propriety.
Using the Regent's name to carry out the King's rewards
is an act of overstepping one's authority.
It cannot be done.
The Grand Marshal is a senior minister of four reigns,
relying on his merit, does not acknowledge me as the King.
Minister Yuan, you are a scholar, you should
understand the way of ruler and subject,
which is the foundation of the court's order and morality.
Could it be that in Minister Yuan's heart,
you also refuse to acknowledge me as the Great King?
Regent, you put it too seriously.
I dare not.
The Grand Marshal does not disrespect you.
He is doing this to save money for the state.
Hongchu?
I, Qian Hongchu, Prefect of Taizhou,
pay my respects to the Regent.
Rise.
Quickly.
Thank you, Regent.
You've finally returned.
Both Brother and I have heard about what happened in Taizhou.
Brother said that day,
"Hongchu has matured.
Within our royal clan, another capable minister has emerged."
I have failed Sixth Brother.
From childhood to adulthood, I was immature,
making him angry, causing him worry.
But I never imagined when the governance of a state,
such a heavy burden, resting on his shoulders alone,
how difficult it must have been for him.
Enough.
Don't just stand there.
Sit down and talk.
Come.
Sit.
You've returned just in time.
The capital is unsettled, powerful ministers are at court.
I, as the Regent, tremble with fear every day,
truly not knowing when internal strife will erupt right here.
Originally, as per custom, the military rewards should be given.
This Lord Hu, insisted on not distributing them.
Minister Yuan even said it was to save money for the state.
I wonder in their hearts,
whose money they are actually saving.
The rewards?
The annual rewards for the first month,
still have no resolution.
The officers in the army, must be grumbling
incessantly now about me, the new Regent.
Father and Brother were both generous.
Could it be that when it comes to me, I become a miser?
The Minister and the Grand Marshal are indeed saving money.
Hongchu,
what nonsense are you talking?
Seventh Brother, the imperial
appointment has not arrived.
For now, you are only the Regent.
If rewards are given now, and when the imperial appointment
is issued, and you formally becomes the King, then?
If not, resentment will inevitably arise in the army.
If given, this is a double reward.
Double the silver and silk. Double the expenditure.
This is all the state's money.
Good. After being a local official for a few months,
you also keep talking about the state and people.
You've truly made progress.
This is also your money.
You really think of me as some kind of clueless, foolish king
who can't tell good advice from bad.
Bring wine. I want to have a night talk
with Hongchu over drinks.
Yes.
Wuyue Kingdom belongs to them.
The gold, silver, wealth,
all belong to them.
If he wants to reward,
just let him reward.
Those who don't manage a household don't know the living cost.
Father, why must you play the villain in this?
If the military officers hear of this,
they'll resent our family.
The late king is dead, but I am not dead yet.
I cannot allow a young brat to disrupt the court's order.
Hongchu has returned?
After all, they are blood brothers.
He is to either stay in the court or in charge of
military affairs. Must have some arrangement for him.
I have been thinking privately, Father,
that this is not beneficial for you.
Regarding the matter of rewarding the armies, Father,
you should just comply with him.
After all, he is the Regent,
the current ruler of Wuyue.
We must at least preserve enough of his dignity.
Are you afraid that if Ninth Prince takes command of the army,
he will take away the military power from your hands?
A young man who has seen little of the world—
naturally, Father would not fear him.
What I fear regards those
military officers like Shen Chengli.
Ninth Prince,
after all, he has served as Military Inspector,
and as the main commander of the Xiaoshan camp.
So…
Just after eating and taking a walk, to aid digestion,
and you're already panting like this.
How old are you?
Your body is already so depleted.
How can this be?
Father,
after all, your son is already sixty‑one years old.
Youth is truly wonderful.
This…
Campaigning in Fuzhou, seizing the seal in Xiaoshan…
He's a brat who has killed before.
What a pity.
What? What's a pity?
It's a pity that Sixth Prince died too early.
Otherwise, he still had a chance.
These old fellows are not worth worrying about.
This Lord Hu speaks beautifully,
but he may well have his own interests.
All these years, I've been in
the Chancellor's Office handling affairs.
Military matters, I've rarely intervened in.
But not intervening doesn't mean I don't understand.
What are rewards?
Rewards are the army's loyalty, they are favor and duty.
Most soldiers in the camps are men who haven't studied,
what do they know of loyalty and righteousness?
So,
this gold knife is loyalty,
this silver ingot is righteousness.
Hongchu, you've led troops and campaigned.
Entering a camp alone, seizing weapons bare-handed—
you've done such things.
If I were the late king, I would never have sent you to Taizhou.
The command of the Inner Guard
should have been yours months ago.
What are you daydreaming about?
I'm talking to you.
I miss Sixth Brother.
I want to go see him.
How are Sister-in-law and their son?
Tomorrow, after you take command of
the Inner Guard, you can go see them.
I can't control them.
What can't you control?
I can't control the Inner Guard troops.
Seventh Brother, reinstate Eldest Brother.
I know
if you do this, Sixth Brother would be unhappy.
When I kowtowed to him earlier, I already apologized.
This concerns the court.
This concerns the army's morale.
Eldest Brother can help you.
If Sixth Brother's spirit is watching,
he wouldn't blame you either.
I understand.
Since you returned, the only one on your mind
has been our late Sixth Brother.
There are things you would do for him,
but for me, you might not be willing.
Seventh Brother, that's not what I meant.
Then what did you mean?
When the Field Army marched south, you impeached
nine county military officers and executed one prefect.
During Cheng Zhaoyue's mutiny, you rushed
at night to the Xiaoshan Camp,
entered alone, seized command bare-handed.
The disciplinary beatings left the whole camp terrified.
Not to mention in Bianjing city, in the Chongyuan Hall,
before the Khitan Emperor, you drew your blade
and gravely wounded a military governor.
Fine!
What a hero of the realm, Qian Hongchu!
Now you tell me that you can't control
the scoundrels of the Inner Guard?
Do you think I should believe that?
It's precisely because I've served in the army
that I truly know my own limits.
To suppress those arrogant troops
under the pressure of Lord Hu's authority,
a veteran of four reigns,
only Eldest Brother can do that.
I see.
By the late king's final instruction,
Ninth Prince Qian Hongchu is relieved as Prefect of Taizhou
and appointed as Associated Chancellor.
Seventh Brother!
Tomorrow morning, go and report to Minister Yuan.
I am not worthy of employing you.
King, shall I summon the palanquin?
Quiet!
Yes, Great King.
I spoke out of turn.
What did you just call me?
Great King.
I am not yet the Great King.
I am the Regent.
In the southeastern lands,
within Wuyue, there is only one Great King.
The court has not yet conferred the title.
The court has shown no favor to the southeast,
but you have.
The court has shown no favor to me, but you have.
During the Cheng Zhaoyue incident,
if not for your leniency and help, I,
I would have been executed, my clan destroyed.
Your grace in sparing me, even if
I die ten thousand times, I will never forget.
Should I trust you?
I am uneducated, but I've heard
the camp storytellers talk of old times.
The ancients had a saying:
"When the.. load is warrant..."
"the mini..."
"is shamed..."
It's called, "When the lord is worried, the minister is shamed."
"When the lord is shamed, the minister should die."
I have no learning,
I've embarrassed you.
At the grand court today,
I was humiliated.
You just returned and argued?
It wasn't an argument.
What Seventh Brother asked me to do, I cannot do.
If you can't do it, then don't.
This isn't Bianliang, with knives to our necks.
Now we're in our own home.
Who can truly force you?
But Seventh Brother doesn't see it that way.
He thinks...
I am unwilling to help him.
And he's not wrong.
That I cannot do it is true.
That I do not want to,
is also true.
The state lacks funds.
The local prefectures and counties also lack funds.
To gather the tribute silver for New Year's congratulations,
Sixth Brother even searched the inner palace.
Now Sixth Brother is gone.
Seventh Brother is the Regent.
He asks not about the prefectures,
nor the common people, nor taxes.
He's in a rush to reward the armies, to win over the generals.
Lord Hu and Minister Yuan opposed him,
so he wants me to take command of the Inner Guard.
It's obvious,
he wants me to challenge Lord Hu and Minister Yuan.
But I truly cannot do it.
And I truly do not want to.
Then, if Sixth Brother were still here,
what do you think would he have you do?
Sixth Brother simply would never have asked
such a thing of me.
He made me Military Inspectors to oversee army provisions.
He sent me to Taizhou to fill the gap
from taxing first and measuring later.
He had me handle affairs.
Seventh Brother wants me to help him seize power.
And when Father was alive,
we brothers all lived under the shade of this great tree.
No matter the wind and rain outside, the suffering of the world,
this great tree shielded us from it all.
After Father left,
Sixth Brother became that tree.
But I was foolish then.
I was willful and argued with him.
I thought he wronged Third Brother,
and wronged Eldest Brother.
But I never considered however difficult it was
for Sixth Brother then, he never pushed me
or Seventh Brother to the forefront.
Those underhanded schemes, Sixth Brother
not only didn't let us do them,
he never even spoke of them to us.
But now
Sixth Brother is gone.
Seventh Brother is that tree.
Yes.
Well...
let the tree do the tree's duty,
and the grass do the grass's.
It doesn't matter.
If you're truly weary,
along with that "Associated Chancellor",
let's not do that either.
Resign from everything.
I can't resign Associated Chancellor.
That is what Sixth Brother wanted me to do.
It is also my duty.
I am a Qian.
I am of the royal family.
Imperial Brother Hongchu, by nature sincere and loyal,
wise from youth, is specially appointed,
by the late king's behest, relieved as Prefect of Taizhou,
and may participate in major governance.
Granted the privilege of wearing sword and shoes in court,
referred to by title in edicts.
Alas! Ruling by institutions and ritual is the foundation
of a states' governance.
The royal sons are the city's bulwark, the reliance of state
and family. This is our harmonious brother relationships.
I see your diligence in state affairs. This is the blessing
stored by ancestors, and a joy shared by state and family.
We shall further plan the methods of governance, to
accord with the canon of promoting the worthy.
Approved.
Let the authorities implement this.
I, your subject and brother Qian Hongchu,
humbly obeys the late king's behest.
For the Regent to personally pour wine,
the courtesy is excessive.
I dare not accept.
The Shuiqiu family has been our kin for generations.
Since King Wusu's humble beginnings, you have shared
fortune and misfortune with the Qians.
Lord Shuiqiu is a pillar of the state,
the foremost gentleman of Wuyue,
deeply respected by two generations of late kings.
I am young, suddenly bearing great responsibility.
There are many areas where I must rely on you,
far more than one or two.
It is merely a cup of wine.
If you dare not accept it, then in the entire Wuyue,
who else would dare?
You flatter me, Regent.
Daughter's Wine?
Indeed, Daughter's Wine.
Daughter's Wine is for celebrations.
Regent,
anything good happened?
I hear you have a daughter,
virtuous, chaste, and serene.
I am young, my inner chambers still empty.
I wish to seek her as my bride, to preside over
my household, awaiting the imperial seal.
Regent,
there is no need for this.
I was entrusted by two generations of late kings
to assist you, Regent.
I will exhaust all effort, and give my life for you.
Marriage with the Shuiqiu family?
Yes.
The Regent hosted wine at the Hall of Merit today,
seeking Shuiqiu Zhaoquan's eldest daughter
as his principal consort.
How can this be?
Can he not even afford a matchmaker?
Truly, each generation declines.
The Shuiqiu clan are hereditary kin,
within the state, their roots are deep and branches wide.
Shuiqiu Zhaoquan is hailed as a gentleman,
esteemed in both court and country.
The Regent's move
likely aims to use Shuiqiu's prestige and troops in the army
to balance court and country and restrain you, Father.
Haste makes waste.
Even if you swallow it whole,
you cannot chew it,
and it will upset your stomach.
The Regent is too impatient.
The armies are the vital instruments of the state,
the sovereign's authority.
They are not for subjects to lightly seize.
Although the Grand Marshal
is a veteran of four reigns,
he cannot monopolize power in the camps.
Having led troops for so long,
he may be arrogant and unruly,
but to say he has intentions of rebellion,
I do not believe that either.
Reporting.
I have escorted the Duke of Wuxing
back to his residence and come to report.
This matter is plain to see.
Minister Yuan does not believe it,
my own younger brother does not believe it,
now even Lord Shuiqiu does not believe it.
In these thirteen prefectures of Wuyue,
who else would believe me?
Do not worry, Great King.
The Duke of Wuxing and the Ninth Prince
A do not believe because Lord Hu...
that old traitor Hu has not yet shown his hand.
If he were to show his hand,
I fear this inner city of Hangzhou
would no longer be named Qian.
As the saying goes, hearing is not as good as seeing.
I believe
the more he hides his tracks, the more we must
force him to reveal himself in public.
Then,
the Duke of Wuxing, the Ninth Prince,
and Minister Yuan will have to believe.
He is the Grand Marshal.
Who can force him?
The old traitor is arrogant.
In court, he shows no regard for your dignity.
Great King,
of course you need not spare his feelings.
Tomorrow is the Mid-Autumn Festival.
As per custom, you will host a banquet in the main hall of the Hall of Meritorious Officials.
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles
stretch towering mountains. ♫
run surging rivers. ♫
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles
cry warhorses. ♫
there are emotions unspoken. ♫
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles,
flowers are blooming along the road. ♫
gooses are returning to the north. ♫
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles,
we stand through storms. ♫
we hope for a safe return. ♫
♫ Tens of thousands of miles is not enough, ♫
♫ for a lifetime's sorrows and joys. ♫
♫ for the endless seas and rivers. ♫
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles, ♫
♫ love will overcome all barriers. ♫
♫ we are together in life and death. ♫
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles. ♫
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles, ♫
♫ the moon shines in the boundless world. ♫
♫ My heart has its hometown to return. ♫
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles, ♫
♫ who is the one crossing the waves with me, ♫
♫ with our hearts unrepentant,
through countless lifetimes. ♫
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles, ♫
♫ oceans and lands witness that♫
♫ the world will be safe and sound. ♫
♫ Across tens of thousands of miles, ♫
♫ my heart is unchanging. ♫