(Hundred Million Stars From The Sky)
(Seo In-guk)
(Jung So-min)
(Park Sung-woong)
(Hundred Million Stars From The Sky)
I don't like you being a jerk.
I'm scared because it seems
like you're going the wrong way.
Are you going to take the job?
I won't do it
if you tell me not to.
Then don't.
Promise me you'll
become a good man.
Then teach me.
(Episode 10)
Hop in.
Damn, aircon!
No wonder it was too cold.
Aircon?
You didn't even notice
that the aircon was turned on.
Yours is turned on too.
No, mines is turned off…
Uh? It's turned on.
What's gotten into you?
Driving me to work?
So you like it or not?
I love it!
I would've just left
if you were even a minute late.
Yoo Jin-kang, you're lucky today.
Lucky day!
So what will we do about
next Thursday?
I almost forgot.
Next week is already November.
I didn't even notice
it was autumn already.
It's okay. I don't even remember
what year we're in now.
Should we make some gimbap?
Is that too much?
Why not? Let's bring some gimbap!
It'll feel like we're
going on a picnic.
Yeah?
And Jin-kook,
please buy some new sneakers.
Yours are too old.
- Have a good day!
- You too.
Hey, ugly.
I was a bit harsh last night.
I know you're all grown-up.
So, I trust
you'll deal with your own stuff.
I won't bring it up anymore. Okay?
Okay.
(Jang Se-ran)
Yes or no?
Have you decided?
(Delete)
- Let me make my own.
- I already made you one.
- Really?
- Here you go.
Thank you.
Uhm, what's this?
- It tastes creamy.
- Right?
It's not sweet at all. I like it.
- Uh? President.
- Thanks.
Jang Se-ran majored in the Arts.
Right, I searched for
her interviews and
she seems quite interested
in installation art.
She even personally owns
Yayoi Kusama's piece.
So I think it would better to go
for a dimensional graphic
than a plane plot.
What about Kim Moo-young's taste?
Jang Se-ran's taste is important
but Kim Moo-young is
the actual person who will run it.
We must consider his
preference as well.
I don't think he will.
- Uh?
- What do you mean?
I mean…
I ran into him yesterday
in my neighborhood.
At the mart.
You know, he's my neighbor.
So I asked him
but he said he won't do it.
He said he won't do it?
You should've asked him clearly.
Is he still thinking
or has he decided
not to take the job already?
So what is it?
I think…
He made up his mind already.
No, he has.
He has made up his mind
to not take the job.
Did you just smile?
While delievering this bad news?
Did I?
No, I didn't.
I must've done it
because I was too shocked…
As I told you,
Jin-kang is acting
very weird today.
I know, right.
She's been humming for 2 hours!
Humming? Was I?
Yeah, you're looking great.
No.
What do you think, Mr. Choi?
To be honest,
I think he's being rude.
Right?
Maybe I treated him too well.
There's been an order to transfer Lim Yoo-ri
to prosecution by tomorrow for murder
and to investigate Kim Moo-young
for another week.
Why separate the case instead
of taking them together?
They said our evidence is insufficient
to ascertain a motive.
- Lee Kyung-chul.
- Yes, sir.
Do you know that
Sergeant Yoo requested
to transfer to a patrol
team next term?
Did he?
Yoo Jin-kook.
You must know
why I called both of you in.
Yes, I'm good with
wherever I'll be disposed to.
There are only 2 months left
until the next personnel shift.
Be thankful that
they let it slide this time
and don't cause any trouble.
I'll be furious
if they take disciplinary action.
Frankly speaking,
Sergeant Yoo deserves it,
doesn't he?
If he let us know right away
when Lim Yoo-ri turned herself in,
we wouldn't have announced
Kim Moo-young as the culprit
to the media.
With that,
I was impetuous.
Sergeant Yoo didn't expect us
- to arrest him that soon...
- What?
Hey, leave him alone.
Eom Cho-rong has a special
relationship with Sergeant Yoo.
Didn't you know that his girlfriend
is Sergeant Yoo's sister?
Seriously?
- Unbelievable. How's it going?
- Yes, sir.
Regardless of how much you like her,
pick the right side.
- Alright.
- Get yourself together.
Damn, nobody got suspended.
- They let it slide this time.
- What a relief!
I'll keep it short.
Let's be like how we were
before this incident.
I don't know why
you were so obsessed with
Jung Mi-yeon's case,
but we were okay before then.
Act as if you aren't even here.
Uh?
Let's not trouble ourselves.
Sergeant Yoo.
It's tea.
Would you like some?
(Kim Moo-young's Call History
Frequent Contacts List)
Thanks.
(Kim Moo-young's Call History
Frequent Contacts List)
I know you wouldn't have done it
if it wasn't her.
I don't regret it.
I did it even though
I knew I shouldn't have.
I'm sorry for not letting you know
about Kim Moo-young
and Lim Yoo-ri beforehand.
Right, that was your fault.
I know.
That's fine with me now but…
But?
Nevermind.
Anyway, I'm so glad
we didn't get punished.
- Cho-rong.
- Yes?
What's this?
My old boss back in Haesan
gave it to me
telling me to buy some snacks
for Jin-kang.
You buy it for her.
Buy something delicious for her.
You can go.
I'll get inside a bit later.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I really didn’t…
want to hear that.
I'm sorry, Cho-rong.
Hey, Sergeant Yoo.
It didn't go well with Jin-kang.
I thought I should tell you.
I don't want to have any regrets
left either.
You introduced her to me but…
I'm sorry things didn't work out.
Eom Cho-rong.
Shall we go for a drink?
No, next time.
Next time.
Let's take the bus.
- Let's go.
- Sure.
I'm going to Hongdae today.
I'll drop you off nearby.
No thanks, I'll take the bus.
You don't need to take the long way
around with all this traffic.
Thanks to the bus-only-lane,
buses are pretty fast.
I'll take the bus.
Let's use public transportation.
Fine.
Then can you drop me off
by the subway station?
No, I said I'm going to Hongdae.
It's the opposite direction!
You walk.
- Go.
- Goodbye.
- See you tomorrow.
- Bye, bye!
This is such a hassle.
I'll take the bus too.
Will you?
She's taking the bus too.
Nevermind.
There'll be too much traffic.
I'll just take the subway.
- Okay.
- See you tomorrow, Manager!
She's taking the subway.
She's taking the bus.
What does 'she's taking
the bus' mean?
She's taking the subway.
It's so nice to walk like this.
This is my favorite season.
The weather feels like
it's allowing me
to be lonely, right?
Right?
What? What did you say?
Why?
Are you nervous
because November is coming?
Nervous?
It always comes.
Then what are you thinking?
I mean…
Jin-kang broke up
with Cho-rong.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
Cho-rong said earlier that
it didn't work out with Jin-kang.
That's too bad.
Cho-rong is the best man ever.
I know.
I shouldn't have said that
if I knew it earlier.
What did you say?
I told Jin-kang that
I'm going to trust her
and I won't nag her anymore.
Well done.
Too bad they didn't work out
but what else can we do?
They aren't for each other.
Right?
Hey, don't be all talk.
Wait in a relaxed manner.
Just chill out.
Why did they break up anyway?
I don't know.
But I think it has something
to do with him.
Ah…
Kim Moo-young?
What? You know something?
Not exactly.
Oh, right. The pub in Sungsoo-dong.
Did you say
you won't take the job?
You didn't?
What do you think I did?
You turned her down.
Actually, my boss really wanted
you to take the job.
She thought we could get
a bid from you.
If I took the job,
I would've definitely
picked your company.
I feel so guilty.
But why would you hate it that
much if I worked there?
It's much cooler
and pays better than now.
- You don't like money?
- I don't?
No way.
Everyone loves money.
You must earn a lot!
Fine.
I love money,
it's just that I don't want you to
be around those people.
They're people who can do
whatever they want.
You must keep your word that
I can ask you whatever I want.
Because I'm really going
to ask you everything.
There's a lot of stuff
I'd like to ask you
and I need to ask you,
but not now.
I was always so upset
every time I met you.
I was either upset, crying, or worried
and told myself that
I wouldn't see you anymore.
I never smiled.
So I want to smile
before doing anything else.
Don't smile.
Why not?
You look scary when you smile.
Eat up.
Okay.
Can we go that way?
Let's try going that way.
So you know why.
Of course.
I don't want to upset Jin-kook
if possible.
You know he doesn't
like you much, right?
I know.
I like him though.
No.
I'm not sure if I like him,
but he's funny.
I feel like I want to tease him
or mess with him.
Whatever.
I act up whenever I'm with him.
Isn't he so funny?
You smiled before.
What?
I think I'm going to continue
hating you.
How's the cat doing?
What's its name?
Last name is Jin, first name is Kang.
Jin Kang.
I'm the idiot for asking.
I think I'm going to continue
hating you.
Good luck with that.
You smiled exactly 3 seconds
after saying that.
How do you remember that?
Oh, right.
What about cat?
Did you try looking for it?
I did
but I couldn't find it.
But I got a text yesterday.
He's busy with his girlfriend.
He told me not to wait
for him anymore.
I think I'm going to continue
hating you.
Good luck with that.
It's a flower shop!
When did it open?
Let's check it out.
Good evening!
Welcome.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
Autumn is the season
for chrysanthemums. Looks good.
- Aren't these pretty?
- They are.
I bought them on the way here.
- A flower shop opened up front.
- Really?
Are you going to drive me today?
- Yeah.
- Hooray!
After you, Your Highness.
Oh, Jin-kook.
I'm working late today,
so don't wait for me.
You'll have to buy the
gimbap ingredients alone.
Bring some gimbap to
Cho-rong tomorrow…
I wonder if he's gone to work.
Why are you working late so often?
I must work a lot beforehand
so I can go on a picnic with you.
Let's go!
Please say something!
Why did you find out just now?
Please give us a comment!
Sergeant Yoo.
Could you please check the rest
before you get off?
- What?
- About Kim Moo-young.
We're supposed to
interrogate him tomorrow,
but he's not picking up his phone.
It'll be very bad
if he disappears or something.
2PM tomorrow.
Okay, 2PM.
Yeah.
I don't have battery.
I should go.
I'm going to work late today.
- Don't come by my office.
- I won't.
If you drop by my house,
check under
the chrysanthemum pot.
Okay.
Why did you turn down my offer?
I've decided to
learn something new,
and I thought accepting your offer
would disturb it.
What are you learning?
How to be a good man.
What?
It doesn't suit you at all.
That's why it's a challenge.
I think
I've explained enough to you.
I recognized you right away.
I don't think you have yet.
We're the same kind.
We can't be good people.
Boredom is what got me
to where I am now.
When I was born,
I was already here.
Nothing's fun
and nothing attracts me.
Sometimes I see something that glitters
and chase it like crazy,
only to realize that
I'd been fooled in the end.
Everything's boring.
But I've lost nothing.
Because time has passed.
And right now,
you look like the shiniest
thing to me.
What would you do if you were me?
You would check it out, right?
You'll end up seeking me out.
I can bet on that.
This tastes bad.
When will he be transferred
over to prosecution?
The number you've dialed
is unavailable…
Aren't these pretty?
I bought them on the way.
I'm working late today,
so don't wait for me.
The number you've dialed
is unavailable…
What? You know something?
Not exactly…
When Kim Moo-young was arrested
for murder,
Jin-kang called me
and asked if it really was
Kim Moo-young on the news.
But…
She sounded too…
If Kim Moo-young really is
the kid you're looking for,
he shouldn't be seeing Jin-kang.
Hello?
- Hello?
- Jin-kook?
Yeah, it's me.
Why didn't you say anything?
I thought you dialed the wrong number.
Where are you?
Why didn't you pick up your phone?
Did you call me a lot?
My phone was on vibrate.
Where are you now?
I'm at work.
I told you I had to work late.
Late?
Manager Yoo, I don't think
it was uploaded.
What? I'm sure I uploaded
it into the log folder.
Wait, I'll go and check.
Jin-kook, I'm in the middle of…
Okay, go work.
I'll hang up. Bye.
Bye.
Are you going to my place?
Yes.
Didn't you get instructions
when you were released?
Ah…
Pick up calls from the police
If you missed it, call right back.
Report beforehand if you'll
leave town.
If I'm out of reach for too long,
I'll be placed on the
wanted list. Right?
You know very well,
so why didn't you pick up your phone?
My phone was dead.
I was going to call back
after I charged it.
Why? Something wrong?
2PM tomorrow.
Interrogation.
Okay.
Are you…
dating my sister?
Don't date my sister.
Why?
Because I don't deserve her?
No.
You can't because it's you.
I'm opposed to you.
Don't ever meet her again.
I'm not asking you for a favor.
This is a warning.
Sir, please stop up there.
If you drop by my house,
check under
the chrysanthemum pot.
Kim Moo-young. Kim Moo-young.
Kim Moo-young.
Where are your cups?
There are none.
Just give it to me.
You don’t have any cups?
No.
What did you dream about?
Was it a nightmare?
My dad died.
Your dad died in your dream?
Yeah.
He was shot.
This was the 5th time
I had the same dream.
Do you keep having the same dream?
The story is always the same
but it gets clearer
as if my memory
is getting clearer.
What kind of dream was it?
The beginning is nice.
I'm really happy.
I'm like 4 or 5 in my dream.
I play with toys in the woods.
It's like I'm playing
with my brother.
When I go home…
Dad…
I like him so much,
so I try and go to him.
But, the sound of a kettle.
The water is boiling.
And a gun.
I can see a gun
beyond the steam.
A gun?
Yes, someone is
trying to kill him.
It becomes a nightmare from then.
I'm so scared.
I can't see the shooter's face
but I can clearly see a gun.
It feels like he's about to
pull the trigger.
I'm about to call my dad, but…
he falls down after getting shot.
That's where my dream ends.
I can't wake up
as if it's sleep paralysis.
And I hear your voice.
My voice?
Yes, Kim Moo-young.
You call my name
just like you did earlier.
Really?
Yes, so I thought
I was still dreaming earlier
because I saw you
when I opened my eyes.
When did you first have
this dream?
When I was in the Yangso accident.
I heard your voice then too.
Kim Moo-young.
How do you know it's my voice?
I'm sure it's you.
That's strange.
It might not be…
a dream.
Then what is it?
My lost memory.
I don't have any memories
until the age of 5.
Nothing?
No, nothing.
I'm not even sure until 5.
I don't even know
when I was really born.
What is your first memory then?
Walking.
I was walking somewhere endlessly.
I was so tired and hungry,
but I kept walking because
I didn't know where I was.
I think I was worried
about someone.
I couldn't stop walking because
I thought someone was waiting for me.
Who?
Mom?
Dad, mom, me and my brother.
He looks mischievous,
doesn't he?
He really does.
This is my only lead.
I got lost and a grandma took
me in and raised me.
She died even less than a year
after she took me in.
So the head of my town
took me to an orphanage
and I had this drawing
in my pocket then.
How do they look?
They look so happy.
They're all smiling.
Look, there's an angel too.
Doesn't he look like a policeman?
A policeman?
But his hat is purple.
Then maybe he's not?
I always thought my dad
was a policeman.
My father in my imagination
is still looking for me…
Somewhere…
Desperately…
For his lost son... me.
So…
I wasn't abandoned.
I was lost.
I know it sounds childish.
Not at all.
How many times have
you had these kinds of thoughts?
Countless times.
What?
How do you know this feeling?
I feel it too.
How?
I just do.
I just…
Look.
Your family looks so happy here.
I would've thought the same
if I were you.
Is that so?
Did you try looking
for your family?
Yeah once when I was 8
and once when I was 20.
I didn't find anything.
Should we look for them again?
You're scared.
That your dream might be real,
right?
You're home?
You still came early.
- Ah, gimbap.
- Right.
Try it. Ah.
When I made gimbap in the past,
you liked eating
the ends the most.
You sat right next to
the chopping board
and wanted to eat
like a baby bird.
I still love the ends the most!
- Here are your ends.
- Thanks!
Get some sleep.
We can just leave late.
Why? Do you want to eat
before you sleep?
You must be hungry. Just wait.
Gosh, my back.
Jin-kook…
I don't think I can go to
the temple with you.
Really? Why?
Do you have a lot of work?
I'm busy with work.
And I also have to prepare for
the competition next week.
It's pretty important.
I told the president
I couldn't go today
but I still think I should work.
I lie so easily now.
I must've been influenced by you.
I was just joking. Eat up.
Let's not lie from now on, okay?
You're just messing with me.
Isn't it delicious?
It's so delicious.
He's good enough to
open a gimbap shop.
He never once missed
my school trip or sports day.
He always made gimbap for me.
- But why today?
- What?
Why do you go to a temple
every November 1st?
I don't know.
Why today?
We did it ever
since we lived in Haesan,
- so I haven't really thought about it.
- Are you alright?
Thank you. Are you alright?
- Thank you, Mister.
- But I guess I just liked it.
- Yeah.
- Like an annual event for just me and Jin-kook.
I waited for November 1st
more than my school trips
when I was young.
(New Haesan Station)
Tak, did you arrive?
Thank you so much.
Yes.
Please hang out with my brother
instead of me today.
Alright.
So this is what Haesan Station
looks like.
I thought I'd remember
but I can't remember at all.
New Haesan Station.
(New Haesan Station)
Ah…
The old Haesan station
used to be in the city.
It's gone now.
It's my first time in Haesan.
I never came back after
I moved to Seoul.
I didn't think much of it
because my brother said
he was transferred to Seoul.
But think about it.
How could he be transferred
from Haesan to Seoul?
I'd have understood if it was
Seoul to Haesan.
He requested a transfer for me.
Was he a police officer
in Haesan too?
Yes, he's been a police officer
since he was 22,
so of course he was
one in Haesan.
But you're from Haesan.
Are you sure there isn't a single cop
you know in Haesan?
No.
What is it?
No, it's nothing.
Let's wrap it up and go home.
Why? We should interrogate
Kim Moo-young at 2PM.
It's been put off until tomorrow.
He's out of town.
Gosh, I'm so jealous. Where?
Haesan. Nothing I can do about
it when he's already there.
I can't go catch him.
Hey, where's Sergeant Yoo?
He said he had some business
to take care of.
Some business?
Oh right.
He never shows up
on his days off.
He requested a transfer?
He should've done it sooner.
It'll finally be peaceful now.
What really happened between
captain and Sergeant Yoo?
And why was the old team disbanded
because of Sergeant Yoo?
A suspect died
while they were chasing him.
Died?
He was a violent criminal.
When Sergeant Yoo
went after him,
the suspect fell off
a cliff and died.
Fell off?
So he fell to his death?
Or suicide?
Whether the suspect
tripped and fell
or he committed suicide
because there was
no other way out,
if Sergeant Yoo can't chase
criminals because he's scared,
how can he catch them?
So he was disciplined?
Not at all.
There were a lot of violent crimes
and the public was okay with him,
so he wasn't in trouble.
Then why?
That's why our captain
thinks he's pathetic.
You know those people
who feel guilty for nothing.
I guess he made a fuss
about dying or whatever.
So the team got disbanded
and the members scattered.
But still, he saw someone
die right in front of him.
I understand
why he was traumatized.
Come on, it was a time when
even the death penalty was given.
If he didn't fall off and die,
he would've received
the death sentence.
He was going to die anyway.
It's so delicious!
It's been 17 years since
I had your gimbap.
17 years?
Don't you remember?
When you were working
in Hyeongbok Police Station,
I went to Jin-kang's sports day
in your stead.
Right, when Jin-kang
was in 5th grade.
- You remember?
- Yeah.
That elementary schooler's
all grown-up now
and she even thinks of
finding her brother's date.
Goodness!
- Eat up.
- Thanks for the meal!
But Jin-kang doesn't know
why you bring her here every year,
does she?
She doesn't, and…
she shouldn’t know.
But they're really blessed.
Thanks to you,
they were able to see
how their daughter
grew up every year.
It's good
if they think of it that way.
But I come here for no reason.
Just to get some fresh air
with Jin-kang once a year.
It makes me calm when I'm here.
Shall we go?
Love is always patient.
Love is always mild.
Among faith, hope and love,
love is the best.
Love is the best.
Here.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Who is she?
A girl I'd like to look good for.
Hearing that is reassuring.
What is being a nice person?
What kind of person
is a good person?
A person with a lot of love.
That's definitely not me.
You're right.
What? Do you want me to deny it?
Wow.
I didn't think
you'd make me laugh.
Why did you just leave that day?
At Sister Theresa's funeral.
Even Doctor Yang was…
I'm here to ask you a question.
You said…
before I came here,
a detective from
Haesan police station
once came looking for a boy
who looks similar to me?
But Moo-young, that boy is…
I know.
(Looking for a missing child)
It was a year before I came here
when he came looking for a boy
(Disappeared on Tuesday,
November 9, 1993)
when he came looking for a boy
(Disappeared on Tuesday,
November 9, 1993)
with a burn scar on his shoulder.
(Disappeared on Tuesday,
November 9, 1993)
with a burn scar on his shoulder.
And you even checked
with the police
when you saw my right arm
after I first got here.
And he had already…
found the boy when you called.
So I wasn't the boy
he was looking for then.
But I still went by
the police station.
I guess I wanted to make sure.
When?
When I was 8.
I thought
he was my father.
But as I expected,
nothing was there.
But why again?
I still think I need to start
from here.
And here I am
again.
There's a lake
behind the orphanage.
The rock in the middle of the lane
across the lake was my seat.
What did you do there?
Nothing.
I just sat there.
What did you do
while you were just sitting there?
Just watched this and that.
Men who were fishing,
people on dates.
What are you looking at?
I was looking at you.
Even when you were little,
you looked like a troublemaker.
Did you find anything?
Nothing much.
I thought about orphanages
a lot when I was little.
I always wondered how it'd feel
to live in an orphanage.
Because you might've been sent
to an orphanage if it
hadn't been for Jin-kook?
Yeah.
I found out
when I was in middle school.
You know there's a time
when mysteries
you don't understand
perfectly come together
like a puzzle.
And then
you realize…
Oh, that was why.
For example, why don't I have
any baby pictures?
How could I be born in 1990
if my dad died in 1988?
I told you before,
my sister immigrated
to the States.
I wondered
what she meant when she
told Jin-kook something
before she left.
What did she say?
Your sister is me, not her.
I'm not his real sister.
It doesn't feel weird
telling you that.
I thought I wouldn't tell anybody
until I died.
I already feel so sorry to him
for just thinking of it.
You must've had
a lot of questions.
You couldn't ask him anything because
you were sorry to him?
Yeah.
So I thought about it a lot too.
An abandoned child.
A lost child.
But I always thought
I was abandoned.
What kind of people
were my parents?
Why did they abandon me?
Why did Jin-kook have
to take me in
when he was younger
than I am now?
The saddest thing is that
I can't tell him thank you.
Or thank him for raising me
when I was nothing.
Even if I want to tell him…
I want him to be happy.
He really is a great man.
I want to give Jin-kook the world.
Why does makgeolli taste so much better
in the mountains?
Hold on.
I wonder if she's skipping dinner.
I'm sorry I'm here with you
instead of Jin-kang. I'm so sorry!
It's strange.
You're pretty when you're angry.
Cut the crap.
Are you even worried about me?
Worried about you? Why would I be?
Forget it.
Pretty, my ass.
I knew it.
What are you talking about?
I don't quite follow
what you're trying to say.
Listen.
You're worried about
everyone in the world
except for me.
When I see you, I realize
love is all about worryings
What?
This is why you're never
worried about me, ever!
Tak, you're a brave woman.
Okay, fine.
I don't expect anything from you.
But remember one thing.
Think about
who's worried about you
the most in this world.
You know who that is?
Tak!
- What did you do? Are you insane?
- Tak, did I get it right?
Seriously…
I wish there was a time machine.
What would you do with it?
I want to go back in time
and hug you.
Little boy Kim Moo-young.
It's not too late yet.
I want to sleep with you.
Me too.
We have work tomorrow again.
Let's drink!
We have work?
If not, we can skip it!
Right.
That's it!
You should smile!
It's good to see you smile!
You look like a fool.
- A fool?
- Yeah, you're a fool.
I highly, highly admire you.
Even if everyone says it's not
your fault, you still
feel sorry for a long time.
That's why I like you so much.
But I still hope
one day you'll forget
about coming here
and say 'I must've gone crazy'.
I really want that day to come.
It won't ever happen.
Gosh…
I don't know.
Maybe when I get old
and get dementia or whatever.
Otherwise, I shouldn't forget.
Do you know why
I wanted Lim Yoo-ri
to turn herself in so much?
I didn't want her
to become like me.
What do you mean?
A person died because of me.
I didn't know what to do.
I was thinking of
committing suicide.
But I couldn't.
My dad had passed away,
Jin-yi was still in high school,
and mom was so…
So I had to keep living.
I had so many days left to live.
I wouldn't have known
time passess this quickly back then
because I was only 24.
Do you know
what the worst thing was?
That I didn't go to jail.
That I didn't pay the least
for what I did.
That tortured me a lot.
Jeez…
Why would you go to jail?
I agree with Lee Kyung-chul.
It's not your fault.
Whether it was suicide
or he missed his footing,
you did your best
to catch a culprit.
He didn't commit suicide.
Or miss his footing…
Nor did he fall off the cliff.
He didn't even try to
run away…
I shot him with a gun.
(A remake of the Japanese series A Hundred
Million Stars Falling From The Sky)
(Hundred Million Stars From The Sky)
Is Moo-young dating your sister?
What do you mean?
I'd never approve of him.
Your sister won't ever end it.
I've never seen my brother
hating someone so much
like this before.
Why do you think
he hates him so much?
What time is
Kim Moo-young's interrogation today?
Mind your own business.
What's so wrong with
a detective asking
for the time of an interrogation?
Am I wrong?
Please stop it, please!
Think of who raised you until now!
I have no intention of getting in
your brother's good graces.
How can you say that
when you know how much
he means to me?