1。
Are you asleep?
He seems to be asleep.
Luckily, he didn't notice us today.
If we leave early and come home late,
it's hard for Wen Qi not to find out.
Otherwise, we still
can't do it.
Absolutely not.
If he finds out,
there will be another risk that this matter will be exposed.
If you get involved with Tang Wenqi again,
when the mountain leader finds out,
I'm sure he'll be punished heavily.
It's better if you don't know.
By the way,
remember to keep the student roster.
I almost forgot if you didn't tell me.
All right,
you're not taking me to play,
I'd like to see what you two are up to.
I'm so sleepy.
I didn't get it.
Boss,
what are you doing?
Cover me!
In broad daylight,
is it possible that someone wants to assassinate you?
Boss,
what are you doing?
Humorous,
Smile
I told you to laugh.
Well,
aren't they always like this?
Yes.
By the way,
let's go now.
We have to clean up the classroom today.
Yeah, I almost forgot.
Let's go.
Boss,
where are you going?
Get lost!
Change your clothes first.
I'll go to the library to get your books.
Thank you, Brother Qi.
I want to see it today.
What are you hiding?
Why is he here?
Strange.
I saw that she put it in the closet.
You're not a man.
Can you speak?
You're actually a woman?
Get out of here if you see it.
Who saw it? What did you see?
You girl,
can you go out first?
Wait till I get dressed.
You said
you didn't know to close the door?
Brother Qi,
are you okay?
Brother Wu,
Sister Wu,
It's not right.
Oh,
How can you get used to it?
Okay Brother Wu,
you're actually a girl?
Gu Yuan Academy doesn't accept female disciples,
so I came in as a man.
So you want to study?
A talented woman disguised herself as a man,
in fact, for gunpowder.
Kind of.
That's very brave of you.
No wonder you used to speak up for women,
but now I understand.
In fact, what I want to say is,
we are still the same as before,
Just treat me like a man.
Hold on.
I have a question.
You ask?
I saw it. You
don't have to be responsible.
Keep rolling.
I'm not willing to do it if you want to.
That's good.
Any other questions?
Yes,
What are you two doing behind my back lately?
What if you don't tell me?
I'll go tell my father.
You're not a man,
Wen Qi Wen Qi,
Okay Let me tell you,
actually Brother Wu and I
have been preparing a civilian academy recently,
It's a place
where all the people can come and learn.
This is a good thing.
Why didn't you tell me?
I kept it from you because I didn't want to get you into trouble.
Silly girl.
I don't care.
I know it anyway.
I want to join you.
Let's go together.
What are you going to teach him?
To teach people to shoot guns,
then I'll ask my father.
What should she do when she enters the Academy?
Wen Qi,
I shouldn't have let you know.
let's be
so kind together,
I don't believe you can teach people to read.
Calm down.
I have another question.
It's so annoying. Ask me.
Since your gender is fake,
what about your background?
My father is the real General Wu,
otherwise I wouldn't have been able to study in the Academy.
However,
I really haven't seen my father for a long time.
It's been a long time since we last met,
I think she's going to turn the tables.
General Wu, calm down.
I asked you to escort her back to her mansion.
That's how you do things for me.
Subordinate,
I didn't expect that,
Why would you stay in Gu Yuan?
She even disguised herself as a man and entered the Academy,
where she ate and lived with a group of men.
Someone else knows about it.
Which other family wants her?
I'm willing to make meritorious deeds,
and go to Gu Yuan to pick you up.
Okay,
You're leaving today.
Be sure to take her back to the northwest.
Yes.
She's the girl in green that day.
Get out of the way!
Get out of the way.
Hurry up!
Could it be that
this is the legendary love at first sight.
I've been looking for you for so long.
It turns out that you've always been by my side.
I'm fine now.
Isn't this the girl from that day?
Why are you so dazed?
Do you still remember me?
I'm going to get changed.
It's not like I'm going to change my mind.
Brother Wu,
you wear women's clothes,
It's so pretty.
I think so, too.
Okay, let's go pick up the students.
It shouldn't be.
Why doesn't she remember me?
Wait.
Wu Wancheng,
think about it.
Wen Qi,
why are you here?
I want to take you to class,
just you?
Master Wu,
it turns out that you are the young woman Wen Qi is looking for.
Me,
Zhou Yang,
don't talk nonsense.
Brother's sister Qingyi is so gentle.
Look at
what she looks like.
Luckily,
it's not Master Wu. You're a woman.
Aren't women not allowed to go to school?
Why can't a woman go to school?
Everyone can go to school here,
so can my sister also come?
Of course.
All right, all right.
Let's clean it up.
Let's start our class.
Go to
your place.
Let me ask you one more time.
You really don't remember anything?
What should I remember?
That day.
Do you remember?
Are you crazy?
Students, open the bamboo slips,
and let's review yesterday's lessons.
Yesterday, we learned thousands of characters,
Heaven and Earth Xuanhuang,
The universe is wild,
the sun and the moon are full,
Make a list of Chensu.
He must have taken the wrong medicine today.
Can you stop messing around?
I'm listening to the class. Do
as you say,
I didn't say anything.
Can you stop staring at me?
Why am I staring at you?
You've been staring at Qi Shan?
Nonsense.
He's in class.
I'm not staring at him. I'm staring at you.
Is the class difficult?
I can do it, too.
I'll give you one.
Watch carefully.
Stop messing around.
Today, I'll give you a chance
to test the teacher.
Is that okay?
Okay,
Okay, I'll go first.
Winter comes and summer goes,
autumn harvests and winter hides. What's the next sentence?