1。
Darn Tang Wenqi,
if my leg heals, I'll kick you to death.
Brother Wu.
Are your feet feeling better?
What are you doing?
We haven't seen each other for a few days.
Why do you suddenly have such a hobby?
Are you feeling better?
It's this one.
How do you know?
I just ran into Lingxiu at the door.
She told me you were badly hurt.
She told me to take good care of you.
It's okay.
It's just over-dressing,
Look,
you can still move,
That's good.
No,
Why did you come back early?
My father found me a royal physician back home,
and I took a few medicines,
I'm fine now.
That's great.
-No. -Are you okay?
It's okay.
Let me help you to bed.
No.
Let me help you.
What are you two doing?
Wen Qi,
you're back.
Brother Qi,
don't talk to him.
He's the one who hurt me.
No, I didn't.
Don't wronged others.
I wronged you.
I found the evidence and I wronged you.
What kind of evidence?
Have you seen the soles of Brother Qi's feet?
I've seen his feet. I
just want people who pass by that road,
There will be black mud on the soles of your feet,
how can you say that I am the murderer?
Me,
I am
… Why didn't you suspect Brother Qi?
Why would I suspect him?
He's recuperating at home.
How could he have time to harm me?
Okay,
Anyway, you two are the best in the world.
No,
your friendship,
Unbreakable,
Anyway,
I will definitely find the murderer.
Wait till then to apologize to me.
Wen Qi,
Brother Wu … It's not that I don't listen to
him.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no.
I don't want to listen.
I'm sleepy.
Sleep,
Wen Qi,
I didn't mean that.
Brother Wu,
what are you doing?
You don't understand.
The exam is coming soon.
I want to pray for the koi to be possessed,
but I didn't get the koi,
Just use a few goldfish instead.
It's amazing to pray that
you must pass every exam.
I'll say goodbye, too.
Wait.
I always get the first place in the exam.
Why should I worship it?
Good tea.
All right,
get ready for class.
Qi Shan,
where's Tang Wenqi?
He,
I think he's out of his mind.
You don't even dare to attend my class.
Mr. Shan,
let's go to class first.
All right,
Master Feng,
Go and get him back.
What's going on?
I don't know.
Oh no.
Tang Wenqi will surely be beaten up this time.
What?
Fifty rattan sticks.
That's right.
Or did you call him personally?
That's called "cruel".
How is he now?
There's only half a life left, right?
Although he often skips classes,
he will never be absent on an important day.
Unless there's someone more important.
Don't mention it.
Boss went to the temple,
the temple,
Did he really go to look for the girl in Tsing Yi?
I don't know what happened to him recently,
but he saved a woman in Tsing Yi some time ago,
As a result, I fell in love with my family at first sight.
A few days ago,
I learned that he was staying at the temple,
As soon as I got the news,
I hurried there.
For a woman,
the mountain leader was furious when he found out,
Hang it up and hit it.
Brother Wu,
let's go get Wen Qi back.
Qi,
you go first. I'm going to get something.
I'll see you in the supervisor
later.
Brother Qi,
I asked Lingxiu for some medicine to promote blood circulation and remove blood stasis,
You can give it to Tang Wenqi.
You even know how to get me medicine?
You're injured and you're still playing.
What are you playing?
This is a coincidence,
not a toy.
I'm sorry.
What?
I'm sorry,
I saw you looking for someone on the street that day.
I just want to play a little joke on you.
I told the beggar that I had seen her.
I didn't expect that you would really go.
He even skipped the exam.
I didn't expect Mountain Owner would be so cruel.
I know you said it.
You know,
why are you still going?
I didn't go.
You didn't go?
I lied.
I didn't go to the temple.
I went to the smithy,
the smithy,
I'm going to investigate the real murderer for you, right?
So,
it's really not you.
Ridiculous.
I, Tang Wenqi, have been sitting straight all my life,
how could I do such a little trick behind my back?
Then why did you lie?
Because I found out that
the person who released the trap was actually Chen Lan,
Chen Lan,
when did I offend him?
There's something fishy about it.
Let's talk about it after I figure it out.
It seems that I really wronged him.
Wu (Wu)
(Why did you come to the ancient times and do stupid things?
Okay,
Got it.
how about
Apply the medicine for me.
You hurt me.
We can't just let it go.
I'd like to see what you're doing. What are you doing?
apply medicine
Where is it?
Nonsense.
Ass, of course.
butt
Take off your pants.
You don't have to take it all off.
Why don't you take it all off?
If it's not convenient for you,
let me take it off for you.
Fine, fine,
that
I … I … I … I … Wait for Brother Qi to come back.
Wait for Brother Qi?
I can take it off for you now.
No, no, no.
No, I really don't need it.
Thank you.
Help! Brother Qi.
What?
Lower your voice.
Do you want everyone to hear it?
Wait for me to sort it out.
Could it be that
you have feelings for Tang Wenqi too?
My point is,
Tang Wenqi is not the one who dug the hole.
Got it?
Understood.
So you like Qi Shan a little more?
Tang Wenqi is a bit more,
I don't think you understand.
This is so romantic.
A handsome young man,
and a young playboy,
How will the heroine choose?
What a bloody Mary Sue.
What will you choose, Sister Wu?
Calm down.
I'm not done yet.
Tang Wenqi also said that
the person who bought the trapper,
It's Chen Lan.
Could it be that,
Someone is going to join this romantic fight again.
I shouldn't have come to you today.
Goodbye.
Chen Lan
Mr. Shan is here.
Boss, you scared me.
Cut the crap!
Why did you lend me your shoes?
Why do you ask?
Of course you have to wear shoes.
If you keep talking nonsense,
I'll get out.
Okay.
It's good to be punished.
I don't have to attend classes,
and nobody cares about me.
The people who live in Tianzi,
don't they have brains?
Younian is right. Look at them
getting hurt one after another,
I'm really relieved.
Wu Wancheng,
the son of a mere general,
You deserve to show off your power in front of me,
and Tang Wenqi,
You deserve to embarrass me
in public.
Yes,
our senior is His Lordship's son,
They only know how to play tricks,
but they don't dare to do anything.
And Chen Lan,
I just threatened him
with his father's small official position.
He's as good as a dog,
and he knows how to dig holes.
Why are you here?
I saw you and Chen Lan sneaking around,
so I sneaked out to have a look.
You heard it.
Yes, I did.
I have to beat him half to death today.
Calm down.
By the way, you're really nice to Chen Lan,
yet you're willing to beat a prince of the Marquis's Mansion for him.
It's not just because of him.
More importantly, he hurt you.
He did it for me.
I mean,
okay,
I'll go back to class first.