For me,
to be or not to be,
this is not a question.
I have only three months left.
I want revenge
for my mother
and for myself.
No matter where I am,
in what kind of way,
I swear to make them
pay for their actions.
Before,
there was only hatred in my world.
But that is not the case anymore
after I met her.
It should be here.
Nice.
No one knows I'm here.
Time is precious.
Besides revenge,
I can't waste a moment on other things
including medical treatment,
taking medicine
or dealing with
trifles.
Boss.
Boss, go slowly.
Your leg suffers comminuted fracture.
Don't tire yourself out.
Meng Guo.
You're just an assistant.
How dare you make a decision for me?
Boss.
The treatment can't be delayed any longer.
No.
Anyway,
there are only a few days left.
It's not like I haven't seen an expert before.
Is there any recovery?
Instead of wasting time on doctors,
we might as well come up with some ideas
to deal with Second Uncle.
Boss,
your health matters the most.
Don't throw a tantrum like a child
whenever the treatment is mentioned.
We tried our way to move to this remote place,
so keep it a secret.
The fewer people know, the better.
Alright.
I'll check around.
It seems
I can only spend the last few days
in this resort.
Fenfen, stop it.
I did all the work
for you all day.
Let me sleep for a while.
It's really a poor place.
A cleaner dare sleep on the guest's couch.
Mannerless.
That's good.
No one will think of me, Huo Yunting,
to hide in such a place.
Wake up.
Leave now.
Fenfen.
Let me sleep for a while.
I'm too sleepy.
So it's a dream.
Sir.
You're really pretty.
Old tricks.
Can she be worse
in acting dumb?
Tell me,
who sent you here?
What did you hear
just now?
I don't understand
what you're talking about.
What do you mean
by who sent me here?
I'm really sleepy.
I'm going to bed.
Boss, I've checked all the places.
It's safe...
Meng Guo.
Who is this woman?
Boss, be careful.
Ming Xiaoxiao.
Did you finish my work?
Come back as soon as you're done.
I heard
the high-maintenance Mr. Huo is coming.
Don't bump into him.
Xiaoxiao,
pay attention to
the bed leg over there.
If you still can't make it well this time,
the manager will be angry again.
Okay, Fenfen.
Since the day shift and evening shift yesterday
to the whole day today,
I've been working for you.
Can I
get some sleep later?
Xiaoxiao, thank you for your hard work.
Just hold on a little longer.
The houses in the resort
are so beautiful.
Making them clean
every day
delights me.
You're poor yet happy.
With our low salary,
even working for a hundred years,
we can't afford a bedroom here.
A hundred years?
We can afford it.
As long as I work hard every day,
and with such a long time of a hundred years,
I'll be able to save money to buy a house.
And
in the house,
there will be daddy, mommy and baby.
How happy will I be!
Fine. You win.
Xiaoxiao.
Since you want to save money
to buy a house,
let me introduce a good work to you.
What work?
Mr. Huo's villa,
the Building 2 in West Zone.
I'll leave it to you to clean later.
The Building 2 in West Zone?
Isn't that also
the work that Manager Wang gave you?
Do you have to draw a clear line
between my work and yours
when we are so close?
How about this?
You clean it for me
and I give you half of the overtime pay.
There's overtime pay?
Alright then.
Who are you?
Who sent you here?
You approached me
with what intention?
You're speaking so fast
that I didn't catch you.
Moreover,
you're too fierce.
Giving irrelevant answers
cannot prove you innocent.
It's weird.
The floor has been cleaned
for three times today.
But there's no wind or rain
that dirtys the floor.
Is it possible that Mr. Huo
is doing this on purpose?
Mr. Huo?
Is that
Mr. Huo who wears a long face
and likes to throw a tantrum?
That's right.
I heard
that he is ruthless
and difficult to deal with.
You haven't told me
about the cleaning yesterday.
Everything went well
and you didn't get on his nerves, right?
Well...
Xiaoxiao.
You need to speed up.
Before getting off work,
remember to fetch some soil.
Mr. Huo wants to grow plants here.
Manager Wang.
My workload today
seems to be overwhelming.
I haven't had my lunch yet.
That's right.
Even I have to suffer.
Manager, what's going on?
Xiaoxiao.
How did you
offend Mr. Huo yesterday?
I'm telling you,
you'd better
apologize to him.
Otherwise,
he will keep arranging works for you
and giving you a hard time.
It's definitely not what you want, right?
He should do it on purpose!
Brother Zu, slow down.
Are you sure
Huo Yunting will stay in this kind of place?
There's even no road.
Is your information accurate?
As sure as a gun.
He does live here.
But Brother Zu,
aren't we
taking Huo Yunting too seriously?
He's just a president with disease.
What's good about him?
Brother Zu, as long as you give the order,
I'll deal with him today.
And you can have
the property of the Huo family tomorrow.
What nonsense!
If it weren't for you
who ruined the car crash plan
by giving out a lot of flaws,
I wouldn't be scolded by my father
and come all the way to apologize to him.
I...
Just stop it.
He has no actual evidence
to prove it was us behind the car crash.
It doesn't matter to me.
But Brother Zu, you are
the legitimate descendant of the Huo family.
How can you be embarrassed
by an illegitimate son
like Huo Yunting.
Here.
What does he think he is?
If my uncle hadn't chosen him
as his heir,
Huo Yunting would have died.
Boss.
I have investigated.
That Ming Xiao Xiao
is proved to be
just a regular cleaner.
She is an orphan raised in a welfare home
so she really has nothing to do
with Second Uncle.
And
she's young and has low response.
Please don't be angry with her anymore.
You sure know how to care about the weak
and beg for leniency for others.
Brief me what you found.
Look at this.
Lin Group,
after being exposed to financial fraud,
was delisted, and cannot hide
their huge losses and foreign debts
from the public anymore.
As you expected,
they won't last long.
Did Mr. Lin do anything?
Is there any sign of him
plotting with Huo Fenglei?
Not really.
Second Uncle
can't handle the Lin family.
After Mr. Lin resigned,
the Lin family is now managed
by his only daughter, Lin Xi.
In my opinion,
she came to us for help.
Boss.
Since we will swallow the Lin family
sooner or later,
why don't we
let her come and talk to us?
Lin Xi.
With her ability,
she should be able to find me by herself.
See.
I said I could find Huo Yunting.
I'm a man of my words.
He's here now.
How will you thank me?
Young Master Huo, thank you for all the hard work.
Don't pretend in front of me.
Every one
can see through your thoughts.
All is done for Huo Yunting, right?
Forget it.
I don't care about your mess.
My dad
asked me to give it to you in person.
Sign it now
so my part will be done.
The acquisition contract of Lin Group?
Sorry, Mr. Huo.
If you only want to drink,
I can keep you company.
If you want to talk about acquisition,
I think I'll pass.
We
have no intention of selling the company.
Didn't you talk about it
with my dad already?
What?
You changed your mind?
My dad said
now the Lin family is in trouble,
you little girl
can't solve it alone.
Why don't you ask him to help you?
It's good for everyone.
Mr. Huo.
Do you still think of yourself
as a three-year-old child?
You're old enough
to think by yourself
instead of relying on your dad.
You...
Lin Xi.
You'd better read the contract.
Although the price is a bit lower,
you and your dad
won't have to
suffer hunger and sleep on the street.
It's better
than waiting for Huo Yunting
to love and save you.
Whatever, I'm willing to.
It's up to you.
You'd better not regret it.
Right!
I forgot to tell you.
Without me,
even if you come,
you can't find Huo Yunting.
Mr. Huo.
I won't bother you
with such a small matter.
See you.
Special Assistant Meng.
Hello.
I'm Lin Xi from the Lin Family.
I have communicated with you before.
Sorry, Miss Lin.
Mr. Huo
is occupied recently.
He really can't spare some time to meet you.
Hello, Miss.
Welcome to check in.
I'm the cleaner for you today,
Ming Xiaoxiao.
The room has been
cleaned up.
Is there anything lese
you want me to do?
It's okay.
It's quite clean.
What's your name again?
My name is Ming Xiaoxiao.
Ming Xiaoxiao.
You've done your work well.
How about this?
Let's befreind on WeChat.
From now on,
the cleaning of my place
will be all yours.
Don't worry.
I won't treat you unfairly.
I...
I don't understand.
I'm a little slow.
Are you telling me
to go back to work?
It's OK today.
Your work is done.
Take out your phone.
Let's add each other on WeChat.
WeChat?
Miss.
I don't know much about WeChat.
Can we text?
Text?
Then...
Mr. Huo used to laugh.
You know him?
He's Mr. Huo.
Great, little sister.
Come and sit down.
If you tell me
where Mr. Huo lives,
I will
treat you to a cake.
Xiaoxiao.
Brother Lang Feng,
why are you here?
I was just thinking
to take a photo and send it to you.
A beautiful Miss
gave me a super delicious cake.
Xiaoxiao,
when it comes to eating cake,
you are so happy.
You said so many words in one breath.
You didn't even stutter at all.
You're making fun of me, right?
I won't talk to you.
But
I have two pieces of good news for you.
Xiaoxiao, if you ignore me,
you won't be able to hear it.
What good news?
The first good news is that
I have graduated successfully
and also got
Certificate of Honor for Outstanding Graduates.
Brother Lang Feng,
you're great.
I knew it.
You're the best.
The second good news is that
my boss assigned me to work here.
What about it?
Are you happy?
Really?
That's good!
We can meet every day.
However,
will your mom agree?
She doesn't like our meeting.
My mom is always like that.
Don't bother her.
Xiaoxiao.
I'm already an adult.
In the future,
I will earn a lot of money
and form my own family.
Anyway,
I just want to be with you.
Well,
I will try my best too.
In the future,
let's work together.
Come on.
We will have our own family.
Yes.
There will be
our own home.
What's wrong with you?