EPISODE 7
Did you have to show your face to U-ram?
I missed him, that's all.
Take off your mask.
I can't hear you properly.
What about Hyang-gi? Since when
did you feel the need to see him?
U-ram's still young
and is our youngest child.
You're supposed to be their father.
You came by so that he could spot you
after asking me to keep it a secret.
I only hoped to get a glimpse of him.
In your car,
right in front of the entrance
to our apartment building?
He's considerate for a boy,
so how would he have felt?
You're always so selfish.
I told him it was easily treatable.
And yet he burst into tears.
I'm sorry.
This isn't me lying or making excuses.
I just think about them more
now that I'm sick.
I've grown weaker.
So you must want comfort
and a boost in courage.
Have you already forgotten?
I still remember it
as if it were yesterday.
What good would regret do?
Is that doenjang?
Don't you wash your dishes?
I do it all at once.
That…
-Take it with you.
-What is it?
-You get cold easily.
-Tell me what it is.
I ordered it after seeing it on TV.
It looked warm.
Aren't you taking it with you?
Return it.
My gosh.
What is it?
I was just lost in thought.
Park Jun-ho's decent, isn't he?
He is.
-Good day, then.
-Sure.
-Yes, Director Jung.
-I'd like a word.
You did fine work producing your show.
There was a definite uptrend in ratings.
But you've been at it
for three seasons now.
Right.
So how about a break from it?
You can start developing other things.
-Who'll take over?
-Han Gyeong-a wants a shot at it.
Don't I get a say in this?
Take a year off
and come up with something new.
As if he's doing me a favor.
Stealing successful programs
is what Ms. Han does best.
I think it's unethical.
It is without a doubt.
You should have said
you'd like to stay on the show.
Begging is the last thing I want to do.
I met her on my way to work yesterday,
and she nitpicked how I ran things
as if it was advice.
A person like that exists
everywhere you go.
It's not him.
As if Mr. Seo's brother
would be at a cafe like this.
Did you run into him?
The day before yesterday at Yeoksam Hotel.
You've met him before, you know.
He paid for our wine that one time.
-That dashing young man?
-Yes.
He was having breakfast with Mr. Seo
at Yeoksam Hotel.
I don't remember his face.
Just his overall look.
He picked up your tab?
When we turned down
a bottle of wine he sent to our table,
he just paid for our drinks instead.
-He showed interest in you.
-I doubt it.
He knows who Hye-ryung is
and that she works with his brother.
That's why he was generous.
It makes sense now.
-Did he give you his card?
-Only later.
We met again at a hair salon.
Really?
We had dinner
so that I could thank him for the wine.
-Just to be polite?
-No, it happened naturally.
I treated him to the meal.
But still, you didn't know?
Didn't he tell you?
No.
You can imagine how shocked I was
to see him have breakfast with Mr. Seo.
You should have asked
why he didn't introduce himself.
It didn't seem appropriate at the time.
Besides, Mr. Seo left right away
to attend a friend's funeral.
It was his close friend.
What is he like?
Compared to Mr. Seo,
he's more of a perfectionist.
He's cynical,
but he's super confident too.
-What is it?
-Something silly crossed my mind.
What if I had dated his brother?
Any other woman
would have thrown herself at him.
He's clearly from a wealthy family
and is handsome and fit.
He's not your usual wealthy brat either.
Our situation would have been hilarious.
I know.
-Oh, Ms. Sa.
-Yes?
Can I set you up?
It's my close friend's cousin
who is also divorced.
His ninth-grader son
is being raised by his ex.
He's a director
at the Ministry of Foreign Affairs.
-He must've passed the state exam.
-And he's from a good family.
-How old is he?
-Forget it.
Agree to at least one date.
Even men in their fifties
go after women in their thirties
if they have the ability to.
Unless you plan on staying single.
Are you interested in remarrying?
Have you forgotten?
That I went after Mr. Seo?
With another guy, I mean.
What are those? Oysters?
-No, lobsters.
-I'm not too fond of those.
Blue crabs are better.
Or maybe snow crabs.
They're not just for you, you know.
Like me, Sa-hyeon prefers blue crabs too.
-Place them in the fridge for now.
-Yes, ma'am.
Keep it down. You'll wake him.
-Hye-ryung likes stir-fried lobster.
-I see.
-Is she coming by today?
-It's been a few days.
She seems to have grown attached
to our Jeong-bin.
Isn't that right?
There's no need to sigh.
If not the best, then the second-best.
It'll all work out.
I guess Song Yuan
was just a brief encounter in his life.
She would have lived out her life
had she not met Sa-hyeon.
We should just accept what has happened.
Thanks to her,
we were able to welcome Jeong-bin.
Our precious little grandson.
U-ram, have some persimmons.
Don't worry about your dad too much.
Exposure to cold, overfatigue, or stress
can cause that condition easily.
It happened to a friend of mine
while writing a doctoral dissertation.
-Are you sure it's treatable?
-Yes.
I saw him this morning
and he's in much better shape.
Dig in.
-I'll cut the rest.
-I'm already full.
I'm sure you're aware
that I've been dating Mr. Seo.
Of course.
He asked me to marry him.
-When?
-He'd rather not drag out the inevitable.
-You should marry him.
-Is that what you want?
Must you ask?
Of course she's on the same page.
I'm not sure. It doesn't seem right.
What do you mean?
I'm fond of Mr. Seo,
but this is a different matter.
It really isn't.
How can being a nice family friend
be the same as being our stepdad?
Would you prefer some old man instead?
Can't it just always be the three of us?
-Hey!
-All right.
Mom, it's not like
we'll be living together forever.
Aren't you going to marry?
-Even high school kids have girlfriends.
-I won't.
I doubt you plan to die a single man.
Must she give up
a new chapter in her life for us?
That wouldn't be the case.
What about her happiness?
Men like Mr. Seo don't come by easily.
What will you call him?
Can you call him Dad?
My friend's dad seems like an uncle.
He had her at 22, you see.
He married early, right out of school.
Mr. Seo may not seem like it,
but he's the same age as Dad. Right?
We can call him that.
Don't be a baby, but be her son, U-ram.
Are you looking for something specific?
How many carats is that?
Two, sir.
The D color, VVS1 clarity,
five-carat diamond, please.
It'll have to be shipped from New York,
so it will take some time.
How long?
NAM GA-BIN
So even though
we only recently started dating,
he seems like an old friend.
We're comfortable around each other.
How fascinating. Right, U-ram?
Is it okay to say that I'm happy for you?
-Aren't you?
-Me too.
I'm embarrassed to tell you about us.
Don't be, Mom.
The heavens are rewarding you.
He'd like to take us out to dinner.
Of course. I can't wait.
Who is she?
Are you saying he already
found someone else?
-I doubt it.
-I asked if someone had caught his eye
and he said it wasn't his eye but his ear.
He never lies. More than anything,
he's too straightforward.
He doesn't care if he hurts others.
I don't know what to say.
Is he eating…
and doing well?
He left for the German office today.
-For good?
-No.
He's the devil I shouldn't have met.
It wasn't love.
I know he's my brother,
but even I can't condone his ways.
There are times when
I don't understand him myself.
Although, he'd say the same thing.
Anyone you end up with
will be better than Dong-ma.
He can be cruel
when it comes to the women in his life.
Where did you get that pretty shirt?
It's from my favorite brand.
You could probably wear that
even when you're not golfing.
I normally do.
Good shot.
Pi-young, you should
take my wife out to golf often.
But you're the one with the cleaner swing.
I'd be more at ease with you.
A few classes and private lessons here
helped me improve.
Really? Maybe I should
take some classes too.
You'll see an improvement in no time.
Then it's settled.
I'll leave my wife in your hands.
Mom, I gained a kilogram.
Hardly. You grew taller, that's all.
Mom, can't you stock up on some juice?
Of course not. That's only sugar water.
I'll probably live forever.
-Thanks to me?
-Who else?
A long and healthy life
is how you can do everything you want.
I'll play video games every day
when I become a grandma
and eat everything I want.
My dream is to die while eating.
I'm not kidding.
Ice cream, juice, chips, and chocolate.
There are too many delicious snacks.
Nothing brings you more happiness
than good health.
Cancer cells live on sugar, remember?
They have good taste, I give them that.
Ji-a.
Is it normal for people
to have a change of heart?
Or is it not?
Well, it should stay the same.
Only a saint would achieve that.
For people, it's perfectly normal.
You argued with your best friend So-yul
over something trivial
and now you hardly talk.
You did nothing wrong
and what So-yul did wasn't that bad,
but that's what happened.
It's the same with me.
I no longer feel the same about your dad.
Just like others, he made a few mistakes.
And they upset me.
I wanted to let it slide,
-but I couldn't.
-What kind of mistake did he make?
Not everyone is perfect.
I get why he did it,
but now I've gotten used to
living apart from him.
I like the life we built here together.
Are you upset?
A little. Shouldn't you
have cut him some slack?
It's not about forgiving
or teaching each other a lesson.
I find it better to have a separate life.
And while doing so,
if he and I find someone
we are more fond of,
we will begin new relationships.
Are you and Dad divorced?
Actually, yes.
I'm sorry
for deciding on it without asking you.
I knew something was up.
You'll learn once
you marry someone later on in life.
You could disappoint your husband
and you could be the one
who's disappointed.
To forgive or to divorce.
A choice must be made.
In life,
we go through many events
and make countless decisions.
Decisions that aren't easy to make.
Whether you calmly accept our divorce
or throw a tantrum is up to you.
There's nothing I can do
if you neglect your studies
because of your sadness.
Your life is yours to manage.
I can't live it for you.
Children and parents
can't live each other's lives for them.
So take your time and choose wisely.
Some things in life
are controllable by willpower,
but some are not.
When I walked down the aisle
in my wedding dress,
I thought I'd be happy forever.
Life not going as planned
doesn't mean you'll be unhappy.
Do I look sad to you these days?
Do I seem depressed?
There are many paths for people to take.
Some even live without ever marrying.
A coworker of mine
only found true happiness
after a third marriage.
There's no right or wrong.
We just have different paths in life.
Was what Dad did unforgivable?
It depends on how you look at it.
I guess you can say
I could have understood him
and looked past his flaws.
It's just
I couldn't bring myself
to hug him and kiss him anymore.
It seemed off.
And still living in the same house
only made things
uncomfortable and unnatural.
I like how things currently are.
There's no big difference.
It's not like you can't see your dad.
We can go out to eat from time to time.
The only difference is we're not living
under the same roof.
Is this hard for you to accept?
You'll understand with age.
Right now, you won't understand
no matter how much I explain it.
I only thought
this happened in soap operas.
This can't even be categorized
as misfortune.
When I was a young girl,
I heard my aunt humming this song.
"Heartbreaking Mia-ri Hill."
This may not be word-for-word,
but the lyrics go like this.
Gunpowder smoke blinds me
As I wander not knowing where I'm going
You
Bound with string wire
Look over your back again and again
Limping barefooted
You're dragged over this hill
The Mia-ri Hill
Full of heartache and sorrow
Imagine that scene.
It depicts a woman watching her husband
get dragged to North Korea
bound tightly with string wire.
Imagine that it happened to you.
What if that's the last image you see
of the person you love?
It's sad. It scares me too.
There's no need to be lost or in pain
over what will never change.
What I hope
is for you to maturely accept this.
The fact that I have as well is why
I'm still on good terms with your dad.
Your dad and I
started off as strangers anyway.
It's like having a falling out
with a friend.
At first, I thought some time apart
would help me forgive and forget.
That's why I kept the truth from you.
But now I've adapted to this way of life.
If we were still under the same roof,
I'd nag your dad from time to time.
How would that make your Dad feel
when he's a prideful man?
I get it.
I understand what you're saying.
Your dad has adapted too.
There's no man in this world
who enjoys being nagged anyway.
Besides, your grandma's been
taking good care of him.
Keep your distance from the golf ball
and hit the golf ball.
I think you're quite good.
-Yes?
-Hello?
-Can't you hear me?
-Where are you, Dad?
The music's loud.
I'm out with some friends.
A club?
Somewhere similar.
-Got it.
-What's this about?
-It's nothing.
-I see.
-I'm hanging up.
-Sure.
It was Ji-a. We should get home.
-But we're still dancing.
-You got to loosen up, didn't you?
As if that was enough.
I guess I don't need to worry.
The children accepted it
easier than expected.
It's what I said.
Let's get married before the holidays.
Are you sure about
not asking your family first?
-I don't need my father's permission.
-Still, it doesn't seem right to me.
It's not like he asked for my opinion
when he remarried.
But you and your brother are close.
I once met him while out with Hye-ryung.
Don't they make a great couple?
What about Dad though?
-What about him?
-He'll be shocked to hear this.
You reap what you sow.
We may not need him
since we have Mom,
but we are all that he has.
Out of sight, out of mind.
Besides, I don't care
if we're related by blood.
It's natural to not care about
someone who abandoned us.
-But I still do.
-What are you getting at?
-Are you at ease?
-Should I not be?
Just think about Mom and her happiness.
Don't get in the way.
-I'm not trying to.
-Then what is it?
Doing nothing is how you can help.
Have you not seen how cheerful she's been?
She seems more vibrant
and we like her this way.
This'll hurt Dad.
What about us? He hurt us first, you know.
He made his own bed to lie in.
I'm sure he regrets it.
The ship has sailed.
He dumped his own fortune.
And now Mom's being rewarded.
So let this teach you to be a good person.
Not good in a gullible way, but sensible.
It was a long road.
Are you sure I'm fully recovered?
Yes, just come in from time to time
for moxibustion.
Thank you, doctor.
Don't overexert yourself
and maintain mental stability.
Stress can be the cause of all diseases.
Yes, doctor.
Do you have that in size 66?
-Yes, sir.
-I'll take it.
-Is it a gift?
-Yes, for my wife.
ALARM
Hello?
Are you up?
-I want to stay in bed.
-Aren't you well?
It's just that I wish you were here.
I miss you every day and every moment.
Then shorten your trip and come.
I think my stay will be extended a week.
Then I'll see you in the new year
which isn't bad.
It's not bad, you say? Take that back.
-When will you quit your job?
-Maybe ten years later.
You're so mischievous.
-Cheer me up?
-How?
Scream at the top of your lungs for me.
That'll get me out of bed.
Wash up and head out.
And don't forget to eat something.
Are you telling me to hang up? Really?
-Yes.
-I don't want to.
-I'm hanging up.
-That's cold.
-Be nice, will you?
-How much nicer can I be?
No more childish complaints.
You'll be the only one
who gets to see this side of me.
What would you do for me if you were here?
-Tell me what you'd do for me first.
-Love.
I'll love you in every way.
I'd make you breakfast.
Many prioritize eating,
but I value love more.
Love takes priority for me no matter what.
Breakfast isn't why
I asked you to marry me.
Pi-young.
-Yes?
-Ich liebe dich.
Have a good day then.
-Who was that?
-My gosh.
Why are you jumpy?
-Did you wrap up the show?
-Yes.
It was Ji-a.
-School's on break, isn't it?
-Of course.
Please bring the receipt
should you want a refund.
Sure thing.
I'm going to get you whatever I want.
I already have too many clothes.
So you're greedy in a way.
My brother sends some over
while shopping for himself.
Aren't you thirsty?
Ji-a.
Could we talk? I'll buy you bread.
You're lucky to have a brother like him.
I bet he has a girlfriend.
-What is it?
-He's too much of a player.
He sees a lot of women?
No, but his relationships don't last.
He leads them on
under the premise of marriage.
It's only a phase.
Better he breaks their hearts now
than breaking them later
after getting married.
-I'm worried he'll stay this way.
-What's his type?
He doesn't have one.
What about Hye-ryung?
I'm not saying we should set them up, but…
It'll only be a fling.
Only set him up
if you want to be cursed at.
What do you think about Mr. Seo?
-In what way?
-He and my mom are getting married.
Really?
But it's not bad news.
I'm surprised though. When's the date?
-In the new year.
-Aren't you happy about it?
It's just that I feel bad for my dad.
He's better than any other guy though.
I don't know.
My mom seems happy,
but I'm not.
Why would you be happy
when it's not your wedding?
-What did Hyang-gi say?
-She loves the idea.
The same goes for my mom,
but your mom spent her life
raising you and your sister.
Think of it as returning the favor.
Isn't there a way for everyone,
including my dad, to be happy?
We'll want to marry someone
when we're older.
In dramas and movies,
you see the heartbreak in situations
where family members don't approve.
Don't be that person.
-My mom and dad also divorced.
-Why?
I don't know. All I can do is speculate.
You must be just as upset.
Will we be this way as adults too?
Is he asleep?
Yes.
Do you have the magic touch?
You're even better than we are.
Is Sa-hyeon this late every day?
Well, it's the year-end.
-Does he check on Jeong-bin?
-Of course.
He checks on him on his way out as well.
-What are you up to on Christmas Day?
-I have a formal event and other plans.
-Will a pre-recorded show be aired?
-Yes.
You're probably tired,
so head home and rest.
You keep stopping by.
-We're grateful, but--
-It hasn't even been an hour.
This is just as relaxing anyway.
Isn't Jeong-bin's 100th day
the same as Lunar New Year?
No, it's a week apart.
What a relief.
You'll be throwing a party, right?
We'll have the family gather,
order a rice cake,
and hand it out to our neighbors.
-Can you make it?
-If my schedule allows it.
-I should be here if I can.
-You know…
-Hye-ryung.
-Yes?
How about you two get back together?
It seems inevitable.
At least that's what we believe.
There's no need to doubt his loyalty now
and there's nothing about him
that'll give you a hard time.
It never crossed my mind.
If you're not going to stay single,
isn't Sa-hyeon the best choice out there?
In what way?
All men make that kind of mistake in life.
-Except me, of course.
-We're not forcing you.
It's only our opinion.
We mention it because
you seem to adore Jeong-bin.
I feel bad for him.
Exactly. Which is why
if you can be his mother,
you both…
Well, Jeong-bin will be one lucky boy
and we'll be less worried.
Sa-hyeon can't move on that quickly.
Time will solve that.
It always does.
Of course.
That's why people say,
"Out of sight, out of mind."
I've been out of mind for him for a while.
They just weren't meant to be.
Besides, she was too old for him.
I'm older than him too.
Not by today's standards.
Being a year older is nothing.
It's over between us.
You didn't end on bad terms.
I poured my disappointment
and hatred out on him.
It ended well because I backed off.
I don't have
any feelings left for Sa-hyeon.
I just keep thinking about the baby.
Exactly. Consider it as doing a good deed.
Sa-hyeon will be able
to meet a nice woman.
We can't accept just any woman again.
For your good deeds,
the heavens will grant you
a nice daughter-in-law.
-Are you leaving?
-Yes.
As if I'd take back a shell of a man.
Serves you right.
Did you see Hye-ryung on the way in?
-No.
-But she just left.
My son, did you have a good day today?
-Dinner?
-I've eaten.
You should wash your hands first.
-Sure. Was he fussy today?
-No.
My poor sweet puppy.
She'll give in
if I ask for forgiveness every day,
given our kids and her personality.
Which book did you order?
RECIPIENT: LEE SI-EUN
Is that an engagement ring?
Yes.
Is that real diamond?
-Of course.
-How many carats is this?
It's too big to wear every day.
I couldn't wear it to the office.
Why not? You totally should.
-He can obviously afford it.
-Don't tell U-ram about this.
Why not? You should have been
treated this way a long time ago.
Enough with the worn-out t-shirts.
Start sleeping in feminine pajamas now.
I'll buy one for you.
-It's fine.
-I saved up working part-time.
Mr. Seo likes that I'm down-to-earth.
This isn't what you'd call down-to-earth.
To put it in good words, it's frugal,
in bad words, it's being a penny-pincher
but that's rude.
Gosh, this is beautiful.
No wonder people go crazy over diamonds.
Don't worry, I'll doll myself up now.
Being a woman,
I know what's nice and pretty.
I just had to give that up for the family.
Hae-ryun, I'm truly grateful.
I guess it's true that hardships
can be a blessing in disguise.
We've been barking up the wrong tree.
As Hae-ri says, we fell flat on our faces.
She could already be seeing someone.
Already?
She's pretty
and has always had many male fans.
Regardless of gender,
it helps no one
to only look pretty on the outside.
Their character matters more.
Our youngest son
is one of those pretty faces.
Sa-hyeon's a good man.
On the inside and the outside.
But no one knows that.
Besides, we need Hye-ryung
to think that way about him.
But he really messed things up with her.
If not an unmarried man,
isn't the devil you know better?
It's better to be with
someone you already know.
Exactly.
Hell hath no fury like a woman scorned.
I know that all too well.
She's been coming by
every three days to see Jeong-bin,
so I thought she was interested.
She won't come by anymore
now that we've scared her off.
So be it.
Find someone decent for Sa-hyeon, then.
He needs to be on board first.
Her grave is still fresh.
Just push women on him.
You know how it is.
One is bound to catch his eye.
I heard that Mr. Seo and U-ram's mom
are getting married.
-Why didn't you tell me?
-It's between grown-ups.
Your issues sometimes involve us too.
Did U-ram tell you?
-What did he say?
-He feels bad for his dad.
I know that humans
are naturally forgetful,
but what about what he did to them?
You know how kind and forgiving he is.
-What about you?
-I can't say I'm cruel.
That's true. Only the kind-hearted
find success in life.
Don't you forget that.
Look how U-ram's mom
is being rewarded in her later years.
Mom, please don't say things like that.
-Why not?
-You sound like a fortune-teller.
That's a profession too,
and you shouldn't discriminate.
I bet you'll be seeking some out
with friends when you're older.
-Why?
-For fun, of course.
How you choose to treat people
and what you choose to do
can change your fate.
Just don't become an ardent believer.
Got it.
But what puzzles me is,
why did Mr. Seo
pick U-ram's mom and not you?
I get that they met as kids, but…
I didn't know you liked him as well.
Hyang-gi's taking us to a bookstore today.
That's great.
I had lunch plans with
Hye-ryung and U-ram's mom.
You meet every day.
How can you have so much to talk about?
It hasn't been every day lately.
Things haven't been smooth between
Hye-ryung and U-ram's mom,
so I'm taking them out to talk.
I guess grown-ups are just like us.
You sulk and argue too.
We don't necessarily argue,
but misunderstandings sometimes occur.
Grown-ups aren't that different.
We must all keep maturing.
I bet I'll be less stressed
when I grow up.
No more studying.
That'll be replaced
with worrying about making a living.
You can think of it as stress,
or as a challenge.
Have you told Ji-a about me?
-No.
-Isn't it okay to tell her now?
She saw me that day,
so wouldn't she remember?
When the time is right.
Which is when, exactly?
Is marriage even on your mind?
It's the hospital.
Hello?
Ji-a, wait. It's your dad.
SUNRISE AT THE WEST SEA
ESSAY COLLECTION
Do you know me?
-Yes.
-Why did my dad leave?
He got a call from the hospital.
It must be an urgent patient.
I'll talk to her for a bit.
Call us.
What if they fight?
As if a grown-up
would argue with a little girl.
Ji-a can be scary when angry.
I think we should keep an eye on her.
I think we met.
How about a beverage?
They have ice cream here.
An orangeade, please.
Did everyone go out?
Yes, but without telling me.
It sure is nice to be home.
You should have called.
-I even got you a gift too.
-Mine as well?
Are you his girlfriend?
-Yes.
-Since when?
-It's a long story.
-Has it been over a year?
I'll take that as a yes.
-My mom knows, doesn't she?
-Yes.
We're actually quite close.
I even call her by her name.
I have her number
saved on my phone as well.
We meet once in a while.
What do you two talk about?
Just this and that.
You should ask her.
Do you like my dad?
-Yes.
-Is it love?
Are you going to marry him?
Probably.
I've been wanting to meet you.
Me? Why?
No reason. It'll be nice
for you, me, and your mom to get together.
I don't get it.
If you're on good terms,
my mom would have told me.
It must have been hard for her to explain.
Tell me about your family.
I grew up in the US since the age of five
and I moved to Korea
less than two years ago.
My two younger brothers
and parents still live there.
My biological father was in Korea,
but he recently passed away.
My name is A Mi. Mi is my first name.
I don't really care.
I've always wanted a little sister.
Are you saying you want me
to see you as my big sister?
You just said you're friends with my mom.
In Korea, we call this
a mess of a family tree.
Do you have a job?
I shot a few commercials up until recently
and had a minor role in a movie.
Ms. Sa asked me to take Ji-a home.
Why? Can't I have my burger?
She said to come right away.
It must be urgent.
Do you live at my house…
with my dad?
Please tell my dad
that I wish him a good life.
It won't kill us
to have a heavy meal at lunch.
Of course not.
Shouldn't you lose some weight
for the big day?
I probably should.
But you're naturally slim and slender.
Was there a grand proposal?
The ring said it all.
He proposed to me at a church.
-I left it at home.
-A diamond ring?
-Yes.
-How many carats?
I doubt he would have gotten her
a small one.
Are you going to move into his place
after the wedding?
Isn't it obvious?
That reminds me.
Did your ex have a boy or a girl?
They had the baby, right?
-A boy.
-Well, I'm glad.
Chairman Pan must be thrilled.
Not really.
His youngest son
didn't get to marry the mother.
I guess you can say he's a widower now.
What do you mean by that?
-Did they break up?
-She died straight after giving birth.
-My gosh!
-What happened?
She paid for her sins.
The baby's adorable. He really is.
I don't know if Sa-hyeon's parents
are shameless or clueless, but…
-Why?
-They want us to get back together.
Of course his parents would want that.
Why is that?
I'm fully aware of how they were.
They cared for the pregnant mistress.
I'm the one who demanded this divorce.
Wasn't it the other way around?
It's the same thing.
So how could they possibly
want me to take him back in?
Either way, there's no need
for you to doubt him anymore.
-As long as he can move on.
-As if.
He'll keep her buried in his heart
and forever miss her.
Divorce is better
than losing a spouse by death.
What he did
erased any feelings for him I had.
It's the same for me as well.
What about the little one though?
Tell me about it.
It kills me to think about the poor baby.
-Does he smile at you?
-He's barely two months old.
-They smile even after one.
-Boys sometimes take longer.
His grandparents will raise him.
Right. They're staying in Seoul for now.
It must be hard for them.
Babysitting isn't a joke.
They're not that old.
Just imagine how fun it was for them
to care for the pregnant mistress.
What is this?
-A tree.
-For Christmas?
-Yes.
-Where should we put this?
Over here.
-Where is Sa-hyeon?
-He went out.
A high school friend is getting married.
I'm off to the restroom.
Sure.
A MI
Don't you think Hye-ryung's a bit harsh?
She tends to only think about herself.
The mother must have
held on for dear life.
I know.
The doctor said deformation
didn't mean infertility.
What have I got to lose?
I should just make my play.
Older brothers are said to be better,
but Mr. Seo in his fifties
while his brother is in his thirties.
His brother is way better then.
I still hate Ms. Lee's guts,
but throwing her a bone would be wise.
Thank you.
-Here you go.
-We'll take it for the road.
-Thank you.
-My pleasure.
Christmas Day is only two days away.
Who would set it up?
Us.
We're not kids, you know.
And it's not like we're in a festive mood.
Jeong-bin won't understand it.
Why wouldn't he when he has eyes?
He gazes up at us and follows the rattle.
But we're not in the mood.
Well, it's not just for Jeong-bin.
It's for Sa-hyeon too.
He comes home to two old bats
and a housekeeper.
I thought a tree
would lift his spirits
and our overall mood.
Let's get it done before he gets back.
When will we get all of these done?
It'll take us all night.
Stop complaining and just do it.
-What are these?
-Tree lights.
-Who's that?
-Probably Song Yuan's friend.
I'm right.
She was in the neighborhood
and wanted to see the baby.
I never thought they actually meant it.
You should keep working
even though Mr. Seo tells you to quit.
I'd be lost if you leave the show too.
Gosh, when it's your name on the title?
Producer Han's not only weird,
but she's bad at her job too.
The song choices are a mess.
You've been on our website, right?
She's a kiss ass
and easily grovels to those with power.
We only need to hang in there for a year
and then you'll be back.
She won't back down.
Director Jung will have no choice
once the ratings plummet.
She even asked me
to introduce someone
to her talented niece.
-She asked me too.
-What does she do?
She's a cellist for an orchestra.
By the looks of it,
her brother's quite well off.
From her photo,
I saw plastic surgery madness.
-Plastic surgery?
-And a lot of it.
Maybe you could consider her
as a sister-in-law.
Ban will be against it.
-Why?
-Because his brother's a player.
He's handsome and wealthy.
Of course women
would throw themselves at him.
I bet he's seeing someone.
He was, but he ended it,
and now he's at the Munich branch.
Okay, nice. There's a chance for me.
-They must have an office in Munich too.
-Right.
What about your wedding though?
He'll be back in a few days.
Won, your baby's a sweetheart.
It takes a player to handle a player.
The pedestrian crossing sign
has turned green.
Please cross the crosswalk.
But a true player
never reveals their true colors.
Look at this innocent face.
What about the musical actress
who was with you at the funeral?
She's been having a hard time lately.
We all go through hardships in life.
That's just how life is.
Are you already packing up the tree?
But Christmas is two days away.
On the contrary.
He just got one for us today.
In hopes of creating a festive mood.
Wouldn't Jeong-bin love to see the lights?
-It'll help develop his senses.
-Of course.
-I'm actually good at decorating trees.
-We'd appreciate the help.
My wife's already been
nagging me about this.
For making a fuss.
Hyang-gi dropped you off, right?
Yes.
Grandma's back.
-Did she call?
-Yes. And she bought gifts for us.
-Did she call us over?
-I said you were out.
I didn't expect this to be so much work.
It's all done. You should sit.
Jeong-bin, take a look. Isn't it pretty?
-Is that sikhye?
-Yes.
Please have some. You must be hungry.
Not at all.
I'll watch the baby
while you buy her some dinner.
Not at all. I need to get going.
Goodness. Did we keep you here
when you're busy?
No, I just need to order a cake.
They'll be sold out on the day.
So?
She didn't say
what they talked about and I couldn't ask.
You should borrow a page
from Ji-a's book sometimes.
You want me to be like her?
Yes, since you explode from time to time.
With good reason.
You know what it's been like.
Whatever.
I saw a different side to Ji-a today.
It's Dad!
-Dad, your paralysis is gone.
-It is.
Are you done with your treatments?
Yes.
-Here. I wanted to thank you.
-There's no need.
You took me to a clinic
that came highly recommended.
It's fine.
You're embarrassing me
in front of the kids.
I bet you haven't had dinner.
They're not hungry,
so we were taking our time.
May I sit?
Is there something you need to say?
You should sit too.
I'll cut right to the chase.
Let's go back to how things were.
Go back how? After all this time?
I have repented hundreds of times.
And I will not make
the same mistake again. Ever.
Please forgive me.
Forgive me, guys.
I'm going to devote myself
to you and the family.
This is wrong. It's over between us.
I'll do whatever is needed
to earn your forgiveness.
Yours as well.
It was stupid of me.
I didn't realize
that I had what most people desire.
I looked back on my ways
and repented with tears.
I'll beg on my knees if I must.
Are you here to confuse the children?
-No, to apologize.
-You should go for now.
Go home and meet me at Deung tomorrow.
-Do you have plans for Christmas Eve?
-We do.
-U-ram, what about you?
-We're going skiing.
With Mom and Hyang-gi.
Where? Yongpyong?
I'll drive.
-Did you throw my skis out?
-I did.
I'll buy a pair or rent one at the resort.
Actually, I'm fine with just driving you.
Mom…
You can go without me
if you don't feel like it.
Follow me out.
Mom, you can talk here.
Come on.
-I'll get going then.
-Sure.
Dad will be shocked.
What do we do?
You should go after them.
You stay home.
It's late, so have tea instead.
Two cups of chamomile tea, please.
MR. SEO
Good health is everything.
Anything cold is bad for you.
You should cut back on coffee too.
Letting it soak for too long--
I'm getting married.
You're getting married?
-With whom?
-That's what you want to know?
-This must be a joke.
-Since when do I joke?
Do the kids know?
-When?
-In the new year. Next month.
Don't pry. It's a long story.
Do the kids approve?
Did you have their approval?
They're not against it.
Don't confuse them
with this issue ever again.
What does he do?
I don't need to answer that
and you have no right to ask.
I wouldn't do anything about it.
I don't want to explain myself to you.
I made a fool out of myself
in front of the kids.
Do you really love him?
Or is there another reason?
What other reason?
You don't easily open your heart.
How long have you known him?
It turns out
we knew each other a long time ago.
We're done here, right?
Take good care of yourself
so that the kids won't worry.
Is he taking you skiing?
Why didn't you come in?
-My gosh.
-Were you leaving?
I brought over
a portable seat for Jeong-bin,
but I thought Father
would be uncomfortable.
Don't be absurd.
Shouldn't the housekeeper
take out the trash?
I wanted some fresh air.
-Here. It looks heavy.
-It's actually not.
Sa-hyeon's father is taking a shower
and Sa-hyeon went to a friend's wedding.
An evening wedding?
No, but he probably stayed behind
for the after-party.
-Which friend?
-He teaches English.
Oh, him. He must have found someone
that satisfies his high standards.
-My gosh.
-Hye-ryung's here.
Sure.
-I'll wash my hands here.
-Sure.
-You probably haven't eaten.
-I had some cake.
Gosh, he's awake.
Allow me.
He had his milk,
so he must have wet himself.
Hey.
What's that?
A portable seat.
Gosh, how cute is this?
They make
just about everything these days.
When will we get to take him out?
When he can sit up.
He could sit with us at the dining table.
We could eat with him.
Nice and dry.
Feels good, doesn't it?
Let's stretch.
Jeong-bin.
I just suddenly got emotional.
Is your world falling apart?
Maybe I was just seeing things.
That can't be.
You didn't even call.
-I just can't believe it.
-I did well, right?
You're the best.
He didn't call or text yesterday.
Maybe he fell for a blonde in Germany.
I'm here. Should I go up?