EPISODE 13
It feels like yesterday
when we all came here together.
You may as well enjoy your time here.
I guess it's just not my day.
Dad saw a photo of you.
He said you look haggard
and is worried about you.
-You should eat more.
-I am eating.
You're eating much less now.
-I feel good and light.
-Even I think you look haggard.
That's okay as long as my soul looks fine.
What about my soul? Does it look okay?
Mr. Seo.
Hello.
I see you're here with your mother-in-law.
-I am.
-This is my younger brother.
-Biological?
-Yes.
Goodness. I didn't know you had a brother.
She's Ms. Sa, my colleague.
Hello. I'm Seo Dong-ma.
Come to think of it,
you do kind of look alike.
Goodness. Hello.
-Fancy seeing you here.
-Likewise.
They're brothers.
She's my mother-in-law.
I see. Hello.
You're both so handsome.
Shouldn't you get going?
-Is it just you two?
-Yes.
-See you next time.
-Goodbye.
-Mr. Seo.
-Yes?
I got divorced.
Why tell him?
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
He would have found out eventually.
Maybe she's joking.
Who jokes about that?
She's not much of a joker.
And yet, they're golfing together?
She's a second wife.
So she's not his real mother.
People could mistake her
for Ms. Sa's aunt or sister.
-I should tell the chairman that I'm here.
-Does he not know?
No.
He'll probably come running.
Isn't that him?
Goodness, speak of the devil.
Mun-ho.
Hey.
-Hello.
-Are you here with your family?
-Daughter-in-law.
-Hello.
It's been a while.
We met at the funeral last year.
Right. I'm sorry I couldn't greet you
properly because of everything.
Don't worry about it. Sit down.
Enjoy your time here
and see you next time.
Okay.
Thank you for the green tea.
My pleasure.
You look well.
-Take good care of her.
-Okay.
I'll pay for your drinks.
-It's okay.
-Really?
-Goodbye then.
-Goodbye.
-See you around.
-Yes, ma'am.
Honey, you want orangeade, right?
Yes.
-Two glasses.
-Okay.
You were so cold.
She was taken aback
because you were acting so differently.
They have a great relationship.
After Song Yuan gives birth,
I'll tell Coach Choi to teach her
how to play golf.
-Who'll take care of the baby?
-She has us.
About Hye-ryung…
I somehow feel like we were duped.
She never wanted a baby.
A woman can't get pregnant
whenever she wishes.
It happens in good time.
She needs God's blessing.
I wonder why God blessed
Song Yuan with a child?
Every now and then
I think about what Sa-hyeon said.
We can go in now.
-Let's go to Daejeon.
-Now?
-You don't want to watch the movie?
-Yes.
-Why?
-I'll tell you later.
Over there.
You don't need to prepare dinner for us.
We already ate.
You may be full, but he must be hungry.
After all, he's a full-grown man.
I'm not hungry. It ate a lot.
-Are you tired?
-It's fine. I just golfed today.
That producer you work with.
Ms. Sa?
Yes. She came to golf
with her mother-in-law.
It was nice to see them get along.
What do you think?
You have no interest in us.
You haven't asked about it.
You got matching rings?
Yes. It's been a while.
You've been doing
everything she wants these days.
She's been doing what I want.
-It was your idea?
-Yes.
-Why?
-Stop asking so many questions.
If Byeol-hui and Hae-ri were here,
they would've called that a lame reply.
I just wanted one.
Doesn't this ring make her look younger
than those huge ones
she used to wear?
Yes.
So what brings you two here?
They probably just wanted to visit us.
They don't need a reason to come here.
I'll divorce you.
I'll sign the papers.
Why all of a sudden?
Weren't you going to give it another try?
Aren't you glad?
Are you getting a divorce for her sake?
No.
It's because of him.
Did you say something?
No.
That woman, Song Won, must have
a big belly now.
Yes.
Did you say she was due next month?
Either next month
or the beginning of June.
Is that what you fought about?
Did you argue?
No. We were at the movies today,
and a pregnant woman passed us by.
And I saw him gazing at her
without even realizing it.
That broke my heart.
Get the papers ready by tomorrow.
You should be there when the baby is born
and be its father without shame.
Is that really the reason?
Yes.
What else could there be?
Do it before I change my mind.
I know the baby is the only thing
on your mind.
I can see that you're trying
not to show it with all your might.
Won't you regret it?
I shouldn't.
Is there anything you want to say?
I'm sure you're genuinely happy inside.
You desperately wanted a divorce.
He wasn't adamant about it.
-He had no other choice.
-You heard it too.
Right here.
He said he loved her.
That was also because
he felt responsible for the baby.
It doesn't matter.
Just like how I'm being considerate
of him and your grandchild,
I'd like to ask the same from you.
Eventually,
everyone in the country will know
that I'm divorced.
I have great pride in myself.
And I got married during my heyday.
I understand.
We'll give you enough money.
We'll register your current house
under your name.
I want a different house.
I won't be able to live there by myself.
Sure, then. Look for a new place.
Could you get me a place
at Cheongdam Villa?
Cheongdam Villa? It sounds familiar.
I have my fair share of hardcore fans.
-That place has good security.
-Okay.
Only conglomerates live there.
Don't be ridiculous.
They live in houses
located in Hanchung-dong.
Their kids and the new rich live there.
-You think it's a waste?
-Okay.
Check if any are on the market.
Are you calling a realtor?
I can just look it up.
Would a house be enough?
I don't have any money saved up.
The property tax and maintenance cost
will amount to a hefty sum.
She's been working all this time.
She couldn't have spent it all
on housekeeping, so where did it all go?
And her job pays well.
I'm sure she has her own nest egg.
She just wants some alimony.
I heard the price of a luxury villa
is on a par with that of a small building.
She deserves that much.
We ought to give her what she wants.
We have enough money for that.
I know women tend to be fickle,
but she had vehemently refused
to divorce him.
But after seeing a pregnant woman,
she had a change of heart?
She may seem cold-hearted,
but she's kind at heart.
And I'm sure it was painful to live
with someone who didn't love her anymore.
It's not like she lacks anything.
I should let her know right now.
-Song Yuan?
-Yes.
Are you that happy?
I'll just visit her tomorrow.
Good thinking. It's late already.
Her due date is just around the corner.
I was frustrated,
but Sa-hyeon is the father after all.
He promised not to see his own baby.
That's ludicrous.
I pity Sa-hyeon too.
But my heart breaks for Song Yuan.
And the baby too.
Would it be odd to remarry right away?
Probably. They'll take care of it.
Sa-hyeon will be too excited to sleep.
I wonder what Hye-ryung's family
in Canada will say.
What if they fly over here
and cause a scene?
Why would they?
We agreed to pay her handsomely.
For parents, it's not about the money.
They must be upset and heartbroken.
They must hate Sa-hyeon.
She could meet someone better.
Many divorced stars
get married to bachelors.
That'd be great.
We'd be relieved as well.
Shouldn't you at least thank me?
How could I?
Is that because you're sorry?
Yes.
And to my parents as well.
Because I'm taking their money?
Is that it?
-No.
-Don't lie.
They're suffering because of me.
-I'm a terrible son.
-They'll be elated once the baby is born.
What is it?
The baby's gender.
I don't know.
You must want to call her, so go ahead.
Tell her.
Let her know.
Hello, Ms. Sa.
I hope it's not too late.
It's only 9 p.m.
-Are you out?
-Yes. Can you come out?
Ms. Lee is coming too.
Of course.
The phone is turned off.
Your call will be directed to…
I stopped by your house.
You must be out. The lights were off.
Please call me as soon as you get this.
How do I look?
-Elegant?
-I've never seen you like this.
This is new.
I do drink every now and then.
I called Hye-ryung too.
You only drank with us.
You never drank alone.
Right.
I tried to dress up nicely,
but I still look shabby.
That's fine. You don't live
to impress others.
Please give us two new glasses.
Si-eun, order some appetizers.
-This is fine.
-I know you like fruit.
Let's wait for Hye-ryung.
There she is.
You should've invited Mr. Seo too.
Do you think he'd come?
He'd come if you called him.
I saw him today at your golf club.
-I see.
-I thought he was an only child,
but I was wrong.
He was golfing with his younger sibling.
-A sister?
-A handsome brother.
Their parents must be good-looking.
Ms. Sa, did you score a hole-in-one today?
Or else, why would a perfect wife
call us out this late for drinks?
Is your husband on a business trip?
This perfect wife has resigned.
Are you protesting something at home?
We're in our cooling-off period.
Knock it off.
Are you not shocked?
I'm being serious.
Order your favorite wine.
Tonight's on me.
Let's finish this first.
Are you serious?
-Why?
-My husband also cheated on me.
That can't be.
I don't believe it.
How could Dr. Shin do such a thing?
Exactly.
You shouldn't think lightly
of other people's problems
or think that it won't happen to you.
Si-eun, men don't cheat
because of a reason.
Are you serious?
The cooling-off period will end soon.
What about Ji-a? Does she know?
Not yet.
Did he bring up the divorce?
Then just sweep it under the rug
just this once.
I witnessed it with my own eyes.
How could I?
It won't be easy, but do it for Ji-a.
I wanted to let it slide for our kids.
I said I'd give him another chance.
But he was determined to leave.
I just don't get men.
All women are the same.
No one's special.
All men are the same as well.
I decided
to get a divorce today.
He has an illegitimate child.
-Your husband?
-Yes.
-Is it a son?
-I don't know yet.
The baby's due next month.
-Do your in-laws know?
-Of course.
They're earnestly waiting
for the due date.
The world is ridiculous.
-Did he come clean?
-He got caught.
How did it happen?
Are you adamant about the divorce?
Do you know what's funnier?
She's ten years older than him
and nine years older than me.
What's wrong with us?
Should we blame ourselves
or those men?
I'm truly baffled.
At times, I wonder if I'm to blame.
Then I think no, I lack nothing.
I wonder if this is my fate.
It was a living hell.
I couldn't tell anyone.
It was eating me up.
I tried to let it slide,
but it was impossible.
I understand your situation
since a baby is involved.
But, for you, it's best to
forgive and move on.
He was one-of-a-kind.
Exactly. That's why it's even more
difficult to forgive him.
He was truly a wonderful husband
and a father.
-So how could he?
-It was a mistake.
But a serious one.
Not all misdeeds can be
considered a mistake.
In retrospect,
it may not be the best decision
as a mother.
After all, we're not perfect either.
That's how we are.
We shouldn't expect perfection.
I thought I was a perfect wife.
But he got a woman
nine years older than me pregnant.
-Is she pretty?
-She's over 40.
How pretty could she be?
She's just average.
I just don't get it.
Both of you lack nothing.
Is it because you didn't want a baby?
It did boil down to that.
We have a son and a daughter.
They all have excuses.
Just like how death is inevitable,
I guess all men are inevitably cheaters.
I agree. They're just wired that way.
They say experience
is the mother of wisdom.
Take Mr. Seo for example.
He doesn't date anyone.
-Married men are worse.
-Who knows?
You can tell by his face.
Your facial expression changes
when you're in a relationship.
You have sparkling eyes
and a different aura.
Mr. Seo seems uninterested in women.
He spent his weekend golfing
with his brother.
Maybe he was in a traumatic relationship.
Just like how there are playgirls,
there are also playboys.
Some women are elegant,
and some men are like Mr. Seo.
And it's impossible to tell
until you experience it yourself.
They all wear masks
when in a relationship.
Tell me about it.
My husband was obsessively clean,
so I never thought he'd cheat on me.
I guess this is just our fate.
Some women are blessed
with loyal husbands.
I know one.
Who knows what he's like?
Will you really not reconsider
your decision?
I've thought about this numerous times.
The phone is turned off.
Your call will be directed to voice mail.
There's a reason why you two
can easily decide to get a divorce.
What do you mean?
Don't you get it?
You're young.
You still have time to meet someone new.
And you're competent.
You're competent too.
Fifty-one is still a young age.
We don't always have it easy.
Thinking about everyone finding out
and the hardships I'll go through
already gives me a headache.
Many celebrities have gotten a divorce.
Men will soon start hitting on you.
If your husband doesn't get remarried
and still wants to get back with you,
you should do that.
How could he not remarry
when that young girl
is head over heels for him?
I would let him back if I were you.
He's competent and handsome.
I bet your husband will
come back to you with his child.
I'm not holding my breath.
If I thought that he'd come back,
I wouldn't have made this decision.
You never know what the future holds.
We had no idea we'd be talking
about such things a year ago.
Next year,
we could be celebrating your remarriage.
-Maybe yours?
-Or yours.
-Shouldn't you leave?
-I'm sleeping over.
I'll give you a massage.
It's because of work, right?
-It's because I'm old.
-Dad's turning 80 soon,
but he's still alive and well.
He's always been healthy.
-It's because of your work.
-And you?
I don't have any.
-What do you think?
-You always have an ulterior motive.
You're not sincere with people.
That's true.
This may sound like an excuse,
but I'm a businessman.
I need to read people's thoughts.
-It gets lonely.
-Are you?
-Or do you mean me?
-Keep that up,
and you'll be left
with only those who are sly.
Like me?
Do you think I treat you that way?
Be half as nice to women as you are to me.
Not materialistically,
but with your heart.
I can assure you.
That will be impossible in this life.
To celebrate being single again…
What was her name again?
Let's go watch Nam Ga-bin's performance.
We should go before it ends.
It's ending next week.
Did you already watch it?
No, she didn't.
Invite Hyang-gi too.
Or would she not want to hang out
with old women like us?
There's something I haven't told you.
Promise me you'll keep it a secret.
-Of course.
-I heard Ga-bin said that she was
-seeing someone when she was on our show.
-Right.
It's my ex-husband.
Did you know about this?
Are you serious?
They said they were getting married
right after the Lunar New Year.
I haven't heard from them.
They must have postponed it.
Did she appear on our show
not knowing who you were?
Thanks to her appearing on the show,
we found out about each other.
He had kept his mouth shut
and didn't even mention her name
because he was afraid I'd hurt her.
What about Hyang-gi?
She knows everything
and she's accepted it.
Gosh, that's just shocking.
I'm at a loss for words.
Were you home alone last night?
With the housekeeper.
Does Mom drink often?
No.
I've gone swimming with Dad.
Hello. I asked around for your number.
I want to talk to you.
I have something to discuss with you.
Sincerely, A Mi.
-I need to make a call.
-Sure.
Could you get me some coffee?
Have you had dinner yet?
What's Dad doing?
I'm at the salon.
We're airing a pre-recorded episode
since it's the weekend.
But I have a shoot.
Mom, don't worry and listen
to what I'm about to tell you.
News articles about me
will be released soon.
I'm getting divorced.
Sa-hyeon is at fault here,
but I'm also partly to blame.
There's a problem with my uterus.
So it's difficult for me to get pregnant.
Getting treatment
won't guarantee anything.
I don't want to go through that.
My in-laws don't know.
They just think I'm divorcing him
because of other reasons.
Please let Dad know
and make sure he doesn't worry too much.
Don't worry about me.
You know how strong I am.
EXTERNAL CALL
What brings you here?
Are you going to keep me out here?
I came alone.
OPEN
I've missed you so much.
Tomorrow,
we're going to court. She wants a divorce.
-Really. She wants a divorce.
-What did you say to her?
Nothing. She brought it up first.
Let's get married as soon as possible
once the papers are filed.
It must have been tough on your own.
Look how big you've gotten.
I'm sorry to bother you on your day off.
One Americano, please.
Milk tea for me.
I didn't know you were busy.
I'll just cut to the chase.
I was wondering
if you would ever change your mind.
You could have asked via phone or text.
Are you worried I might?
Don't worry. I always stand by my word.
Did you send your mother off well?
It must have been hard for you.
You think that's the
only reason I had a hard time?
I doubt you know the meaning of "ojirap"
since you were born in the US.
No, I was born here.
It means it's none of your concern.
I'm quite an honest person.
I want to be honest with you from now on.
I love him.
And that won't ever change.
Then why did you lie?
Yu-sin said that would be for the best.
How so?
I suffered just as much
as you did, Pi-young.
We're not close enough
to call each other on a first name basis.
Do you want me to console you?
I know it's not right for me to call you
by your first name, but…
You dated a married man.
Was that right?
-I'm sorry.
-If you can't fix your mistake,
"I'm sorry," won't cut it.
What you did hurt me
and you're trying to squirm
your way out with those two words.
-That's being irresponsible and brazen.
-You're right.
I know you're seeing
red and can't understand me.
But I don't hate you.
Because you're not
the victim in this story. I am.
Someone with a sound mind
wouldn't hate their victim.
I can swear too
and do even worse than that.
-Go ahead.
-Are you taunting me?
Not at all.
If you swear at me, I'll listen.
If you hit me, I'll just take it.
Yu-sin said you were a good person,
and I can see that.
Did he say it was okay to betray me
since I'm a good person?
It wasn't easy for him either.
Problem solved.
Now, you just need to be happy together.
My parents taught me better than this.
-I had no idea this would happen.
-I don't want your life story.
-Are you justifying yourself?
-Are you sure
you won't have a change of heart?
Who knows?
You just said you had no idea
things would pan out this way.
Could you address me by my first name
instead of calling me "you"?
As if we'd see each other again.
Do you seriously think we would?
If you're okay with it,
may I stay with him at his house?
-Just get married.
-He has no plans to do that right now.
He says he needs time.
We've never even been on a trip
or spent the entire day together.
I want to live under the same roof as him.
You don't need my permission to do that.
I don't live there anymore.
I have a strong desire for food
or materialistic things,
but they're incomparable
to my desire for love.
You love him that much?
I do.
I don't care what you guys do whether
it's living together or getting married.
I'll take that as a yes.
Did he tell you to ask me?
No. We rarely meet these days.
He's been quite depressed.
I heard his stepmother was his first love.
Didn't you know?
Did he not tell you?
Judging by the way she treated me,
it looked like she was jealous.
When she yanked my hair,
it hurt for an entire week.
Not only did she yank my hair,
but she twisted it as well.
She was so strong.
You're leaving?
We're done talking here,
and I gave you my answer.
-Right.
-I'm not a saint.
I'm holding back.
I'll do anything you say.
What if I tell you to break up with him?
I hope you live
happily ever after with him.
I understand what you mean,
but he's not that flirtatious.
He has great manners
and is upright.
That's why I fell in love with him first.
And he was swayed by my feelings.
I'm truly sorry.
I was wrong.
I'll live my entire life in repentance.
Did you hear about
how I met my biological father?
You probably won't believe it.
It's too surreal for me too.
Does this concern me?
I guess I missed having company.
Lately, I haven't been meeting anyone.
I've just been boxing.
Hey, Ji-a.
I'm out right now.
I'll be home soon. Okay.
I'm curious about Ji-a
and would love to meet her.
Don't cross the line.
Don't hesitate to call me if you're sick.
I can make porridge for you.
I'll take care of you.
I mean it.
Nothing beats youth or innocence.
I had neither. It must have felt new.
He sure is different from most men.
We were taken aback too.
Maybe she was just being rash.
Not at all. She called us on our way here.
She said she found a place
she could move into right away
and asked if we could sign the contract.
She said she'd leave right away
once we made the payment.
-Really?
-Yes.
It'll be uncomfortable living together
when you're splitting.
That's right.
Tomorrow, they'll hand over
their divorce papers,
and I'll buy her that house.
We'll finish everything in a day.
So relax.
-Your baby brought us luck.
-Precognitive dreams must be powerful.
Of course.
Shouldn't we get you some new furniture?
-Let's go shopping.
-Right now?
Are you not feeling well?
No. It's just too sudden.
I know it is sudden.
But give it a day,
and you'll be just fine.
This may sound wrong,
but I was too excited to sleep last night.
It felt like things
were finally going right.
Hye-ryung may be a bit prickly,
but she sure is decisive.
I doubt she had a change of heart
simply because he gazed
at a pregnant lady.
That was probably just an excuse.
Maybe someone around her
showed interest in her,
so she probably saw no point
in living with a distant husband.
And perhaps
she might realize that
this was a losing game.
Whatever it may have been,
it was a wise decision.
I never imagined
things would pan out this way.
-Neither did we.
-My grandchild.
Are you listening, my lucky grandchild?
Are you okay with walking?
Walking is good for easy labor.
Is that right?
She must be hungry. What are you craving?
Welcome.
-Should we check out the couch first?
-Sure.
A baby is on the way. It's our grandchild.
This couch is good for people with kids.
-It's nice and comfortable.
-It's popular.
It's perfect for pregnant women. Sit.
Go on. He wants to buy one for you.
-Be careful.
How is it?
Is this the moving company?
I'd like to ask about your price.
Not the entire family. Just me.
You're so silly.
This is good.
You should get new curtains.
Change up the house.
Hello, would you like
to browse these curtains?
This material is permeable
and lets in light.
It's our best product.
I'm going to move in with him
no matter what Yu-sin says.
He refuses to eat any of the side dishes.
I had to throw them out last week.
He only drinks alcohol and eats ramyeon.
He's lost so much weight.
What if he gets seriously ill?
We should take care of his health
whether we like him or not.
Don't you think so?
Just because of Yu-sin…
No wonder he's not hungry at all.
AUNT SEO-RI
-Hello?
-It's me.
-Hello.
-How are you doing?
-I'm getting by.
-The living must go on.
Pi-young, congratulate me.
I'm getting married.
Goodness, are you serious?
-Why wouldn't I be?
-With who?
Can you come over next month?
I should. I'll do a pre-recording.
Don't be shocked.
He's 20 years younger than me.
-Goodness.
-He's a sexy Filipino.
He cherishes me deeply.
He's Filipino?
Yes. He runs a small travel agency.
Seo-ri, I love you.
Did you hear that? He loves me.
That's the only Korean he knows.
Is he a bachelor?
He was married twice,
but he's pretty much a bachelor.
He divorced in less than a year
for both marriages.
Aunt, I think you should reconsider this
and not act rashly.
Are you trying to ruin my day?
You sure take after your mom.
To be frank, she's the reason why
I couldn't get married all this time.
Who were you drinking with?
You'll get sick.
You're the only woman for me.
I guess you're right.
Everyone else is gone.
She gave me permission.
-Who?
-Ji-a's mom.
I met her today.
She said she won't change her mind.
Still, this isn't right.
Why not? She said it's over.
And you're not going
to live here by yourself.
You said you'd marry me.
I don't want to be alone anymore.
-I'll come by often.
-My neighbors recognized me.
They saw me in a newspaper ad.
Whether it's work or success,
nothing matters if you're not by my side.
I feel the happiest when I'm with you.
And my mom doesn't call me anymore.
Move in when Ji-a
is old enough to accept this.
But Pi-young said she didn't mind at all.
-She didn't mean that in a good way.
-Whatever it may be…
What?
-Did you call her over?
-She told me I could live here.
Who? Ji-a's mom?
-Yes.
-Don't lie.
You can check with her.
I just met her today.
-Do you want to call her?
-Leave.
Get out, or I'll kick you out.
I'm going to stay.
You little…
Use your words. This isn't you.
Do you think that's possible?
Do you think she'd listen?
Did you hear what she said?
"I'm going to stay"?
How dare she run her mouth?
Gosh.
Leave while I'm still being nice.
Did you not hear me?
That's enough. I'm tired.
Are you allowing this?
No. Make her leave!
This is why I should be here.
How dare you come here?
You two can stay here.
I'll go to Seongbuk-dong.
It was sold last week.
They're moving in next month.
They're going to renovate the place.
Damn it.
-Hey!
-My name is Mi.
I'm A Mi.
I don't care what your name is.
You're not welcome here!
We're going to get married.
Let me be your daughter-in-law.
I don't want you to be my daughter-in-law.
Pi-young is the only one.
It's over for them.
She and Yu-sin have split up.
You and I will never be family.
Get out this instant!
Yu-sin.
How dare you put on a show?
Get up.
-Hello.
-Pi-young.
I'm at Yu-sin's place--
-Hello?
-Hello.
Did you let her come here?
I don't want to get involved.
It's their problem.
Will you just sit and watch?
You two aren't completely over.
You have Ji-a.
She said you allowed her to move in.
-I never said she couldn't.
-Why not?
Yu-sin will take care of it.
It's their problem.
And to be frank, I feel sorry for her.
What do you mean? Are you a saint?
He's bound to get married again.
-Sooner or later--
-Whatever!
Damn it.
What will you do?
I'll do my best.
Do what? To whom?
To you, Mother.
I may have been raised abroad,
but I watched how my mom treated
my grandma. I can do well.
I know how to be a daughter-in-law.
A daughter-in-law?
Please let me stay.
I can't stand to be alone anymore.
I find myself relying on alcohol.
Goodness. She's also an alcoholic?
Fine, stay here.
You'll be wanting to leave in no time.
Let's see how well you live
with your old first love
and your mistress.
You've made your bed.
-Mom.
-Yes?
May I come in?
Sure.
Are you hungry?
No. I think I'll be fine for tonight.
Dad must have eaten a lot too.
No, he said he was on a diet.
He looked thinner than last week.
Ji-a. Your great-aunt is getting married.
-Really?
-With a Filipino.
-He's 20 years younger than her.
-She's amazing!
Marriage isn't always peachy.
I'm going to respect your decision
even if you decide not to get married.
Why? Didn't you say
that you were glad you got married?
When you win some, you lose some.
I'm happy and thankful to have you.
But if I didn't get married,
I could have done more in society.
In any case, you need
to take responsibility for your decisions.
We'll just watch
and support you from behind.
So I hope you do the same for us.
I will. That's what I'm doing these days.
I put myself in your shoes,
and I think you'll be heartbroken
for at least a year.
I think of Grandma all the time too.
Could you get me a can of beer?
-I feel hot.
-Is it in the fridge?
Yes.
-Mom.
-Yes?
Maybe Dad's marriage fell through.
If not, why are they so quiet?
Maybe they postponed it.
They were preparing to get married
after the Lunar New Year.
All I hear about Nam Ga-bin
is her musical performance.
Maybe no news is good news.
Perhaps, they called it off.
-I doubt it.
-What will you do if that's the case?
What do you mean?
I know how soft-hearted you are.
I think you'll take him back.
Your dad isn't the type
to let go of his pride.
What if he does
and asks for your forgiveness?
That won't ever happen.
Even if it did, we can't go back.
Okay then.
Are we having stir-fried potatoes?
No, it's for the stew.
Doenjang stew with potatoes and zucchini.
Then two potatoes would be
more than enough.
You're sharp.
-You should cook today.
-How?
You always say that.
If you like something,
you should know how to make it too.
-Right?
-Yes.
There will be
many bachelors in the future,
and they won't have anyone
to cook for them.
So you should learn how to cook.
I bet you won't last ten days.
Ma'am, you don't need to come
for the time being.
You'll still get paid.
Where is she?
In the room.
WHY ARE YOU COMING OUT OF THERE?
Why were you in there?
I was unpacking.
Use that room.
Go on!
I'm not a child,
and I'll soon be his wife.
Not yet. Who knows what will happen?
How could I possibly sleep
in Ji-a's room? Right?
It doesn't matter
which room she sleeps in.
You won't get your way.
Aren't you coming?
Coming.
Get the lettuce and cucumber and
wash them. Julienne the carrots.
-Do you have the tool?
-I don't know.
Isn't that sea bream?
I use drinking water when I wash the rice.
Dry rice will soak up the water.
I don't want it to smell.
They sell assorted vegetables at shops.
Some are pre-washed too.
You just need to rinse them once.
That fish is tasty,
but the bones are too sturdy.
If one gets stuck in your throat,
you're done for.
A close friend of mine
has a brother who lives in Jeju.
He said you should avoid
eating black hairtail.
I'll tell you why later.
All that knowledge
must make you crave a lot of food.
You're right. I love eating.
Is this funny to you?
You should ask Yu-sin
for psychological counseling.
Right. Hold on.
How could he possibly have fallen for her?
Song Yuan should stay
with us until her due date.
Yes, I agree.
Should we tell
Byeol-hui's family while we're at it?
Tell them tomorrow.
They're probably having dinner.
They may not welcome the idea
of Song Yuan being their in-law.
Why not? She's much better than Hye-ryung.
Song Yuan is eight years older.
Gosh, they'll get used to it in no time.
Byeol-hui's mom is easygoing,
and so is Song Yuan.
Tell her to come out!
A Mi?
-Is she not there?
-She's not in there?
Where is she?
You…
She told me to wait. Where did she go?
Call her.
Let her be. Maybe she's taking a walk
and looking around the neighborhood.
When I told her to wash the lettuce?
She's slacking off.
Let's wait for now.
You can't just assume that.
Just call her.
She left her phone at home.
-That one.
-Okay.
How many candles do you want?
-None.
-Okay.
-You bought a cake?
-Yes.
-Is it your birthday?
-No.
Then? Didn't I tell you
to wash the lettuce?
Let's celebrate our first day.
-What do you mean?
-We're now a family.
Don't say anything to her.
Are you going to interfere every time?
No one here likes cake.
You should have asked.
It was my money.
Did it really take you an hour?
I couldn't buy just any cake.
This store sells the tastiest cakes.
I got lost because I left my phone.
Don't you dare
slack off like that ever again.
Scoop the rice.
I'll do the dishes.
You have a dishwasher.
Who doesn't have one?
I didn't.
Who told you to talk back like that?
You asked if there was anyone
who didn't have a dishwasher.
It was a question.
Mother, would you like to give a speech?
You go ahead.
Yu-sin.
Let's not cause a ruckus
and just live in harmony.
Okay.
Aren't you eating?
It's good.
Isn't it?
Yes.
Was she happy?
I'm sure you met her.
She has mixed feelings.
Is her belly big?
-Yes.
-How does it feel?
To be a dad.
I think it'll finally sink in
once the baby is born.
Yu-sin.
Let's do something new.
We've never taken a bath together.
I swear I'll have her
run away within a month.
Doesn't it feel good?
Yes.
Yu-sin.
Putting aside our issues,
I really like Pi-young.
She's charming.
She's elegant and admirable in many ways.
I told her
to call me if she ever got sick.
I told her I'd take care of her.
-What did she say?
-It may take some time,
but she will eventually
understand my sincerity.
Then we'll be on good terms
like those families abroad.
If we become close,
Ji-a will open up to me as well.
So don't you worry
and just focus on treating your patients.
I have nothing to fear
if I have your love.
Breakfast.
What time did you get up to make these?
It didn't take long.
I set the timer
for the rice cooker last night.
The seasoned beans, jangjorim,
and stir-fried anchovies
are from your mother.
I only made
the tofu stew with pollack roe.
It's slightly salty.
No, it's not.
Invite me over when the baby is born.
I'm curious.
Will she not like that?
I doubt it. She'll appreciate it.
Have you thought of a name?
Not yet. Father will name the baby.
I did well, right?
My decision.
I kind of like the new me.
I was…
a lousy husband.
I'm not sure about that.
Speaking about the past and regretting…
No, I don't regret it.
It's all in the past.
But it was me who encouraged you
to hire a personal trainer.
SEOUL GANGNAM FAMILY COURT
FLOWERS
-Are you playing games with me?
-Of course.
Can you buy me a latte?
Mr. Seo. How about a cocktail?
-Meet your future sister-in-law.
-Hello.
It's nice to see you again
as a future family member.
-Same here.
-Really?
Have I ever lied to you?
You must have been an angel
in your past life.
A lot of married couples
get back together after getting a divorce.
You know what wake-up calls are, right?
Well, I'm only here
to see my two princesses.
Don't you want me to stay?
Sir, could I hold
a press conference tomorrow?
It saddens me to deliver the news…
I got a divroce.