EPISODE 16
What's so funny?
Your grandma came by
and said something funny.
What did she say?
It's a joke only grown-ups can understand.
Whether I can understand it or not
is for me to decide.
Right?
It's about someone she knows,
and it doesn't feel right
talking behind their backs.
It should stay with me.
Let's get married.
Marry me.
This isn't a joke.
At this moment, you're probably serious.
Just go.
Professor Park isn't the man for you
in more ways than one.
Is him not being right for me
the reason you want to get married?
-Of course not.
-He's someone I can talk to.
That's why I was drawn to him.
What you feel for him isn't love then.
What we had wasn't love either.
You know you're lying.
Don't deny the truth.
Is breaking up with someone
you love a pastime for you?
Emotions aren't that simple, you know.
It's all in the past now
-and I'm over it.
-Are you sure?
I don't want to argue with you.
It's not like it'll make a difference.
VOLUME
The phone is turned off.
Your call will be directed to…
Here you go, Mother.
Yu-sin, isn't the living room floor shiny?
I vacuumed the floor
and wiped it with a rag.
With a mop.
It's the same thing.
I did two batches of laundry
to wash all the cushion covers.
Back in the day, laundry was done by hand.
The machine does all the work anyway.
Unloading and hanging is a lot of work--
-Do you know how expensive--
-It can be washed.
Don't be too harsh on her.
Where's the housekeeper?
It's worth its price.
I'll have it dry-cleaned.
The housekeeper
hasn't been here for a while now.
She said we don't need one
since two women live here.
I used more elbow grease
when I vacuumed your room, Mother.
-Call the housekeeper.
-I'll take care of it.
Just focus on your work at the hospital.
I sleep like a baby
after doing household chores all day.
All day, my foot.
I wash dishes after breakfast
-and after lunch.
-The machine does the work.
Someone has to load it though.
After the machine is done,
the dishes must go back in the cupboard.
Then I do the laundry.
No matter how fast I work, cleaning
still takes me at least three hours.
I have to clean the bathroom,
fold the laundry,
-go grocery shopping, cook--
-I make the side dishes.
But I prepare all the ingredients
and the big pots
have to be washed by hand.
I had to wash these strawberries
under running water too.
Time has been flying by every day.
I may not even have time to read,
but I'm still happy.
Call the housekeeper.
We're doing a favor by hiring help.
-I'm already paying her.
-But you're not making her clean?
Why? To make me do the chores?
No, that's not it.
To teach me how to manage a house?
That's just wrong.
How can you pay someone
when they're not even working?
Have her back starting tomorrow.
I made barley tea
and porridge just in case.
I want to be alone.
My mom and dad…
I feel like they followed me back here.
I'm sure they're here.
All right.
Did you send them off okay?
The chairman said that breakfast
will be at Shimseong Hotel.
Got it.
Can you ask Gyeong-suk
to pack some meals for a picnic?
-Right now?
-Bring it to the firm by 11 a.m.
-Two portions.
-Sure.
I'll prepare the wine myself,
so it won't be necessary.
Sure thing.
Yes?
I'm not feeling so good.
Cunning bitch.
Sure, Dad.
-Mom.
-Yes?
Dad will be here soon to please us
and he wants breakfast.
His presence alone pleases us, doesn't it?
That must be him.
-Welcome, Dad.
-Thank you.
I smell the sweet scent of oil.
-You're here.
-Hey.
-Is this guacamole?
-Yes.
It's been a while.
-How will you please us?
-Later. Eating should come first.
Dad, you're always hilarious.
-Isn't he, Mom?
-Sure.
Mom, did you finally get it?
-Yes.
-What do you mean?
See how paper-thin this is?
-You could see through it.
-Tell me about it.
-What's the secret?
-Love.
No way. I'm sure there's a secret recipe.
I won't tell you.
I'm your daughter,
not your daughter-in-law, so tell me.
Maybe later.
You wouldn't be able to make it yet
even if you knew.
Gosh, this is delicious.
I prefer wheat pancakes over nacho chips.
-I agree.
-The texture's better too.
-Interested in a part-time job?
-Doing what?
I'll come for breakfast every day,
-but not for free.
-Deal!
You're not the one cooking.
But you'll get paid
for adding a set of cutlery.
-It'd be weird to decline.
-Exactly.
And we'd get to see Dad.
Dad, you truly have a big heart.
Although, it's probably
out of love for Mom.
Just your mom?
Let's be honest.
I know I'm second on your list.
There's no list when it comes to love.
So how will you please us?
Is it an allowance?
An allowance and then some.
Starting today, I'll drive you to school.
-Is it doable?
-I quit swimming in the morning.
-It's fine.
-You're far more of a priority.
Then do that
without coming in for breakfast.
You can serve me cold rice,
soy sauce, and salted shrimp.
Am I pleasing you or what?
I'm more than pleased.
-Mom, have you changed?
-What do you mean?
You usually give him a kiss
in these situations.
-On his cheek.
-Not when I'm eating.
Here.
Your wife's here.
You can drive Ji-a to school,
but don't come in for breakfast.
Does it make you uncomfortable?
When it's just breakfast?
Yes, it is. Very much so.
Just be grateful that you can
see Ji-a anytime you want.
They say greed leads to one's demise.
Aren't I already at rock-bottom?
What if I told Ji-a?
She won't even want to see you anymore.
Is that what you want?
I'm being as generous as I can be,
so don't test my patience.
Just because
he's the son of SF Electronics' CEO,
you're drawn to that
old man who's an engineer.
You're just as
materialistic as other women.
As a man, I'm far better.
Got it.
-Feels good, right?
-You have it better than me.
The chairman even bathes you himself.
Yes, Father.
Do you know those bubble baths
you see on TV?
I'm in the bathroom.
Do you perhaps have any?
-I do.
-Don't tell Sa-hyeon's mother,
and let me find it myself.
Did Sa-hyeon's father go out for a walk?
Isn't he in the bathroom?
Still?
Could he be sick?
-Lady So!
-He must be.
I knew that big breakfast
would cause trouble.
Aren't you sick?
Take off your clothes.
My clothes? Why?
Let me give you a bath.
Who?
-Me?
-Yes. Consider it a service.
Let me help.
What are you doing?
You were jealous of Dongmi.
Are you insane?
I made you a bubble bath, so get in there.
-Have you lost it?
-Yes, I have!
Song Yuan will laugh at us.
Why would she when we're a married couple?
Act your age, will you?
-I'll scratch you.
-Go ahead.
Give me five red lines, if you must.
Unbelievable.
Just think of it
as a memorable experience.
One that displays my love.
How's this for an experience?
Let me wash your hair.
-Stop--
-I'm sorry, but Boo Hye-ryung is here.
-Who's here?
-Hye-ryung.
-As if she's welcome here.
-Maybe we heard wrong.
Hello.
I know I'm the last person
you want to see,
but I couldn't shake off the guilt.
On the day of the press conference,
my emotions got the best of me.
It's been hard on Sa-hyeon, hasn't it?
It was difficult for us too
with all the phone calls.
I'm sorry, Mother.
Maybe I should talk to the press again
and tell them that
the divorce was amicable
and that nothing bad
should be said about it--
Forget it.
It's better not to be in the spotlight.
-It'll only do worse.
-I'm upset about this too.
I can only imagine how you're feeling.
Are you feeling all right?
Recent events
must have been stressful for you.
I'm fine.
Since her due date is this month,
I figured you'd be staying here.
If it were me, I would have been upset.
We were at first.
We're human after all.
Phones rang off the hook,
which startled us.
I'm sorry, Father, Mother.
Don't you have a show to be on?
You don't want puffy eyes.
It's a radio show, so no one will see me.
I cry a lot these days.
Just about anything makes me cry.
It's in the past now, so all we wish
is for you to meet someone better.
Someone who doesn't cause you trouble.
I've lost faith in men now.
People are all different, you know.
Sa-hyeon's young, so consider that
as the reason for his shortcomings
and let go of any bad feelings.
I already have for the sake of you two.
Have some tea.
Could you contact me
when you start having contractions?
-I'd like to be there.
-But you're busy.
To congratulate you.
Would that be okay?
Sure.
I don't have anyone in Korea, remember?
We may not be a family anymore,
but I truly meant what I said last time.
I'd like to see you from time to time.
Sure.
What's there to life…
without love, right?
Please invite me to your baby shower too.
When the child is being bathed?
People hold parties when babies are born.
-The 100th-day party?
-No, it's different.
Let me know if there's anything you need.
I know you're home.
-Hey.
-Please leave. I want to be alone.
I'll just drop the coffee off then.
You like the coffee Gyeong-suk makes.
-I'm fine.
-Open up.
You were crying.
I quit coffee for a while, you know.
So what will it be?
Would you rather
lean on me and sleep or go out?
-Leave.
-I'lI do the opposite.
You did more than any sibling would
despite your busy schedule.
-Thank you.
-Just in words?
Express your gratitude.
I hate when it's just words.
Come on. Let's go out.
Why are you doing this?
Do you feel sorry for me now?
No. My feelings for you are back.
You'll soon move onto how you felt
when you broke up with me.
-I won't.
-I've moved on
and I'll be married soon.
But you haven't yet.
I don't have the energy to talk
and I'm not in the mood.
You will be after spending a day with me.
You can just leave as you are.
Put me down.
Are you insane? Put me down.
At least let me put on some shoes.
What if someone gets on?
-Pretend to be sick.
-You're out of your mind.
Do you think you can
treat me however you want?
-When you're in a good mood.
-Well, I'm not.
Basement floor one.
She must be sick.
Yes, a little.
-Did she pass out?
-Yes.
Goodness me. How did this happen?
She's anemic.
Eating well is the best cure then.
Raw liver does wonders, you know.
-I see.
-You have to be able to stomach it though.
She's not one of those people.
This is the first floor.
Thank you.
You're killing me.
They didn't see your face.
When did you get so light?
The key is in my left pocket.
Can I at least get my shoes?
-You always do what you want.
-But with reason though.
She was like
a completely different person.
Her face and gaze especially.
She only looks different
because of her makeup.
Come to think of it,
she no longer has soot on her eyes.
I can't believe her anymore.
Does she mean it or doesn't she?
Her tears seem like she's genuinely sorry.
Dogs are clever animals.
Especially our Dongmi.
-But she didn't greet Hye-ryung.
-I know.
When Song Yuan first visited,
she couldn't stop wagging her tail.
Dogs know whether they're loved or not.
That's right.
Hye-ryung never patted Dongmi
because she didn't want
to get covered in dog hair.
Are you really going to
invite her to your baby shower?
She wants me to.
I think it'll look weird.
Do you know my shoe size?
I remember all your measurements.
The phone is turned off.
Your call will be directed
to voicemail after the beep.
Do you have that in size 36?
Okay, go again.
Should I buy you a phone?
One for just us two.
-Do you know how to play hwatu?
-Go-stop?
-Yes.
-Of course.
I'm on my way to buy the cards.
Can you teach me?
They look good on you.
Don't I still have good taste?
Do you really think
I'm in the mood to drink wine?
-Besides, you have to drive.
-My secretary will pick me up.
Wine is offered even at mass.
Sometimes, you need a buffer
to remedy the pain and sorrow.
-It won't work.
-Still.
I'll pour two glasses.
Your parents enjoyed wine, right?
They left such a beautiful world.
No, not just the world.
They left you behind too.
I don't have many regrets,
but seeing your parents off
got me thinking.
I should have met them
when we went to Granada.
Not just as your boyfriend,
but as your husband-to-be.
It's not like you
to say what you don't mean.
-I mean it.
-Don't mess around with me.
I know Seo Dong-ma better than anyone.
You've had misutgaru before, right?
I only had it a few times
because it had a grainy texture.
But the grains
sink to the bottom after a while.
Those grains at the bottom?
To me, that's you.
-You are deep inside my heart.
-And you didn't notice?
I mistook those feelings for you
as a signal to end things.
You don't want to get
involved with me again
and I feel the same way.
Accept me as your husband.
I'll be by your side forever.
My recent trip to Spain
taught me that I'd never
be able to be free from you.
Once time passes, you'll realize
you were only being sentimental.
What you feel for me isn't love.
-You pity and feel bad for me--
-Yes, I feel bad for you.
I pity you too.
It's like my mom often says.
My heart aches for you.
But I don't want to
be with you out of pity
and pitying someone
is disrespectful in a way.
I just want to be with you.
I want to see you every day
and talk about the little things.
I gave in to my true feelings.
It must have hurt your pride.
I love you.
I won't ever ask you
if you love me though.
Because I can feel it.
True feelings,
whether it's hatred or affection,
are directly conveyed.
You never got over me, did you?
I haven't,
but I don't want this.
Someone I know well told me
to only marry a man who I knew
I wasn't going to fall in love with.
A man told you that, right?
Anyway, I want to go home now.
Give me 50,000 won so I can take a cab.
-I'll tell him myself.
-As if you have the right.
I do, as the man who loves you
and your future husband.
You're so arrogant.
Hardly. This is me in love.
During our marriage,
I might be tempted by other women.
But I won't wreck our marriage,
so let it slide.
Gyeong-suk
took the time to make this for you,
so have a little to stay focused.
Whether dead or alive,
saying goodbye is a part of life.
I believe that those
who can accept it are the strongest.
Are you drawn to weak people?
I, the man who loves you,
is five years younger,
and am more fragile than I seem to let on.
I'll always show you my true self.
Even when I'm vulnerable.
You should share these among you.
-What's this?
-Hotel breakfast vouchers.
You're the one
who needs them for breakfast.
I have too many.
-Who gifts you with such valuable things?
-We all have our guardian angels.
-Thank you.
-Me too.
-I'll see you at seven tomorrow.
-Mr. Seo?
Sure.
Which hotel is it?
The Palio Hotel in Yeoksam-dong.
It's a six-star hotel.
I expected no less from him.
You're home early today.
What do you think?
She made a sincere apology
and it looked like she meant it.
-I don't want to see her again.
-Likewise.
She might not even mean it.
I can't tell anymore.
-It didn't seem that way.
-Whatever.
Hey, the monk came up with a name.
This for a girl and this for a boy.
-I like them.
-Song Yuan?
They're both beautiful and meaningful too.
Your credit card was delivered.
Mother, let's play hwatu.
I learned how to play with you.
As if I like stupid games like that.
They say it helps prevent dementia.
Worry more about yourself.
You've been quite forgetful lately.
You look for your phone
when it's in your hand.
When I opened the microwave
to heat up some water the other day,
I found some tenderloin
defrosted in the microwave.
A phone call distracted me.
People forget things.
Not as often as you though.
Even yesterday,
you called me over to say something
but completely drew a blank.
Did you perhaps forget about that too?
-Are you saying I have dementia?
-But it's the truth.
You sometimes take sea bream out
after saying you'll grill corvina.
-You know I never lie.
-Is that so?
Yu-sin, isn't hwatu
good for preventing dementia?
You should play.
She took the time to learn it for you.
Play it yourselves.
I'll write down a list of mountain names
for you to memorize
starting with those in Gyeonggi Province.
Why that little…
You're the one who poked the bear,
so get ready to have your head bit off.
Let's get pregnant
and welcome a baby next year.
You'll be 42 next year,
so let's not drag it out.
My mom says that praying actually works.
So go to a temple
and pray for your parents
to be born as your children.
Say that's how much
you want them back in your lives.
I saw that the lights were on,
but you weren't answering your phone.
Have you had dinner?
I had a late lunch.
Were you out?
Yes.
Mango or cherry?
Neither.
-How about some milk tea?
-I'm good.
The living must keep living.
I'm sure that's what
your parents want too.
I'd like to go out on a walk.
Really?
You should put something on.
The night air is chilly.
The sky's clear of fine dust.
Wasn't the weather great today?
I'm here for you, Ga-bin.
I'll forever be
the solid rock by your side.
A tree with a thick trunk doesn't sway
no matter how strong the wind blows.
Will your phone be off tomorrow too?
We should get you a phone just for us two.
Is it hard to walk?
Do you want me to carry you?
Please get back up.
But no one's around.
And who cares if anyone sees us.
I'm sorry.
About what?
I know how you must be feeling
and how difficult it is for you.
They say you can move on
when your parents pass away.
That's not always the case though
since it was hard for me too.
My mom and my dad…
While sending them off,
I realized that I should marry someone
I truly love.
What they had was true love
and they even died together.
I like you, Professor Park.
But…
I don't think it's love I feel.
I told you everything
as honestly as I could from the start.
But…
I can't marry you.
I just can't.
I'm sorry.
Don't you like me anymore?
That fan who came by
your green room to see you.
He's your ex, isn't he?
Yes.
Are you seeing him again?
He's not the reason.
I just want to marry someone
when my heart is filled with love.
This isn't that moment.
Please forgive me.
I know I'll regret it.
Please don't cry.
I'm pathetic, aren't I?
You're honest, not pathetic.
And it's better to be honest,
as cruel as it may be.
I didn't get you a gift.
As if I expected one.
So why did you go there?
I'm going to marry Ga-bin.
Mom and Dad won't approve though, right?
If you back me up that would be great.
-Did she agree?
-We're discussing it.
What about the man she's about to marry?
-She can dump him.
-As if it's that easy.
There's nothing that can't be done
if you put your mind to it.
This shouldn't be a passing thought.
You might hurt her again.
I won't.
-As if.
-That was before I wanted to marry her.
It's different this time.
Take good care of yourself.
Your heart will need time to heal,
but at least let your body rest.
I can't tell you not to mind me
and say I'd be all right.
To be honest,
it hurts.
However, it's something
I need to deal with myself
and my pain is probably
nowhere near yours.
If you change your mind…
That won't happen though, will it?
It was a joy being with you.
I'll cherish the memories.
I don't want to live with you.
You want a divorce?
PI-YOUNG
-Yes?
-My computer broke down.
I called the repair man,
but he couldn't come at this hour.
-I'll be there.
-I need to use it.
Sure.
You don't always get
what you want in life.
Mom was the only person
who catered to you at all times.
And there's no one like her.
Mom was your lottery ticket.
Does this actually work?
Yes, my friend guarantees it.
How do I look?
I can't just wear anything
when we're going to a hotel.
When you're young,
you look good in practically anything.
I brought my laptop just in case.
-Is Ji-a asleep?
-Yes.
-Yes?
-I didn't want you to meet Mr. Park.
I know his number,
so I was going to see him tomorrow.
I ended it a moment ago.
Good.
This doesn't mean
we'll pick up where we left off.
I never said we should.
We should move on
in the direction of marriage.
One's feelings have no shape
which is why they can easily change.
Get some rest for now.
I'll leave you a text tomorrow.
All right?
Thanks.
I'm standing by 24-7,
so think of me as your errand boy.
Can I get a glass of water?
I'm thirsty from running over here.
Have a seat.
-Don't wake her.
-I won't.
-You'll give her a kiss.
I'm just going to take a peek.
I'm craving some ice-cold beer.
You don't have any, do you?
But you drove over here.
I'll call a driver.
When you live close by?
You don't even have
barley tea let alone beer.
I'm useful though, aren't I?
I will forever be that way.
Must you be so arrogant?
I'll stop.
If only there were stars tonight.
There are. We just can't see them.
Don't you still find me
comfortable to be with?
I am.
This is something I can settle for.
Seeing you every once in a while.
I'll be your plumber,
electrician, and computer guy.
You can call me for just about anything.
-Do you know what today is?
-It's not a special day.
I meant to give it to you this morning.
-What's it for?
-I'll take it back if you don't want it.
It's the day we went
on our first official date.
-You wore a flowy dress.
-That's a silly thing to remember.
It's not silly at all.
I guess the memory is etched in my heart.
Don't you want it?
It's only a gift.
Put it on me.
-It looks good on you.
-Thanks.
For gladly coming over.
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm grateful that you called.
I feel guilty for receiving
a gift without giving one.
You're the receiver and I'm the giver.
That's how it'll be.
You'll be in the red then.
Love isn't a business transaction.
I know myself,
and my feelings won't change.
This may sound like an excuse to you,
but it's like
I got drunk and tripped myself over.
But you're drinking again.
A glass of beer hardly counts as drinking.
Do you like it?
I'm grateful.
Could we get together
once in a while for a meal like this?
Who's texting you at this hour?
Si-eun wants me to join her
for breakfast at a hotel tomorrow.
Professor Park must still pay the bills.
Mr. Seo gave us vouchers. Ten each.
There she is.
I texted her to pick you up.
Hi.
Hey.
I'll get going,
so finish up here if you want.
-I'll drive you home.
-I live just around the corner.
Did Nam Ga-bin give birth?
Is it a girl or a boy?
NAM GA-BIN
-Hello?
-It's me, Nam Ga-bin.
I'm at your apartment complex.
I looked up your address before
to send a gift during the holidays.
-You're at my apartment complex?
-Yes.
Why? Are you with Hae-ryun?
No, I'm alone.
Will he be all right though?
What if something happens to him?
Is something wrong?
I have a bad feeling.
Are you really outside Building 1703?
Yes, should I come up?
No, just hang up for now.
I'll be right down.
I'm being punished.
My mom and dad
died because of me.
Because I sinned.
I caused your divorce.
This is karma.
So what now?
-You should get back in your car.
-Please forgive me.
Hasn't Professor Park called?
Please call him.
I heard about your parents.
I'm being punished, aren't I?
Did you perhaps take any pills?
Mom and Dad…
I miss them so much.
But…
I can no longer see them.
I had their remains rest in a temple.
Could you go there with me sometime?
I'll ask for forgiveness
in Buddha's presence.
When did you last see Hae-ryun?
I'm sorry.
I know what I did was wrong.
But this whole situation…
I don't know.
How did things get this way?
What I do know
is that this all started
because of what I did.
Please forgive me.
Why did I turn out like this?
This isn't how my mother raised me.
Mom!
Get the car key.
Because of their immoral daughter,
my parents were taken from this world.
God took them.
It's all my fault.
I finally get it now.
Mom…
Help me with her.
What if something happens
to Professor Park?
I'll be sinning once again.
What is this about?
We broke up.
I told him that I didn't love him.
Is there a way
to turn the clock back a year?
If I could, I wouldn't do what I did.
I only thought of myself
and my pains.
Please call him.
Check where he is. I'm losing my mind.
The phone is turned off.
Your call will be directed to voicemail
after the beep.
This is his house, right?
Put these on.
How can I move on with my life?
I don't think I can.
I miss my mom.
Dad…
I'm so sorry.
Please forgive me. I'm sorry.
-There you go.
-Good job.
You did great.
-Goodness.
-Good job.
You did well. Great job.
Okay, here we go. One, two, three.
All right. One, two, three.
Could you look into the camera?
Here we go again.
One, two, three.
Wake up, husband.
Can you sit down for a second?
Once Bada is born
and if you're feeling up to it,
let's have
a simple wedding at the hospital.
It'll be meaningful.
Just me, you, Bada, and my parents.
Let's ask them first.
Why bother when
it's our decision? They'd love it.
The birth has to go smoothly then.
I'm sure it will.
My parents pray every day and so do I.
So how about it?
I think it'll be meaningful.
Exactly.
I'll prepare everything
including your dress.
And the official wedding will take place
in the fall after careful planning.
Would you have the time
when you're busy day and night?
You can do anything
if you have the time to eat and sleep.
You're here.
Mr. Seo won't know what hit him.
You look exceptional today.
I could say the same for you, Ms. Sa.
I couldn't wear anything to a hotel.
The food here is really amazing.
It's almost therapeutic.
Let this feeling keep you on your feet.
He says to hang in there.
Let's all cheer up.
Maybe I should get all teary-eyed myself.
That would fluster me.
If I cry my eyes out?
Because you'll have to treat me to meals?
I could treat you every day.
-Do you mean that?
-Yes.
How will you manage
if you spend all your salary on us?
I'll spend less on myself.
He doesn't need much being a single man.
I bet you haven't thought about
what it's like to be poor.
That's not something he knows about.
-Do you?
-Not really.
-And you, Ms. Boo?
-I guess it's inconvenient.
Why not answer your own question?
I was reminded of a poem
that I had read recently
while I was having this food.
What kind of poem?
Emptiness, on nights I call your name.
One day, you settle quietly
like a deserted island
and a cellophane-like stillness
gets caught in my mouth.
The wailing of the night
buried under low eaves.
In the morning
when green leaves lift their heads,
Emptiness, you come to me straight
in the form of freshly cleansed sunlight.
The bored window
pulls and pushes the clouds all day.
And I, who's even more bored,
pull and release
the clouds by their horns.
And between the lines of my poem
spreading like ink
you come to me, Emptiness.
My gosh.
What's it called?
Take a guess.
Like you did with the movie before.
"Emptiness"?
Yes.
I was just about to say that.
The poet wanted to portray
"unstained poverty."
Can you text it to me? It was nice.
Me too.
Isn't he good?
She's having contractions!
Contractions?
But you still have a week left.
What else do you enjoy apart from golfing?
Listening to music.
When I'm feeling down, I play the drums.
-The drums?
-Yes.
She's quite good.
-You should show him today.
-Maybe I should.
We'll all go together.
-I have to get back to Ji-a.
-U-ram's home alone too.
-Can I play baseball with U-ram sometime?
-Sure.
Can you let Ji-a join and watch?
Sure.
We'll go when the others are available.
-You look great!
-Such a handsome groom.
-You look dashing!
-Nice!
-You look great.
-How handsome!
-Congratulations.
-Can the bride say a few words?
-My gosh.
-Gosh, are you all right?
You can put it back down at the venue.
The bride and groom will enter together.
Here comes the bride and groom.
OPEN DOOR
Did you forget the lock combination?
It's still the same.
That's not very ladylike.
Son, let's go golfing.
-Get ready.
-Ji-a.
Are you mimicking your grandpa?
Goodness. Ji-a, you're here.
Kim Dong-mi!
You're the reason I…
Ji-a!
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING
LOVE (FT. MARRIAGE & DIVORCE) SEASON 2