FINALE
Is Father in his room?
He's in the study.
-We need to talk.
-Sure.
Some tea?
I'm not thirsty.
I already had red ginseng tea.
Are you not feeling well?
Emotionally, no.
I'd like to move out with Si-eun.
-Why?
-It's for the best.
You must have a reason.
I don't like
how you discriminate against her.
What do you mean?
Do you really not know?
You only favor Pi-young.
I can see that you adore her so much.
That's not why.
I don't need you to explain.
I'm sure Si-eun felt it too if I could.
She's just staying quiet
since she's kind and easygoing.
I have my reasons.
You gave the tasty dishes to Pi-young
when the kids were there too.
You even told Si-eun
to grab a glass of water.
You also gave Pi-young
your card a few days ago, right?
I saw you give her a ring
earlier today as well.
You're right.
It must be difficult
to take care of her so secretly.
We'll move out
so you can do as you please.
Why did you even tell us
to move in with you?
Hear me out.
They say people never change.
How could you hurt me again?
I must have sinned a lot in my past life.
-To you.
-Dong-min--
I've erased that name from my life.
You could get the wrong idea.
I've wanted to tell you guys too.
But they wanted it to be a secret.
Pi-young is pregnant.
And Dong-ma only found out
on his honeymoon.
She was too embarrassed
to let the others know.
I had no choice but to take care of her.
And about that ring…
It was a ring your stepmother cherished.
You wouldn't have liked it
had I given it to Si-eun
since it was your stepmother's.
You'll have your first nephew
or niece in September.
And you, the baby's uncle,
had the conception dream.
I was thoughtless.
How would you have known?
I would've been hurt and upset
if I were you as well.
-I had no idea.
-Me neither.
This is great news.
It's been decades
since a baby came to this house.
You're right.
Don't tell anyone.
She'll think I'm a blabbermouth.
But she'll show soon.
She's especially embarrassed
to tell the kids.
Pi-young and I were right.
Your father died a premature death.
She murdered him.
She overfed him carbohydrates
so his blood vessels would get clogged.
Had they used a defibrillator,
he would still be alive.
Do you still not believe me?
After what you heard?
I don't get it.
I just can't.
How could she?
My grandmother used to say
that humans are the most vicious.
-She was right.
-But to Father…
she was a perfect wife.
-She was sincere.
-She was faking it.
-But why?
-Maybe he was too old for her.
-After all those years?
-Who knows behind closed doors?
How could she have deceived
even me for all those years?
All lies are bound to be exposed.
She has countless faces.
Maybe she's suffering
from schizophrenia and delusions.
Maybe it's just her subconscious.
You're impossible.
She's not even your real mother.
Are you really a neuropsychiatrist?
Why would someone so carefree get sick?
Her guilt must have eaten away at her.
Plus, Father refused
to leave and even possessed Ji-a.
It all makes sense now.
He was too resentful to move on.
You decide.
I'm too scared to live with her.
What if she harms me?
Either admit her to a hospital,
or I'm leaving.
-Should I go pack?
-She was young when she came.
She raised me
as if I was her biological son.
I owe all my success to her.
She had an ulterior motive.
-She had feelings for you--
-Shut it.
I was only seven.
I didn't say it happened then.
You became a wonderful, young man
and then reached your prime.
And your father became an old man.
Meanwhile, she was still young and lively.
Take her to the hospital
or tell them to pick her up.
I can't do this any longer.
I can't live with her.
I truly love you
-Get changed and come out.
-But it's late.
It doesn't matter. Let's eat out.
What are we eating?
What do you want to eat?
Go to your room.
Stop staring at me and go.
I want pizza.
Let's order in.
Did you really ignore Father…
while he was having a heart attack?
I don't want to talk about it.
Why?
You loved him more than anyone else.
You said you admired and loved him.
What do you mean "admire"?
-Did you not like him?
-I despised how that old man reeked!
You'll become old one day too.
It's natural.
Whatever.
Are you attacking me right now?
Are you scolding me?
I hate all of you!
Father…
Don't call for him like a baby.
Call someone over.
Open up.
The key.
You better not come in.
I'll kill myself!
Why are you here?
We're here for someone.
Why are you still here?
-Who?
-Don't ask.
-It's a secret.
-When?
Within a month of our arrival.
Can you at least tell me
whether it's a male or female?
Is it the chairman?
Don't ask. It won't do you any good.
Where's my phone?
Here you go.
INCOMING CALL
A MI
-Yes?
-Where are the room keys?
In the utility room.
Or check the shoe shelf.
Ms. Kim locked herself in her bedroom.
What you and I suspected was true.
She confessed that she killed Father.
What did she say?
It's a long story.
Put this on.
You shouldn't catch a cold.
What's wrong with you? Calm down.
Fine. You can just stay home.
Don't touch me.
Get lost!
Right now.
Prepare a room for her.
Aren't your legs sore?
No.
Hyang-gi ordered our drinks.
Hey, people will get the wrong idea.
Circumcision?
I can't help it.
Where's dinner? I'm hungry.
Who are these young men?
They're from the hospital.
Sit down for a minute.
Take a seat.
Let me go!
Touch me, and I'll pee.
What are you doing? How dare you?
Let me go!
I'm going to tell
Dr. Shin to fire you all!
Yu-sin!
What did I do? Tell me?
Do you want me to die?
Should I kill myself in front of you?
How about you kill me yourself?
Fine! I'll let you do it.
Just kill me with your hands!
How could you do this to me?
You of all people!
Help me, A Mi.
I'm sorry.
I'll treat you better from now on!
Yu-sin! My son!
Spare me!
I won't be able to live! I'll die!
Can you live without me?
Please!
They're going to kill me!
They will kill me!
Help me!
Let me go!
If I die, I want to die here!
I want to die in my own house!
You'll be punished.
You'll die a painful death.
You'll see.
Is this how you repay me?
Shin Yu-sin.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Dong-mi.
Hi.
Since it's late,
have dinner with me before you go.
Let's drink instead.
Did you think of me from time to time?
I'd be lying if I said no.
I wanted to call you many times,
but I stopped myself.
Is it really impossible
for us to go back to the way things were?
They say traitors never change.
My conscience won't allow it.
Ms. Kim is an avid fan of mine.
She treats me like I'm her daughter.
She was very eager to introduce me to you.
I didn't think it was right to refuse.
So I told her I'd just see who it was
and agreed to come out.
In any case,
don't you think this is fate?
I won't just think of myself and use you.
All pain subsides
over time.
So it's because of your baby?
-Yes.
-You're too attached.
And that's where all your pain stems from.
They say a sparrow near
a school sings the primer.
Being a Grim Reaper for a century
has made you patient.
I just couldn't leave my child behind.
How could we understand?
We only lived as men on this earth.
Do you think
I had sinned too much in my previous life?
Trouble sleeping?
I should be the one tossing and turning.
-Why?
-Let's buy another bed tomorrow.
-Suppressing my urges is hard.
-Let's sleep in separate rooms.
-Are you serious?
-Yes.
Why are you upset?
Tell me. Did I do something?
Was it because of what I said?
I was joking.
I just wanted to hug you, but I couldn't.
I can't sleep
because I'm craving bibim guksu.
Then have some with some kimchi.
-We ran out of noodles.
-Even ramyeon?
Then we can make some noodles.
Do we have flour?
We do.
Where are you going?
I'll make you some, so you can go to bed.
How did you two become Grim Reapers?
It was due to our karmas.
Due to our actions on this earth.
This job does you no good.
Why are they still up?
Maybe they want a late-night snack.
Do you know what's funny?
Despite being a ghost,
I still crave food when I see them.
How about you guys?
It'll subside over time.
It's a habit from when you were alive.
-Flour?
-Yes.
You've never done this before.
But I watched others do it.
-On TV?
-Yes.
I just need to mix it with water.
Let me. Just roll it later for me.
Don't touch it. Go back to the room.
-I'll bring it up.
-You, Master Dong-ma?
That's not me anymore.
I'm a husband. Your husband.
-My dear husband.
-Do you love me?
Of course.
All right. Go to our room.
Maybe take a nap.
I said I couldn't sleep.
It doesn't matter. Just lie down.
-How will I eat it?
-With chopsticks.
-I feel bad.
-Every time you do, just…
Kalguksu?
No, sujebi.
Father…
-… has happened.
-After getting married,
I've realized that
keeping myself in good health and…
Right.
Who is that?
It's me.
I'm sorry,
but where is your foot massager?
Why do you ask?
Pi-young can't sleep
because she craves guksu.
Then get her some.
-Good night.
-Are you cooking?
Then who else? You?
It's kalguksu.
But I stepped on that.
You stepped on the middle,
so I'll use the corners.
But still…
I need a tool.
I'll put flour on it.
-Is everyone eating?
-Is that a lot?
Of course, it is. Where will you make it?
That's too small.
I know.
It's perfect.
Bring half of the dough.
And enough flour.
We didn't move back in with my parents
to just live with them.
It was because we both had to work,
and we didn't have enough money.
But you keep
treating my parents like that.
We're going to live all together,
so could you please…
Let me.
This requires skill.
Do it evenly.
She'll never forget it
if she can't have what she wants.
When your mom was pregnant,
she craved ice flakes
in the middle of winter.
Nowadays, they're sold
during the winter too.
But that wasn't the case back then.
She always brought it up.
I remember her telling me.
Gochujang bibim guksu
or kimchi bibim guksu?
Kimchi, I think.
Do you know where the kimchi is?
Probably in the kimchi fridge.
And exactly which one is that?
We should have some too, right?
I could eat.
Just consider yourself unlucky
when it comes to having a wife.
You can't be blessed with everything.
I'm blessed with parents, a wife,
children, wealth,
and even good health.
Enough with the bragging.
You can't be certain about your health.
Right. I take that back.
I'm blessed with everything but one.
I have no daughter.
Devote yourself to Jeong-bin from now on.
Hye-ryung is…
How do I put it?
She tends to be a bit heartless.
She's self-centered too.
Don't let it get to you.
But she's still pretty and competent.
He's right. It'd be perfect
had she been friendly and affectionate.
Just focus on raising Jeong-bin.
And don't expect anything from her.
Even if she curses at you,
just ignore her.
She's extremely on edge right now.
It's best not to provoke her.
The noodles are a bit thick.
My knife skills aren't great.
Thank you so much, Father.
I helped out too.
I can't believe this.
We tried it, and it tasted fine.
It's really tasty.
I'm glad.
Goodness.
-What's wrong?
-One minute.
She wants to take a photo.
It's nothing grand.
Cooking is painstaking.
I should always be grateful when eating.
-What's my temperature?
-It's 36.7°C.
It's perfectly fine.
Your blood pressure is normal too.
I have a piercing headache.
I'll inform your doctor.
Is it a girl?
Goodness. How did you know?
I could tell.
Pi-young.
What happened?
Please give us the grocery list.
One minute.
I'll be honest.
I've wanted to tell you
this numerous times.
But I just couldn't bring myself to.
You're pregnant, aren't you?
Did Father tell you?
I could tell.
I don't even have morning sickness.
I have a bigger appetite.
I wanted to ask you,
but I held myself back.
When's your due date?
You heard, right?
Your brain is healthy too.
But I'm still in extreme pain.
Rest up. Relax.
Don't think too much.
I miss Jeong-bin.
I can't bring him here though.
He's becoming cuter by the day.
Sa-hyeon is still young.
I know he still lacks a lot.
If you'll understand and be patient,
he'll become
a better husband in all aspects.
Men tend to mature slowly.
-I'm not that great either.
-That's not true at all.
You have a successful career.
I bet Jeong-bin's mother was feminine.
The same goes for you.
Look at yourself.
JUST YOUR FACE
Father made them?
-Yes.
-It's unimaginable.
-Right?
-Was it tasty?
The noodles were…
I'm not exaggerating.
They were as thick as Ji-a's fingers.
Dong-ma must've kneaded
the dough since he's strong.
It was chewy and delicious.
And they put in just enough kimchi.
On top of that, they added an egg.
A boiled one at that.
-You're craving some.
-Yes, since you mentioned it.
I can't make it myself.
Let's go to my favorite place in Jongno.
To be honest…
I'm pregnant as well.
No way.
Goodness.
I couldn't believe it at first either.
What did Mr. Seo say?
I haven't told him yet.
-Why not? He should be the first to know.
-What if I end up like Hye-ryung?
I only just saw the test result.
-On the pregnancy test kit?
-Yes.
I'll tell him after I visit the OB-GYN
next week and know for sure.
Is it a honeymoon baby?
I believe so.
You must've had one steamy night.
I was worried you just held hands.
Don't tease me.
I'm not. The Seo family
will have two celebrations back-to-back.
Plus, Mr. Seo is the eldest son.
He'll be ecstatic
once he hears about this.
Who knows?
I know.
Not only will he be happy,
but Father will be delighted.
Please keep it a secret
until I know for sure.
Si-eun, you can trust
the pregnancy test kit.
I can only be assured
once the baby is three to four months old.
Si-eun, I'm so happy for you.
This ought to be a big celebration.
So that's why
you haven't been eating much.
I thought you were on a diet.
Fatty and creamy dishes make me nauseous.
Just like when I had Ji-a.
Do you think it's a boy or a girl?
It'd be great if it was a boy.
Father will be on cloud nine.
It's not their eldest son, is it?
-Is it?
-We can't tell you.
If we do, we can't be Grim Reapers
anymore. We could reincarnate as animals.
The number you have dialed
is currently busy.
Please leave a message after the beep.
INCOMING CALL
SHIN YU-SIN
-Hello?
-Can you talk?
Yes.
I heard about it. How is she?
She's being sedated.
She's more frightening than I thought.
How could she?
I should've listened to you.
Tell A Mi to prepare a ritual for Father.
-You must do that.
-Okay.
Will she move back in
with you once she gets better?
A Mi refused vehemently.
And I don't think I can anymore.
I would've felt the same way.
You used to make alcohol
every now and then. What's the recipe?
I'll text it to A Mi.
Okay. How's Ji-a?
She's doing well.
Is she adjusting well to school?
Yes. I didn't tell her about Mother.
She doesn't need to know.
It'll only trouble her.
Goodbye.
Hello.
Hey. You're home early.
I'm going out again.
What's with the flowers?
-Oh, my.
-These are for Pi-young.
-Pi-young.
-Yes?
They're from him.
Gosh, I love them.
Thank you for buying me some as well.
Brothers-in-law
always cherish their sisters-in-law.
What about my love for you?
That means a lot too.
I'm touched.
You're the best.
STUDY CAFE
-So?
-Is this the recipe?
Yes. I followed hers.
I like it.
Did you want more foam?
You need to drink it in one shot.
-Beer?
-Try it.
Cheers.
Drink up.
-It has a unique taste.
-Drink it all at once.
This is for the flowers
your brother got for us.
If I buy them tomorrow,
can we drink this again?
What's the recipe?
I used to work part-time back in the day.
I was a bartender.
-Oh, please.
-I'm serious.
-I was popular.
-Among the customers?
Among the men.
Tell me. You better talk
while I'm being nice.
I learned from a Japanese cuisine chef.
Which restaurant?
Did you flirt with him?
I'd never do that.
I just smiled at him.
Why couldn't he just focus on cooking?
The drink was on the house.
I said it was tasty, so he taught me.
It's not windy today.
Tell me about it.
We can just take a stroll
around the neighborhood for today.
What's your relationship with A Mi?
She's not just your client, is she?
- A Mi?
-Yes.
Is "A" her surname?
-Don't play dumb.
-Who is she?
Bring her over. I'm curious.
Do you really not know her?
Call her, or we can all meet together.
I don't get you.
Hello. It's been a long time.
Hello.
Are you here alone?
Yes.
Would you like
to have some tea downstairs?
When is your next musical?
I haven't looked online lately.
This fall.
You're always working.
I'm just blessed when it comes to work.
You know about me and Ms. Lee, right?
A Mi must've told you.
I do.
I heard Ms. Lee got married.
Yes. She met a wonderful man.
Seeing her,
I guess being kind pays off in the end.
I heard
you got back together with your ex.
And we broke up once again.
Does she not work anymore?
She should take a break.
She's been working since university.
It's almost been 30 years.
I'm taking a sabbatical too.
I agree. Everyone needs downtime.
But musical actresses are too afraid
of being forgotten.
Could you tell Ms. Lee
that I would like to meet her again?
Putting aside everything that happened,
she's like a life mentor to me.
-You're an only child, right?
-Yes.
I'm also an only child,
so I know how you feel.
We want to have close friends.
Si-eun is…
I call her by her first name.
She puts others before herself.
She has a big heart.
You're right.
Did you not meet Professor Park again?
I ran into him recently.
I never really loved him.
So I was pretty calm.
DOCTOR'S OFFICE
Ms. Han Hui-won?
LIVE STUDIO
-Good work.
-See you tomorrow.
INCOMING CALL
SI-EUN
Yes?
Are you done?
Yes. Should I go home early?
No.
Then should I go elsewhere?
Treat me to dinner.
We have Korean cuisine at home.
French? Chinese? Italian?
Italian.
I'll make a reservation and call you.
-Okay.
-Call me more often.
It's nice.
She doesn't want it.
-Did you say it was gelato, not ice cream?
-Yes.
I shouldn't have gotten it.
I thought she'd eat this.
What if she has a serious illness?
The doctors said she didn't.
She got a thorough checkup.
There's this friend I used
to go to middle school with.
Six months ago,
his checkup showed no issues.
One day, he collapsed
and went to the hospital.
He has a stage-four brain tumor.
Jeez. Be careful what you say.
Sa-hyeon isn't doomed
to have no wife, is he?
We didn't expect
Song Yuan to pass away like that.
After going through that we need
to be more careful.
She has depression.
I told her to get therapy,
but she refused.
Who cares about rumors spreading?
Her health comes first.
She can barely eat anything.
This is good.
So this is why people love ice cream.
-You're old.
-Me?
You like it because you've aged.
Isn't it the opposite?
Doesn't this mean I'm still young?
-We'll have this wine.
-Yes, sir.
Do you have good news?
Will you only treat me
if there's good news?
No. I'd love to treat you anytime.
I've wanted to come here with you.
DIRECTOR JUNG
Hello?
Yes.
Ms. Lee is doing well too.
Not yet.
Our youngest is in
middle school now, so she's busy.
She's a mom too.
Yes.
Okay.
He wants you to work.
But he has many writers.
It doesn't matter.
Most of them are incompetent.
Should we take up horseback riding?
It'd be nice to join our kids.
-You can.
-Just me?
You know I get easily scared.
I'm scared of dogs
that are bigger than Danchu.
SEOK-JUNG
I thought I could enjoy
this evening with you.
I should turn it off.
Yes?
I hope you reincarnate as a human.
They must've been so lazy and bled
people dry to reincarnate as a dog.
Judging by its owners,
they must've not been that bad.
Do you not like it?
I hope Lady Luck is on your side.
She already is. I got to marry you.
Our kids like this.
Let's order some to-go.
Three would be enough, right?
It won't taste good cold.
What does "calzone" mean?
"Stretched pant legs", was it?
I wish someone grabbed my pant legs too.
-Who?
-You.
I'm going to do that now,
and I won't let go.
Okay.
Have you ever thought
about having your own kid?
Do you feel pressured?
Do you not like the idea?
I'd be lying if I said
I didn't think about it.
But it's important
to be happy with what you have.
I'm more than content
with what I have right now.
Perhaps…
If God allows us and you're lucky enough,
you may become a dad this year.
What do you mean? Do you want to adopt?
I'm five weeks pregnant.
I'm a bit worried
that I might have a miscarriage.
I went to the OB-GYN today.
They ran a blood test.
I'm pregnant.
I can't believe this.
Me neither.
Pinch me.
Does it hurt?
Not one bit.
Oh, dear. Then this must be a dream.
I could be stabbed right now
and not feel a thing.
I feel totally numb.
So this is how it feels
to become a dad.
We don't know what'll happen.
I'm always going
to prepare myself for the worst.
Don't do that.
That's not a way to treat our baby.
We should love it.
Should we?
We should put our trust in our baby
and hope it will grow well.
We should shower it with love.
Even if it's a fetus.
Okay.
You're right.
How do you judge other people?
I've never judged others.
Even if you don't, others will judge you
once you grow up and start work.
I'll think about it.
I judge them on the impression I get.
When it comes to material things,
those who say, "What's mine is yours,
and what's yours is mine," are ignorant.
Someone who says, "What's mine is mine,
and what's yours is yours,"
is normal.
Someone who says,
"What's mine is yours,
and what's yours is yours,"
is respectable and admirable.
Can you do that?
To be honest, no.
What about you?
I can do that every now and then.
But I'm far from being admirable.
But you make so many donations.
Lastly…
someone who says, "What's yours is mine,
and what's mine is mine,"
is evil. The Talmud says so.
Thieves and robbers are examples of that.
They believe what others have is theirs.
That's why they don't hesitate to steal.
At times, they go
as far as hurting others.
Do you understand
what kind of person you should be?
-Yes.
-It won't be easy though.
This world would be easier to live
without those who are evil, Father.
Why are you home already?
You should've enjoyed some alone time.
Did I do something wrong again?
-No.
-You can tell me.
I shouldn't have sold my dream
to Dong-ma last time.
-About the big snake?
-Yes.
Why? Did you buy a lottery ticket?
She's pregnant.
I went to the OB-GYN today.
I'll be careful
so I can have a healthy baby.
So you're pregnant as well?
Yes.
Hold on.
April Fools has passed, right?
It has.
Two babies at our house?
When is your due date?
December.
Are you unhappy?
No.
I'm okay.
I was a terrible father.
But look at this.
I'm truly touched.
You're better than me.
Thank you.
Aren't you happy?
I am.
I'll do my best as well.
But you should take good care of her.
She shouldn't trouble herself.
It'd be nice if you could take a leave
and tend to her around the clock.
Would you like that?
I'm not joking.
It's okay. I'll be careful.
Call Dong-ma and Pi-young over.
We're going to tell the kids first.
We should receive their help too.
Right. Okay.
I don't deserve this from you.
I couldn't be more grateful.
I mean it.
We should celebrate over some beer.
You can have some. We don't need to drink.
It's only meaningful if we all drink.
Don't rush things. Take your time
with the baby and give birth next year.
We'll only be a few months apart.
Still, our kid will be older.
Give it a nickname.
It's not mandatory, right?
Still, wouldn't it be nice
to call it every now and then?
How does Janggun sound?
That's a boy's name.
What about something neutral?
We don't know the gender yet.
-Right.
-Would you like something?
No, I'm okay.
-Are you sure? Don't you crave a drink?
-I do.
The men should drink for them
to celebrate their pregnancy.
So try to do things on your own.
Try not to make your mom move
as much as possible.
Okay.
-Why are you crying?
-They're tears of joy. Right?
-Are you worried about her?
-I am.
INCOMING CALL
DONG-MA
I'll take good care of her.
-Yes?
-Dad wants to celebrate. Come downstairs.
To a safe delivery.
Congratulations.
Hire more housekeepers this instant.
Take good care of your bodies.
-Okay.
-Yes, Father.
Don't forget that you're our treasures.
We feel much happier
since you're here with us.
Really?
Yes.
-Any other precautions?
-No.
Shouldn't we buy baby stuff soon?
It'll only take a day or two.
-Make sure I go with you.
-Gosh. You're busy.
I can still make time.
Loosen up. You're making us tense.
Be honest. Do you want a girl or a boy?
-Honestly?
-Yes.
I want twins.
DOCTOR'S OFFICE
Everything's fine.
He's greedy. He wants twins.
My Cutie wants naengmyeon.
What do you crave?
I crave buckwheat noodles.
-Should we split up?
-I want buckwheat noodles too.
Hye-ryung is hospitalized here.
Right.
But if she sees us…
Maybe next time.
We'll only upset her.
Look.
Everything's fine.
Her blood vessels are clean too.
Then why is she still in pain?
It's neurological.
The only way to get better
is for her to overcome it.
I'm dying here, but they can't find
anything wrong with me.
I can tell. You don't look too good.
They say it's neurological.
You have a headache and no appetite.
You must be tired
since you're not eating well.
-Yes.
-Maybe it's lupus. An autoimmune disease.
I got a checkup for that too just in case.
Just like us,
you've been working too hard.
I agree. Your body is telling you
that it wants to rest.
Your husband must be worried sick.
-He is.
-Don't feel anxious.
Just rest for a year or two.
What if people forget about me?
Sorry.
PROFESSOR PARK
Why is he calling me?
He could've just texted.
Professor Park?
Sorry. I was too thirsty and hot
that I ordered first.
She's all dressed up like a wealthy lady.
What would you like?
A hot cup of chamomile tea, please.
-Okay.
-In this hot weather?
U-ram got good grades.
He did.
I need to move out.
I thought you two were close? Why?
His family member is coming from Busan.
And the place is so rundown
that the AC always breaks.
You should move.
You have enough money
to find a new studio apartment.
Paying monthly rent would be a waste.
Can I move into our old apartment?
-It'll still be yours.
-I rented it out.
Pay for the move and the brokerage fee…
-I'll do it.
-You could've just called.
I thought it'd be nice to see you
and talk about the kids.
They must be too busy to call.
They only reply after several texts.
They don't have time to chat over text.
Out of sight, out of mind.
The tenants moved in less than a year ago.
I can't tell them to leave.
-Yearly or monthly rent?
-Monthly.
I gave them a good deal,
so I doubt they'll want to move out.
Get a two-bedroom studio.
New studios nowadays are pretty good.
They're structured differently.
-Do you want to cut your hair?
-Yes.
Which designer?
-Is this your first time here?
-Yes.
Sit down.
-You can sit here.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
I should thank you instead.
You would've already given birth
the next time we meet.
Yes.
Be careful.
We hope you'll have a safe delivery.
Thank you.
Door closing.
Hey.
The driver is waiting.
Let's talk.
Later.
I realized that quacks
don't only exist in the medical field.
I think some Grim Reapers are quacks too.
I really do.
I was worried,
but your entire family is still alive.
And the Grim Reapers disappeared.
It's funny how our minds work.
It was only for a brief time.
But I wished
it was you who would die.
Because I'm lonely.
I was kicked out of Sa-hyeon's house.
I can't see my baby boy anymore.
I thought it'd be nice
to spend my time chatting with you.
I'm terrible, aren't I?
You look happy these days.
You look good.
I'm sorry.
Was there traffic?
No. The GPS took me to the one in Jamsil.
I didn't know there was another branch.
-How's Ms. Kim?
-She's doing fine.
Or is she just pretending?
You really are pregnant.
I was surprised when Yu-sin told me.
It's belated, but congratulations.
Your husband must be delighted.
Kiwi juice, please.
Do you sell vanilla shakes?
Yes.
We're getting married.
When?
-October 10.
-In 2 months.
-Yes.
-How's the preparation going?
I've picked out my wedding dress.
We're not buying any household goods.
Get new furniture. That's a given.
We'll keep the ones we have.
Does he not give you any money?
Ask for some.
That's not why.
I'd like to use the same furniture
you did and gain some luck.
You're lucky.
For getting married twice?
It was an upgrade.
You chose the life you live.
Even my mom said that I dug my own grave.
But what matters is the result.
I wish you well.
Thank you.
Anyway, call me whenever you need me.
I'll put aside whatever I'm doing and go.
Are you feeling okay?
Are you due anytime soon?
Next month, the 20th.
Sit down.
It's about Hye-ryung.
Maybe she needs to become a shaman.
You also heard, right?
People like her feel extreme pain.
But when they get a checkup,
they turn out to be fine.
That can't be.
We're talking about Hye-ryung.
I'm certain of it.
I've been observing her lately.
Come on. They said it's neurological.
She's a fussy one.
Don't you dare say a thing.
Isn't it hot?
Yes.
How do you feel today?
I felt too bloated
and couldn't eat all day.
Who is he?
No one's here.
Do you see something?
Hey, kid. What's your name?
Have some grapes.
I don't have an appetite these days.
You'll feel better
during your final month.
Shouldn't you get ready?
We decided to eat in today.
Ji-a shouldn't skip academy either.
But it's your birthday. You should enjoy
the day with your husband.
I just want to spend it with my family.
Hold on.
You should've told me in advance.
I thought you were eating out.
I asked the housekeeper to make kongguksu.
I craved some.
Does your wife wear a size five?
She was a size four,
but that might change after childbirth.
These are the new arrivals
for the fall and winter seasons.
-Take your time.
-Okay.
Give me the birthday gift I want.
What is it?
Come home early
and spend some time with me.
Don't bring anything home.
Okay. I'll carry it on my back.
No gifts.
I just want you. That's more meaningful.
All right.
I'll come before 5 p.m.
I'll set my alarm.
To Min General Hospital!
Take him there!
-What will you do?
-What do you mean?
Someone else
is going to snatch that old man.
Who are you?