[Thailand]
[THAI SWEET]
Come on.
[Episode Highlights]
I believe he'll give
the most genuine reaction.
The view up there is good.
And it makes you feel good.
Give it a try, will you?
Do you want to play?
I'll try it then.
Come on!
Let me down!
Okay, it's time to let her come down.
Let's go squid fishing.
He's like a walking emoji.
It's exactly the same.
You can do it too?
Because we're Thai.
It doesn't look scary to me.
I'll go too.
[Exit the audience]
Go for it!
I believe he'll give
the most genuine reaction.
[Flying low]
Why is he down there?
[Stepping on the water]
Why is he going down?
That's quite scary.
[Full speed ahead]
[Start ascending]
He's up.
He's up now.
So pretty.
Na Na, the photo you took is so pretty.
Do you want to give it a try?
I don't dare.
You won't feel anything.
[Highly recommended]
There won't be any sudden jolts.
You're making me
want to go parasailing too.
[He even started singing]
[Landing steadily]
He was even singing a song
as he came down.
Mike.
How do you feel?
Really great.
Was it fun? Was it scary?
[Three consecutive questions]
It wasn't scary at all.
It was fun.
It's fun. Not scary.
Give it a try. I mean it.
[Really?]
It's not scary?
It's really not.
Not scary at all.
[Trust us]
It feels really comfortable.
Not scary at all.
You want to play?
No.
Last year,
when I was filming a costume drama
in Hengdian,
I had to be hoisted up on wires
all the way to the ceiling beams.
I couldn't even talk.
You'll just feel the wind blowing.
Exactly, all you feel is the wind.
The view up there is really nice.
And it makes you feel good.
Give it a try, will you?
Do you want to play?
I'll give it a try then.
[Give it a try]
Take off your shoes.
You need to take off your shoes.
Take them off.
Will this do?
My shoes will fall off, right?
Yes.
It's really nice up there.
Very peaceful.
Very quiet.
It's very quiet up there.
You'll only hear the wind and the sea.
It's really comfortable.
Are you afraid of heights or...?
[The only audience]
Yes, I'm a bit afraid of heights.
Right, as long as you all have fun.
Seeing you happy makes me happy.
Is this safe enough?
Help me check.
[Try as you may, fear as you will]
Are all the straps fastened?
Yes, all fastened.
Go for it.
Tightened?
Mike.
Can you check it for me?
Is it safe?
It's safe.
Why does it feel kind of loose?
It's not.
It's fine.
Come on!
Wait a second.
I don't think I...
It should be attached to me
like this, right?
And hold onto the two black handles
with your hands.
These ones?
I felt a little scared at first.
Come on!
But everyone kept encouraging me.
Don't be afraid. No need to be afraid.
I don't dare.
[Never dared to try]
Give it a try.
Do you want to give it a try?
All you feel is the wind,
to be honest.
It makes you feel good.
I'll give it a try then.
Go for it!
They gave me the courage to try.
[Take this step with courage]
Come on!
[Getting higher and higher]
It's okay, actually.
It's just like the wire work.
[It's not that scary]
The moment I lifted off,
I suddenly wasn't scared anymore.
Many things in life are like this.
Once you take the first step,
you already succeed.
With friends around,
everything feels joyful.
Hi!
Mu was very brave today.
Actually, she didn't dare to do it
at first,
but since we gave Mu
a lot of encouragement,
she managed to fly up
bravely in the end.
I think that scene
was really cool.
[Mountains and rivers are not important;
what matters is meeting a kindred spirit.]
Is this done?
[Want to get down]
Wave your hand!
Let me down!
Wave!
It's okay!
Bye-bye!
She said it's okay.
She wants to come down.
Let her chill there for a while.
[Being naughty]
Bye-bye!
[I agree]
Let me down!
Okay, it's time to let her come down.
[Start landing]
I kept saying "let me down,"
and you kept saying hello to me.
You know what?
I wasn't really scared,
because this felt exactly the same
as the wire work.
Impressive.
This feels just like
[Esther on the flying wire]
the wire work I do every day.
It's about the same height too.
[It's just a routine]
We never do wire work.
[Different trades, worlds apart]
We do wire work all the time.
[Going back]
[THAI SWEET]
[Exciting]
What's happening?
What's going on?
You scared me.
This time, it's all about
going a little crazy
with friends.
Feeling free, having a lot of fun.
I think everyone
feels the same—
you just don't want it to end.
[From the script to tacit understanding
in real life, we support each other]
[Turning the fate of our roles
into a lifetime of friendship]
[Embark on a dark night duel with squid,
unlocking an adventure to the deep sea]
Go, go, go.
Let's go squid fishing.
[Night activity: overnight squid fishing]
Squid fishing.
Go.
Let's go.
I should charge you for the beanie.
Skinny people really have it easy.
Every shot looks like a photoshoot.
[Forcefully]
I'm also skinny.
[Sucking in the lips]
No one asked you.
[The harder you try,
the more bittersweet it feels]
[Trying too hard]
He's like a walking emoji.
He probably looks like many emojis.
Is it because you guys saw this before?
You look exactly the same as this.
[Got carried along]
You can do it too?
Because we are Thai.
[Thai comedy brothers]
It's in our DNA.
[Comedy genes]
Then you do it.
One more time.
One, two.
Wait! Wait for me.
Together.
At the same time.
Three, two, one. Action.
Tell me, seriously,
can we shoot this all over again?
[Setting the next date]
Why not?
You mean coming here again?
Let's do it somewhere else.
Somewhere else.
Where to?
-Chiang Mai.
-Pattaya.
Mike.
Can you
be the organizer next time?
[Cued]
[Offline]
Can you be the organizer of
our next reality show?
Aren't you both a producer
and a screenwriter?
Me?
You want me to do it?
I think... I can.
[No confidence at all]
What will you take us to do?
We could go to that...
Water park.
Water park?
Right.
[Sounds good]
Water park. The water splashing festival.
It's fun.
The water splashing festival
is like...
Everyone can participate.
You know,
during the water splashing festival,
if you see someone you like,
[Note: Thailand's Water Splashing Festival
is one of Thailand's grandest festivals]
you can smear the white clay
[and the traditional New Year celebration
for the Thai people]
[During this festival, people splash water
and smear white clay on one another
[as a way of expressing blessings]
on that person's face.
[Note: The core dates of the Festival
are usually April 13–15, may be extended]
Is that so?
Isn't it?
Am I wrong?
[Also the first time this local
heard about it]
I don't know either.
You can smear it however you like?
I mean, for example,
if I see someone...
Didn't you say smear it however you want?
Like...
Are you trying to slap me?
What are you doing?
It's almost like a Thai drama.
They started acting all of a sudden.
They started acting.
What's up, bro?
[THAI SWEET Little Theater]
They used to be good friends,
but now they are fighting.
What's the reason behind this?
Please stay tuned.
We're almost there.
[Arriving at the destination]
Go.
We're here.
Get on board.
This boat is amazing.
We're about to go night squid fishing.
Here you are.
Thanks.
THAI SWEET! Let's go!
It's so much fun.
[Join #THAI SWEET night squid fishing#
discussion and share your views]
Squid fishing. We'll catch 100 squid.
Keep fishing
until we get tired of it.
Even if we can't catch any,
it doesn't matter.
Like, this breeze feels perfect.
Like...
I think it's worth it.
This is the first time
[A brand new experience]
I'm going fishing
in the middle of the night.
Fishing in the sea
It's so beautiful.
When you shoot in this angle,
the light looks really beautiful.
That green light is truly beautiful.
It feels like we're surrounded
by the aurora.
So pretty.
For real.
When you shine light on it, it glows.
[What did he say?]
I didn't understand even a single word.
What did he say?
This kind of green light
[Interpreter here]
can attract
tiny fish
over.
[Note: Squid are sensitive to light,
especially 450–550 nm green light,]
When the shiny fish come over,
[which most effectively activates
their visual perception system]
the big fish will come to eat them.
[Fishermen use high-power LED lights
to mimic the bioluminescence of plankton,]
And then, the squid will come
to eat the fish.
[causing squid to mistake it for food
and move toward the light]
[Big fish eat small fish;
squid eat big fish]
That's how it works.
We're going to catch 100 squid today.
[Setting a small target first]
100.
It's not possible today.
How many can we catch today?
About 10 at most.
He said we might not even catch 10.
We're ready.
Time to fish squid.
Lower the line all the way to the seabed.
Let out the line like this.
I'll show you how to do it.
[Squid fishing tutorial]
Okay.
Watch him.
Are we fishing directly from our hands?
Just drop what we saw just now
to the bottom of the sea.
[Step 1: Sink the hook to the seabed]
Then you pull it up.
It's about this high.
How do you tell
when you've hooked a squid?
It gets a little heavier.
If it's a fish,
it'll be like...
[Step 2: Feel the rhythm of the line
being tugged and reel it in promptly]
But if it's a squid,
its rhythm will be like this.
[The phone's learned it]
Can we actually catch anything?
It seems so difficult.
[It's not that easy]
That's why he said
we might not even catch 10
this whole night.
Right? It seems really hard.
Here you go.
[Start fishing]
He just handed it over to him
since he couldn't catch anything himself.
I'll try.
I'm going.
Be careful.
How far should I cast it?
Just let it go all the way to the bottom.
To the very bottom?
How do you tell it's reached the bottom?
You'll feel it
stop moving,
then you'll know it's reached the bottom.
[Already caught something?]
I feel so dizzy.
So dizzy.
[Dizzy]
I need to squat a bit.
I can't. I think I need to sit down,
or I'll really faint.
[Shaking]
[Everyone casts a line together]
Can we actually catch anything?
I think it's quite difficult.
Let's see how it goes.
I'll go over there.
[Fei moves to the other side]
I think there are too many people here.
That's true.
If so many of us
can't catch even a single squid,
we'll be really disappointed.
That won't happen.
We'll definitely catch some.
I think I've got one.
You got one?
No, I didn't.
Alright.
[All excitement for nothing]
It's not that easy.
The teacher
didn't give us any bait.
You know...
You need to jiggle it.
It's actually hard
to get the right feel for it.
You know,
it's like...
The squid's like,
"You guys are so stingy,
not giving me anything to eat
and still expecting me to come up."
[Fishing with no bait]
How about this?
If we don't catch anything today,
we won't go back.
Sounds good.
Okay.
We'll stay until sunrise.
Sounds good.
We must catch something.
Come on, little squid.
Come on, we've even got
the sauce ready.
[Come to us]
We're just waiting for you, little squid.
[Trying hard alone]
Fei, so it's possible that we got
the dipping sauce ready
but catch absolutely nothing, right?
I think that's very likely to happen.
I didn't expect squid fishing
would be this difficult.
Nothing.
What happened?
[Got something?]
You saw a fish, right?
No.
What did it feel like?
Is that a fish? You've got another fish?
Are you some kind of fishing expert
or something?
I caught one...
I got one here!
Really?
Yes, really.
I can feel it.
It's...
Let me record this for you.
But I'm a bit scared.
Come on, you can do it.
Is it gone?
[Empty]
No.
It got away!
[I'm free]
There really is!
I see it!
They've really come!
It's gone!
[Boss got one]
He caught one!
That's amazing!
He caught one too!
That's awesome!
Did mine just get away?
It probably did escape.
Yes.
She just caught one too,
but then it escaped.
[Envious]
That's impressive.
Did you let the line all the way down?
Yes, and every 5 seconds,
[Sharing techniques]
I gave it a little tug.
Then I felt it coming up.
You let the whole line down?
Yes, almost all of it,
just a little bit left.
Feels like we're getting close
to our goal.
[Experience up]
[Skill points up]
What did it feel like?
I kept my hand
in that position,
and it felt like it sank down.
So you lowered it every 5 seconds?
Every 5 seconds, I gave it a little tug.
You know, imitating the movement
of a small shrimp twitching.
[I see]
What's wrong?
Did you get one?
No,
something just flew by.
Something just jumped by.
There's a small fish jumping.
A small fish?
How cute.
Really.
They're jumping fish.
Jumping fish.
Super chill.
[Zoning out]
Little fish, little fish, take the bait.
[Relaxed]
The squid says, "I gave you a chance."
It feels so cool.
Why does it feel like
the waves have gotten bigger?
Be careful!
[The wind and waves are getting stronger]
The wind is getting really strong.
This is the sea breeze.
[The fishing line is starting to
get out of control]
[So sudden]
Such strong wind.
What's wrong?
[Urgent]
The wind is getting strong.
What's happening?
I don't know either.
Wait a moment.
[Lights off]
[Weather at sea can change rapidly]
[If strong winds or waves arise,
return to shore as soon as possible]
[Making a sharp turn]
Why isn't he telling us anything?
[Going back]
Are we heading back now?
[Confused about the situation]
So are we just leaving like this, or...?
[We haven't caught any squid yet]
[Slowly reeling in the line]
We're caught in wind mixed with rain.
We need to get to shore first.
He means the wind's rising,
so we have to head back.
[The sea conditions are no longer
suitable for continuing the voyage]
Let's go.
The weather's bad.
How many have we caught so far?
Four.
We've got 4 squid.
Who caught them?
Him.
[The boss's small haul]
Come back.
Why's everything happening so suddenly?
[Today's Moments caption:
such a pity—next time]
What a pity.
Didn't catch anything.
[Such a pity] [Disappointed]
This looks a bit like when we first
came over on that boat.
The wind is so strong.
Would you like some squid sashimi?
Yes, sashimi.
I'll make it for you.
Squid sashimi.
The boss is going to cook now.
Cooking.
This boss clearly knows how to cook.
That's right.
I really want to eat it. Hurry up.
Hurry up.
Are you hungry?
I'm hungry again.
[Note: Thai squid sashimi is a raw dish
made from freshly caught live squid]
[Commonly found at street night markets,
known for its sour-and-spicy flavors]
[and distinctive way of eating]
Sashimi.
Even though I'm Thai,
I still want to film this.
[Since I'm already here]
Delicious?
Delicious.
Be careful.
This is the squid's ink (sac).
It's its ink (sac).
Black.
The opening where the ink comes out.
Chinese people (use it)...
For writing.
For writing, yes, yes.
It's really clean.
All transparent.
It's raining.
So beautiful.
I love it.
[Today's Moments caption:
such a pity—next time]
this trip's worth it]
Paipai, let me take a photo for you.
[Hitcard exclusive photographer, Esther]
Don't move. Right.
Stay still.
Good.
[Handsome]
[Recording]
I really love this feeling.
It's raining at sea.
It's truly beautiful.
I want to look at it more,
so I can keep it in my mind
for a long time.
[The weather's unpredictable—
better to enjoy the moment]
You all, sit down. Here it comes.
In the rain.
The atmosphere is amazing.
Don't eat the head first.
Why?
[Lemon]
[The perfect way of eating]
It really changed.
The color keeps changing.
Look.
Cool, right?
Why is that?
[Note: After a squid dies, the pigment
cells in its skin lose neural control,]
It's not changing.
Its cells are changing.
causing its color to quickly fade
to white or pale.]
I thought the world's programming
had a glitch.
Your descriptions are all so funny.
So magical.
It's like code flying everywhere.
This is so cool.
I want to take a photo.
It's really cool.
Don't you think this scene looks
just like the moment our legs went numb?
You could feel your legs
turning entirely gray,
with little black dots scattered inside.
So fast. So cool.
I feel so sorry for it,
but I'll try it anyway.
You can eat it directly.
There's no fishy taste at all.
But I think this sauce
covers up
its original flavor.
I'll dip it in wasabi.
Really?
Otherwise, you can't taste
[Mu's food pairing:
squid sashimi with wasabi]
its original flavor.
Thanks.
[Delicious]
Doesn't this taste better?
[Let me try it too]
[Delicious]
You can really handle spicy food.
I'm alright.
[Yin Haoyu, who can handle spice,
one bite]
This sauce is absolutely amazing.
[2 bites]
I want to learn how to make it.
[3 bites]
[Drinking some beverage]
It's so spicy.
[Fact check: he can't handle spice]
So good.
This feels incredible.
It's cooked!
Thank you.
Isn't this just amazing?
Grilled squid.
It's worth it.
Today's trip is worth it.
Really.
Not a wasted trip.
Even though we didn't catch any squid,
I still think...
I still think this flavor is
[She loves squid sashimi the most]
more impressive.
Because it's so fresh.
It feels like it came straight
from the sea to my mouth.
Yes.
This is delicious.
What do you think?
Delicious. Very fresh.
[San Lai peeling shrimp]
[Feeding Mu]
What a gentleman.
Thank you.
[Feeding Diamond]
[Feeding Na Na]
It's okay. You eat more yourself.
It's okay, I...
I can peel it myself.
Take it.
Thank you, Shrimp-Peeling Man.
[Shrimp-Peeling Man]
Thanks.
What's a Shrimp-Peeling Man?
A superhero who peels shrimp.
That's right.
Shrimp-Peeling Man.
Just take this.
I'll peel them all.
You're too kind.
He peeled all the shrimp.
Yes, Fei is such a gentleman.
No.
It's because I really enjoy
peeling shrimp.
You like peeling shrimp?
I really enjoy peeling shrimp.
Why?
Is it stress-relieving?
Very stress-relieving.
And the main reason is that I think
once you start peeling with your hands,
you might as well finish the job.
I find these things too troublesome.
He has a strong sense of family.
Yes.
I'm full.
You're full?
Can't eat anymore.
Today's schedule was very packed,
but it was also very enjoyable.
Of course,
there were also some small scares
and many unexpected gains.
I really hope that
time could pass more slowly tonight.
[From the daily camaraderie on set
to the warm companionship during the trip]
[Friendship shines brighter
in the laughter]
THAI SWEET!
[If a journey is an adventure,
it's good to have friends' companionship]
After being in the sun for so long today,
I need to do some
urgent whitening treatment.
Oh no. I've run out.
Don't worry.
I have extras here.
Great.
My sunburned skin is saved.
Nothing beats the Mageline Time Trilogy.
Repair, whitening, anti-aging.
All in one set.
8x whitening, 5x firming.
After using it,
skin becomes soft and glowing.
Tomorrow Na Na
will definitely be even better.
Keep it up!
[Next Episode]
To give this trip a perfect ending,
let's have one last party together!
Sure!
Sure.
We'll set things up.
All the heavy, tiring, hard work.
Let's all get ready separately.
Alright.
We can discuss
what kind of performance we should do.
That's so sudden.
Why don't we each prepare a surprise?
That works too.
Welcome everyone
to the THAI SWEET "If" Party.
Hello everyone,
I'm Jiang Mu.
Next, we'll have an award ceremony,
and there will be a little
surprise reveal.
We'll be giving each of
our good friends an award
related to the word "Thai."
Who is it?
[Stay tuned for the next episode]