Where are we going now?
We're
going to...
Welcome to Thailand.
Why didn't you two
make that "whoa" sound?
We haven't started shooting yet.
Then I'll take you to
a very special restaurant in Thailand.
Dinosaur egg.
Black sand.
Your teeth are all black.
No, they're not.
Black Teeth Restaurant.
It's so white that it's glowing.
Look at yours.
Look, it's not particularly
bright on my side.
Those things I sent you...
that you need to help me shoot,
have you learned how to do it?
But it's mainly about the vibe.
Look at me.
I look very natural like this.
Smiling.
Look at me.
You're not really...
You think you look natural,
but actually
how it appears on camera
is like this.
I said look at me,
and then you're like this.
No way.
Where? Let me see.
I didn't capture it.
But it's just like that.
See how natural it looks?
You need to do dynamic poses with me.
I need to do this too?
You do your own cool pose.
No, I can only learn and imitate.
What?
Why do you keep doing that?
I can't capture your clothes.
My hairstyle today
is a sleep-friendly hairstyle.
Why?
It won't get messy.
It's already messy.
Handsome Zhao and Pretty Mu.
She'll only play around
for 10 more minutes.
Then she'll be out of energy.
I can force myself to stay energetic
and talk non-stop.
Talk about what?
Talking to yourself?
Talking to you.
Talking to someone nearby.
She'll only play around
for 10 more minutes.
Are you sleeping?
I'm going to Thailand first.
Stop talking.
We're almost there.
Let's go.
I ran into a female celebrity
on the plane.
What are you doing?
Touching up my makeup.
Keep going.
Zhao, are you going to eat
the in-flight meal later?
I won't eat it.
Will I eat it then?
You'll just fall asleep.
Probably won't eat it.
Don't keep trying to set me up
to feel sleepy.
I won't fall asleep.
I'm excited.
Let's go.
You need to look handsome.
Okay.
Let's go.
I'm going to Thailand first.
Do I look good?
Yes. Not puffy.
Going back to Thailand again.
Where are we going now?
We're going to...
Shanghai.
How long did you keep this pose?
Hold on.
Hold on!
Let's just go
and ignore him.
Hold on!
Are you okay?
No, let's do it together.
Come on.
Okay, together.
Time to dance.
Dance.
Come on.
Dance!
You need to join us.
This is Thailand's welcome ceremony?
No matter how sweet Thai coconuts are,
they're not as sweet as
the looks between you two.
There's more.
There's more?
Welcome to Thailand.
Thanks, bro.
Welcome back to Thailand.
Flowers.
Are you hungry?
Yes.
Okay.
Then I'll take you to
a very special restaurant in Thailand.
What restaurant?
My restaurant.
Then let's go.
Okay, let's go.
Let me.
Okay.
Welcome to Thailand.
Back in Thailand again.
Well...
We need some music in this car.
Singing. Karaoke.
Okay.
Lin Sui, is this your car?
Of course not.
Welcome to Thailand.
What?
Bye.
I'll play you
a Thai song I loved when I was little.
Okay.
Thai song?
Before... Mong kon orn aen...
What?
Mong kon orn aen lae mong kon rong hai...
Is this Thai?
Yes.
It's that song.
I've heard it.
Have you heard it before?
Yes, I have.
Mong kon orn aen...
What is this?
I'm going to continue
taking photos of you.
Mong kon orn aen...
Right?
Good.
Nice.
Good. Look this way a bit more.
Sawadee krab (Hello).
It should be "kop kun krab (thank you)."
Kop kun krab (Thank you).
Why didn't you two
make that "whoa" sound?
We haven't started shooting yet.
We haven't started yet.
Let's reshoot!
We're here.
Tell me,
what kind of reaction
should we have when we get out?
It looks a bit like...
a mecha head.
So fancy.
Such a magnificent restaurant!
Come on, let's take a photo
for our check-in.
Are we the first customers?
Yes.
Wow.
Let's go.
You look so beautiful.
Okay.
Hello.
She's so beautiful.
First,
you need to take
this lamp.
This lantern is for you.
Thank you.
It's a place with a great atmosphere.
It's like an escape room, right?
It's so cool here.
Isn't it?
Hello.
Wow.
Okay.
First, we have a welcome drink.
This is our welcome drink.
Gold dust.
What's this?
Dry ice.
And then,
you can drink it.
I need to remove the base, right?
Yes.
Cheers.
Welcome to Thailand.
Welcome to THAI SWEET.
THAI SWEET.
Try this first.
What's this?
Just try it first.
Try it first, then guess.
I'm afraid.
You try it first.
Just eat it like this?
What's that expression?
What does that mean?
It has a mysterious flavor.
What?
It's soft and bouncy.
Pomelo jelly.
Pomelo.
Next we're having a...
bread.
Bread?
It's very special.
Next one, right?
Is it Thai bread?
Eyes of the dragon.
Eyes of the dragon?
Ice of the dragon?
It's dragon...
Dragon's eye.
Longan.
Yes.
Dragon hand.
This is not longan.
I think we've misunderstood.
Eyes.
Eyes of the dragon.
Longan.
Do you want to...
Light it?
I'm afraid to.
No.
You do it.
I don't dare.
Do you dare to do it now?
Yes.
This is very cool.
Right?
Let me tell you,
this is edible.
Which one is edible?
The candle is edible?
This one.
Is it chocolate?
No,
this is butter.
How do you say butter in Chinese?
Huangyou.
Black butter? Never seen that before.
Won't it turn your teeth
black after eating?
No, it won't.
Try one. Let me see.
Okay.
There's also this inside.
Let me see.
There's cheese inside.
Your teeth are all black.
No, they're not.
Take a look.
That's why we have mirrors.
So that's how it's designed.
Come on.
What's wrong?
This bread is quite delicious.
The bread is good.
The butter is salty.
I'm going to make the next dish myself.
I'll change my clothes first.
Thank you.
I know this one.
Okay. First, there's a lobster.
Lobster.
Then there's a Thai-style steak.
Are you ready?
Yes, I'm ready.
Mike looks so charming
when he's focused.
Yes.
Do you think so?
Super charming.
Zhao,
when can I taste
the food you cook for me?
Didn't I make you
stir-fried eggs and tomatoes?
You mean in the show?
Yes.
Then I'll cook something for you.
Let me serve you in person.
What would you like to eat?
I don't need to eat anything.
Just enjoy your cooking.
Please sit down.
I'm Avatar.
Sit down.
I know you too well.
You just want to play around.
Too sweet!
It's burnt, bro.
Mike!
Look, I was watching you chat
and I forgot.
I'm telling you...
I completely forgot!
It should be fine. You can cut it.
You can just trim off the outer layer.
It's fine.
Do you really know how to cook?
I do.
Add some butter for me.
Turn down the heat.
Okay.
It's too burnt.
It's fine. We can eat it.
It's done.
Done?
Okay.
Try this first.
It's okay. Let me do it.
Thank you.
It looks nice.
It tastes sweet
because it has cream.
Thai delicacy.
It looks so delicious.
This is lobster mousse.
You made it look nice.
The way you drizzled the sauce,
you've clearly practiced.
I'm not joking.
You've learned it for a long time.
Not really.
Delicious.
Does it taste authentically Thai?
Yes.
Right?
I never expected Mike to be so handsome,
cook such delicious food,
be so patient,
so dedicated to his work,
and so charming.
This restaurant will surely become famous.
You guys.
Come rest.
Stop working.
Alright.
Good job.
Well done.
And you can eat...
this one first.
Open this.
Moonlight Box.
Is it beautiful?
Yes, it is.
It's so pretty.
It even has gold foil.
Dinosaur egg.
Black sand.
This is fish.
Here's another beautiful one.
Each of his dish designs
is quite interesting.
Abalone.
This is abalone.
Black rose.
This one is quite beautiful.
Let me take a good photo of it.
Open it.
Okay. Then eat it like this.
Eat it like this.
How do I eat it?
Just eat it directly.
Is this the only way to eat it?
This also has a sweet and sour taste.
It's Thai flavor.
Sweet and sour.
Yummy.
We're really good at
exploring restaurants together.
And it has coconut.
It's tasty.
Can I eat this now?
Can I eat it now?
Yes. This is fish.
This is delicious. It's also spicy.
It's good, right?
There's a sword.
Thank you, Zhao.
This will make our teeth
black again after eating.
Black Teeth Restaurant.
So what do you think about my restaurant?
Any suggestions?
I do have a suggestion.
It's about the presentation.
Everything is too black.
If I want to post on social media,
it's all black.
You should have some other colors.
But not white.
Not white.
You could add some purple.
Black-purple, black-red.
And silver, right?
Black-blue.
Okay.
Good.
Do you want to go for a walk?
Or should we
continue eating?
We can go for a walk.
Weren't we planning to go to...
Chinatown?
Chinatown.
The place where we filmed.
Let's take a stroll there.
Okay.
Xin.
I've prepared a surprise for you.
You guys,
turn around.
Look.
Let's go to Chinatown.
Okay.
Isn't this where we filmed?
Yes, this is the place.
Right.
I want to play Mu once.
Let's switch roles.
I want to play too.
Zhao,
why don't you ever compliment me?
What exactly do you want me to say?
I miss you.
Me too.