[English subtitles are available]
I guess so.
But Mr. Situ
does not look like this kind of person.
So it's a thief crying "Stop thief" trick.
What did you say?
Liu says that
the deceased said "go away" in Russian last night.
Ma Shiying can't speak Russian.
Then who can speak Russian?
Mr. Situ.
Wan Jixiang,
and Liu.
Liu is a conductor.
And I was talking to Wan Jixiang.
So whoever
doesn't have an alibi
is the killer.
Didn't you two both meet the killer,
which is the conductor?
And now you're telling me
that Situ Yan is the killer.
I only caught a glimpse of him
passing down the aisle
when I was sitting in my room.
It was impossible for me to see that clearly.
But Mr. Situ also rang the bell,
when Ms. Qi Hong found the killer.
I don't think he was the killer.
It was room three you firstly went to,
before you went to room one, right?
Yes.
Then Situ Yan should have time
to come out of Room Three first
when you went in to check,
and then went back to wait for you.
Well, if that's the case,
the man I saw
might not be Situ.
Is this a challenge or a warning?
Everybody, stay put.
I understand
there was a homicide happened in this train,
and you want to solve it before the train arrives.
But I didn't leave my room last night.
I went to bed early.
And I know nothing about it.
So I'm not gonna answer any questions.
Mr. George Blair,
I just have one question for you.
Is there any other...
Are you crazy?
He is a diplomat
with diplomatic immunity.
Even if he's the killer,
it's beyond the scope of our duties.
Using diplomatic immunity to escape from punishment
makes no difference to
Ma Shiying using his foreign nationality to do the same thing.
You'll get into big trouble
if you keep making a scene like this without any basis.
It will be a diplomatic incident.
It's not just about you.
He's a lefty.
And Ma Shiying' s fatal wound
was caused by using left hand.
What do you want?
Do you know who I am?
Here's the thing,
Mr. George Blair.
We're investigating
a homicide
happened on this train.
You are a diplomat,
but...
Then you should know
that you have no right to interrogate me.
For a homicide happened in China,
we have the right to investigate anyone
who was in the vicinity of the crime scene.
You haven't even confirmed
ownership of this rail with the Russians.
What rights are you talking to me about?
I'm not in charge of the rail.
But I make the call on this train,
because I own it.
You're being unreasonable.
Mr. George Blair,
I want to ask you a question.
Go away.
Is there a woman in your room?
Hands off.
You ordered two meals.
Is there a woman in your room?
Answer me!
Let them in.
You have disturbed my wife.
I'm not gonna let this go.
Hello, madam.
I'm sorry to bother you.
My health condition is not good
and I could catch a cold easily.
So my husband was just worried about me.
Please don't mind.
Say what you want to say
and then go.
We don't like to be disturbed.
Can I see your passports, please?
Madame, you are Chinese, after all,
Can I have your Chinese name?
Fang Ting.
Are you going to Harbin?
My husband
is a consul at the American Consulate in Harbin.
Have you been
to Harbin before?
Sure,
we spent most of our time in Harbin.
Have you heard about the tragedy at Xu family?
When did it happen?
Twelve years ago.
I was eleven or twelve years old,
and hadn't been to Harbin yet.
So I have no impression on this.
Is the case that you're investigating
connected to this matter?
We're looking for clues
the killer left behind.
As offensive as it is,
we still hope to...
No, you have no right
to search our luggage.
Well, what if I just want to see
madam's jewelry box?
Is that okay?
Can I have a look at that?
What happened to these pearls?
I accidentally broke my necklace
when I was packing.
There was no time to fix it,
so I had to take them on the train.
Have you ever left the room since you got on the train?
Like going to the bathroom or something.
What exactly are you suspecting?
Get out of here.
Stop doing that.
Leave him alone.
Stop this.
I need help.
Hands off him.
Coming.
Stop this.
Stop!
Leave him alone.
Let go of me.
I'll answer any questions,
as long as you let him go.
I haven't been out of my room
since I got on the train.
I was in the room all the time.
And I went to bed early last night.
In fact,
all we know is that somebody was killed.
We don't even know
who's dead.
I'm gonna make you regret it.
If that's the case,
how do you explain this?
What do you mean?
This is what we found at the crime scene.
I believe
that madam must have broken the necklace
at that moment.
You missed one
when you were collecting the pearls.
If you are telling the truth,
how come somebody who has never been outside the room
could get the chance
to leave a pearl in someone else's room?
I really don't know what you're talking about.
Don't kill me.
It's okay.
Everything will be okay.
This is the murder weapon.
I was trying to get a pack of cigarettes,
and I saw the dagger right there.
I don't know why it is under my purse.
I really have no idea.
The killer
probably put it there
when he was getting out.
He will be back.
He will come back for sure.
You guys are so irresponsible.
You should publicize your investigation.
Now the killer is among us.
Anybody could get killed.
Everyone is having a nervous breakdown.
We've almost found the killer.
There's no need to be scared.
Can I see what's in this purse?
The murderer left too many clues
in your room.
I believe
he may come back anytime.
I don't want to die.
Don't kill me.
I won't say anything.
I won't tell anyone about anything.
Don't kill me.
Can you stop making her agitated.
I think she'd better leave her room
and go to your place.
Stay with her.
You are the one who has seen the murderer.
So your memories
are very important to us.
And once we catch him,
you'll be safe.
I've said everything I remember.
So many clues,
and so many witnesses.
But you still can't find the murderer.
You just can't find the murderer.
Don’t worry.
Bai Lu will be with you.
We can send someone to protect you
if you need.
You won't be in danger.
So,
could you please recall
what happened last night?
For example, this communicating door,
was it open
or locked?
I don't know.
I really don't know.
This is very important.
Please think about it carefully.
Well.
I remember now.
Last night,
I hung my wash bag
on the handle of that communicating door.
It was blocking the door lock.
I didn't check it.
So,
I didn't see it clearly.
Right there!
The door lock was blocked.
I know...
I know you're scared.
You don't have to trust me,
but you can trust him.
He will find the murderer.
And what I can do
is to protect you.
I'll be relieved
if you all leave me alone.
This next question I'm going to ask
may be a little offensive to you.
But from what I saw yesterday,
you are very close to Ma Shiying.
In this case,
you probably wouldn't mind
if the door was locked or not.
Why would you ask Liao Yun
to confirm again?
It was because
there are too many evil men in this world.
That's why there are so many poor women.
I think you misunderstood me, Mr. Situ.
I'm no longer
the kind of woman you think I am.
And I'm no longer young.
Now,
all I do to earn a living
is to make people happy.
I'm just a singer.
You're still a singer?
Yeah.
Now,
I just play the piano and sing.
I was afraid that
Ma Shiying would do something to me.
That's why
I would repeatedly check if the communicating door was locked at that time.
I'm sorry.
I've been so rude.
May I
leave now?
What's wrong?
I was wondering
why she would lie.
Who are you talking about?
Hello.
Her Highness wants to see you.
Please.
I heard
you found a pearl.
Yeah.
We have found the owner.
I believe that the murderer
will soon be found as well.
The pearl you found
must be the one I lost.
Look,
this silver pin
of this hairpin broke.
That's why the pearl fell off.
I don't wear this hairpin often.
The silver pin has turned black.
Go check if the pearl you found
is also stained
with some blackened stains.
Do you know
where I found this pearl?
I don't even know when it was lost.
I wore this hairpin
yesterday,
but didn't pay attention to it.
Then I put it back in the box.
It was after you asked my servant
about the pearls today
that I went to take a look.
Pearls
are round,
so they may roll around.
What do you think a smart person would do
if he or she wants to free the guilty?
At least
that person wouldn't try to frame a diplomat.
Things are getting weirder.
The murderer
was hiding in Ma Shiying's room around 1:00 yesterday.
Meanwhile,
Wan Jixiang,
Zong Yan.
and Liu Zijie
were drinking together.
Bai Lu and Liao Yun said that neither of them had left last night.
Shi Chunsan was in Princess Rong Xiang's room.
Liu Zijie can prove it.
Then,
the only people without an alibi
are me,
Qi Hong,
and the Blairs.
Around 1:15,
Shi Chunshan saw the strange conductor
in the aisle.
At that time,
Qi Hong and I rang the bell almost at the same time.
Liu Zijie can testify that.
Zong Yan has already said that
you had time to commit the crime at that time.
But I chose to trust you.
Are you suspecting me?
If you still can't find out the murder,
I have every reason to suspect that
you are using me to confuse the situation.
I won't explain this to you now.
Go away.
I'm sorry.
Here's the thing.
Our original intention is to solve the case as soon as possible.
I don't want to see you.
Please go away.
Xu Fangting!
Hiding your identity won't help you in any way.
She has nothing to do with this.
You're right.
I'm Xu Fangting.
And I know that it was Ma Shiying who died.
So I didn't dare to say who I am.
Once I tell you,
you will doubt me.
Just like now.
We just want to get closer to the truth.
You have no right to judge Ma Shiying.
But someone else did it.
You should be applauding,
not looking for the judge.
Whoever he is,
he is a good person.
No matter who he is,
he's a murderer.
But he killed my sister-in-law and her child.
You think they deserved to die?
You knew Ma Shiying was the murderer?
I saw him
on the day of the crime.
That devil.
But he was not guilty now.
It's like what happened in Beijing
the other day.
He became a lawful citizen.
If you say I don't deserve to be a member of the legal profession,
then do you deserve to be Chinese?
Do you?
The police ignored my allegations,
the evidence left at the scene
and anything else.
This is fate.
Fate made me witness his retribution for sin.
So you hid in the box
because you were afraid of being recognized by Ma Shiying?
He had never seen me.
So he didn't know me.
But I knew he was the devil.
How could my sister-in-law have extra money?
She had exhausted her strength
in maintaining the household of her whole family.
That bastard didn't find money.
But after he saw my sister-in-law he tried to molest her.
She told me to run with the baby.
I was so scared at the time.
Who are you?
Let go of me!
Stop it!
Please.
Let go of me!
Please! Let me go!
Mom!
I ran away.
I left them behind and ran.
You were only twelve years old.
There was nothing you could do by staying there.
It wasn't your fault.
I'm the one who got my niece killed.
It was me.
None of this would have happened
if I had grabbed her hand a little tighter
or covered her eyes.
This had nothing to do with you.
It wasn't your fault.
I really wanted to kill him myself.
But I didn't even have the courage to look at him again.
I'm a loser.
I'm useless.
So,
someone killed him for you.
I know what you're suspecting.
But that's not what we did.
Maybe...
there are other people on the train who know the Xu family?
I don't know.
I only heard that
Princess Rong Xiang is also on this train.
She's my sister-in-law's godmother.
But she's too old.
Besides,
she and my sister-in-law
stopped seeing each other a long time ago.
I'm afraid she's not the one who killed Ma Shiying.
What were the names of the servants in your house at that time?
We did not usually call them by their names directly.
What kind of person was the one who reported the crime at that time?
She was just a student.
A student?
Yes.
She studied English with my sister-in-law.
But I can't remember her name.
Could
she be on this train too?
Maybe I can remind you of her name.
For example,
Qi Hong or Bai Lu?
Han Shuang? That's right.
Her name is Han Shuang.
I remember now.
Han Shuang?
Yes.
She was a student twelve years ago,
she can't still be a student now, right?
Her age doesn't match.
I've checked her identity-document.
There is nothing wrong.
Her name is Bail Lu.
No.
I'd like to talk to you alone.
What are they going to talk about?
About changing name.
I think you know that
Xu Huichang's sister is also on this train, right?
I haven't met her.
You were there
when the Xu family tragedy occurred.
No.
Then why did you call the police?
You were an accomplice?
No.
You helped the murderer?
I didn't mean it.
What did you do?
I was nine years old
at the time.
I learned English from Mrs. Xu.
She was very nice to me.
She was like a mother
to me.
There was always a coachman loitering at the door
a few days before the crime.
I took a ride in his car once.
He said that Mrs. Xu had done something unseemly.
I haven't seen him
since the crime.
So I suspected him,
and I went to the police.
The police said
that the appearance of the person I mentioned
was the same as that of the murderer Fangting mentioned.
So you killed him
when you met him again?
Mr. Situ,
he once made you nothing
in court.
So you have a motive to kill too.
When exactly did Han Shuang
change her name to Bai Lu?
She didn't.
Han Shuang is Bai Lu.
Bail Lu is Han Shuang.
Then why?
When I was reading the list of people on the train
to the Blairs,
she hurriedly told me a name.
That means she knew there are people
on the train who knows her.
People who lie in an emergency situation
are most likely to use the words they associate with.
For example.
Green reeds are thick and dense.
Clear dews become frost thence.
That's my guess.
Her Highness is Mrs. Xu's godmother.
The Blairs
are Mrs. Xu's sister and brother-in-law.
Bai Lu was the one who reported the crime.
Then I wouldn't be surprised
if all the passengers in this compartment
are related to the Xu family.
I would rather
everyone has nothing to do with the Xu family.
Yes.
Shi Chunshan
was the cook of the Xu family.
She accompanied Yuqin when Yuqin got married.
She was also displaced
after the Xu family's accident.
She met me two years ago,
and I just happened to be short of
a suitable person.
This case is related to the Xu family.
I think it's better to save trouble.
We didn't kill anyone.
And we don't want to get ourselves into trouble.
You were there
when the Xu family tragedy occurred.
I'm the one who got Mrs. Xu killed.
That devil would not have
come in through that door and killed her
if I had not forgotten to
close the back door that night.
If I hadn't,
she wouldn't have died.
So you killed Ma Shiying to avenge her?
No, it wasn't me.
I never knew who the murderer was.
After the crime,
we servants were locked up
for investigation.
I...
I wasn't released
until Ying died.
The Xu family
no longer existed at that time.
I didn't know where to go.
I wanted to go back to Madam,
but she was very sick.
I wandered around
until I came across Her Highness.
I finally found a place to stay.
I didn't dare to say
what relationship I had with the Xu family.
I was really
scared.
Madam was seriously ill?
I see.
All of you are related to the Xu family
and Mrs. Xu.
Did you bring that book?
Why?
May I have a look?
Sure.
You were so beautiful when you were young.
Sir,
I think you've got it wrong.
That's my daughter
holding my grandson.
They took this two years ago.
I probably
didn't keep it very well.
You're lying.
This photo may develop wrinkles
if you do not keep it well.
But the yellowing of the photo can only be due to the passage of time.
I can see that you've been preserving this photo very carefully.
Even if it is an old photo from thirty years ago.
I think
it's probably because your daughter has passed away.
I was afraid that you would be sad
and didn't want to mention it.
But now I have to say that
the people in the photo
are not your daughter and your grandson,
but you and your daughter.
That trip to Harbin to see her
must have been the hardest thing you've ever done in your life.
And you.
What about me?
You hinted to me that
Ma Shiying
had the habit of taking sleeping pills on the train.
You said
all these things.
I don't know about these things.
He had a fully loaded pistol under his pillow.
It means he was so worried about the threatening letter.
So he couldn't have been taking sleeping pills
while he slept.
What does it have to do with me
if he took or not?
The threatening letters he was afraid of
were not the two you gave me,
but the one you have burned.
But Wan Jixiang didn't have time to kill people.
He was just an asshole.
He shouldn't have killed Mrs. Xu.
My parents died early.
So I would do anything
to survive.
Stealing.
Robbing.
Cheating.
People thought I was a child
and would let me go.
But later,
I met someone who was not easy to mess with.
He wanted to beat me to death.
It was Mrs. Xu who saved me.
I met the murderer
before the crime.
I tried to steal from him
and he caught me.
I didn't want to give up.
So I followed him all the way
to Mrs. Xu's house.
I didn't go in.
I didn't.
I can responsibly tell you that
Wan Jixiang definitely did not leave the box at that time,
at least not when Ma Shiying died.
Xu Huichang died in a naval battle.
At that time, the entire fleet was wiped out.
And the ground landing point of Japanese army
happened to be Weirong.
That's nothing.
Back then,
we surrendered without even fighting in Weirong.
Give in when it's time to give in.
Why don't you drink?
You really want to know?
Then I'll tell you.
I was responsible for transferring my sister-in-law
first to Fengtian
and then to Harbin,
but I received other orders midway.
When I returned to Harbin,
it was the day of the murder.
I was drunk
that night.
I was supposed to be there that night
to make sure she was safe.
But I was drunk.
So...
Liu is an experienced conductor.
He has been working from the first train until now.
Ying's last name is Liu, right?
It was me.
It was all my fault.
I can't believe I didn't trust my own daughter.
If it wasn't for me,
she wouldn't have killed herself.
She had a grievance.
I'm gonna get this straight.
Yeah.
I knew her,
and had known her for a long time.
When I was in Nanjing,
I had a terrible illness,
before she was arrested.
It was her who looked after me.
She just cared about everything.
I was a prostitute at the time.
But she just kept persuading me to quit.
While meat and wine go to waste behind the vermilion gates of the rich,
the poor is frozen to death on an empty stomach by the roadside.
I did that to make a living.
I didn't steal anything or rob anyone.
What did I do wrong?
How could her always have her nose up to tell me what to do?
I was pissed.
So I told them about the stuff between her and Huai Chang.
It was all her fault.
Why did she have to advocate reform at that sensitive time?
After that,
She ran away
to Harbin.
Why was I so scared?
I was afraid of the killer
to kill me.
He was here
to avenge Mrs. Xu.
You said you left your wash bag on the door handle.
So you didn't even know if the door is open or closed.
But if you really did so,
you would find that the bag won't be able to stop anything.
Because the door handle
is lower than the door lock.
I read an editorial before I get on the train.
I don't remember the content.
But I do remember
that the author's name
was Huai Chang.
You've got the pipa pick in your purse.
But there are no calluses
of plucking strings on your fingers.
Instead, you have calluses
on the outside of your pinky
and middle finger.
You've stopped being a prostitute for a long time,
and become a writer.
You had kept Mrs. Xu alive
in your own way.
I just wanted to show her
that I can live a good life.
But it was too late.
Everyone on this train except me
is connected to the Xu family.
I don't think
it's a coincidence.
Doctor estimated
that the time of death was between 0:00 and 2:00 am.
All of your descriptions
are trying to lead me
to a made-up fact.
At midnight yesterday,
a fictitious killer got on the train
from Jinzhou Station.
He wore a conductor's uniform,
and used a master key to open the Ma Shiying's room.
After his murder,
he made an chamber of secrets,
and left Qi Hong's room.
He took off his clothing in Shi Chunshan's room,
then disappeared
at the direction to the bathroom
wearing a red cheongsam.
It would have been a perfect story
if the train hadn't stopped.
The killer should have got off the train by now.
Unfortunately,
the train stopped all night.
And no one could get away from here.
All of you were working together
on describing a killer
who didn't exist.
When exactly did Ma Shiying die?
His broken dial
seemed to suggest that
he was experiencing a violent event.
Ma Shiying was devoted to watches.
How could someone like him
sleep with a watch on?
That means
1:15 is the fake time of death
created by the killer.
Since the time of the crime was not 1:15,
could it be before then?
That's what you want me to believe.
At 00:40,
I was woken up by the loud noise in Ma Shiying's room.
And then I heard him
telling the conductor to get out in Russian.
Then Wan Jixiang and Zong Yan told me that
Ma Shiying didn't speak Russian.
Because you also wanted me
to be involved in this perfect alibi.
It was like the time of murdering
was really before 1:15
But what if it was after 1:15?
Like
1:30,
1:40,
or even
a time infinitely closer to 2:00.
Then all of your...
All of your alibis
would be null and void.
The victim was stabbed nine times.
Some of his stab wounds were deep
and some were shallow.
Those shallow wounds
pierced only the superficial layer of his skin.
And one deep wound
went straight through his entire lung.
Nine stabs.
One,
two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine.
You happen to be nine people as well.
You...
have given a trial to him.
But your trial was illegal.