[English subtitles are available]
[Romance on the Farm]
[Episode 19]
Lady Hua'er,
I saw that Boss Wu
went to Lian Man'er's restaurant just now.
The wagon of vegetables
was pulled to her restaurant too.
Alright, I got it.
You may leave.
Honey,
your sister
is quite smart.
Where did she get so many
out of season vegetables?
No.
Why are you complimenting others
to ruin your own prestige?
I'm not blaming you,
but why didn’t you go up
to Boss Wu just now?
I don't dare.
Why not?
You just have to
do some small talk.
Hua'er,
what's wrong?
I'm just worried for you.
Have you forgotten what I told you?
As long as
we build connections with Boss Wu,
not only will we get a foothold in the household,
but Mother and Eldest Brother
will also think highly of you.
Hua'er, it's okay.
There are more chances.
Master Wu,
these two are indeed
quite capable,
especially that young man surnamed Shen.
Although he is a farmer,
he doesn't look
like a commoner.
His actions are quite mature too.
He even made an appointment with me.
I believe
he's not a simple man.
Got it. I'll check it now.
As for the details,
I'm not clear either.
Stop asking around.
Anyway, the store's business
suddenly turned bad.
Come here.
I'm telling you,
the fresh vegetables from Young Master Long’s sister-in-law
are incredibly popular.
Really?
Her business is so much better
than the business at Young Master Long’s restaurant.
I heard that our restaurant...
Hua'er,
you should at least calm your temper.
Otherwise,
they'll tell your mother-in-law
about your flaws again.
All right, don't be angry.
It's not worth it to hurt your health
over this.
Mother, why exactly are you here?
Look at you.
Can't I visit you?
Alright.
I have an idea for you
to vent your anger.
What is it?
[One Fresh Move]
Delicious.
Here come the pork knuckles.
Come on.
Hey, you took it all.
Well,
let me say something.
Man'er wants to say something.
Okay.
Thank you all
for rushing to harvest the hot spring vegetables,
allowing our small shop
to attract so many customers.
I promised you all
to have dinner together after the matter's done,
but I only had time recently.
Although
this is a small shop
and it's nowhere close
to the scale of other restaurants,
I believe
we
will grow better and better.
Yes!
Come on, cheers.
Cheers.
Come on.
Great.
Thank you, everyone.
Come on.
Come on, let's eat.
Man'er,
why are you being so formal?
We're from the same village.
It's our duty
to help you.
That's right.
Besides,
if your business is successful
and you open
a restaurant or an inn later,
the idle people in our village
can go to you for work.
Yes.
Yes, my father is right.
My father is right.
I told you
Man'er's restaurant will definitely succeed.
That's right.
Look at
the doorway.
It's all trodden down.
That's right.
Our shop
is in the corner
of an alley
and the business is still great.
If we opened a shop facing the street,
then our business
would be 100 times better
than Hua'er's.
Yes, that's right.
Yes.
Man'er,
where are your parents?
Why didn't you call them here?
My mother said
that my granny always eats
pickled vegetables in winter,
so she went with my father
to bring her a lot of hot spring vegetables.
It'll take a few days before they're back.
How filial.
Master,
the yard is full of vegetables
that we'll use tomorrow.
Let's hurry to inventory it.
Okay.
There are still many dishes that haven't been served.
Take your time eating.
Okay.
Go on with your work.
Man'er.
For me?
So beautiful.
It looks too expensive.
I can't accept it.
Take it.
Look.
Only a white jade container
can match this color.
I made it specially for you.
You'll definitely look good with it.
Thank you
for letting me sell rouge here.
You even gave me so much money.
I never gave you
a decent gift.
I should thank you instead.
Most of the female customers
are here for your rouge.
It's you who helped me.
No.
Thank you.
Do you like it?
Look.
What are you doing here?
Nothing.
What is this?
This is Man'er's.
This is so beautiful.
Ye'er,
make one for me too.
She's very skilled.
You take advantage of everything possible.
Hey.
You...
I didn't mean that.
Ye'er!
[One Fresh Move Diner]
You've been squatting there all morning.
You're still not done?
Mother, I...
My stomach hurts so much.
I can't stand up, Mother.
Who told you to eat alone?
You deserve it.
What happened to me?
Grandma, who's inside?
I want to go to the toilet.
Your mother.
She's been squatting there all morning.
Why are you all vomiting and have diarrhea?
Open the door, Lian Man'er!
Lian Man'er, come out!
Come out!
Lian Man'er!
Lian Man'er.
She's out.
Everyone,
what’s wrong?
You're asking us what's wrong?
What did you give us
to eat at the restaurant last night?
Yes.
What did we eat?
Nothing.
Dongpo pork knuckles,
stewed fish,
stir-fried bamboo shoots,
cooked greens...
Man'er.
You still have time
to recite your menu?
My diarrhea is so bad
that I'm almost leaking.
Everyone has diarrhea?
Yes.
After coming back last night,
I immediately started experiencing diarrhea.
I really couldn't stand it anymore,
so I came here this morning.
That's right.
Impossible.
I ate the food too.
Look,
I'm totally fine.
Do you think
we're lying to you?
There must be something wrong with your food.
Either
you treat us,
or
I'll report to the government immediately.
Report to the government immediately!
Don't get off topic.
Why are you talking about that?
What happened?
They said they have diarrhea and vomiting
after eating our food.
We got poisoned.
Quickly resolve this.
Calm down, everyone.
We will
definitely get to the bottom of this matter.
If it's truly
a problem with our food,
we will take full responsibility.
Look.
We can't waste any time.
Hurry up.
Listen to me.
Miss Man'er
was kind to treat you all to a meal.
Man'er,
go find Wang Youheng.
-Don’t worry.
-Man'er, don’t go.
We will give you everyone an answer.
Youheng, come with me.
Man'er, where are we going?
Many people in the village are sick.
Come and have a look.
Man'er.
I...
I won't go.
Go to the town
and find a real doctor.
Are you still concerned about that matter?
Youheng,
if there were
another dying person lying in front of you
right now,
would you save them?
If you say no,
I'll leave immediately
and find another doctor.
But if you
have any hesitation,
that means you haven't given up.
Where are they?
Come on.
Ye'er, does it still hurt?
I feel much better.
I'm fine.
I'll put you down.
I really...
Don’t worry. Take a seat.
Shen Nuo!
Come here.
Youheng, here.
Check your Aunt He first.
Okay.
Come, Aunt He.
Let me check your pulse.
Hurry up and take a look.
Why are you two
able to get treated first?
Go away.
This is our child.
Youheng.
One by one.
Everyone will be treated.
Look at you.
Okay.
I'm in a lot of pain too.
How is it?
I'll do acupuncture first.
I can't stand the constant
bathroom trips.
Give me acupuncture first.
It's urgent for me too.
Don't panic.
Calm down.
Hurry up.
It's urgent for me too.
One by one.
Okay.
We'll treat everyone.
Don't worry.
Don't panic.
One by one.
Hurry up.
Okay.
What's going on?
Father.
They...
Don't panic.
Serious cases will get acupuncture.
Light cases can take the medicine
and the diarrhea can be stopped immediately.
Man'er,
find a way to get some fresh garlic.
Burn the garlic and peel the skin off to eat.
This can relieve diarrhea and stomachaches.
Hurry.
Okay.
Does garlic work?
Yeah, does it work?
Hurry up.
What are you waiting for? Hurry!
No hurry.
What are you waiting for?
Take off your shoes first.
Here.
No.
Don't kill me from the acupuncture.
Don't.
No, no, no.
Treat us.
I believe in Mr. Jin.
Give it to the others.
How is it?
How are you?
Doctor, put it in.
Why aren't you moving?
Okay.
Don't panic.
It's okay.
Everyone will be treated.
Okay, can you walk?
Yes, I can.
Okay, thank you, Doctor.
Be careful.
Father.
Why are you...
I started studying medicine
when I was around 14 or 15,
but
I gave up in the end.
Son,
do you know
what doctors fear the most?
Maybe
it's to face death.
Death is the inevitable of life.
The scariest thing
is drowning in the pain of death
and losing one's vigor.
Back then, I gave up on being a doctor
because of that.
I didn't allow you to study medicine before.
I thought that practicing medicine
wasn't as good and easy
as collecting interest.
I didn't want you
to repeat my steps either,
but when I saw you
save people without hesitation,
I knew it.
You're better than me.
If you truly love this field,
don't give up.
You can't lose the chance
to heal the sick and dying
just because of one accident.
If one day,
you don't want to do this anymore,
I can still take care of you.
Mr. Laojin, Youheng,
thank you so much for today.
Without you two,
I wouldn't have known what to do.
But
I'm lucky today too.
I saw Mr. Laojin show off his skills,
and Youheng too.
Can you two determine
what the villagers ate
that caused this emergency?
I was in a hurry to save people earlier.
I forgot to tell you in detail.
When I checked their pulse,
I found their pulse was erratic.
The meal that Man'er invited
the villagers to eat yesterday
was all homemade dishes.
Logically,
it shouldn't cause
such serious consequences.
So,
there is only one possibility.
Someone poisoned
the food.
The symptoms of vomiting and diarrhea are obvious.
It's Rheum palmatum.
Rheum palmatum has weak toxicity and slow potency.
This is why the villagers
didn't immediately get poisoned
after eating Man'er's food.
It has a fresh fragrance
and is hard to notice.
Overdosing it leads to diarrhea.
Youheng,
go to the restaurant with Man'er
and see if you can find anything.
I'll go to these people
to make sure they are fine.
Okay.
I'll go with you.
Look.
I dug this out of
the swill bucket.
There are other vegetables in here.
Can you find anything from this?
They're inside.
I found it.
What?
It is indeed Rheum palmatum.
This herb causes major diarrhea.
After eating it, one may have a stomachaches, diarrhea,
and indigestion.
In serious cases, one's life could be in danger.
Whoever did it is cruel.
Let's go.
Constable, you're just in time—
Someone reported
that your restaurant's food
is not clean.
We were ordered to investigate.
You are not allowed to take away
anything from this shop.
[Jinyang County Magistrate Sealing Notice]
This is the document.
Listen to me.
We were framed.
Look.
The Rheum palmatum on the spoon
is the evidence.
This can't prove anything.
Constable,
please handle the case impartially
and clear our name.
The magistrate will see
whether you're innocent or not.
You may leave.
We're going to tape the seal now.
Seal it.
Yes.
Who reported this?
Who is the most jealous
that our restaurant is popular?
Take the money and leave.
[Sealed by Jinyang County Magistrate]
Stop looking.
The restaurant has been closed by the government.
It won't open.
I didn't know it's Master Lian.
Master Lian,
rumor has it
that your hot spring vegetables are poisonous.
Why are you here
instead of keeping a low profile?
Auntie,
my food is not poisonous.
It's not?
Then why did the government
seal your shop?
We were framed,
but we've already found
evidence of being framed.
However, the officials didn't believe it.
They didn't even give us
the chance to explain.
The heavens are watching.
I will definitely
find that person
and reopen this shop.
Man'er.
Hua'er.
Where are you going?
Home.
It's good to go home.
When you go home,
you can have peace and quiet.
You're not like me.
I have to work.
Look.
I'm so busy.
As your sister,
I have to warn you.
In business,
you can't have so many fancy tricks.
Some things
seem novel and gimmicky,
but they're also prone to problems.
Business should be done
like me.
Slow and steady
wins the race.
Yes, in business,
you must be slow and steady.
Hua'er,
I sincerely hope
that you're not the one who did this.
Do you really think
it was Lian Hua'er?
I'm not sure.
It was such a vicious act.
I hope it wasn't her.
As soon as it happened,
the government came with an official document
to seal the restaurant.
The speed is indeed suspicious.
The person who reported it
is most likely partners
with the poisoner.
Whether Lian Hua'er did it or not,
I will find out the truth.
Youheng said
that mistakenly eating Rheum palmatum
could kill you.
One mishap
and all those villagers...
I'm scared just thinking about it.
Don't worry.
It will pass.
Right now,
the restaurant is already closed.
Rumors about the food being poisoned
will spread soon.
With such a bad reputation,
we won't be able to
start a new store
quickly.
Then there's no hope
for you to enter the Jinyang Guild,
not to mention
approaching Wu Zhonglian.
This matter hasn't ended yet.
It may not be hopeless.
Why do you say that?
Do you remember
when Wu Zhonglian came to our restaurant
and agreed for me to bring him vegetables?
But the food in our restaurant
are all poisonous now.
Is this a good time?
Instead of being sitting duck,
we should take the initiative.
[Shufang Garden]
Shen.
Shen,
what is this for?
Sorry to bother you, Master Wu.
These are the vegetables that I agreed
to bring to you before.
I've delivered them now.
As far as I know,
something went wrong
with your hot spring vegetables
and you've been sealed by the government.
How dare you
still deliver them to me?
Truly nothing
can be hidden from Master Wu.
However, you are far-sighted.
You're no ordinary man.
Whether there's something wrong with the vegetables or not,
I believe you'll have
your own judgment.
Shen, you didn't come
just to deliver the food, right?
As I said,
I want to join the Jinyang Guild.
But your store
has already been sealed.
Master Wu,
I encountered difficulties today
because I don't have any support
in this place,
letting those who envy and hate me
act wantonly.
Master Wu,
I won't ask for your help,
but if I can solve this,
can I join the Jinyang Guild
and rely on you to make a living?
I will
accept the vegetables.
As for whether you can join the Jinyang Guild or not,
it depends on your ability this time.
Master Wu, thank you in advance.
Goodbye.
Man'er.
As soon as I came in, Ye'er told me
that your restaurant was closed.
What happened?
I'm so worried.
A few days ago,
I invited the villagers who helped us harvest the vegetables
to a meal.
I didn't expect
that everyone would get food poisoning.
The government also found out,
so we got sealed.
If we'd known,
we wouldn't have
sent vegetables to your grandma.
At least
I could've helped keep an eye out for you.
Man'er,
if the government
comes to arrest someone,
you can blame this on me.
I'll deal with it.
It's okay, Father.
At most,
they'll just close the restaurant.
It's obvious someone framed us.
Once the government solves the case,
our restaurant will reopen.
But...
It's okay.
How many times have I encountered
things like this?
Every time,
we find a solution.
It will be fine this time.
But...
Go and rest.
Man'er, listen.
We trust you,
but if anything happens,
you have to tell us promptly.
You can't bear it alone.
Okay, okay.
That's right.
Go back to your room.
You must tell us if anything happens.
-Okay.
-Yes.
We're back now.
Hurry and go sleep.
Where is Shen Nuo?
He went to keep an eye on someone.
Who? Lian Hua'er?
If it's as we expected
and Lian Hua'er is the culprit,
do you think she's dumb enough
to do it herself?
If you were her
and you ordered someone to do this,
what would you do next?
Of course,
I wouldn't keep him by my side anymore.
I would kick him out.
That's right.
Young Master
has already found out who left the Song family.
He's keeping an eye on that man
to see what he can discover.
Alright.
Although Shen Nuo is investigating,
the truth is still unknown.
We can't just sit and do nothing.
[Bounty Notice]
You want to use a bounty
to find the person who framed the restaurant?
Will this work?
What I want is the attention.
The more people know, the better.
Even if people only come for the money,
we must use these people
to spread the news of the bounty.
This way,
the person who did it
will feel that there's danger everywhere
and give themselves away in panic.
Then...
In that case,
there's something wrong with your writing.
What's wrong?
Look here.
[50 taels]
Fifty taels per piece of information.
It's so expensive.
Who would believe it?
You don't understand.
Look.
Even you're surprised
by this bounty amount.
If you post this,
others would be extremely excited.
It'll help us more
to achieve our goal.
Right?
That makes sense.
How about
we change the 50 taels
into 100 taels?
That's even better.
This is quite novel.
There's actually someone
who wants to buy information these days.
More importantly,
they have such a high bounty.
Is this real or not?
The notice is posted all over the city.
I don't think it's a joke.
Probably not.
I only heard about
the poisonous food matter,
but I don't know who the perpetrator is.
What a pity.
You don’t know, but I know.
-I’m going to get the bounty now.
-You know?
Me too.
Wait for me!
Does that mean I can get the money too?
One hundred taels.
Go, go.
Boss Zhang often faces One Fresh Move
and grits his teeth,
complaining about you stealing his business.
The noodle restaurant next door
says your malatang isn't as good as their noodles.
A few days ago,
I saw a burly man
standing on the wall of One Fresh Move.
Thank you.
Okay, remember to
let me know.
Next.
Kid, you don't have time for the bounty.
Do you know
who framed our restaurant?
Of course.
I really saw it.
Great. Hurry.
Tell us now.
I saw someone
poisoned your food.
When? Where?
It was that day.
The day before
news spread that your food caused diarrhea,
I saw someone
in the back alley of your kitchen.
He had a medicine bag
about this big.
That big?
And then he went in
the back door of your kitchen.
That's when he put in the poison.
What kind of person was he?
What was his physique?
What did he look like?
A man.
His height was about...
About this tall.
And
he had a pretty big face.
That's pretty big.
He had a beard too.
It was too dark.
I didn't see it clearly,
but I swear
I really saw that person.
He obviously didn't look like a good person.
Well said.
We must
record this.
I'll write it down.
Can I get the bounty now?
Not yet,
but when we catch him,
we'll delivery the money to you immediately.
Let's make it clear.
As long as
the person you catch
looks similar to the description,
all the credit is mine.
Okay.
What's your name?
Where do you live?
Dong Si'er, the back alley.
Sure thing.
Man'er,
haven't you realized
that all these people are lying?
They don't know
who framed our restaurant at all.
They just want the bounty.
I know.
Then why are we still wasting time?
Look back there.
There are so many people in line.
Maybe in your eyes,
they're taking advantage of me,
but in other people's eyes...
Did you hear about the bounty?
Of course I know.
When I came here,
I saw many people giving reports for the bounty.
The line is so long.
She offered so much for the bounty.
Even if her restaurant
had great business previously,
could she really make that much money?
She's risking everything
to catch
the mastermind.
Does this mean
she really was framed?
I think it's probably true.
If her food
really was poisonous,
how could she have the confidence
to offer so much money
for the bounty?
Lady, what's wrong?
Wang, right?
Didn't we let him go?
Why are you asking about him?
Keep your voice down.
He is so greedy.
If he sees
Lian Man'er's bounty,
what if he
betrays me?
If he has already left,
he won't be able to see the bounty notice.
No.
You have to take me to his house.
I have to see with my own eyes
that he's already left Jinyang County
before I can be at ease.
Okay.
Okay, go work now.
[Long stay]
Someone suspects
that the steamed buns seller at the entrance
often steals firewood from the restaurant.
No wonder
the firewood in our store
gets used up so quickly.
It turns out someone has been taking it.
Look.
Zhang Lao'er reported Li Laosan
for poisoning our store.
There's another one.
Li Laosan reported Zhang Lao'er
for secretly poisoning our store.
What's with this?
Who's the one that did the poisoning?
-Blaming each other.
The response to the bounty
is quite big.
It's quite big,
but it's not very useful.
It's definitely useful.
The notice was a great help.
You found something?
That's right.
I've been watching Wang,
a servant of the Song Mansion these days.
Steamed buns. Hot steamed buns.
I'll take two.
Okay.
Here.
Put it on the tab.
What's wrong, Wang?
You lost all your money again?
Hot steamed buns! Hot buns!
Fresh steamed hot buns!
Wang is a gambler.
He did this
to get money to pay off his debts.
Are you bringing me money
because you know
that I lost all my money?
After your bounty notice was released,
I followed Wang today
and had a new discovery.
However,
Lian Man'er's bounty
is more than this.
You're too greedy.
We already gave you
a sum of money
to leave Jinyang County.
It's fine if you don't leave,
but we're giving you another sum now
and you still think it's not enough?
If you're going to be so petty,
let's talk to the government together.
You're the one who put in the poison.
If you report it,
what's in it for you?
Cut the crap.
Lady, give me a better amount.
If you don't,
I'll expose everything.
The government will give me prison meals every day.
I won't need to worry anymore,
but I'm afraid you won't like the food.
So, it really is Hua'er.
She's too much.
Let's send Wang to the court.
A scoundrel like him
won't tell the truth
even in front of the government.
What should we do?
We know who it is.
Is there nothing we can do?
Don't worry.
I thought of a solution.
What time is it?
It's 9 o'clock.
Nine o'clock.
It's time.
Why is Wang so slow
even when getting money?
What if he really went
to get Lian Man'er's reward?
Lady, don't worry.
I don't think he dares
to admit it.
Brother.
I mean, sir,
aren't you beating the wrong person?
Wrong person?
You're the one I want to beat up.
You're the one
I'm beating.
Sir, sir.
Sir, let's talk.
No need to fight.
You want money, right? I have money.
I'll pay.
I'm going to get
a sum of money soon.
I'll give it to you after I get it.
How dare you take money from the Song family.
The Song family's money.
You dare take
the Song family's money?
The Song family?
Sir,
please spare my life.
I promise I won't stay here anymore.
I promise to get lost.
I won't harass the Lady anymore.
It's not up to me.
Go tell them yourself.
Get up. Let's go.
Young Master Song,
I brought the man to you.
Wang?
Young Master, please spare my life.
I shouldn't have been greedy
and extorted the Lady.
Wang,
what do you mean?
Why did you extort her?
Well...
Tell the truth.
The Lady...
[Mission: 1,000 taels of gold]
[Income: restaurant income, 1757 taels]
[Expenses: restaurant expenses, 99 taels]