[English subtitles are available]
[Romance on the Farm]
[Episode 14]
The newlyweds serve the tea.
[Song Hailong, the fourth son of the Song family]
Father-in-law, please have my tea.
Okay. Good.
Hailong.
After you get married,
make sure to unite as one
and depend on each other.
The most important virtue of a man is filial piety.
Be filial to your elders and respectful to your siblings.
May you two have children soon,
and please be a good example for them.
Yes, Father-in-law.
I'll bear it in mind.
Mother-in-law, please have tea.
Hailong.
I'll entrust Hua'er to you.
Make sure you treat her well,
and love and respect her.
Got it, Mother-in-law.
Hua'er.
After marrying into his family, revere and respect the elders.
Make sure you two
share weal and woe
and grow old together.
I understand, Mother.
Hua'er.
The auspicious time has arrived. It's time for the bride to depart.
Hua'er, although you're married now,
don't forget about me.
You're marrying into the Song family.
That's a wealthy and influential family.
I'll see who dares to cross me in the future.
The wealthy families' bridal procession
is indeed different.
Look how extravagant this is.
Who else in our village can compete with them?
Of course.
The one who's getting married is the fourth son of the Song family.
Of course the Song family pays great attention to it.
Exactly.
Hua'er has married up into a wealthy family.
Mr. Lian can also live in comfort
from now on.
Step forward with your right foot first.
The left is superior.
So the groom must be the one to step forward with the left foot.
The bride must not break the rules.
What does that mean?
It's obvious that they're setting rules for the bride.
You know what?
Not long ago, Lian Hua'er
broke the jade pendant
in the Song family's betrothal gifts.
She borrowed a lot of money
from the private bank to make up for it.
Looks like
Madam Song
is still angry about that.
That's why she asked
the wedding attendant to give her a hard time.
In the future...
Stop it.
Hua'er will definitely have a hard time there.
Sedan up.
[Song's Residence]
Come on.
[Champion Red Brandy]
Greetings, masters.
I am
from the bride's maiden family.
To celebrate her wedding,
I brought
the specially brewed Brandy here
for glorification.
Brandy? Have you heard of it?
Can the bride's family also come here?
Exactly. This is...
My Lord, please try it.
Okay.
How is it?
It tastes sweet and fragrant.
Good stuff. Good stuff.
My Lord, you have a great taste.
This wine is made
according to our ancestral recipe.
After drinking this wine,
the soreness in your waist and the pain in your legs will be gone.
You'll be able to carry 80 catties of rice,
walk ten miles in the mountains,
and read all night
without dozing off.
So magical?
Let's all try it.
Come on.
This wine is magical.
Pour us some as well. Come on.
No problem. Please wait a moment.
Pour some for us
to try. Come on.
To be honest,
our wine
is made from the water of four seasons.
It includes raindrops on March 3rd,
thunderstorm drops on June 6th,
sweet dew on September 9th,
and snow water on December 2nd.
In order to collect the water of four seasons,
we went through
a lot of trouble.
If the wine is this good,
bring us some
to try as well.
Exactly.
Give us some.
Here.
Please enjoy.
Bring us some bottles too.
Coming.
[Iris and Orchids on River Banks]
Miss, how much is a jar?
5 taels.
5 taels?
So...
So cheap?
I'll order 10 jars.
10 jars?
Say no more.
I'll have 10 jars first.
Miss, I want 5 jars.
Give me 5 jars.
I'll have 10 more jars.
No problem.
Come on.
Miss, I'll have 5 more jars then.
Got it.
5 jars. 5 jars.
Don't worry.
There's enough for everyone.
If you buy 5 jars,
I'll give you garlic peanuts as a gift.
Buy 10 jars, get 1 jar for free.
Good.
Thanks a lot.
Miss, I want 5 jars.
I want 5 jars.
The price was set too low.
These people coming to the Song family's banquet
are all dignitaries.
Miss. Miss.
5 jars, right?
Yes.
Got it.
Today is so eye-opening.
The bride's family
actually came here.
How could the bride's family
come to the wedding banquet?
She's indeed from a poor family.
Peasant.
She's married into the Song family,
yet she still doesn't know her manners.
Not only that,
but they're also shameless.
Have you ever seen anyone
peddling their goods on a wedding banquet?
Not to mention
on her own sister's wedding day.
How could she just sell wine in public?
Stop it.
It's embarrassing even talking about it.
Master Wu.
Song Haikun wants to see you.
Please have a taste.
Since he lost the registration book,
I can see that
he's been stupefied.
Now, you've stopped assigning
dispatching work to him.
He couldn't sit still anymore.
So he came here to butter you up with this wine.
If Young Master Song could
treat his work with such great care,
he wouldn't have
lost the book.
Since Young Master Song is trying so hard
to make up for it,
let's give him a chance.
Master Liu.
Master Wu said the wine is pretty good.
Order 100 jars and get them delivered to the capital city.
This time,
be careful.
If anything goes wrong again...
Let Master Wu rest assured.
I got it.
I'm on it.
[Song]
Mother.
Please have some tea.
Lady Hua'er.
Do you admit your mistake?
I don't know what I did wrong.
Please enlighten me, Mother.
You lost the jade pendant we gave you
even before you married into our Song family.
You bought a fake jade pendant to replace it.
Not only did you marry into our family with debts,
but you also
try to be clever
and lie to Her Ladyship now.
You don't know what you did wrong?
I know what I did wrong.
About the jade pendant,
I shouldn't have lied to you, Mother.
But when I lost the jade pendant,
I was so anxious.
My husband has always been nice to me.
I really don't want to
cause him trouble.
That's why I got confused
and bought a fake jade pendant.
Sit down and talk.
I'm glad that
your husband treats you well.
As a husband,
it's his duty to treat you well.
But
you've been plotting
against your husband, haven't you?
Mother.
Why do you say so?
I have never
been disloyal to my husband, Mother.
Even if I have all the guts in the world,
I wouldn't dare to plot against him.
Then, do you know
your husband is not my biological son?
No, I don't.
Didn't you marry into the Song family
in the hope of raising your social status?
Mother, I'm not...
Didn't your mother tell you
not to interrupt when the elders are talking?
But you plotted
too early.
Although Hailong is nominally my son,
in terms of wisdom and knowledge,
he inherited these from
his inferior mother.
He's mediocre and feckless.
And he never fights to be the best
among his brothers.
So,
even when he wanted
to marry a girl from the countryside,
I didn't say no.
From now on,
as long as you live in peace and don't cause trouble,
I will make sure you live comfortably.
I got it, Mother.
Her Ladyship is kind and nice,
but I'm not.
Lady Hua'er.
Think about it.
What else are you hiding from Her Ladyship?
I don't know.
Please enlighten me, Mother.
Since you don't know,
from now on,
deduct half of Lady Hua'er's household's monthly salary,
and cut the charcoal by half.
Only leave 3 or 4 servants
for her.
I really don't know, Mother.
Please enlighten me, Mother.
Return the money
your maiden sister made
at the wedding banquet as is.
Dong Xiang.
Take your lady back to her room.
Yes.
Honey.
Remember to remind
Man'er that
the wine Eldest Brother ordered
needs to be delivered to the capital city
at Boss Wu's order.
So be careful
and make sure nothing goes wrong,
or Eldest Brother will blame me.
What's wrong, Hua'er?
Did Mother give you a hard time?
Honey.
Didn't you tell me
you are the most esteemed son
in the Song family?
Mother told you everything?
So why did you lie to me?
Today is my first day
marrying into the Song family,
and you put me through such humiliation.
Yes.
I did tell you that.
But I only said that
to make you like me.
Although no one in our family admits,
and they say good things about me
in public,
I... I know that
I'm not
valued in the family.
Mother isn't willing to get closer to me
due to my background.
Eldest brother doesn't allow me
to meddle in family business either.
He could tell I'm bored,
so he gave me some chores to do
to kill time.
Do you know
how much effort I made
to marry you?
Of course I know.
So you must trust me, Honey.
I didn't mean
to lie to you.
It's just...
It's just that it was really hard to tell you this.
Honey, are you really mad?
Honey.
Don't worry.
As long as we don't cause trouble
and live our own
peaceful life,
we can still live happily
in this mansion.
I'm not mad.
What I want has always been you,
not your identity.
By the way, Honey.
You just said
the wine Eldest Brother ordered from Man'er
was entrusted by Boss Wu?
Who is Boss Wu?
Man'er.
Youheng.
My father just withdrew this money
from the bank.
He said he'd lend it to you without interest.
Thanks a lot, Youheng.
But as the saying goes, "Even with your own brothers, keep clear accounts."
I can't break Mr. Laojin's rules.
I'll pay the interest as I should.
Typical you.
Always taking things so seriously.
Why are the garlic peanuts
tied to the wine jars?
Didn't you sell the recipe?
Although the recipe was sold,
the garlic peanuts
are much more famous
than the wine I just started to make.
It doesn't cost much
to gift peanuts to those who buy my wine.
And I can sell more wine
with the help of the reputation of garlic peanuts.
Youheng, you're here.
Uncle Lian.
How much did you borrow this time?
200 taels.
How about we start small?
Didn't you already borrow 60 taels
from another private bank?
Putting it together, that's quite a lot of money.
Besides,
Master Liu
and Master Qin
are famous for being difficult to deal with.
What if you can't pay them back?
What should we do?
Man'er.
You also borrowed money
from Master Liu?
I have to buy the ingredients.
There are not enough wild grapes on the hill.
Besides, I need more manpower.
But I feel uneasy
borrowing money to do business.
Father.
Song Haikun
ordered 100 jars from me
and asked me to deliver them to the capital city.
It must be for
the dignitaries.
If the dignitaries like it after drinking,
and order 1000 jars or even 2000 jars
from me later,
I'll be able to make
1,000 taels of gold.
Besides, as long as
I deliver the wine to the recipient
and get the contract signed,
Song Haikun will pay me right away.
Don't worry.
What Uncle Lian said
makes sense.
It's better to be careful.
I'll go deliver the wine with you.
No need.
Someone will come and get it
after I cross Pingfeng Mountain.
It'll take less than a day to make a round trip.
Man'er.
Father.
Don't you worry.
It'll be okay.
This place you picked
is really remote.
I wonder
what you want to buy, a house
or rare animals?
I'm not buying anything.
I want you to send a message for me.
I heard
you have contact with those mountain bandits.
Can you make a trip there for me?
Three days later,
a batch of goods will pass through Pingfeng Mountain.
[New location unlocked: Black Tiger Fortress]
Master.
How did it go?
Did you figure it out?
Yes.
The goods belong to the Song family.
But the fixer wouldn't tell me
where he got the news from.
Was there anyone following you?
Absolutely not.
They don't know
the location of our Black Tiger Fortress.
I only met with him in the posthouse
down the mountain.
It's the Song family again.
We're destined to cross paths with them.
Many of our men
were forced to become bandits by the Song family.
Now we get to rob them again.
Of course we can't miss it.
What do you think, Shen?
Do you want to go on another round with us?
Master.
Why are you...
My brother and I have lived here
for quite a long time, right?
And we've helped you a lot.
But you haven't given that thing back to us
as you promised.
Now you want us
to rob the Song family again?
Isn't this
a little inappropriate?
How about this?
After this last robbery,
Master,
give that thing back to us.
What do you think?
Of course I will.
What do you think, Shen?
Do you have
any opinion this time?
We used the trick of diversion last time.
This time,
how about we use
the trick of replacing the real thing with a fake?
[Song's Residence]
Breaking news.
Hurry up!
Eldest Young Master lost his temper in the front hall.
Hurry up and send people there in attendance.
Honey.
Is something wrong?
Why do I feel
everyone in the mansion is panicking?
It's about the wine Eldest Brother ordered
from Man'er.
What a coincidence.
The wine went missing on the way.
What do you mean the wine went missing?
According to the messenger,
the government set up a checkpoint and took the wine.
But Eldest Brother inquired about it just now.
No checkpoint was set up at all.
We don't know
who robbed the wine.
Will this matter
get Man'er involved?
Of course.
Now that the wine's gone,
Eldest Brother will definitely
not pay for the wine
and let Man'er bear the consequences herself.
I'll tell you more about it when I'm back.
Honey, take care.
Yes.
Laojin.
We didn't want to come out either.
Yes.
Boss has been urging us.
He can't pay the bill.
Laojin.
Man'er, you're back.
Mr. Laojin.
Why are you here?
I happened to
run into these two masters.
They were looking for you.
So I
chatted with them for a while.
Miss Man'er.
We're here to collect money today.
You should pay our money back today as agreed.
Yes.
Masters. I...
I may need you to wait longer.
Wait longer?
If I can't get the money,
how should I explain to Boss
when I go back?
Exactly.
Don't worry.
I will get the money and pay you back
as soon as possible.
Just...
Just give me a few more days, okay?
How many days has it been?
Look at you.
Don't make it hard
for a little girl.
She must have a reason for not being able to pay it back.
She's not trying to bilk.
Besides, it's just a few dozens of taels of silver.
Do you have to collect it now?
We have bills to pay too.
Listen.
I watched Miss Man'er grow up.
I know what kind of person she is.
Don't worry.
She will definitely pay you back in full.
But, Laojin,
Boss has been rushing me.
Well...
How about this?
After half a month,
if Man'er can't save up enough money,
I'll pay you back for her, okay?
Laojin, you said that.
Don't go back on your word.
When did I ever do that?
Mr. Laojin.
I already owe you hundreds of taels.
No hurry.
It's normal to need turnaround time
for business.
Alright.
It's getting late.
You can leave now.
But...
Come to my place for a drink some other time.
Come on. Alright.
I have
Miss Man'er's Champion Red Brandy
stored at my place.
Come and have a drink some day.
Okay, let's go.
What should we say when we go back?
It's a deal.
You...
Didn't you go deliver the wine today?
The Song family didn't pay you?
Some government officials took the wine.
Some government officials took it?
What happened?
Tell me about it.
Come to think of it, it's quite strange.
I was on my way delivering the wine.
As soon as I left town,
I got stopped by some officers who set up a checkpoint
along the way.
What did they say?
They said the government was inspecting smuggling.
But I got the approval document
for my wine from the government long ago.
I didn't get to explain yet,
and those people took my wine
brutally
without a word.
Smuggling?
When I was drinking with
some government officials the other day,
they didn't mention this.
I'll take you to the government office tomorrow to inquire.
Maybe we can get the wine back
with a few taels.
I already went to the government office.
I didn't get anything out of them.
The government officials only
told me they didn't know.
Those scums.
Don't you think
it was odd?
Did they show you
any document for their seizure?
No.
But Mr. Laojin,
who could they be
if not government officials?
Let me ask around.
Don't worry.
I won't be able
to get this batch of goods back any time soon.
Now I can only make another batch
to pay off my debts.
Okay.
Ask Youheng for help
if you need anything.
Go back and rest early.
Your parents must be waiting.
Thank you, Mr. Laojin.
All right, I'm leaving.
Take care.
Okay.
I'm leaving.
Being an official feels so good.
Check it out. I feel much more authoritative
in this outfit.
Nonsense.
Of course it feels good, Three.
Don't you know the government officials
only do conscienceless things?
How can you be proud wearing this?
Four, you...
You're right.
Just let me have some fun.
I'll take it off later.
All right.
Stop messing around.
Open the boxes.
Be careful.
Why isn't it gold and silver jewelry?
Why is it all wine?
We're not short of wine here at Black Tiger Fortress.
Where did you get that
useless news from?
How would I know?
This...
Well.
It's still good.
Three. Four.
Although
this batch of goods isn't worth much,
we still managed
to make the Song family angry.
So our trip is still worth it.
Thirteen, you...
You're right.
See? He's right.
That's more like it.
That makes sense.
Young Master.
Four. You were a bit tough today.
She's just a little girl.
So what?
She had to work for the Song family.
Come to think of it, though,
why would the distinguished Song family
ask a weak little girl
to deliver the goods
for them?
How would we know?
What does that girl look like?
She's very pretty.
Really?
What are you talking about? Pretty?
You and Shen didn't go,
so you missed the dramatic part.
When we were robbing the goods,
she started to curse, and it was so irritating.
If it weren't for my tenderness towards women,
I would have brought her back here.
♫Wind blows through the rice field♫
♫The smoke is blown away♫
♫A bird stands on a branch alone♫
♫Gazing at♫
♫The skyline♫
♫Reverse♫
♫Back to the start♫
♫On second thought♫
♫We meet on the clouds♫
♫Burn incense to redeem my wish♫
♫A wisp of smoke♫
♫With regrets left♫
♫Always on my mind♫
You're here, Shen.
What do you want to see me for?
I have a request.
Just kidding.
I know this is what you want.
Not only that.
I want
the wine we robbed yesterday.
Shen.
Although that wine is not worth much,
it's still the result
of our men's hard work.
If I let you take everything you want away
from the Black Tiger Fortress,
how should I explain to my men?
How can I establish my prestige in the fortress?
Master.
Actually, this batch of wine doesn't belong to the Song family.
It belongs to a friend of mine.
I didn't know about it before we did the robbery.
But this batch of wine
means a lot to me.
You have to give it to me
no matter what.
I have to take it away.
Shen Nuo.
Even if you take the registration book away,
with so many of my men outside,
do you think
you can take it
out of the fortress?
Today, you can only choose one of them,
the registration book or the wine.
Which one do you choose?
It seems you choose the wine.
Master.
Please keep your promise.
Shen Nuo.
Do you have a grudge against the Song family
or Jinyang Guild?
Jinyang Guild?
I've read the registration book.
It records
all the bosses of the merchant guilds
in Jinyang Guild.
They're all famous people
in the county.
I'm flattered, Master.
I'm just a commoner.
How could I possibly have grudges
against the big names?
I just want to extort some money.
Right.
You went through so much trouble
to get here,
and you even fought with me.
I didn't expect
what you take away would be a few jars of wine.
Is it worth it?
Yes.
She is very important to me.
The delivery girl?
Till we meet again.
You've finally come down the mountain.
Young Master.
Yu Xiangjin gave you
both the registration book and the wine, right?
I exchanged the registration book for the wine.
I'll come and get the rest of the wine
in a few days.
But...
What about returning to the capital city?
Thirteen.
I know you like Miss Lian.
But now,
you're totally ignoring the big picture.
You know how important
the registration book is.
It records the salt smuggling transportation routes,
name lists,
and rendezvous
of local rich merchants.
What did we spend
so much time
in Jinyang County for?
Isn't it for getting the evidence as soon as possible
and returning to the capital city to report to the government?
I'm sorry.
Our efforts have come to naught.
What should we do now?
Just now, Yu Xiangjin told me that
the people recorded in this registration book
all come from a local guild called
Jinyang Guild?
That's right.
Although we didn't get the registration book,
there is another way.
I need to make a trip back to Shisanli Camp.
Maybe there's someone
who can help me.
Master told us
Shen is an affectionate lover.
Master offered him the registration book,
but he exchanged it for the wine.
He took all the wine away.
What's the use of that stupid book he left behind?
The winter is around the corner.
So many people need to be fed.
What should we do?
Three.
It seems the registration book can actually be of use.
What use?
We can blackmail
Young Master Song with it.
Master said
what's recorded in the registration book
is the delivery list.
Shen wants it,
and the Song family kept a close eye on it.
What does that mean?
That means the registration book is very important.
We can totally
get a large sum of money out of it.
Forget it.
Given the temper of
Master and Second Master,
they wouldn't agree.
Yes, of course they wouldn't.
Given Master's temper,
she would never
bend the knee and ask for money.
But the registration book
is useless to us.
It's better to exchange it for money.
When we put the hard cash we earn
in front of their eyes,
will they blame us?
You're right. Let's do it.
I'll ask the fixer
to spread the news right away
and tell Song Haikun.
I'll go check
if there are
any of our old costumes left.
We need to put on disguises.
We can't reveal our identity.
Also, we need more people.
Those guards of the Song family
are very tough.
Let's go.
Miss Man'er.
Master Qian.
Why are you here?
I came
to collect the money you owe me.
Didn't we agree that
you could give me a few more days?
It hasn't been long.
Besides,
Mr. Laojin vouched for me.
Please pardon me, Miss.
I don't want to go back on my word either.
It's just
my boss blamed me.
He said that
I lent too much money.
If I still can't collect it,
my position as the master
will be on the line.
Besides,
Wang Laojin is also a loan shark.
It doesn't make sense
collecting debts from a peer loan shark.
Today,
I must bring the money back to report to my boss.
After I sell the wine here,
I'll be able to pay you back.
If you don't have money, offset the debt with these.
Come on.
These grapes are worthless.
I need them to make wine.
Don't take them.
These grapes are really worthless.
They are worthless.
These grapes are worthless.
Master.
These grapes are really worthless.
Master Qian.
Youheng.
It's only right and proper that she pays off her debts.
Your father is Wang Laojin.
I don't want to have any beef with you.
Stay out of this.
I'll
pay this money back for her.
You could have asked him to pay the money back for you sooner.
Let's go.
Man'er.
In your memory,
what's something
that makes you happy?
Eating.
Making money.
And watching fireworks.
Once,
I saw so many fireworks.
So I made
a small wish.
I didn't expect
it came true the next day.
I wish I could see it again.
Forget it.
There wouldn't be any fireworks here.
[Mission: 1,000 taels of gold]
[Income: Selling wine, and money borrowed from Mr. Laojin and other private banks: 620 taels.]
[Expenses: The cost of wine production in high volume: 728 taels.]