[English subtitles are available]
[Romance on the Farm]
[Episode 10]
My chickens...
How dare you split?
How dare you build a wall?
I won't pay you.
How long will it take for you
to finish fixing the wall like this?
What else can I do?
If my parents wake up and see it,
they'll feel upset again.
Stop it.
I have a better idea.
What is it?
What are you laughing at?
I didn't expect
to be able to meet you here.
What do you mean?
At least I'll have
a place to stay now.
It's good to have these roses.
Okay.
This way, even if the wall collapses,
your parents won't be upset.
Finally, we're done splitting the house.
In the future,
I can make money without worries.
Go back to sleep.
I have something to do tomorrow.
♫You charge through the lands♫
♫I'll go get a perm♫
♫Shy and silent, like someone who's complaining♫
♫If you want to do it, let's keep drinking alcohol♫
♫Instead of learning female social codes and embroidery♫
♫It's better to get rich♫
Be careful.
♫The thick willow fights against the thin willow♫
♫Shallow people fear being born ugly the most♫
♫I can't open bottles and don't want to hurt my knees♫
Okay, stone. One.
♫I act weak and cute whenever necessary♫
♫Cry from losing against a dog but win against a man♫
Take the bait, fish!
♫I'm not afraid of the old lady♫
♫I'm born with money and I'll use it all♫
♫After using it, I'll have to work♫
♫I don't know any of the sophisticated arts♫
♫I eat, drink, ride horses, and chop firewood♫
♫I'm the bravest♫
♫We're both in the same boat♫
♫Others use bowls, but I use basins♫
♫The sun's up, but I don't want to get up♫
You got one!
♫I think I'm sick with narcolepsy♫
Liar.
I got one!
Let me help you!
It seems to be a big fish.
One, two, three!
I got one!
Hurry up.
Choose carefully, Seven.
♫I can't open bottles and don't want to hurt my knees♫
♫I act weak and cute whenever necessary♫
♫Cry from losing against a dog but win against a man♫
♫I'm not afraid of the old lady♫
♫I'm born with money and I'll use it all♫
♫After using it, I'll have to work♫
♫I don't know any of the sophisticated arts♫
♫I eat, drink, ride horses, and chop firewood♫
Here.
♫I'm the bravest♫
♫We're both in the same boat♫
♫Others use bowls, but I use basins♫
The fire is too strong.
♫The sun's up, but I don't want to get up♫
You should hold it further away.
We're here to eat fish!
♫Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-la-pa♫
You're roasting fish?
Come join us.
Smells good.
♫Don't ask where swallows come from♫
Why did you
decide to fishing today?
♫Take care of your boring life♫
♫It's more important♫
Careful.
Thanks for your hard work.
Miss Lian.
This is the money
for 50 catties of garlic peanuts.
Take it.
Thank you, Mr. Zhang.
Miss Lian, Mr. Shen,
have you thought about
selling the recipe for
the garlic peanuts?
There are more and more people
who like these peanuts.
We've sold peanuts
to many restaurants and stalls.
I want to make more money with this.
If others can figure out
a recipe for even tastier peanuts,
then your recipe
won't be special anymore.
Why don't you
sell this recipe to me now?
You can make money and buy more land
so that you won't have to work so hard all day.
Mr. Zhang,
if our recipe
is so easy to figure out,
you wouldn't be here
persuading us to sell it.
We're from the countryside. We're not afraid of hard work.
With this recipe,
we can make more money every year.
It's a long-term business.
It's a good thing
for both of us.
Don't you think so?
Fine.
In the future,
if you change your mind,
come to me first.
Sure.
What time is it now?
You haven't started cooking.
Do you want to starve the whole family to death?
Take a look at the village.
See if any other daughter-in-law is as lazy as you.
Back then,
when I was a daughter-in-law...
Your mother is reminiscing about the past again.
Where is the eldest daughter-in-law?
Come out and work!
Are you waiting for me
to invite you out?
Coming, Mother.
Coming.
Honey,
when are we
going back to town?
When we first came here,
we agreed
to only stay here for a few days.
We were supposed to return after the harvest.
But now,
we're still staying here.
Winter is coming.
Your youngest brother
and his family split away from us.
Shouyi's wife is pregnant.
Your mother is still furious
about the family splitting.
I'm the only one she can order around.
She scrutinizes me all day.
How can I bear this torture?
Let go.
Do you remember
what you promised
my family
when you proposed to me?
You said you were going to become an official soon
and I would be the official's wife.
In the future,
I would enjoy endless glory
and wealth.
You even swore that
you would never
never let me suffer
or feel wronged in the future.
But look.
Look here.
Here. And here.
Mother, have some tea.
Mother.
I have something
to tell you.
The festival is over.
The harvest is done too.
Tomorrow,
I'm going back to town.
First, I want to calm down and study.
Second,
I want to find a school
and get a tutoring job.
Okay, go back now.
Don't delay your work.
Yes, Mother.
I'll go back and pack my things.
Come back. Only Shouren needs to go.
You'll stay here.
Shouyi's wife is pregnant.
If you don't stay here and work,
do you want me
to serve the whole family instead?
Mother.
She has to go.
If she doesn't go back with me,
who will do the laundry and cook for me?
Who will clean my house?
Besides,
don't you always
want a grandson?
If you keep her here,
how will you
get your grandson?
I've made up my mind.
I know what she's capable of.
Laundry and cooking?
Do you think I'm a fool?
She didn't learn anything good in town,
only those dirty tricks.
Not only did she lead Hua'er astray,
she even implicated Xiu'er.
Stay with me
and learn
how to manage the family.
You can go back
when you have learned it.
As for Hua'er, I don't care if she
leaves or stays.
Mother.
If you have no time to tend to your house,
when you return to town,
just hire a maid.
I'll give you five taels later.
Why are you just standing here
like a block of wood?
Go and feed the pigs,
sweep the yards,
and wash the vegetables in the backyard.
Go.
Mother.
Are you really not going to see Father off?
Why should I?
He has no conscience.
He left me
just like that.
What?
Am I supposed to put on a smile,
chase after him, and beg him
to let me serve him?
He.
Look, I'm clumsy and busy.
You are always so efficient
when you work.
Why don't you give me a hand?
Gu.
it's not that I don't want to help.
It's just that
I'm pregnant.
I can't stand the smell of oil and smoke.
I just came in to get some water.
Enjoy your water then.
Isn't this Hua'er?
Finally, you stopped hiding in your room
and came out to see people.
Are you feeling better?
Ignore her.
Mother.
I...
Shouren's wife.
Are you stupid
or just clumsy?
The food is burnt.
Look at you.
You're so troublesome.
I can't look away for a single moment.
You need to
learn from He.
She's more competent in her work.
Seriously.
Is the sun rising from the west today?
Didn't you say you couldn't stand oil and smoke?
Why are you still here?
I'm leaving.
Right away.
You're right.
The pot is burnt.
Grandma.
It's not winter yet.
Aunt He is wearing so many layers.
Isn't she hot?
She's just fat.
Mother.
Easy does it.
How much did we make this time?
According to the amount
confirmed with the restaurants,
we still have to make more.
We need to buy some peanuts.
We still have some money.
Let's buy some more.
Why don't you buy it from your grandpa?
If my grandma knows
we are selling garlic peanuts to make money,
she'll make trouble again.
We sold it so openly.
All the restaurants know that
Miss Lian is doing business.
But your grandparents don't know?
We just split from the family.
My grandma must be furious.
She has no time for us.
Stop!
Mother! Mother!
Mother, listen to me.
I didn't want my belly to be cold
so I wrapped a cloth around it.
Be careful of my baby.
Even if you're actually pregnant,
I'll still beat you up, you lazy woman!
Mother!
You're right.
I'll beat you.
Come on.
You lazy woman!
People over there.
Stop working. Go over there.
Don't waste time.
Got it.
Hurry up.
Come here.
Tell the people behind to hurry up.
Those below.
Come up.
Hurry up.
Why are the officials here?
Let's talk when everyone is here.
Come on.
The tax is
10 taels.
Ten taels?
That much?
Didn't we already pay the land
and head tax this year?
The higher-ups have issued a new order.
The treasury is empty now.
It demands the people
to pay another poll tax.
Besides,
your field was originally
under Scholar Lian's name,
so the taxation amount was reduced.
But now your field
is no longer under Scholar Lian's name.
Naturally,
the land tax cannot be reduced.
But we got a poor field.
How can we be taxed the same amount
as rich fields?
No matter the fields
or the yields,
you have to pay.
Magistrate.
His Majesty has always been considerate of the people.
Why would he issue such an order?
He cares about the people.
Who told you that?
Go and argue with them instead.
Enough.
I have to go to the next village.
Hurry and pay up.
Where do we get so much money?
We have no money. We just paid recently.
Father.
I spent all the money I have
to buy peanuts.
Sir,
can you give us a few days?
No delays.
If you can't pay,
your leader
has to go back to the government office with us.
Can you be reasonable?
Why are you arresting him?
This...
Be reasonable.
How can you arrest people?
But now,
we really can't fork out
10 taels.
How about this?
We have some dried fruits,
chickens, and ducks.
Can we pay with that instead?
We just split houses,
and this is all we have left.
Why is the tax so heavy?
Not every place is the same.
Ever since His Majesty took the throne,
he has always insisted on minimizing taxes.
I didn't expect that over here,
the local officials pretend to be obedient
and secretly come up with so many ways
to extort the people.
The taxation here is far higher
than the amount submitted to the imperial government.
Most of the silver
must have ended up
in the pockets of corrupt officials.
How do you know so much?
I heard about it when
I went to the capital in the past.
I thought there was someone above you.
The life of ordinary people here
is so miserable.
I want to go back.
Where will you go back to?
Another world.
A world on a star.
There,
there are no exorbitant taxes.
In fact, subsidies are distributed
when disasters and accidents happen.
It has advanced agricultural technology.
You can plant crops
without bending over the soil.
Are you having a fever?
I'm not.
I'm telling the truth.
I was...
Go and dry the peanuts.
People in the restaurants are waiting.
Right.
When the garlic peanuts
make it big
and make a lot of money,
this little money
wouldn't hurt anymore.
Are you that confident?
Are you not confident?
Are you not confident
in our garlic peanuts?
I guess I am.
The crops are rotten.
Did the officials go to your house?
Yes.
The taxation is
getting higher over the years.
Yes. They almost
took away the pot and utensils too.
My family too.
We've paid land tax for a whole season.
Now we have to pay again.
Don't you think it's too much?
Exactly.
Mother, have some peanuts.
I have bad teeth. It's hard to eat.
You can have it.
Mother, try it.
It's really good.
No need.
You can have it.
Mother, try it.
This is really different.
I bought it yesterday.
It's really good. Just try it.
No need. Save it for yourself.
Mother, I've peeled them for you.
Try it.
Try it, Mother.
It's really delicious.
No need.
You have it.
Try it.
I have good teeth. I'll eat.
These peanuts are so good.
If not for the additional taxes,
we could have bought two bags of these too.
You don't need to buy them.
What do you mean?
Isn't this made by
Man'er of your family?
They sell really well in restaurants.
We have to wait in line to buy them.
Yes.
Let me peel some more for you.
Oh no.
What's wrong now?
Look at you.
I forgot I have
family matters to attend to.
I have to go.
It's always your family.
You are so troublesome.
You always have things to do.
It tastes so good.
Eat up.
What's wrong?
Your tooth fell out?
I see how it is.
We don't have enough vegetables, so we're cooking stones now.
All our money went to paying taxes.
Don't eat if it's too little.
What are you doing?
Saving some for my wife so she doesn't starve.
She won't die if she starves a little.
What took you so long?
Let's eat.
Our food
is too shabby
compared to Shouxin's family.
He.
Did you have dinner with Shouxin?
His family had
stir-fried eggs with chives, eggplant with minced meat,
stewed ribs, and...
Pork ribs?
Shouyi, listen.
Although the ribs were stewed,
they tasted so good.
Smell it. It still smells like ribs.
What else?
And stewed chicken,
stir-fried pork with mushrooms,
and tofu.
Dishes cooked with meat and seasoning
taste so good.
I've never eaten
such delicious dishes
and drank such delicious soup before.
The dishes smelled and tasted so good.
You...
Mother, stop talking.
Sit down and eat.
I can't eat. I'm full.
Where did Shouxin's family
get the money to buy ribs?
Don't they need to pay taxes?
Their family is not short of money.
Man'er has been selling
garlic peanuts recently.
They sell very well.
She even gave me a pack.
Let me try.
When Shouxin wanted to
split from the family,
I was worried about them.
I was wondering how
they would make a living in the future.
I didn't expect
our girl Man'er
to be so capable.
They just split from us
and already
thought of a way to make money.
Shouxin and the others
looked so honest.
I didn't expect
them to be so capable
of earning money.
Mother,
you can rest assured now.
It's delicious.
Delicious.
Shouxin.
Mother.
Come out!
Why did you call me here?
What's wrong?
Are you so busy that you can only
come here if something is wrong?
Mother.
That's not what I meant.
You made a lot of money selling peanuts recently.
Every time I see you returning from the market,
you're holding
either a fish or a big piece of meat.
Man'er started a small business
and made some money.
The money she earned
is only enough to buy some food
to snack on.
What are you afraid of?
I won't borrow money from you
even if I have to beg for food.
Don't worry.
Don't say that.
You didn't ask me for anything.
But if you do,
I should be filial and give it to you.
Fine.
Give me
the recipe for the garlic peanuts.
Give it to me.
No, Mother.
I don't know
the recipe for the garlic peanuts.
Well done, San'er.
You've become smarter.
Now you know how to fool me.
No.
I really don't know.
Don't think I don't know that
the garlic peanuts
were invented before our families split up.
You want to earn money without telling me and your father?
I've never thought about that.
I should have strangled you to death
before you were born.
Then you wouldn't be treating me
like a thief right now.
I'm so disappointed.
Mother, I...
Sister, what should we do?
Don't worry.
Let me think about it.
Go get Grandpa.
Hurry up.
I already have
one leg in the coffin.
Mother.
I'm going to town
to have tea with my friends later.
You've been working hard lately.
Do you need me
to bring you anything?
It's okay. Go by yourself.
Sit. Why is your grandma kicking up a fuss again?
I told Grandma this morning that
my friends in town mentioned it before.
Uncle Shouxin's family started
selling garlic peanuts a long time ago.
It has been sold all over the town.
Actually, the recipe for garlic peanuts
was created before we split up.
Logically speaking,
this recipe
belongs to the entire Lian family.
If Grandma gets it,
we can do business too.
Life must be better than now.
You.
You don't care that your parents are
eating coarse grains and vegetables.
I care, I care.
You have no conscience.
Are you trying to kill us?
What are you doing?
Man'er. Get up.
Man'er.
Stop it.
Mother, get up.
Don't touch me.
Can we
live in peace for a few days?
Do you have to lure the villagers here
and laugh at us
so you would feel better?
No.
Go back to your room.
It's embarrassing.
Mother, let's go back in.
All right, you guys go back too.
No one will ask you for the recipe.
I've never been at peace.
Why are you crying?
I didn't do anything wrong.
Let's go, Father.
A dream by the West Lake.
I had everything in my dream.
There is everything.
A pretty girl fell from the sky.
You can play with her in the rain.
As expected of
the daughter of the magistrate.
This tea is
like lotus flowers blooming among snowflakes,
refreshing and refined.
You're about to get married.
The tea you made is so delicious.
Your in-laws must be so happy.
Really?
My engagement with Young Master Song
is happening soon too.
It seems that our wedding dates
will be close to each other.
What do you mean by ours?
Please enjoy.
These garlic peanuts
have been popular lately.
I ordered it in advance
so we could have it today.
I only managed to buy it a few times too.
But I heard that
the peanuts
were made by Hua'er's cousin.
Your cousin made these peanuts?
My cousin earned a lot of money
selling these garlic peanuts.
Even so,
I've been worried about it.
Why?
I'm just worried that
my cousin
shows her face too much
doing business outside.
How will she get married in the future?
It's really inappropriate.
I tried to persuade her several times,
but she didn't listen.
She's running the garlic peanuts
business in secret
without telling our family.
I'm afraid this will upset
the elders of the family,
so I dare not tell them either.
I'm out of ideas.
I wonder...
Sister.
Sister, do you have any idea?
It's easy.
Leave it to me.
Thank you, Sister.
I brought you
a small gift.
Please accept it.
This lame thing?
Even the maids at home are tired of it.
How dare she gift it to me?
Then why did you accept it
and promise to help her?
I have nothing to do anyway.
Why not find some fun?
Besides,
do you think Lian Hua'er has good intentions?
She just wants to use us
to deal with her cousin.
How do you know?
If she really cared about
her cousin's reputation,
she wouldn't tell us this.
I have a fun idea.
Are you Lian Man'er?
You didn't report your garlic peanuts business
to the government.
How dare you do business without a business document?
You sure are bold.
Pay the tax you missed out on.
100 taels.
100 taels?
Are you crazy?
You might as well rob us.
Magistrate,
do you have any
official documents?
Who do you think you are?
How dare you ask me for an official document?
Within three days,
send your money to the government office.
As far as I know,
we only need to report to the government
if we're doing business in a foreign land.
The business volume must exceed 30 taels
to qualify for tax payment.
This is just a small business.
Do we need to report it to the government?
Besides, according to our law,
whoever gets more than 50 taels of fine
will be given seven days.
I wonder how you
came up with the three-day limit?
Cut the crap.
If you can't deliver the money in three days,
you'll be imprisoned.
Imprisoned for how long?
Just take me away now.
We're short of hands at the salt mine.
You're not going to jail.
You'll be joining the major criminals
at the salt mines instead.
I don't want to waste time talking to you.
Remember,
pay the money in three days.
I'm just a vegetable seller.
Why do I need a business document?
The tax collectors
keep coming.
There's no end to it.
If the local government officials
get some power,
they will do whatever they want.
They don't give the people a way out.
Without the business document,
I can't do anything.
Where am I supposed to find
100 taels of silver?
Mr. Laojin is not here?
My father went to another town to collect debts.
I guess he'll be back
in 10 to 15 days.
I'm preparing some medicine
while my father is not around
to bring them to town tomorrow.
It's almost
flu season again.
Is something wrong?
I...
I just want to borrow some money
from Mr. Laojin for an emergency.
Borrow money?
Man'er.
What happened?
I didn't report my garlic peanuts business
to the government.
The government officer gave me a fine
of 100 tales.
How could this happen?
Man'er.
I have some money here.
It's not enough for 100 taels.
Take it for now.
Thank you, Youheng.
I'll pay you back when I have the money.
No hurry.
I'll think of a way to get more.
Youheng, do you think this matter is strange?
Although
we do need to report businesses to the government,
Man'er is running
a small business.
At most, it should be counted as
a common citizen selling excess food.
It's everywhere in town.
I've never heard of the government asking about it.
Then this much money is enough.
Here.
Count it.
Enjoy your meal.
I won't bother you.
Is it done?
How is it?
This is a business document.
But we have to pay the rest of the money.
He gave us 10 more days.
[Jinyang County Government Business Document]
Thank goodness.
Regardless,
we can earn money by selling peanuts again.
Let's go back now.
It's still early.
We can make another batch of peanuts.
Yes.
Let's go.
I asked the officer just now.
Just as I thought.
The government is not interested
in your small business at all.
You were fined 100 taels
because you offended someone.
Offended someone? Who?
He wouldn't tell us anything.
It must be that young lady.
You mean Lian Hua'er?
Uncle Shouren left.
Grandma orders
Aunt Gu around all day.
She can't even leave the house.
Who else in the family
might be related to the government?
What are you two talking about?
We were talking about how
we don't have peanuts at home.
We're thinking of buying more from the village.
Don't bother.
Your grandpa
just recently harvested some from the fields.
I'll talk to him.
We'll use the peanuts at home.
After we get through this,
I'll pay him back.
Grandma just recently made a scene.
How do you know
he won't make things difficult for us?
Your grandpa has given the order.
I don't think he will.
Besides, your grandpa always said
members of the Lian family should help each other.
Now that we're in trouble,
they will surely help us.
No way.
Don't even think about it.
When you make money, you split everything
with us clearly.
Now that something's wrong, we're suddenly a family again?
Now that something's wrong,
you suddenly need us,
so you're here to pretend to be close to us.
[Mission: 1,000 gold]
[Income: Selling garlic peanuts, Wang Youheng borrowed money: +185 taels]
[Expenses: raw peanuts, payment to government office: -280 taels]