Mast! Lay down the mast!
Hurry up and get the rope!
Bow and stern face the banks! Quick!
Thousands of homes are brightly lit,
and the doors to them are wide open.
This is East Capital.
New wine at Sunyang Restaurant!
Welcome to enjoy it!
​If you want to know what happens next,
wait until next time.
People from all over the world gather here,
and envoys travel to and fro.
[Riverside Code at Qingming Festival]
[Adapted from Ye Wenbiao's Novel Series of the Same Name]
[Episode 5]
[Morality is valued and honored only when a person possesses it. - Zhou Dunyi]
Sir.
Is he here to buy a horse?
Yeah.
He's from a foreign country, though.
According to the Song Dynasty law,
we are not allowed to sell a horse to a foreigner.
Someone's tailing you.
If you don't want to die, come with me.
Mo'er.
Do you want the horse or not?
Buyou, this way.
Quick, hurry.
Mo'er, go check if someone's behind us.
Did you see them?
No.
Those two men were coming for you.
Did you see that?
Yes.
Now
only he and I can save you,
you understand?
What do you do then?
We're from the Kaifeng Court.
We arrest bad people.
Are you from Thindu?
I'm from Samboja.
Geographically speaking, Samboja is right next to Thindu.
That's right.
Are you the Thinduese who made the Auspicious Sign?
Yes.
Hey, listen.
Don't move.
Just speak with your mouth.
Are you the Thinduese who made the Auspicious Sign?
Yes.
All right.
It's him!
Come on, take a seat.
Don't be anxious.
Just tell us
what really happened.
Take your time.
My grandpa is
(Thinduese name).
His name is
So it's a name, all right.
He had a brother.
His brother was
(Thinduese name).
It's a name, too.
I understand.
They had a few brothers.
But we didn't have enough food at that time.
Later,
a friend of him from Samboja...
I understand.
How about this.
Let's not start from your grandpa.
I want to know about you.
How did you arrive in East Capital?
Six mouths ago,
those two merchants
asked me to hide in the boat,
and brought
me to the Capital.
I know how to light fireworks.
When I got here,
I arranged shows everywhere.
Later,
someone arrested me.
Why did they arrest you for lighting fireworks?
They said I didn't have the documents.
I was smuggled here.
I see.
Where did they bring you?
The Office of Justice.
The Office of Justice?
Yes.
What's next?
Later,
an officer
brought me somewhere else,
a room in sheer darkness
inside a teahouse.
I couldn't see anything.
They forced me to make the Auspicious Sign.
Can you tell me
how did the person look like
who made you do this?
I couldn't see anything!
But there was something special to his hand.
Something special, how?
Where was it?
On his thumb.
His thumb was
carved with four characters.
What characters?
What were the characters?
It means
"A mind tranquil as still water."
"A mind tranquil as still water?"
Yes.
You said you were locked
in a room of sheer darkness.
You couldn't see anything.
How was it possible for you
to see the characters on his thumb ring?
I remember
when he first asked me to make the Auspicious Sign,
I refused to do it.
Then
he pointed his finger
at my forehead.
Zhao Buyou.
What's your job here at the Office of Justice?
Copying books.
Turns out you know that's your job.
Why bother solving cases then?
I understand.
At the Office of Justice.,
it's Di Lun.
Mo'er.
Keep an eye on him
and send him to Kaifeng Court in a while.
Brother, be careful.
Shout out loud when you see a bad guy.
Buyou.
Mo'er.
That man ran away.
He heard we were about to bring him to the Kaifeng Court
and said he was afraid of government officials.
I tried to stop him
but I failed.
Did you see him?
No.
What should we do now?
That Thinduese is an important witness.
We have to take our chance.
I can't wait anymore.
Wen Yue.
Buyou and Mo'er will be here soon.
Mo'er.
A white horse?
Where's Buyou?
He said
he couldn't bear leaving you.
So he's not coming back.
Oh right.
He also wrote a letter for you.
He bought that horse?
Right.
Buyou said you'd know when you saw it.
Why would Buyou buy a white horse for his wife?
Listen to me,
throughout the entire continent,
and compared to the Han and Tang dynasties,
not even a single city
is as big as East Capital.
East Capital is just huge in size
with numerous opportunities.
As long as you're a living person,
you won't starve to death in this place.
I guess
you know what I mean, right?
You...
I...
So this is where we part ways.
[To my beloved wife]
[Divorce Letter]
I wish you can live a life of happiness.
A life of happiness, huh?
That's very resolute.
This
doesn't look like what he will do.
What did you do with him
except buying the white horse?
Come over here.
Ban'er.
Where have you been?
And what did Buyou say to you?
He said, don't hesitate,
and leave the city right away.
There's nothing else?
Zhao Buyou.
We expected you to come
work at the Kaifeng Court.
But you didn't show up.
Why did you run off to this place?
Inspector Gu, Judge Wan, please sit.
I want to buy you some tea.
What's the matter?
Here's the thing.
I lost my job a few days ago.
I was afraid my wife would find out.
So I was anxious
to find a job at Kaifeng Court.
Let's just wait another day.
I'm not in a hurry now.
That's not up to you.
Continue.
I came here today...
Just tell us already.
Inspector Gu.
Back then when Bao Zheng resides at Kaifeng Court.
Wait a second.
Who's that again?
I said Bao Zheng.
Why did you bring that up?
When he was in charge,
Anyone could file a lawsuit in court.
All grievance must be avenged,
and all evil must be eliminated.
May I ask, Inspector Gu,
can we do that in today's Kaifeng Mansion?
Zhao Buyou, listen carefully.
Before we had Bao Zheng.
Now we have Inspector Gu.
In East Capital,
everything is put under our control.
We'll arrest every criminal.
My investigation shows
Li Yan's case fifteen years ago
and the Auspicious Sign today
are the works of the same person.
Do you dare to arrest him?
Who's him?
The prosecutor,
Di Lun at the Office of Justice.
Boss.
I knew something's off with this man.
He's been hanging around since the trial opened.
Do you have evidence?
I have.
I am the witness.
That doesn't count as evidence.
I can guarantee sure it's him.
Your guarantee doesn't mean anything.
You can't prove that man's guilty.
Zhao Buyou, I didn't know you were such a conspicuous man.
You seriously want the Kaifeng Court to go against the Office of Justice?
Is that correct?
A few days ago,
you were fired by Mr. Di.
So
you hold a grudge against him.
You plan to pin this on him.
Am I correct?
That's what happened.
And then he just took off.
Try to give it another thought
and see if you have missed something.
Have I missed something?
Oh, right.
He wrote another letter.
He mentioned
an abandoned place in the eastern suburbs.
I don't know what it is.
He seemed to arrange a meeting, but he wouldn't let me know.
The eastern suburbs.
Abandoned?
Wen Yue, where are you going?
Mr. Zhao's getting a divorce!
- Wen Yue, you can ride a horse? - What are you doing?
I knew how to do it when you were still kids.
Wen Yue, you are leaving?
Take care of my Father.
Yue!
You forget about this.
Sir,
our people saw
Zhao Buyou was hanging with the Thinduese.
Later, he thought of your name.
He already figured it out
that it was you who ordered the man to make the Auspicious Sign.
Rest assured, sir.
The Thinduese is right here.
Alright, take it away.
Clear the room for us.
Turns out I have
underestimated Zhao Buyou.
I didn't know he'd collude with the pirates?
You were smart and resourceful.
You used Rice Noodles with Shredded Chicken
to find out Xiao Yishui wasn't from Meishan.
I missed Rice Noodles with Shredded Chicken in my hometown.
Yeah, it was so tasty.
I just don't understand.
You already figured out the problem yesterday.
Why don't you capture them at once today?
The Auspicious Sign is very important.
We've been doing this secretly.
A bunch of hooligans wouldn't know
there are some treacherous officials behind this whole thing.
You want to know who's behind this?
Yes.
If we don't find out who's behind this,
what am I supposed to tell the higher-ups?
As for Xiao Yishui,
keep watch on him.
As for Zhao Buyou and his wife,
go get them.
Everything's set?
Yes, sir.
Tonight, you will be posed
as kidnappers,
and captured Zhao Buyou and his family.
But remember
to keep it low.
Sir.
Why don't we just kill them
under the cover of night?
I want them alive
for a reason.
Go get prepared.
Report!
Mr. Di.
You've got a letter.
The messenger said it was urgent.
Bring two bottles of flowing glow to the abandoned ship graveyard
in eastern suburbs at 7 p.m..
Zhao Buyou.
What's this man up to, really?
Two bottle of flowing glow.
Go prepare the wine.
Yes.
[Abandoned ship graveyard, Eastern suburbs]
Buyou.
Search the area.
You got here early.
See what you've done.
We've been working together for over a decade.
Yet you even sent me an invitation just to drink together.
That's too polite.
The problem is you invited me here,
yet I'm the one to bring the wine.
No wonder everyone said
you are the most frugal man in the Office of Justice.
Let's drink.
You seem odd today.
You used to be more obedient.
If you want to say anything, just spit it out.
You were right.
I always thought I'm the biggest loser
in the Office of Justice.
Listen.
For over a decade,
I drafted your closing files.
Your household chores,
like sweeping fallen leaves in your courtyard,
writing invitation letters,
and escorting your relatives
when they see the doctor,
I was in charge of them all.
I thought I was a huge loser,
until recently I found out some secrets of yours.
Then I found out
you were the biggest loser among us.
What secrets?
Tell me.
I saw you sucked up to the Chief Minister all the time.
It's understandable.
But his wife
is old enough to be your mother.
Why hooked up with her?
You're not doing this to pry into the secrets of
the Office of Justice, right?
Cheers.
Listen, man.
You like to treat the higher-ups to some meals,
and suck up to them.
It's fine.
But last time I was in Sunyang Restaurant.
When I looked inside your booth,
you were dancing there.
You even sang for them.
You were not trying to be an actor, right?
You're a prosecutor, after all.
Didn't you feel ashamed?
Cheers again.
Anything else?
I heard you also worked for someone
outside the Office of Justice.
They must have your salary deducted all the time.
Otherwise, why would you
try to deduct the salaries
of us subordinates.
It must be hard for you.
I bet you hasn't got much from this.
That's all?
That's all for now.
All right, Zhao Buyou.
You asked me here in the middle of the night.
If that's what you want to talk about,
I'm done with it.
Do you still remember
the ship in front of you?
Fifteen years ago,
Li Yan and his family, along with the crew,
were murdered by some pirates.
You were the one
to hire those pirates, right?
Fifteen years later,
you arranged the Auspicious Sign
over the Bian River to cause confusion among the people.
The problem is, why would a prosecutor like you
have the guts to do this?
Lately, I've gathered some evidence.
Clearly,
there's a really powerful man behind you.
He ordered you to do this,
right?
Now die!
So I was right.
Unsheathe your sword.
A scribe who got fired by his superior
attempts to spread rumors and smear his superior.
This is a felony.
Take him away.
Tie him up.
Don't move!
The Office of Treasury is colluding with the Office of Miscellaneous Purchases.
Am I correct?
I heard Mr. Di is about to be transferred there.
A fat job at the Office of Treasury.
The man behind you
has promised to help you
transfer to the Office of Treasury, right?
Keep dreaming.
That position was taken yesterday.
Really?
You don't believe me?
I have evidence with me.
It's in my pocket.
Let me take a look.
The man who took the job yesterday
has ordered some umbrellas
in my wife's shop.
We have his signature.
If you don't believe me,
go ask around.
Someone from the Office of Treasury came looking for you.
He said their newly appointed leader,
Mr. Wei is planning to
buy some umbrellas for the palace.
[The Office of Treasury has purchased 50 green umbrellas with 36 guan of gold.]
[Wen's Umbrella Shop will deliver the green umbrellas]
[to the Office of Treasury in 25 days.]
[The goods have been paid for.]
[Wei Santong, person in charge in the Office of Treasury]
Di Lun, now you know
who's the most pathetic man in the Office of Justice, right?
You do all the dirty work for him.
Yet he fooled you.
What's that sound?
Go check.
Why sneak around?
I dare you to show yourself!
Honey.
What a pleasant  surprise.
Get her.
Yue, watch out!
Mr. Di.
Let's go!
Zhao Buyou, run!
Zhao Buyou.
Come out now.
Let's go.
Lay down the shabby umbrella in your hand,
now!
It's all set.
Honey.
When you came here,
did you see the others?
What do you mean?
You're expecting someone?
I didn't see them.
We'll talk once we get out of here.
Burn it.
Burn it!
Di Lun.
Fifteen years ago,
I came to you with Li Yan's case file.
There was a problem with the closure.
Right now,
I'm a dying person.
Can you at least tell me the truth?
You want to know the truth?
Let me tell you this.
Even I don't know about the truth!
Because of the man you just talked about.
Because I was born into a poor family.
I took the imperial exam with his financial support.
That was why I had to sign
a 20-year contract with him.
I have to stay in this position.
I have to hide in the Office of Justice
and do all the dirty work for him!
You're damned right.
He did promise me.
If I managed to make that Auspicious Sign,
I could transfer to the Office of Treasury
and took that fat job.
Then I wouldn't have to hide anymore
and lived a life of great fortune.
But I was wrong.
Right.
Fifteen years ago, I didn't do it clean
with Li Yan's case
and let you stay alive.
I thought if I handed you over
I could make up for it.
Who would have thought
he had given up on me long ago.
Twenty years.
What did I get from twenty years of hard work?
Completely nothing
and a tarnished reputation.
Di Lun.
Did you change your handwriting
to engage in secret communication with him?
Yeah.
I practiced for three years.
The fire at the National Archives,
you did it, right?
You wanted to burn all the files
that concerned you, right?
I spent all night picking through the files.
Who do you work for?
What are their name?
Tell me their name.
I'd know who to get revenge on if I have to die.
Who are their name?
Di Lun.
Release my wife!
Watch them burn to ashes before you leave.
Yes.
If I knew we would end up like this,
I would've surrendered to them.
That was exhausted.
Honey, didn't I tell you to run?
Why did you come back?
Then you should've said something harsh.
It was my fault.
I'm always a burden.
It seems
we can't make it out alive.
Honey.
It occurred to me
not long after we met each other,
[Wen's Umbrella Shop]
you were running the umbrella shop.
I came to your shop one day.
You leaned on my back just like what you do now.
When you were making umbrellas,
every time I watched you put the tool behind you,
I'd secretly move my hands there.
I was waiting for you to put down the tool.
If I got lucky, I'd touch your hand.
I was thinking
it would be wonderful if I could hold her hands for the rest of our lives.
Now
over ten years have passed.
Honey.
If afterlife truly exists,
in our next life,
and the life after that,
let's be together again, all right?
Enough! That's not the time
for this.
Do you want to die here?
Promise me.
Let's be together again, all right.
All right.
Gu Zhen!
I'm dying because of you!
Who's that?
Inspector Gu?
Right!
Gu Zhen!
You're such a jerk!
Zhao Buyou!
Judge Wan.
Hurry up!
Judge Wan, what took you so long?
He didn't say
who's the man behind him.
Hurry!
Let's go!
Slowly.
Over here.
All right.
Just put it there.
Zhao Buyou.
What's the show you've put on?
This is not a show.
I was going all out.
It almost cost me my life.
Di Lun.
Buyou, my brother!
I'm glad you're fine.
What a relief.
We will talk about this later.
As long as you're okay.
What's this? You...
Hang on a second.
Inspector Gu.
Can we have a moment?
Let's talk right here.
All right.
We're all allies now.
Inspector Gu.
Do you even know who's behind me?
You said who's behind you?
Isn't it Wan Fu?
Yeah.
It's me.
Judge Wan, please don't joke about it.
I know
I've done many things wrong for all these years.
But I've decided
to tell you who's behind me
and all the dirty work I've done
for him for all these years,
every last bit of it,
including the case
concerning Li Yan fifteen years ago.
How about this?
You and I cooperate to take him down.
You agree?
So you were the one
who killed Li Yan?
That's correct.
Is this?
Member of the Jingyuan Triumphant Army,
Gu Zhen.
And the Commander of the same army
is Li Yan.
It's right here.
It's been fifteen years.
I've been looking for you for fifteen years.
Go to hell
and apologize to my brother.
Gu Zhen
of the Jingyuan Triumphant Army
has avenged the Commander
Li Yan!
Wen Yue.
How did you get away?
Li Yan's a good official.
I couldn't bring myself to do it.
Our employer told me
to kill them all,
every last one of them.
Kill them!
Kill him!
We'll talk about it later.
It's the Office of Justice.
They are here.
We're here for an investigation.
You've been surrounded.
Surrender now!
Later, those people from the Office of Justice arrived.
They told us to surrender
while shooting arrows at us.
In a moment of despair, I jumped into the water and went ashore.
That's how I got away.
When he died,
did he suffer?
It happened
in the blink of an eye.
Inspector Gu.
What do you plan to deal with us?
With laws?
Or morality?
I'll come see you one day.
Let's go.
You seemed tough
when you wrote the divorce letter.
"I wish you a life of happiness."
So I came to your rescue.
Happy now?
I swear to Heaven,
I sincerely hoped you could leave.
I wanted Gu Zhen
to arrest that scumbag.
Husband and wife are supposed to share weal and woe.
If I forsake you to live a peaceful life,
do you really think I can get over the guilt?
Let's go.
Go home.
Honey.
I've been thinking about it for a while,
but my legs feel like jelly.
You said,
as long as we're living people, we won't starve to death in East Capital.
Is it true?
Of course.
So you're not leaving?
I'm staying.
Please help me up.
Zhao Buyou, wake up.
Hang in there, we're home.
If you still feel dizzy and nauseous,
try to chew a slice of ginger.
Honey.
Am I too much of a wimp?
I'm a grown man in my late thirties.
Yet it almost scared me to death.
I can't even begin to imagine
how you pulled through
while you were still in your teens.
But rest assured.
Di Lun is dead.
No one can prove it now.
As for Inspector Gu,
he dared take such a great risk
just to avenge a fellow soldier.
I think he's a man of integrity.
He won't be coming for us.
I'm worried about your fellow disciple, though.
Yishui is
indeed a trouble.
Honey, how about you just go slice the ginger for me?
[Kaifeng Court]
Boss.
I can assure you
no one will ever find the man.
I never doubt your competence.
There's one thing I don't understand.
Well.
Why did you do that?
Don't you think he deserve to be dead?
That's not it.
He deserved it, that's for sure.
I mean
why did you do that
in front of Zhao Buyou and Wen Yue?
Don't you think you were a bit reckless?
Normally,
when you receive bribes,
will you do as they say?
I never take bribes.
That depends on how you define a bribe.
I take their money
and help them get their job done.
This is no bribe.
I work hard to get the money.
That's not what I mean.
So what do you mean?
After you help them get their job done,
why do they willingly give you the money?
That's
because I've done a great job.
After you get their job done,
you receive their money.
That's why they think
both of you
have got something on each other.
Then you will literally
become allies.
You mean to make them...
How do you think of
that couple?
[Fashion in Song Dynasty]
[Song Dynastypedia]
[Flowing Glow hard to get, Flying Fairy out of stock, Narrator: Hou Yansong]
How did the Song Dynasty people lose the freedom to brew liquor?
Aside from official liquor, the East Capital
adopted a wine-making system where businesses purchased
the distiller's yeast from the government and make their wine.
People were forbidden to make and sell liquor.
There were two types of liquor-selling stores, main stores the foot stores.
Main stores were magnificently decorated
with the rights to make and sell liquor.
Foot stores
could purchase liquor from official liquor warehouses
or buy it from main stores by wholesale.
Aside from the government's strict control on alcohol,
Flowing Glow is a hit product of Gaoyang Restaurant.
Two bottles of Flowing Glow
are equivalent to the expensive, rare,
and finely decorated Maotai in today's liquor market.
So when Buyou asks Di Lun to bring the wine
not because he's stingy,
but because he is
exceptionally stingy.
♪Rowing across the river with a load of fish♪
♪Paddling the oars while singing a song♪
♪Guests travel with lanterns under moonlight♪
♪In the corridor, joy fills the table♪
♪Come and enjoy the cool under the canopy♪
♪My new hometown brings peace to my heart♪
♪I love the city hustle and bustle, and the grass in mountains♪
♪Walking down roads, strolling along alleys♪
♪Look, the swallows glide with a beakful of spring mud♪
♪With hope, they gently take off and fly away♪
♪Guests come from far and wide♪
♪A bowl of wine, a mouthful of ambition♪
♪Eyebrows unfurl, for prosperity awaits ahead♪
♪Singing loud happily, you get to pick the broad road you want♪
♪Under the immense sky, dusts dance with the wind♪
♪Your root is where your original aspirations lie♪
♪A thousand households are brightly lit♪
♪Bursting into song, they set off for another journey♪
♪For youngsters, their ambition is burning bright♪
♪Just seize the opportunities and make adventures♪