Mast! Lay down the mast!
Hurry up and get the rope!
Bow and stern face the banks! Quick!
Thousands of homes are brightly lit,
and the doors to them are wide open.
This is East Capital.
New wine from Sunyang Restaurant!
Welcome to enjoy it!
If you want to know what happens next,
wait until next time.
People from all over the world gather here,
and envoys from various countries come to communicate with the authorities.
[Riverside Code at Qingming Festival]
[Adapted from Ye Wenbiao's Novel Series of the Same Name]
[Episode 19]
[A single thing, two manifestations, that's qi.]
[Unified, it holds mystery; divided, it defies prediction.]
[By Zhang Zai, Northern Song Dynasty]
According to what you said,
the three dead people at Fan Tower
were the judges
of the Dong family's massacre case back then.
Would it just be a coincidence?
I can't be completely certain yet.
Zhao Buyou,
there's something I want to discuss with you.
It's time to tell Mo and Ban
about their true origins.
We've kept it from them before,
but now they're grown up,
and Shan Shiliu is dead.
Besides, Mo has already
started suspecting his background.
If outsiders find out
he's investigating this,
it might put him in danger.
Why don't we
just tell Mo and Ban directly,
explain the stakes to them,
and have them strictly keep it a secret?
That would be much safer.
You have a point, dear,
but
it depends on how we say it.
Let's do it today.
Go to the Office of Justice
and tell Mo
to come home for a family reunion dinner tonight.
We'll talk during the meal.
Also, while you're at the Office of Justice,
verify
if the judges of Dong Qian's case
are indeed the three deceased at Fan Tower.
All right.
Are you coming back for dinner too?
How can it be called a family reunion dinner if I'm not there?
Did you buy the firecrackers I asked for?
Yes, I did.
Dear,
why do we need to light firecrackers
before entering this Wuyou Cave?
It's a rule of the jianghu.
[Dragon Boat Racing Murder Case]
[Senior Judge Dong Qian's Massacre Case]
We've identified the three bodies
on the table.
They're Zhao Muyan, Transportation Inspector of Kaifeng Court;
Yue Qide, Deputy Commissioner of Salt and Metal;
and Zhang Qi, Left Assistant of the Ministry of Revenue.
Why do these names sound so familiar?
[Zhao Muyan, Yue Qide, Zhang Qi]
Zhao Muyan,
Yue Qide,
Zhang Qi...
So it's them after all.
Mr. Dong!
People like us
are born to stay here.
As for the upper world of East Capital,
you
shouldn't even think about it.
[Dagger]
It's mine!
You little rascal!
Come and eat, all of you!
Dear,
why do we need to light firecrackers
before entering this Wuyou Cave?
It's a rule of the jianghu.
Do these firecrackers work?
Don't worry,
I personally checked them.
They're absolutely reliable.
What on earth is this?
I'm Xiao from Jiangnan's Water Dagger Sect.
I'm bringing my disciple here
to seek an audience with General Wuyou!
[Wuyou]
What are you doing here?
I'm a disciple of Jiangnan's Water Dagger Sect.
I request an audience with General Wuyou.
What does this mean?
One firecracker is a greeting,
two is a provocation.
Are you tired of living, daring to stir trouble here?
No, it's a misunderstanding!
Misunderstanding or not,
you only have yourself to blame!
Attack!
I'm not here to cause trouble.
I came to see General Wuyou.
Understood.
It's all a misunderstanding.
To meet the General,
you must first...
I understand the rules.
What did you mean by lighting a third firecracker?
Zhao Buyou, you idiot!
You almost got me killed!
Have you eaten yet?
Why are you here?
Me?
I'm on duty today.
Then why aren't you wearing your clerk's uniform?
You're really cooperative, aren't you?
You fool,
I...
I was dismissed by the Office of Justice a long time ago.
In the future,
you'll definitely do better than me.
You left in such a rush.
I noticed you didn't bring much.
I brought
your clothes from home.
And on the way,
I bought a snack you like.
Are you settling in well?
I think it's not bad here.
I don't lose sleep here,
and I won't disturb Ban anymore.
You wouldn't know...
with you not clanging around the house,
Ban says
she can't sleep at all.
If you've got time, go back
and make some noise for her.
Oh, by the way,
I came today
to bring you something good.
I have written down
everything I've learned
in my life.
When you're free, take a look.
It's all about my failures
over the years
in the Office of Justice.
You might
find it useful.
[Examples of Communication Skills]
How is it?
Isn't it impressive?
Thank you.
Between brothers,
there's no need for formality.
Wen Yue
asked me to tell you
to come home for dinner tonight.
She said the whole family
should gather together.
Also, tonight,
I'll tell you both
something important.
Buyou,
are you planning to tell us
Ban and I's...
We'll talk at home.
Just remember to come back tonight.
I'm heading off now.
Buyou,
have you ever heard of Dong Qian,
the Senior Judge?
Of course.
Why are you asking about him all of a sudden?
I've been reading this book lately.
[Chongning Case Precedents]
It documents some cases
investigated by Judge Dong.
With his efforts alone,
he cracked many tricky and challenging cases.
But, unfortunately,
his death was very suspicious.
I discovered that the three dead people at Fan Tower
were the judges
of the Dong family massacre case back then.
Do you think these two cases
might be connected in some way?
Well, let's talk more when we have time.
I still have some things to take care of.
Don't forget to come back for dinner tonight.
Zhao Mo,
let them know
that one of the bookshelf legs
is missing a piece.
Ask them to fix it another day.
Got it.
[Wuyou]
What is she doing here?
We've arrived.
Stop. Don't move.
Who is this?
Ever since that old guy from the Water Dagger Sect died,
no one has come down to play with me.
[General Wuyou]
Are you Wen Yue?
It really is you!
So,
you've come down to see me?
I need your help.
Fifteen years without seeing each other,
and you immediately ask me for help?
How boring!
Too boring!
Go on,
what do you need me to do?
Recently, there's been a murder case at Fan Tower.
The bodies were transported through underground routes.
I want to know
the transport routes.
She is from the authorities!
If the officials find out the routes, it'll be over!
No way.
Absolutely not!
If I give you the transport route map,
it would reveal the layout of the routes.
Those corrupt officials above
have always wanted to figure out the routes
so they can wipe us out completely!
And anyway,
what use is it to you?
To save someone.
That won't do.
The person you want to save isn't yourself.
Wuyou Cave
has never helped outsiders for free.
Then what do you want?
You're in my territory now.
You'll have to follow my rules.
Bring it out!
Great!
[Life; Death]
Do you have the guts?
Spin it and let fate decide.
Life or death is destined.
Wealth and honor are determined by heaven!
Life or death is destined! Wealth and honor are determined by heaven!
Do you dare?
[Life; Death]
This is the will of heaven.
Bring it out!
It will lead you
to the place you fear most in your heart
to face the person you dare not confront.
If you walk through, the clouds will clear.
If you fail,
your soul will remain in eternal darkness.
You...
why are you here?
I should be the one asking that.
You were the one who cruelly left first.
I...
I had no choice but to leave.
You can leave too.
If I leave,
who will bear
Su Yue's regret and pain for you?
Back then, you left me alone.
I pleaded with you many times,
but you ignored me,
pretended not to hear.
Yes,
I was selfish.
I always
tried hard to completely forget you,
to completely rid myself of you.
But
I have never forgotten you for a single day.
The happier I am,
the stronger the unease in my heart grows.
I know it's because of you.
Do you blame me?
No.
I've never blamed you.
I'm
just afraid of you,
afraid that you'll
pry my hands open
and take away everything I'm holding onto.
That's not fear.
It's disgust!
It's just like how I disgust myself.
If we both feel disgusted,
then my existence has no meaning.
No!
Please, let go.
I'm begging you...
Give me the knife!
I can't take it anymore.
Why, when I've done nothing,
am I still tormented by so much?
Seeing you again
is really nice.
This time, I'll take you out with me.
Getting out?
What's the point?
Even outside,
I can't shake off this mess.
I never thought
that one piece of bread
would trap me in terrible trouble,
unable to escape.
Do you think
I'm a burden to you?
Not at all.
I've always tried my best
not to let you down.
Why?
Even though
you suffered so much
because of that bread,
I survived because of it.
One must
accept oneself in the end,
neither too humble nor too proud.
That's how you find your place in the world.
The world?
I want to see your world.
Is it bright?
Is it good?
Sometimes it's good,
sometimes it's not.
What's it like when it's good?
When it's good,
spring breezes for miles,
and plants competing to thrive.
And when it's not good,
tossing and turning,
unable to sleep at night,
just wanting
to kick the person beside me out of bed.
That sounds funny.
It's great that you're living for me.
Don't you want
to have a world of your own?
Me?
Would you dare to eat it again?
I'll join you.
Can I have my own world too?
When?
When...
you meet a fool
who buys you a white horse.
Don't let him slip away.
You did it!
What's this about?
Fifteen years ago, that old man brought you down here.
I could see then that you had worries in your heart.
Now I'm giving you a chance
to walk out on your own.
Today,
I can say I've done right by your master.
Give it to me.
This is the transport route map.
Don't let it fall into the hands of the authorities.
Wen Yue,
farewell forever!
Don't you think it's strange?
Zhao Buyou, a man so stingy,
actually treated me to steamed dumplings.
What trick is he up to this time?
Boss,
this morning in Yulin Alley, there was a street fight.
In Yu Alley, someone stole wine.
In Yutang Alley, someone got bitten by a dog.
It's all here.
How's the list going?
All posted.
Any progress?
No real results.
Why not?
Very few of the families
of the missing women
have come forward to report.
Progress is slow.
As expected.
Why do you say that?
These women,
confirmed to be missing,
mostly come from poor, ordinary families.
They're confirmed as missing
is because
their families
at least reported them missing to the Kaifeng Court in the past.
What does this tell you?
It shows that at least their families
care about them.
Come on,
sit down and take a careful look.
The rest of the missing women
are likely from low social classes,
or they're orphans and drifters.
They are someone's daughters,
wives,
or sisters.
But even knowing they're missing,
their families don't come forward to report it.
It's either because of saving face,
not wanting to damage their reputation,
or because
no one really cares whether they live or die.
Your cold,
formal missing persons notice
is certainly useless.
More than half
of the suffering of this world...
is borne by us women.
Draft another notice,
this time saying
that the family of each listed missing woman
can come to the court to collect compensation,
two guan of money.
In less than two days,
I guarantee
you'll gather all the information on the missing women on the list.
As for the money,
take it from my father's monthly salary.
She's so filial, huh?
Zhao,
are you treating me to dumplings
or trying to get information on the case?
- Eating dumplings. - Another bowl, please!
Waiter, two bowls!
Right away!
This dumpling shop is pretty good.
The dumplings are well-made,
and the maker is impressive too.
Judge Wan,
you mentioned earlier
that the three victims of the Red Silk Case
had met
with a mysterious woman
before they died.
A mysterious woman
in black.
Do you know what she looked like?
She had her face covered.
No one saw her clearly.
Sir...
The bill, please.
- Right away! - Another bowl!
Coming up!
What are you doing?
Well...
I haven't touched this bowl yet.
Untouched?
Untouched!
I don't eat what others have touched.
Here it is!
This bowl is still mine.
All right.
What did you just say?
Nothing, forget it.
All right, enjoy your meal.
He's faster than usual today.
Did that woman in black
leave any clues about her whereabouts?
She hired a carriage.
When we found the carriage,
the driver took us to Quyuan Street
in the southern part of the city.
We searched the alley there for a long time
but found nothing.
What's the name of the alley?
Ban Alley.
Ban Alley?
There's a small, nameless restaurant
[Nameless]
in the front half of the alley.
Their grilled pork ribs are exceptional.
What are you thinking about?
Nothing.
I'm full.
All right then.
Sir,
the bill, please.
Got it!
No need!
I'll pay.
Sir,
tally it up.
I'll pay in a bit.
All right!
No!
Judge Wan,
I invited you out,
so I should pay.
Why should you pay?
I said I'll pay.
No,
I'm treating you.
You're treating me?
Then how would I cook the books on my expense account?
Wan,
are you always this straightforward?
Yeah. What's wrong?
Won't Inspector Gu hold you accountable?
Inspector Gu?
He despises dishonesty the most.
He hates secrecy.
I always handle things directly.
If it works, it works.
If it doesn't, forget it.
I never keep things hidden.
You ate six bowls today.
Later,
how many will you report?
Sixty bowls!
Now I'm getting a little hungry myself.
Can I also...
You're quite dishonest!
Sir!
- Another bowl. - Make it three.
Got it!
Are you that hungry?
Here!
Ban!
Yao He,
you can ride a horse?
I know a lot of things.
You'll discover them over time.
What have you found?
I asked around earlier.
They said they hadn't seen Aunt Su
in the supply area for days.
That means
Lu Sanzhen might be lying.
I've been tracking Lu Sanzhen here for some time.
I saw her paying respects at a grave.
She even seemed to be crying.
But look...
this burial mound is freshly made.
There's no headstone either.
I don't know whose grave it is.
Could it
be Aunt Su's?
Aunt Su?
Are you saying
Lu Sanzhen killed Aunt Su?
If...
if Lu Sanzhen did kill Aunt Su,
then why would she come here to mourn, burn offerings,
and even cry at the grave?
What if
it's because she feels guilty?
It's possible.
That makes sense.
We'll know whose grave it is
once we dig it up.
Don't rush.
According to "The Song Penal Code,"
anyone who digs up a grave
is sentenced to exile with labor.
If you open the coffin,
it's the death penalty by hanging.
If you don't open the coffin,
it's three years of imprisonment.
What does that mean?
It means anyone who digs up a grave
will face punishment.
If you open the coffin,
you'll be sentenced to death by hanging.
If you dig up the grave
but don't open the coffin,
you'll get three years.
Easy!
We can report it to the Kaifeng Court
and let them open the coffin.
Right,
that's smart.
Someone recently visited the grave.
Ci's disappearance is suspicious,
so I followed Lu Sanzhen.
She visited the grave because of a guilty conscience.
Uncle,
this must be a murder case.
I trust Ban's judgment,
but if anything goes wrong,
I'll take full responsibility.
Yao He,
you're quite clever.
You've memorized "The Song Penal Code" well.
Here I go,
digging up the grave.
But what if it's not a murder case?
Can you bear the responsibility?
It's still my problem, isn't it?
Stop messing around.
Let's go.
Judge Wan!
If you don't believe us,
please keep this a secret for Yao He and me.
No matter what,
I'm digging up this grave!
Did you learn something?
I did.
What did you learn?
I learned...
Trust yourself!
Dig!
Judge Wan,
we've dug it up.
Open it!
Yes, sir.
It's not Ci.
What?
It's not her?
Oh...
Zhao Ban,
why did I even trust you?
Uncle...
What now?
I...
Wasn't this supposed to be a murder case?
I don't know either.
Then who is this?
Wait!
I know this person.
Who is she?
Song Yingying from Jinxiu Embroidery Workshop.
I once met her at Welfare Center!
We are embroiderers
here to teach embroidery to the girls.
She is Auntie Song,
Song Yingying.
[Song Yingying]
She's on the list.
It's not a mistake.
It's not a mistake anyway.
She's on the list.
You still have the nerve to laugh?
You scared me half to death.
This is the place.
Judge Wan,
this is the room shared by Lu Sanzhen and Song Yingying.
This one is Ci's room.
Search.
Yes, sir!
Who is it?
Wen Yue!
I'm Dong Qian,
the Senior Judge of the Office of Justice.
I was supposed to capture a gang,
but you messed it all up.
You spent seven days ruining three months of my hard work.
Since when has the jianghu ever been honest?
Drink and eat meat!
- There's a small, nameless restaurant - Sir, bring some wine!
in the front half of the alley.
Their grilled pork ribs are exceptional.
Wine works better than medicine!
Here are ten skewers of grilled pork ribs.
All right.
A jar of wine.
Enjoy your meal.
All right.
Hero...
No...
Senior Judge Dong,
are you sure you don't need me to accompany you to the clinic?
Wine works better than medicine.
We ordered just one jar of wine.
Why did they bring two?
Regulars get a complimentary jar of their private brew.
Newcomers don't.
Next time you come,
you won't need to order it.
Here.
Eat up.
Sir.
What would you like to order?
Two skewers of grilled pork ribs.
Why didn't you let me go down the well
with Wen Yue?
What's at the bottom of that well?
Didn't I stay out of it too?
Go investigate.
Yes, sir.
Investigating cases is dangerous.
Don't act recklessly.
Come,
let me take you search this room.
Then why can Wen Yue
go all the way down there?
She's skilled.
She's skilled?
She's skilled in her craft...
She's skilled in her craft?
Wen Yue
is able
to make umbrellas.
She can turn bamboo
into umbrellas.
That's
incredible craftsmanship.
She's skilled.
But she can go down the well...
Enough about her.
I don't know her well.
Go ask your brother if you want to know.
For now, let me take you to investigate this case.
Look,
this room
belongs to the embroiderers.
Tie Chi.
Here!
Come over here.
Take these items
back.
Find someone
to compare them with the embroidery
on the red silk.
Understood.
Ci Rou...
[Ci Rou]
My mother said she found this.
Hey...
I'm not as good at autopsies as you are,
but you're inexperienced when it comes to investigations.
If you disturb the surface clues,
you can easily destroy crucial hidden evidence.
Understand?
Judge Wan,
there's a handkerchief in Ci's room,
identical to this one.
Really?
That one also has the characters "Ci Rou" embroidered on it.
They're good friends,
aren't they?
It's normal for them to have something similar.
This is what we call surface clues.
Come on,
let me take you over there to investigate.
Surface clues...
You sent Yao He to perform the autopsy on his own.
Can he handle it?
Judge Wan.
He can!
There's a discovery.
Song Yingying's missing person notice.
[Song Yingying's Missing Person Notice]
This
is called a critical clue.
Let's go.
[Nameless]
Sir,
I didn't order any wine.
It's the rule of our restaurant.
When regulars visit,
they receive our private brew.
You used to come often over ten years ago.
I remember.
That Mr. Dong,
who loved drinking,
hasn't been here in a long time.
Did he accomplish that earth-shattering task of his?
Mr. Dong...
has traveled
to another region.
I didn't expect you to still remember me.
Please, have a seat.
All right.
I haven't been here in over ten years.
I thought your shop had closed.
Wen Yue,
I truly appreciate it.
I get paid for the service,
so, of course, I need to do my best.
Wen Yue!
What's really down that well?
Be careful!
Inspector Gu,
there's something at home tonight,
so we'll take our leave now.
Lady Wang is still down the well.
Please take good care of her.
Wen Yue, why wouldn't you let me go down there?
Boss,
this
was found in their room.
Gu Zhen!
It's fine.
[Fashion in Song Dynasty]
[Song Dynastypedia]
[Local Enrollment Started in the Song Dynasty!]
[Narrator: Xia Meng]
Did you know?
Local enrollment began in the Song Dynasty.
Back then, the imperial examination was highly competitive,
and preliminary exam spots were allocated by region.
This led to frequent cases of examination migration.
So,
to prevent these abuses,
the Song rulers continuously refined the household registration system.
Examinees had to be registered locally
and take their preliminary exams in their place of origin.
They were forbidden from falsifying identities, impersonating others,
or forging family ties.
[Household registration information]
They were even subjected to a three-generation background check,
ensuring their character
and that of their fathers and grandfathers
was free from offenses
like rebellion or disrespect.
These regulations
[Examination Hall]
effectively upheld the integrity of the exam system.
So, Mo checked his household registration before taking the exam,
and urgently sought to know his true identity
to enroll in the Imperial Academy.
This action
was very much in line
with the imperial examination background of the Song Dynasty.
Freezing rain lingers for months
Followed by cold snow
Through boiling waters and raging flames
Chase eastward along the Bian River
Time flows day by day, month by month
Feign joy with drinks before the camps
Stagger home after the drinking games
Such is the state of the world
In the years of displacement
Heads are bowed to the ground in poverty
Burning desires unveil sorrow and joy
Despair everywhere
Hidden within the painting
A lifetime feels so long
Yet life itself is so short
Seeing mountains first as mountains, then as more
Dreamlike, yet not distant
Parting the clouds reveals a clear yet cold sky
Oh, the mortal world
A lifetime feels so long
Yet life itself is so short
Seeing mountains first as mountains, then as more
Dreamlike, yet not distant
How painful it is to see unrest beneath prosperity
Whoo, whoo
How brief a sweet dream is