Mast! Lay down the mast!
Hurry up and get the rope!
Bow and stern face the banks! Quick!
Thousands of homes are brightly lit,
and the doors to them are wide open.
This is East Capital.
New wine at Sunyang Restaurant!
Welcome to enjoy it!
​If you want to know what happens next,
wait until next time.
People from all over the world gather here,
and envoys from various countries come to communicate with the authorities.
[Riverside Code at Qingming Festival]
[Adapted from Ye Wenbiao's Novel Series of the Same Name]
[Episode 4]
[Afraid of the bitterness of parting.]
[There are many things I want to spit out but choke back instead.]
[Li Qingzhao, Song Dynasty]
Buyou, where are we going?
We need to hurry home.
Buyou!
Ban'er, what's the matter?
Something is wrong.
Wen Yue is not home.
She left a note.
I don't regret meeting you
for the last fifteen years.
If I don't return,
take care of our father and siblings.
When you got back,
were her clothes and jewelry still there?
Yes.
​A hotchpotch of all the food of Sunyang Restaurant.
It is from Xiao Yishui, a bamboo merchant.
According to Mr. Xiao, he was going to find his junior sister.
Oh no,
something bad happened.
- Buyou. - Buyou, where are you going?
Do you two have any money on you?
Give it to me.
Money?
- Quick! - Money.
Mr. Xiao said he was going to a woman
called Fu Ling.
He said she was good at prescribing.
He went to her every time he came to East Capital.
Hurry up and go home!
Go home?
​On the night of Qingming,
let's do something big.
Master,
what are we going to do?
West Rainbow Bridge.
Kill Li Yan.
[Fifteen Years Ago]
Who is it?
Master,
I know Li Yan. He is a good official.
Go!
Kneel!
Li Yan, you corrupt official!
Get ready for your death!
Come and see.
What does it say?
What's written on it?
Yes.
What happened?
- What happened? - Have a look yourself.
What does it say?
A blood message?
Kill the corrupt official
for justice!
[Spring Water Pavilion East Capital]
The night view is beautiful.
Let's go there.
- Let's go. - Go.
Let's go. Come in, please.
Excuse me,
please kindly let me go in first.
I'll be done in a minute.
Who is he?
What is he doing?
May I ask
are you Lady Fuling?
I think you know.
Have a seat.
Lady Fuling,
you can write a prescription, right?
Have you come here before?
No.
I've never...
It's my first time.
Are you introduced here by an acquaintance?
I heard from a friend
of my father
that when a patient came to you for medical treatment,
you would ask them their preference
and write a prescription based on that.
She's clever.
​She is said
to have given many prescriptions to men on the ship
to make them feel comfortable.
What illness do you have?
I have no illness.
I...
I'm not here for a prescription.
I want to ask you something.
Is that okay?
You know my rule,
right?
Sure!
Did anyone
with the surname Xiao come to you a few days ago?
Xiao?
Yes.
Would you tell me
what he came to you for
and what he said?
Got it.
​I have not much money with me.
The man you referred to
indeed came to me a few days ago.
He paid me a lot of money
to hook up with boatmen of a ship.
I came up
with an idea for him.
[Barren Lake Suburb of East Capital]
Look over there!
Beauties!
- Beauties! - So many!
- Beauties! - Come to me!
Let's have fun together!
It's indeed true.
Those men who make a living on water like
to have fun with women
on ships.
Lady Fuling,
do you know
what his purpose was in making these boatmen pass
from the big ship to the little one?
Maybe give them a chance to pursue pleasure.
You look familiar.
It may be helpful for you.
Drink!
I saw several crawling
into the big ship in the dark that day.
Lady Fuling,
do you know where he is now?
Yes.
Would you mind telling me?
I have no more money.
He has been
in the Fan Building every day these days.
He also invited two beauties over today.
They're said to be
in the Meilan Hall.
[Fan Building East Capital]
Welcome! Come in, please.
Good evening.
Come in and have a seat!
Welcome, please follow me in.
Get me the case file of the Office of Justice tonight,
or you will lose your entire family.
Welcome to the Fan Building!
Good evening! Come in, please.
Come in, please.
[Meilan Hall]
Good!
Have a drink.
Yishui.
[Xiao Yishui A pirate in the South]
Get out!
You guys!
Make a body search.​
Pull out the hairpin and give it to me.
It is this scent.
More than ten years have passed,
but I haven't forgotten the scent for a day.
Jiu'er,
just go back with me.
​They said all the culprits had been brought to justice.
I thought you were dead.
​Now it is fate
that has brought us together again.
Do you remember this?
When I tried to make out
with you back then,
you ended up sticking this in my arm.
​I've been wearing it to this day.
You said this morning
that you would let me go
if I helped you get the case file.
I want both
the case file
and you.
No way!
Where are you going?
Go away!
Did you get the case file?
Yes.
I don't have it with me.
Don't give me your attitude.
Hush!
Welcome!
Come in, please!
Manager Bao, I'm sorry to trouble you.
Today, a pig's head appeared
in the Bian River.
Have you heard of it?
Yes.
​We followed the clue
to a pig shop.
The manager there said this batch
of pigs were all sold to you.
Inspector Gu,
pigs' heads are not valuable
to us.
We usually throw them away after cutting out the key parts.
Everyone might pick them up.
​Besides, with so many customers here every day,
it's hard to know who picked up that pig's head.
​Has there been a recent customer here
with the surname Xiao?
He looks very strong.
Well...
There is indeed one.
​He has been here a few days.
He's here right now.
Inspector Gu, this way.
Jiu'er, don't be angry.
I've taught him a lesson for you.
Give me a handkerchief to wipe my face.
You two clean this up.
Jiu'er, come back to me.
This is the life you should be living.
On the run,
living a dangerous life.
​What a miserable life you have been living
for the last ten years or so!
Why do you want the case file?
​What are you going to do next?
[Culprit-Arrest Abstract Volume]
Will you get me in trouble?
What are you talking about?
I want the case file to avenge my father.
Master was killed by those from the Office of Justice.
​Everyone on the banks was a witness.
Look over there! What's that?
​The employer wanted us
to kill everyone
and leave no survivors.
Kill!
Go ahead and kill them!
I'll handle you when we go back.
We're from the Office of Justice!
You are surrounded!
Surrender and confess quickly!
Don't you think those from the Office of Justice
came too quickly back then?
​And when they arrived,
they shot everyone to death indiscriminately with arrows.
It's totally illogical.
Back then,
on the ship,
- Master... - We're from the Kaifeng Court!
Hold on!
- Quick! - You can't go in.
Manager Xiao, sorry!
They're from the Kaifeng Court!
He is the one I referred to.
His surname is Xiao.​
It's you.
Just now I heard
a ship mentioned.
​Which of you is going to explain?
What happened
on the ship?
What did you say?
What did you two do?
You are indeed here.
You're away too far.
What's going on?
Buyou,
let me explain.
Explain what?
Shut up!
A man and a woman alone,
what are you doing here?
She is my wife.
Are you trying to seduce her?
What are you doing?
​I have fallen in love with your wife.
I don't mind telling you about it.
I'm going to compete with you.
How dare you!
Tell me.
How did you meet?
Haven't I told you?
I wanted to buy bamboo.
He's the bamboo merchant.
I'm talking business.
Business?
Are you sure it's a good place to do business?
Lady Wen,
I want to propose you marry me.
Ever since I met you,
I've been fascinated by you.
All I can think about is you.
What should I do?
​From now on,
you will be the most important treasure
to me.
You're mine.
I want to have a baby with you.
Inspector Gu, please kindly help me.
Silence!
Show me your customs document.
Do you have it?
I see.
My customs document.
Here it is.
Read it.
Yes.
Xiao Yishui.
It's me.
Hush!
You are from Meishan, Chengdu Prefecture.
On February 21, the third year of Xuanhe,
you came to East Capital to sell bamboo.
The goods include 200 jun of Shouzhu,
100 jun of Arrow Bamboo, 50 jun of Sinocalamus Affinis,
30 jun of Bambusa cerosissima McClure, and 30 jun of Mottled Bamboo.
Xiao Yishui, Jingxi South Road.
Issued by Meishan, Chengdu Prefecture.
Xiao Yishui?
Yes.
How do you spell your surname?
X-i-a-o.
​As for my first name,
it's Y-I-S-H-U-I.
Xiao Yishui.
Nice body.
I lived a poor life when I was little.
Tell him about your situation.
​I am a Sichuan merchant who sells bamboo.
Lady Wen specializes in making umbrellas.
Why you again?
So we met each other
and become familiar.
I see.
A bamboo merchant.
That's right.
You're from Meishan?
Yes.
Inspector Gu...
Prosecutor Di from the Office of Justice arrives!
You are from Merishan, right?
I'm from Leshan.
We are from the same place.
It's amazing?
Are you serious?
Are you really from Meishan?
Can I take a look?
Mr. Gu,
what's wrong with you?
Why didn't you tell me
you had a clue?
Mr. Di.
I haven't been back to the hometown in over ten years.
No wonder I feel warm in my heart
when I see you.
I really miss the Rice Noodles with Shredded Chicken from the hometown.
Yes, that's delicious.
​I have heard that the men
of Meishan are so good to their wives.
​Those who marry our men there live happily.
They enjoy an easy life,
and they don't need to work.
​Lady Wen, if you marry me,
you will have a happy
and easy life.
Prosecutor Di!
What are you talking about with each other?
Don't you think it's improper?
Wen Yue is my wife.
You useless! Shut up!
Wan Fu.
I'm here.
Is there any problem with the document?
No.
Mr. Di.
Let's go.
Yes.
Here you are.
I'm leaving.
See you.
​I will leave you to your own affairs.
I'm leaving as well.
I won't bother you anymore.
Did you enjoy it just now?
I seem to understand a little why Jiu'er married you.
You have a good mind.
Smart.
Alright.
Now that you're here,
let's have a talk.
Don't be afraid.
It's an underground culvert in East Capital.
If people die here,
[Underground Culvert East Capital]
they will never be discovered.
Tell me.
Where is the case file?
What is he talking about?
Didn't you tell him?
I did everything by myself.
He doesn't know anything.
Wen Yue,
you have been to the Office of Justice?
​Have you heard of my dismissal?
We can talk about it later.
I didn't mean to...
Let's talk about it later.
Free him,
and I will now take you to get what you desire.
No way!
Well...
You...
Big brother,
what... what file do you need?
I have no relationship with you.
Cover his mouth!
I won't say a word anymore.
I won't.
Free him.
​Do you believe I would kill him now?
Then you can get nothing.
Don't even try to avenge your father.
Jiu'er,
I care about you the most.
I agree with you on everything.
I'll free him right now.
Free both of us.
You can go now.
What are you guys doing? Zhao Buyou!
Bury him!
Let me ask you again.
Where is the case file?
Don't you plan to tell me?
Don't regret it after he dies.
From the moment you walked in today,
I felt something was wrong.
Tell me the truth.
You didn't get the case file, did you?
You...
How did you cut it open, Jiu'er?
Free him!
Okay.
Free him.
Untie!
Okay. Untie.
Hurry up and leave!
Let him go!
I'll take you to pick the file up now.
Don't deceive me, Jiu'er.
You didn't get the file, did you?
Otherwise, why would you do this?
You want to trade your life for his?
Do you think it's worth it
for such a useless man?
Wait!
Li Yan, the Deputy Commissioner of Transport of Liangzhe Region,
was assassinated on the Bian River.
No one on the ship survived.
​The murder weapon was a triangular dagger.
Li Yan's head was gone.
It was replaced by a pig's head.
The culprits were presumed
to be refugees from the South
who killed Li Yan due to his corruption.
What did you just read?
I can recite all the files in the National Archives
of the Office of Justice.
But if you dare to hurt my wife,
I may forget.
Why didn't you say it earlier?
You didn't ask me either.
No.
Hold on.
Didn't Jiu'er tell you?
Then how did you know that I wanted this file?
Aren't you a pirate of the South?
You guys get money from others
and avert disaster for them.
Fifteen years ago, someone paid you
to board a ship and kill Li Yan
to perform a scene
in which refugees take revenge on a corrupt official.
​After you had done so,
all those who had boarded the ship were killed.
Someone from the Office of Justice was behind it, right?
Otherwise, why did those from the Office of Justice
get there so quickly at the time?
Who is behind the matter?
Who?
I don't know.
​I've been reading that case file for years.
I didn't find anything strange.
What do you exactly want the case file for?
I want to know who tricked my father.
I want to avenge my father.
​My father was hired to kill Li Yan at the time.
But the case was hastily closed
with the conclusion of refugees retaliating
against corrupt officials back then.
No one even looked into who was behind it.
The person investigating this case must have been involved.
I need to get the case file
and see who closed the case.
This is probably the man
who tricked my father.
I remember now.
It was an Administrative Judge of the Office of Justice who closed the case.
Cheng Rui.
Do you know where he is?
He died of illness three years ago.
He had a low official rank.
I don't think he had that ability.
Then he is not behind the matter.
But he must have been ordered.
It's the same person
who tricked my father back then
and made the fake Auspicious Sign today.
He won't die.
Today, I destroyed the Auspicious Sign
to seek revenge
and declare war on him.
You don't even know who this person is.
How can you be sure they are the same one?
Of course I can.
​I have two letters in my hand.
One is a secret letter
from the person who hired my father
to kill Li Yan back then.
The other is a secret letter from the person
[Secret letter]
who planned the fake Auspicious Sign today.
Same handwriting.
Doesn't it prove
that the same person is behind both?
How did you get the secret letter
of planning the Auspicious Sign?
It's none of your business.
What I want is that case file.
You go to the Office of Justice now
and get me that case file.
It's too late.
The National Archives caught fire,
and the case file was burned.
[Assassination Case of Li Yan,]
[the Deputy Commissioner of Transport of Liangzhe Region, on the Bianhe River]
That file happened to get burned?
What a coincidence!
Yes.
Who set the fire?
I don't know.
But I know who was the last to leave.
Who?
His name is Luo Zhun.
But I don't know if he set the fire.
I don't know.
​I know how to confirm if it's him.
Jiu'er, as soon as I finish what I'm doing,
I'll pick you up at your house.
Zhao Buyou,
I have been a refugee before.
You know that.
Later,
as I couldn't afford to eat,
I joined the pirates.
​I did not mean to tell you this,
but now you know it too.
Gan Liang was killed by me
because he knew about my past
and threatened me.
​I thought I had escaped from them.
But they came to me again.​
Xiao Yishui disguised himself as a bamboo merchant
and asked a broker to invite me to talk business with him.
I only found myself in his trap
when I arrived at the ship this morning.
Jiu'er,
it's been fifteen years.
Have you forgotten who you are?
​You were the one who told Gan Liang about my past.
He bullied you so much.
I felt bitter for you.
So I gave you a chance
to kill him
and recollect who you truly are.
You didn't let me down.
You haven't changed.
You still have good martial skills,
and you didn't become a coward.
Jiu'er, come back to me.
Let's do something big together.
Come over.
A good show is about to start.
I like the way you are.
Did you see it, Jiu'er?
This is the life you should be living.
I didn't mean to say it,
but you didn't choose a bright future.
I really don't understand why you married Zhao Buyou.
But now it seems helpful to me.
There is a file at the place
where he works.
It's about the Li Yan case from fifteen years ago.
I need that.
​Ask him to get it out for me.
​I want to see
if you can get out of it again.
Xiao Yishui forced me into the game
by pushing me into the water.
In a moment of desperation,
I took off the clothes from the boatman's body
and covered my face.
So the person you saw
in the water this morning was indeed me.
​Later, as I ran home,
I received those food of Sunyang Restaurant from him.
He said that if I didn't follow his instructions,
he would ruin our family.
I had no choice but to go to the Office of Justice
to steal the case file and settle the matter.
​This is what I've been hiding from you for the last few days.
Coincidentally,
you went to the Office of Justice.
You must have known about my dismissal.
​That's what I've been hiding from you for the last few days.
We are even.
Let's go back.
Something else to do.
Hurry up, Buyou is back.
Don't rush me.
Wen Yue?
You are back.
Wen Yue, I thought you didn't want us anymore.
Buyou, what happened?
I'm fine.
I fell down.
Wen Yue, the note you left...
By the way, Wen Yue,
I need to tell you one thing.
Tonight,
a man from the Office of Treasury came to you.
​He said their newly appointed official,
surnamed Wei,
is preparing to buy a new batch of green umbrellas for the palace.
So he wants to talk to you about a deal.
Alright.
I see.
It's a dangerous day today. Luckily, we are safe now.
Wen Yue,
For large orders from the Office of Treasury,
those officials must have made a lot of money.
I think we can raise the price
appropriately by then.
Sign it.
What is this?
A Letter of Divorce.
Wrote by Zhao Buyou from East Capital.
Ten years ago, introduced by a matchmaker...
Wen Yue,
what do you mean by it?
You saw Xiao Yishui today,
​and you know what he is like.
He even dared to destroy the Auspicious Sign.
I'm not sure if he will cause any other big trouble.
​I must leave, or I'll get you into trouble.
Besides, I lied to you,
father,
Ban'er,
and Mo'er.
In the morning, you told me to run.
You're probably right.
Maybe it's my fate to be on the run.
Sign it.
I won't sign it.
When did I say I wanted to divorce you?
Why do you make decisions for me?
I strongly disagree.
I'm going to burn it.
It's ashes now.
Zhao Buyou, didn't you hear everything today?
Xiao Yishui said that he would come to me again
after he finished what he was doing.
I'm sure he will come to me.
​If he comes to Sparrow Lane
and lets all the neighbors know that I was once a pirate,
how can you, father, Ban'er, and Mo'er
continue to live here?
This is the 800 guan
that we mentioned before.
From this day forward, it's your responsibility to keep them.
Don't spend them recklessly.
You
earned this money
by making umbrellas
one by one
day and night.
You must use the money to buy a house.
Buy house?
Will you come back and stay here after I buy it?
​Since the day you mentioned buying a house,
I've been thinking
about getting a new bed
in our room
and hanging a mosquito net
in your favorite color.
If you're not home,
is that home?
Alright.
I'll listen to you.
​I will use the money
to buy the house you mentioned.
​After buying it,
I will live there
with my future wife.
Also, we'll drink iced plum wine
in that yard.
Sorry that you can't enjoy it.
You can only watch.
Alright.
Remember to reserve the south room for your father.
I see.
Wen Yue,
you're ruthless.
Then, don't blame me.
Come here. They're quarreling again.
I'll let others judge who's at fault.
What are you doing?
You...
What's the matter?
I heard that Buyou is going to divorce Wen Yue.
What?
Father,
what are you arguing about in the middle of the night?
- Father. - What happened?
Buyou and Wen Yue want to divorce.
Father,
Wen Yue wants
to divorce me.
It's my fault.
I've brought shame on this family, and I can't stay here any longer.
Wen Yue,
what's going on?
It...
It's been years,
but I haven't given birth to a child for Buyou.
I feel sorry for it.
Wen Yue, ​you are not the one to blame.
It's his fault.
Father said you had bad kidneys.
When did I say that?
Even so,
you don't need to divorce.
​It's already tiring to provide for you guys.
What?
Have another burden?
Anyway, if Wen Yue leaves,
Ban'er and I will go with her.
Let's go pack up.
Don't make more trouble!
It's getting late.
Go to bed.
Let's talk about it tomorrow.
Father,
stop her from leaving.
Okay.
Speak at my instructions.
Hush!
Wen Yue, you're up.
Buyou has made a farewell meal for you.
​He wants you to have a full stomach before you leave.
No need.
Wen Yue,
Mo'er made it last night.
​When you step on it,
it can massage your shoulders.
And you can do laundry easily like this.
Mo'er made it last night,
trying to release your burden.
Father,
speak.
It's good.
Wonderful!
Brother, don't worry.
The chair I made will
definitely keep Wen Yue.
That chair probably will only be used by our father.
We all know Wen Yue very well.
She has made the decision.
You can't keep her.
Since we can't change her mind,
I can only make her feel better when leaving.
Buyou, you...
Don't act on impulse.
What's on your mind?
Go buy a horse for Wen Yue.
She will understand me at the sight of it.
[Great Shop of Mules and Horses East Capital]
Welcome!
Are you here to buy a horse?
I like this one.
How much?
Let's bargain with gestures in the sleeves.
It's too expensive.
Can you cut the price a bit?
Are you joking? It's not expensive.
Excuse me,
may I ask if this horse is around three years old?
Yes.
​Based on the weight of the horse,
an average of nine jin of hay per day would be required.
​It costs 10 wen for a jin hay.
For three years, it won't exceed...
Mo'er,
you can't bargain like this.
He knows a lot about horses.
Actually,
I bought your horse before.
When?
Fifteen years ago.
Excuse me,
how much is the white horse?
You have a good eye.
This one is a bit more expensive.
20 guan.
It's been passed down in the family.
If you sell it to a pawnshop,
you can at least get 20 guan.
No wonder you look familiar.
Give me a discount.
I'm a regular customer.
Alright.
Then I'll make a bid.
Is it okay?
Okay.
Deal!
Okay, this is your horse now.
Hey,
how much is this horse?
Hold on a second.
Good horse!
Buyou.
Judging by the man's accent, he seems to be a foreigner.
It's not strange.
There are many foreigners in the city.
Buyou,
come closer.
Look at the foreigner's sleeve.
There are traces of magnesia, sulfur,
and carbon powder.
How did you know that?
It's exactly the same traces left on my sleeve
when I tried magic Auspicious Sign that day.
Go!
- Well... - Please kindly give me a discount.
10 guan.
Alright.
Trust me.
It's good horse.
The price is not high.
But...
There is only one point...
Hey,
is he buying a horse?
Yes.
He's a foreigner.
According to the Law of the Great Song Dynasty,
- you're forbidden to sell horses to foreigners. - Someone is going to kill you.
If you don't want to die, come with me.
[Fashion in Song Dynasty]
[Encyclopedia of the Song Dynasty]
[Visit Business Centers, a Great Place for Song Dynasty People]
[to Have Fun Narrator - Xia Meng]
Business centers are actually entertainment centers that operate all day long.
You heard me right.
They're also known as business markets and business buildings.
They are large complexes of entertainment and business.
Equivalent to modern Disneyland.
As all-day entertainment centers,
they are a great place for the public to spend the day.
​As many as nine business centers have been recorded in East Capital.
[Storytelling]
There are many entertainments,
such as storytelling,
singing and playing,
[Puppet Play]
variety plays,
and puppet plays,
which are dazzling.
During the holiday season,
almost every business center is packed.
It is a great place for Song Dynasty people to relax and have fun.
♪Rowing across the river with a load of fish♪
♪Paddling the oars while singing a song♪
♪Guests travel with lanterns under moonlight♪
♪In the corridor, joy fills the table♪
♪Come and enjoy the cool under the canopy♪
♪My new hometown brings peace to my heart♪
♪I love the city hustle and bustle, and the grass in mountains♪
♪Walking down roads, strolling along alleys♪
♪Look, the swallows glide with a beakful of spring mud♪
♪With hope, they gently take off and fly away♪
♪Guests come from far and wide♪
♪A bowl of wine, a mouthful of ambition♪
♪Eyebrows unfurl, for prosperity awaits ahead♪
♪Singing loud happily, you get to pick the broad road you want♪
♪Under the immense sky, dusts dance with the wind♪
♪Your root is where your original aspirations lie♪
♪A thousand households are brightly lit♪
♪Bursting into song, they set off for another journey♪
♪For youngsters, their ambition is burning bright♪
♪Just seize the opportunities and make adventures♪