Timing and subtitles brought to you by
Are You The One Team @ Viki
Oh? Where is my car key?
I am sure I put it in my pockets...
It's gone, it's gone, it's gone.
Sorry!
Why is Cookie saying that he's sorry?
What happened?
So we can go to work together.
After that, with smiling faces,
should we break up?
Don't be distressed by yesterday's memories.
Don't have a hard time about tomorrow's worry.
I'm sorry.
Today, the two of us will just laugh, enjoy, and love.
After loving her as much as I can
for one month,
I'll break up with her.
It's written as "farewell"
but let's read it as "love."
♫  It's my first feeling  ♫
♫  You make me lovely, lovely smile  ♫
The weather is so nice.
I know, right? It's a good day for a kiss.
No?
♫  Awkward feeling  ♫
♫  The heart which is lost and confused is yours  ♫
Are you busy today? Let's eat lunch together.
I will look at my schedule first.
♫  “You are my starry night”  ♫
You are late, right? Should I increase the speed?
Drive safely.
There was no need for you to rush over like this without stopping.
Anyway, thank you.
What do you mean thank you?
Even if I go to work early, there is nothing to do anyway.
Oh? You are doing that again.
Since you came out in such a hurry, did you leave your responsibilities as the director of The One on the shoe rack?
I wore it as my innerwear.
Because today is the day to send the products, there's nothing special to do.
Ah, yes.
- I am the one who is thankful.
- What do you mean?
For helping us advance to Lafayette and allowing our products to be sold to countries far and wide.
It was the fantastic collaboration between you and Team Leader Ha.
Should I say that I just set the stage for you?
Of course, it was very superb.
My father has been doing "tsk tsk tsk" less often.
A real big congratulations for that.
It's a first for me.
That someone would recognize me and love me
without caring about my father's backing or my qualifications.
Because you are someone that I can't help but like, Miss Chi Sook!
Arrived. Have a good day.
- I will contact you.
- Okay.
Senior Manager!
You haven't had coffee yet, right?
The latte that you like.
- Assistant Manager Seo.
- It's just coffee.
Let's be comfortable like before.
We were good together.
Those little punks.
Hello, this is Ha Yeong Eun.
Yes.
Yes, thank you.
They asked to make sure you call them back.
Calls asking for you have been flooding in since the morning.
Yes.
Thank you for the suggestion. Yes.
Hello, this is Ha Yeong Eun.
At this rate, our team leader might be going to a different company.
For our Team Leader Ha, Olivier was like...
He did a seal clap like this for her.
It's reasonable that multiple places want to recruit her.
Fashion is Paris. It's better to pack up in advance, right?
One second... did anyone say that they will take you?
Excuse me, sunbaes... if I didn't run around with those wires that day,
Olivier wouldn't have been able to connect.
When they said that the circuitry was unstable,
I fixed it in one shot with the skills I gained from my gaming days.
You know, right?
You must know.
Really, again? Are you going to keep speaking informally to me?
Where do you think she will go?
If she's going to leave anyway, I hope it'll be to somewhere at least at the level of Olivier.
Manager, you are going to follow her, right?
Of course! What about you?
If you and the Team Leader all leave, that position is mine...
- I'm torn.
- What should I do with you?
I'm going. You are going too, right?
If Team Leader Ha says "let's go," then of course I will.
There's one important thing. Does anyone know how to speak French?
Bonjour.
("Hello" in French.)
You only know how to say that!
- Yeah!
- So what? It's fine.
What is it?
- An expression of my heart to our company's treasure.
- What?
Having lived this long, there is one thing that I've learned.
Life is a series of temptations,
but you must never follow others blindly.
Just in case, by chance, if your heart wavers or you consider changing jobs
because other places are asking you to go to them since you held one successful show,
I'm asking you to not be swayed.
It's a plea from a sunbae.
Of course, I know very well that you aren't someone who would do that.
- I will drink it well.
- Ah yes, of course,  of course.
That's why I'm giving it to you.
- Ah, it was so good.
- Ah, I'm so full.
Then, today too... fighting! Fighting.
What is he doing here again?
I guess he heard the rumors.
That's why he should have treated us better before.
Yes, this is Sonó design office. Yes.
Nam Na Ri, you checked for the color differences on the fabric that's being re-ordered, right?
- Yes.
- I understand.
Team Leader. Team Leader, Team Leader!
- What are we going to do?
- What?
Ah, what happened now? Who was it?
- Nouvelle Vague.
- What about Nouvelle Vague?
They want to interview our team leader!
- What?
- What? Are you serious?
Yes! They just called!
Isn't that awesome?
Are you sure? Are you sure it was Nouvelle Vague?
- What's going on? What is it this time?
- This is fantastic news!
I'm Nouvelle Vague's editor-in-chief, Kim Seo Hyun.
It's nice to meet you. I'm Ha Yeong Eun.
Congratulations. I heard that Lafayette responded positively.
Thank you.
Although it isn't the first time that a domestic brand has advanced into Lafayette,
I think Sonó is the first one that Olivier personally ordered from.
- Is that so?
- That's why I wanted to meet with you.
I wanted to interview you as the up-and-coming designer for our next month's issue.
It's a six page article.
For a domestic designer, you will be the first.
Of course, she has to do it!
- Then our clothes must get displayed next to the interview, right?
- Amazing!
It costs several million won to display one photo in a magazine like that!
To have our product be displayed on the cover...
- is that too much to wish for?
- Even if they say they can do it, we can't.
We would need to pay at least 100 or 200 million won for the cover.
Plus, I'm sure they have a year's worth of covers lined up already.
Then when they interview our Team Leader, can she wear our clothes?
- That would be so great!
- It would be amazing, right?
Even if magazines are out of season, since people will share the interview
from the online magazine on social media anyway,
it will have a huge promotional effect, right?
Wait a minute... on that note, my design will be displayed first.
Ah, there's no such thing. Let's play rock, paper, scissors.
You didn't do anything. You stay out of it.
- Then what should I do?
- Okay, rock, paper, scissors!
- Ah, what is this?
- You're out!
If it's not too burdensome and if the company asks us to do it, we will.
I don't think it'll be bad for Sonó either.
Why are you only mentioning this now?
Why?
I ate two cookies. What do I do about the carbs?
Am I swollen? Am I swollen?
Then I'll tell them to send us the questionnaire.
I approve for now.
There are no other requests?
They don't need an interview with the director?
If they do, I approve that too.
Tighten up.
Vice President Shin, when was it that I asked you to renew the contract with Sonó?
There's already another brand slated to enter in place of Sonó.
We can't break the promise now.
Promise.
If the circumstances or your feelings change, what breaks are promises.
- Senior Vice President.
- Look here, Vice President Shin.
Can you not do it or do you not want to?
If you care for the department store,
retain profits, not your pride.
That's what you have to do right now.
Don't retract the termination letter.
We, Sonó, will not sell at The Hills.
It's not that The Hills is firing us, but we are cutting off The Hills.
So Yeong, is this everything?
- Yes, I checked.
- Seon Joo, confirm it.
- Okay.
- Here.
So Yeong, make Chi Hyeong be in charge of the boxes exclusively.
He seemed to have so much energy when I saw him during the show.
Why am I always the only one who does the physical stuff?
I'm better with my head than body too.
She's the one with the strength.
Come on, let's get work done.
We have to prepare for the next season soon.
Time goes really fast, right?
Yeah, when I...
If you type the word "person" (사람) quickly,
it becomes the word "life." (삶)
How did it go?
What is it? Did it not go well?
That little bastard. I told him to treat you well.
Two months.
He'd like to start a pop-up store at Galeries Lafayette for two months.
For me, a woman who bought my picture, that no one else glanced at,
changed my life.
Because of that, when I was about to give up on photography,
I didn't end up doing that.
The concept is urban secret garden.
For the highlight, special effects should go in, right?
Extravagantly without holding back.
That's because you're the only man in the world whom I can whine to.
As much as you want.
Perhaps meeting people
and loving them
is writing out your life.
2021 Work Order
A meal?
Thinking about it, I don't think I've  ever properly bought you a meal.
I'm not that kind of person under any circumstance.
Let's do that. Where should we go?
We were going to make it?
I thought it would lack sincerity to show thanks
by taking you to a restaurant that we can go to at any time.
Do you know how to cook?
What's there that isn't found on the internet?
Hold it a bit higher.
A bit closer.
Is it onions next? Onions...
Move back now.
- You can come closer yourself.
- For about one minute.
A bit closer. A bit closer.
After heating up the pan.
Go back. Hurry. About 0.3 centimeters...
You are doing this on purpose, right? Why don't you hold it yourself, read it, and cook?
- What are you even saying right now?
- Why did I  smile saying that?
One millimeter makes a huge difference in clothing.
Isn't it wrong to just say "fry all these ingredients well"?
People who are meant to understand it will understand it.
I will do the dishes.
Of course.
You know, we could have made a simple dish like pasta.
A homemade meal is the hardest.
It was so that you can eat a homemade meal.
I opened the refrigerator earlier. There was just water, beer,
and containers of side dishes that I don't even know when you last opened them.
Oh, it's boiling. Open the lid.
Put in the sliced tofu.
Draw a half circle as you pour the sesame oil.
- Half circle.
- Not a full circle, but a half circle.
I understand.
I think you drew a full circle.
Quite a bit came out.
You will fix the recipe?
No, I was asking if there is something I can use to fix the recipe.
Oh, something to use?
There isn't.
It looks so good.
It looks good, right?
I'm hungry.
- You are hungry, right?
- Yes.
The soybean paste soup also looks good.
It'll be ridiculously amazing.
Oh no, there's big trouble.
Leave this to me
and go over there to get that ready.
Okay, I got it.
Then, should I get started?
This dress is really pretty.
Thank you.
I, I, I will...
The pain will get worse and worse.
The cancer cells have spread to the nerves around the pancreas.
So the upper abdomen here will hurt a lot.
Mom, take your medicine.
Gosh, why are you taking care of my medicine?
Dad does this as well.
You don't need to do this.
Ji Min, just watch the cartoon. I will do it.
The pain will subside.
It's okay. Watch the cartoon.
It's been a while since I ate a solid homemade meal.
Does it suit your taste?
It's totally my style.
You can do it alone next time, right?
Since you practiced it once, make it at least once or twice a week and eat.
I will remember it well.
♫  The fuzzy world seen though eyeglasses  ♫
Wait a minute.
Yes, it's Yoon Jae Gook.
Yes, I will do that.
Yes.
Who is it? What are you going to do?
It's the real estate agent.
I was to use it only for two months while it stayed vacant.
But?
It seems that there is someone who wants to move in.
I'll have to move out next month.
But you will continue it until next month.
Yes.
♫  When the one star in my small room goes out  ♫
♫  Stay my shiny dreams  ♫
- Isn't it a bit spicy?
- It's not spicy at all.
It's delicious.
Should I try the soup first?
This one is the most delicious.
It's totally delicious.
You made it and you say it's delicious.
- It's delicious.
- How do you cook so well?
- If you don't have anything else to do later on, you should open up a restaurant.
- Should I?
- I think it would be great.
- Then should I really open one?
Yes!
It looks delicious.
Let's see.
What about my meal?
We are strangers now. Why should I make food for another man?
You're pulling a power move over mere rice?
Mere rice? Then you make it and eat it.
I'll do it. I'll do it! You're so cheap. I will make it.
If I wash the rice and set it, the cooker will do everything. Aigoo...
Go ahead.
Aigoo...
You sure are being noisy for making rice.
Will you be able to eat before your seventieth birthday?
Yeah.
Let's go somewhere great and eat.
Try reserving at a nice place.
Call all of our classmates.
Yes, okay.
Where are all my socks? I don't have any to wear.
You were a teacher all your life,
so how can you forget everything that you learned last time?
We... are in the middle of a divorce.
Why are you asking another woman where your socks are?
Really? Are you going to be this unfair to me?
You were the one who said I had no rights to this house
because I didn't even earn 10 won.
Considering all of the times you mentioned how you earned money as your power move,
I didn't even get started!
What am I supposed to wear right now?
Should I let you borrow it? If so, it's 2,000 won.
One, two, three.
I heard that you are going to another brand.
Since they are removing Sonó, what can I do?
There was an opening at a foreign brand.
Thank you for everything.
Gosh, I can't believe they are removing a brand that's entering a Paris department store.
I'm so upset.
You are saddened too, right?
It's already been decided.
I don't want to hold on unnecessarily.
All right, I'll do my best until the shop is removed.
Okay, thank you.
Shall we look at it?
Pin it up here so it looks more casual.
- Yes, that much.
- Is that okay?
- Is this as tight as it can go around the waist in the back?
- Ah, the back? I'll pin it a bit more.
Yes, please pin it a little more.
Congratulations, Ha Yeong Eun.
I thought you were very reckless.
It was clearly an impossible task, yet you jumped into it.
Selling our clothes and getting our name out in foreign countries...
That's not why I did it.
We wanted to shatter the idea of it being impossible,
and we wanted to show the people who said it was impossible
that their fixed idea was wrong.
Do you think that you've succeeded?
Somewhat.
This outcome may not last long.
But still, you called me back.
We didn't have to voluntarily pay an increased commission
or come with our heads already bowed.
The Hills reached out to us first
and that is enough as a result of my risk taking.
If the outcome isn't good during the next season,
contract renewal will be brought up again.
Please take anything related to contract renewal officially to our business team.
Ha Yeong Eun, can you let Jae Gook go?
You said that you loved him.
If you love him, can you let him go?
The thing about love is that there isn't just one aspect.
And I believe that holding onto someone isn't the only way to continue to love.
Oh, Mi Sook.
Ha Yeong Eun, are you busy today?
I'm on my way back after checking the display at The Hills. Why?
My lovely friend, you should take the afternoon off and have fun with me.
Right now?
Jeon Mi Sook, you are too much.
You guys always play best friends without me,
so why did you call me first this time?
Chi Sook is getting bitter. You should start quickly.
Why are you making so much kimchi?
I can't make kimchi this fall.
I also made pickles, so don't forget them on your way out.
But you guys, would it actually be a little scary
to see my kimchi and pickles staring back at you
whenever you open the refrigerator after I'm gone?
- She says those words like it's nothing.
- Yup.
I have no regrets.
I washed winter blankets and left them to dry in the sun.
I made one container of kimchi for each of you.
I received a lot of love while being alive, and I am loving back a lot as I leave.
With all  that, I think I lived an okay life, don't you?
It's Mi Sook's kimchi. What's the use in talking?
How great will it be this time?
Take a bite. See how it tastes.
How is it? Is it so delicious where you can't say anything?
Should I try it?
How is it? It's bland, isn't it?
I must've bought the wrong salted shrimp.
I kept adding it, but it's still bland.
No, no. It's not bland at all.
The doctor said that I might lose my taste due to hormonal changes.
No, it tastes good.
It tastes perfectly fine.
But who are you giving that to?
Just someone.
Do it quickly! Are you going to work all night?
How many heads of cabbage are you planning on using?
Yeah, she's happier because she's going to her grandmother's house instead of going to Taekwondo.
Don't worry about her and have fun with your friends since it has been a while.
Ji Min, say good night to Mom.
Mom, good night!
Okay, good night.
Cheers.
Man, spending time like this
makes it feel like we are on a field trip.
Your first love, our PE teacher, must be in his sixties by now.
Hey, he told me he would wait for me to graduate,
but then sent me a wedding invitation a month after.
It was a total betrayal.
That was my life's first breakup.
Life is all about farewells.
Living day by day is saying farewells day by day.
Ah, the dress shirt! What should I do?
Hey, should you be worrying about dress shirts right now?
If he doesn't have any, tell him go around naked! The  living will live on somehow.
Don't even worry about your husband.
I know... Those who are living must live.
But is she prettier than I am?
Who?
Assistant Manager Seo. Seo Min Gyeong.
Ah, Assistant Manager Seo?
Hey, what's pretty about her?
She's just a fox in hiding.
You knew about it?
Mi Sook...
Aigoo, forget it.
I'm fine.
I'm fine, so both of you... don't say anything.
Wow, really!
Hey! What do you mean by "don't say anything"?
I held it in thinking of you.
If it were up to me, I would rip him apart and it wouldn't satisfy enough.
How are you like this even though you already knew about it?
Are you Buddha? Are you a bodhisattva?
Soo Ho just turned 36.
His future is still promising.
Should I ask him to live just thinking of me after I'm gone?
Ah, you're right. It is upsetting.
But it's also a relief.
Because it's someone that I know.
Because she seems like a good person.
Hey, there's no need to look at me like that.
Those who are living must live. What can I do?
Hey, talk about yourself.
Tell me about your dating life. Is it going well?
Ah, seriously... I'm so upset.
What do you mean by that, Cookie?
Saying that you won't extend your contract with our Vision PR, what kind of unannounced farewell is this?
You said that I could terminate whenever I wanted,
so don't hold me legally responsible.
Why? Did someone ask to sign a contract with you?
Who is it? Where is it?
I got an offer from Paris.
What kind of offer?
The photography association there wants to hold an exhibition.
An exhibition? Really? Wow!
You are finally doing the exhibition that you wanted, huh?
So when are you starting the project?
No, when are you coming back after you are done?
Hey man, did you perhaps...?
I've decided to break up with that person.
Are you okay?
I'm not okay.
I'm saying so many farewells, Mi Sook.
My mother, my father,
and that person too.
It's okay.
I can endure everything.
But, Mi Sook,
how can I part ways with you?
How can I let you go?
How can I...
let you go alone?
Ah, you wench...
But I am also really afraid...
Yeong Eun, I am very, very afraid...
I wouldn't have known if we didn't break up.
How precious these moments are.
How limited our time is.
Aren't you going around a lot?
Since it's morning rush hour, there's probably a lot of traffic.
What if you are late?
- Then I'll just be late.
- What?
What are you doing today?
I'm planning to arrange my Paris schedule.
You are going to Paris?
Paris, Marseille, Nice, Alsace.
I got an offer to work on a project while traveling around the major cities.
You are going to all those places?
Just hearing about it makes me envious.
What about you?
Today, Nouvelle Vague said that they would send their questionnaire.
I'll be adjusting them and putting my house up for sale... Well, about that much.
Are you moving?
I'm planning to do so.
You can hang out with me in the evening, right?
I should set aside that time.
As if nothing happened...
As if we are okay...
I am going out to face
a breakup.
Team Leader.
Did you get the Nouvelle Vague questionnaire?
Yes.
Daebak! Is Sonó's name finally going into the Nouvelle Vague?
I'm so deeply moved, Team Leader.
But what's wrong?
Did something go wrong?
I will not participate in this interview.
I think you already know the reason.
I can't say ... What part did you not like about it?
"How did you feel when you were acknowledged by the world's trendsetter, Olivier?"
That is a general question that people want to know about.
"What do you think is the reason you were acknowledged by Olivier?"
It's a question that the subscribers would be curious about.
"Did you have Olivier in mind when advancing into Paris?"
Was that not it?
"Are you expecting a recruitment offer from Olivier?"
As would everyone.
There aren't any questions about Sonó.
You want to question me about how great a person Olivier is
and how much of an honor it was that he nodded once in approval.
I'm saying that I don't want to hop on a bandwagon to praise Olivier.
Even if I ask about Sonó,
what subscriber would be interested in that?
Nouvelle Vague only covers luxury brands, and that's our career.
And Sonó is like an innerwear that helps show off the luxury brand?
Or would you want to pay 6 million won per page, a total of 36 million won?
I am aware that you must be excited from the success of the buyers show.
But a chance that you may or may not have ever again in your life...
Are you just going to let it go?
What opportunity?
It's written in Korean on a magazine that Koreans read,
but we're throwing English words around since it's used globally
and standing as a side-kick to advertise another country's luxury brand. Is that an opportunity?
That's still the place for domestic brands right now.
Just because our place is in the back,
it doesn't mean our value is also in the back.
I don't want to bow down to be published in a magazine that doesn't recognize that.
Please excuse that I am leaving first.
What kind of person is Ha Yeong Eun?
A person that I envy?
There is a woman that you envy?
For a very long time.
But then again, I acknowledge her this time.
So you're saying that Shin Yoo Jeong acknowledges her...
I'm getting more and more curious.
Since the work I needed to do today was finished so quickly, I'm going to leave work right now.
What should I do?
I still have one more appointment.
Do it. I'll wait.
Hello, I made an appointment yesterday.
You said that you wanted to take a passport photo, right?
You can check your look before we start.
Turn your head just a little.
Yes, good! One, two!
Lower your chin a bit. Yes, good.
Your call could not be connected...
What is this girl thinking?
You turned it down? Why?
It's a global fashion magazine!
Other people spend their lives dreaming of this, so what are you doing?
Hey! Ha Yeong Eun!
Yes, good. One, two, good!
One, two... yes, good.
Mr. J, we hope to receive a call from you once you have reserved your plane ticket. (in French)
We are waiting for your response ASAP. (in French)
Hello?
Hello, Assistant Manager Seo. This is Ji Min's mom.
Hello, madam.
You worked so hard taking care of Ji Min that day,
but I feel like I didn't thank you properly.
No need to thank me. It wasn't difficult at all.
Do you happen to buy and eat kimchi?
I made too much kimchi this time.
If it's all right with you, I was going to ask if you would share it with me.
Kimchi?
Then please send some through the senior manager.
Since he's someone who really doesn't like doing that kind of thing...
If it's not too much of a hassle, would you like to come over for a bit?
I would also like to have a cup of tea with you.
Okay.
My wife did?
Since she's giving it with good intentions, I couldn't say no.
I said that I would go.
She didn't say anything else?
Nothing else.
Since the pictures taken at the show have come out,
I'll deliver those at the same time.
Rejecting her would be stranger.
Don't talk about anything else.
Don't worry too much, Senior Manager.
The only employee who would ignore the director's message is you.
If you weren't my friend, I would just–
What the heck?
Why out of nowhere?
Noona, how are you?
Noona, I can't forget you.
Why are you telling me about your situation? Screw off.
CEO Seok, what are you doing?
We want to appoint you as the honorary chairman.
What? Is that true?
Yes, ma'am. The board of directors...
Goodness, either watch the drama or listen to music!
Just pick one. It's too loud!
It's the washing machine calling for you saying that your socks are done.
It's been over seven years since we bought that washing machine,
and you're only hearing it now?
I'm looking forward to seeing how that laundry turned out.
Turn out? All you have to do is put in water and detergent.
You didn't tell me I had to separate them first!
Do you study while mixing Korean and English books?
Say something!
Being honorary chairman
and giving up all of your stocks...
Since you're a smart teacher, figure it out on your own.
Is this a purple pattern or a white pattern?
Please tell me that at least.
Then will you give me this house?
Don't then! Don't tell me! Don't tell me!
Is it fun for you to punish me like this?
If this is punishment, have I been living while being punished for 40 years?
I understand, but this isn't it.
It's not a punishment.
This is your life from now on.
I am your wife.
What?
Your inheritance is my inheritance.
My opinion...
Noona! Noona!
Noona...
Have you not realized that I have been rejecting you?
I want to clear up your misunderstanding.
So soon? Why didn't you start next year?
From now on, that will never happen again.
My heart is so weak that I couldn't overlook a person with nowhere to go.
I'm not even curious anymore.
Noona, let's start again.
I heard that you have no work. Is that why you came?
I don't participate in worldly love like that.
How could love be that way?
How could something else get between us?
Are you shooting a movie alone? If you're done, I'm leaving.
Give me a chance.
I'll treat your wounded soul.
It's all healed. I have a man.
There's no way...
There's no way, you say?
Who are you?
My boyfriend.
Since you've seen him yourself, I don't need to explain anymore, do I?
- Let's go, CEO Seok.
- Okay.
He is a CEO?
Tomorrow?
I've never had a chance to take photos of scenery like this.
I see...
But don't your legs hurt?
It seems like we have walked quite a lot.
When going home or to work,
I always passed by this road.
But... I think this is the first time I've tried walking it.
In the spring, I think of what will be trendy in the coming fall
and what I should make.
In the fall, I wonder if spring will come early next year, and what colors I should choose.
Doing that, I never once got to live through the actual seasons for myself.
I guess this season smells like this.
I'm glad that I have today as a memory.
On this day next year and the year after,
or on this day any year after, if I ever walk on a road like this,
I'll think of this.
Of today, of us.
Is Jae Gook late today?
He likely will be. He said he was going to the suburbs to take photos.
Is that right?
Wow, your cooking is just–
Does it suit your taste?
It must be nice to be Jae Gook.
Before leaving for Paris, he gets to eat his mother's cooking to his heart's content.
He's going... to Paris?
You didn't know?
Have a good shoot tomorrow.
I'm sorry that I can't leave for work with you.
If you have a shoot tomorrow, there must be a lot to prepare.
Hurry and go home.
After I watch you go inside first.
Let's go together tomorrow.
I want to be with you.
♫  Lean on me for a bit and close your eyes  ♫
♫  Don't worry about anything  ♫
♫  Don't look back on the days that have passed  ♫
♫  Let them go now  ♫
♫  Let's talk each night like we did today  ♫
- This is pretty.
- It is, right?
I think the background scenery is really pretty.
You take pictures well.
You took this well.
♫  When we are together, there are more things to laugh about  ♫
I asked to break up first,
but I keep losing confidence.
It's not the end, Yeong Eun.
Even though they are not beside you, their memory remains.
Nobody can stay
by your side forever, Yeong Eun.
♫  Fall asleep peacefully  ♫
I'm sorry.
The person you are trying to reach is not available. Your call has been forward to an automated voice message system.
Please leave a message after the tone.
This is your first time drinking with me, right?
Yes, it is.
Since I have something to say, I asked to have a drink with you.
It is a secret as well.
If you mean, a secret...
Chi Sook also must not know about it.
After seeing you change Chi Sook,
I saw you in a different light.
Thank you.
So I'm planning to offer you a partnership with The One.
You had the capacity to hold a successful buyers show and advance Sonó to Paris.
I would like you to take over promotions for not just Sonó but also the men's clothing line
and all of the other brands under The One.
Are you sure?
Since marketing is your specialty, I will entrust it to you.
How about a 15% increase from our current contractual fees?
You are offering such a steep raise. Thank you.
- Here!
- Okay.
By the way, is it going well with Chi Sook?
I believe that she opened her heart fully to me.
Last time, I didn't have a car.
She personally came to my house and drove me to work.
I will support you from the back, so do your best.
Thank you!
Yes, come in.
The meal is coming in.
Yes, thank you.
I will pour you a cup.
Ah, yes.
You've worked hard.
Senior Manager, I think you need to come see this.
What is it?
An email just came from DPHP.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. Take the call.
Ah, yes. Then I will just check my company email.
This is the email that came from Olivier just now.
It's regarding the recruitment of Team Leader Ha Yeong Eun.
Recruitment?
It seems that Olivier wants to officially recruit Team Leader Ha Yeong Eun,
and he is asking Vision PR to help with the process.
What are you talking about all of a sudden?
This is so out of the blue, out of nowhere.
I'm saying that I'm the only man who truly loves you.
Other men? They just love your background.
It's not "I love you,"
but "I love money."
Crazy guy. What are you talking about all of a sudden?
You aren't going to tell me directly?
How is your schedule tomorrow?
It's been a while, so I want to be alone with you.
This little...!
I will pour you a glass.
What do you mean by recruitment? Recruit whom?
Who is it?
Ah, you see, this is regarding my business affairs.
Does it perhaps involve our company as well?
Did someone ask you to poach someone from our company?
Who is it?
No... that's not it.
Is it Yeong Eun?!
Another day is passing.
When are you going to Paris?
Perhaps... soon.
A gift.
So you can use a new bag from now on.
It's a really good one.
I scrapped even my soul for it.
This isn't a farewell gift.
It's a gift to congratulate you on your new start.
I wish the best for the work you have in Paris.
You really... don't want to go with me?
I thought good-byes... hurt endlessly.
But during the last couple of days, I was very happy multiple times.
Perhaps breaking up might be a time given
to realize how much you love one another.
If perhaps we are given
a coincidence-like fate once again,
I won't make an excuse then.
I will insist that it is fate.
Okay.
When that happens,
make sure you do that.
♫  I miss you  ♫
♫  Both the season of youth and the warm wind  ♫
Then, I too will...
never let you go.
♫  Because you're not here  ♫
♫  To clear my head  ♫
♫  When I keep aimlessly wandering the streets  ♫
♫  Without being aware, I'm here in front of your house  ♫
The person you are trying to reach is not available. Your call has been forward to an automated voice message system.
Please leave a message after the tone.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by
Are You The One Team @ Viki
Hello?
♫  Both the season of youth and the warm wind  ♫
♫  Don't mean anything  ♫
♫  Because you're not here  ♫
♫  To clear my head  ♫
♫  When I keep aimlessly wandering the streets  ♫
♫  Without being aware, I'm here in front of your house  ♫
♫  At first, I was calmer than I thought I would be  ♫
To be honest, I bought a plane ticket.
- When is it?
- Jae Gook will go to Paris.
That's the correct choice for him.
Just once... I want to grab her just once.
If I don't, I'll go crazy.
This is Olivier's official offer.
I heard that you came up with the name Sonó yourself.
I didn't come up with it.
A no name photographer in Paris came up with it for me.
Sonó was started because of that no name photographer.
I will ask you once more.
♫  Survive like this  ♫
♫  I couldn't let you go  ♫