=Yummy Yummy Yummy=
=Episode 11=
Taste again.
- No way.
- Yeah.
How could pork be cooked
to taste like this?
I've tried for days,
and I just can't do it.
You good-for-nothings.
You can't even copy it right.
What are you doing?
Are you asking for a beating?
Mr. Lu.
Mr. Lu. Mr. Lu is here.
(Yunlai Ledger)
(Lu Yun, owner of Yunlai Tavern)
After a fierce battle,
we failed to crush the Shen family
and suffered a significant loss.
They've made a comeback,
and you have no new strategies at all.
I...
You have seven days
to shut Shen's Diner down,
or you'll be kicked out of Yunlai.
Yes, yes.
(Shen's Diner)
Fengxia.
Wait, wait.
There are some things
that haven't been made clear.
I think it's necessary
to clarify them.
As the Best Chef
in Juxian,
I was busy
with my career before
and neglected your feelings.
That was my fault.
But you have to remember:
I'll never forgive you
when I'm successful.
When we first came to Yong'an,
you pawned your gold ring
just to make ends meet.
It's okay.
I bought you a new one.
Why not try it on?
Hold out your hand.
Hurry.
With such a big ring...
Look at you.
This is the middle finger.
Oh, the middle finger.
Right.
How odd. This is the size
we bought when we got married.
Enough, stop it.
It hurts.
You didn't expect that, did you?
Think about it.
How much work have I done these years?
My fingers must have gotten thicker.
No way.
It must be the jeweler
who made a mistake.
I'll go to him tomorrow
and get it changed.
But that's a minor issue.
Don't worry about it.
The key point is
that your husband is now a man
who can make a lot of money on his own.
From now on,
just follow me
and live a good life.
Mind your temper.
Enough, Best Chef in Juxian,
get back to work.
What's wrong now?
Your attitude is off again.
I used to be poor
and couldn't buy you gifts,
so I understood you were mad at me.
Now that I have money
and can buy you gifts,
you're still mad at me.
Listen.
The Culinary Master Competition
is coming soon.
If I win first place
in the competition,
I'll be the Best Chef in Yong'an.
I'll be a big shot.
Yes.
You've changed already.
Back then, you at least helped me
with some chores
and handled the ingredients.
Now, all you do is brag,
calling yourself the best chef.
Aren't you ashamed?
Aren't I helping you?
I'm just too busy.
I'm busy with my career.
Besides,
my social status
and influence
have improved a lot.
This diner
depends entirely on me.
Without me,
this diner...
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
Social influence?
The diner depends on you?
How can you even say that?
Shen Jianshe,
is this your true nature,
or is it just because you've never had
a stage to show off before?
It's because I've never had a stage.
If I had one,
I would've made it big long ago.
I'll make you famous right now.
Famous, huh?
Why kick me?
Hurry up and cook.
- How did this happen?
- Always like this.
No, no.
What happened to him?
- Is he okay?
- What's wrong with you?
Sir, sir.
- What's going on?
- Are you okay?
- Sir.
- What's wrong?
Let me help you up.
- Get up.
- Slowly.
Come on, slowly.
Brother.
- Is it a stomachache?
- Are you okay?
Don't scare me.
Are you okay?
- What's wrong?
- Brother.
- Are you okay?
What's wrong with you?
Gongcai.
Go call a carriage.
Deyuan, take him to the clinic.
Sure.
- Get up.
- Come on.
Jicai,
I think this
is food poisoning.
Your food is unclean.
I'm going to report you.
(Princess Fuhui's Mansion)
Vice Prefect, this way, please.
After the Qixi Poetry Gathering,
all the factions
have sent their visit letters
to the Princess,
and she refused them all
but ours.
But I'm increasingly feeling
that something is off.
We want to find out something
from the Princess,
and perhaps she also wants to know
something from us.
Let's just wait and see.
I thought you'd have
to engage in a long game with me
before getting to the point.
You're wise.
Why should I beat around the bush?
Over the past ten years,
the position of Prefect
has changed hands 16 times,
with the longest tenure being two years.
Naturally,
I want to seek advice from you.
It's not just a recent thing.
Who
doesn't want power?
What about the case of selling
official positions 17 years ago?
Prefect Cui Ning
didn't gain a single benefit
and lost his entire family's lives.
The case has become a solid verdict,
but the real beneficiary
walked away unscathed.
Now,
he might still be hiding in court.
Judging from your words,
you seem to think
that there's more to that case.
It's just a guess.
I'm not interested in meddling in that.
But you don't need to worry.
Even if there's any trouble,
I'll be on your side.
With someone protecting you,
you have nothing to fear.
Thank you for your favor.
(Pavilion of Jade
in the Fairy Mountains)
Favor?
The word you just used
is quite apt.
Newcomers who are favored in court
- Your Highness.
- are indeed
more endearing than those old-timers.
Anran,
I feel
that I really hit it off with you.
From now on,
you should visit me more often.
Your Highness...
You can even bring friends
along.
Your Highness.
Your Highness,
someone from the Prefecture
needs the Vice Prefect urgently.
What's the matter?
Your Highness.
Vice Prefect,
someone got poisoned at Shen's Diner.
It's crowded there.
You've harmed my brother.
Today,
I'm going to shut down this place.
- Don't you dare come near.
- We'll investigate.
Listen to me.
Before we get to the bottom of this,
don't be impulsive.
Think twice.
My brother is still in bed.
His life is hanging by a thread.
And I can't be impulsive?
Guys,
smash this place.
Smash it.
Don't come near us.
Move.
Stop them.
Stop them, stop them.
Back off.
Listen.
Don't be impulsive.
The case is not yet concluded.
If anyone dares to move,
they will be treated as a mob.
Do you hear me?
Whoever causes trouble
will go to jail.
Officials,
you have to do justice for us.
The Prefecture officials have arrived.
Good.
Shen's Diner caused poisoning.
The owners should be imprisoned.
Yes, imprison them.
Do you have any evidence?
You don't have any evidence.
You're just talking nonsense.
I've heard it before.
Your family is related
to Vice Prefect Lin.
Right?
No wonder this evil shop
has been able to stay open,
and you've never been imprisoned.
As it turns out,
Prefect Lin has been protecting them.
Yes.
He's been protecting them.
The truth is not yet clear.
Why arrest us?
You don't want to find out the truth.
You keep shouting to shut us down.
There must be someone behind you.
Yes, someone is behind you.
My brother was poisoned at your place,
and you're slandering me?
He's lying.
I'll fight with you.
Grandpa!
Are you okay?
You all saw it.
They're trying to kill me.
Are you alright?
Get out of the way.
They want to kill me.
I might as well die.
- Let me see.
- Every inch of my flesh
has been bitten to shreds by him.
They've harmed so many people,
and now they want to kill me
right in front of everyone.
Look at this; it's serious.
This is really bad.
Look at how badly you've bitten him.
Look at the bites.
Grandpa's flesh is gone.
Why just stand there?
Smash this diner. Smash it.
How dare you!
Stop them.
Stop them!
Keep shouting.
It hurts!
Stop.
They're going to kill me, too.
The Vice Prefect is coming.
Hurry, the ancestor is coming.
He'll definitely be on our side.
Finally here.
Get up.
It's okay now.
Though you have
a relative in court,
you still can't twist the truth.
Everyone saw it.
They're bullying us with power.
Stop talking nonsense.
Who can do justice to my brother?
- My brother.
- Stop shouting.
You have to trust the Prefecture.
Yes.
Mr. Lin has always been upright.
He won't cover for them.
Exactly.
Since they are relatives,
he should recuse himself from this.
- Recuse yourself.
- Vice Prefect.
You must recuse yourself.
Yes, you must recuse yourself.
You can't be involved.
My brother...
Seal the diner
for investigation.
Vice Prefect, how can you
seal our diner?
- Vice Prefect.
- No.
Vice Prefect.
- Why seal our diner?
- Vice Prefect.
Vice Prefect.
(Sealed by the Prefecture,
25th of the 7th month)
Bear with it.
Such an old villain.
Why did he
have to bite here?
This place is
where you usually pinch me.
It's a sacred ground.
It's a protected area.
Why did he bite it?
Why are you still so flippant?
At a time like this,
you're still making jokes.
- It's done.
- It's done?
- Put it down.
- Alright.
No wonder the ancestor
agreed to break off the engagement
so readily before.
He was just afraid we'd drag him down
and wanted to get rid of us asap.
Let me say something unpleasant.
At his age,
in this era,
he's definitely
a super old bachelor.
We did him a favor
by giving him a betrothal.
Doesn't he know it?
And yet...
Enough.
I've told you so many times
not to bring it up again.
Just let it go.
Why keep mentioning it?
Dear,
let me say something.
If I'm wrong,
you can criticize me.
I think what Gong Cai said is right.
Isn't it?
Things haven't been clarified yet,
and he sealed our diner right away.
As an ancestor,
for the sake of his career,
he just ignores his descendants
and stands by.
Is that appropriate?
Has the ancestor really abandoned us?
Without finding out the truth,
he pasted such a big seal on the door.
That's his way of standing by us.
He meddles in everything.
Enough. We can't just
count on his help.
He's helped us enough.
We're still living in his house.
Still, he can't seal the diner.
Didn't we want to stand
on our own in Yong'an?
We can't just rely on him.
I think Jicai is right.
Mountains can collapse,
and the ancestor can leave us.
We can't always rely on luck.
This time,
we have to rely on ourselves
to get through this.
Dear, you're right.
We have to rely on ourselves.
I've also discovered something.
Well.
You see,
the first man to report us
and the man who said
that we are related to the ancestor
is the same man.
The very villain who bit me.
I can't help but feel
that he caused trouble with a purpose.
He must've been sent by Yunlai.
They stand to gain the most.
Unable to copy our pork dishes
or beat us,
they resorted to underhanded tactics.
Folks,
in this battle to defend our diner,
we must take the initiative.
My brother has been vomiting all night.
Physician, you must save him.
What's going on?
How could a Shen also get poisoned?
The physician has gone in.
- It seems serious.
- Lady Deyuan,
what happened
to Mr. Shen?
Don't even mention it.
We are not like Yunlai Tavern.
We eat the same meals
that we serve to our guests.
That's why Mr. Shen was poisoned.
Poisoned?
Did Mr. Shen really get poisoned
by the food from your own diner?
He was truly poisoned.
It was terrifying.
After eating,
he vomited,
had diarrhea,
and then fainted.
- Let's do it here.
- Okay.
Hold on tight.
- Don't let me fall.
- Okay.
Someone's coming there.
Don't stop me.
Let me go.
- Don't do this.
- Let me die.
Don't be impulsive.
What's wrong?
If there was a problem with our food,
how could I let my son eat it?
My son is almost dead from poisoning.
The poisoner must be someone else.
Don't do this.
We must live to clear our name.
We're innocent.
(Help me)
Please do justice for me.
(Wronged)
I am innocent.
Folks,
our food was somehow poisoned.
My son is now
(Wronged)
barely clinging to life.
He's on the brink of death.
Folks,
you must've seen wrong cases.
Have you seen one worse than this?
I am utterly wronged.
(Help me)
Folks.
Do justice for me.
(Wronged)
I'm innocent.
(Shen's Diner)
My brother is weak from poisoning
and can't catch a cold.
How can he see you now?
(Sealed by the Prefecture)
Lady Shen.
Everyone is saying
that Mr. Shen has also been poisoned.
Let us take a look.
We will surely find out the truth
and clear your name asap.
Please do us a favor.
My father has just died.
We barely managed to bring him back.
If you let him catch a cold,
he will die for sure.
Who died?
Shen Yangyang, I'm your father!
Lady Shen,
let us take a quick look inside.
I'll definitely find the poisoner.
Just one look.
We'll be quick.
We'll find out the truth ourselves.
We don't need you anyway.
You're making things hard for me.
Leave this to me.
- Vice Prefect.
- Leave us.
- Auntie.
- Okay.
Your brother
is not poisoned, right?
Without asking anything,
you sealed our shop,
and now you're trying to probe?
Isn't it too hasty to build
a righteous reputation
at the cost of our family?
You're too bad.
I don't want to talk to you anymore.
Vice Prefect, please leave.
It's not like that, Shaoguang.
Lady Shen,
the only way to make the poisoner
let their guard down
was to seal the diner first.
During this time,
I have found some clues.
What were the symptoms
of the poisoned diners?
Mostly vomiting and dizziness.
Some even said they saw
little people jumping.
It looks like mushroom poisoning.
I asked the merchants in West Market
who sold you mushrooms.
They confessed
that the steward of Yunlai Tavern
had approached them several times.
Everyone in West Market
does business by the rules.
There shouldn't be any problem.
It's probably that steward from Yunlai.
He found out which mushrooms
were supplied to us
and secretly replaced them
with poisonous ones.
That's also my guess.
But for now,
we don't have any evidence.
Vice Prefect,
we were wrong
about you before.
We thought you
only cared about your own reputation
and just left us alone.
We're really sorry.
Come on, hurry up.
On behalf of my whole family,
I'll apologize
to the Vice Prefect
who has been doing good deeds
for generations.
- Sorry.
Vice Prefect.
- We were wrong about you.
- No.
We were wrong about you.
It's not necessary.
I should've explained
from the beginning.
It was my oversight.
No, no.
How could you have an oversight?
All these mistakes
are mine.
I was too impulsive.
I even cursed you behind your back.
I really deserve to be punished.
Shen,
you cursed me behind my back?
I...
Did I?
Everyone, please sit down.
So, what should we do next?
Right.
The ancients are superstitious.
Actually, we should...
No.
As the ancients said,
people in Yong'an are superstitious.
Right? Look.
I'm pretending to be ill anyway.
Why don't I just fake my death?
You can dress up as ghosts
to scare that steward
and get him to talk.
When did the ancients ever say
that people in Yong'an
are superstitious?
It might actually work.
Manager Feng is very fond
of believing in mysteries
and fortune-telling, right?
There are indeed many shrines
in Yunlai Tavern.
And I often see Manager Feng
casting moon blocks with the steward.
If they believe in ghosts and spirits,
it might be worth a try.
Auntie,
you look so ghostly.
You really do.
It's done.
Be extra careful.
Don't worry.
Deyuan and I have rehearsed
several times in Yunshui Manor.
I'm very familiar with it.
Be careful.
Go for it, Auntie.
Someone's coming.
Are you alright?
Thank you.
Wow, there really is such a thing
as lightness skills in this world.
Vice Prefect,
how did you just fly up?
Can you take me for a spin?
What spin?
We haven't finished our business yet.
Go for it, Auntie.
Be careful.
We still have things to do.
Don't hurt yourself.
Wait.
Be careful.
(Yunlai)
Who?
Who's there?
Why did you poison me?
You killed
Handsome Shen!
Who did it?
Tell us the truth,
or
we'll die together.
It wasn't me.
Manager Feng ordered it.
I didn't want to kill anyone.
(Capital Prefecture)
Silence.
Steward Liu Mo,
poisoning people with mushrooms,
violated the law.
(Cao Rong, Ministry of Justice)
You turned yourself in,
so you get three years of labor.
The principal offender, Feng Li,
has fled out of fear of punishment.
A wanted notice should be issued.
It's now been proven
that Shen's Diner was framed
and did not intentionally
serve poisonous mushrooms.
It'll be unsealed immediately.
Thank you, Vice Minister Cao.
Court dismissed.
Vice Minister Cao
from the Ministry of Justice acted
as the Inspector to adjudicate
the case in the Prefecture.
He's known for his integrity
and impartiality.
He'd never cover for the Shens.
I knew the Shens were innocent.
Vice Prefect,
thank you for your help.
Why offer incense
to thank me?
It's a custom from our hometown.
You've done us such a great favor.
You deserve any thanks we can give.
Sorry about that, sorry.
Master,
please accept me as your disciple.
I want to learn lightness skills
from you.
What are you doing?
Get up, get up.
This is all from the drama
I watched with Grandma.
I should do this to get myself a master.
Master,
please accept me as your disciple.
If you refuse,
I'll just keep kneeling.
I won't get up.
I'll even roll on the ground.
- Yangyang.
- What drama?
Yangyang.
Get up.
How can you
take the Vice Prefect as your master?
If you take him as your master,
what about your seniority?
Isn't that right?
Agate Meat.
That's right.
If Mr. Lin is Yangyang's master,
she'll be only below him.
I'm the father of Mr. Lin's disciple,
so you all
should offer me some incense, too.
Alright, stop joking around,
or the food will get cold.
Everyone, take your seats and eat.
Vice Prefect, take a seat.
- Right, let's eat.
- Come on.
Mr. Lin, would you like some rice?
- Here.
- Okay.
- Have some meat.
- Vice Prefect.
- Serve him a piece.
- Here's a lamb chop.
I stewed it.
Thank you.
Here, let me serve you a piece.
I want to learn lightness skills.
Yangyang,
eat first.
I'll teach you after the meal.
Okay.
Vice Prefect, have some of this.
It's very delicious.
Shen, that's enough.
- This.
- Have some greens, Yangyang.
- I made this.
- Thanks.
Come on.
Hurry up and eat.
Master, hurry up.
Master,
I want to learn lightness skills.
I want to fly up to that pavilion.
Come on.
Ancestor, let me down.
Ancestor.
Let me down.
Auntie, save me.
Ancestor.
Let me down.
Auntie.
Yangyang, what did you just call me?
Ancestor?
It's an exclamation word
from our hometown.
When someone is very scared
or excited,
they shout "Ancestor".
You are getting used
to talking nonsense.
Didn't you want
to learn lightness skills?
Why are you scared now?
I forgot.
I got vertigo
from my father.
Yangyang,
you won't be afraid
if you try a few more times.
Do you want to try again?
No.
I'll go wash the dishes.
She just chickens out.
Washing the dishes?
The only thing she knows
how to wash is herself.
But Vice Prefect,
what did it feel like
when you used that lightness skill?
Lady Shen?
You were trying to scare me.
How could I?
I thought you were curious
about the lightness skill.
Clearly not.
Alright.
After all, I thought
you abandoned us for your career.
It's my fault.
How could it be because of that?
Then why?
(Letter of Engagement Dissolution)
Forget it.
I was being petty.
Please don't take it to heart.
How could you be petty?
As the dignified Vice Prefect,
how could you be petty?
The curfew-lifted Yong'an
is just as beautiful
as our hometown.
You always mention your hometown,
as if compared to Yong'an,
you still prefer that place.
Each place has its own merits.
But in our place, everyone is equal.
Life is convenient.
And there's no curfew.
There's more freedom.
Marriages and funerals
are all based on personal will.
These things are indeed better.
You once said
your hometown wasn't Qingyang,
and you met my parents
after you moved to Qingyang.
So, where exactly
is your hometown?
Why is it governed that way?
It's called Future Village,
a very remote place.
You might not have heard of it.
Future Village?
A place that has yet to arrive.
You're so good at making things up
that even Zhuangzi would consider you
a kindred spirit.
How sophisticated the way you insult me.
If I hadn't read a few books,
I wouldn't have understood.
But I'm not making it up.
It just needs
another thousand years or so
for you to see
the Future Village
where everyone is equal.
Indeed,
equality can only be achieved
when there is an abundance of resources.
It's impossible now.
But if we expand farmlands and markets
and make the people
materially and spiritually satisfied,
so that we can live at ease,
free from illicit acts.
Then we might get a little closer
to the Future Village you described.
I'm surprised you understand this.
The economic base
determines the superstructure.
I've never heard of this before.
The economic base
determines the superstructure?
That's really interesting.
You understand this sentence?
You are truly ahead of your time.
I never thought
that someone in this era
could understand this.
When my father became the Prefect,
my family moved to the Capital.
Soon, he was charged
with selling official positions,
implicating our clan.
Liu Chang and I barely escaped
with our lives.
But my parents and everyone else...
Though we were not officially engaged,
this must have affected you as well.
Life back in your hometown
must've been hard.
That must be why you didn't want
to tell me the real situation back then
and made up the Future Village.
I can understand that.
It's alright.
It's all in the past.
Now, it's us
who are troubling you.
You've gone through so much hardship.
I'll definitely
pay more respects to you.
In the past, during festivals,
I was indeed not very sensible.
Pay respects?
I'll attend to you.
Among friends,
that's not necessary.
Didn't you say before
that you don't make friends?
People can change.
So, we are friends now.
Let's do this.
In the Future Village,
friends shake hands.
Shake hands?
So beautiful.
Though I still miss my hometown,
after going through
these things recently,
I seem to like it here more and more.
During the Lantern Festival,
there is no curfew.
The city with lights
will be even more beautiful.
Then,
I will take you to see it again.
Really?
Thank you. You're so kind.
(Shaoguang's Food Notes)
(Why not eat pork?)
(The people of Yong'an are stubborn.)
(Lamb is the best in the world.)
(Pork can never be on the table.)
(Before,
pork could only be steamed,)
(boiled, and roasted.)
(Even the slightest mistake in breeding,
slaughtering, and deodorizing)
(can ruin the taste.)
(But I want the people of Yong'an)
(to easily enjoy delicious meat,)
(so pork is something I can start with.)
♪Wear a sunset glow upon the brow♪
♪Breeze sways,
wind chimes hang below the cloud♪
♪Hear one chime ring,
tugging at the heart♪
♪True feelings perhaps
can only be sensed♪
♪Misty is you, clear is you♪
♪Seeking stars in fog,
seeing your shadow under the moon♪
♪Words held back, feelings unrestrained♪
♪Could the road ahead,
let us gaze but not doubt♪
♪Mistook all eyes see as cold ice♪
♪Yet let dusk dye
the ears and temples red♪
♪Even holding breath
couldn't help but stop♪
♪Exposing my warmed heart held tight♪
♪Bustling is you, desolate is you♪
♪Reservedly drawing you into this life♪
♪Hesitating, undecided,
the heart hard to deceive♪
♪Worldly rules and taboos,
how could they make me give up♪
♪When rushing to you,
leaving my deep thoughts in disarray♪
♪I still foolishly see it
as a good time♪
♪Heart stirs,
wind swirls the lightest ripples♪
♪A thousand tangled thoughts concealed♪
♪Saved a whole lifetime,
hastening to you, urgent over miles♪
♪To make the wandering heart
return home henceforth♪
♪To draw near what seems beyond reach♪
♪Through life and death changes,
only we never cease, never yield♪
♪Perhaps affection barely passes muster♪
♪But love forever♪
♪Will make up for our mutual care,
mutual bond♪
♪Saved a whole lifetime,
hastening to you, urgent over miles♪
♪To make the wandering heart
return home from now♪
♪To dare approach
what seems beyond reach♪
♪Through life and death changes♪
♪Only you, never cease, never yield♪