Star Media presents
Dmitry Fomenko
Sc hers
Grigoris Gonzalov
Glebov
Star Media presents
Alexei Kravchenko
Dmitriy Kravchenko
Yuliavernツ
D도r
Sergey K revive
Alexey Kravchenko
Dn6
Brk
Translated byHHH
(* Diese Pierre,FLIPODное tractionant How the inter-cathedrals unify
Jurchres Un줘-覺
Jun
and it was shaped into a Xie's stick.
The people from the West came to China.
They were told to come to our place.
It was a very unique experience.
My grandfather suggested that we should improve the Biro.
He said that after a thousand years, people will change their mind.
Maybe the taste will change.
People will forget the Biro.
But if we keep innovating,
maybe this food will be passed on.
Innovate?
Create new ideas?
This word is interesting.
It seems that your grandfather has made the Shenzhen restaurant so well.
He has not only created new food,
but also has a unique idea.
How can there be no tea in Biro?
I want to drink your tea.
I asked them to buy it.
Your Highness, let me do it.
No need.
I'll do it myself today.
Okay.
I ordered your big, dirty, and green drinks.
I told you not to mind me.
The court is in a fight with Lin Shao Ying.
She is good at boxing.
She was suspended by my brother.
What?
The court is in a fight with Lin Shao Ying.
She is good at boxing.
She was suspended by my brother.
What?
Your Highness, the Minister of Defense is here.
Minister Meng.
I came to see how you are.
You are still alive.
Don't worry.
I came from the backyard.
No one saw me.
Okay.
I'll go to the kitchen.
Nana.
Ada.
Can you tell me
what happened to the enemies
encountered by Aruhail ...
tens of thousands
But that's why they dared to stab you.
You want to persuade me to marry Mu?
But I want to marry a good son.
If Anran becomes my grandson-in-law,
he will never suffer from the whip again.
I don't want to marry a good son.
Go back.
You haven't got off work yet, but you still come to see me off.
Do you think there's too little work?
The
End
Whatever happens, we brothers will be with you.
Yes, yes, yes.
Young Master, Lady Shen is here!
Father and I made some new-tasting birch.
We're going to sell them in the shop.
Please help us with the work.
You know everything?
Young Master, the shop is closed.
Shall we go back and check the shop?
Yes.
Let's go.
Come on.
I'm afraid I'll get you involved in the case.
You've helped me a lot with the case.
Now,
you must protect yourself.
A family is in danger.
How can you not protect yourself?
Shao Ying, I have something to tell you.
That day Lu Yun set up a trap for you in Yunlai.
Someone leaked the news.
The new cook, Yu San,
is the man of King Zhao.
Yu San?
What about him?
Is everyone in your family all right?
Yu San is not a bad person.
He was forced by King Zhao.
King Zhao trapped his parents in the Wind Wailing Formation.
So he had to help King Zhao.
If we can save his parents,
he'll be willing to help us.
Wind Wailing Formation?
Can you trust Yu San?
I've been doing business for years.
I've learned to read people's minds.
I think I can.
But it's...
I trust you.
Leave the rest to me.
I'll go to Wind Wailing Formation as soon as possible.
It's raining heavily.
Lady Shen, get on the carriage.
The rain stopped suddenly.
Is it related to the case?
Is it King Zhao's brush?
I'm sorry.
I have to go back.
I forgot to tell Lady Shen.
The umbrella!
Lady Shen, the umbrella!
Thank you.
Wind Wailing Formation
Don't come here!
Father.
Father, are you dead?
Am I going to...
Am I going to turn around?
So I can see my father again?
Father...
From now on,
you are my adopted son.
You are my adopted son.
You are called...
Ye.
Yes.
Good.
You are getting better at archery.
Your Highness, you are the one who taught me how to use it.
I hope you are not disappointed.
You will never let me down.
Are you tired?
Have some tea.
Here.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Your Highness, I heard you want to move to Yongan.
I thought if I could enter the capital and make a great contribution,
I wouldn't disappoint Your Highness.
Good.
Your Highness, I gave you your name.
Do you know what it means?
I don't know.
Your Highness, I hope I can live a peaceful life.
Now the capital is in a bad shape.
How can you make me feel at ease?
I have lost my beloved son.
I don't want to lose you again.
My love.
The whole world is under my control.
Only the people my love love me.
Go song or 34 years old.
I want to ask Isla Long Que.
All right.
I will find her.
Aaahhh!
Why me?
You're too calm.
But there are things
that make you sick.
So, Young Master,
you'd better tell me
what's going on.
My Keye
is so sad.
He said
Liu Changchu and I
spread out
and sick.
He said
I need to learn fencing
when I pass away.
He looked
so upright
and taught me
that you must
He speaks correct law surely.
I know
because he did the same to me.
Li suo who fuxible as I am now
took those course in a meal.
He got the place of light and love from it.
Even the word Anran,
was prepared by him for Li Sheng.
But I still thank him.
I thank him for saving me from the flood.
For teaching me to fight the dream.
But I never thought that...
Never thought that...
That Li Sheng would be able to save me.
He took over my family.
And pretended to be my family.
Seventeen years.
He was full of immoral people.
But he caused the Cui family to be destroyed.
And the whole family was destroyed.
I don't know how many...
Innocent and innocent people were killed.
I don't know.
But I think...
Fortunately, you look like the son he cares about.
Fortunately, when you don't have the ability to protect yourself,
you were sincere to him.
And you survived.
If you found out the truth early on,
even if you can pretend,
you will suffer too much.
Once a person suffers too much,
he will lose the ability to be happy.
My family and yours,
don't want you to only get revenge.
Now you know the truth.
You have the ability to protect yourself.
And to deal with the bad guys.
This is the most worth it.
You care about me.
I care about you.
Anjie.
I will solve everything.
I will never let your family worry.
And I will never let you suffer.
When everything is settled,
I will beg you.
Okay?
It shouldn't be me.
The training center said...
Don't believe those rumors.
Just believe me.
If Anran becomes my grandson-in-law,
she will never suffer again.
Thank you, Tan.
But you have not only seen me clearly,
but also underestimated your granddaughter.
The training center is in trouble.
I have a solution.
Otherwise, I wouldn't be qualified to be the governor.
As for Shen Jingwen,
she has her own world.
You should ask her,
what she really wants.
There is a liar.
I don't have one.
I will never be friends with anyone.
Why?
I can't figure out what you are thinking.
But I know myself.
I know.
If it were you,
I would never be happy.
What about you?
Lin Yan.
Do you remember?
I told you that I come from
a place called the future.
The future has a chance.
There are many things
that are beyond this age.
You asked me why
I always say strange things
and do strange things.
That's because
my family and I
are not from this age.
We came from a thousand years ago.
If you want to reject me,
you don't have to go through
this absurd situation.
The Cloud Water House is our ancestral house.
We came here through the ancestral house.
Our ancestral house is the only one
in the world.
The only one in the world.
According to the map
that we saw in the city,
the Cloud Water House is over there.
We came from there.
We have to find a way to enter.
You are actually my fiancee!
I am lying to you.
There's no other way.
But we've failed many times.
There's no other way. We can only stay here.
And you...
We're related.
Because the Cloud Water House is your place,
it's our ancestral house.
So you're our...
Your關robe,....
Lini,
thanks for your multànも糹
when my grandfather died.
The story my grandfather told us
when he died
was just a dream.
That's why I knew you would chain me,
The white clouds are in the sky
The clouds are in the sky
It's too ridiculous
It's impossible
Do you remember the lock in the study?
Why can't you break it?
But I can open it easily
Because the lock
It comes from our time
Why can't I break it?
The lock can be opened so easily
Today I see three stars
Three stars
No, no, no
Let's go, let's go, let's go
Come on
Let's go, let's go
The future is good
It just needs to be developed for another thousand years
Then you can see the future is good
The world is good
Uh
Enough
Naive
People don't win
Then I won't kill you
Want someone to kill you
The child's health is important.
How about letting him vent his anger?
He was fine when he jumped into the pond.
He was skinny.
But his body is strong.
He needs to vent his anger.
But when he's upset, he always troubles himself.
I understand.
He was like this when mom left.
Yangyang, you're right.
That was the only time the Communist Party taught him.
Dad...
Enough. Don't worry.
I know my daughter.
Give her some time. She'll get better.
You're right.
Mr.Snowflake
Xie Mingyi.
Mr. Snowflake.
What are you looking for?
It's dirty. Let me help you.
I found it.
Tang Jun, Tang Jun, I'm listening to you.
The gold that was stolen by Lian Ritong and Zhao Xingzhi
the night before his disappearance
was set on fire.
You...
Tang Jun, are you okay?
Let's get down to business.
I invited those gold Ape to have a few drinks.
Finally, I got the answer.
After the city gate was closed,
the car that was supposed to deliver food
was out.
The city gate was open at night?
Even if it's good for the gold Ape, how dare they?
That's the point.
The car that was supposed to deliver food
had a public entrance.
It was for the benefit of the gold Ape.
No wonder the gold Ape didn't say a word.
Zhao Xingzhi must be in that car.
Hurry up!
Tang Jun ordered that
these goods must be transported to Fenglin Town tomorrow.
If the gold Ape comes, it'll be a problem.
Hurry up!
Fenglin Town again.
It seems that their destination is there.
Why did you ask me to come?
I'll go to the palace tomorrow morning.
Then I'll go to Fenglin Town.
You stay here.
Take care of the Shen Family.
Very good.
Go!
Why are you here, Mr. Shen?
I'm looking for Young Master.
Young Master is not here.
Just tell me what you need.
Actually,
Ji told us everything.
I know
that Young Master is in a bad mood
after being suspended from his post.
He also had a little problem with our Ji.
I can understand all of this.
But I can't stop
my evil business.
What should I do with my talent?
So I asked Young Master
if he had anything to do with me.
He told me that
you should take care of yourself
if he is here.
How can I do that?
I'll ask him myself.
Mr. Shen,
Young Master is not here.
If he is not here,
I'll wait for him.
Don't you know
how we worked together
when we were in the cloud?
We had a great chemistry.
We had a great feeling.
And now
the key to the case is
how can he not have me?
Young Master is not here.
So it's useless for you to wait for him.
Young Master was expelled from the capital so quickly.
Our Young Master
went to Fenglin Town.
Fenglin Town?
What a familiar name!
When Young Master went to Fenglin Town,
he went to Zhao Fu Zi and Yu San's parents.
You don't know
that I went to Fenglin Town
when I went to the martial arts.
At that time,
I was begging for food.
I was begging for life!
I walked across every inch of the land there.
So I could feel the love
and the love of the land
before I left.
I was so proud of it!
No one is more suitable than me to help him.
Before my husband left,
he was so kind to me.
He asked me to take good care of you.
How can I be like you?
How can I explain to him?
Lady Shen!
Please persuade your brother.
I have to go to Lin Ye.
Where is Zhao Xun?
It's all here.
Shao Yin!
Zhao Fu Zi!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Do you know
where they keep the others?
I heard about it.
They are in Fenglin Town.
Follow me!
Go!
Hurry up!
I didn't know you would come here.
Lu Yun, you fool!
You told me you didn't find anything.
It seems that I know you better.
Lin Ye,
I've been waiting for you here.
I've been waiting for you here
because you look like my brother.
So I let you live for a few years.
I'll kill this bastard
who was supposed to go to hell 17 years ago.
Mother,
why are you talking so much?
Who can hear the end?
I'll kill him!
He must go back to his room!
Stop!
I taught you how to use swords.
He never did this to me.
Today I'll kill you
and bring you to my father
so that he can see
your miserable death.
I'll kill you!
You're a loser!
Get out!
Slow down.
Mr. Li,
hold on a little longer, okay?
Come on.
Oh, my God.
Watch out!
Someone's here!
That's...
Mr. Li.
Young Master!
Mr. Li!
Li,
it's okay. I'm here.
It's okay.
It's okay. I'm here.
Yu San's parents
were locked up
in other places in the Fenglin Town.
Father Zhao ordered
Zheng Wu
to take them to him.
Liu Chang will be here soon.
Hold on a little longer.
He's right behind you.
Don't fall asleep.
Hold on a little longer.
Liu Chang!