=Yummy Yummy Yummy=
=Episode 8=
You can't swim.
What were you thinking, jumping in?
Before acting heroically,
could you people here
at least consider
your own safety?
I jumped in to save you!
You mustn't give up on life.
Understand?
Save me?
You thought I was trying to die?
No.
I just slipped.
No wonder.
I was wondering
how you swam back so easily.
Then I lost big time.
I risked my life
for nothing.
Lady, what were you thinking?
You can't swim, yet you jumped in.
So what?
Besides,
there was
nobody else around.
If you were suicidal
and I didn't act,
you'd really be gone.
Right?
Next time, prioritize your own safety
when saving others.
Relax.
My mother had my fortune told.
I'm blessed with nine lives.
See? Even when I rescue someone,
it's a swimmer like you.
Who saved whom here?
Obviously, I saved you.
Next time, you rescue me.
Where's the fish?
Little guy,
let's go home.
Go home.
Well...
Lady,
our tavern is nearby.
Come change out of those clothes.
You're wet,
and you may catch a chill.
Sure.
Let's go.
(Yunlai)
Lady,
we're almost there.
Here.
You're from Yunlai?
Lady, please keep your voice down.
Don't let Manager Feng hear.
Lady,
I can't bring you through the front.
This hole's big enough.
I get through it. You can, too.
Heavens.
Lady,
you're so thin.
This is my smallest outfit,
yet it's still loose on you.
Come here. Sit.
Make yourself at home. Just sit.
Let me pour you water.
If you're this skinny,
young men won't fancy you.
Never mind.
Who cares what they like?
- Liking yourself matters most.
- Thank you.
Exactly.
In this dynasty,
plump figures like yours
are considered lovely.
What's the use of beauty?
Lady, you should eat more.
At least,
you could defend yourself
if bullied.
Well...
Lady,
my mother calls me Deyuan.
What's your name?
Deyuan?
I'm Jicai.
It means shepherd's purse.
Shepherd's purse?
How funny.
Naming someone after greens!
I've an elder brother, too.
His name's Gongcai.
Gongcai...?
Gongcai means dried mustard stems.
I'm from out of town.
We call them that.
Preserved Mustard is tasty.
Lady, your family must adore food.
We're in the catering trade.
Then your cooking must surpass Yunlai's.
You've just met me.
How can you judge?
I judge Yunlai's skills
with full confidence.
Do you know why?
They can't cook.
But they slap dishes
on silver plates, golden bowls,
and secret-color porcelain.
Then they charge exorbitant prices.
It's my first time
hearing Yunlai operate this way.
Alright.
Enough about them.
They're the big earners.
Lady, where are you from?
I come from Shu.
It's wonderful there.
Fewer rules
than in Yong'an,
more freedom.
Why do you come here?
Debts.
I pressed my thumb
on a Slave Deed,
lost
my commoner status,
and became a slave.
I can't go home now.
Me too.
I can't go home either.
Lady, can't you go back home either?
You must miss home badly.
Yong'an's summer heat
is unbearable.
It's not as cool as my hometown.
Ours is hot, too,
but we've ways to cope.
Lady, have you been to Shu?
I have!
Really?
We have so many delicacies there!
(Capital Prefecture)
Hu,
it's past noon.
Shouldn't we inform
Vice Prefect Lin about lunch?
Eat your meal.
Does the dynasty's most
promising young Vice Prefect
need your concern?
- Eat up, all.
- Fine.
I'll eat.
Young Master,
let's dine.
Let them eat first.
(Yong'an)
They've started.
At court and in the palace,
none dared slight you.
Yet here, petty guys test you.
They eat without the Vice Prefect?
How disrespectful!
A junior
surpassing them
naturally breeds resentment.
But martial men wear hearts
on their sleeves,
with no hidden schemes.
Unlike those
overly polite types,
who veil treacherous currents.
How exhausting.
But you seem poised.
You've already got a plan
to handle them,
right?
Handling is pointless.
I seek
genuine respect.
Here,
I feel adrift,
with no sense of belonging.
- Hungry?
- A bit.
Shall I cook for you?
But I've nothing here.
There's some lard I rendered.
Deyuan, do you eat lard?
Doesn't this dynasty
disdain pork?
How...?
When poor,
you eat what's there.
Sheep and sows
are both my four-legged treasures.
They call pork
"rank and cheap",
so they won't touch it.
What? Does that
make them noble?
Does it raise their wages?
Deyuan,
do you have any fermented sauce?
Fermented sauce?
This afternoon,
the Vice Minister of Works
will review
the Capital road repair budgets.
Who'd like
to assist?
What's this?
Who cooked?
The rice is half-raw.
Cheng Hu.
Oh, you're Yan.
My apologies.
I took a fall recently.
Bad leg,
sore back.
I can't handle this task.
Where are your manners?
Daring to address
my Young Master by name!
So what? I called him that,
so what?
I'm a rough man.
Besides,
the Vice Prefect is
younger than me.
He could call me "Uncle".
Exactly.
Cheng Hu,
do you know my relation
to Chancellor Meng?
How dare you
demand "Uncle"!
You...
you're Chancellor Meng's...?
But Vice Prefect,
I've heard
you're not from a noble house.
True.
I'm merely privileged to serve
alongside him.
You mocked me!
Yes.
Mocked.
Had you not fawned
upon learning of my "connection",
I'd have respected you.
What a pity. You're not that man.
Is that your integrity?
I know.
You doubt my capability
due to my youth,
and you resent following me.
But consider this.
The Capital Prefecture is a hot potato.
No noble scion would take it,
or they'd quit
within days.
You want achievements
in the Capital?
Good.
Then choose it.
You can
leave now.
I'll fund your departure,
no hard feelings.
Or
unite with me as true brothers.
You earn the right
to call me Lin Yan.
I swear that
if I prosper,
you'll build
legacies, too.
Everyone's here?
Perfect.
I brought food.
Auntie,
they're all hot.
Guaranteed
to make you
adore our dishes.
Here, pass these around.
Lamb Skewers
and chicken cutlets
bigger than your face.
Eat while it's hot.
Here.
Take some.
Smells good.
Why hesitate?
Quick, eat while hot.
Don't hesitate. Come on.
Vice Prefect,
I see
you've threatened
and now soothed.
Perfect.
Discuss over food.
That's perfect.
Everyone,
I'm Vice Prefect Lin's family.
Call me "Auntie"
if you like.
You work hard
daily.
Just eat up.
Eat while hot. Don't hold back.
Just taste it.
Quick, here.
Take it. Eat while hot.
Have milk tea.
Here.
Cheng Hu,
you're 37 years old,
poor,
and unmarried.
I can't promise you a wife,
but I'll secure your livelihood.
I've petitioned
to raise our salaries.
Really?
Second Master Xu,
second sons are often neglected.
You're one of them.
But by year's end,
there'll be promotion opportunities.
Return home then,
who'd dare slight you?
I'll strive
for each of your aspirations.
My word
is sworn to heaven.
Listen.
Listen!
I won't claim
Vice Prefect Lin is flawless.
But he empathizes,
if...
What does that mean?
It means
standing in your shoes
to address real needs.
You've worked here for years.
You know how rare that is.
Follow him,
and he won't shortchange you.
Now, quick.
Everyone, eat.
Food's getting cold!
Quick, move.
Hu...
Why stare?
Eat!
Here.
More milk tea.
I smelled it long ago!
Vice Prefect,
haven't eaten?
Sit.
Let's eat together.
Eat.
Here, sit down.
Vice Prefect.
- Please eat.
- Here,
try this.
Let me mix it for you.
What... what is it?
Cold skin noodles.
It's rice paste-based.
Rice...?
Let me try.
Wait.
Let me.
Must mix evenly.
There, taste it.
Then... I'll indulge.
Delicious!
So chewy!
Good, right?
Everyone, try some!
Try some.
Here.
Listen,
if you like,
when our eatery opens soon,
come feast!
Okay.
Auntie, your skills are superb.
We're blessed by the Vice Prefect.
Right.
Never tasted such snacks!
Vice Prefect, your family's so kind.
This one.
Food's ready.
We can eat soon.
Okay.
What's this?
A rabbit!
Gone already.
Next time, I'll make it again.
Smells great.
Is it ready?
- Try it.
- Okay.
Let me try it.
So fragrant. Tasty!
Such humble ingredients
become extraordinary
after being tossed with others.
What's its name?
There's no name.
I can only afford cheap grains.
But with fermented sauce
and lard for aroma,
even husks shine.
I think
it's the treasure of our poor people.
Just call it
"Paupers' Joy".
How do you like it?
Witty.
Now eat.
Deyuan, this injury...?
It's fine.
It's okay.
Chunyan!
Chunyan, are you in there?
Hussy.
Why's the door locked?
Lady, I must work now.
Wait a while before leaving.
But you'll need
to exit the way we came.
At Yunlai, they call you "Chunyan"?
I hate that name.
Just call me Deyuan.
My family did that
when they were alive.
Alright.
Lady, I'll go now.
Keep the clothes.
We'll likely never meet again.
They're worthless.
Don't fret.
I'm leaving.
Deyuan...
Byebye.
(Forget it.)
(A fleeting encounter,)
(why should I meddle?)
Here, Vice Prefect.
Our family is opening an eatery.
We have been busy cleaning,
and we only had time
to make this bowl for you.
None for them, just for you.
Thanks, Auntie.
Mr. Liu,
what's wrong with your throat?
Unwell?
I'll bring honey water later.
Honey water?
Honey water for throat...
Auntie,
may I discuss something?
Urgent?
If not,
let's talk at home.
I must return to the shop.
Only Jianshe and Shaojie are there,
and they can't decide
anything about renovations.
I can't take care
of both sides.
And they are
useless to each other.
Yeah.
Actually,
it's... not that urgent.
Good.
Then eat, Vice Prefect.
I'll take my leave.
After work...
No.
After finishing your work,
bring the lunchbox back.
Okay.
I'll go.
Let me escort you.
No need, Vice Prefect.
Stay and eat.
I'm leaving.
- Byebye, Mr. Liu.
- Auntie, go safely.
About breaking the engagement,
Young Master, why can't you
bring yourself to tell Auntie Li?
Don't tell me
this meal
managed to win you over?
Did it make you feel at home?
You might even think:
why not go with the flow
and become a real family?
Fine. Who told you to eat it?
I'll explain.
(Yunshui Manor)
Why do you come here?
Debts.
I pressed my thumb
on a Slave Deed,
lost my commoner status,
and became a slave.
I can't go home now.
Auntie!
Grandpa and Grandma keep fighting
about the renovations.
What should I do?
Auntie, why won't you answer me?
Auntie!
Be good, Yangyang.
Vice Prefect.
Your mother sent me food.
I brought it back after my shift.
Thank you.
Thank you, Vice Prefect.
Lady Shen...
Yangyang, take it
to the kitchen, would you?
Okay.
- About the engagement...
- I have...
Vice Prefect, what did you say?
I didn't catch it.
You first.
Vice Prefect,
if someone voluntarily
signed a Slave Deed
and became a slave,
how can they regain commoner status?
That would
require a special pardon.
Or marrying an official.
Her husband could change her status.
Why?
Did you just say
someone willingly signed themselves
into slavery?
If she's a commoner
selling herself into slavery,
she must first go to the Market Office.
The registrar verifies her identity,
confirms parental status,
establishes a public contract,
and issues documentation.
Only then can she be a slave.
Merely signing a Slave Deed
doesn't count.
Thank you, Vice Prefect!
I need to step out briefly.
We can discuss upon my return.
Vice Prefect!
Where's Auntie?
She just left.
But Grandma said
Auntie was upset
and told me to watch her
and stop her from running off.
Why is she unhappy?
Because of you.
Me?
Auntie said
you were her last hope.
Now that's gone, too.
I've seen her cry
secretly several times.
Last hope?
But earlier,
she didn't seem eager to marry me.
Yangyang,
has she
guessed
I intend to break the engagement?
Vice Prefect, you want to break it?
Well...
It shouldn't matter.
This isn't her first broken engagement.
Don't you adults always say,
"first time strange,
second time familiar"?
Do you even know what it means
to break an engagement means?
Of course, I do!
Why ask a child?
You wretched trash!
You wretch!
Dodge! Let's see you dodge!
You worthless scum!
How dare you dodge!
Think I'm joking?
Filth!
I'll beat you dead!
(Yunlai)
I've every right to kill you!
You piece of trash!
I'll beat you dead!
Beat you dead!
You vermin!
Listen here,
catching my eye is your blessing.
You dare resist?
Listen,
your family's all dead.
Nobody's backing you, okay?
Besides,
I own your Slave Deed.
I've every right to beat you dead!
Every right!
Beat you dead!
You shameless wretch!
Showing off?
I'll show you what I'm capable of!
- Manager Feng!
- I'll...
Why such fury?
Don't harm your health.
Lady Shen,
to what do I owe this?
Earlier, this young lady
lent me clothing.
I came to return it,
and just happened to see
she displeased you.
Children misbehave,
but we can't just use rods.
If you truly dislike her,
sell her
for silver.
Or let me take her
and teach her manners for you.
So that's why she
grew bold lately.
Turns out she met Lady Shen
and thought she had backing.
Manager Feng, what nonsense.
Before you,
what backing could I possibly be?
Her boldness comes from
knowing your masculine virtue,
towering integrity.
You wouldn't stoop
to quarrel with a mere girl.
If she angers you so,
why keep her?
The neighbors say
you consult
diviners.
If you believe in mystical signs,
why choose her?
Frankly, Manager Feng,
I know physiognomy.
Her blade-sharp nose,
sunken marriage aspect,
and vicious glare
are textbook husband-killer signs.
Lady Shen,
let me be clear.
This trash's Slave Deed
belongs to Yunlai Tavern.
She's going nowhere.
As for discipline,
a lady like you shouldn't watch.
Maybe
you should leave.
Not so, Manager Feng.
People should heed omens.
Enough. No more.
Chunyan is a bought good.
Her life or sale is my decision.
She'll kill whom I say.
As long as I own her,
she can't touch me.
Well,
your family's opening an eatery
at Juxian Alley, yes?
Listen,
tend your own affairs.
Meddle
less.
Now leave.
Now leave, Lady Shen.
You wretch!
Daring to involve others?
Lady Shen,
you wouldn't have dealings
with this trash?
That's why
you came with this nonsense today?
You just wait!
Goodbye, and don't return.
(Yunlai)
(This is Yong'an,)
(where people can)
(be traded as goods.)
Who can I protect?
You wretch!
Daring to drag in Lady Shen?
Seeking backing?
Have a death wish?
Come here.
I'll beat you dead.
I...
- You wretch!
- Stop!
Get up.
Manager Feng,
let me clarify,
this young lady and I
aren't merely acquainted.
We're friends.
She told me she only signed
a Slave Deed to become a slave.
But as a commoner,
proper procedure requires
Market Office verification
by the registrar.
They confirm parental status,
establish a contract,
and issue documentation.
Then she can be a slave.
A mere signed Slave Deed is invalid!
What nonsense?
Afraid to admit it?
Then take the Slave Deed
to the Market Office for verification!
You...
You wouldn't dare.
Because you know,
without a full procedure,
you're coercing a commoner into bondage.
Manager Feng,
for a small tavern,
you're bold.
I thought you just illegally
expanded into the back alley.
Never imagined you traffic
in kidnapped commoners!
More lies and I'll rip your mouth!
Then you've persecuted another commoner.
Doubly guilty now!
Give me Deyuan's Slave Deed.
Guards!
Seal the gates.
Let's see you two
leave today.
The Capital Prefecture forces are here!
Keep them secured.
- Yes!
Vice Prefect!
Auntie!
You said
to seek your help
if in trouble?
I must go to Yunlai Tavern.
If I don't return,
bring some people
to catch them for illegal expansion.
A surprise inspection
can easily get evidence.
For you, new officials
need achievements.
Don't worry.
Manager Feng,
Yunlai Tavern's
back-alley expansion
violates
the Market Office's regulations.
Hello, Deputy Cheng.
Deputy Cheng,
why the strictness?
Listen,
all these years,
nothing
happened.
What are you doing?
What?
Besides,
nothing happened?
In April, the bookshop caught fire.
Your alley clutter
delayed rescue.
That's why it burned so fiercely!
Lies!
You...
The bookshop workers!
The bookshop workers are here.
Come here!
You! Come here.
You
tell him,
was this so?
Speak truth.
Speak!
No...
If you doubt me,
ask others.
You all.
You all!
Speak.
Tell him,
- is it true?
- No...
If it's true?
I don't know...
Really?
- Vice Prefect.
Vice Prefect.
It's the Vice Prefect.
You arrive on time.
Your officer slanders us
and blames Yunlai
for the delayed
bookshop rescue.
Injustice, Vice Prefect.
You must uphold the law.
Jinwu Guards records show
the April fire
killed three
because the Yunlai Tavern
blocked the alley.
If those dead souls
hear your denial,
would they crawl from hell
demanding vengeance?
No. That...
Manager Feng, you believe
in ghosts and gods.
Don't you
feel afraid?
It's... impossible!
That... that clutter blocked the alley,
but no deaths!
Just one...
He didn't get out,
but he just
burned his arms.
So you admit it.
No need
for further tricks.
You...
Vice Prefect,
do you know
who backs our owner?
Vice Prefect,
it's best for you to show mercy.
Your owner's connections?
Manager Feng,
are you suggesting I bend the law
for influential patrons?
I...
I see now.
The bookshop fire
was covered up
by you
in this way, too!
Right?
You have connections?
No wonder
witnesses stay silent!
- Vice Prefect.
- Demolish!
- Proceed!
- Yes!
Yes!
No! Wait!
Well...
You...
Release them!
- Vice Prefect!
- Don't move!
Halt!
All stop!
You! Out of my way!
And you!
Get away!
Impudent!
Dare strike
the Vice Prefect?
Go away!
Vice Prefect,
it's a misunderstanding.
Today,
that pancake-seller, Lady Shen,
in Juxian Alley,
tried to abduct my slave.
I merely
detained them.
You bullied her?
I...
I... I wouldn't dare bully Lady Shen.
He bullied you?
Vice Prefect! I wasn't abducting!
Manager Feng tricked a commoner.
Nonsense!
Continue.
Deyuan was a commoner.
Manager Feng fooled her
into fingerprinting a Slave Deed.
No Market Office visit.
Right, Deyuan?
The Market Office?
I never went.
See, Vice Prefect?
Deyuan never went.
She's still a commoner.
Manager Feng can't detain her.
Manager Feng,
is it true in this?
This...
The Slave Deed.
I'll count.
Three...
Two...
Fine...
(Slave Deed)
Buying commoners into bondage
requires bribes
and complex procedures.
You cut corners
and preyed on her naivety
with a fake thumbprint
for lifelong servitude.
Manager Feng,
do you know your crime?
Now,
destroying
this fake Slave Deed
won't suffice.
Do you mean
this Slave Deed is void?
It's illegal.
You were illegally imprisoned,
and you could sue him.
Feng Li,
when I first arrived
penniless in Yong'an,
you "kindly" bought me noodles,
and then, you claimed they cost gold.
I had no money.
So you tricked me
into signing the Slave Deed.
Now, even that was fake?
Feng Li.
Feng Li, I'll sue you to death!
Feng Li!
- Sue me?
- Feng Li! Spit it out!
Give it back!
Spit it out! Give it back!
Sue... me?
Enjoy chewing paper?
I'll burn you plenty more
to fill you!
Deyuan, you're free.
Let's go.
Dare you stop
those I release?
You can go.
Let's go.
(Shaoguang's Food Notes)
(Lard Rice)
(Yes, it's Yong'an survival food.)
♪Like a sunken boat in a dark current,
not a single light of night is seen♪
♪Ahead is hazy,
light and shadow interlaced♪
♪Sadly this heart, toyed with by fate
several times, hangs suspended♪
♪Falling into fog, tracking blindly♪
♪If not for thoughts stirring the heart,
again provoking strife♪
♪How would I know it's so unfathomable♪
♪Had I known it would entangle us,
we should never have met♪
♪A clean break♪
♪Only when walking deep within
do I realize how thick the fog is♪
♪Who knows which way to go♪
♪Passing through the world,
looking back at the dream♪
♪Is it still there♪
♪Like a sunken boat in a dark current,
not a single light of night is seen♪
♪Ahead is hazy,
light and shadow interlaced♪
♪Sadly this heart, toyed with by fate
several times, hangs suspended♪
♪Falling into fog, tracking blindly♪
♪If not for thoughts stirring the heart,
again provoking strife♪
♪How would I know it's so unfathomable♪
♪Had I known it would entangle us,
we should never have met♪
♪A clean break♪
♪Only when walking deep within
do I realize how thick the fog is♪
♪Where should I go♪
♪Passing through the world,
looking back at the dream♪
♪Is it still there♪