[Yin's Command Center]
Zhuoyi.
Recently, Bronze Leaf has raided
several smugglers' dens.
The confiscated money
has been added to the treasury.
I think it can help to solve
part of the military provisions issue.
This money
won't solve the fundamental problem.
You should take it back
and give it to Bronze Leaf.
There's one more thing.
This gold piece
was found on Lu Yi.
She reported that the Thunder Gang
was colluding with One Heart.
Uncle Lei tried to kill Lu Yi back then
in order to silence her.
Our Yin family has to clear her name.
How much do you know about Lu Yi?
Not much.
If you don't know her well,
then how can you determine
whether the coded message
on this gold bullion is true or not?
Lu Yi's death is full of
suspicious points.
It's a human life after all.
We have to investigate it thoroughly.
Yes.
We should investigate it.
Uncle Lei rushed into
the wedding venue to kill people.
Now he's still missing,
and that's certainly suspicious.
What about Lu Yi?
What about those photos of her meeting
with the people of One Heart?
Three years ago,
why did she replace her fiancé
with another one?
These are all suspicious points.
We need to investigate them all.
Lu Yi wouldn't be a member of One Heart.
Zhuofeng,
I'm only one year older than you.
I'm not trying to pull rank
as your eldest brother.
If Lu Yi is innocent,
I'll definitely uphold justice for her.
If Uncle Lei
is really a member of One Heart,
I'll definitely deal with him
according to the law, too.
You've always worked hard
for the Yin family
and been impartial in all matters.
Hearing what you've said,
I can finally put my mind at ease.
Zhuofeng.
I heard everything you guys said.
If there's really something wrong
with Lu Yi,
then Lu Ye...
I'm sure the two sisters are innocent.
Don't let Zhuoyi know that
Lu Ye is in Bronze Leaf's camp.
Got it.
Commander.
Last month's financial report
is out.
In addition,
that foreign tobacco company
keeps contacting me.
Lieutenant Xu.
No matter how desperate we are for money,
we absolutely cannot do things
that cross the line.
I'll keep figuring out a solution
to our financial problem.
Alright.
Got it.
Is there any news from Yin Lei?
Not yet.
We're still searching everywhere.
We need to find him quickly
and retrieve that piece of land he has.
Then it might help to
relieve our financial stress.
[Your Sunshine]
[Episode 6: The Smell of Blood]
Your room is nicely decorated.
Someone is looking for you.
Come with me obediently
so that I don't have to use violence.
Lu Ye!
Don't move!
Jia Fan!
Let go of her!
Loser, what are you doing here?
With what you're doing now, do you know
what the consequences will be?
What?
You want to save her?
Come on!
Let go!
Loser, let go of me!
Let go! Let go!
Lu Ye,
go find Yin Zhuofeng.
Yin Zhuofeng!
Take him away.
Tell me.
Who asked you to take her away from here?
No one asked me to take her away.
I just thought she was such an eyesore,
so I wanted to capture her and sell her.
Women should go to the places
that are suitable for them.
Jia Fan.
I'll give you one more chance.
Who ordered you to do this?
Is it Yin Huanyuan?
No one ordered me to do this.
You're so loyal to the mastermind.
Does it look familiar?
All these years, you've earned
quite many bounties outside
behind Bronze Leaf's back.
I don't even care about that.
But today, you tried to hurt
your own fellows from Bronze Leaf.
We need to settle this score properly.
Don't hurt women and children.
Don't kill our own fellows.
Don't let traitors stay alive.
Take it.
He's yours now.
No matter how you treat me,
I can even not care.
But Qiu Cheng...
What did he do wrong?
He did nothing wrong.
He's a loser,
so he deserves to die.
Shut up, you devil!
Lu Ye, watch out!
Go to hell!
Do you know how dangerous it was just now?
Not holding your knife steadily
is like giving others a chance
to kill you!
♪ How many people in this world
love across great divides ♪
♪ Like waiting for migratory birds that
never return, trapped in eternal winter ♪
I'm sorry.
I scared you.
♪ That sea guards the mountains,
burning with every wave ♪
I was too impatient just now.
I'm the one who should apologize.
I couldn't stand steadily.
♪ Only then may fate show mercy ♪
I won't let that happen again.
♪ How strange, meeting
and parting, like accidents ♪
♪ Like glimpsing light,
yet unable to hold it ♪
This
is the smell of blood.
Can you feel it?
♪ Half my world is dust ♪
♪ But I was lucky to have
seen the purest white in you ♪
♪ Must we always have
regret to be complete? ♪
♪ So mismatched we can't fit ♪
♪ Yet we still met—how cruel ♪
♪ I tried to understand and become ♪
♪ The rose they all praise ♪
♪ But worldly tastes make people dull ♪
♪ And courage comes from ignorance ♪
♪ Even if the wind never stops ♪
♪ I'll cross the boundary of pride ♪
Zhuoqian has gone back to deal with
Qiu Cheng's funeral arrangements.
Don't worry.
We'll burry him properly.
If you can't stay in that storage room,
I can take you away from Bronze Leaf.
Why can't I stay there?
I can stay there.
That's the place where Qiu Cheng saved me.
Alright.
Wait.
There are still wounds on your back.
Can't you feel them?
Just tear it open.
I don't mind.
Okay.
You used too much force.
I'm sorry.
C-Can I continue?
It's done.
Thank you.
I'm so useless.
I thought I had improved,
but I couldn't even hold a knife steadily.
You couldn't do it
because of fear.
Fear is your greatest enemy.
Have you ever been afraid?
I found the people
who had helped One Heart
blow up the school.
Though they had committed serious crimes,
I still couldn't bear to kill them.
Weakness,
incompetence and fear
were suffocating me.
In the end, only with my survival instinct
did I manage to fire that shot.
Since that day, I've sworn that
I'll never be afraid again.
I have to be more ruthless
and more fearless than others.
Only in this way can I go further
on this path through hell.
Later,
shooting guns became my instinct,
and I could even do it without thinking.
Now I can't even remember
how many people I've killed
with these hands of mine.
How did you
become like this?
Like a monster.
Right?
That's not what I mean.
Just like you,
it's for my closest ones whom I love
and for those over 100 people
who died in that explosion.
To hell with weakness!
To hell with incompetence!
To hell with fear!
This is for you.
From now on, use it to protect yourself.
Yin Zhuofeng.
I'll be like you,
holding the knife in my hand firmly
and taking control of
my own destiny.
[The next day]
[Moonrise Tavern]
Who are you?
What are you doing?
Yin Zhuofeng!
Why are you venting your anger
in my place?
Don't you know what you did
in Bronze Leaf's camp?
This is the affair of our Yin family.
You have no right to interfere.
Get lost.
Zhuofeng!
Stop it!
Zhuoyi.
I have to teach him a lesson today.
While Yin Zhuofeng is here,
take some men to Bronze Leaf to find her.
Go now.
Zhuoyi.
You have no idea how many dirty things
Yin Huanyuan, that bastard, has done.
What are you doing here?
We're here to capture
a member of One Heart.
Have you seen a woman?
A woman?
No.
This voice sounds a bit familiar.
It's her!
Stop!
I'm asking you to stop right there!