Tonight,
Lu Ye is on an urgent mission
at the Golden Pleasure Club.
We need to be ready
to assist her at any moment
to ensure her safety.
Everyone, stay here.
Before I give you the order,
don't act rashly.
Don't worry, Zhuofeng.
I'll keep an eye on everything.
[Your Sunshine]
[Episode 18: Run for Love]
Come on.
Cut me,
but not too deep.
Cut me.
Cut me!
The official you'll be receiving tomorrow
is the director
of Hai City Water Resources Bureau,
Zhang Chongzheng.
There's nothing wrong with his background.
But his medical examination report
shows some abnormalities.
Every once in a while,
new wounds would appear on his body.
I suspect...
Cut me!
He must have some unusual fetishes.
Another one with no sense of fun.
Where's the gun?
Very good.
Come on. Come on.
Cut me again.
It turns out that he's a pervert.
Director Zhang,
does your wound still hurt?
It doesn't hurt.
It's fine.
Director Zhang.
What about your collaboration
with our boss lady?
Tell the Priest to come see me
next Monday.
We'll sign the contract.
Thank you, Director Zhang.
I finally got a lead on the Priest.
Don't be afraid.
Everything's fine now.
Come on.
Try this on.
It looks so good on you.
I was right about you indeed.
These are all your rewards.
Thank you, Miss Ding.
Mr. Zhang will stay in Tang City
for five more days,
so during these five days,
please spend more time with him.
Miss Ding.
I might be too nervous just now,
and I haven't calmed down yet.
I want to...
I want to go out to get some fresh air.
20 minutes.
Thanks, Miss Ding.
♪ I can't wait to see you ♪
♪ Because I can't bear
to part from you for three days ♪
♪ Mature and dignified ♪
♪ But panic is where love begins ♪
♪ Always afraid of falling in love,
longing to feel safe ♪
♪ Yet I still rush into this danger
without hesitation ♪
♪ Restraint won't speak
what's in my heart ♪
♪ Grown-ups should say goodbye
to secret crushes ♪
♪ I want to love you openly ♪
♪ Let the sun
reveal my feelings to the world ♪
♪ With flowers in hands, letters written,
I'm ready to see you anytime ♪
♪ I'm sincere
and I'm willing to do whatever it takes ♪
♪ I want to love you openly ♪
♪ Let romance
live through countless summers ♪
♪ Share smiles, hug tears
and feel your feelings ♪
♪ Turn love into a memorable fate ♪
I'm fine.
I'm good.
It's fine.
Why are you breathing so hard?
I'm here
because firstly, I want to tell you
that I finished the mission successfully.
Secondly...
Secondly, I want to ask you a question.
That day, at the Golden Pleasure Club,
when you mentioned
that you liked the girl
who made stars appear
for you on the dark night,
what exactly did you mean by that?
I...
What I meant was...
I like you.
Three years ago,
when you protected me and saved me
at the Lu family residence,
I started to like you.
However, back then,
you were going to marry my sister.
So I told myself
I couldn't like you anymore.
Three years later,
I met you again.
We've been through so much together.
Just now,
I thought I was going to die.
I thought I could never see you again.
Yin Zhuofeng.
I like you.
What about you?
I...
I like...
Zhuofeng, something happened
at the Golden Pleasure Club!
There's no sign of activity.
As long as you give us the order,
I'll immediately lead our men
to break into...
Lu Ye.
Did you escape from there,
or did you finish the mission
successfully?
What do you think?
Lu Ye, you're really amazing.
Zhuofeng,
I told you Lu Ye
would handle it perfectly, huh?
Why are you glaring at me?
One Heart and Zhang Chongzheng
have reached an agreement.
Next Monday,
Zhang Chongzheng will sign the contract
with the Priest personally.
That's great.
The leader of One Heart
is finally going to show up.
When the time comes,
I'll use the excuse
of broadening my horizons
to persuade Zhang Chongzheng
into taking me to meet the Priest.
By that time,
I'll make the mantel clock fall
to give you the signal.
Okay.
Once the signal is given,
I'll rush upstairs
and capture the Priest.
I can only be out for 20 minutes.
I have to go now.
So soon?
Remember my question.
When we meet next time,
remember to give me an answer.
What question is it?
Zhuofeng.
What answer is it?
Priest.
Zhang Chongzheng has agreed
to collaborate.
Now we just need to
sign the contract with him.
How's it going with Yin Zhuoyi?
How's the progress?
He...
I'm sorry.
I've really done my best to deal with him.
I've tried every way
I could think of, but he...
I understand.
You did your best, and that's fine.
I won't force you.
Then what about my younger sister?
How is she?
Don't worry.
We'll do our best to save Ding Le.
We won't let her die
on the operating table.
What do you mean by that?
Apart from Zhang Chongzheng,
I can still find ways to convince
other officials in Hai City.
I can make them all used by me.
But my sister...
I beg you.
Your sister's life or death
is up to you.
Whether she can leave
the operating table alive
depends on
whether you can make Yin Zhuoyi
sign this railway transport contract.
Ding Xi.
I'm looking forward to your good news.
Commander.
Are we really going back
to Hai City like this?
Have you prepared the car
for our return to Hai City?
Commander.
Xu Hai!
How about I let you
be the Commander of Hai City?
I've scheduled meetings with the Chairman
of Hai City Chamber of Commerce
and the President of Fenglong Bank.
We need to go back as soon as possible.
But those two people have always...
I'll go prepare the car.
Lieutenant Xu.
Why are you here again?
Are you leaving?
Can you please
not leave?
Yin Zhuoyi,
are you trying to run away?
You're such a useless and pathetic man.
There's a great opportunity for you
to make a fortune, but you don't want it.
Now you're going back
to Hai City in disgrace.
No wonder you have a financial crisis!
Take care.
Ding Xi.
You think now that you're the boss lady
of Golden Pleasure,
the people of One Heart
will actually respect you?
In my eyes,
you're just like a caged bird,
being servile and obsequious
with no self-respect.
Yin Zhuoyi.
I never thought that one day,
you would actually point a knife at me.
Let go of...
♪ If it rains heavily ♪
♪ Does it mean the tears
hiding at the eye corners ♪
♪ Won't need to hide so deep? ♪
♪ If breaking the tail is for survival ♪
♪ That bird will fly high
towards its destiny ♪
♪ Unwilling to turn into dust ♪
♪ I've seen a storm,
and I've also passed by the clear sky ♪
♪ How much light in that eye
can be left now? ♪
♪ Even though I'm tired,
I'm still trying to smile ♪
♪ I'm like a chameleon,
but I've never hidden the truth ♪
♪ The essence of evolution
is survival of the fittest ♪
♪ But I'm never used to surrendering ♪
♪ If you're tired, just smile bravely ♪
♪ Like a scarecrow dancing in the wind ♪
♪ Remember what your motto is ♪
♪ Don't lose your soul
while trying to survive ♪
♪ Even though I'm tired,
I'm still trying to smile ♪
♪ I'm like a chameleon,
but I've never hidden the truth ♪
♪ The essence of evolution
is survival of the fittest ♪
♪ But I'm never used to surrendering ♪
♪ If you're tired, just smile bravely ♪
♪ Like a recorder singing for life ♪
♪ Even if we are going to turn into dust ♪
♪ We still want to kiss the stars ♪
All these years...
Why didn't you tell me
about your sister earlier?
Someone like me
has lived in misery since childhood.
Those who are nice to me
are either plotting against me
or using me.
I don't trust anyone.
So I can't say anything to yield,
especially to the one I love.
Besides,
when One Heart used my sister's illness
to approach me,
your father had just passed away.
All the burdens fell on your shoulders.
About One Heart,
I promise you.
No.
I'm not saying this to make you pity me.
I'll just consider it
as helping myself this time.
Zhuofeng.
Today's operation
was both exciting and successful.
The Priest wants to use Zhang Chongzheng
from the Water Resources Bureau
to smuggle opium into Hai City.
Next Monday,
as soon as he appears,
we'll assassinate him at once
when he's totally off guard.
Zhuofeng.
Why aren't you letting me eat?
In terms of your performance today,
you only deserve to eat plain rice.
I waited outside the Golden Pleasure Club
for totally five hours today.
I didn't slack off at all.
Without your order,
I rushed back immediately.
It was good that you rushed back.