You saw Zhuoyi while following Ding Xi?
At first, I didn't want to believe it.
But it really was him.
And...
they acted very close.
If he came to Tang City to find Yin Lei,
why didn't he inform us beforehand?
Could it be...
he's like Zhang Chongzheng,
also being targeted by One Heart?
And Ding Xi is the honeytrap.
Find out everything
between Zhuoyi and Ding Xi,
past and present.
[Your Sunshine]
[Episode 19: A monster]
Here are the contract terms.
Please have a look, Commander.
I heard
you've also been courting Zhang Chongzheng
from the Water Resources Bureau.
You're a businessman.
Preparing
for both water and rail transport—
that is understandable.
You mean...
I
hate playing both sides most.
If you want my railway,
I must be your only choice.
I believe in
your sincerity, Commander Yin.
But you're not satisfied
with our collaboration proposal.
Ding Xi,
you failed to deliver.
Yes.
I failed to convey
your intentions to him in time.
Commander Yin,
Prie...
I can help you transport the liquor here.
And I can help you
infiltrate all of Hai City.
I've got the distribution network.
Looks like
this contract
isn't getting signed after all.
The contract is wet.
We can draw up another one.
I must be
your only choice.
Commander Yin,
you truly have majestic demeanor.
I'll consider
your terms.
[Golden Pleasure]
Tomorrow is the day Zhang Chongzheng
meets with Priest.
Take some men and station them
at the entrance of Golden Pleasure
and in the alley nearby.
Stay on standby.
Brother Zhuofeng, don't worry.
Half the coachmen and vendors
outside Golden Pleasure
are our people.
Priest.
Let's get straight to the point.
Director Zhang,
please take a look at the contract.
According to our discussions,
I agreed to offer you
one year of waterway access.
Why does the contract now say five years?
Director Zhang,
one year is too short—
gone in the blink of an eye.
We'd like to work with you
for a bit longer.
Using my authority
to get your goods into Hai City
already carries significant risk.
If we make it five years,
that could very well
cost me my life.
Do you have a better suggestion,
Director Zhang?
I'm not afraid of taking risks,
but the profit split
needs to be renegotiated.
For every shipment
that goes through my waterway,
at least this much.
And the shipping schedule—
I'll decide that.
Director Zhang,
you're putting me in a tough spot.
The choice is yours.
If you're willing,
we can sign the contract right now.
I'm a businessman.
Business
is about mutual benefits
and about
give and take.
Director Zhang,
since you've laid your cards on the table,
I...
can't make a losing deal either.
In that case,
give it some more thought, Priest.
Goodbye.
Daisy Wild,
let's go.
Stop!
Take care of her too.
Lu Ye!
Young Master Zhuofeng,
so you had it all planned out long ago.
Don't let them escape!
Let's go.
[Meiqi Grand Theater]
Do you remember the first time
I forced you to kill someone?
You couldn't even hold the dagger steady.
Now your grip is firm,
but your body is covered in wounds.
And now you're trapped here,
about to die with me.
You taught me how to hold a dagger
and how to take control of my own life.
Master,
we won't be trapped.
Let's fight our way out together.
I'm not your master.
I even kind of hate
that damned "Brother-in-law" you call me.
What I didn't get to say last time is—
I like you.
♪ How many people in this world
love across great divides ♪
♪ Like waiting for migratory birds that
never return, trapped in eternal winter ♪
I like the way
you conjure stars for me in the darkness.
♪ That sea guards the mountains,
burning with every wave ♪
♪ Only then may fate show mercy ♪
You...
♪ How strange,
meeting and parting, like accidents ♪
♪ Like glimpsing light,
yet unable to hold it ♪
♪ Half my world is dust ♪
♪ But I was lucky to have
seen the purest white in you ♪
♪ Must we always have regret
to be complete? ♪
♪ So mismatched we can't fit ♪
♪ Yet we still met—how cruel ♪
♪ I tried to understand and become ♪
♪ The rose they all praise ♪
♪ But worldly tastes make people dull ♪
If we make it out of this alive,
let's ride across the open plains,
♪ And courage comes from ignorance ♪
soar through the sea of clouds,
♪ Even if the wind never stops ♪
and live a life of freedom and joy.
♪ I'll cross the boundary of pride ♪
Okay?
♪ Follow across barren coordinates ♪
Whatever you say.
♪ You shone with brilliance in that instant ♪
♪ Made me drop my guard and cry ♪
Nobody move!
Brother Zhuofeng.
Take Lu Ye and leave first.
I'll handle the rest.
It's over.
Give me the dagger.
Give it to me.
Do those wounds on your body hurt?
No.
Not at all.
I've seen you conjure stars.
I've seen you let off fireworks.
But in the end, I turned you,
who were pure and flawless,
into a monster that doesn't feel pain
and doesn't even fear
blood.
Lu Ye.
Lu Ye,
it's alright now.
It's alright. We're safe now.
Wake up.
♪ I covered myself
with the quilt tightly and huddled ♪
We're okay now.
♪ Waiting for your good night
seems to have become a habit ♪
♪ Don't care if the flowers on the window
are in full bloom or not ♪
♪ All I care about is when the sun sets ♪
♪ So I split a heart into two halves ♪
♪ I want to be seen through by you,
but I'm afraid you'll get sick of it ♪
♪ We miss each other on this deep night ♪
♪ Is it a kind of romance? ♪
I'm sorry.
♪ I keep waiting till it's getting late ♪
♪ I keep sighing till the moon
becomes full ♪
♪ I'll count to three
and wait for your good night ♪
♪ On this sleepless night,
my heart is broken again ♪
♪ Why don't we count the sheep
and say 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6 to the sky? ♪
♪ Then let's evade the stars
and meet the moon secretly ♪
♪ In the hush of night,
let's hold each other tight ♪
♪ Let's sneak away together ♪
♪ The Milky Way needs our help ♪