=Lost And Found=
=Episode 23=
(You said I know nothing about love.)
(After I learned it,
you want to leave me)
(It's not that easy.)
(Si Qingye.)
(I'll destroy her
since I can't have her.)
(I want you to feel)
(the pain of losing someone you love.)
Sir.
My name is Mu Yunge.
I'm not the Ning Wuhui
you're looking for.
You're Ning Wuhui.
I'm not.
You are.
I suggest you
not to waste your time on me.
I'm afraid you'll be disappointed.
Do you know who I am?
Si Qingye.
I know you're not Ning Wuhui.
I hope you're not her too.
You're in love with me, are you?
Will you marry me?
I...
No.
I have no choice but say yes.
Haven't you been looking for someone?
I'm
Ning Wuhui.
I think
You've become a stranger.
♪It turns out
that only part of your world rains♪
♪And I'm not in that sunny area♪
Yunge.
Yunge!
Sorry.
I was late.
Mu Yunge, don't die.
Don't leave me.
Yes.
Sorry
for lying to you...
Yunge.
in
the
beginning.
I lied to you seven years ago.
What if one day
I lied to you?
Why would you lie to me?
This is my wife.
Will you marry me.
I'll play this wedding march
for you
when you marry me.
Promise me
to marry me when we get back.
I missed you.
I didn't expect
to have so many memories with you
seven years ago.
No.
♪It turns out
that only part of your world rains♪
♪I'm too redundant♪
Don't die.
I beg you not to die.
I've already forgiven you.
No!
I never blamed you.
Whether you're Ning Wuhui or Mu Yunge.
Don't sleep.
Mu Yunge.
Look at me.
I love you.
You can't die.
Mr. Lu.
It will be too late
if you don't leave now.
Hurry.
Save her!
Mu Yunge!
International wanted criminal, Lu Xiao.
You are surrounded!
Put down your weapons!
♪That's why I was kicked out
of your life in advance♪
Get down.
Don't move.
Go.
♪Perhaps leaving is♪
♪A decent epilogue♪
(Three Months Later)
Daddy, Mommy's awake.
- Daddy, Mommy's awake.
- Yeah.
Mommy's awake.
Yeah.
Daddy, Mommy's awake.
Yeah, Mommy's awake.
Mommy's awake.
Daddy, Mommy's awake.]
♪If you need practice to fall in love♪
♪Practice makes perfect.
Have you practiced?♪
♪You suddenly looked at me♪
♪I fell in love suddenly♪
♪It's like a sudden encounter♪
♪Already having a result♪
♪Sorry I made you miss me♪
♪Suddenly breaking free
from the shackles of memory♪
♪Fate has many twists and turns♪
♪Your arms are warm♪
♪It turns out all the ups and downs♪
♪And unwillingness to settle
are all for this moment♪
♪This heart is lazy♪
♪Yet it beats for you♪
♪All reunion after a long separation♪
♪Is because of love♪
♪You suddenly looked at me♪
♪I fell in love suddenly♪
♪It's like a sudden encounter♪
♪Already having a result♪
♪Sorry I made you miss me♪
I'm hungry.
Okay.
I'll treat you to a feast.
Mommy.
Go.
- Mommy.
Mommy.
Daddy.
♪Is because of love♪
Xingxing, hurry.
Coming.
Slow down.
Okay, got it.
Darling, look at this.
Hurry. Faster.
Okay.
Is this all right?
Yes.
This is for you.
Xingxing.
I'm going to catch up with you.
♪There will be a sudden silence♪
♪There will be a sudden vulnerability♪
♪Someone will suddenly ask me♪
♪Why I'm upset♪
♪If you need practice to fall in love♪
♪Practice makes perfect.
Have you practiced?♪
♪You suddenly looked at me♪
♪I fell in love suddenly♪
♪It's like a sudden encounter♪
♪Already having a result♪
♪Sorry I made you miss me♪
♪Suddenly breaking free
from the shackles of memory♪
♪Fate has many twists and turns♪
♪Your arms are warm♪
♪It turns out all the ups and downs♪
♪And unwillingness to settle
are all for this moment♪
♪This heart is lazy♪
♪Yet it beats for you♪
♪All reunion after a long separation♪
♪Is because of love♪
♪Fate has many twists and turns♪
♪Your arms are warm♪
♪It turns out all the ups and downs♪
♪And unwillingness to settle
are all for this moment♪
♪This heart is lazy♪
♪Yet it beats for you♪
♪All reunion after a long separation♪
♪Is because of love♪