=Lost And Found=
=Episode 5=
Baobei, Xingxing.
What do you two think of Mr. Si?
Great Grandpa, I like Mr. Si.
I want him to be Daddy.
But they always argue
when they see each other.
We can't have that.
What's wrong with arguing?
In a relationship,
the more you argue, the better.
You really do keep up with the times.
What are we having for dinner tonight?
Snow clams cooked in bird's nest
and bluefin tuna.
Okay.
Get ready.
We'll be having some good food later.
Are you Mu Yunge?
What does it have to do with you
whether I'm Mu Yunge?
Get her.
I'll ask you one last time.
Are you Mu Yunge?
I'm Mu Yunge.
You, get her.
Watch me kill you.
Tell me who sent you.
Who was it?
Mu Yaner sent us here.
Mu Yaner?
How dare you hit my buddy?
Watch me kill you.
Why is she grappling them?
Let's go.
You guys. I...
You're a dangerous woman.
Why are you grabbing me?
You...
Si...
Do you remember something?
Ning Wuhui is best at martial arts.
I learned it in self-defense class.
I only know a few moves.
Keep making it up.
Tell the truth.
Let go.
You...
You're grabbing... Let go.
- Are you going to tell me?
- Enough.
Mr. Si, you and Mommy make a good match.
A good match?
Why do I feel like they're both angry
and want to kill each other?
You don't understand.
It's always like that on TV.
The men and women will fight
and argue and then become a couple.
I'm officially announcing
that I'm going to work hard
to make Mr. Si our dad.
Baobei, don't talk nonsense.
Boss,
we found the mastermind behind this.
Mu Yaner sent them.
Got it.
No.
No, you found out too.
Of course.
Ms. Mu.
Could you be a little less impulsive
next time you're in danger?
Please keep me safe
while you send me
to and from work.
Don't let me get frightened again.
I...
Come here.
Mommy.
Boss, we...
Okay.
I'll leave.
Hello?
Hello? Ms. Mu.
We failed.
Idiots.
You can't even handle such a small task.
Sooner or later, I'm going to throw her
into the sea to feed the fish.
Mu Yunge.
I'm lucky to have you, Baobei.
I'll take care of your beauty.
By the way, Baobei,
Don't get too close to Si Qingye.
Why?
Because he's moody,
unpredictable,
and has a tendency to violence.
He's scary.
Is he scary?
Super scary.
Hello.
Hello, Ms. Mu.
I'm Gu Xiao.
Gu Xiao?
I think I've seen you at work.
Please enjoy.
Thank you.
I invited you here today
to ask you a favor.
Go ahead.
Please stay away from Si Qingye.
Is that why you invited me here?
I've known Ye for over ten years.
I know him
best.
I don't think
you're right for each other.
Have some self-respect.
Ms. Gu.
Who are you talking to me as?
I'm talking to you
as Mr. Si's fiancee.
If that's the case,
Ms. Gu,
this is between the two of you.
You should talk to Mr. Si.
(Mu Yunge.)
(You're really charming.)
(It's been seven years.)
(Si Qingye is still in love with you.)
Miss.
Please have a look at this new model.
It's made in the United Kingdom.
It starts from as low as 1.2 million,
but your fondness is priceless.
Babies, take a look.
What a beautiful car.
This one suits you.
This yellow one is nice.
I still think
the one earlier was better.
Right, Baby?
Mommy.
Madam Mu, Ms. Mu.
Welcome.
Take a look. Our new model is over here.
Yunge.
I didn't expect...
Auntie.
...to run into you here.
Mom.
This shop isn't very classy.
Let's go to another shop
to look at the cars.
I didn't check the Imperial Calendar
before going out. How unlucky.
And you said
you didn't want Grandpa's fortune.
You've only been home a few days
and you're already buying a car
with his money.
Did the manure tanker pass by your house
and you want to have a taste?
Mom, look at her.
Yunge.
We can't let Mom
get bullied by bad people.
Yes.
I'm all right.
Thank you for your concern.
I heard you had a hard time abroad.
If you ever need money,
let me know.
It's not good
to always worry Grandpa, right?
Okay.
Could you buy this car for me?
Kids, come here.
Thank Grand-aunt.
Thank you, Grand-aunt.
Don't mention it.
Mu Yunge, do you have any shame?
I gave you a chance,
and you really took advantage of it.
If you don't want your mouth,
I can sew it up for you.
Guess
what will happen if I told Grandpa
that you sent someone to attack me?
What?
Do you have proof?
Let him go.
Mu Yaner sent us here.
Yes.
Don't send it.
Don't worry.
I won't tell Grandpa.
What happens next
depends on your behavior.
Calm down.
Be good.
Stop!
Don't.
Mr. Si, you really came.
Ms. Mu, you have such a bad temper.
Looks like you didn't remember
my warning to you
last time.
Mr. Si, what a coincidence.
Are you here to check out some cars too?
It's not a coincidence.
I came here on purpose.
Mommy.
I called Mr. Si
to capture the bad woman.
Who are you calling a bad woman?
Mr. Si.
Why do you keep defending
Mu Yunge?
There aren't that many reasons.
Madam Mu.
Have you forgotten my rules?
Mr. Si.
Yaner is young and doesn't understand.
Be the bigger person.
Wait for me.
Mr. Si, you're amazing.
Mr. Si, you're mighty.
How obedient.
Let's go.
Baobei.
Will you stop bothering Mr. Si?
It doesn't matter.
I don't mind.
Mr. Si is so handsome.
Yeah.
Ms. Mu.
A mysterious customer
has ordered
a limited edition model for you.
Please sign it.
What?
It's a gentleman
who called himself Pursuer X.
♪There will be a sudden silence♪
♪There will be a sudden vulnerability♪
♪Someone will suddenly ask me♪
♪Why I'm upset♪
♪If you need practice to fall in love♪
♪Practice makes perfect.
Have you practiced?♪
♪You suddenly looked at me♪
♪I fell in love suddenly♪
♪It's like a sudden encounter♪
♪Already having a result♪
♪Sorry I made you miss me♪
♪Suddenly breaking free
from the shackles of memory♪
♪Fate has many twists and turns♪
♪Your arms are warm♪
♪It turns out all the ups and downs♪
♪And unwillingness to settle
are all for this moment♪
♪This heart is lazy♪
♪Yet it beats for you♪
♪All reunion after a long separation♪
♪Is because of love♪
♪Fate has many twists and turns♪
♪Your arms are warm♪
♪It turns out all the ups and downs♪
♪And unwillingness to settle
are all for this moment♪
♪This heart is lazy♪
♪Yet it beats for you♪
♪All reunion after a long separation♪
♪Is because of love♪