Master... Daoming Si?
You know who I am?
Why won't I?
I'm your teacher.
My teacher?
What's wrong?
A flat tire.
Master Daoming Si.
You can leave the lowly work to me.
You shouldn't be bothered by it.
It doesn't bother me.
This is my responsibility as a student.
What an honor.
Seriously, I'm totally fine.
Why are you so scared of me?
No, I'm not.
I'm not.
So why are you so nervous?
Really.
If you can recall your memory someday,
and you remember
you changed a tire for me, I'll be doomed.
What?
No, nothing...
You stepped on my foot.
I stepped on your...
I'm sorry. Please don't move...
-What are you doing?
-I'll wipe it clean for you.
No. Why are you doing that?
I'm wiping your shoes...
No, you do not have to.
No, that's totally fine.
This is how it works.
It's like some understanding between us.
-An understanding.
-An understanding?
Have I told you to do it before?
Was I that harsh?
No, not really.
Not at all.
No.
Please be honest.
Master Daoming Si.
Do you... really not remember anything?
Mr. Ah Liang...
Now you're flattering me...
Don't keep saying "flattering," okay?
All right?
Oh, okay...
Could I please...
Actually...
I have a question.
You're flatter...
I'll work flat-out to answer the question.
Any question.
The past me and the new me.
Which one do you think is more fun?
Of course it's...
Do I have to answer it?
Of course. I wouldn't ask you
in the first place.
Oh, the answer.
How should I put it?
The new you...
The new you is...
nicer than before.
More like us.
Like you got rid of your harsh part.
That's it.
I see.
Thank you, teacher.
My pleasure, Master Daoming Si.
It's my pleasure.
Could you please do me a favor?
Yes, of course. I'll do my best.
Could you please stop calling me "master"?
I will.
Okay...
Why are you laughing?
No, nothing.
I mean, I've never imagined that I can
sit next to Master Daoming Si one day.
I can even chat with you
on the side of a road.
Great.
Right.
Where are you going?
I'm going to a wedding party.
I dress pretty formally today.
Really?
My friend is getting married.
Where are you going?
-I was supposed to go to the market.
-For dinner?
HUAZE LEI
Hello?
Did you sleep well?
I slept well, thanks to your blessing.
Why did you wake up so early?
Because I miss Yingde.
This should be enough.
"This should be enough"?
It is far from enough!
How is it possible?
I hope Master Daoming Si is here.
You're right.
No, honey.
Don't worry.
If I can sell that car today,
I can have an advance on bonus.
I'm afraid...
There is nothing to be afraid of.
It will be successful this time.
Yes. It's about Shancai's tuition fee.
We must succeed!
-This is it!
Dad, mom, I'll go hang out with Huaze Lei.
Okay...
Honey.
Did you hear who Shancai
is going to meet up with?
I think it's Master Huaze.
Master Huaze?
You mean Master Daoming Si
is no longer in Shancai's life...
but she got...
A handsome, gentle,
-and generous Master Huaze?
-Master Huaze?
Honey.
-That's great!
-Indeed.
Do you feel that suddenly,
our house is brighter?
We don't even need lights anymore.
That's because a bright light
is shining on us.
I didn't know that our daughter, Shancai,
has such a great future.
I can't open my eyes.
Me neither.
It's too bright.
Too bright.
-Too bright.
-That's great.
The sky is as blue as it used to be
even after you graduated.
Yes.
How is it possible?
I thought the skies in Yingde
would change.
That's weird.
You used to tease me a lot.
Now I'm missing the days
when you boys were around.
That's good to hear.
Come and visit me.
We can watch the sky together.
Shancai.
I'll be flying to Japan this afternoon.
How long will you be there?
I don't know.
Don't let me worry about you.
Hey.
Didn't you promise me just now?
It will be fine.
I feel lonely all of a sudden.
Daoming Si went missing.
Now you are going abroad.
So this is what graduation is like.
We can never be together
like the old days.
What are you doing?
Do you know you're making a long face?
You had so many expressions before.
You laughed when you were happy.
You railed when you were angry.
You stood here scolding us F4 when we met
on the rooftop for the first time.
You do remember that.
Do you want to scold us again?
Now?
Why should I do that for no reason?
Because we deserved that.
If we didn't step into your life,
you must be working and learning happily.
I miss the Shancai who scolds people.
I used to scold people a lot before.
I forget how I scolded you.
You cursed us to go bankrupt.
To die because of obesity.
To go to hell in the afterlife.
You called us "Pig Head 4."
Pig Head 4!
You jerks!
I curse you.
I curse you to have brain hemorrhage.
Especially the big pig's head Daoming Si.
I curse you choke on eggs
and be hit by meteors,
until you remember everything.
You shall crawl and scramble
back to me now!
And you, Huaze Lei.
I curse you to be exhausted from sleeping.
And I will scold you in your nightmares.
Scold about what?
About you.
If you fail to come back to Taipei soon,
I'll fly to Japan
and shave all your hair off.
Remember,
no matter what you will encounter,
you need to have the spirit
just like that.
This is the Shancai I know.
But I didn't hear that.
Hear what?
The promise you made to me.
I swear to God, I won't let
Huaze Lei worry about me anymore.
Why are you standing here?
Why did you hit me?
I'll call the police.
That's all. Thank you.
Is "Shancai" some kind of vegetable?
Oh, no.
It's a kind of grass.
It'll still sprout in spring no matter
how hard people tread on it.
What a lively name!
My name is Yesha.
Is "Ye" your surname?
No. Yesha is Elsa.
Yesha.
It's a good name.
Any special meaning?
In Hebrew, Elsa means
"Promise with the God."
That's special.
A promise with God.
What did you promise?
That's a secret.
Nice to meet you, Shancai.
Same here, Yesha.
Two fruit shave ice. Please pay first.
Okay, the bill is on me.
Consider it a welcome to Taiwan gift.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
Shancai.
I have a question.
Does your hand hurt?
Yes.
It hurts badly.
Me too.
I didn't imagine I'd meet a girl
punching with her fists like me.
I guess your boyfriend must
respect you a lot.
Sorry, I didn't mean it.
That's okay.
-Here you are.
-Thank you.
How about you?
Your boyfriend must respect you, right?
I don't have one.
Tell you a secret.
I have never fallen in love.
Liar.
You're pretty
and have such a good personality.
I don't believe you.
It's true.
Shancai.
What does love feel like?
Love is...
When you fall in love with someone,
no matter what happens,
he's always the first one
who comes to your mind.
Your heart beats so fast
when you're thinking about him.
There seems to be a hole in your heart
when you lose him.
No matter where you are
or what you are doing,
there is an invisible wound
that gives you pain.
So you were in love with someone before?
Here is your change, 80 yuan. Thank you.
Thank you.
I had forgotten I have to get to work.
Where's your workplace?
It's a cake store.
A cake store?
Are you in a hurry?
It's very cold.
Can I go with you?
It's super cold.
How's this place?
It's a cute store.
-Here you are.
-Thank you.
Even your suits are so cute.
It must be a joy to work here.
I think so,
but the others don't share
the same thought.
We often don't have enough people
around here.
Really?
So, can I work here?
-You really want to work here?
-Yes.
I'll tell my boss, then.
Okay.
Great.
I should tell Ah Xing too.
Ah Xing?
You tell everything to Ah Xing.
Who is Ah Xing?
A stray dog.
A stray dog?
He got lost so I adopted him.
I'll bring him in someday
to meet with you.
Okay.
Is it a boy or a girl?
It's a boy.
Is it fierce?
Sometimes.
Eighty bucks per hour.
It was a cute cake store.
My new friend is cute too.
Why don't you come and visit?
I can introduce her to you.
Okay.
I'll take her here tomorrow.
Why so sudden?
Because she is amazing.
I think you will like her.
"Shancai"?
It's a weird name.
So is Daoming Si.
Fine...
Can I pick you up
when you get off work tomorrow?
Deal.
Don't be a liar.
Fine. You're so mean.
Don't you have an early shift tomorrow?
Go to bed.
No.
Come on.
I'll beat you up if you don't.
"Met a new friend, Shancai."
Cover yourself with the blanket.
-It's hot.
-You'll get a cold.
-No.
-How childish you are.
Don't mess around.
Just get some sleep.
Yesha.
Does it hurt again?
Where is your medicine?
Is it in your bag?
Where is your bag?
Where is your medicine?
Yesha.
Does it hurt?
Just a second.
Open up! I need some medicine!
Hey.
Why are you yelling this late at night?
My sister is in pain
and she needs some painkiller.
No pharmacy is open this late at night.
Take her to the emergency room.
I don't care!
Where is the emergency room?
In the hospital, idiot!
That's really good.
Yesha.
I'll take you...
Let's go to Kenting, okay?
One day, granny, Ah Xing, and I will
travel to Kenting.
We'll watch the sea and the starry sky.
How is that, granny?
We can discuss later.
It's hard to make promises
with this granny.
No, I will keep promising to you.
What nonsense are you saying?
I can't reason out with you foreigners.
Deal?
We will travel to Kenting one day.
Let's go to the hospital.
Granny got me some painkiller.
It doesn't hurt anymore.
It won't cure you.
Did you hear what I said?
Let's go.
You'll have a full-body checkup.
You must be losing your mind.
Didn't I just tell you I'm fine?
I'm no longer in pain.
You were in so much pain just now.
Just like what happened in the wine house!
There's nothing serious if it just hurts
every now and then for girls, okay?
It's not okay.
Never mind.
I hate hospitals.
I'll get angry.
For real?
It's nothing.
I know my body.
It just hurts a little sometimes.
Nothing serious.
Don't get angry.
Shitball.
What should I do?
Ah Xing is angry at me.
He's really scary when he's mad.
I'm so scared.
Your feet...
Did you go out barefoot?
Stand still.
Don't move.
Give me your feet.
-For what?
-Just give it to me.
Step on this.
Thanks.
This is a footprint of Ah Xing
when he rushed out barefoot
to buy medicine for me.
Don't be mad.
I promise I'll go to the hospital
if it hurts again.
Don't be mad.
Do you know why I'm mad?
Because you scared me.
I'm scared by the idea of losing you.
No matter who I am now,
I just want you to know that...
I care about you.
I want to take good care of you.
I want to stay with you forever.
Okay.
Welcome.
Madam, do you want to buy a car?
It's "young lady."
You should call them young ladies
to make a good impression on females.
How about male customers?
You should praise their tastes
and their status.
Understand?
Yes.
Understood.
Honey, let's try it one more time.
No wonder why you can't sell a single car.
Once more chance, please.
-Young lady.
-Young lady...
This is Shancai's sweet home.
Boss?
Yes.
Okay, just a second, please.
Phone call for you, Shancai!
Boss, thank you
for taking care of Shancai.
Come and visit us when you're free.
Okay...
Hi, boss.
Yes, I'm heading there.
Buy some oranges?
How many do you need?
Okay, got it.
No worries. Bye.
Mom.
-Mom.
-Come here, Shancai.
Do you think this is a suitable car
for mom?
-This one?
Yes, it is!
Madam.
This...
-Young lady!
-Young lady.
This is our latest model.
It has this aerodynamic design.
It has the trending silver
and pink combination.
Take a look.
You two are elegant and graceful.
What a beautiful pair of sisters.
Just like the sisters in that TV show SOS.
This is the best car for you.
Definitely a perfect match.
What are you doing?
-We are practicing.
-Practicing.
Practicing what?
Your dad has a poor sales performance.
So as your mom, I have to sell myself.
No...
I have to teach him how to sell cars.
Shancai. What is your opinion
about your dad's selling techniques?
Dad, you're trying your best.
I believe the sales will be high
this month.
That's great.
Did you hear that, honey?
After hearing Shancai's words,
I have more faith in myself.
I believe my sales
will be the highest this month.
But honey,
I think you should show more honesty
for selling cars.
Don't flatter the customers
with words like "elegant" or "graceful."
That's embarrassing.
Is it?
Shancai.
-Do you think it's embarrassing?
-Yeah.
What's embarrassing is being forced
to call your mom "young lady."
It's warming.
Warming.
Shancai.
Do you have any suggestions
for your dad on selling cars?
I don't know either.
But based on my experience selling cakes,
we will ask the customer
what's the cake for at first.
They might send it or eat it.
Or maybe it's for a party
or for someone's birthday.
Then we can suggest flavors accordingly.
So, dad, you can ask your customers
why do they want a car?
Get to know the customers' needs,
so that you can be more persuasive.
Shancai, it makes sense.
Shancai, you're so smart.
You've got a point.
No, you've got nine points.
You are my good daughter.
Yes. Shancai is the smartest.
Honey, let's do it again...
-One more try.
-Okay.
Come on. Okay, listen.
Be honest. Right. Then what?
Dad, I'm off to work. I'm rooting for you.
Okay.
-Bye.
Madam.
Are you satisfied with our cars?
What will you use it for?
Let's see.
I want a car that I can drive
around myself.
My husband's business is booming now.
He's extremely busy.
He has no time to drive me around.
Before we got married,
he once rented a lemon.
He drove us to the Yangming Mountain
to watch the night view.
He drove us to the beach
to enjoy the seaside.
I thought I was the happiest woman
in the world.
However, this didn't last long
Before my dream shattered
So, sir, is there a car
that can go into the wild?
A robust car that let me travel around?
A car strong and steady enough?
Sir?
Honey!
Concentrate.
Right.
Madam.
I would say a hatchback is what you need.
Right.
You can take your husband, your daughter,
the whole family to the beach.
To the mountains.
You will enjoy that beautiful life
as a whole family.
Great.
So...
Can it be customized
as an electric flower car?
-That would be unnecessary.
-Why?
You can customize it into a hearse.
All you need to do is driving it uphill.
No need to drive it back down.
Honey, concentrate.
I know...
-Have you learned anything?
-I tell you what.
If I got the highest sales number
this month,
I will be able to buy a nice car
and take all of us for a ride.
Great, I believe in you.
Okay, one more.
Honey, thank you.
CHICKEN SALAD
MANGO YOGHURT SALAD
Goodbye.
Listen...
What?
Not bad...
Come on. Listen.
Listen.
This is the best part.
Is it?
Not bad.
Pretty cool.
Why are you in a rush?
None of your business.
I'm worried about him.
He's gonna pick up Yesha at the store.
Wait.
Take this.
It's fine, take it.
Don't forget to hand in
your experience reports.
I should find a girlfriend
as soon as possible.
Then, I can be as focused as him
when it comes to working.
Plus, I can get off work early.
It must be nice.
Not on my watch.
That's not fair.
That's because you're my star employee.
After all, you're my best classmate.
I'm rooting for you.
Really?
I swear.
Go wash the dishes.
Brother.
Good brother.
This is not fair.
My wifey.
Look at the sunset. Gorgeous, right?
How can there be a sunset
when it's noon now?
Daoming Si.
Daoming Si!
Shancai!
-It seems like yesterday.
-Shancai!
Daoming Si was chasing the bus I was on.
He chased me so far.
From Taipei to Barcelona.
He finally got me off the bus
with all his efforts.
I understand how strong he was.
This time, I'm the one chasing Daoming Si.
No matter where he is,
I will get him back.
Bye, boss.
Hurry up.
What's the hurry?
Why is Shancai not here?
She hasn't been around for a while.
Maybe another day.
Come on.
Why are we coming back here?
To get your drawing tools.
Why?
You always put
your pens and pigments everywhere.
There must be a lot
of your pens and pigments.
Right.
You didn't color your paintings recently.
I told you last time...
See? You never put away your stuff.
I'm always the one cleaning things up.
I'm talking to you, okay?
Your pigments.
What are you looking at...
DAOMING SI, I KNOW YOU ARE
ON YOUR WAY HOME.
I WILL BE WAITING FOR YOU FOREVER.
Someone is waiting for you.
Someone that seems to love...
No.
Someone that loves you deeply.
You're not the only one who's astray.
Her love is astray too.
Daoming Si...
Daoming Si.
Who is she?
Subtitle translation by Kristin Tsang