I'm pretty straightforward.
I guess I'll just get straight
to the point then.
I've decided to be your girlfriend.
What kind of reaction is that?
It's an honor
to have a girlfriend like me.
I'm telling you.
A lot of guys are pursuing me.
Get up. Ask them if you don't believe me.
Don't you know how many people
are pursuing Ah Mei?
Dada liked her for a long time too.
That's right.
Ah Mei is the most beautiful,
most popular,
and most courageous girl in our town.
You've got some nerve.
-What?
-You're...
-You're very lucky.
That's right, you're really lucky.
That's right. Dada is not as lucky as you.
That's right, you're lucky.
Did you hear that?
I'm not really interested in girls
that a lot of guys are pursuing.
You can't pursue me from now on.
I'll kick anyone who pursues me.
Do you hear me?
Did you hear me?
All right.
It's okay. Nobody's pursuing me now.
I'm also not interested with girls
that no one else likes.
Then what are you interested in?
Sleeping.
So are you rejecting me?
You're really cute.
You're even cuter today.
It's just that I'm not really interested
in you.
Ah Mei, actually, Lei is...
Wake up.
Why are you treating Ah Mei like that?
Go and pursue her.
Don't you like her?
Ah Mei.
Ah Mei!
Wake up.
Why are you here?
Do you want to be my girlfriend too?
That's okay.
But you have to be nicer.
What are you talking about?
Aren't you worried about Ah Mei?
She's going to be fine.
Don't you think Ah Mei is so brave?
Lei, how do you feel right now?
How do I feel about what?
About being confessed to.
Don't you think Ah Mei is cute?
I really admire her courage.
Wake up. You've been sleeping all day.
Lei, it's already late.
Are you a pig?
I'll go make some food.
Ah Mei.
-Ah Mei.
-What time is it?
What time is it now?
-Past 9:00 a.m.
It's past 9:00 a.m.
Shouldn't you go to school then?
When do you want to graduate?
You guys don't know how blessed you are.
You're such a fool.
Go to school, you jerk.
Go.
I'll go to school then.
Who's stopping you?
Why are you looking back?
Go. Hurry!
What is he trying to say?
So what if he's handsome?
So what if he knows
how to play the violin?
His hair is too long.
He's too tall.
And he's always wearing white.
If he goes out at night,
he'll surely scare people.
He looks even scarier than a ghost.
His mouth is basically useless.
He doesn't talk. Is he mute?
He doesn't like me.
He rejected me. I'm rejecting him too.
How strange.
Reject me again.
Try to reject me again.
So what if he's handsome?
So what if he knows
how to play the violin?
Don't ever say I'm cute again.
Don't ever talk to me again.
If you tell me I'm cute again,
I'm going to blow your head off.
Don't ever stand beside me.
How petty.
Who's petty?
A girl who stops talking to a person
because she can't be his girlfriend
is the pettiest.
I'm not petty.
You're the one looking down on me.
Why should I talk to you?
Did I say I'm looking down on you?
You are looking down on me.
Hey.
If you don't like me
because you like someone else,
I can accept that.
But if you don't like anyone
and you still don't like me,
isn't that considered
as looking down on me?
You look so cute.
Stop telling me that I'm cute.
You say I'm cute,
but you still don't love me.
You're a playboy and a flirt, Huaze Lei.
You don't love me either,
yet you want to be my girlfriend.
So you're also a playgirl.
And a flirt with a big face.
Who said I don't love you?
Then tell me three reasons
why you love me.
-Three?
-Yes.
You said I'm cute.
You don't have a girlfriend.
Your hand is very beautiful.
Is that love?
What else would it be?
That's like, not love.
To be in love,
you must understand each other.
I don't get it.
Take a look at my hand.
You have a good life.
Look closer.
There are a lot of calluses.
Yes.
So now you know my hand
is not that beautiful.
When I was little,
I really loved the sound of the violin.
And I was very curious about it.
How can that weird-shaped box
produce such a nice sound?
So I started studying how to play it.
First, the skin
peeled off of my fingertips.
Then it bled.
Finally, it developed calluses.
It was a painful process.
And it made me want to give up.
But the more I understand the pain
of learning the violin,
the harder it was for me to give it up.
Because I fell in love with it.
Do you understand it now?
You like me.
I love the violin.
I still don't get it.
I don't know if you're talking
about the violin
or Shancai.
Of course it's Shancai.
You like Shancai, right?
Because you like Shancai,
you became friends with her.
And the more you understand Shancai,
the harder it was for you to give her up.
That's why you go wherever she goes.
Because...
Because you fell in love
with Shancai, right?
If you're rejecting me
because you love Shancai,
I feel like I'll be happy with that.
You're in pain because of Shancai, right?
You love Shancai, right?
You're an indecisive man, aren't you?
Good thing I don't like you that much.
The answer is not there.
The answer is over here.
Sha.
I have good bottle of wine.
1995 Spanish Collection.
I feel so happy.
Do you want to ask Yesha
to come and share this happiness?
Sha.
I opened this wine for us.
I see.
She'll finish this quickly if she sees it.
And that won't be good for us.
So let us handsome guys enjoy this.
Tell me.
I regained my memories.
You regained your memories?
Everything?
The days from when I woke up
at the hospital
feels like a very long sleep.
Suddenly, it's like...
everything just happened yesterday.
I remember everything.
Including my love for Shancai.
I clearly know
that the one I love is Shancai.
You can't do this.
You can't love Yesha then--
This is not something I can control.
I also want to have just one memory.
It doesn't matter if it only
has Shancai or Yesha.
Why can't I have just one memory?
Why is God playing this trick on me?
I don't know what I should do.
No matter what I do,
I'll hurt someone I love.
I'm trying hard
to get my feelings for Yesha back.
I want to love Yesha.
But as my feelings get clearer,
I feel more guilty when Yesha
treats me nicely.
How can I lie to Yesha?
Sha, tell me. How can I lie to Yesha?
You can.
You should lie to her.
Sha.
Don't you want Yesha
to have real happiness?
You are her happiness.
Do you know
how much she sacrificed
to bring you and Shancai together?
I came back from Spain
with this ring.
Yet your ring was stolen.
She was worried and scared
that the curse mentioned
in the legend would happen to you.
So she kept this ring with her.
She loves you.
Yet she wants to give you back to Shancai.
She'd rather have you misunderstand her.
She'd rather bear all the pain.
And secretly cry in a corner.
Because she's sick.
She's dying.
What did you say?
Three months.
Maybe half a year.
Yet she used the time she has left
to make a deal with your mom.
So that Shancai can stay beside you.
So that you can regain your memories
and be together with her.
Then she plans
to peacefully face her own death.
She sacrificed so much for you, you know?
But that day,
when she saved you from the pool,
that's when she completely broke down.
She completely broke down.
God can take her life away
but He can't take her love for you away.
She just decided
to love you no matter what.
Ah Xing, I'm begging you.
I'm begging you.
I'm selfish.
I'm not that kind.
I feel sorry for you and Shancai.
But I'm begging you.
I'm begging you.
Please continue loving Yesha, okay?
Ah Xing, promise me.
Ah Xing.
Ah Xing!
I'm so hungry.
I must have forgotten to eat
because I was concentrating too much.
Do you want to eat something?
I'm fine.
I was just sitting down for too long.
Let's go.
It hurts.
What's the matter?
Painkillers.
Yesha, where's your medicine?
It's in the cabinet.
Didn't you say...
that you won't hide anything
from me anymore?
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm sorry.
I'll take you to the best doctor.
You are the best doctor.
I don't like hospitals.
I don't like being intubated.
I just want to spend
the remaining days of my life
loving you.
Do you blame me for being so selfish?
Someone who doesn't stand a chance
is still clinging on to you.
Then I will be gone one day,
leaving nothing behind.
Memories.
What?
You'll leave memories with me.
No one can take that away, right?
Yesha.
When are we going
to travel around the world?
You don't know how happy I am.
I don't want to give you back
to Shancai anymore.
Ah Xing.
Thank you.
I don't like hospitals.
I don't like being intubated.
I just want to spend
the remaining days of my life
loving you.
Just put more aiyu jelly.
Shouldn't you order aiyu jelly then?
Why are there so many people
ordering dessert today?
Dada's not here.
Here.
Ah De.
Ah De!
Darn you, Ah De!
See what I'll do
if you don't come out now!
Here, this is your dessert.
-I'm going to make some grass jelly.
-Okay.
Guys, I'm sorry.
We're closing early today.
Can you have your dessert for takeout?
I'm not done eating yet.
All right. Your dessert's on me today.
You don't have to pay.
No, I want to finish it here.
I don't want to leave.
Please, okay?
I'll add more ingredients and ice, okay?
-Who does business this way?
-Tell me what you want me to add.
Please, we really have an emergency today.
Thank you.
Come on, tell me what you like.
I'll add them. Come on.
We were so busy earlier.
Why isn't there anybody here now?
They left after they've finished eating.
It's because you're too fierce.
You scared all the customers away.
I'm too fierce?
You look 100 times fiercer than me, okay?
I look nice when I'm fierce,
but you don't.
I don't look nice when I'm fierce?
Business doesn't seem to be good today.
Yeah, it's not.
Good timing.
Shancai wants you to have dinner with us.
Really? That's great.
I happen to be hungry.
I want to earn money. I can't go.
All right then.
Ah De, let's go.
Okay.
I'll go have dinner.
Hey.
What are you eating?
Why does your house look like this?
What are you guys talking about?
Nothing. Be careful. Don't fall again.
What are we eating today?
There are many delicious dishes.
Shancai.
-Where's Shancai?
-I don't know.
Shancai.
Is there a power outage?
Why don't you turn on the lights?
I don't know.
Why are there so many candles?
Happy Birthday!
Happy Birthday.
Happy Birthday to you
Happy Birthday, Happy Birthday
Make a wish.
I wish...
I wish for someone
that can watch the dessert shop with me.
I wish that everyone who's lost their way
could get back on track someday.
You...
And I wish...
This one's a secret.
-All right. Blow the candles.
-Blow the candles.
Help her.
Yes!
Ah Mei, happy birthday to you.
This is your birthday gift.
Open it now.
Oh.
Where did this come from?
I bought this, of course.
You're lying. Where did you get
the money to buy this?
I really bought this.
I swear, okay?
Nine out of ten
of your promises aren't true.
Tell me. Where you did you buy this?
When did you buy this?
How much is it?
Why don't you believe anything that I say?
Am I that useless to you?
Then tell me. Where did you buy this?
Ah De really bought this ring.
I'm a witness.
I was with him when he bought it.
Ah Mei.
Regardless what Ah De did before
and how much he had hurt you,
have you ever thought
about who else in this world
would remember your birthday this well?
Who's willing to work hard
just to let you have a good birthday?
Who wants to give you a gift
even if people misunderstand him?
You know,
I'm really jealous that you have
a brother who loves you so much.
Who says he loves me?
He left the dessert shop
to me without a word.
I always have bad dreams
that he got killed, hurt,
or caught by the police.
When my mom left, she left nothing.
Nothing but a troublemaker like him.
I don't want him to take care of me.
He just needs
to take good care of himself.
I just want him to be a good person.
Who doesn't steal or rob from anyone.
What are you doing? That's my ring.
Actually, it looks quite good.
Even on my claw-like hand.
Shancai, thank you.
You don't have to thank me.
But can you tell me the truth?
I thought you considered me as your friend
that's why you defended me.
Turns out you also think I'm a thief.
I don't.
But that ring was mine before.
It was yours?
I get it now.
You mean I stole your wallet
and your ring.
Don't forget that you've already
falsely accused me once.
Can you not accuse me again?
If you want to accuse me,
please present some proof.
That ring cannot be bought
anywhere in Taiwan.
It came from Barcelona.
I have a friend
who brought it back from Barcelona.
Then a thief stole it
from an old house.
That's impossible.
That kind of coincidence is impossible.
Ah De, I won't tell anyone.
For Ah Mei's sake, I won't say anything.
I just want to confirm if it is my ring.
Because that ring is very important to me.
It made me lose the one I love
and it changed my life.
That ring pushed me off the cliff.
I'm hiding here
and trying to forget everything
because of that ring.
Then God lead me to it again.
Ah De.
Is that my ring?
Shancai, I'm sorry.
Ah De.
Ah De, I'm so dizzy.
I think I should drive you home.
No.
Why did you drink so much?
I have a bad headache.
Why are you two chatting over there?
Ah Mei, are you all right?
How weird. Shancai's my friend.
So why are you two talking?
Okay, fine.
-Don't talk to him. He's a bad influence.
-All right, I know.
I have a bad headache.
Are you okay?
You shouldn't drink that much.
I'm going home.
Lei, take them home.
-That's right.
-No, don't.
-We'll go home by ourselves.
-It's fine.
Ah De, crouch down.
How can I go home
if you don't crouch down?
Fine.
How would I walk if I'm dizzy or tired?
-I know.
-All right.
Your wine is so good.
-Come again next time. Be careful.
-Okay.
Ah De, be careful.
Be careful.
Bye.
-Thank you.
Be careful.
Shancai told you to be careful.
After the entire summer,
I saw the meteor ring again.
However, it seems like it's not meant
meant for me.
Daoming Si and my story is over anyway.
The meteor ring is meaningful
and irreplaceable to Ah Mei now.
But what should we do
about that unlucky legend?
Hurry.
I'm really going to faint.
Great news.
I think this is
really great news.
The hospital said...
They found a bone marrow.
Really?
There's a good match between the
donor's bone marrow and yours.
But the precise matching process
needs to be done in Hong Kong.
We can get the results in a week
or in a month at the latest.
Just go back and wait for the results.
Then what can we do while we're waiting?
As usual,
take your medicines on time
and maintain a healthy lifestyle.
The most important thing is to relax
and wait for our good news.
Doctor, excuse me.
You can stay here. I'll go ahead.
We need to prepare for surgery.
What's the matter? Do you feel tired?
I've originally decided
to live for just three more months.
But now I'm reluctant
to leave because of you.
Now, I want to live three more years.
Thirty more years.
Three hundred more years, for you.
Mr. Qiu.
Qiu Zhengde.
Come with us to the police station.
Why should he go with you?
Did he commit a crime by sleeping at home?
Some incidents seem to be related
to Mr. Qiu Zhengde.
We're taking him for questioning.
Let's go, take him.
Wait.
Didn't you promise me already?
Speak.
I really made up my mind to be good.
All right. We'll talk at the station.
Let's go, take him.
Ah Mei.
Ah Mei. Why did Ah De
get in the police car?
That's none of your business.
Go to school.
-But the car's leaving--
-I told you to go to school.
Go!
Subtitle translation by Coleen Chua