Yesha.
How are things with you today?
Not very well. And you?
Not very well.
I can see it from your expression.
What happened?
You first.
Actually, it's nothing.
I...
actually just got a few minor problems.
You first.
I won't tell you mine
if you don't tell me yours.
It's nothing.
It's just...
My boyfriend...
Did he dump you?
You could say that.
This guy must be a pig head.
I used to call him a pig head.
Because he deserves it.
You are so cute.
Only a pig head wouldn't treasure you.
It's actually not his fault.
He actually...
Of course, it's his fault.
This is too much.
He dumped you!
But rest assured,
he'll get what he deserves.
Something bad has indeed happened to him.
You see?
There will be more bad things
that will happen to him.
I curse this kind of guys.
Please don't.
-He--
-Yes, I will.
And I will curse him with all my power.
I will curse him that he will
step on dog poops every day.
And the toilet paper will run out
when he's in a rush to poop.
Anywhere he goes,
everyone will think he stinks.
And...
starting from today, his nose hairs
will grow backwards.
Ingrown nose hairs?
That's so ugly.
It will grow longer and longer.
It will grow inside.
It will grow into his head.
It will grow into his brain.
His brain will be surrounded
by the stinky and dirty nose hairs.
He won't be able to think straight.
And when his hairs are all gone,
then the nose hairs will grow out
of his head with boogers.
Oh, that's so disgusting.
Your turn.
My turn?
Your turn to curse him.
Then I curse him that his nose hairs
will continue to grow.
It will grow out of his ears.
There will be black curly hairs
in his ears
so he can't hear I'm calling him.
More.
More?
His nose hairs will grow out of his eyes
so he can't recognize anyone.
That's perfect.
No one will like such an ugly guy.
That's so funny.
It's so funny.
It's really funny.
Feeling better now?
Yeah, much better.
There will be nose hairs
all over his body.
Oh, my gosh, that's so funny.
Shancai.
If what we said really happens to him,
will you still love him?
Yes.
You love him so much.
For your happiness,
I'm going to take back all my curses.
Thanks.
Shancai.
Is love a painful thing?
Sometimes, it is painful.
But sometimes, it's sweet.
Yesha, what happened?
Nothing.
That stray dog I kept, he found his owner.
Oh, my god.
But you've bonded with it.
It's a difficult time, right?
Yesha, you can talk to its owner.
You two can care for it together.
-Together?
-Yeah.
You can make a schedule.
It lives in your house
on Monday, Wednesday, and Friday.
It lives in its former owner
on Tuesday, Thursday, and Saturday.
It's a good idea.
If he really is a dog, I'll do that.
You mean...
Unfortunately, he is a man.
Yesha...
But that's okay.
I didn't fall in love with him.
I decided to return him to his owner.
My shoulder isn't wide enough,
but it's pretty useful.
If you want to cry, just cry.
Let it all out.
Actually, I don't want to cry at all.
I feel relieved.
Thank you, Shancai.
No problem.
Then, next time I want to cry,
you will lend me your shoulder.
Deal.
Let's drink.
Thanks.
Why are you standing here?
I was searching for my memories.
It's like sitting alone in a cinema
watching a movie featuring myself.
But the whole night...
Apart from me...
you're the only one in the movie.
Every movie is about you.
There's no one else.
Only you.
Yes, you don't remember her.
Don't you care
about all the things she has done?
Caring isn't falling in love.
That's how you feel now.
Are you sure you didn't love her before?
I don't know if I loved her or not
because I don't remember.
I don't remember!
Didn't it occur to you
that she is innocent?
Am I not innocent?
What about you?
Aren't you innocent?
Why can't I choose to be who I am now?
That's your choice.
And I...
And you still choose to leave me, right?
I just want to give you back to her.
How?
Tell me how it's done.
Don't you know I'm in love with you?
I can never go back.
You have to.
After all, you are Daoming Si.
Fine.
I will go back.
As long as you look me
in the eye, and tell me...
you've never loved me.
You don't love me anymore.
If you can say it...
I'll go back to being Daoming Si.
Tell me.
Tell me!
I don't love you.
I don't love you!
You're crying.
You should be happy
for telling me your thoughts.
Why are you crying now?
Stop pushing me.
Is it really painful to be with me?
I won't push you anymore.
What?
Aren't you going to leave?
Fine.
Let me throw my own memories away.
It is said that over a million people
pass through here every day.
I don't know them.
And they don't know me.
In this minute, I don't know
how many people have passed by me.
Right now, I am holding your hand, Yesha.
I'm afraid I can't be with you anymore.
I'll try to forget the hand I held before.
But you have to promise me one thing.
Don't look back when you leave.
I want to look at your back.
I want to remember your back.
It suddenly occurs to me that I'm
responsible for retrieving your memory.
Your memory is on vacation
and my mind is on vacation, too.
So let's make a deal.
I can only...
Didn't you say the client is sure
to sign the contract yesterday?
How should I know?
We got a "what if" situation here.
Then what should we do?
Shancai is going to register today.
How should I know what to do?
Honey, I got an idea.
We can call Master Huaze for help.
Right!
We can call Master Huaze.
But we don't have his phone number.
Well...
You go ask Shancai.
You do it.
No. I'm bad at acting.
She will see through me.
You're good at it. You do the acting.
You should go ask her.
I'm not good at it, too.
No need to be humble.
Didn't you join a drama club before?
You love acting.
Just...
Go. Just ask her.
What is it?
Mom, Dad, what's the matter?
Well...
It's about your dad.
Well... Not me...
Well...
It's about your mom, me.
-Yes, her.
-Me.
I miss Master Huaze.
I want to call him.
You know, chat with him.
Mom, you want to chat with Huaze Lei?
I promise you, Shancai,
your mom will never borrow money
from Huaze Lei.
Mom! Dad!
You fool.
What happened?
I deserve it.
I'm a fool.
I'm a fool. I didn't get enough money
to pay your tuition for this semester.
I spent so much time.
I'm useless.
Don't worry about the tuition fee.
My salary and student loan can cover it.
Is... is it true?
Really?
Is everything fine now?
Is it true?
-Daughter...
-I'm running late.
You're amazing!
-I'm leaving now.
-Amazing...
One more thing.
Don't keep borrowing money. Okay?
-Okay. I know...
-Okay.
Bye-bye.
Shancai, bye-bye.
Great.
We have such a smart, capable,
and hardworking daughter.
Well, I'm so useless.
I can't even provide
my daughter's tuition.
Honey, don't say that.
This is a difficult time for everyone.
Of course, cars are hard to sell.
-Yeah.
-So...
As your wife, I can't just stay here
and do nothing in a time of crisis.
Like I said, you're a great wife.
Thank you for saying that.
I'm thinking right now.
I have to come up with an idea that works.
Do you have any good ideas?
Well, when I'm watching TV,
when people are selling cars,
there will always be a hot girl
posing beside the car.
You're right.
Cool cars and sexy girls
have always gone well together.
There always seems to be a sexy girl
beside the nice car to flatter...
Honey, you mean...
At this point, I have to...
sacrifice myself,
and use my beauty to help you.
From now on, I'll sell cars with you.
I'll be right next to the car
you're selling and get on it.
I'll lean, bend, and roll over it.
Stand up and lie down again.
Show all sorts of sexy poses.
Honey...
I think you're really great.
You're an outstanding woman.
If you really will roll over my cars,
they will all be sold.
The more you roll, the more I sell.
No one knows my charisma better than you.
Yeah.
I'll be the one buying all the cars
you roll over on.
I'm so touched.
You love the cars I rolled over on so much
that you won't sell them.
I'm so touched, honey.
-Wife.
-Yes?
You don't need to be so touched.
Because you would've crushed all the cars.
How could I not buy them?
Who wants to buy a car
crushed by a bulldozer?
I have to get to work.
Shancai.
Qinghe.
Awesome.
The classes finally start.
We can meet each other every day.
Yeah.
-Right! The tuition of this semester...
-Not a problem. It's settled.
I lost the opportunity to express
the meaning of friendship.
The best Valentine's Day presents
are your friendship and support.
Really?
Of course.
You should hurry up and register.
What about you?
I'm done registering.
I have to go to the cake shop.
Do you have work today?
I thought I could chat with you.
My class is about to start.
We can chat every day.
I'm leaving now. Bye-bye.
The power of friendship is so great.
Looks like I finally cheered her up.
Did you read the registration notice?
Did you?
What's this?
You think you can just walk in like that.
Is that right?
The notice told you that
the tuition fee is 158,303.50 NT Dollars.
You want to register
with only 30,000 NT Dollars.
Are you blind or have you lost your mind?
Sir, I'm sorry.
I know I haven't got enough money on me.
But isn't there student loans
for students with financial problems?
Look here.
Only the top students can apply
for student loans.
Pay the tuition fee first.
What are you looking at?
Sir, do you mean I can't attend Yingde
if I don't pay the full tuition?
Do you need to ask that?
Next!
Sir, please let me ask another question.
Is there any other way?
You don't have to attend Yingde
if you can't afford it.
It's all about money. Nothing else.
Who is that?
Should poor people be looked down upon?
Do they lose their right to education
because they're poor?
What are you doing?
One can live without money,
but not without the support of a friend.
I will lend you the tuition.
You...
Wow, what a pretty breakfast.
Did you make it yourself?
No, it was made by my friend who works
at the breakfast restaurant.
Your friend can make
such a pretty breakfast.
You're upset about the stray dog.
You have a breakfast with hearts today.
You'd better tell me everything.
Shancai, come in and eat.
The lovely breakfast made
by "stray dog" Ah Xing.
I won't dare eat it.
There are two portions.
Ah Xing. What a unique name.
Do you like it? I gave him the name.
So it's you?
What's his real name then?
His...
Welcome!
Hey.
You'd better tell me everything.
Tell you what?
Playing the fool, huh?
You're so brave.
If you won't tell me,
I'll do it the hard way.
-Nothing.
-Tell me about it.
Come on. Tell me.
Hey, Yesha.
I'm going to kill you.
You said there's nothing.
Don't be like that.
You'll get sick
if you keep it to yourself.
I'm in love.
Huh?
What?
Are you deaf?
Really?
Wow, you hook her up?
Hey, thanks to me, right? Tell me.
It's because of me, isn't it?
All thanks to me, right? Tell me.
Hey.
You two didn't start working here
on the same day.
Are you planning to get fired
on the same day?
Aren't we closed?
Why don't you mop the floor?
-Come on.
-Did you hold hands?
Did you kiss?
Did you do this?
Tell me about it.
Hello.
Yes.
We have delivery service.
Tomorrow? No problem. One moment please.
Okay, go ahead please.
Twelve-inch birthday cake.
Recipient is Ms. Zhang, right? Very well.
Ms. Zhang.
Your last name, sir?
Mr. Gao.
And the address is?
Section three.
Okay.
Can I have your number, Mr. Gao?
Great.
Tomorrow. No problem. Of course.
Thank you. Bye.
It's already eleven.
I didn't eat breakfast.
No wonder I'm starving.
What do you want to eat, sir?
I'll get it for you.
Let's go. I'll treat you to lunch.
I saw a friend.
I'll treat you some other time.
Are you working here?
Yes.
We are closed.
Where are you going?
I'll drop you off there.
That's okay. I have a bike.
Ah Si.
Can I have a word with you?
I can't believe you were able
to learn all this.
You used to--
I don't want to talk about the past.
I'm doing well now.
I have many friends.
I learnt a lot.
I got a job.
The past means nothing to me now.
But we're worried about you.
I said I'm fine.
-I'm leaving now.
-Ah Si.
Is there anything I can do for you?
If you want to do something for me...
Please leave me alone.
Unbelievable! Old hag.
Hello.
I don't want it.
She doesn't want it.
This is the cake Mr. Gao
sends to Ms. Zhang.
I said I don't want it.
-Get lost.
-You can't reject it.
-What should I do about the cake?
-Return it.
-Good day, client!
-Hi, I'd like to ask...
Please dial the extension number.
Sales Department, please press 11.
Administration Department,
please press 21.
Planning Department, please press 31.
Accounting Department, please press 51.
Connecting for you.
Please stay on the line.
This extension is busy.
Press pound to wait. The operator
shall be with you in a moment.
Hello?
Wait a second.
I'll do it.
Why are you still here?
I'm sorry, Ms. Zhang...
I don't want it...
How many times do I have to say it?
You're really annoying.
I'll call the police if you don't leave.
Please let me explain, okay?
I can't contact the sender, Mr. Gao.
But he already paid for it.
My conscience won't allow me
to just go and not deliver it.
Feed it to the dogs then.
Ms. Zhang, I...
Granny, why didn't you accept the cakes?
Today is your birthday.
None of your business.
Hey!
I care about you.
What a strange old lady.
CASH REGISTER OPEN
Thank you. This is your receipt.
I hope you win the prize.
Please come again.
Bye-bye.
Why did you bring the cake back?
She's a strange old lady.
She won't take it.
Why is that?
I don't know.
There were some cakes left at the door
when I got there.
I think she must have rejected those, too.
What now?
I don't know.
I can't contact the sender, Mr. Gao.
That old lady told me
to feed the cake to the dogs.
Then let's feed it to the dogs.
I'll take it to the pet shop later.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
Wow, such a pretty cake.
All the baker's work has gone wasted.
Also, the sender's efforts were in vain.
I think there must be a story
behind this cake.
No one will refuse others' blessings
angrily for no good reason.
Yeah. Why wouldn't she accept it?
Maybe this cake isn't about
caring or blessing.
Maybe an unfilial son wants to placate
her mom by sending her a cake.
So the mom was so angry.
Yeah, that must be it.
I don't know what the story is.
I'm sure that there's a misunderstanding.
You're right.
Even if the delivery failed,
we must let the sender know
the misunderstanding hasn't been resolved.
I agree.
The problem is, I can't find Mr. Gao.
No one answered the phone?
It seems like it's a business number.
I can't get through.
What should we do?
We can call them and get their address.
Then we can meet Mr. Gao in person.
Right. Why didn't I think of it?
We have a Chinese saying, "Three cobblers
are equal to one Zhuge Liang."
The two of us make a great team.
Three what?
Cobblers.
Never mind. I mean,
the two of us are awesome.
Shancai and Yesha are the best.
Hey, watch out!
I'm sorry. I wouldn't dodge
if I knew you're there.
Are you okay, Grandpa?
It's nothing. Accidents happen sometimes.
Hey, aren't you going to apologize?
Did the ball hit you?
No, but it hit this grandpa.
You should apologize to him.
If apologies are useful then...
All right. Sorry.
Young lady.
You have a strong sense of justice.
Thank you for standing up for me.
You're welcome.
It's important that you're fine, Grandpa.
I should go ahead.
-Bye-bye.
This way please.
Hi, I'm looking for Mr. Gao.
Please register for me.
Okay.
But I don't know his full name.
All I know is he's Mr. Gao.
Do you know which department he is in?
I don't know.
Could you come back
with necessary information?
Okay.
Thank you. I'm sorry.
Excuse me, sir. Are you Mr. Gao?
-Sorry, no.
-Oh, I'm sorry.
Are you Mr. Gao?
-Sorry, I'm not.
-I'm sorry.
Madam, do you have a Mr. Gao
in your department?
Excuse me, is your last name Gao?
Is anyone of you Mr. Gao?
-I'm not.
-No.
I'm sorry.
Are you Mr. Gao?
-Sorry, you got the wrong person.
-Oh, sorry.
Are you Mr. Gao?
-No.
-Sorry.
Are you Mr. Gao?
-No, I'm not.
-Sorry.
Sorry.
Are you Mr. Gao?
No.
I'm sorry.
Subtitle translation by Logan Zhao