We should talk to Ah Si.
What for?
To ask him face to face.
Fine.
I'll go with you.
-Let's go.
-Meizuo.
Do you remember what Ah Si said?
Regardless of what he said,
it's impossible for Yesha
to be engaged to Ah Xing.
You keep saying it's impossible.
Why exactly is that?
That's because...
Because...
Because Yesha doesn't love Daoming Si.
Yesha told me she's not in love
with Daoming Si.
She really said that.
That means...
this is not just a simple engagement.
That's right.
Someone must have set her up.
However,
who would set her up?
Hey.
It's you.
Is there a need for this?
Okay, I'll be there.
Daoming Feng wants to meet me.
Excuse me.
Welcome.
Thank you.
Shancai,
you haven't eaten, right?
See if you like any of these dishes.
Thank you.
I'm not hungry now.
Tell me what you want.
That's good.
I'll get straight to the point then.
Shancai,
you know very well
I've never liked you.
I still don't.
Ah Si is already engaged.
I know.
Ah Si loves Yesha now.
I'm very happy to become
in-laws with a royal family.
This is considered icing on the cake
to the Daoming family.
The Bhutan monarchy itself is not rich.
To put it simply,
one side of this marriage
wants fame,
the other desires financial gain.
You can say it's a win-win situation.
Why are you telling me these things?
Because Yesha doesn't love Ah Si.
She just agreed to this engagement
for the sake of our families.
What does that mean?
That means
that this engagement will end
once Daoming Corp. gets the royal prestige
and Yesha's father
gets his financial support.
You're doing all this for fame,
but what about Daoming Si?
Of course.
I don't want them
to cancel the engagement.
Ah Si losing his memory
and falling in love with Yesha
is an unexpected situation.
However, Yesha doesn't love Ah Si.
This is a fact.
So to prevent Ah Si from hating me
in the future,
I only hope he regains his memory
before the engagement ends.
And...
I'm also giving you one last chance.
I promised you before
that I owe you one chance.
What kind of chance are you giving me?
From now on, you can work
at Daoming Corporation.
That gives you a chance to see Ah Si
and be in contact with him.
However,
whether or not you can win his heart back
is all up to you.
I don't understand.
Don't you consider me an unpleasant weed,
a stumbling block?
Why are you giving me this chance?
I told you.
I still don't like you.
However,
I have to admit I saw
how much you love Ah Si
all this time.
I think that maybe only you
are willing to give up everything for him.
That is the answer.
Giving you a chance
doesn't mean I'm willing to accept you.
A chance is just a chance.
Thank you for giving me this chance.
But I don't want to be your accomplice
in lying to Daoming Si.
I'll still give you one day to consider.
Because the main focus of all this
is not me,
but the innocent Ah Si.
If you still decide to give up,
then you don't need to give me an answer.
I, Daoming Feng,
don't have time for a loser.
Madam.
Here, have some Coke.
Okay, Mrs. Dong.
You should eat something too.
Shancai.
Are you all right, Shancai?
Did you see Yesha?
What did Mrs. Daoming say?
Did she show off, threaten you,
or she...
None of the above.
Thank you for your concern.
However, I'm so confused now.
I'm really confused.
Can I tell you after I have
thought about it carefully?
So we waited the whole night for nothing?
Sha,
give Shancai time to think.
I don't believe
you don't want to know the answer now.
Shancai put up a brave front all day.
We should let her face her own emotions.
Meizuo.
Get a good sleep if you can't
think it through.
If you really can't figure it out,
remember that we're just here.
Hey!
Shancai.
Did she mention anything?
Let Shancai rest.
Save it for tomorrow.
Did she?
Good night.
That means
this engagement will end
once Daoming Corp. gets the royal prestige
and Yesha's father
gets his financial support.
I only hope he regains his memory
before the engagement ends.
And...
I'm also giving you one last chance.
I promised you before
that I owe you one chance.
What should I do?
Yesha doesn't love Daoming Si.
Daoming Si doesn't love me.
They're engaged.
However, I have a chance.
What should I do?
What exactly should I do?
What are you doing?
Are you trying to test
if my is heart strong enough?
You went missing,
got engaged,
and now you're here to scare me.
Okay.
What exactly do you want? Say it.
You're such a bad friend.
You know I'm engaged,
and yet you're not congratulating me.
Congratulate you?
Do you think I'm so stupid
that I can't tell you're unhappy?
You take your own marriage so lightly
and you want me to congratulate you?
Who says I'm unhappy?
I'm very happy.
Really.
I just thought things through.
Since I like Ah Si so much,
why not enjoy this short period
of happiness?
Anyway...
Anyway, I'm...
Say it.
Say it. Why won't you say it?
You're not good at lying.
You can lie to everyone in the world,
but you won't come here and lie to me.
That's why I need you, Sha.
I feel like I'm not myself
when you're not beside me.
Please help me, okay?
Go back with me to that cold place, okay?
Sure,
if you'll tell me the truth.
Then you also have to promise me
that you won't leave the Daoming household
for three months,
and you won't tell anyone
what we discussed today.
I'm telling you the truth.
I'm engaged.
I'm happy.
Very happy.
Then you don't need me beside you, right?
Sha.
This is my problem.
I can't bear to see someone
treating themselves horribly,
especially if I tried my best to protect
and take care of that person.
So,
it's better if you're out of my sight.
Please leave.
I'm leaving.
I'm going back to that cold place alone.
You might not see me again.
Sha.
No matter where I am,
please remember,
you're my best friend.
Stop reading that newspaper, okay?
Mom,
take that newspaper away...
or else,
Shancai will surely be sad
if she sees that.
That Daoming Si
doesn't have any conscience.
He's marrying a princess.
We're just ordinary citizens.
So what if he has a conscience?
What are we compared to them?
What princess?
From Bhutan?
What a joke!
Maybe if people like us migrate there,
even you can become the king
and I, the queen.
They're just indigenous people.
Aboriginals who have not evolved.
Every day, they're just...
Like that, right?
If Daoming Si wants to marry
an aboriginal,
let him.
He's just...
Shancai.
You're awake.
Come on... Let's have breakfast together.
Mom, Dad.
I want to say something.
Tell your mom if you have
something to say.
-Yes.
-I'm going to work now.
That's right.
Actually, Daoming Si...
I've decided to drop out of school.
What?
Drop out?
I've decided to work for Daoming Corp.
Well... are you feeling too sad?
Or... you've lost your mind?
Dad,
this might be my last chance.
Although Daoming Si is engaged,
I still want to fight for my love
one more time.
At... this moment...
I don't want to give up.
Don't give up.
That's right. Don't give up!
We only live once.
We must fight for our love until the end.
I fully support you.
Okay?
Dad!
I have nothing to be proud of in my life.
However, there's one thing
that makes me smile
even in my dreams at night.
And that is having such a tough daughter.
She is my true princess.
Dad.
Shancai.
Thank you, Mom.
I heard Daoming Si got engaged
to a princess.
That's so cool.
Hey... Then... what about that Shancai?
I heard she's dropping out.
I told you...
-she'd get dumped sooner or later.
-Shancai!
Are you all right?
Qinghe.
Why are you dropping out?
Why are you giving up on yourself
for that Daoming Si
who lost his memory?
Why?
Because I want to fight for my love.
I want to make an effort one last time.
Make an effort one last time?
Fine.
If you drop out, I'll drop out too.
Let's go beat Daoming Si
until he snaps out of it.
Qinghe,
I'm dropping out
because I'm going to work
for Daoming Corp.
So dropping out doesn't mean
I'm giving up.
Instead, it's a new start.
However,
I won't be able to see you
in school anymore if you drop out.
As long as we know we're both doing well.
Even if we can't meet every day,
we can still think of each other.
But...
Hey.
Mimi.
Dinner tonight?
Gosh. I'm very busy now.
I don't have time for you.
Bye.
Qinghe, even though I'm not here,
you still have Mimi.
I can tell that she really likes you.
You have to be nice to her, okay?
Don't be like me.
I always rejected Daoming Si before.
It's all over now
and I just realized how much I love him.
I'll go ahead.
Shancai.
Qinghe, don't think it's natural
for someone to treat you nicely.
Treasure it.
You must treasure it.
Shancai.
You know what?
I've always treated you nicely.
Hello, miss.
I'd like to see your president.
Can you contact her for me?
-Good day, Ms. President.
Miss Shancai,
anything I can help you with?
I'd like to talk to your president.
Madam.
Miss Shancai...
I've decided to accept your chance
and work for Daoming Corp.
Shancai,
I know you won't disappoint me.
Very well.
Based on your experience,
I'll arrange for you to work
for the general affairs.
You can officially start tomorrow.
Any questions?
None.
Okay.
Go and report to the HR department now.
I've already informed them.
Shancai, welcome to our company.
I'll do my best.
I never thought Shancai would be willing
to work here.
Her fighting spirit
is unlike any other girls.
No matter how strong
her fighting spirit is
I only have one daughter-in-law.
And that is Yesha.
Qinghe.
I'm happy that you visited me.
Didn't you ask me to come?
Yes.
Please come in.
Please have some drinks.
Thank you.
Qinghe,
you don't seem to be in a good mood.
Is it because my face...
Mimi,
Shancai dropped out of school.
My best friend left Yingde.
I'm so upset.
Qinghe,
I understand.
An outstanding person like Shancai
left Yingde.
It's not only your loss,
it's Yingde's loss too.
So Qinghe, please tell me,
how can I comfort you?
Mimi,
Shancai is right.
You're really a nice person.
Even if my face looks like this now,
do you still think I'm nice?
A person's appearance does not
represent who he really is inside.
Shancai always say
that we can't judge a person
by his appearance.
Do you know that?
Shancai really has so many good qualities
that I should learn from.
Of course.
Shancai has many good qualities.
She's tough.
She's kind.
And she has a bright smile.
I think I won't be able to find
another girl as good as Shancai
in this lifetime.
Qinghe.
Qinghe,
if you meet a girl
who is at par with Shancai,
would you mind if her face
is full of pimples
and cucumbers?
Of course I won't.
Regardless of what Shancai has
on her face,
I won't mind.
Qinghe,
please date me with marriage in mind.
Daoming Si's the one getting married,
what does that have to do with me?
My dad said...
What else did your dad say?
If a man doesn't judge a woman
by her appearance,
that means he's a good man that focuses
on inner beauty and virtues.
Once such a good man gets married,
he'd definitely be faithful
and won't leave his wife,
even when she gets old.
My dad said that is the type of man
I can depend on.
Mimi...
You...
I think you've misunderstood.
I'm a shallow man who focus
on appearances the most.
Qinghe, stop being humble.
I went through a lot of trouble today
covering up my beautiful face,
just so I can put you to the final test.
Congratulations, Qinghe.
For what?
You've already passed
my three tough tests.
Three tests?
What tests did I exactly pass?
First,
you drove me home before 10 p.m.
Second,
you didn't fall into temptation.
Third,
you didn't judge beauty
based on outward appearance.
Qinghe, let's officially start dating now.
From now on,
can I call you "my dear Qinghe"?
Okay.
To be fair,
I have to test you too.
I'm willing to accept all your tests.
Great.
Starting today,
you must...
You must...
learn all of Shancai's good qualities.
It's a deal.
So, my dear Qinghe, please wait patiently.
I won't let you down.
Lei, have you heard?
Shancai is going to work
in Ah Si's company.
Why are you guys here?
What do you want us to do with you?
What?
A week ago, you stood on the loft
and told us you love that kind of life.
That you're a brand-new Ah Si.
Fine, we accepted that.
However, a week later,
you're back to being Daoming Si.
And you got engaged.
You didn't even inform us
about the engagement.
We had to see the news to find out.
All right... My bad.
That's because it happened too fast.
I'm not sure why my mom and Yesha
suddenly wanted me to have
an engagement press conference.
I didn't even have time to react.
-She already...
-That means...
the one who planned
this engagement conference
is Yesha.
Even though you didn't inform us
about your big day,
we still have to congratulate you.
There was no time,
I'm sorry.
Let me make a toast to you.
You've been back for a few days already.
Are you used to living here?
To be honest,
not really.
I wouldn't come back if my mom didn't
find Yesha.
However...
I'm so happy
to see Yesha again.
You're happy.
Your mother is also happy.
That princess should be happy, too.
Great.
This is awesome.
But why did your mom
arrange a job for Shancai
at the Daoming Corp?
Isn't that good?
I don't think it's a good arrangement.
I thought since Shancai accepted
to work for us...
that maybe she's willing
to accept the new me.
I hope I can care about her
as a friend in the future.
Is it wrong
to think that way?
Actually, that's fine.
I believe you can be good friends again.
However, I need to remind you...
Never mind that you secretly got engaged,
just don't get married in secret too.
We've made a promise before.
No matter who gets married first,
the other three will definitely
be groomsmen.
Really?
I forgot all about it.
I must tell Yesha
this good news immediately.
Then treat this as your stag party.
That's right.
Let's make another toast
for Ah Si's farewell to singlehood.
-Thank you.
-Cheers.
Cheers.
Miss Yesha.
Madam wants to inform you
that Shancai will officially become
an employee of Daoming Corp. tomorrow.
What should I do, Sha?
Yesha,
it's me.
Yesha.
You're probably sleeping.
However, I still want
to tell you that I'm so happy today.
Good night.
No way.
We can't let Shancai work
in Daoming Corp. no matter what.
Meizuo, that's her decision.
We don't have any right to change it.
We at least we have the right
to protect her and keep her safe.
What do you think, Lei?
I support Shancai.
Shancai, you can do it.
Nice to meet you, Ms. Liu.
Your name is Shancai?
Yes.
What kind of weird name is that?
We have loads of miscellaneous work
over at the General Affairs office.
Can you remember instructions
by just standing there?
Yes.
This shipment urgently needs
price quotation.
Remember,
you need price quotations
from at least three companies.
Yes.
This is the warehouse inventory
information from 1999.
It needs to be updated.
Also, here's the minutes of the meeting
for the Mid-Autumn Festival employee gift
over the years.
Make a summary chart for reference.
-Yes.
-Mid-Autumn Festival is coming.
Don't delay everyone's benefit.
Understood.
This is a design
for the Autumn Festival uniform.
You need to do a price inquiry
and complete that today.
Yes.
This is the stationary distribution list
for each department this month.
It's urgent too.
This is the information required
for an important meeting tomorrow.
Make 30 copies before you leave today
and place them on my desk.
Yes.
All right. That's your work for today.
That's all.
Yes.
Thank you, Ms. Liu.
Operations Department,
thank you for your hard work.
I'm really glad to introduce you today
to my only son, Daoming Si.
And to my future daughter-in-law, Yesha.
Hello, everyone.
Daoming Si will soon become
the third successor of Daoming Corp.
In the future,
please support Ah Si
and his soon-to-be wife, Yesha,
the same support you've shown me.
Shancai.
Long time no see.
-I...
You go first.
Do you know Sha is looking for you?
I know.
Thank you.
What did you want to say earlier?
I...
I forgot.
Shancai.
I remember what I want to say now.
Follow me.
But, I...
Save that for later. Let's go.
How nice.
We're eating mango dessert,
just like we used to do.
That's right.
Just like we used to do.
Shancai,
I'm really happy you accepted this job.
You can do it.
This way, I can get my freedom back.
So...
I'll share my courage to you.
With your courage and my courage together,
we can do anything.
Yesha,
we're good friends, right?
That's right.
So you won't lie to me.
Right?
That's right.
Then tell me,
why are you sacrificing your own freedom
for this scheme?
Did Daoming Feng threaten you
with some kind of condition?
No.
No, really.
I don't believe it.
This is not like you.
How come?
How come it's not like me?
I'm naturally playful.
Adults, they play around with politics.
As for us children, we play our own games.
After I left Bhutan,
I've been playing hide-and-seek
with my Dad
while traveling around the world.
I'm busted now.
So I can only wait for a good opportunity.
When the time comes, I'll sneak away.
Before I leave, though,
I hope I can help get back
Ah Xing's memory.
I want to see you two back together.
That's it.
But...
Hey.
Yes.
Manager.
I...
I'm with my friend.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Okay, I'll go back
and take care of it right away.
Yesha, I'm sorry.
My manager is looking for me.
I have to go.
It's my treat this time.
Okay, it's on you today.
I'll go ahead.
Shancai.
Let's have mango dessert again next time.
The season of mangoes is almost over.
We can have strawberry dessert next time.
Okay. Let's eat strawberry dessert.
Bye.
Daoming Si.
You need to make photocopies?
It's fine. You can go first.
It's fine. I'll come back later.
Shancai.
I can't figure out
how to use this machine.
I'll help you.
Thank you.
Why didn't you ask your assistant
to do this for you?
It's okay, I'm free anyway.
How would you like to copy that?
I want to shrink it
so I can paste it on my notebook.
Okay.
I'll shrink it to 50 percent then.
Like that.
Just press that button.
Will that do?
Yes.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Stupid Shancai.
Why are you shaking?
Have you forgotten why you are here?
Stupid.
Shancai.
Do you need anything else?
Nothing.
I just wanted to say...
welcome to our company.
Thank you.
This is a good beginning.
That's right.
As long as I don't give up,
every day will be a good beginning.
Subtitle translation by Kristin Tsang