Shancai.
-Qinghe.
-No work today?
I got someone to cover my shift today.
That's great.
We can finally have a nice chat today.
Qinghe.
Qinghe, do you remember me?
You are...
Don't you recognize me?
I'll give you a little hint.
During the morning registration
at Yingde College,
there was a poor girl
who was being humiliated.
Then, a hero showed up.
This hero solved the girl's problem
and gave her confidence.
From then on, the girl remembered
the figure of the hero in her heart.
Figure?
Do you remember, Qinghe?
Oh, you must be that hero, right?
You're so funny.
That hero is you.
Me?
I'm that girl who accepted your money.
I'm Mimi.
Mimi.
I remember now.
Sorry, I didn't recognize you earlier.
That's okay.
My dad said that a true hero helps people
without expecting anything in return.
I forgot to say. Please accept
my deepest gratitude.
Thank you.
Qinghe, why didn't you tell me
about that good deed?
Qinghe, this is...
This is my best friend
and my most understanding schoolmate,
Shancai.
You're that "weed,"
that hardworking virgin.
Shancai, the girlfriend
of the handsomest, richest,
and the leader of F4, Daoming Si.
I...
I'm so lucky.
I met two big shots
the moment I'm in Yingde College.
Shancai, may I shake your hands?
Oh, okay.
I'm so lucky. I'm holding Shancai's hand.
I'm so moved that I'm about to cry.
Nice to meet you, too.
Mimi.
Oh, Mimi.
It's an honor to meet both of you.
The honor is mine.
I believe your hero, Qinghe,
will take good care of you.
I'll do my best to repay your favor.
Oh, you don't have to.
Qinghe, I have a tiny problem right now.
Go ahead.
Please accept my sincere gratitude
and have dinner with me.
What? Dinner?
Hello, Shancai.
Morning.
School is about to start.
Even the air in Yingde College
smells different.
Is it because of the absence of F4?
Sorry.
Do you like my back-to-school gift?
Lei.
Why did you tease me like that?
I just want to remind you
of those disasters the F4 had caused.
So you will treasure the change.
Don't worry, I'll make my life better.
Why are you still sitting on the floor?
Stand up and chase your happiness.
Frightening me with a frog.
I'm here to apologize.
I'm sorry, I hit you at the airport.
I was too emotional.
I want to tell you that I won't give up
whether you like me or not.
I'll do everything I can
to bring back your memory.
This is my phone number.
Call me whenever you want.
That's okay if you don't want to call me.
I'll come to see you every day.
Boss, 10...
10:00 a.m.
Slow down, what's the rush?
Yes, sir.
I've just received a meeting notice.
The President and department managers
will review your marketing plan.
General Manager.
-General Manager.
Why are you so nervous?
Relax.
Yes, sir.
I'm not nervous at all.
-President.
Take your seats.
Let's cut to the chase.
We have Manager Ximen here. He will
brief us about his Autumn marketing plan.
Morning, everyone.
I don't have to tell you how complicated
marketing is.
I have the simplest explanation
for the marketing concept.
Great marketing comes
from sincere attitude.
This is the 2002 Autumn marketing plan
that I'll show you this meeting.
First, let's see the first slide.
This is our 2002 Autumn report.
We can see the difference among seasons
one, two, three, and four is small.
So I believe, in this way,
we can achieve...
What?
Sir, I'll go with you.
Thank you for your kindness.
But you can't.
Secretary Xu, try your best.
I hope I can visit you every now and then
after I leave this office.
But...
Manager Ximen, please go
to the General Manager's office.
Face what you have to face.
Sir.
That was amazing, Ximen.
Sir, you're flattering me.
No, I mean every word I said.
It was amazing.
No wonder why this morning
the President called me.
He said that he read
your whole plan last night.
And he loved it.
He thought it was great.
He was afraid of not being objective
when it comes to his son,
so he asked me to arrange this briefing.
He was so nervous about your briefing that
he booked a later flight to Singapore.
He saw the satisfied expressions
on the managers' faces halfway through it.
So then he went to catch the plane.
He even called me on the way.
He told me to convey his words to you.
The President told me
to tell you six words.
"Work as hard as you can."
Sha, pick up the phone already.
Pick up the phone.
Come on, pick up the phone!
Customers are coming.
Hey. Wipe that table for me.
We'll be late for class, hurry up.
-Thank you for coming.
Here you are, hot coffee.
Sir, please clean the table for me.
You didn't wipe the table.
Can't you wipe it by yourself?
-What's wrong with you?
-I'm sorry.
Please take your seat.
Wiping tables is what the boss does here.
He is bad at wiping tables. I'm sorry.
Please calm down,
and I'll take your order.
What would you like to eat?
-I'll have a hamburger with egg.
-Got it. Coming up.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
You are a jerk.
What do you mean I'm a jerk?
You are totally a jerk.
How could you take it out
on Ah Lun's customers?
Did Ah Lun force Yesha to leave?
Or did that customer force her to leave?
Don't you think you're being selfish?
What now? Want to fight?
Come on.
Let's see if you have the guts
to vent to me.
Don't take it out
on our breakfast restaurant.
Do you know why we are working so hard
at this breakfast restaurant,
with all these "Thanks for coming"
and "Welcome" we say every morning?
We consider it a real privilege
to see the sunrise every morning.
If the three of us can travel
around the world,
saying "Good morning" to the sunrise,
that will be our greatest happiness.
The three of us made a deal to travel
every corner of the world
to see every sunrise and to learn how to
say "Good morning" in every language.
To make it come true,
Ah Lun set up this restaurant
with his father's insurance compensation.
Making a fortune is never our goal.
All we want to do is achieve our dream.
I know my words are harsh,
but I'm telling you the truth.
I know you don't feel easy
after hearing my words,
but we care about you.
We don't know how to help you.
I drank with you yesterday,
but it didn't work.
You have to figure out by yourself
how to make yourself feel better.
Be happy.
If you're a tough guy,
you get her back.
Did I say something wrong?
It's full tomorrow.
How about the day after tomorrow?
Great, thank you.
It's full the day after tomorrow.
Why is it always out?
It's peak season now.
I don't care if it's peak season.
I didn't mean...
Could you find any available seats
at a later date? Thanks.
There's one three days from now.
Okay, I'll take it. Can I book it now?
No? Why?
40,000 bucks?
Cash only?
Okay, thank you.
40,000.
37, 38, 39, 40.
I think that's enough.
That's all we got.
I just want to ask you...
how to earn 40,000 bucks in two hours?
You can't earn 40,000 bucks in two hours.
But...
I lent it to you which means you have
to repay it later.
These two are the ones--
-Thank you.
-Don't you dare think of
terminating our dream time deposit.
Hey, what are you doing?
You borrowed money,
and now you want to hug my babe?
What? What will happen if I hug him?
I'll hug her for Ah Si.
-Get lost!
-What's wrong with hugging for Ah Si?
You two...
-Welcome.
-Sorry, sir, we're closed.
-We're closed.
Young master.
Young master, I'm the secretary
of your mother, Mrs. Daoming.
She told me to visit you.
Young master, I know you must be confused
by my unexpected visit.
Please accept my apology.
She worries about you.
She tried everything
to know where you are.
She just wants to meet you.
I know you're concerned
about the whereabouts of Miss Yesha.
Miss Yesha hasn't left Taiwan.
It's easy for her to locate Miss Yesha.
All you need to do is ask her.
Young master, I've told you what she said.
Goodbye. I won't take more of your time.
Goodbye.
-Thank you for coming.
"Young master"?
Who are you?
Do you feel better today?
We're working on your examination report.
You should stay in bed for a few days.
You need a good rest.
-Hi.
The staff of this hospital
have no common sense.
How is there no decoration,
not even a single flower in Yesha's room?
Besides the lack of common sense,
the doctors here are so ugly.
They hit the jackpot for receiving
such a beautiful patient.
Thank God you're here, Sha.
I missed you so much.
Me, too.
What?
Yes.
Okay, I'll be there to greet him.
Young master, you're finally back.
Young master, welcome.
-Young master, welcome.
I want to meet my mother.
-Hurry, guide our madam here.
-Understood.
Ah Si.
You're finally home.
Butler Liu.
Lead your young master to his room
to rest himself.
Understood.
Young master, this way, please.
Don't bother.
I have one favor to ask.
It's easy for us Daoming Family
to find someone.
I can find Yesha for you.
Are you sure?
I have the daily list
of the people exiting Taiwan.
Yesha clearly hasn't left Taiwan.
You know what I can do from this, right?
Is it true that Yesha hasn't left yet?
Trust me, Ah Si.
I can definitely get Yesha back for you.
But...
there's one condition.
Come back home, Ah Si.
I'll come back here when you find Yesha.
Deal.
I'll find her in one week.
I'll visit you in one week.
Yutian.
You only have one week.
Sorry, I fell asleep.
I was just worried about you.
It's good to see you back.
I'm leaving now.
We became enemies
because of this red note.
Then from enemies, we became...
This box contains a lot of our past.
I've thought about it.
Our past is no longer important to you.
But I want you to give it one more try.
I'll be relieved if you still decide
to be who you are now
after you've seen these memories.
Daoming Si.
Could you please take a good look at them?
I'll leave it to you.
Goodbye.
Hey.
Come in.
TAKE CARE
These are your memories.
Those are mine.
Shancai.
I just want you to know...
that it's never my intention to hurt you.
But these memories are everything I have
in my mind.
The only thing I can say to you is...
I'm sorry.
That is not true.
You own everything in this box, too.
Daoming Si.
You can love what you have now.
But you can't deny what happened
in the past.
Please try harder, okay?
Maybe things in this box
can wake up your memories.
What if they can never be woken up?
Should you wake up from your dream, too?
This is not fair.
Of course, they'll be forgotten
if you don't open the box.
Maybe you won't regret
if you forget about them.
But at least you can
try to get to know me again.
Hello, Daoming Si, I'm Shancai.
Shancai is a kind of weed.
A kind of weed that will stand straight up
even if it's stomped onto the ground.
I'm a person who never surrenders
to unfairness easily.
That's all for today. See you tomorrow.
Ah Si has lost his memory for now.
Who knows if he will
remember everything someday?
Shancai.
A lot of tomorrows are waiting for you
in this world.
Lei is right.
Maybe Daoming Si will remember
everything tomorrow.
Daoming Si will remember everything
tomorrow.
Wait.
Let me go through it again.
You fell in love with him.
Ah Xing fell in love with you.
You decided to back out
because of a girl called Shancai.
Yesha.
I don't understand
why you have to do this to yourself.
Ah Xing and Shancai
would remain a happy couple
if the accident didn't happen.
Shancai is the one who suffers the most.
Will Ah Xing be happy
if you give him back to her now?
He has forgotten Shancai long ago.
He loves you and you love him.
You're torturing everyone now.
But, one day, Ah Xing will be in pain
for loving me right?
Miss Yesha.
Your doctor is waiting for you
in his room.
Miss Yesha.
The examination report shows
that you have an autoimmune disease.
It's called multiple sclerosis.
Multiple sclerosis?
What does it mean, doctor?
It's a very rare disease.
The symptoms are complex and various.
It might damage your nerve endings
and muscles.
It may cause atrophy or paralysis.
It may damage your brain nerves
or your eyesight.
The symptoms may differ greatly.
Due to the limitation
of current medical technologies,
bone marrow transplant
is your only choice.
You mean...
I'll be lying in bed forever?
Or blind?
Well...
Doctor, if a bone marrow transplant
will fix her,
I'll donate mine to Yesha.
The problem is,
it's hard to find a compatible one.
Even if she receives the treatment,
her chance of recovery is fairly low.
When will I be blind?
When will I not be able to move?
How much time do I have left?
Considering your increasing symptoms
and your complications,
I think...
you have about three months.
Why did you get up?
Sha.
I'm going to leave the hospital.
-Yesha.
-I don't want to waste my life.
Sha, no one knows me better than you.
I'm running out of time.
How could I stay here?
I'm going to travel the world.
I'm going to see every corner
of the world.
Remember them.
Paint them.
Before I go blind,
before I can't move...
I'm going to live my life to the fullest.
Sha, I'm going to leave the hospital.
Okay.
We'll leave tomorrow.
We'll travel the world tomorrow.
Sha, you're the best.
You're the best.
Ma'am.
So the reason why it's so hard to find out
who Miss Yesha is,
she isn't an ordinary person.
So I assume everything
is under your control now?
Yes, ma'am.
Daoming Si!
Daoming Si, I miss you so much.
I really miss you so much.
You're right in front of me,
but why do I miss you more?
Subtitle translation by Logan Zhao