Why are we going to the library?
Like Zhongze said,
if our family business in Taiwan
is that big,
we can find something about my family
by searching through
all the newspapers and magazines.
Maybe,
this can make me remember something.
I know this isn't a smart idea, but...
You know, I can't expose who I am,
and I can't let my family know I'm looking
for them. It's a hard thing to do.
Yes.
I mean, you can't just grab someone,
and then ask, "Do you know where
the Daoming family is?"
Why not?
The problem is...
Young lady.
Excuse me. Do you know where
the Daoming family is?
-The Daoming family?
-Yes.
Of course, I know.
Who doesn't know the Daoming Family?
What?
Where is the Daoming Family?
They own many corporations in Taiwan.
So many. Like everywhere.
-Yeah.
-Really?
So...
So where is it? You didn't tell me.
Do you see that palace-like building?
That's run by that family.
You're really weird.
Seriously?
What a coincidence.
Then...
Shall we take a look?
No way.
-The pillow in the room isn't soft enough.
-Yes, ma'am.
-The fruit basket isn't fresh enough.
-The room delivery service is sub-par.
-Yes, ma'am.
-The menu needs an update.
Useless people have no place
in the Daoming family.
We fire employees who deserve it.
Yes, ma'am.
Of course.
You are included.
Yes, ma'am.
So remember the words I just said,
because I won't say them again.
-Do you understand?
-Yes.
Also,
that's not your dust storage.
-Wipe it clean as soon as possible.
-Yes, ma'am.
I don't know what I'm afraid of.
My mother can't be meaner
than the landlady.
Yet I don't know why my feet...
An abnormal stranger.
That's okay if she's just any stranger.
She's a stranger
that should be familiar to you.
That's what you're afraid of.
I'll see what I can dig up.
Your mother is our only lead.
However, since you have a huge family,
your mother shouldn't be
your only family member.
I believe there must be nice people
in your family.
Your mother is really killing it.
She got tons of work every day.
No matter she's in her office or others',
she is always doing business,
even when she is eating.
She won't eat the dishes she ordered.
When she's free from business and eating,
her mouth still won't stop,
because she's scolding people.
Hey, the routine.
My mother's routine is the point, okay?
Speaking of her routine, we got a problem.
There are some places
that she visits every day,
like restaurants and offices.
Yet she doesn't have a fixed schedule.
Sometimes she would go straight home,
change her clothes and head out again.
Then, what are we doing here?
Don't worry.
I've followed her for days,
and I finally get an action window.
This is her only fixed routine.
The restaurant is her first stop
every day.
After 12 minutes, at 7:57 a.m.,
she arrives at the restaurant.
Once she receives the message,
we have 12 minutes before she comes back.
Sir.
-Young master.
-Get out of my way.
Butler Liu, the young master comes back...
It's strange. How...
Young master. It's indeed you!
You finally come back.
Okay, start timing.
Start...
What's the matter?
Hello, ma'am, I'm Butler Liu.
Yes. I'm reporting to you that
the young master is back.
He brought a girl with him.
She is not Shancai.
She... looks like a foreigner.
Listen.
Stop the young master no matter what.
Understood. I'll go find him right now.
Understood...
Everyone, assemble!
The young master is back
but he's gone again!
Find the young master!
Tell the driver to park the car
at the entrance. Quickly.
There are more up there. Let's go.
Quick.
Young master...
Why don't you tell me
there are so many people?
-How could I know?
-Let's go.
Go after them!
Young master...
-Yesha, quick...
-I thought I lost you.
Quick.
Be careful.
Quick, Yesha.
-Come in, quick...
-Come in here.
Young master, I finally found you.
-You...
-I'm warning you.
Don't follow me. Do you hear me?
Quick!
Young master, don't run away!
Young master, come back!
What are you waiting for? Go get them.
-Understood.
You go that way. I'll go this way.
Ah Xing.
Ah Xing, what's wrong with you?
Is this the right room?
Young master.
Young master, you come back.
Young master, what's wrong with you?
You don't recognize me?
You don't even recognize me.
I'm Aunt Yu.
Only eight minutes left.
Young master.
Don't be afraid.
It's me, Aunt Yu, who raised you up.
How can I harm you?
Take them down.
What are you doing?
The madam told us to keep you here.
Don't make this harder.
Quick, go.
Young master, don't leave me.
Young master, come back.
-Young master.
-Get out of my way.
Young master.
Follow me.
Go.
Watch out, Aunt Yu.
Ma'am, the young master...
He... is gone.
You useless people!
Keep searching.
Inside and outside the house.
Find them no matter what.
Yes, ma'am.
You, go that way. You two, go that way.
You two, follow me.
The gate must be heavily guarded.
Don't fall into the trap.
This is the only way.
Now, go.
Young master.
Go.
Ma'am.
Where are they?
Who?
You mean the young master.
I heard he's back.
I might saw him just now.
I followed him and...
he disappeared.
You useless people!
You can't even stop two people.
Continue searching.
You must find them.
Understood.
That was close.
I know my family is rich,
but I don't know the house is that huge.
I felt so cold in there.
-Cold?
-Yes.
Cold.
Except around that granny.
You mean Aunt Yu.
Aunt Yu.
Weird. She seems to be
a nice person to me,
but why can't I remember anything?
-Who is she?
-Leave it be.
Now, we have the photo.
They seem to be your classmates.
We have new leads now.
Your school and your classmates.
Ah Si came back? Was he alone?
No. There was a girl.
I don't know her.
Could it be another Zhongze?
She doesn't look like a bad guy.
She was helping our young master.
She was kind to him.
How kind?
Well...
Master Ximen.
I... I'm not sure about that.
No matter who she is,
she's good if she treats Ah Si nicely.
Aunt Yu.
They just broke in,
messed around,
and left again?
He was afraid of being caught by Madam.
If he was caught again,
he'll be locked up.
Is it like challenging the 18 Bronzemen?
Yes.
Ah Si is always full of surprise.
No one can predict his next move.
This is something Ah Si could do.
Masters, I've been here for a long time.
I have to get back now.
I'll tell you if there's any news
about the young master.
Thank you, Aunt Yu.
What are you doing?
I will tell Shancai about this.
How do you like it, sir?
Thank you.
Please have a taste of our fruit wine.
Do you want to give it a try, young lady?
It's very delicious. Do you want
to taste fruit wine, young lady?
It's really delicious.
Please have a taste of our fruit wine.
Do you want to give it a try, young lady?
Orange, strawberry, Hami melon flavors.
It's really delicious.
Please have a taste of our fruit wine.
She's not answering.
It's weird. Shancai's phone
is either off or not answered.
You, too?
What is Shancai doing?
I don't think she's doing anything.
She's hiding.
Doing or hiding. It's fine
as long as she doesn't lose her memory.
We can just search the entire Taipei.
Boss.
This is Ximen.
Is Shancai there?
Could you please tell me
the other places she's working at?
Aunt Yu, you're back.
Ma... ma'am.
Did you meet Ah Si?
That's just what I thought.
There are so many people in the house.
Ah Si and that girl
don't have wings on them.
How could they just disappear?
Aunt Yu.
Did you help them sneak out?
No, ma'am.
I met Master Ximen and Master Meizuo.
I... I didn't meet our young master.
I don't know who he's with.
I don't know where he is now.
Aunt Yu.
At your age,
your brain's not working very well.
Ma'am.
Are you bringing up my retirement again?
I shouldn't have pitied you.
You said you heard Ah Si was sick
and you're too worried to sleep.
You kept begging me,
so I brought you back.
But the person you are now
can't tell what's good and bad for Ah Si
and can't be assigned to manage the house.
Quit your job and enjoy your life,
or it'll be a burden
for the both of us.
Ma'am.
No one knows more
about this family than me.
I'm not in charge of managing it.
But our young master.
Why did he have to sneak
into his own house?
Why did he have to run away like that?
The young master was raised by me.
So, no matter what,
even I'm too old to walk,
I will protect the young master
to the end.
Don't you remember?
Ah Si doesn't remember you anymore,
so your appearance in the house
has no influence on Ah Si.
You've done a lot
for the Daoming family in decades.
So...
Don't sabotage your reputation
built by yourself at this age.
Your things are packed up by Butler Liu.
Just tell Butler Liu to send a car
to take you to your desired place.
Please have a taste of our fruit wine.
Orange, strawberry, Hami melon flavors.
It's delicious.
Do you want to taste
our fruit wine, young lady?
Please have a taste of our fruit wine.
Do you want to taste our fruit wine, sir?
It tastes strange.
But it's not bad.
How do you know I'm here?
We're here to sort you out.
Shancai, some friend you are.
Why are you wearing such an ugly costume?
Sir, do you want to taste our fruit wine?
Thank you.
She said "thank you" to us.
How should we scold her?
Want to taste it? It's very delicious.
Thank you.
Want to drink some fruit tea, young lady?
No, thank you.
Hey, Shancai.
Why are you exhausting yourself like that?
I want to make some money.
Besides paying my tuition,
I...
I'll tell it to you straight.
Do you know
those large electronic billboards?
I want to put on an ad to find Daoming Si.
Of course, I won't expose his identity.
However, it costs a lot to have such ad,
so I'm taking on one more job.
Why didn't you tell us about this?
Because you said it's stupid
to go high-profile.
The more I think about it,
the more stupid I realize it is.
I'm glad I didn't tell you that day,
or I would get scolded for shit.
Really?
I haven't seen a stinky snail before.
Who are you implying a snail?
I haven't scolded you yet.
What kind of message is that?
How can snail go upside down
with its shell?
You can carry me on your back and try it.
I'm not gonna fall into your trap.
If I stand upside down with you
on my back,
I will be the snail.
It's weird.
He told me to come here
without showing up.
What is Meizuo up to?
HUMOR TIME
AH SI, I'LL BE WAITING FOR YOU FOREVER
0917-595600
Lei, Ximen, Meizuo, thank you.
Thank you.
AH SI, I'LL BE WAITING FOR YOU FOREVER
0917-595600
-Hi.
-Where are you?
-Who is this?
-I'm Si.
-No, you're not.
-Oh, I miss you so much.
Quit messing with me.
I'm waiting for a call.
Hello.
My name is Ah Si, too. I can show you
my ID card if you don't believe me.
Sir, you're going too far.
Come on, making a friend
costs you nothing.
I'm begging you, okay? I'm waiting
for a very important phone call.
I'm taking on two jobs,
working over ten hours every day
just for this ad.
He is missing and he might be in danger
and all I can do is to wait.
Waiting to hear his voice.
Even what he looks like
when he is talking is getting blurry.
I regret I didn't take more photos of him.
I regret I didn't record him with V8.
Do you know what is regret?
Have you ever experienced it?
Because if you have,
I'm begging you to leave me alone,
and stop jamming the phone, okay?
Hello.
Sorry, it's me again.
I forget to tell you
that I hope you can find Si very soon.
I'm rooting for you.
PAYPHONE
Hello.
Shan Cai, why didn't you answer
your phone?
Did you see that?
Thank you.
Hello.
Do you want to know where Ah Si is?
Come out and drink a cup of coffee.
Boring.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It's just...
I've been answering
random calls all night.
Didn't Ah Si call you?
Everyone was claiming they were Ah Si.
Young lady, do you want a cup of coffee?
Great, where?
Talk.
-Meizuo.
-Why don't you talk?
-What are you gonna do?
-Beat him up.
Forget it.
Hey, why did you turn off the phone?
Do you want to get those harassing calls?
What if Daoming Si calls me?
Your call will go to voicemail.
We'll start charging after the "beep."
Please hang up
if you won't leave a message.
Hello.
Hello. Talk.
You are Ah Si, right?
I'm telling you, you boring sick bastard.
I'll beat you up if you call again.
Why are there so many boring people?
Give it back.
Shancai.
Maybe this is not the right way.
Give it back.
Could you please see the reality?
I like it, okay?
This is my only hope now.
I didn't get the person
but a bunch of problems.
I should've left my phone number
and taught them a lesson.
We hope Shancai could be the first one
to get Ah Si's call.
Turn off the billboard.
The more you hope,
the more disappointed you will be.
I'm worried about another breakdown
of Shancai.
Maybe after a few breakdowns,
she can accept the fact.
Sometimes I really wonder
if you're from outer space.
I am.
Come on.
There won't be four of us anyway.
We won't have many opportunities
to drink together.
Cheers.
Why won't we have
many opportunities to drink?
I was hoping to celebrate with you
after we find Ah Si.
Celebrate for what?
I'm going to work tomorrow.
The graduation trip is over.
It's time to do some work.
That's right.
The graduation trip is over.
Cheers!
You are not the "si"
in one, two, three, four.
You are this "Si."
You're called F4 in Yingde.
Do you know what is F4?
You're young dudes that are like brothers.
Like four flowers.
Everyone in our school knows you.
I've been asking around. See.
I got their phone numbers and addresses.
I called them.
I saw their missing person poster.
What missing person poster?
The electronic billboards on the streets.
I called them and was scolded.
Who are they?
How could they scold people like that?
They're looking for you
but are scolding you.
Maybe they didn't know who you are.
Even I wasn't myself,
they can't scold people like that.
Maybe I shouldn't know who they are.
Maybe I shouldn't know who I am.
Ah Xing.
Why does it seem
that everyone around me is bad?
What kind of people was I?
Who am I?
What are you doing?
Tearing down the house?
-Granny.
-See.
I knew it. You won't help me water them.
My flowers are dying of thirst.
Let me help you.
-Now?
-Okay.
-Right now.
You should change if you want to.
Your past stays in the past.
It's who you are now that matters.
The most important thing is,
remember paying your rent.
-Go water them.
-Will do...
If my babies die of thirst,
-I'll come for you.
-Don't worry, Granny. I'm watering them.
-What are you doing?
-Putting out your fire.
You're the one that should be watered.
Why did you water me?
You're laughing now.
Are you happy now?
-Out of water...
-You...
Senior.
Who are you?
I'm doing a life interview
about the graduating seniors.
I don't know if you're available now.
Life interview?
I don't think it's necessary.
Please, senior.
This will affect my sociology score
in the next semester.
Please, senior.
All right, get in the car.
Thank you.
I don't remember meeting you in Yingde?
How could you remember
all the girls in Yingde?
I remember all the beautiful ones.
So I'm not beautiful enough?
You are.
You are beautiful and smart.
I'm so happy
that I get praised by a senior.
Right, have you started working?
We want to know what you will do
after graduation.
You must be working
in your family corporations, right?
Speaking of it, Ximen is the first one
to settle down.
Lei and I will start working soon.
How about Daoming Si?
He hasn't returned
from the graduation trip.
Please don't get mad
at the question I'll ask you.
Go ahead.
Why are there rumors saying
that Daoming Si is in trouble?
Are there?
Who says that?
The missing person posters
in the newspapers
and the large billboard on the street.
You must be very worried, right?
You're so close.
Isn't this a life interview?
Why is it a soul interview now?
Subtitle translation by Logan Zhao