Our manager wants you to send these
to the shipping department.
Oh, thank you.
Hello.
Ximen is in the hospital?
All right. Got it.
Okay, thank you.
Daoming Si.
-Ximen--
-Ximen is in the hospital.
The five of them turned back
into what they were before.
Great.
Come on.
I brought you video games.
Put it away.
And VCD.
You throw things at me
after I just had a surgery?
All right, there's more.
You can watch whatever you want.
I'll set it up for you later.
How do you like it?
Is there anything else you need?
I'm going to leave the hospital very soon.
You weakling. Staying here
for a few days won't kill you.
Lei and I will visit you every day.
Right, Lei?
I'm fine with it.
But I have a condition.
What is it?
I'll lie in your bed.
Ximen has such a huge bed.
You two can lie together.
Hi, Meizuo.
Hey, Shancai.
Ximen.
Why did you just tell us now
that you're in the hospital?
Are you okay?
I became okay the moment I saw you.
Take a seat.
Are you okay?
Why do you have such dark circles
under your eyes?
I do?
Yeah.
You can let Ah Si tell you.
Really?
Thanks.
Oh, my gosh.
It's pretty serious.
But at least I don't have
gastric perforation.
Ximen.
She's being sarcastic.
That's our Shancai.
She thrives in hardship.
I think the Empress Dowager brought out
your weed spirit.
Who's the Empress Dowager?
The Empress Dowager is your mother,
Mrs. Daoming.
That is the right word for her.
Hello.
Do I have to go?
Okay.
What's the matter?
My mom...
It's nothing.
How could you say it's nothing
with your long face?
Yeah.
You look upset.
Are you going to have a blind date?
Am I right?
No way, Meizuo.
Why are you laughing at me?
It's already a bad day for me, okay?
Go ahead.
Go see your perfect wife
that your mom has picked for you.
What does she look like?
What do you think she looks like?
A big butt that will have my baby.
Always having that auspicious look
on her face.
Stop laughing.
It hurts.
Don't let me catch you having a surgery.
I tell you that.
She's Ying Xiaociao, the daughter
of the president of Jundi Construction.
She just graduated from the US.
Another precious pretty face
with no brain.
You've turned into a young adult
after all these years.
This is Mrs. Ying.
Nice to meet you, ma'am.
Nice to meet you.
Xiaociao just received her master degree
in music in the US.
She can play cello very well.
I heard her performance just now.
Thank you, everyone.
I'd like to know if there's any song
you want to listen to?
I'll perform it for you.
Meizuo, what do you want to listen to?
I'll have Xiaociao play it for you.
The world's famous, "Doraemon."
I'm sorry, I don't know this song.
No?
Such a classic.
Never mind, that's okay.
Just play whatever you like.
Not bad, right?
What's wrong with finding one
with the same social status?
What's good about it?
Besides having the same social status,
what's wrong about it?
Her education, her family.
She's beautiful and elegant.
I think she is perfect.
The harder you push me,
the worse I think she is.
I tell you what, I'm not pushing you.
What I mean is
you can be normal friends at first.
You keep changing your girlfriends.
You can treat her like a normal friend.
If you think she's good, good.
If not, I have a long list in my hands.
You can pick from it.
How is that?
Do you want to date her,
or you want me to find you another one?
Fine, I'll do it.
I'll ask her out on a date
when I'm free, okay?
Okay. I have planned it out for you.
You'll pick Xiaociao up at her place
at 2:00 p.m. tomorrow, okay?
How could you?
I won't do that.
Fine. Then I will arrange a date for you
with the daughter from the Fuguo Hotel.
Mom.
Are you going or not?
I'll go.
That's my boy.
Hello, I'm Ah...
I'm Daoming Si.
Mom.
No, Ximen is sick.
I just visited him in the hospital.
Shancai is his friend.
Why can't she be there?
Okay.
I know.
Master Daoming Si.
Why are you here in person?
If there's anything you want,
you can just call--
I'm looking for Shancai.
Got it.
Shancai, come here.
What's the matter?
I'll leave you to it.
-I heard your dad sells cars?
-That's right.
Could you do me a favor?
Order a van for me.
I want it to be exactly the same
as this design.
It's so cute.
Yesha designed this.
Yesha designed this?
How is she so talented?
Remember, the same as this van.
I'll try my best.
Great, thank you.
I knew you would help me.
-No problem.
-I have to go now.
No wonder Daoming Si loves Yesha so much.
She is pretty, smart, and talented.
What do I have to compete with Yesha?
He's gone now. What are you staring at?
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Did I wake you up?
How do you feel? Are you hungry?
Do you need some warm milk?
You can go rest.
That's okay. I'm fine.
What's the matter? Can't fall asleep?
I slept too much in the day.
This book is pretty good.
I just started it.
"Maybe as I get older,
I become more mature.
I'm done saying what I have to say.
People don't have the desire
to listen to me anymore.
Maybe I'm bored with this shady world.
People keep questioning my stories.
It's just like when I was in biology class
in high school.
I was fiddling with
and poking that anesthetized frog.
I was observing the origin of life.
In the end,
that poor little thing was killed."
In 25 years,
it seems that I've never read to you.
We've never had a talk,
because you never come home.
It's not like I didn't want to.
I have a home that I can't go back to.
Because Mom...
I've only loved one woman in my life.
But she's never loved me
even for a minute.
The first time I saw your mother,
I told myself,
"I would get her no matter what it takes."
Her fiancée worked for your grandfather.
It couldn't be easier to break them up.
I was thinking
that it was so easy
to win a woman's heart.
But I was wrong.
I've been doing this business for decades.
I think ahead of others.
I defeated so many enemies.
I survived so many crises.
But I can't survive this one.
I can't defeat this man.
Because...
he's hiding inside your mother's heart.
He's untouchable.
Finally, I understand.
I'll never have the chance
to defeat this man.
Dad.
Could you please
finish reading that article?
"No matter what the reason is,
I find there are fewer and fewer people
telling the story of Christmas box
at Christmas."
Ximen told me
that the Empress Dowager brings out
Shancai's weed spirit.
Do you know who is the Empress Dowager?
The Empress Dowager is my mom.
It's funny, right?
It's so funny.
Right. I gave your design to Shancai.
She said she will help.
She kept saying that you're so talented.
Of course, I said
that my Yesha is the best.
Yesha.
You have to paint more.
And you have to paint really hard.
I'll arrange an art show for you.
Do you hear me?
Yesha.
She must have fallen asleep.
You lazy pig.
I'll pick you up at eight.
Get off the car.
Eight might be too early.
Aristocratic girls like you
are good at shopping.
I'll come here at ten.
See you at ten.
Now get off the car.
May I ask why?
This date has been arranged
by our mothers.
I think we're independent people,
so we don't have to stick
to this boring plan.
Happy shopping. See you at ten.
She's got some strong personality.
You keep changing your girlfriends.
You can treat her like a normal friend.
If you think she's good, good.
If not, I have a long list in my hands.
You can pick from it.
How is that?
Do you want to date her,
or you want me to find you another one?
It's so late, and the wind is so strong.
Why hasn't Shancai come home from work?
Honey!
I'll do it.
What are you doing?
I'll stop now. Don't get the food.
Here.
It's amazing.
Just look at it for a while.
-Veggie egg porridge.
-Honey.
-Yeah.
I suddenly got this bad feeling.
-What?
-I think we'll finally be destroyed
by that woman, Daoming Feng.
Yeah.
That woman is up to no good
from the start.
She assigns overtime work
to our daughter every night,
but she only gives her a low salary.
Well... No.
Money is not the most important problem.
The most important thing is, Shancai comes
home so late every day because of her.
She wants me to starve to death.
So I'll never let her scheme succeed.
-Stop eating.
-Oh, you...
-Fine. I won't eat.
-Mom, I'm home.
-Shancai, you're back.
It smells so good.
Grab some food to restore your strength.
So that you'll have the power
to fight that evil woman.
Who is that evil woman?
Who else could she be?
Of course, I mean that Daoming Feng.
Fine.
Dad, why are you staring at them?
Let's eat.
That's right.
You could've said it earlier.
I've waited for it for so long.
Why did you come home so late?
Come on. Take a seat.
-Let's eat. Come on.
-All right. I'll put my bag away first.
Okay. Hurry up.
Hey. Eat slowly, will you?
There are vegetables here.
-Mom, this is for you.
-Okay.
I feel so happy that our whole family
can eat dinner together.
-Dad.
-Yeah?
There won't be any problem
about the car delivery tomorrow, right?
Honey.
Your veggie egg porridge is perfect.
It's so amazing
that I can never have enough of it.
It's all thanks to your sales performance
for this month.
Otherwise, we might not be able
to afford congee.
Shancai, you should introduce your dad
to more rich guys.
No. I mean, good friends.
No matter who they are,
as long as your dad is selling cars,
our sales performance will be improved.
-Just like the last time,
-Yeah, right.
that Master Huaze Lei.
He is our lifesaver.
-Thanks, Mom.
-Right? Hey.
Got rice on my face?
Just wipe it off.
Shancai, who is the one
ordering the van from us?
It must be Master Qinghe, right?
No.
Then it must be
your new aristocratic friend, right?
Actually, it's Daoming Si.
He...
Has he regained his memory?
That's great.
Your relationship with Daoming Si,
hey, is just like
this veggie egg porridge.
It's so thick that no one can break it.
You're inseparable.
Dad, stop writing your cheesy script.
Daoming Si hasn't regained his memory.
He ordered that van for Yesha.
Yesha?
You mean that weird princess?
Shancai.
Things between Daoming Si and me
are not what you're thinking.
All I can say is that we're friends now.
Maybe it's hard for you to imagine,
but this is the most suitable word
to describe our relationship now.
At least he won't reject
my concern for him.
This is very important to me.
Really very important.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Hello.
Daoming Si.
Tomorrow morning at nine o'clock,
you can go talk to my dad.
You're welcome.
Dad, tomorrow morning at nine o'clock,
Daoming Si will be there to take the van.
No problem. I know.
Let's eat.
In the story of Daoming Si,
I've turned from the protagonist
into a supporting role.
Everyone thinks that I'm stupid,
that I'm crazy.
This is how things are.
I can't step out
of the Daoming Si's story.
There's no way out.
Guess who I am.
What?
Are you thinking about something?
No.
Let me tell you something.
It's bad news. Don't get upset.
What is it?
Promise me first that you won't get upset.
Just tell me already.
The breakfast van is ready.
-Really? Are you sure?
-Yes.
-Yeah.
-How did you know that?
I just saw it.
-Really? You saw it.
-Yeah.
Or did they just tell you that?
What do you think?
Why is your score so low?
You suck.
Okay, one more round.
I'll defeat you.
You've told me that ten times today.
You look down on me, huh?
Maybe I can't beat you in some things,
but today, I'm going to win.
Yeah, you're the best.
Your mind is somewhere else.
What happened?
Whose mind is somewhere else?
Just go if you have things to do.
I'm going to be out of the hospital today.
Didn't you say that I got nothing to do?
Give me a moment.
Hello.
Didn't I tell you I'm with Ximen
at the hospital?
This is not an excuse.
This is a reason.
Fine. I'll pick her up.
Still on your blind date tour?
Are you dumping her
because she's too ugly?
It's not like that.
So maybe she's too hot
and out of your league?
Nonsense. I, Meizuo--
Then go get her.
What are you doing here?
It's because you're going
to be discharged today.
I'll take you home.
Oh, come on.
My mom and dad will pick me up
after I get discharged.
It's because you like her so much.
You're acting like you don't like her.
Who's acting?
It hurts! I'm a patient!
Fine.
I'll go get her.
I'll let her know that I'm not a guy
she can handle.
What a friend you are! It hurts!
Okay. I'm sorry.
Soda.
Good boy.
I'm leaving now.
-Drive safe.
-Okay.
Why are we here again?
Shopping must be a hobby
for ladies like you.
I have no interest in shopping
with a lady.
I apologize for our last date.
I should've paid your bill.
Everything you are going to buy today
is on me.
You don't need to pick me up.
I don't need to?
Be careful.
Mom, I'm fine now.
Don't treat me like a patient.
The doctors only allowed you
to leave the hospital.
They didn't say
that your body is fully recovered.
I know.
That's why I didn't go to the company,
instead I went home with you.
Don't think about your company for now.
I tell you what. You have to rest at home
for at least one week.
Three days.
Five days.
Four days, okay?
Five days, that's a deal.
I'm not doing business with you.
Ma'am, your husband is back.
I just went to the hospital.
The nurse said you had already gone home.
I thought you were busy
so I didn't call you.
Let me help you set your things up.
You should chat with your dad, okay?
Our son just came home.
How about we have dinner together tonight?
Right, Mom.
It's a chance to help me recover, right?
What would you like to eat?
Spicy wontons, of course.
You can't eat spicy food now.
Then they are just wontons, right?
You just can't eat spicy food now, okay?
Mom, what's the matter?
Did you send Xiaociao's friend home?
What?
I didn't know
that my son is so thoughtful.
I loved that dress.
What are you talking about?
Don't be shy.
Xiaociao brought the gifts home.
You're so dumb.
Why didn't you send Xiaociao back first
before you sent her friend home?
Xiaociao brought a lot of stuff
by herself.
You don't know how to take care of others,
just like your dad.
Okay, I just want to tell you--
-Mom, that--
-I'm very happy now, it's okay.
Xiaociao...
What do you want?
What do you mean?
I mean, do you have any idea
what you're doing?
My mom and your mom
are planning our future for us.
Don't you know that?
Yes, I know.
That's why I'm dating you.
You mean, you accept
what they planned for you?
Do you like being their puppet,
doing whatever they tell you to do?
You're right that my parents
have encouraged me to date you.
But considering our family backgrounds
and education,
we are perfect for each other.
Why can't you be like me?
Calm down
and try to be in a relationship with me.
After all, you're a man.
You won't lose anything,
no matter how this turns out.
But we don't have feelings for each other.
Feelings can be developed.
And you don't know me at all.
You don't know me, either.
But at least I know you're a good man.
Okay, I'll show you how good I am.
Come on.
Tired, right?
Cheers.
-Cheers.
Meizuo.
Don't you want to introduce us?
Hi, nice to meet you.
I'm Xiaociao, girlfriend of Meizuo.
Girlfriend?
What a coincidence.
I'm Meizuo's girlfriend number 8.
She's number 20.
What about you?
What's your number?
I don't know what my number is.
But I'm sure that I'm the last one.
I think you don't really know Meizuo.
Since you know Meizuo very well,
can I consult you about Meizuo
from now on?
You want to consult us?
But Meizuo still surprises us
in different ways every now and then.
What part do you want to consult with us?
The best parts, of course.
But I'm afraid
that you can't learn them well.
There's nothing I haven't learned well
since my childhood.
Especially your so-called best parts.
Can you learn something like this well?
Hurry up, Daoming Si
has regained his memory!
Subtitle translation by Logan Zhao