(2025 Madam Sun's Dumplings)
(Printing Agency)
(Demolish)
(March 1, 2024, 10:00)
(March 1, 2025, 10:00)
(If you can connect
to the dual space-time phone,)
(then it's still not too late.)
=Present, is Present=
(Fu Ming Hospital, Inpatient Department,
Outdoor Parking Lot, Indoor Parking Lot)
Dr. Xing,
don't just look at the X-ray image.
Look at us too.
The X-ray image is more interesting.
I'll look at it first.
He's shy.
Hello, Wei.
What?
(Fu Ming Hospital's Doctor, Xing Nan)
Okay. I'll be there at once.
Dr. Xing, thank you for today.
Although there's nothing wrong
with your physical examination today,
if you feel unwell,
visit me at the hospital at once.
Mr. Wei, see you tomorrow.
Have a rest tomorrow.
Take it as a replacement leave.
Thank you, Mr. Wei.
Mr. Wei.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. Are you okay?
I'm fine too.
What were the two of you doing?
Fast and Furious?
Yuan Xia's car was tampered with.
I suspect that she was targeted
by Zhou Wei
due to what happened
in the bar last night.
He wouldn't go that far.
We are under the rule of law now.
You can't just kill someone
as you please.
Moreover, you were in the car too.
With your dad's will as a safety amulet,
Zhou Wei has no reason to kill you
before the next Board Meeting.
If you die...
No. I'm just saying
that if anything happens to you,
all 54% shares of the MU Group
will be donated to charity.
Zhou Wei is not a fool.
I got into her car by chance.
Zhou Wei wouldn't have known
that I would be in Yuan Xia's car.
Based on the condition of the car,
the person who tampered with the car
wanted to kill Yuan Xia.
Even if she didn't die,
she would be severely hurt.
Does Yuan Xia know about it?
The less she knows, the safer she is.
I'm just worried
that if she continues staying
by my side,
she'll eventually...
It's time to make a decision.
=Episode 2=
(The Gears of Fate Has Begun to Turn)
- My car is totaled.
- Your car is totaled.
- Compensate me.
- I'll compensate you.
I'll compensate you.
My phone too.
I'm sure there's
a silver lining to this.
(I wonder if this old phone
still works.)
(March 1, 2024, 20:00)
Mr. Heng.
Are you looking for me? Come in.
It's okay.
Some urgent came up and
I have to go out for a while.
I have a present for you.
You have to take good care of it.
(I wonder what happened
to that young boy)
(and Mr. Heng who gave me the phone.)
I...
I have been fired?
(Termination Letter)
(Printing Agency)
Wei Ziqi.
How dare he fire me?
How could he fire me just like that?
How could he?
Even if he wants to fire me,
he has to give me a reason.
Yuan, are you here
to eat dumplings?
No.
I'm rushing to the company. Thank you.
(Madam Sun's Dumplings)
Move aside.
Wei Ziqi.
Why did you fire me?
Do I need a reason to fire you?
I've had enough of you.
You are so controlling of me.
And that's very annoying.
Do you know that?
Also, have you forgotten
that I almost died because of you?
I've specifically asked
our Finance Department
to give you the 2N+1 compensation.
For the sake
of our two years of friendship,
let's settle this amicably.
(Lancheng Bank)
Should I thank you
for being so generous?
Yuan Xia,
there's no need to reject the money.
You agreed to become my assistant
because of the money too, right?
Take the money and leave.
I'm paying this money to buy my freedom.
Of course I won't reject the money.
If it wasn't for money,
how do you think I endured you
for the past two years?
At first, I thought
that you were just lazy
but still a decent person.
I even worried
about the situation you were in.
But now, I think you deserve everything
that's happening to you.
Miss Yuan, don't be
so foolhardy just because
Mr. Wei is being nice.
Did I allow you to speak?
I want to hear
how much resentment you've accumulated
against me over the years.
I have nothing to say
to a person like you.
What is it?
You have nothing to say, right?
Why aren't you leaving?
What are you doing?
Are you trying to scam me?
Yuan Xia.
Yuan Xia!
Don't just stand there!
Call the ambulance!
Yuan Xia.
Yuan Xia, don't scare me, okay?
(Fu Ming Hospital)
Ms. Wang.
Let her do
a brain CT scan later.
There's no need to refer her
to another doctor.
I'll look at the scan myself.
Okay.
Thank you.
Dr. Xing.
What is it?
Actually, today is my...
Your birthday, right?
I know. I've prepared a gift for you.
So, you remember.
Then tonight, I...
I remember the birthday
of everyone in our department.
Did you not buy this eye cream
just for me?
I bought a gift for the matron
for her birthday.
I bought two pieces for 20% off.
She loves the eye cream.
I'm sure you'll like it too.
You'll love it.
Wei.
How's Yuan Xia?
She's fine.
She fainted because
of emotional stress and hypoglycemia.
I've arranged a full body check-up
for her. I'll get the result tomorrow.
That's good.
By the way,
why did she suddenly pass out?
Was Zhou Wei behind it again?
It was me this time.
I fired her.
Wei Ziqi, you make me speechless.
The Board Meeting will commence soon.
You have to be more cautious
for the next two days, right?
Why do you have to hurt
both her and you?
Moreover, I really don't think
that Zhou Wei would do something
against the law.
You don't know
Zhou Wei well enough.
Zhou Wei is willing
to do anything for money.
Death awaits me at the Board Meeting
that will happen in a few more days.
Before that, he won't do anything to me.
But for Yuan Xia,
he won't show her any mercy.
And I can't guarantee
that she'll be as lucky next time.
By doing this
at this critical time,
you'll rouse Zhou Wei's suspicion.
So, before I can take down Zhou Wei
once and for all,
I hope that Yuan Xia can continue
staying at the hospital.
Take good care of her for me.
That's easy.
She can stay in the VIP ward.
I'll reserve the ward
if you are willing to pay for it.
But I'm afraid that she won't agree
to stay in the hospital.
What are you thinking?
You have to keep her in the hospital.
I'll leave it to you.
Okay?
No.
(Indoor Parking Lot,
Physical Examination Center)
You are awake.
Do you feel better now?
I'm fine.
I feel dizzy
because I just woke up.
Dr. Xing, what's wrong with me?
Yuan Xia.
Actually, you have...
You have...
Actually,
there's nothing wrong with you.
If there's nothing wrong with me,
why did I pass out?
Because...
There's nothing wrong with you.
You just need to take a good rest.
Is that it?
How can I contact your family?
I'm all alone.
If there's anything,
you can just be frank with me.
Is there something wrong with my body?
No.
Your body is healthy.
There's nothing wrong with you.
Why do you want
to contact my family, then?
(Possibly pancreatic cancer
with multiple enlarged lymph nodes.)
Dr. Xing.
This is not your medical report,
Yuan Xia. You...
You don't have to comfort me.
I want to be alone for a while.
I'm an evil person.
(Possibly pancreatic cancer
with multiple enlarged lymph nodes.)
Hello.
Yuan Xia, is that you?
Who are you?
Is your current time
twelve o'clock on March 3, 2024?
I have something important to tell you.
Remember.
On December 31, 2024,
do not go to the Lakeside Hotel
to look for Wei Ziqi.
I know that I'm not making sense.
But you have to believe me.
Otherwise, your life will be in danger.
My life is already in danger now.
If you are trying to scam me,
save it.
Stop calling me.
I don't even have the money
to save my life!
(Change of Personnel Announcement)
A personnel change?
Why did he fire
Yuan Xia at this critical moment?
Isn't that too much of a coincidence?
Mr. Zhou.
Ziqi. Why are you here so late at night?
I want to buy
a new limited edition sports car.
But those obstinate financiers of yours
are not willing to give me the funds.
Who did something so foolish?
Fire them tomorrow.
It's just a car.
I'll ask someone
to deliver it personally to you
tomorrow in the afternoon.
That's more like it.
I've inherited this company from my dad.
So, the company's money is my money.
Is it wrong of me to spend my own money?
Not at all.
Don't care about what others say.
After the Board Meeting
next Tuesday,
no one will tell you what to do anymore
after you take over the company.
I need to be alive
to take over the company, right?
What nonsense are you talking about?
You know my assistant, right?
I asked her to take me home.
But she was rushing
to meet her blind date.
She took a detour
and got us into an accident.
I almost died.
Really?
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
Why didn't you tell me
about something so serious?
I did.
When I came back,
I asked HR to fire her
right away.
Forget it.
That's not important.
I just need you to tell me
when I can get
my limited-edition sports car.
I want to hold a racing party
with my friends.
Don't worry.
When have I ever disappointed you?
You are the best.
I'll get going now.
Bye.
Is he really dumb
or is it just an act?
If he's just acting,
then he's really hard on himself.
It has been 11 years
since Mr. Wei Senior passed away.
Besides, Lin Yu has stayed
by his side the entire time.
He has never made a slip.
So, I still think
that it's just a coincidence
that he fired Yuan Xia.
He compensated his assistant too well.
We'll find out soon enough
about his relationship with her.
Mr. Wei, you are so cool.
Mr. Li, here.
Why is Mr. Li here?
He made such a ruckus
at the bar last time.
How dare he show up here?
But I hear
that Mr. Li's dad is close to Mr. Zhou.
Did he complain against you
with Mr. Zhou?
MU will belong to me
in a few more days anyway.
I have nothing to fear.
He's just here to ruin the party.
Forget about him.
If we beat him up together,
I wonder how Mr. Zhou
will feel about it.
Mr. Wei, I need to talk to you.
(Why is she here?)
(Shouldn't she be at the hospital?)
Why are you here? Trying to scam me?
No. I'm here to get my bank card.
You said that it was
compensation for firing me.
So, you are here for money.
You almost killed me.
And you want money from me?
Lin Yu!
I fired her, right?
Why is she still here?
Take her away at once!
Mr. Wei, just give me the money
and I promise
that I'll disappear from your sight.
You are so annoying.
You only think about money.
Leave at once.
She's here for money.
Mr. Wei.
Mr. Wei, come out from the pool
and give me the money.
Then I'll leave at once.
Mr. Wei.
Give me...
Have you been fired?
It's okay.
It's not the end of the world.
I happen to need an assistant.
How about you work for me?
Don't worry.
Compared to Mr. Wei,
I'm a gentle and generous man.
Don't touch me.
I don't have time for you.
Mr. Wei.
You just need to give me the money.
That money is very important to me.
I need the money to save myself.
To save yourself.
Wei Ziqi, that's wrong of you.
Why do you refuse to give her
the money to save herself?
Why do you need money?
I can give it to you.
Here. Drink this glass of wine.
Wait.
What is the meaning of this?
Are you going to protect
your subordinate again
like what you did in the bar last time?
She has been fired by you.
Do you want to get hit again?
You want the money?
Come here.
I'll tell you how you can get the money.
You really know how to have fun.
How is it? Is it fun?
Money to save yourself?
What do you need to save yourself from?
I need it to save my life.
I have terminal pancreatic cancer.
I need to get treated
as soon as possible.
Mr. Wei, I beg you.
Can you give me the money?
Do you hear that?
She has terminal pancreatic cancer.
Aren't you going to give her the money?
So, you are going to die soon.
Are you dumb?
Do you actually believe her?
That's right. Who would believe her?
I don't believe you.
Mr. Wei.
What can I do to make you
give me the money?
Finish this.
Drink it and I'll give you the money.
Finish it?
He's setting her up to fail.
She can't possibly finish it.
Are you not going to drink it?
Then you can't get the money.
I'll drink it.
She's really going to drink it.
She's desperate.
She's good at drinking.
Did you ask me to come
to the company
just to choose an assistant?
They are chosen carefully
by the HR Department.
You should take a look.
(Yuan Xia)
♪Because you are too good to be true♪
♪At sunrise,
I'm still thinking about you♪
♪Because my heart fell for you♪
Wei, I'm Yuan.
Are you at home?
Why aren't you opening the door?
I've brought you dumplings
from Madam Sun.
Wei.
Wei, open the door.
Wei!
Yuan.
What's the filling
in the dumplings this time?
I like the spicy one.
You scared me.
I thought you didn't want me anymore.
I'm sorry, Yuan.
I apologize.
I promise you
that I won't abandon you anymore.
Promise me one thing.
Okay.
According to the news,
there'll be a rare
Perseid meteor shower next week.
Wei.
Let's watch it together next week, okay?
That's great.
I've prepared a special gift
for you.
♪Because you are too good to be true♪
Yuan.
Thank you.
Mr. Wei.
Whatever. I'll just choose one randomly.
(Yuan Xia)
Hello, Mr. Wei.
I'm your new assistant.
I am Yuan Xia.
♪Just like walking on the moon♪
I know.
Yuan Xia.
I've waited a long time for you.
♪Light up♪
♪In the dark♪
♪Tell me, Dear♪
♪I'm not someone else♪
♪I'm not, I'm not someone else♪
I've finished it.
Give me the money.
You've finished it?
Leave now if you've finished it.
I don't have money.
Are you done?
Wei Ziqi, you are a scum!
The thing I regret the most
is applying to MU
and becoming your assistant.
I didn't work so hard to learn
those foreign languages
and get those certificates
to help you translate comics,
pick up girls for you,
and clean up your mess after you!
But I had no choice.
I needed money.
You paid me enough
to break my dream
and my pride.
For the past two years,
I kept telling myself
that you might
be lazy and irresponsible,
but at least you were not a bad person.
At least you were not like
those scoundrels over there.
Who are you talking about?
I'm talking about you!
All of you.
All of you
who are born with a golden spoon.
Do I look ridiculous to you?
I want to make money
and I want to defend my pride.
I'm unbelievably greedy, right?
Yes!
Let me tell you.
It's not shameless to want money.
It's not shameless to be frugal.
And it's not shameless to make money
with your own capabilities!
But what about you?
I hope that you can stay rich forever
if you are that capable!
Especially you!
I want to see
how long you can muck around like this.
If I could turn back time,
I wish that I had never met you.
♪Fighting against God♪
♪The two of us who approach
each other in the mass of people♪
♪The two of us who continue to connect
with each other after our separation♪
♪Even if I have to do it
again and again♪
♪I'll come back for you♪
♪I believe love can turn♪
♪The gears of fate♪
♪I've confirmed all the paths♪
♪And all paths lead
to the door of your heart♪
♪I'll continue to love you
despite the future♪
♪Is full of different possibilities♪
♪Hold you tighter by a fraction♪
♪Just like this♪
♪Until the end of time♪
Why are you just standing there?
Let's continue to party!
Yes! Let's continue to party!
Lin Yu.
Cheers.
Where's the key to my new car?
Give it to me.
Mr. Wei.
Cici.
Come. Let's go for a ride.
Great!
Again!
Mr. Zhou.
Yuan Xia came to find Wei Ziqi just now.
She told him
that she had pancreatic cancer
and wanted to get money
from Wei Ziqi.
What was Wei Ziqi's reaction?
He treated her coldly.
He was very mean to her.
Where is he now?
He went for a ride.
Are you dumb? Follow him.
He is probably
on his way to the hospital
to check on Yuan Xia.
Mr. Wei. I'm following you
because I'm worried about you.
You've misunderstood me.
Misunderstood you?
Are you saying
that I've misunderstood you
for being loyal?
Lin Yu.
What's going on?
(Mr. Zhou Wei)
Mr. Zhou.
I'm Ziqi.
Ziqi.
Did you go on a ride to lure me out?
I never thought that you would
be so interested
in my relationship with Yuan Xia.
You took the bait so easily.
That's quite disappointing.
Wei Ziqi.
You have only two more days
to be so arrogant.
After the Board Meeting,
without your father's will
to protect you,
how long can you survive?
By the way,
there's something that you may not know.
Your father's death
was not an accident.
♪I'm not just a passerby♪
♪I'm trying my hardest♪
♪To reunite with you♪
♪If time could testify♪
♪I've searched for it
over and over again♪
♪For the same look in your eyes
as before♪
♪This voiceless yearning
transcends time and space♪
♪Love redeems each other,
never faltering♪
♪How I wish with one turn♪
♪Two could become one♪
♪I believe love can turn♪
♪A thousand possibilities♪
♪Hold you tighter by a fraction♪
♪Just like this until the end of time♪
♪Let love take root♪