♫  Baby, baby, let me come along  ♫
♫  Every single day I belong  ♫
♫  Keep you happy all day long  ♫
The phone is turned off. After the tone...
- Yes, Chief Oh.
- Prosecutor.
Go Yang Hui stopped by the company and is going somewhere.
He's headed to Sangnam Liquor.
As long as you make up your mind,
you can leave.
Your mistake is that you were so busy watching Seo Ji Hwan...
that you never saw me.
- Chairman!
- Who is this?
What the hell, you bastards!
This is why you said a real son is different.
Everyone stop!
S-Seo Ji Hwan...
- Hyungnim!
- Seo Ji Hwan!
You bastard!
Hey!
Everyone freeze!
Put down your weapons!
Seo Ji Hwan!
Cuff him.
Seo Ji Hwan...
You have the right to remain silent...
Let's go.
Officer, call an ambulance!
- Call an ambulance!
- Seo Ji Hwan!
- Go!
- Hyungnim!
Ji Hwan!
Seo Ji Hwan!
Hyungnim!
Hurry up, hurry up!
Hurry up!
Hyungnim!
Seo Ji Hwan, please open your eyes!
Hyung!
Oppa!
Hurry up! Go!
Go!
Hyungnim!
Thankfully, he's alive. However, due to brain damage from the bleeding,
he's in a coma.
We're keeping him alive through medication, but I can't guarantee when he'll wake up.
What does that mean?
You don't know when he's going to wake up?
He should wake up once the anesthesia wears off.
Doctor, you said his surgery went well.
If you need blood, take mine.
- We have the same blood type A.
- Hyung.
- Do it.
- Let's see how he does.
Hey! Take my blood!
Please?
What if he dies?
Why won't they take it?
Hyungnim...
Wake up soon.
Your brothers are waiting for you.
Please get up soon, aigoo...
Hyungnim.
Yes, Chief Oh.
How's it going?
One is talking too much, and one has his mouth shut.
Go Yang Hui denies everything,
and Seo Tae Pyung is silent.
Lee Gang Gil is the only one talking.
Got it.
I'll be there right now.
Everyone, go to work.
I'll stay here. Don't worry, go on.
Hyungnim is unconscious. How can we go to work?
Think of what the CEO would want.
Would he want us to worry endlessly by his side?
Or bravely go out there and do our jobs?
Do what he would want.
This is crazy.
You didn't say anything to the police.
Kidnapping, imprisonment, assault, profiting through criminal activities, violating legal protocols.
Violating aggravated crime laws.
So you're denying everything?
If Seo Ji Hwan doesn't wake up,
accomplice to murder will be added to that list.
He hasn't...
woken up yet?
You were scared, right?
It's okay now. I'll be by your side.
This room won't stay empty, will it?
Hyung...
You're not crying, are you?
No.
You said Hyung was really strong.
They say you can speak something into existence.
I need to hear it, like a spell.
Can you tell me again? That he's strong?
I just want to hear it from someone else.
Go to the Catholic church nearby and pray.
I'm not Catholic. I'm Protestant.
I'm leaving.
Hey! Just say something!
Hey, just this once!
Seo Ji Hwan, Seo Ji Hwan! If that bastard wasn't there,
I would have killed that old man!
What?
Are you scared Seo Ji Hwan is going to die?
Look down. How dare you stare at me like that, you asshole.
You need to stop.
What did you say, bastard?
Can I get a new cell?
Please be quiet.
Can we switch cells?
Thanks. I'll call you. Okay.
- Who's that?
- Ye Na.
Are you guys best friends now that you did the challenge together?
So many people are worried about him and checking in. He'll wake up soon.
You're right.
He's a light sleeper. He won't stay like this long.
Hey, should I try to scare him?
What?
Hey...
Right. He needs to sleep in order to recover.
I was so rude. He's sleeping deeply.
I'm sorry.
He's not even frowning. He must be at peace right now.
I'm heading out.
Right...
Here.
You left it at home. I fixed it.
Thanks.
Eun Ha.
If you want to cry, cry.
Don't hold it in.
Don't hold it in. Just cry.
He won't stay asleep, right? He'll wake up, right?
Of course. It'll be like nothing happened.
He'll wake up soon.
He would never leave you behind.
I was going to stop by, but I'm still at work.
It's okay. You must be busy.
Still, I'll be there soon to get a victim statement from Seo Ji Hwan.
Seo Ji Hwan said he would cooperate.
And he always keeps his word.
Seo Ji Hwan.
Yes.
I'll be bothering Seo Ji Hwan for a while.
It might be a competition between you and me over Seo Ji Hwan.
I'll let you win.
I don't want to keep him for myself that badly.
Let me just borrow him for a bit,
then I'll...
let him go back to you.
I'm just getting your permission in advance.
Thank you, Prosecutor.
Thanks to you, Eun Ha.
I brought everything you asked for.
Oh, really?
Do you need anything else?
No. I can buy the other stuff downstairs.
No, I'll go.
I'll go. I need exercise.
Please stay by Ji Hwan.
Really?
She can't even take a shower...
Hyungnim.
Stop making Little Rat suffer here. Let's get up now.
Okay?
He's been through so much that his hair has turned gray.
Geez, I didn't mean to pick that one.
Wrong one again.
Are there tweezers anywhere? Right, I packed a pair...
Geez, I picked the wrong one again.
Not again...
It hurts.
Stop pulling my hair.
Hyungnim.
Hyungnim...
Doctor!
Hyungnim! Hyungnim!
Hyungnim, you're awake, right?
Are you awake? Doctor! Doctor!
Hyungnim!
Thank you! Thank you!
Doctor! Thank you...
Thank you... thank you...
Jae Soo.
Yes, Hyungnim.
Quiet down.
♫  I’ve waited  ♫
♫  For your expressions  ♫
Oppa...
♫  Perhaps our comfortable smiles hold our time  ♫
♫  On sleepless nights  ♫
I knew you would wake up.
I knew you would wake up...
I'm so late. I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
It's okay...
♫  My everything  ♫
♫  So precious to me, more than I deserve  ♫
♫  You became my everything  ♫
♫  My everything  ♫
♫  I've ever dreamed of  ♫
♫  Even when I’m in pain  ♫
- Really?
- What?
- Hyungnim is awake!
- Really?
- He's awake?
Hurray!
See? I told you!
Eun Ha, thank goodness!
Got it, Hyungnim. I'll be right there.
Got it. I'll call you.
I'm so happy!
Oh, my gosh!
♫  My everything  ♫
Whatever.
- Hell—
- Hi.
I-It's me.
Hyung is awake.
Thank goodness.
She's so icy.
It's charming.
As for being an accomplice to murder...
you won't worry about it anymore.
Let's start the interrogation.
Right. This necklace broke.
- It broke?
- Yes.
The day it happened, I was making dinner, and it just broke.
Why did it break out of nowhere?
But the weirder thing is,
you woke up when I put it back on. Isn't that weird?
Really?
Prosecutor!
Congratulations.
I'm here as number one on the wait list.
Are you here to get his statement?
I had a reservation.
I promised, so I'll let you have him.
What? What did you promise?
- You two can chat.
- Thanks.
Eun Ha, you don't have to leave.
Seo Ji Hwan, you're lucky.
If you had woken up a little later,
I was going to snatch Eun Ha away.
Who says you can?
Well...
Seo Tae Pyung...
admitted to all his crimes.
He was completely silent.
But when he heard you woke up,
he started talking.
He'll get at least five years or more.
I know it's been tumultuous, but in any case,
you can relax now.
How do you feel?
Do you feel a little better?
Where is my father?
In custody.
How can I feel any better?
I have the life I've lived.
I have the things I did that were wrong.
I know there's no end to this.
All I can do is...
work harder and live each day.
I'm here to say I'm sorry as your child.
Just as I'm not the child you wanted,
you're not the father I wanted, either.
I know the link between father and son can't be cut easily.
But if I ever see you again as someone different,
I want to fulfill my duty as a son.
I won't be seeing you again.
I don't expect anything from you.
Don't expect anything from me, either.
You are...
no longer my son.
Officer!
When you were gone, Hong Gi was great at something.
That something? What could it be?
- Does he need to know?
- He can beat you, Hyungnim.
Hey, everybody. It's late.
Let's get some rest. You guys have work tomorrow.
Yes, got it.
But before we go! Karaoke!
Let's go!
- Are you in pain, Hyungnim?
- What's wrong?
My stitches feel tight. Maybe because I'm tired.
- Oh, no. Not your stitches!
- Take this to him.
Let's clean this up tomorrow. Go rest. I'm going upstairs.
- Got it, Hyungnim.
- Wait.
But before you go, sing a song even if your stitches are tight!
- Let him go, man!
- Sing a song!
Let him go!
♪  My heart  ♪
♪  My heart is touched  ♪
- ♪  My heart is touched  ♪
- Drop the beat!
Drop the beat!
Done.
It hurts, right?
It's okay.
Done.
Get some rest.
Where did you go this afternoon?
To see my father.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
♫  Faint stars in the night sky  ♫
You went through so much.
You must be tired. Go to bed.
Let's stay together tonight.
♫  As if time had stopped, I’ll remember this moment  ♫
♫  To my heart that was once shaken, you came back again  ♫
Eun Ha, I love you.
I love you, too.
♫  In my dream every day  ♫
♫  I want to be with you in every moment  ♫
- Subscribe...
- and like...
Please!
Do you want one of these?
He's the best.
Wow, look at Il Yeong. Was he always that smiley?
He's been all smiles ever since he met Mi Ho.
He's a totally different person.
I can't live like that, even if that means I don't get married.
Not "don't." Can't.
No, it's "don't."
- Hey, stop being jealous.
- I'm not jealous.
Who are you...
even looking at?
Aigoo, Yoon Byul!
- Miss Korea is here.
- Aigoo...
Hello, Miss Korea!
Aigoo, so pretty.
Aigoo, you don't like Uncle Man Ho.
You don't like Uncle Man Ho.
You like Uncle Jae Soo better. Aigoo...
This is who you're looking for.
We have to take photos.
She likes me.
I think she likes me.
Hold her so she doesn't cry.
What an angel. Aigoo!
- So pretty.
- You made her cry.
No, you did.
Here. One...
Hey, come here.
- No, no.
- Hyungnim, aren't you going to get married?
- Married?
- Right!
That noodle incident was already 10 months ago.
If he gets married, we all have to move out. Do you have a plan?
- Do we have to move?
- Yes.
Do we have to move?
We can't live in a house with newlyweds. We'd have to move.
What's mommy doing?
But we already live with them.
Then there's no need to rush a wedding.
That's right, Hyungnim.
I've always heard that it's better to date for a long time.
Yes—
Hyungnim.
- Hyungnim.
- He's doing that thing again.
Hey, let's go get ready.
Man Ho, go.
Excuse us.
One, two, three!
Eun Ha.
Aigoo, so pretty.
Let's take a photo.
One more.
Okay, okay. Look over here!
All right. One, two, three!
- Congratulations!
- Thanks.
All right. Here are the red bean and honey cakes you've been waiting for.
Thank you.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Would you like any japchae or jokbal?
Aigoo. It's fine.
- Thank you.
- I'm so glad.
Thank you.
- Sit down.
- My goodness...
Uncle Dong Hee is so handsome!
She fell asleep!
She fell asleep?
Eun Ha, why are you so busy these days? We haven't seen you around.
She needs to clone herself these days.
Her play study project is a hit. Everyone wants to work with her.
It's not like that.
She has more than a million followers.
Really?
When our baby is a little older, she'll play watching her aunt.
Aigoo, if you're so busy, when are you going to get married?
Me? Married? No.
I'm happy to just have a niece.
Try having your own child.
- Of course.
- You won't even look at our baby.
What are you doing standing here?
N-Nothing.
Yes, right.
- You got it?
- Aigoo.
- Our son-in-law!
- This looks so good.
You're a big guy. This is it?
- Join us.
- Great work.
- Not at all.
- Thank you.
Father and Mother, bottoms up, please.
Bottoms up?
Father, it's a special day for Yoon Byul.
Could you make a toast?
Oh, sure.
- Eun Ha.
- Yeah!
Are you ready for the event tomorrow?
- Almost there.
- Oh, really?
Eun Ha, Il Yeong and Mi Ho earlier...
Don't they look so happy?
They do. Il Yeong is a lot more relaxed now.
Right.
Maybe it's because they're parents. Mi Ho is different, too.
Speaking of...
Oppa, can you put those over here?
Of course.
These...
- Can I help with anything else?
- No, it's okay.
Okay.
Eun Ha, there was something...
you asked me before.
Huh? Asked you what?
Well...
One second.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll bring the materials. You can just get the kids ready.
We'll have the snacks that we discussed, right?
How many? One second.
One, two, three, four, five...
The refrigerated bulgogi that we developed this time is fresh.
The freshness is the core of this! Just like me.
Oppa, have you ever thought about getting married?
- Marriage?
- Yeah.
You're not that young, Oppa.
Right.
- Right, I'm not that young.
- No.
- Should we get married tomorrow?
- Sure!
Should I have done that?
Okay.
The sauce, in particular, will perfectly suit the customers' taste...
through our collaboration with a big company.
Welcome.
Hello.
Looking for something in particular?
I'm looking for a small, twinkling engagement ring. I'm going to propose to my girlfriend.
I had an opportunity.
And...
this refrigerated bulgogi is made with pigs we raised ourselves.
I'm confident, Hyungnim!
That concludes my presentation...
for our new product, the refrigerated bulgogi.
Great work.
He's zoning out again.
I know how to wake him up at a time like this.
Good.
The refrigerated bulgogi...
Good. Great work, everyone.
Hey! The time!
Where are you going?
Well, Marketing Team Leader, write up the proposal and report it.
That was good. Move forward.
Hyungnim!
W-W-What?
Not frozen and suitable for customers’ tastes! From pigs we raised ourselves.
- I'm so confident, Hyungnim.
- Good, good. Great job.
It'll be an excellent product. Good work!
Hyungnim...
Hyungnim!
See you later.
Hyungnim gave us the okay, right?
Yes.
Was it Hongcheon today?
Chuncheon.
How come he works harder to be her manager than his actual job?
Tell him to be her full-time manager!
Sister-in-law is so busy.
Now, each team will be four people...
and total to make 20!
Okay!
Ready, begin!
Take a good look at the numbers!
We got it, too!
Each team is four people, right?
Yes!
Then the team that throws the most balls in that basket wins!
Okay!
Start!
Do your best to throw the ball into the basket!
♫  A story from long ago comes back to my mind  ♫
♫  See the moon, moon, moon, we were like that back then  ♫
♫  Your voice that I missed so much, will I hear it again?  ♫
Isn't this fun?
- That was fun.
Seo Ji Hwan.
Mini, why are you...
Having nowhere to go reminded me.
I have a lot of memories of this place.
Are they good memories?
Yes. They're good memories.
With a good person.
Eun Ha, don't fall asleep.
Eun Ha, wake up.
Out of everyone I knew,
he was the best person.
♫  I'm finally almost near you  ♫
Blinking? Finger hearts? Cheek heart? Big heart?
Not because of what happened to me.
Because you're not by my side when I'm scared.
I'm scared you'll never be by my side again.
I don't want to be somewhere safe alone. Why don't you get that?
I want to be with you wherever it is. Why don't you get that?
♫  May it become love  ♫
♫  You  ♫
Good job.
When I was playing with the kids earlier, I remembered things from the past.
When I first went to your house, I was so lost.
Thanks to you, I got to know good people.
So many joyful days piled up.
Now I'm doing what I want to do.
Oppa, you led me down a good path.
Thank you.
Eun Ha.
Oppa, you're getting a call.
What?
- It's okay. Take it.
- I'm sorry. One second.
W-What? I'm busy.
Should I call you back, then?
Yes, call back later. I was about to say something important.
By chance...
that important thing isn't a proposal, is it?
You're not going to do that empty-handed, are you?
Get out of there.
Get out?
- It's okay.
- You'll remember this moment for life.
You should do it after you're fully prepared.
Prepared?
Wow, Mini Unni.
I mean, Eun Ha Unni is dominating kids' events these days.
She's solidified her spot in the play study field.
Her content is good.
You're still watching?
I mean, I'm a subscriber.
Instead, how about you go on the blind date you blew off ten months ago?
My cousin's friend's in-laws' second cousin is now divorced.
She got married right after, and it was over in six months.
That's in the past. I don't think I can go back on it.
Then how about my cousin's friend's niece's daycare teacher's daughter's work colleague?
In terms of phrenology, MBTI, astrology, and even your blood type, you're a match.
But she's basically a stranger.
Six degrees of separation means you know everyone. Maybe you know her, too.
Meet her this time. I won't send anyone else your way.
I don't know.
Right now, I'm not interested at all.
You need to date for us to be happy.
Take your punishment for breaking your promise last time.
Right now.
- What promise?
- Write your name with your butt.
What are you talking about?
Since you enforce the law, you should keep your promise.
Officer, should he do it or not?
He must.
Please write your name with your butt.
- Get up.
- Seriously?
Get up!
That's how we abide by justice. Turn around.
Is this related to justice?
Of course, it's about keeping your word. Start with "Jang."
- Write it!
- Like this?
"Hyun."
- She's asleep.
- She's asleep?
Good job.
It's been so long since we did something special like this.
Your parents are coming tomorrow, right?
Of course.
They're probably soaking in the hot springs right now.
Then...
since it's been too long...
Gosh, too long?
It was yesterday.
What's that?
What? Dad?
Mom?
If you say that there, what do I become?
Was it so bad that we didn't even dip our feet in the hot springs? After we paid?
If you're that upset about money,
you should've soaked it until your skin got wrinkled. Why follow me home?
You took the bag with my clothes and left yours!
What happened? I thought you were coming back tomorrow. Why are you here?
I'm coming back to my own home. Do you have a problem?
Should we move out now?
Are you threatening me?
I like living with you, Father.
See! Our son-in-law likes it!
Right. I forgot something I needed to buy.
Come with me.
It's late. Let's get it tomorrow.
Hurry up and follow me.
Wait.
Is that wine?
Wow. How did you know I like wine?
No, this isn't yours! This is expensive. Very old!
It's expensive?
Really?
No. You don't know anything about wine.
Mother, I'll get it for you tomorrow. Have a drink.
Wow! Sit.
This is really expensive! It's 7— I mean, it's so expensive.
Read the room!
Aigoo, when did you even notice?
- Wow!
- Sorry.
To our family!
Do you want help?
I don't need help. I have a plan.
Dong Hee passed his GED and needs to prepare for his college entrance exam.
What should we do about his job?
I already told him that this week is his last.
You and Eun Ha have helped him so far,
but he needs to go to the academy and focus.
Let me talk to Dong Hee.
I think we could restructure the company's education support system while we're at it.
On top of tuition, we should provide living expenses.
See if there's a way to benefit those who want more education.
Work on it.
Got it. We'll work on it.
Hey, Man Ho.
It was 4 p.m., right?
I think so, but we've been here since noon.
We finished our teas.
Hey, Man Ho. I can't see out of my right eye.
I can't see out of my left eye.
The hairdresser said this looked good.
But do we have to do this to get married?
Right, Il Yeong said Hyungnim is proposing, so we should get mentally ready.
It's not them, is it?
- Can't be.
- No.
Don't look at them.
What is this?
I don't have one. I'll use this.
How's this?
Looks good.
They're here. Hello, Ma'am.
Hello. Ma'am.
Sisters, sit here.
Right here!
- Right here. Have a seat.
- So pretty.
Have a seat.
You're early.
Thanks for coming all the way here.
Let me introduce myself. I'm a man full of affection.
Jung* Man... Ho-ho-ho-ho.
(T/N: Jung means "affection")
I'm quack, quack, Kwak Jae Soo.
Your names?
I'm Choi Cham Sarang.
Miss Choi Cham Sarang.
- How about you?
- Kim Shen.
- Pardon?
You're Chinese. Kim Shen.
Oh, yes.
We love Chinese people.
Now that we've met, let's be frightened... no, no...
let's get frisky.
I mean, let's be friendly.
I prepared some jokes that ladies like.
Chinese people are working on knives.
Guess what another Chinese person said to them?
Oh, I know this one.
Hey, she's Chinese! Of course, she knows!
But we don't know. Tell us.
The person next to them goes...
Slice-zhuan!
What do French people say to make laundry dry faster?
- What?
- Dry Jour!
That'll make it dry!
- You know the actor Nam Do Gu, right?
- Yes.
He can't get on an elevator. You know why?
Do-ors are Gu-losing.
We're out of time. We need to go.
You haven't eaten yet.
It's okay. Something came up at work.
- Bye.
- Wait, wait.
We'll take you.
Have some coffee.
Excuse me! Cham Sarang!
You left this behind.
Keep it. Such schmucks.
Schmuck?
Man Ho!
They called you a schmuck. Hong Gi said that's a good thing!
Wow! Congratulations. You became a schmuck on your first meeting. Congrats.
She called me a schmuck as soon as she met me.
I even got a gift.
If she gave you her lipstick, she's giving you her lips.
The data you requested.
Yes, thank you.
Prosecutor.
Can I ask why you're still watching that channel?
The channel?
I thought you were over her.
I thought you gave up.
I'm rooting for her.
Still.
It's separate from letting go of her.
I genuinely want her to be happy.
Plus, I don't think I could develop such feelings for anyone else right now.
Okay.
Get home safe.
Oppa.
It's so nice out. Should we go on a date later?
You're busy?
It's okay. Next time.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
No problem.
I'll see you at the event next Friday.
Sounds good. Great work today.
Your boyfriend isn't picking you up today?
He's busy with work today.
- I'll see you next week.
- Great work.
I'm done with work. On my way home.
He must be really busy.
Why is this here?
Eun Ha, thank you for always playing with me.
- Play with me always from now on.
- What in the world...
Eun Ha.
Hey, Oppa.
You said before that I led you down a good path, right?
It's the other way around.
You always make me want to become a better person.
From now on, no matter what happens,
I'm never going to leave you.
♫  My breathing gets faster  ♫
I want to subscribe to you for the rest of my life...
♫  Yeah, it's real  ♫
♫  You know, right?  ♫
and I want to like you, always.
♫  Tik-tiktok, getting closer, I might get caught  ♫
Will you let me?
♫  Hidden love, time is now  ♫
♫  Ring my heart, into my world  ♫
♫  It's already started, I already found it  ♫
♫  Can you hear my love?  ♫
♫  You don't have to do anything  ♫
It fits perfectly.
Thank you.
♫  Tik-tiktok, getting closer, a little closer  ♫
♫  I want to tell you, time is now  ♫
♫  Ring my heart  ♫
Yes!
Hyungnim is getting married.
Sister-in-Law, please be happy.
You're not crying because we're getting kicked out, are you?
That's true love, dude.
♫  You just have to show your heart  ♫
♫  In my world  ♫
Where are Il Yeong and Dong Hee?
They went ahead to wait.
On the train to hell, I see.
Hello, Hyungnim.
Everyone ready?
- Let's go.
Let's go!
Let's go.
Who parked in front of our house?
What rude bastard parked here?
It's a shiny car, though.
- Very shiny.
- What do we do?
I don't know. What should we do?
Eun Ha.
This is your car. A gift.
What's all this?
We took a lot of time picking it out.
Hyungnim paid for it already.
We just picked it out.
What a huge gift all of a sudden...
To congratulate you on your marriage.
Sister-in-Law, take good care of Hyungnim.
Just be honest. You're grateful you're not getting kicked out.
Yeah, right, right.
If Little Rat didn't say we could stay, we'd be on the streets now.
I mean...
we're genuinely thankful.
No one else has accepted us before.
Thanks to you, we know what it's like to be welcomed.
We got to be decent human beings.
We couldn't have imagined any of that. So, thank you.
Just take it.
Thank you for everything, Sister-in-Law.
What is this? Making me cry even before we take off.
If you're crying, use the wife.
Not wife, the wiper.
Anyway, come here.
Take a look at your car.
- Look, look.
- We should adjust the seats and mirrors.
I've never gotten a gift like this.
We picked the color.
Get in. Where's the key?
- Get in!
- Are you sure I can accept this?
We got a big car for a Little Rat.
Okay. Should we go?
Let's go!
Thanks to our Channel Managers:
grace_senpai91 and morva  💞
Thanks to our Segmeting Team:
pilar_velasquez, nazsaria, padmalayag and  jo_p66  🔫
Thanks to our Chief Segmenter:
pilar_velasquez  💞
Thanks to our English Translation Editor:
ynonline8  🔫
Thanks to our English General Editor:
moreugesseo  🔫
Thanks to our English Chief:
frkszltn  💞
Thanks to our Other Languages Moderators and Their Teams 💞
💞  Thanks for watching: My Sweet Mobster! 🔫
- Friends!
- Hello!
♫  Wherever, whenever, she appears like ta-da  ♫
♫  It's Policewoman Mini who protects us  ♫
♫  One step after another, my friends  ♫
♫  We'll survive this together, we are the best fighters  ♫
♫  Let's go away everyone, beware of monsters  ♫
- Please like...
- and subscribe!
♫  Policewoman Mini  ♫
♫  Baby, baby, let me come along, every single day I belong  ♫
♫  Baby, baby, let me come along, keep you happy all day long  ♫