Okay, I'll go pick it up.
Um, okay, then I'll call you later. Bye...
Ah, chubby, there are plenty of cheeky guys out there.
Do you know who else he's doing this to?
Oh, why didn't we go to the courtyard?
Oops, sorry.
Forgot your glasses. How can you see like this?
It's okay, Jet. I'll go wash my eyes.
Forgot your glasses! Hurry up!
I'm going to the bookstore. Wanna come?
How's that? Better?
Um.
Is there something wrong? Who called?
We're not going to the bookstore anymore.
Let's just go home instead.
New! We have new books today. I ordered them online.
Want to read them at my place?
Not today, I have something to do.
Something to do?
Well, whenever you're free, come over.
Jet, why don't you invite me too?
Why? If I invite, will you come?
No, haha. There are many people here already.
Just invited New, what's up?
Oh, just because I know that even if I invite you guys, you won't come anyway.
Oh, what a pity.
Or is it true?
Hey Jet, don't forget about me.
Just say the word, and we're ready to dispel your loneliness.
Okay, tonight then.
Yay! Two by two!
Okay, haha.
New! What are you looking at?
Hey, this looks interesting. I want to watch it too.
It looks fun. I'm going to watch it.
Then let's go together.
I already made plans with a friend.
A friend? Which friend?
A friend from another class. You don't know them, Jet.
Your boyfriend?
Boyfriend? That's funny!
Haha, just kidding around, Jet.
Oh well, I'll go watch it alone then.
Go watch with your girlfriend.
There are plenty to choose from, right?
What? Where's this girlfriend? There's none at all.
The person who called you earlier.
The person who called? Oh...
Jet	Hey, where are you going?
Hey, where are you going?
Where are you going, New?
Going to watch a movie.
Let's go then.
Oh, okay.
New!
Oh... Jet.
Um... You're late today.
Not really.
It's just another 15 minutes until the national anthem.
Oh, really? Haha...
Um, New... How was the movie we watched yesterday?
The movie? Uh, it was fun.
Do you want to go watch another one?
Um, yeah, I'd like to.
But going alone might be too lonely for me.
Unlike you, New I have someone to watch with.
Why? Are you jealous?
Haha, come on, stop it.
Hmm, okay then. Let's go watch it alone.
Oh, okay, New. Just a moment.
Oh my, why is it so hot today!!
Well, look at you.
You waste sunscreen for real.
Huh? Did I put it on?
Of course, because I need to look beautiful.
Why? Does my face not look like I've put on cream today?
No, your face looks tan...
Haha!
Hurry up and walk, it's hot in the sun!
Why are you looking?
Haven't you ever seen a beautiful person before?
Are you still daring to say that?
There probably isn't a real mirror at home.
What!? What did we do wrong?
Just because we think No. 1 powder is the best!!!
You gray-faced!
You two didn't even think to remind each other about choosing foundation properly!?
Yes! Tan-faced Low has always been real.
It suits you well.
It's about you guys!! You're not even pretty.
Just because you're rich doesn't mean anything.
So annoying!
Really annoying indeed.
Sorry, didn't see you there.
Are you guys ganging up on me!?
Gang up? How would I know what's going on?
Huh! Why would we gang up?
Face to face, it's going to be awesome!!
So cool! I'm out of here. We're just kidding.
Sorry, if you don't have the guts to face us, don't talk big.
Get out!!
Geez, you're so cool.
Hey, we need to hurry.
There's hope for us, for sure.
Oh, it's really hot.
You guys keep babbling. I'm going first. Bye!
Oh, you're not going to use an umbrella.
Hmm.. it's hot. I'm leaving.
Oh... wait up!!! Ugly ladyboys!!!
You're it, Ugly ladyboys!!!
I'm not sure if this is real.
Hey! Without any greatness, beauty, or anything else!
Oh my! What's this?
What's up! Let's go, guys.
This area isn't that great anyway! It's full of pigs and buffaloes. Let's go!
Yeah, it's hot. Let's go.
Let's go, So!
Pete! What topic are we studying now?
It's probably... human and animal reproduction, right?
Oh, it sounds difficult.
Yes.
Doesn't seem difficult at all. Just reproduction, right guys?
Yes, want to catch up? We'll help teach.
What nonsense are you talking about?
New, don't get involved with this. This spreads STDs.
Go, don't forget to spread it to me too.
You're going too far, Jet. I'm just a charitable person. That's it.
My friend is charitable.
How about donating to me, Go? We want it too.
Wow, Pat, you're really pretty.
Oh, I want it too.
Hmm, you squeeze your own stuff, Pat.
You have your own.
Right, self-made.
Hey, I'm going to get you!!!
Oh, I don't know what they're talking about. Absolutely crazy.
Oh, That’s bullshit Parn!
That's good.
Everyone, don't argue. We're in the same class, same gender,
but I'd like to be a female. Let's study together.
Everyone, show respect.
Hello, sir/ma'am.
Hello, students. Last week we studied human and animal reproduction theory.
Today, we'll learn the same topic but in practice.
Alright, don't think too far ahead.
I'll give you students a chance. You'll examine real sperm through a microscope today.
I've brought real sperm for everyone to see.
What do you say?
So, where do we get the sperm, sir?
Why does it have to be me?
Because you're the class leader, you have to sacrifice.
Exactly, you're the most suitable.
Well, don't be embarrassed, Pete. We'll help ourselves.
What are you helping with? You don't have to.
I'm leaving now!!
Calm down, Pete. Stay calm.
I'm not calm.
And why don't you guys do it yourselves?
Oh, I haven't got the mood yet. And I want to save some of my offspring.
Ridiculous! Nonsense, you jerks.
Come on, Pete. It'll be over soon.
What's your problem?
Come on, join us. I promise, just once.
Screw that! I don't want it.
Hurry up, Pete. Teacher Kron is waiting.
Add this one. I have a couple of clips. They're awesome.
I guarantee you'll be impressed.
Damn it, no! I won't do it!
How the hell did you get in here? This is the men's bathroom.
Damn it! We're all men.
Come on, let's go.
Damn it, open the door! I'm not doing it! You guys understand?
You idiots! I can't do it!
Damn it, don't come in here!
Hey Pete, are you done?
Okay, very good. Let me see, please.
How was it? Are you tired?
You did it quickly and spontaneously, my friend.
Hmm, not bad for a newbie, boss.
Did it break a lot, guys?
Don't tease your friend. He sacrificed willingly.
It's a normal thing.
Even the teacher does it. It's common. Don't make fun of your friend.
What everyone should do is to clap and thank your friend together.
New! What are you doing?
Oh, I'm playing with my mobile phone. You guys look beautiful.
Where did you get the flowers from?
Hehe, don't ask.
I secretly picked them from the waterfall stall.
It suits us really well. It just came naturally.
Accidentally turned into a flower.
Haha.
New, do you want one?
We can give it to you.
Oh, no need, thanks.
You look beautiful, New. Just stay still.
Yeah, that's it. Awesome!
It feels strange, though.
Aww, so cute!
How beautiful, right?
Wait until the teacher sees it. I'll be embarrassed.
Oh no, if you take it out, we're doomed!
Let's go.
Oh, where are you going?
New!
What are you doing?
Nothing...
Haha, New, where did you get the flowers from?
Um, it wasn't me. Pat and So gave it to me.
No way!
Like this, it's adorable.
Are you crazy!
I told you it's adorable. Adorable to death.
This is the cutest.
Indeed, it's cute.
How's it going, guys?
Do you like the clip I found?
It's awesome, dude!
Totally teen! Great job, man!
That's the best, Go! I can't stand still anymore.
Cut it out, Nic! I told you to stop.
Stop what, huh?
Stop aiming at my back, that's what.
Oops, sorry, buddy. Almost done, though.
Come on, chill, buddy. Friends help each other. It's all for fun.
I'm already going to get caught by the cops anyway. So, just finish up.
What's all this noise, boys?
This is the library, you know?
There's nothing going on here.
Nothing at all?
Nope, nothing at all, Jeedny.
Can I help?
It's okay, Jeedny. Let's go, guys.
Hey, jeedny, what are you doing!?
Let Jeedny help, please.
With such a sweet face, Go must like it for sure.
Jeedny, don't do this in the library.
People might think badly of us.
Who cares if they think badly? Good or bad,
I'm going to get what I want! If I want something, I'll get it!
Jeedny, you're not a girl. Others might not see us in a good light.
Why do this? It doesn't look good at all.
Fine, Go! If this isn't good here, let's go somewhere else then.
Where are my friends? Why aren't they helping me?
Let me go!!!!
Go, you're actually quite cute!
What are you staring at?
Have you never seen the prettiest girl in this school before?
Oh my goodness! We just criticized Pat and So, and here we meet this beauty queen!
She's like the number one flour, the best of the best!
Oh my, she's so fair she doesn't look human!
The prettiest like a fairytale princess! Even the lowly ladyboys exist.
There you have it, a dejected ladyboy with no one to court. Must be quite pitiful.
Even if I'm alone, I'm still fabulous. At least I study better than you guys.
Unlike you, who lack essence, I look even more ordinary without makeup.
Seeing me, one would be more respectful, you know?
Hey, speaking like this, are you picking a fight, Jeedny?
Fine, I won't accept you guys.
Meanie! Don't pick on us. Just don't!
Hey, what's going on, May?
Oh no, it hurts! Is something wrong, May?
What's wrong, Bell?
Ouch! Ouch!
What are you guys going to do to us, Big?
Trying to bully us in school, huh?
Yeah, Nic is the same.
If you want something, just tell us. No need to do this.
No, we're just rushing to class ourselves. Sorry about that.
Oh no, it's too painful.
My poor husband! Oh no!
You rascals!
Hey, what are you doing? Let us go right now! Let us go!
Please, let us go! Anyone, please help!
You two must take responsibility for us.
Coming to mess with us like this is not good. Beauty can be quite a sin, you know?
That's right! You both are hurting all over, you bad boys! Oh no, it hurts so much!
You both must take responsibility.
You're our husbands, after all. You brutes!
You both pinned us down first. You both have to take responsibility.
You both are to blame!
You think you're the best? You're like a monkey cups!
May and Bell, they're just fake! The hostility is real, the fear is real!
Help us, help us, let us go now! Let us go!
Please, let us go! Tell them to let us go!
What's going on here? Stop right now! Stop!!!
Teacher, these two boys are bullying us. Help us, please, teacher!
Yes, teacher. Kittisak and Kittiphong are bullying us, causing us harm, teacher.
It hurts so much, teacher.
It's an accident, teacher. We didn't mean to, teacher.
You're the one who's intentional!!
Arthit and Pongsak, let go and stop messing with each other.
Let go now! I told you to stop right now!!!
Really messed up timing! Oh my!
They're bullying us, teacher.
It's an accident, teacher. We didn't mean to, teacher.
Teacher, I saw the whole situation.
The situation was like this, teacher. It's like...
Hey, Jeedny, let's meet at the library!
Come here right now.
Meanie!
So, what happened here? There was quite a commotion.
As you saw, I just walked here.
It was an accident, teacher. I didn't mean to, teacher.
We both ran and bumped into those two, for real, teacher.
So, can we go to class first, teacher? Goodbye, teacher.
Okay, then hurry up and go to class.
Excuse me, teacher. Goodbye, teacher.
These kids these days are really naughty, especially the ladyboy daughters.
Hey! They're supposed to be twins. How come they're not the same size?
Oh, that's wicked! I don't think they're always the same.
Even if they're twins, they might not be exactly the same size.
And what about Nic and Big? Do you guys think they're the same size?
Even if they're twin brothers, they're probably not identical.
I think they are the same size, actually.
I don't know, it's just a sense I have.
Are you crazy? I don't think so.
Try subtly asking them.
Oh, and even if they say that, they don't really seem to match.
These twin brothers.
Yeah, but I have a feeling. I think they might be gay.
No way, man! Are you overthinking this?
I think they might just not care about the same gender stuff.
Wow, really? And they're bisexual?
Well, it's not certain, but I'm pretty sure these twin brothers are not ordinary.
These guys here.
So, today, shall we go and find out?
How are we going to prove it, Your Highness?
Don't tell me we're going to sneak and spy on them. Play it cool.
And are you guys coming?
Let's go.
Then let's collect the stuff.
Hold on! No need to collect, I'll bring it. The janitors will come to collect anyway.
We're already screwed.
Hurry up and follow.
Ohhh, naughty!
Come back here!
What did you guys see?!
We could barely see anything clearly.
And when we saw them peeing, will we really know their actual size?
Yeah, true. I forgot about that.
Let's go home then. We'll find another opportunity next time.
Those twins, finding an opportunity won't be difficult.
Yeah, they don't seem to be very careful.
Alright, let's head back.
I want to have some smoothies outside the school. It's so refreshing.
Refreshing like the smell we're inhaling, huh
Indeed.
Satisfaction. Go home!
It's locked.
Help, please!
Oh no!
I can't climb up. Who locked it?
This is bad! How are we going to stay in this school? Why is it so scary here?
Ohhh, don't be afraid anymore. Look at yourself in the mirror.
You're beautiful. You don't have to be afraid of anything. Seriously!
Hey, even if you're scared, why bite each other? Your face is indeed handsome.
I've never stopped being scared. The fear is real!
Hmmm, I'll smack you soon. Newcomers like us need to be prepared.
I've also felt the radiation of evil,
whether it's from overly beautiful gangs, the Olive Gang, or that Jeedny.
There are even other groups like the tough ones. We can't lose, you know.
Alright, I'll fight to the end. I've got the determination to study here now. We won't lose.
And what about your lucky number, huh? Scrape until you see the next new year's numbers. Haven't got them yet? Wait until someone else sees. Embarrassing, huh?
Ohhh, why feel embarrassed? We'll have to wait patiently for the lucky numbers.
Can't ask for the daytime ones. It has to be the nighttime ones.
We can't rush. Our parents can't afford to buy a lot this time.
Just two or three numbers will do, my dear.
Hahaha!
What are you two scraping for? I'll squeeze your necks if you keep going! Hahaha!
Oh no!
What was that sound, Pat? Did you hear it too?
I did, but I can't get up. Help me!
Ohhhhh!
Holy shit, please wait!
What happened to you guys?
Why do you look so down? You seem terrible.
That's because of you-know-who! What's going on?
You didn't sleep all night. Those two are the same.
They look like they've seen ghosts. Are they scaring themselves?
What happened to those two?
We were haunted by ghosts! It was terrifying!
Hey! Does our school have ghosts?
Is that so? Our school has ghosts?
Yes, we encountered them yesterday. It's just as you see here.
Initially, there weren't any. But now there are two.
Really annoying indeed.
Sorry, didn't see you there.
Are you guys ganging up on me!?
Gang up? How would I know what's going on?
Huh! Why would we gang up?
Face to face, it's going to be awesome!!
So cool! I'm out of here. We're just kidding.
Sorry, if you don't have the guts to face us, don't talk big.
Get out!!
Geez, you're so cool.
Oh... wait up!!! Ugly ladyboys!!!
You're it, Ugly ladyboys!!!
I'm not sure if this is real.
Oops!
What's this?
Isn't this your handiwork from yesterday's incident?