"We want to dress in school uniforms according to our chosen gender identity"
Hello, everyone around the world!
Here comes Jeedny!
Wow, look at her! So bold to dress up for school. The ultimate Barbie!
How did she get through the school gate like this?
Absolutely fabulous! She's got the whole package!
I think she must have brought a change of clothes to switch at school. So daring!
She was running to join our group just yesterday, and now this? What's happening here?
That's it! This is worse than I thought.
Look at that fierce expression; it's asking for a smack!
Excuse me, but facing this, it's useless to challenge us.
No matter what she does, she won't outshine us.
Wait until next time; I'll dress up and compete against her.
I guarantee I'll be way prettier!
Today, Jeedny really stole the scene for sure. Gotta hand it to her.
It seems like she won't stop at this point. It's more mischievous than I thought.
Have you guys ever seen a sperm whale?
Heard they can run. How about it?
Dunno, man. I've never seen a sperm whale.
I've seen what they depend on, though.
See it every day. Play with it every day.
Some days, you see it more than three times.
Oh, my. That's quite a revelation, Go.
What are you talking about? We're embarrassed, you know?
What's there to be embarrassed about?
Where's the embarrassment?
I feel embarrassed just thinking about when the guys in the room do things like you, Go.
I feel embarrassed.
Oh, your imagination is so wide. What a scene! How about you?
The daydreaming of the chubby ladyboy is real.
Yeah, girls, it's a natural thing like this.
But, Mac, do they really produce sperm?
Hey, Go, you don't have to tell everything.
You're really overwhelming.
Don't worry, guys. We've learned from the real thing, biology, right?
So, are we going to use real sperm for studying?
Sure!
Where are you going to get the sperm?
Don't say you're going to use an example from someone in the room,
like the older guys said. Hey, it's true?
If it's true, we should use a lottery system then.
Hey, really?
Are you the class leader? Can we take your stuff?
Yeah, we'll take your stuff.
How do we do this? This doesn't seem fair.
May I? I'll take Go's stuff.
Heard that you take it out every day, is it true?
Yeah, what about it, Go?
Oh, that day, I probably wasn't in the mood. I couldn't handle it.
Can we help you, Go?
Oh, the force is strong, Pat!!!
Both force and charm.
That's the best.
Real charm does exist!
We think we've had a fair lottery, but everyone in the room has to participate.
And what about the girls? Will you accept this?
So, to sum it up, the guys will draw lots, and the girls don't have to. Is that okay?
So, if it comes to that day, the guys have to draw lots. Everyone okay with this?
Wow, awesome!
Really looking forward to seeing who'll be the lucky guy
to represent us for the practical biology class.
What are you up to, Jeedny?
Oh, startled me!
Just passing by, heard some chit-chat from room 13.
Well, not exactly eavesdropping, just happened to hear it casually.
And coincidentally heard what exactly, bro?
Well, all the 10th-grade rooms will have a representative for the practical biology class.
I propose myself for the job.
Seriously?
Yeah, true. I've been quietly listening in for a while.
Oh, not eavesdropping, just casually listening.
I think it has to be you, looking all diligent and stuff.
Alright, we'll give up our rights. You go for it, Frank.
Why me? Why does it have to be me?
Oh, no need to argue or struggle.
On that day, whoever it is,
Jeedni will gladly volunteer to scrub and iron the uniform for them.
Jeedny! It’s really scary!
Why should anything be scary?
Can't you see how beautiful I am?
Look closely, please.
So, you're dressed up for class, huh? Alright,
looking good!
We'll excuse ourselves, Jeedny, as we're heading to the restroom.
Alright, see you later, Jeedny!
I am the epitome of beauty in this world.
Hello, I'm Jeedny! Hahaha
Oh, I'm right here. Stop laughing, kids.
Stop and go change into the standard school uniform.
Hurry up before I have to call your parents to meet.
Why can't I dress like this, Teacher Mo?
No matter how I dress, I can still study the same.
You shouldn't have to ask, dear.
Our school is an all-boys school.
You are a male student, and you have to dress according to the school's regulations.
No matter what gender you choose to be, you must follow the rules set by the school.
Our school is open about gender issues. What else do you want?
Look at the teacher and then look back at yourself.
Yes, Teacher. I won't do this again.
I'm sorry.
Maybe the principal will allow it for a week.
Students can wear wizard costumes to study for a week.
I doubt you'll dress like this at that time, right?
Really, Teacher?
I saw how they dressed in the assembly hall a few days ago.
Even if I'm not sure, it's a friendly gesture.
Isn't it? And where is your school uniform, dear?
It's in the locker, Teacher. I'll hurry to change.
Okay, go ahead.
I'll go in to teach first. See you in Thai class, dear.
Demanding attention works well, huh?
Everyone talks about me.
Why is my rating so high? This is just the beginning.
I have to create a bigger wave.
I'm shininggggg!
That team, what's going on? I see only one human;
the rest seem to have escaped from the zoo or the jungle.
Those three girls, can they jump and hit the ball?
They must weigh over a hundred each.
Why not bring the guys down to play?
Stop with this volleyball; let's play something else.
Ugh,
I can't take it anymore.
How about we just hit each other?
Skip the volleyball; I'm done. Let's fight!
Don't exchange blows.
These three won't be affected.
Whatever it is, let's compete with skills and strength, not violence.
True, only good at talking.
Every day, all I hear is complaining about others' behavior. Ugh!
Well, well, these girls look fierce.
How about playing? Look at them, confident and strong.
Should we be a substitute team? Let's see how it goes.
Let's give it a try. Look and see if we can be the team to beat.
Even if it's not a serious competition, we won't hold back. Be ready, girls.
Alright, let's do it!
Hold on!
Stop with the banter and the taunting. Compete instead. Let's go and play.
I'm beautiful,
I'm outstanding,
I'm sweet.
However, I must win. I'm beautiful!
I'll hit the volleyball on your face, one by one. Let's see how you react. Watch it!
Look at their evil glares and feel the shivers. Watch out, girls
Let's see how they feel with a powerful spike. Ready to be scared?
I don't want to insult or curse, but sometimes actions speak louder than words. Hit it!
Slap them with the volleyball. Ready, steady!
Anyway, we have to win. Haha!
It's like a real war, not just a volleyball game. So scary!
Need water?
Oh!
Tired, huh?
Are you giving it to me, Mac?
Yes. I'll open it for you.
Tired, right? Let me wipe your face.
Oh, refreshing, Mac.
Throw up!!!
Thanks, Mac.
I'm really tired. Wipe here too.
Mac! Stop!
What's wrong?
Take this, don't forget the volleyball class in the afternoon.
Another 1,000?
Oh no, what is this for?
Last time, you didn't pay.
Oh, here.
Thanks.
Alright.
I'm truly beautiful. Everyone must envy me.
Oh, friends, there’s a new teacher in charge!!!
Hello, students.
Hello, sir.
My name is Thanawat, or you can call me Teacher Pae.
I'm the new head of the PE department.
I'll be teaching volleyball, basketball, and swimming.
In the next hour, I'll have you all divide into groups for warm-up exercises.
Each group will have 5 members.
Let's get started.
Wait a moment, sir.
What's up, students?
I brought water for you, sir. My housekeeper was busy, so I had to bring it instead.
Thank you very much.
Oh, Jeedny is exhausted. My head is spinning, like there's a storm coming.
Everyone, warm up. I'll take her to the nurse's office.
Oh, what's this? Hey!!! Tell me what this is!
Oh, Jeedny is dangerously cunning, the ultimate schemer. She's a wicked person.
She's ready to challenge us for sure.
She's trying to take revenge on us. Talking too much!
Right now, I have to admit, I'm extremely annoyed.
Annoyed to the max. That flea is unexpectedly malicious.
Give it to her!
This is what they call 'beautiful but not afraid, afraid very fast.'
Oh, this is a clear one-man show.
I won't forget today's events, Jeedny.
We'll see each other well. Oh my!
Jeedny, Crazy person! I won't keep you in my good books.
She's truly wicked. What should I do? Today, I lost two rounds to her.
The taste of defeat is real.
This is just dipping sauce.
I'll challenge everyone now. Watch me!!!
Hahaha!!!
Hello, Teacher Yod and Teacher Dech. Where are you heading?
Hi, just dropped by for breakfast.
Thought of Teacher Pei, so I bought some snacks.
Take it, enjoy. Delicious.
Oh, so touched. Thank you so much.
No need to be touched. We're willing and happy to do this.
Enjoy your meal. If you want something special, let us know.
Thank you very much. I'm truly grateful.
Good morning, teachers.
Wait,
your face looks familiar.
Are you a student in which class and section?
I'm in class 4/1,
studied with you, Teacher Dej, and Teacher Yod throughout junior high school.
Oh, starting to remember.
Wow, you're Niwat right?
The top student for the past 3 years.
Yes, that's me. Jeedny your student.
The one who ranked first in the entire school for the past 3 years.
How did this happen? How did you change like this?
I chose to be like this. It's my happiness and dream.
I don't know why I'd keep it hidden.
So, are you comfortable now?
Yes, I am. Thank you very much, Teachers,
for taking care of me at the nurse's office yesterday.
Still not well.
I'll take you to the nurse's office.
Excuse us, Teacher Yod and Teacher Dej. I'll take her to the nurse's office first.
Sure, go ahead.
This is Jeedny, the troublemaker.
Where did she graduate from? She stole the scene so much.
Encountered a student spreading cake all over her face this morning
instead of getting her face done.
Instead of gaining face, she lost face like that.
How are you, Dad?
The new dormitory is good. The room is spacious and quiet.
The school is also good.
Friends are nice, and the teachers are good. No issues here, Dad.
I prefer studying here, so no need to transfer to your friend's school.
That's all for now, Dad. Everyone has already gone downstairs.
We need to change classes.
I have enough money for now, Dad.
Thank you so much Dad.
Teacher,
the three of us are not good at playing volleyball.
We don't know how to use our hands.
Could you please help us by showing us how to hold hands, arms, and guide us a bit?
Teacher, and what about me?
How should I do it?
Like this, or like that, or maybe like this?
Alright, I'll teach you. Let me show you.
Please teach us.
We're not doing well. What should we do?
How should we hold hands and legs, teacher?
No, you should hold it like this and hit right here.
I can't hit it at all. What should I do?
Thank you, Teacher.
Okay.
Sorry for making you fall.
No need to apologize; it's our fault too.
We sneaked in a bit. Let's both apologize. We're not good at sports.
We'll teach you.
But we'd like to fall like this again; it's comfortable lying down like this forever.
Teacher,
how should I position my hand? And which hand should I use to hit?
What about me, Teacher? My knees are weak until I have no strength left.
Be careful, students.
Are you feeling okay?
Teacher, what kind of water would you like to drink? We'll go get it for you.
I'll have plain water, thank you very much.
Alright, we'll be right back.
Congratulations on this, everyone. Let's go, guys.
Today, we don't have to worry about anything anymore.
Whatever, Parn.
Okay, pay attention.
Keep this arm straight, and then hit the ball here. The ball will fall right here.
Is it okay like this? Try hitting it like this. Can you do it?
I'm here.
Oh, my goodness.
Sorry, Teacher. I didn't mean to.
It's okay. It's okay. I'll take off my shirt, and then I'll teach.
You did well, Parn.
Today, I'll treat you to ten pieces of pork.
Pure joy really exists!
We must thank this water. It's excellent.
I'll give this event a full ten and another ten! Haha!
Today, everyone's spirits are high.
We have to get an A for this subject, right?
We'll be serious about studying, won't we?
So bright!
Stuffed steamed bun! One for you, Teacher.
Go on. Go study, and we'll join you.
Everyone, listen up!
Today, Teacher Dej called and said he's going to teach us how to put on a condom, and...
Yayyyy! Woohoo!
Oh no, not good, not beautiful at all.
Do you like it, though?
Love it!
I'll demonstrate if you want, guys.
Don't want to see a chicken's leg, eww!
Sorry, mine's not small, you know.
Damn, take the biggest one!
Yayyyy!
You're the show-off here.
Funny! You talk too much. You're just showing off.
Or maybe you're not big, but your eggs are cute, huh?
Hey! Watch your mouth, I'm strong!
If it's about big things... spill it.
Oh, big mouth. Seeing the real deal, do you want to stay quiet now?
What will you do then?
Hey, where is everyone?
Who's going to demonstrate today?
Damn it! Today, I'm definitely the target.
Considerate indeed.
Alright, I'll teach the correct way to put it on first.
Everyone should already know why we use condoms, right?
In this day and age, no need for explanations.
Study it yourselves. True, right?
Don't rush to learn something else. But let's go, knowing the right way is better.
But, Teacher, I don't know why we use it.
Do you want to know for personal use or to educate someone else?
Oh, uh, I don't know anything, Teacher.
Well, of course.
It helps prevent pregnancy and protects against sexually transmitted diseases.
Like you, for instance, might need it for the latter.
Who told you? I can get pregnant too.
Deep thoughts!
Oh, my!
Alright,
let's start with the buying process.
Don't buy unknown brand condoms. Choose only those with recognized standards.
The standards may vary between brands,
but they should be certified by relevant government agencies in each country.
When purchasing, select from stores that store products in a cool place,
protected from sunlight and heat, to prevent condom deterioration.
Then, choose a condom size that fits your circumference properly,
avoiding it being too tight or too loose.
It's hard to find my size.
Small?
Put it on and everything is tight. Let me tell you.
Just jerks off, why wear it?
Please don’t look down on me!
Carefully tore the condom from the packet.
Be careful not to let the condom come into contact with your fingernails or sharp objects.
After tearing the envelope out.
You should prepare to put on a condom immediately.
Wear it when the penis is erect.
Gently squeeze the air out of the bulb at the end of the condom until there are no air bubbles left.
If you don't squeeze out the air bubbles.
When ejaculating sperm or having sex, this bulb can rupture.
Well, why not give it a try?
Yes, sir..
Hey! What are you doing?
I will demonstrate how to put on a condom.
I didn't say that the demonstration was the real thing.
I meant to demonstrate with this guy!
Huh! !
Hahahahahahaha
I didn't tell you to use the real thing.
It's not all said yet, let's think about it ourselves.
OK, are you ready?
Okay, this is the correct way. Clap your hands for your friends.
Hello, New!
Why are you standing there smiling alone in the library?
Oh, Jeed! Hello!
You seem to be in a good mood.
But wait, for now, you have to call me Jeedny, not just Jeed.
Oh, sure! No problem.
It's nothing much. I'm just thinking of something fun.
Jeedny in the library?
I came to find more books to read.
I need to maintain my title as the top student,
reigning champion for three consecutive years since middle school.
You know I'm the smartest in our class, right?
I know. Everyone knows that. Jeedny is really excellent in academics.
But I don't want everyone to only recognize me for being smart, New.
I want everyone to accept me for who I am right now.
They will eventually.
And Jeed, or Jeedny, just introduced yourself at the beginning of the semester.
People might not be used to it yet.
Well, New isn't bullied like me. New can speak up.
New knows what we face every day.
Sometimes, the guys bully me. We don't even feel anything.
It follows their group dynamics.
But it hurts a lot when we're singled out for bullying,
especially the Gang of 13, in the same room with New...
True, they might not be as malicious as Jeedny or others perceive.
Sometimes, it's just loud noises, teasing each other.
Initially, there were quarrels,
but it seems like they've gotten along better lately.
People like those eight,
their personalities won't change for the better, New.
It's just a clear act. The manipulation is sharp.
The well-behaved image of New,  they won't catch up.
Well, I’m not that well-behaved.
I’m just an ordinary person with love, anger, and jealousy.
Sometimes, I’m doesn't think like everyone else.
Nobody is perfect, Jeedny.
Anyway, no matter what, You can always talk to me.
Okay, then let's find some books to read together.