This movie,
LAUGHTER
On November 24, 1938,
Yu Jing City,
our strongest army,
had appeared as
a biological cause,
And the youngest army of Red Army
was killed.
The Hillary Elegant ambition is being granted on theEM Korea – go, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you ...
His pride still meixo exposure aware yet
I'm not afraid of the world.
I'm afraid of the world.
Please forgive me.
Because I'm not harmful enough.
Although you're my leader,
if will be the majority danke I am.
Please forgive me.
I'm afraid of the world.
I am afraid of the world.
Don't move!
Be careful. The car is coming today.
Thank you.
If it weren't for you,
I would have burned the food for the chicken.
You're welcome.
I've been working for two years.
Besides, the teacher has taught me
that every person who needs help is a hero.
This is the third one.
My bag?
Little boy, you're a hunter?
I'm not.
But I'm going to join them.
The Iron Valley is about to start with the city of Yu.
You're going to be a guard now.
Forget it.
Night rain.
The longer the night, the darker the darkness.
The more the fear of the cold.
The more shining the light.
Teacher, I will definitely complete your wish.
I will become a great Han Xiaolie soldier.
The Iron Valley is the teacher of Wei Bu Bao.
They've improved a little bit
in the latest trade talks.
At the same time, they've increased the content of the three-layered water content
for the raw materials of the Wa Fang.
Lord Yicheng, it's been two years.
The Iron Valley has changed its mind for the second time.
What do you think?
To be honest,
the Iron Valley is the source of the reputation of Yu's city.
But what can we do?
The Iron Valley has already taken six of its allies.
If we don't sign it,
the heavy-duty He Cheng Shi of the Iron Valley
will be able to defeat us in the city.
Of course we won't sign it.
If we don't sign it?
If the army of the Iron Valley
is defeated,
what will we fight for?
Are you the Dragon Knight of thousands?
Or are you the guard of the gate?
Maybe we really have no choice.
Do you think Yu Jincheng will agree to our offer?
Your Highness,
maybe they still have some tricks
to refuse their own agreement.
It's not important, is it?
We've already started to act.
Yes.
According to your instructions,
our warning has been used.
Not only that,
after today,
Yu Jincheng's base will be gone.
Oh, are there any more
secret arrangements in the Lu family?
Just wait and see.
Now it's Han Xiaoliebin's turn to check.
Han Xiaoliebin?
Is he a teacher?
Please...
Show me your ID card.
According to the latest regulations,
no one in the Iron Valley
can enter Yu Jincheng.
Let me find it.
Where is it?
Sorry, sorry.
I'll pick it up.
Sorry.
The Iron Valley is about to be defeated.
You, raise your head.
Go.
Where is the water?
Don't move.
Get the car back.
Are you from the Iron Valley?
No.
Take the car down.
Please run.
You...
Are you okay?
Let's go.
I'll make it.
Oh, no.
My bag.
How about this?
Get the crystal.
How dare you to be my uncle?
Are you tired of me?
Don't.
What should I do?
The teacher's clothes are still in the bag.
The ID card is the badge of the soldiers.
Ye Yu, take my glory.
Keep walking.
The teacher entrusted me with my glory.
I can't be damaged.
You...
The power of the Qingluan...
Look.
The Qingluan body.
The Qingluan body
is the technology design
that Dr. Suoqi Si from the biological science
mentioned 30 years ago.
It was the Qingluan plan
that shocked the world.
You all should know that
all human behavior commands
are caused by the brain.
However, the development of the brain
and the use of the operation
are limited.
In the design of Professor Suoqi Si,
he used the help of the human body
to create various judgments
to help people's brain.
He also added the star-shaped diamond
and various speed-up secrets.
It makes humans
get the same reaction power
as superman in a short time.
Power.
Such a successful experiment
is called the Qingluan body.
If we can train
a group of Qingluan body soldiers
in the city of Yu Jing,
we can completely
take the scale of Iron Valley City.
Dr. Suoqi Si,
the information of the Qingluan plan
is also in your biological research.
Yes.
However, the Qingluan plan is not perfect.
The number of dead bodies in the forest
is 99.5%.
The population
has become a plant.
Professor Suoqi Si has already made a conclusion.
The Qingluan plan needs to be corrected.
Qingluan body
cannot exist in reality.
You are right.
This ability
cannot be easily confused.
You are Qingluan body.
Let me go back to see the master.
Yan Zao, get ready.
Yes.
Follow me.
Earlier,
there was a true murderer,
raising a daughter of Jin.
I finally have some energy.
Grandpa.
Why are you back?
How did you get the ship?
Grandpa.
What do you want to do?
The Great Yujin City.
The Great Yujin City that we raised.
Today, I will let you pay for it.
Let's all die together.
Oh, no.
Zhong Ji.
I still have to take the ship into the rain.
Let me stop her.
Stop the shooting.
Captain, there is a soldier.
No, stop.
The main force is our mission.
Stop.
Don't shoot.
The Great Yujin City.
Stop.
For the Iron Thread Embroidery.
Stop the shooting.
The first and second soldiers.
They are the worst of the young men.
They are not popular.
Go.
They are moving away.
The direction is bad.
Turn around.
Captain.
Send Captain to the Yujin City immediately.
Leave it to me.
Take her down.
Be careful.
Don't let her die.
The Holy Tomb should be searched.
I think...
This...
Send the Holy Tomb to the city.
It's for them.
Time is up.
Our gift should be sent.
Chafinque's secret door.
Why?
It'sory.
Good move.
The Holy Tomb is waiting for...
Aim, as expected.
Why don't you give it to the one who really loves you?
Let go of that child!
Little brother, we might have to stay here for a few days.
The door is still open. I'm really sorry.
You're a weakling.
You saved me?
You're lying.
I can't eat the dead one.
You can save him, right?
What do you mean?
Not only does he pay, but also find the doctor.
The dead one is waiting for my trial.
That fire
didn't break through, didn't break through, didn't escape
It's always me
who's still silent before the sword
How long do we have left?
I can only endure
the hard journey
I'm too
motivated, I wanna carry on
the wind that lives on
A fresh morning
I load,tes in
freedom
I'm not afraid of the world
I'm afraid of the world
I'm excited
I want to go first
The hot wind
The unbreakable
The wine
I'm not used to
Freedom