THIS DRAMA IS CREATED
FOR ENTERTAINMENT PURPOSES
ALL CHARACTERS, SETTINGS
AND EVENTS ARE ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS
THERE IS NO INTENT TO REFERENCE
ANY ORGANIZATIONS OR INDIVIDUALS
So Dad sent you?
Yes. He wanted to know whether you still
serve the country or became a mole…
A mole? Me?
Hey, you mole!
It wasn't easy for me to get close enough
for them to trust me, Dad.
Right now, they're the only option
to keep this mission going.
Everyone entering Pha Mok now
is locked into the screening system.
If someone who isn't an insider
like me changes the data,
within two days
they'll know exactly
who the seven of you are.
Done.
Where is the agent data?
- Hey! Where's the fire?
- Hey. Hurry up.
- Fire.
- Huh?
Quiet.
Where is she?
What's up?
Nothing suspicious?
Suddenly there's not a damn thing at all?
How is that possible?
See?
If I hadn't helped you, you'd have been
caught back in the server room.
What are you doing? I came to help.
Why are you pointing a gun at me?
You're done. Get off me.
- You're heavy.
- Well.
Are you blushing? Acting all jumpy.
You know "In-car"?
The back seat's this wide, real comfy.
Are you messing with me, you pervert?
I'll stop. Sorry, sorry.
I'll stop. Let go. Get your foot off.
You deserve this.
Please. That's enough.
- You pervert!
- No…
Wait. Hold on!
- I can't take it anymore.
- Hey, calm down.
- You even know how to massage?
- Hey.
Calm down. What did I do wrong?
Calm down. I gave you a massage, didn't I?
Firm pressure, right?
But it hurt, you know?
- I didn't mean to.
- Excuse me.
We sincerely apologize.
If our service wasn't satisfactory,
may we offer additional service,
or another free massage session?
Please, sir.
Fine, but make this guy
go retrain his massage skills.
He's all talk, huh?
I should've taught him Muay Thai instead.
- Walking away already?
- Mr. Songdej.
You're not that tough.
I'll knock you out like this.
- Ugh.
- Mr. Songdej.
Wat Pho-certified?
Dozens of certificates,
years of overseas experience too?
You faked your resume, right?
I'm not feeling well today.
So I didn't do well.
But I didn't want to take leave.
It'd affect my record.
Don't worry about your record.
If you work like this,
then pack up, go home, take medicine,
and don't come back here again.
Huh?
You're firing me? Isn't that too much?
What the hell are you doing, bro?
Only a few hours undercover
and you're fired already?
I was smooth as hell, but that manager
isn't as kind as she looks to be.
Ms. Khemjira, please have some sympathy
for working people like us.
I feel sorry for him.
You know each other?
- No.
- I never met him before.
Khim.
What's going on?
Recently, Mr. Natee ordered
tighter control on everyone here.
I'll report directly to Mr. Natee.
So he can check quickly.
So?
We don't know each other.
I'll drag him out of here right now.
- Go, go.
- Oh.
Yeah, I'll go.
All right, all right.
Well? Total disaster.
Even the gods can't help you now.
I believe you now.
Money really can do anything.
Someone beautiful like an angel
turns out to be a criminal.
Complaining won't help.
If Sarge finds out,
we're dead for sure.
Yeah, yeah. I'll figure something out.
You've been marked by them.
I'll handle it.
Damn it.
This is what you called
"handled properly"?
Huh.
Look.
Here.
What do you think?
Dead quiet.
Of course she is. She's unconscious.
Ugh.
Instead of just suspecting me,
now they suspect both of us.
A manager-level card.
She should have the keys
all the way to central operations
that we suspect.
Let's… Hey.
It was me who started it,
so I have to end it too.
Hang on a sec.
Here it is.
Give it to me.
I'll do it.
Between a sniper like me
and a bomb disposal guy like you,
who's better at going undercover?
And you,
clean this up properly.
Damn.
If those hands are so fast,
go pickpocket around Silom.
Dead quiet, right?
Where's my friend?
Still not answering? Say it.
Where is she?
Where is my friend?
Not yet.
What's taking so long, bro?
Huh?
She was sitting right here.
She was sitting like this,
tied like this, or like this?
What did you say? Say it again.
- Quiet.
- Quiet, right?
Dead quiet, huh?
Do you know
- that hurt like hell.
- Napa.
- Stop, Napa.
- Ugh.
- Stop. He's not one of them.
- You…
- Not one of them?
- Yeah.
So who are they?
I'm getting dizzy.
Finally.
How's the plan going?
The infiltration worked.
In just a few hours,
we got insider-level intel.
Your team's undercover skills are no joke.
- Of course.
- Right?
I told you our Seven Legends
aren't amateurs.
- So how good are they?
- Exactly, Sarge.
Just look at the leader.
Wow.
So how did you get this information?
Well…
It wasn't that complicated.
We got close to people on the inside.
You might not believe this.
Do you believe in sacred things?
- Oh, Buddha amulet.
- Whoa!
- Go on, tell her.
- Ms. Duangnet, do you know Luang Pu Khem?
- Yeah.
- This is Luang Pu Priao.
The monk who walked
on fire path, 600 meters long.
First step, nothing happened.
Next step, the robe started burning.
- Oh.
- Third step, believe it or not?
- What happened?
- Not funny.
Not funny?
I lost fellow agents,
better than all of you,
because of mistakes and secrecy.
Right now, we can't trust anyone.
If anyone else finds out who we are,
it means we're all dead.
Come on, sometimes the job requires risks.
- Don't nitpick.
- Yeah.
- You're being overly cautious.
- Exactly.
Trust my team.
I guarantee these guys
don't screw up easily. Right?
- Yes, Sarge.
- Yes, sir.
A secret stays a secret.
Okay?
Good. Nodding means okay.
- Yeah.
- Then let's get ready
to wipe out their human-trafficking
network completely!
- Yes, sir.
- Yeah.
- Got it.
When Ms. Duangnet speaks,
you all respond in perfect unison.
- Oh?
- But when I say it,
you all don't?
Different people, Sarge.
Again! Understood?
- Yes, sir!
- Yes.
Still not perfect.
Everyone. Understood?
- Yes, ma'am!
Wait.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Where's Dan?
I sent him on a special mission.
What special mission? Why wasn't I told?
CONSTRUCTION SITE
LOWER YOUR SPEED
Hey!
Hey. Hey.
Hey.
Damn. What the hell?
No way there's nothing.
Don't let me find out.
If you really are a mole like I suspect,
you're dead.
See? I knew it.
He really does suspect you.
I'm not stupid enough
to leave evidence tying back to me.
But if Tiangmon's right-hand man
suspects you this much,
it won't be long.
Tiangmon doesn't know yet.
I'm someone he deeply trusts.
If the proof isn't solid enough,
Jack won't risk upsetting Tiangmon.
But if he's this suspicious,
I think…
Wait.
Don't act alone under any circumstances.
You can't afford the risk. If you fail,
all our lives are on the line.
What a relief.
Blood tests and X-rays showed
there's nothing to worry about.
The doctor even said
you're in excellent shape.
You may not need a long recovery.
It still hurts, though.
My arm might be broken.
If it's broken, I'm screwed.
I'm so sorry.
It was my fault.
I wasn't watching the road.
Actually, I wanted
to talk to you about that.
The accident.
I don't think it was a coincidence.
I think it was…
destiny.
Ugh.
I was listening so seriously.
Let's say from now on,
you don't owe me anything.
I'll take care of myself.
And I won't ask you for a single baht.
I think
I can't just leave you alone.
Then,
I'll hire a private nurse to
take care of you until you're discharged.
Thank you so much.
You're beautiful and kind.
Then, do you mind if I ask your name?
- My name is…
- Mook.
Dad?
Tiangmon, a retired soldier.
Phoenix's right-hand man,
the most powerful man in Pha Mok.
So that means this guy's a big shot.
An accident?
Yes, sir. An accident.
Hello, Dad.
I'm not your dad. Don't call me that.
Know your place.
- Dad.
- Come here.
What were you doing out so late, huh?
What? Answer when I ask.
I was looking for my cat.
It ran away from home, and…
I've been searching for days.
- Your cat ran away?
- Yes, sir. My cat's missing.
Very funny.
You think I'd believe that crap?
Spill it.
What were you really doing there?
- Answer me.
- Dad!
Stop doing this, please.
Ouch.
Damn it.
She was out all night.
That's suspicious as hell.
Are you looking for me?
Duangnet.
Hey! What?
Ow! What the hell?
Hey.
Damn it.
Duangnet.
You're not getting away today.
You think you can escape?
Duangnet!
You're so tough, huh?
Hello, welcome…
Juk sent me.
Here you go.
Is he
the special guest you mentioned, Napa?
Mr. Natee.
Yes. This is Mr. Hasus.
Actually, my name is Hazus.
But I like it
when Thai people call me that.
It feels friendlier.
And the reason I can speak Thai
is because I like Thai women.
I like going to Patpong,
Pattaya, Phang Nga, Phuket,
and
I like doing business with Thai people.
I hope this trip
will be a memorable one for you.
Napa, take good care of Mr. Hasus,
I mean Mr. Hazus.
Yes.
All right.
Oh, wait, wait.
- Hey!
Hey!
I want to talk to you.
I heard that
there are special services here.
If I want to use them,
what do I need to do?
My place
doesn't offer any special services
beyond what's listed on the website.
All guests here
can enjoy the same services equally.
Enjoy your stay.
Send someone to tail him.
Dig into his background
and report back to me immediately.
Yes, sir.
Prepare a suite.
The bait's taken.
Don't worry.
My team is good.
I trained them myself.
Right?
Did you ever train me?
Remember what I taught?
Fine, you taught me.
Are you scared?
You have no idea
how twisted Natee Suriyont really is
behind that polished elite mask.
I understand.
Women
are the most beautiful thing
in this world.
Anyone who can hurt women
is not a good person.
This is our last chance.
If you fail,
Napa's sister's life will be in danger.
No matter what I say,
I probably can't put your mind at ease.
This sacred amulet has kept me safe,
protected me,
and brought me victory in every battle.
May I?
I promise you.
I will save Ms. Napa's sister.
And I will destroy
Natee's entire criminal network.
I won't allow him
to hurt anyone ever again.
Sir.
There's nothing suspicious.
He's a newly rich rising tycoon,
owner of a solar energy business
from Dubai.
He just closed
a 40 million dollar deal in Malaysia.
Hey, he looks legit.
That's serious money.
But sir,
for VVIPs to enter
the exclusive clubhouse,
Mr. Tiangmon has to approve it first.
What makes him better than me?
Answer me.
He's just an old fart
who loves the sound of his own voice.
He should already be retired,
and let someone like me
be the boss's right-hand man.
Yes, sir.
Isn't the mountain scenery
around my resort appealing?
Why are you cooped up in here?
Shan bu zhuan, lu zhuan.
The mountain doesn't move,
but the path always turns.
Nature never stands still.
Only people cling and remain rigid.
You speak Chinese too.
Well, lately he's been obsessed
with Chinese dramas.
Chinese series are trending right now.
I guess I'll have to watch some too.
But the reason I came today was to ask you
whether you're still interested
in upgrading to a premium membership.
There's still time.
But you told me earlier
that there were no special services here.
Well, here's the thing.
For the privacy of my members,
I need to scan everyone's background
before approving access.
Hearing that, wow,
I'm very excited.
In that case, how much
is the membership? Just name the price.
If your goods are really
as good as you claim,
I'll go all in.
Jack.
An accident, you say?
LUNG CANCER
According to the foundation's report,
that's what they stated.
Have you checked the CCTV?
Yes.
All the cameras…
What? Were they broken?
Yes.
Jack was taken out
because he knew who did it.
We're not dealing with ordinary people.
This has reached the boss.
Handle this immediately.
THAI PM INVITED TO MEET XI JIN PING
Sarge?
Sarge, come here…
Why are you here?
Do you want to get caught?
Hey, I was worried about you.
If Tiangmon starts suspecting you,
how am I supposed to help?
I can survive on my own.
Survive in a way that made me
clean up after you twice already?
We're on the same team.
Isn't that your job?
Oh wow, now we're a team?
Back then, you pushed us aside,
said we were useless,
we weren't fit for this mission.
Don't do anything reckless.
What if the plan fails?
I don't have time to argue with you.
Even though we dealt with Jack,
if this reaches Phoenix so quickly,
we may be facing dangers
we didn't anticipate.
Yes, Boss.
I was just about to call you.
The agent you ordered me to handle
is dead.
For their network to spread this far,
with gunmen and assassins,
there must be an entire army behind it.
You mean
besides Jack,
there are other dangerous people too?
But if our teamwork is this solid,
they can spread their wings
and bring in an army, assassins,
or even John Wick all they want.
I’d knock them senseless.
Someone like you?
Someone like who?
If you want to talk about good teamwork,
then first prove you can take down
their human-trafficking network
properly, without any mess afterward.
It'll be proper for sure.
I'd stake my he…
I'd stake my heart on it.
My boss's calling.
What are you waiting for?
Don't ruin our plan.
There's an order to heighten security,
especially for Natee's auction tonight.
They might choose that place
as their next target.
Abort the mission…
What? Abort the mission?
- What?
- Abort the mission…
It can't be aborted…
Vitamin C helps strengthen your body.
Have a lot of these, okay, Mr. Dan?
You'll be discharged sooner.
Then I won't take it.
I want to stay here longer.
If I go home, I'll be all alone.
And I still haven't found my cat.
Don't cry.
Eat some oranges. I'll peel them for you.
- Uh.
- Oh?
- Come here. Let me take a look.
- It burns.
Let me see.
Dan, how are you doing?
Hey, whoa.
Sarge, how'd you get here?
Sarge?
Not Sarge.
Serge. His name is Serge.
Serge. Serge.
- Serge?
- Yes.
- Yes, Serge. I am…
- Serge.
- It's Serge. My full name is…
Sergio. I'm Dan's older brother.
- Yes.
- I just knew my bro got hit by a car,
- so I rushed over.
- Thank you.
- You're his brother?
- Yes.
But you said you live alone with a cat.
- Ah.
- Yeah.
Yeah, Dan lives alone with a cat.
I live alone with a dog.
Dan lives with a cat in Pha Mok.
I live alone with a dog in Bangkok.
- In Bangkok.
- Yes, in Bangkok.
Then I'll let the siblings
stay together for now.
- All right.
- Excuse me.
- Okay.
- Come again. We'll just talk a bit.
- Mm, okay.
She's pretty.
What the hell are you doing?
All set.
I transferred fake crypto
into their account system.
That's slick. How'd you do it?
I just created another dummy account.
Then I funneled fake crypto
into the system through a node.
The system shows the numbers rising
in real time, one million dollars.
- Won't they check?
- Yeah, they'll check.
Normally,
the system audits five layers back.
All I need right now is to make it
look real enough for Natee to bite.
By the time he realizes it's fake,
- our mission will already be done.
- Hey.
You're pretty damn good.
I'm the real deal.
This job's easy.
- You noobs.
- Easy my ass.
We're screwed.
Sorry, bro.
Secrets are out.
He met a woman and spilled everything.
Women are the reason we'll fail.
Why are you blaming women?
It was just me and Kla, right?
Can you stop trying to look cool?
One mistake from you means all our lives.
Sarge, but if we didn't get info and help
from Ms. Napa and Ms. Khim,
we wouldn't be here.
Do you know Ms. Duangnet
has ordered the mission aborted?
It can't be aborted.
My sister and the women who were captured
are waiting to be saved.
Mr. Kla, you promised us.
This is our last chance.
Sarge, I'm begging you.
If I wanted fame,
I wouldn't take this mission.
Miss,
tell us what crimes has Natee committed?
Hey, open the door.
Back off.
Hey, hey, don't.
No! Don't.
Come here.
Okay, roger that.
Man, I really want
something cold to drink.
Excuse me, do you have something like…
Something that hits the throat?
What do you mean? Hits the throat?
Like… Something that…
- What are you doing?
- You guys are next.
This is our first item.
Fresh internal organs, guaranteed.
Please begin bidding.
- Hey!
- Run!
I'm here!
So this is how you want to play it?
You're lucky.
You get to see my trick shot.
Meet Dab the Red Inferno!
Then, do you mind if I ask your name?
It's all right.
My name is…
Mook.
And then the car hit me, boom!
That's how I ended up like this.
It's… It's like…
- This is his head, right?
- Yes.
Here. Try hitting it,
and use this to help. See?
- Yeah.
- Use my own hand to push it down?
You know "In-car"?
The back seat's this wide,
real comfy.
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon