So the man in this photo is you, correct?
Yes, sir. My boss ordered me
to deliver money to Seksan.
Money for what?
Payment for helping conceal information
from Air Traffic Control
on the day Mr. Nathi and Mr. Chonlathan's
plane crashed in Surat Thani.
And who is your boss?
Mr. Jaruek Techametisakul,
owner of Heaven Plaza.
Then tell me everything from the beginning.
I'd been trying to buy that plot of land
from you long before they did.
I even offered her several times the price.
I just don't understand
why you sold it to Siamraphe instead.
Hello?
Hello? Hello?
Hey.
I know what happened.
But I won't let them take it that easily.
You'll have to help me.
[Notification]
[Schedule of Mr. Nathi and Mr. Chonlathan -
January 29, 2025]
[2:00 p.m., Phuket Airport.
Private flight from Phuket to Koh Phangan]
Thap, go ahead and start the meeting.
I'll join shortly.
Yes, Father.
I've already sent all the details.
There's nothing much.
Just make sure they use a model
without a black box.
Got it, thank you.
Handle the rest.
Yes, sir.
- Okay.
- Excuse me.
Please, go ahead.
Hey, how's the weather in Phuket?
Full flight?
Good, good. Stick to the plan.
All according to plan.
Hey.
- Hey.
- Nop!
Get an ambulance!
Nop!
Hey.
Hang in there.
- Undo his buttons!
- Okay, okay. Buttons undone.
Nop, breathe slowly. Calm down, Nop.
- Captain?
- Captain, are you okay?
Captain, are you okay?
I don't feel well. I can't breathe...
- Captain?
Captain! Captain, wake up!
- Hey, Captain!
- Captain!
- Wake up!
- Wake up! Captain!
- Captain!
Captain!
Cyanide?
So, was Seksan's death connected to you?
Yes.
I found out he was deep in debt.
So Mr. Jaruek told me to bribe him,
so he'd tell everyone that he hadn't
contacted the pilot on the day of the crash.
After everything went as planned,
I went back to silence him.
Seksan, wake up!
Sek!
Is Seksan okay?
I don't know, sir. He was fine one minute,
then suddenly collapsed.
No pulse.
After you poisoned Seksan,
you placed a suicide note and a bottle
of pills in his desk drawer, didn't you?
Yes, sir.
And do you know who gave Khun Jaruek
the flight information
and other insider data from Siamraphe?
Ms. Seenam.
Thaleh.
Thaleh!
Wait. Where are you going?
I'm going after Aunt Nam.
She killed Dad and Chon!
Wait for Uncle Non first.
You're the only heir Siamraphe has left now!
- Non!
- Uncle Non!
Can we arrest Seenam and Jaruek today?
Not yet.
We have to gather more evidence first.
Thaleh, wait!
Stop!
[Mom]
[Juat]
Hello, Mom called you, didn't she?
Yes.
And you didn't pick up because
you were afraid she'd stop you, right?
They killed Dad and Chon.
Revenge, huh?
It's powerful.
It makes you forget your mother, your family,
everything you've been through.
If you go for revenge, you won't hurt them.
You'll hurt your mother.
She only has you left, Thaleh.
You're all she has to hold on to.
Don't let your anger hurt her again.
Thank you, for reminding me.
I really did forget myself.
Remember this, Thaleh.
Be mindful,
like a gatekeeper guarding your heart.
No matter what comes your way,
don't let it slip easily inside.
Don't let emotions carry your mind away.
And don't let what touches your heart
take control, right?
I remember your teachings.
Thank you again.
[Mom]
Hello, Mom.
I'm sorry.
Don't act impulsively, son.
Non told me they can't arrest anyone yet
because the evidence
only points to Chai as Seksan's killer.
It doesn't directly connect
to Jaruek or Seenam.
We need more solid proof.
If we go after them now,
or if they sense something,
they might escape prosecution.
I understand, Mom.
I'll head back right away.
Okay.
[Mahasamut]
What's up, Mut?
Why did you go to Aunt Yai's house?
Aunt Yai still hasn't woken up,
so we went to get a sacred amulet for her.
An amulet?
Is there anything else
you're suspicious about, Seenam?
We're going to visit Aunt Yai now.
Ms. Yai.
Is her condition getting worse?
Yes, my mother's been worried sick.
Yesterday, when I went to Aunt Yai's house
for the amulet,
I ran into Aunt Nam.
So I told her about Aunt Yai's condition.
Then why are you all standing here?
Is she alright?
- Are you cursing my sister now?
- Lek, calm down!
We don't know yet. The doctor's checking.
Please, come in.
Doctor, how's her condition?
Her lung cancer
has weakened her immune system.
Since she's been bedridden for so long,
there's a high risk of a lung infection,
which could cause sudden heart failure.
You should prepare yourselves.
Yai.
Please don't leave us.
You have to wake up.
Please, stay with us.
I'd like to ask everyone
to keep this matter confidential for now.
Siamraphe's situation is already unstable.
If word gets out,
it'll only make things worse.
Yes.
I have good news.
Ms. Yai is in a coma.
Near death.
And I have good news too.
My source says,
the court is about to
lift the temporary injunction.
You can prepare to sell Siamraphe.
What are you doing, Father?
Dernthap.
Even though Siamraphe is ours,
I want you to break up with Seenam.
But she's the mother of my child.
Seenam isn't fit
to be anyone's wife or mother.
I don't want a daughter-in-law I can't trust.
Think about it.
If she could betray her own family,
what makes you think
she wouldn't betray ours?
Fine.
If you don't approve of her,
after we get married, I'll move with Seenam
and our child to Germany with Mom.
No. You must stay here in Thailand.
I need your help.
I understand you.
I really understand.
I really do. You love your child.
Just like I love you.
Okay, here's what you'll do.
Once Seenam gives birth,
you'll take the child and raise it yourself.
Then find a new wife.
There are plenty of women
who are beautiful, smart,
and capable, just like her.
Build a proper family.
- Is it confirmed?
- Lawyer Wit checked with the court.
The temporary injunction
was officially lifted this morning.
And suddenly, news broke that
Ms. Nam has already signed the deal
to sell Siamraphe.
What?
Where is Aunt Nam now?
She's at the 58th Anniversary event,
in the conference hall.
Thaleh!
Hey...
You really sold Siamraphe, didn't you?
You make it sound so dramatic, Thaleh.
All we did was open the door
for a partner company to join our management.
So that our business can grow further.
Who did you sell it to?
You'll find out soon enough.
At the 58th Anniversary celebration.
Anything else?
I'd like to continue the meeting.
Thaleh!
Let her go.
Let go!
Thaleh!
Thaleh.
I know you're angry, son.
I want to deal with Seenam too.
But not today.
But she's already sold Siamraphe, Mom.
Can we really get it back?
We will. I believe we can.
But you have to be patient.
Once we have all the evidence,
we'll reclaim Siamraphe.
Thaleh, what are you planning to do?
I can't just stand by
and let her take Siamraphe.
The new owner of Siamraphe is your father,
isn't it?
I think so.
But I'll tell you this.
I don't agree with his methods.
Then that means you still want to play fair.
On Siamraphe's 58th Anniversary,
I'll help you expose Nam and my father.
You'd really send your own father
and your lover to prison?
I have to.
Why?
You don't need to know that.
Just know that I'll help you.
But I have one condition.
Don't hurt Nam.
You're still defending her?
That criminal you're mentioning...
She's my wife...
And I'll protect her, no matter what.
Fine. Then everything will go by the law.
The 58th Anniversary celebration
will be held at Siamraphe Hall.
There'll be food stalls
surrounding the venue.
Aunt Nam will probably be sitting in front,
next to the new owner.
How do you know the son of Jaruek
would actually turn on his father?
I don't know how, but I believe he will.
Still, we can't rely only on him.
We need to prepare everything we have.
Sin, don't forget to prepare your men too.
Don't worry.
Force is my specialty.
I believe that If we work together,
we'll take Nam down for sure.
Pour me a glass.
58 years.
You think Grandpa would be angry at us?
Then he should've started yelling
when I went to jail.
Do you think
this will all end with our generation,
like how Jaruek always said about Aunt Yai?
You scared?
Don't mess with me.
I'm not giving up.
By the end of this,
both of them will rot in jail.
What about your case?
You think I'll run away again?
Don't tease me.
I'll fight to the end.
But if I do end up in prison,
I'm leaving Siamraphe in your hands for now.
You're giving me Siamraphe?
I said leaving it in your care.
Then come back soon.
You miss me, don't you?
I'm exhausted.
[Siamraphe]
And now I'm here live at the
58th Anniversary celebration of Siamraphe.
The atmosphere is filled with
high-profile guests from every industry,
including celebrities, socialites, artists,
and top influencers from across Thailand,
all gathered here tonight
to witness a historic new chapter
for Siamraphe.
Most importantly,
everyone is waiting for the answer.
Has Siamraphe truly changed hands?
Hurry up!
Mr. Jaruek! Mr. Jaruek!
Your presence here at Siamraphe's event,
is it related to the rumor
that the company has changed ownership?
Let's just say there'll be a surprise
for everyone tonight.
Alright, thank you!
Hello, Mr. Jaruek.
Well, long time no see.
Dad, I'm going to the restroom.
I'll be right back.
Sure.
Be careful, Thaleh.
Okay.
[Control Room]
I'm already here.
I'm on my way.
Let go.
Didn't you say you were
going to the restroom?
What are you planning to do?
Search him.
Let go!
This is Mr. Li.
This is Ms. Seenam Raphethada,
the new CEO of Siamraphe.
You're betraying your father?
Huh?
Let me go.
I don't want my child to grow up
in the kind of world you and Nam have built.
So I was wrong to let you grow up
with your mother then, huh?
That's why you've never thought like me.
Not once!
Why?
Don't you see? Everything I've done will
one day be yours. Yours and your child's!
I don't want it if it comes this way, Dad.
What do you want me to tell my child?
That we stole it?
It's not stealing.
It's business. Everyone plays this game.
But I won't.
Then fine, just stay out of it.
After this is over,
I'll send you back to Germany
to live with your mother.
Fine.
But I'm taking Nam and my child with me.
Nam is my lawful wife.
We've already registered our marriage.
Idiot!
She told you to sign,
and you ran off to do it, huh?
You don't realize she's using you?
I do, Dad.
I'm going to have her arrested.
And I'll wait for her until she's released.
Then we'll be together again.
[Thaleh]
Don't answer. Hold him down!
Hey!
Dad!
Let me go!
Pack everything up.
Lock Dernthap in this room
until the event's over.
Dad! Let me go! Let me out!
Dad!
What are you doing?
Dad! Dad!
Why are you locking me up?
Let me out!
[58th Anniversary]
Is everything ready, Thaleh?
Mr. Dernthap is missing.
He's not answering his phone.
You think he's changed his mind?
I don't think so.
But Mr. Jaruek is missing too.
I'll be right back, Mom.
Hey.
Looking for my son?
What did you do to him?
I should be the one asking you that.
What did you do to make him betray me?
You should be proud
your son stands for what's right.
What kind of father
wants his child to turn evil?
And what business is it of yours?
Let me tell you something.
Good people don't survive in this world.
That's not true.
No?
Look at your father and your brother.
Are they still alive?
Let's see if you can last.
Here's a tip.
You'll be next.
Hey, this route didn't work.
I'll handle it myself.
Drive straight into the event.
Where's Thap?
Something urgent came up,
so he went back to the office first.
Welcome, everyone,
to the 58th Anniversary Celebration
of Siamraphe.
For more than five decades,
we've stood strong.
Siamraphe isn't just a shopping mall,
but a piece of history,
a place filled with people's memories.
Now, please welcome the acting Chairwoman,
Ms. Seenam Raphethada.
Thank you, everyone, for being here today.
Thank you for loving Siamraphe.
I still remember
the first day I stepped in here.
This place...
has built lives,
brought smiles, and created memories.
We've been through so much together.
Economic crises, global changes...
and yet, we've survived.
Today marks a new chapter
in Siamraphe's history.
We won't stay stagnant.
And for the mall to have a better future,
I must do what no one else
has dared to do before.
I hereby transfer management rights,
opening the way for a new investor
to lead Siamraphe
into its next legendary era.
Please welcome the new Chairman of Siamraphe,
Mr. Jaruek Techametheesakul.
Please, come on stage.
[Raphe Heaven Plaza]
From the bottom of my heart,
I never imagined
that one day, the man once standing outside
looking into Siamraphe
would now stand here as its full owner.
Alright, I'll try not to talk about the past.
It wouldn't be polite to those
who've been here a long time
and who will soon be leaving.
But I promise you this.
Under my leadership,
Siamraphe will not be the same.
It will be better.
If you want to sell Siamraphe,
the first thing you need is a buyer,
and a price that satisfies everyone.
I'll take care of that.
But you need to make sure
the board votes to approve the sale.
Of course. It'll pass.
I have my people on the board.
And I'll handle the legal
and financial advisors.
Once the contract is ready,
we'll sign immediately.
[Control Room]
- You can't go in here.
- Get out of my way!
Where did he go?
The sale only becomes official once the money
and ownership are legally transferred.
We must sell Siamraphe before Ms. Yai
wakes up and tells everyone the truth.
- Ms. Yai.
Nice speech.
But it's too late, because I'm back.
What the...
Get the reporters out!
Take them out!
I think everyone here recognizes that voice.
These two are the ones
behind all the chaos at Siamraphe.
And Seenam is the one
who pushed me down the stairs!
You called the police on me?
I should've had you locked up
a long time ago.
After everything I've done,
I'm not going to prison!
- Let go!
- Give that to me!
No. Let go!
Give it!
Give me those documents!
They stole the evidence
I was going to use against them
and forged documents
to appoint themselves CEO.
Therefore, any transaction Seenam made as CEO
is legally void.
Is that true, Mr. Jaruek?
Ms. Seenam, why did you do this?
- How long have you two been planning this?
- Hey, no filming!
Please answer! Please!
Where are you rushing off to?
The event isn't over yet.
When did Ms. Yai wake up?
Surprised?
I turned myself in, just like Aunt Yai asked.
I won't run anymore.
I'll make sure the people
who destroyed our family
are removed from Siamraphe.
Aunt Yai.
- Aunt Yai.
- Yai.
I'll get the doctor!
Overall, Khun Yai's condition
has improved significantly.
Her body is responding well.
Blood pressure and breathing
are nearly back to normal.
It's a very good sign.
How long until she can speak again?
If recovery continues this fast,
she should be able to talk
in two or three days.
Thank you.
Do you need anything?
What was that?
Wait, Aunt Yai.
Alright, type it out for me.
[Wooden flash drive in Jenga at home]
What is it, Mut?
I know where Aunt Yai
hid the evidence about Mr. Pat.
She told you?
Yeah. It's in a wooden flash drive
hidden inside a Jenga set at her house.
Aunt Nam probably hasn't reached it yet,
so I'll go first.
Got it.
Aunt Yai has several Jenga sets.
We'll need to split up and look.
You two search her bedroom.
I'll check the office.
Nothing in her room.
Nothing in the office either.
Where does she usually play Jenga?
Hurry.
Found it!
Tawan, get ready.
Why did you go to Ms. Yai's house?
She still hasn't woken up,
so we went to get a sacred amulet for her.
An amulet?
Anything else you're curious about, Aunt Nam?
We are heading to see Aunt Yai now.
Ms. Yai.
Is she getting worse?
Yes. Mom's really worried.
Good thing you told me
to bring the amulet.
I was afraid we'd run into
Aunt Nam like this.
A mistake this small...
how could you miss it? So stupid.
You're even dumber for trusting me.