[The Blade of Romance]
[Episode 8]
Song Weiwei.
You little girl.
Why do you always
point that dagger at me?
Always?
You should call me Fifth Brother.
It's so cold today.
Why are you out here alone
in this chilly wind?
Warm your hands with this.
It’s none of your business.
Haven't you
remembered anything yet?
Do you think Wen Zhiyuan
is trustworthy?
What do you mean?
Don't you think there might be
some secrets behind your memory loss?
Wen Zhiyuan is deceiving you.
I know.
No matter what I say now,
you won’t believe me.
However,
I can find someone
to help you recover your memory.
Then
you'll know whether
I've been trying to drive a wedge
between you and your brother.
Fifth Brother,
let's go check over there.
They won’t get away.
They must be nearby.
Search everywhere!
We'll be discovered.
Can you do martial arts?
A gentleman uses words, not fists.
Fighting is too vulgar.
They're after me.
I’ll lead them away.
You go back and get help.
I am your Fifth Brother after all.
How could I let you
lend the enemy away
in this situation?
It will harm
my heroic image.
You're a grown man.
So indecisive.
I'll leave cross marks.
At least if one of us gets away,
it's a win.
The best plan is to run away.
At least if one of us gets away,
it's a win.
My name is Zhifeng,
from the Zhifeng Grass.
I'm from the Chen State.
Zhifeng...
Could it be her?
Who are you?
We're following orders.
If Your Highness has complaints,
just tell the King of Hell.
Are you alright?
Brother.
Are you hurt?
You're injured.
I'm fine.
Your Highness.
Something's happened to Song Weiwei.
We need to take people to rescue her.
Come with me quickly.
I know, Your Highness.
Wen Zhiyuan has already
taken people there.
Please don't worry.
When Song Weiwei was little,
did she ever go to the Xirui Grassland?
Was she ever kidnapped by bandits?
How do you know this, Your Highness?
When Weiwei was young,
she was indeed kidnapped by bandits
on the Xirui Grassland.
But regarding a young lady's reputation,
this matter has never been
disclosed to outsiders.
It really is her.
It's her.
Your Highness.
Chu Qing,
have our people search for her too.
Make sure she’s safe.
Yes.
Life is unpredictable.
If I had known you were Zhifeng,
I would never
have drawn you into this situation.
Don't go outside alone
just to avoid me.
It's not safe.
I understand, Brother.
I'm injured.
It’s difficult to dress.
I've never actually
seen you as my sister.
You're not from the Da Liang royal family.
What do you mean?
You're from Chen State.
We met on the battlefield.
I had no choice
but to bring you back with me.
Actually,
when the Liang State
and the Chen State were at war,
Wen Rou was already dead.
I kept you here using her identity.
So we're not siblings?
No.
I've always had feelings for you.
I told you to stop avoiding me.
I know the timing isn't right,
but I can't
hold back anymore.
I want you to know how I feel.
[Brother.]
[No.]
[He's not my brother.]
[He said]
[he has feelings for me.]
Your Highness.
How's it going? Did you find her?
Yes, we found her.
She's injured,
but it's not serious.
Should I
go see her again,
tell her the truth,
and find a way to recover her memory?
What if she doesn't believe you?
What if
she tells Wen Zhiyuan everything
you said to her?
I really don't feel at ease
keeping her
by Wen Zhiyuan's side any longer.
Wen Zhiyuan
trusts her completely now.
Besides, we don't know
if Wen Zhiyuan
has figured out her identity.
What if you go to see her,
and she exposes herself?