[The Blade of Romance]
[Episode 23]
My name is Zhifeng,
from the Zhifeng Grass.
I'm from Chen State.
What about you?
I'm the cousin of the Liang State's envoy.
I’m Bai Cheng.
And you?
I'm from Xirui.
Lan.
They're over there!
Chase them!
Run!
Don't let them catch you!
Stop!
Don't look back!
Stop right there!
They're catching up!
Let's fight them!
I'll protect you.
No,
if we continue like this,
none of us will escape.
How about
we split up?
I'll draw them away.
You two go in different directions.
Whoever gets help first,
come back to save the other.
No!
The best strategy is to run.
If one gets away, that’s a win.
Is that really how the 36 tactics work?
That's not the point.
Then I'll go back for help.
Good.
Let's go.
Let’s see where you’re running to.
What happened to him?
He was caught while trying to escape.
Tell us.
Tell us, or I’ll kill him.
I know where the thing you want is.
I'll take you there.
Zhifeng.
Don't go!
Let's go.
Let her go!
Zhifeng!
You're here.
I haven't congratulated you
for getting what you wanted.
Now that you're
the crown prince of Liang State.
Wait until I take the throne,
and then you can congratulate me.
Because of Wen Zhiyuan,
Liang's emperor is seriously ill.
The internal turmoil is subsiding,
and your ascension
is just a matter of time.
What about you?
What are your plans for the future?
I never thought
I would have a chance to plan my future.
Now, I have nothing.
No parents.
No home.
Where should I go?
Miss Song,
this is a letter from the master.
I'm leaving.
[For the personal attention of Zhifeng]
Zhifeng.
I am Lan from the grassland.
My real name is
Li Shiyan.
I was the crown prince of Xirui.
The iron cavalry of Liang's emperor
destroyed everything I had.
Xirui fell.
And I
also lost
my identity as Li Shiyan.
For revenge,
I took Wen Zhiyuan's identity
and infiltrated
the Southern Liang Imperial Palace.
The witch doctor said,
from today on,
this look belongs to you.
From now on,
you are the third prince of Liang State,
Wen Zhiyuan.
And you're no longer the prince of Xirui,
Li Shiyan.
I originally wanted to
fight for the throne
so there would be
no more war in this world.
There would be no more people like me
whose country and family were destroyed.
But things didn't go as planned.
I was caught up in it all.
And I sank deeper and deeper,
gradually losing control.
I became a tool
to satisfy Liang's emperor's ambitions.
I let iron cavalry crush your homeland.
I had no choice.
If I hadn’t obeyed Liang's emperor,
I wouldn’t be in this position today.
I met you when we were young.
I gave you a dagger.
This is...
Zhifeng Grass.
Here you go.
You need to hold it flat.
I missed.
It wasn't me.
You little brat,
how dare you hit me.
Can't catch me.
Cheng,
help me catch him.
Okay.
Now you can't escape.
You dared to tug on my ear.
Can't catch me!
If only these days
could continue.
Unfortunately,
I’m about to go home with my father.
I'll be leaving soon too,
and I don't know
when we'll meet again.
There are times
when we gather and separate.
I'll be waiting for you all in Xirui.
You guys remember to come find me.
Sure.
Next time we meet,
I’ll surely be
a female general by then.
Then I want to be
a great scholar, writing books.
What about you?
I want to become
someone who can protect everyone,
allowing people
on the land of Xirui
to have enough food and clothing,
living in peace and prosperity.
Then may we all
become
the people we want to be.
From now on.
I am the mighty
general.
Don't worry,
I've got your backs.
Good.
After our farewell on the grassland,
I thought we'd be separated forever.
But unexpectedly,
by some twist of fate,
you came to my side.
The joy of finding something lost again
is beyond words.
Fate is cruel.
To you,
I am your father’s murderer.
I have no excuse.
And I know that between us,
it’s a deadlock.
No solution.
But after you lost your memory,
I indulged in those moments of happiness.
I dared not ask for your forgiveness
for my selfishness
and despicable behavior.
But having these
fleeting moments with you,
I have no regrets.
I've done too many wrong things,
and there's no turning back now.
But even if everyone condemns me,
I still have no regrets.
In the end,
what I long for most
is to return to that grassland
and back to those carefree days
we once had.
If possible,
you must go see it for me.
To see this peaceful world
and the country in tranquility.
If the wind blows in the future,
it will be me coming to see you.
♪ The faint moonlight casts a cold glow
from afar ♪
♪ Through walls of longing,
thoughts freeze into scars ♪
♪ All the pain in this world is but
love and hate that linger on ♪
♪ Drunken, I swallow sorrow whole,
with dreams as my only solace ♪
♪ Fate's cruel hand, no soul can defy ♪
♪ I can only blame this heart
for the wounds that cut so deep ♪
♪ If there's no cure for this pain I own ♪
♪ I'd rather drift alone, unknown,
in time's cold flow ♪