Taejin Kim
I have to clean it up.
You want to clean it up...
Let's kill him
From the moment that bastard touched my water
I'm already out
But I have the answer
There is no solution
To kill directly
Are you having trouble managing the remaining people?
Park Cheol-min, please lend me a hand.
That way the kids won't get mixed up.
where?
Well, I have something to tell you, so tell me to come up at 9 o'clock.
hey
Park Cheol-min tells me to come up.
yes!
Well then, as for Taejin Kim...
I'll go and tell you
Still, I'm ignoring the guy I used to eat with.
You don’t even blink?
hey
I made it all up so just say you understand.
Ah, why are you like this?
I also have a style that adults find very attractive.
Take care of yourself
what's the matter?
Chairman Park is here
At 9 o'clock in room 902
why?
You want to make up and have a drink?
Why would I tell you that?
We met by chance, why?
What happened to you and Chairman Park?
just
okay
don't worry too much
Did I tell you?
They say they will let me eat everything here.
under...
What are you doing here?
You came alone?
Are you asking me to come alone?
Ah, I don't have that much doubt
What should I do?
from now on
Chairman?
here
What is this?
This is the chairman?
Close the door when you leave
thank you
Still, I'm the only one, right?
Chairman's heart
Ah, then
Then, hmm
When do you do that work?
I can write it, can I?
one...
I told you to come around 9 o'clock
Then I killed him on the street corner.
Write it then what
Can Taejin Kim just catch one person?
I told you to come alone
Well, since I'm an obedient kid, I'll come alone.
Ha, by the time it comes out
just kill it like that
yes!
Oh, by the way, Chairman.
Well, may I ask why you’re suddenly like that?
그 새끼가 선을 넘었어
Well, hmm
Well, I think there's some misunderstanding.
yes, well
You think that's what you did
Didn't someone, Park, Park Cheol, and Park Cheol Min do it?
And aren't you blaming me like this now?
Tae Jin Ah
That's not important now
I believe you did it
What's more important is that I've already decided to kill you.
I can't turn it back now
What am I like, tsk
The Chairman brought me in, gave me medicine, and saved me.
I thought you cared so much
Taejin probably knows that.
however
I brought it here because I thought it might be useful.
Ah, he kept making a fuss so I just left him to die.
Lee Mi-seon saved me.
So the medicine I gave you back then was
Just whatever, cheap vitamins
I'm going to save a bastard like that, that, that, mama's boy
Using antibiotics doesn't make sense.
It doesn't fit too well
Even if it’s like this?
What should I do?
You kill me first.
Park Sang-yong
If I know you're alive after today
You're done anyway
The only chance is today
Chairman Park is more evil than you know.
I'll do it
I'm going to kill you
I will also decide the time
What about Park Cheol-min?
don't worry about that
아, 이 개새끼 도망친 거야, 뭐야, 씨
kid!
No, I haven't figured out what happened for an hour.
I already solved it
I made a deal
Every time you say you're going to the 8th floor
Actually, I'm going to meet Park Sang-yong.
I don't know if your friends know?
Hey, Geunseok
근석이 개새끼
You have a severe headache because of your hearing loss.
You probably got the same offer as me for headache medication.
If you help me
All the headache medicine that comes in from now on is yours.
And now to Park Cheol-min’s seat.
I told you to come alone
Well, since I'm an obedient kid, I'll come alone.
Ha, by the time it comes out
just kill it like that
yes!
and
No, fuck, how could you do this to us, huh?
What should I do?
we'll do whatever you say
Ah, but we can run a bit on our own.
Park Sang-yong
There was always something being said to me
Stop acting like a brat
Become an adult
But we
The world abandoned me before I even grew up.
Now no one is spoon feeding me
survive on our own
You have to become an adult yourself
Now after tonight
There will be no one here more mature than us.
It's going to be a little noisy outside.
Don't go outside though
Didn’t Park Sang-yong notice?
Park Sang-yong is preparing dinner.
Without even dreaming
Who do you think you invited?
Same as my sister
dinner invitation
Look at this
It's true that Park Sang-yong also needs to die.
If things continue like this, everything could go wrong
What are you talking about?
It seems like the person who killed Sejeong was someone else.
Are you advertising that you know how to make poison?
There were red spots on Han Se-jeong's body.
Didn’t she take her medicine too?
It's like poisoning
There was a red spot
They say it's a poison that will do that if you eat it
Mi-seon Lee and her sister Tae-jin Kim are trying to take it out together.
He said he worked in a research lab.
You probably did it to get Park Sang-yong’s attention, right?
Because for that to happen, my sister has to disappear.
No evidence, need to check
After today, when you enter the 9th floor of Taejin Kim,
Doesn’t this all belong to her?
I'll check it later tonight
So you don't go out
Got it, go see it
Ah, headache medicine, headache medicine
yes
This bastard is asking you to take care of him.
Did Choi Hee-ro say it was room 109?
Yes, I think so.
Well, dinner is ready.
Will Lee Mi-seon call me?
I'll eat there tomorrow
Today I will meet someone different.
I have something to check.
What are you looking for here?
I want to occupy this place like you
Do you know that Miseon was trying to go to the 9th floor?
I only see what I want to see
Without even knowing why we are here
sorry
I saw that
Park Sang-yong...
개새끼가, 씨
okay
Everyone has to work to live here.
our kids
I let it in through the collapsed building.
Yeah, it's okay, it's okay
Daddy will be here
Oh, you're good, yeah
From then on
Park Sang-yong stayed away from us.
Sejeong was trying to help us.
So Sejeong used it?
like everyone
I don't just take advantage of others.
Sejeong wanted to kill me more than anyone else.
that day
thank you
For helping me
something is wrong
Mi-seon Lee
Where is Lee Mi-seon?
are you okay?
Choi Hee-ro
Why are you here?
what's the matter?
no
Park Sang-yong on the first floor
They said they kidnapped the girl.
Sehee