If it doesn't work out,
have someone go to Hong Ming's place
to see if there are any clues about Xie Yuxuan.
Remember,
don't tell anyone,
including Zhiqiu.
Why is he looking for me
and trying to break into my house?
Okay.
As soon as possible.
Hello?
- Hello?
- Xiaoxiao?
I'm here.
Xiangyang
seems to suspect us now.
He asked Shi Xiaodi to send someone to break into my house.
What should we do?
Now you know what kind of person he is, right?
I...
So you have no way out.
Don't be fooled by his false tenderness.
But...
His tenderness is only for Ye Zhiqiu.
And who are you?
You are Xie Yuxuan.
The one who killed the person he loved most.
No.
Xiaodi.
I like you.
Xueli.
I know you like Ye Zhiqiu.
Can't we just be good friends?
Of course.
Even though we'll be graduating soon,
we'll still be in the same city.
Whenever you think of me,
just look back,
I'll always be there.
Why did Shelly start using drugs?
You should really ask yourself that.
She stayed in Binjiang
and suffered so much,
changed jobs countless times,
and was even raped when she worked in sales.
She stayed in Binjiang
just to be closer to you.
Ask yourself:
did you deserve her?
This is insane.
You're making my life difficult
and cost me a million yuan.
I'll make you pay back a hundred times more.
I'm sorry.
Last night...
Don't say anything.
Last night was fine.
You don't need to feel burdened.
[Xiaoxiao answers the phone]
Hello, Xuanxuan.
What's wrong?
Xiaoxiao,
Shelly...
she knows everything.
I told you long ago she couldn't stay.
You insisted on being soft-hearted.
We've delayed for so long,
wasting all this time for nothing.
I thought since we were classmates,
she might consider our old friendship
and I wanted to give her a chance.
A chance to send us to our graves, you mean?
This matter,
don't get involved anymore.
I'll handle it.
Xiaoxiao.
What?
You like it here now?
Raising money takes time.
It's always the same line.
I'll say it again.
My patience is limited.
I really can't come up with that much money.
That's your problem.
Don't push me.
Isn't it just about money?
I have some dollars
I'll give them to you tomorrow.
For the rest,
I'll find a way to raise it.
You said tomorrow.
Dollars.
How much?
100,000.
How will you deliver it?
Wait for my call.
I'll tell you
where to meet.
I'll say this one last time.
My patience is truly limited.
Do you want to fight to the death with me?
You're not up to it.
Eat up.
Tomorrow,
I'll buy you some dishes and chopsticks,
and get some pots and pans.
You should learn how to cook properly.
A home should feel like a home.
You understand?
Home...
I've almost forgotten what it feels like.
Xueli.
I'm sorry.
Back then, I...
Don't bring up the past.
It was my own choice.
It has nothing to do with you.
I think
this place you're living in is too small.
I can find you a better place,
a big villa.
How about that?
No need.
A villa?
I'm leaving soon.
Where are you going?
Leaving Binjiang.
Why?
Is it Ye Zhiqiu's idea
or my senior's?
Do you think
the current Ye Zhiqiu is the same as before?
Zhiqiu?
She looks exactly the same as before.
But...
there might be something different,
not the same feeling as before.
Though I haven't seen her for so many years,
maybe my memory is playing tricks on me.
Haven't you considered
that she's an impostor?
Someone who had plastic surgery
to look like Ye Zhiqiu?
I think
Ye Zhiqiu's agent mentioned this before.
But
how could that be possible?
Zhou Ruiqiu, who kept saying she was fake, is dead.
Do you think that's just a coincidence?
So when you recently went to see my senior,
it was about this?
Did he believe what you said?
He only believes that fake Ye Zhiqiu.
Fake Ye Zhiqiu?
Fake Ye Zhiqiu...
What do you mean?
Do you have any evidence?
I want to see it.
Some things
are better left unknown.
Zhou Ruiqiu is dead,
and I'm about to leave too.
Some secrets should just stay buried.
Where's the money?
Why are you in such a hurry?
It'll be here soon.
Are you planning a surprise for me?
What surprise?
How much longer do we have to wait?
Soon.
Have a drink.
No, thanks.
What are you afraid of?
Afraid of ending up like Zhou Ruiqiu
who died after having a drink?
You're being way too cautious.
Miss Ye.
Just put it here.
Actually,
we're quite similar.
I'm nothing like you.
You were born with a silver spoon in your mouth.
I've had to do everything on my own.
Now you know who I am.
I know.
We were roommates for four years after all.
You've finally gotten what you wanted,
marrying the man you wanted to marry.
But I heard
you got divorced recently.
It's really eye-opening.
That Hong Ming who used to be at my family's beck and call
for a living
has now become your right-hand man, Xiangyang,
wagging his tail for your favor.
And then there's Xie Yuxuan.
One of my few friends
now won't answer my calls or reply to my messages
and avoids me whenever we meet.
Xiangyang,
tell me,
is there anyone in this world you can't buy off?
You're blaming all of this on me.
Buy off Hong Ming?
What means do I have to buy him off?
In this house,
I'm walking on eggshells just to keep my place.
Honestly,
Xiangyang,
take a good look at where you are now.
Think back to
what you were like when you first stepped into our family.
Everything you have
came from my family.
But how did you repay us?
Conspiring with outsiders,
leaking company secrets,
secretly diverting project resources.
Xiangyang,
I was truly blind.
My father was right.
You are talented,
a calculating genius
who betrays those who helped you.
I'm a genius?
Why is it that whenever something goes wrong with the company,
all fingers point directly at me?
How many hidden problems did your family have before?
Why is it that as soon as we got married,
all these so-called mistakes
seemed perfectly arranged,
just waiting for me to sign and take the blame?
Enough. I don't want to hear your excuses.
My father was right.
You've achieved what you wanted,
stepping on my family
to reach the top.
Xiangyang,
we're finished.
The two of us
are exactly the same.
We both want happiness,
but we've lost ourselves
and become what we hate most.
What did you put in it?
It's similar to ecstasy.
Ye Zhiqiu used to smoke it too.
Forget it.
I'll keep it.
It's not for you.
For these cigarettes,
I need to add more.
How much?
Put all of these in.
This dosage could kill someone.
I only smoke one per day.
Easy to carry around.
Let me take you home.
I feel terrible.
I think
I overdosed.