Zhiqiu,
let's have a meal together.
With Shen Yixiao.
Your childhood friend.
Oh, her?
But I've been so busy with work lately.
I have so many unfinished tasks.
Maybe another day?
So what do you think
I should reply to her?
Just say I'm not feeling well
and I'm recovering these days.
Then we'll talk when you have time.
Shen Yixiao?
No.
Shen Yixiao? Sun Yixiao?
Sun Yixiao.
She's not Ye Zhiqiu.
Where did Zhiqiu go?
Xiaoxiao.
Xiaoxiao, I think I've been found out.
That Rachel deliberately gave me the wrong name
to trick me.
She really suspects something.
It seems
we need to figure something out.
What should I do?
Is there any solution at all?
What's wrong? You look terrible.
I...
Do I?
Maybe I haven't been sleeping well lately.
Your eyebrows are all furrowed.
Rachel keeps bothering me lately.
I really don't want to see her.
Don't worry.
About Rachel,
I'll help you deal with it.
Pretending to be nice,
that's his usual trick.
You seem quite troubled lately.
Is it because of Hong Ming?
Don't rush.
He won't tell you the truth yet.
Hong Ming was once my best friend.
Alright, let's not talk about this anymore.
Why don't you get some rest?
Xuanxuan.
I'm going to Korea for a few days
to handle the hospital records.
Be extra careful these days.
If anything happens,
call me.
Go to sleep.
Oh my God.
I'm actually responding to him.
What have I become?
Do you want to know the truth?
Knowing the truth comes with a price,
a heavy price.
Okay, see you tomorrow.
Zhiqiu.
Xiangyang.
Why aren't you asleep?
Can't you sleep?
I just returned a call.
I was afraid of disturbing you.
Get some rest early.
You go ahead first.
There's someone I know over there.
I need to talk to her.
Coffee.
Xiangyang.
Are you really confused or just pretending to be?
Even though we don't work together,
we're still good friends.
You can speak your mind.
The current Ye Zhiqiu
is an impostor.
First she's on vacation,
then she's abroad,
disappears for so long,
comes back and wants to retire,
and her stories don't add up.
All of this
is definitely not just a coincidence.
You came to see me just to say this?
Nothing else?
Can't you really see it?
Rachel,
I think you're the one with issues.
The current Ye Zhiqiu
even gets her childhood friend's name wrong.
Has someone brainwashed you?
And you say I'm crazy?
You're even helping her kick me out.
Shouldn't you be concerned about
where the real Ye Zhiqiu has gone?
Enough.
Rachel.
Ever since you installed surveillance in Zhiqiu's home,
you've been acting abnormally.
Don't you realize that?
I didn't install any surveillance.
Why so loud?
What's wrong?
Zhiqiu isn't your cash cow
or your personal property.
After ten years together, let's part on good terms.
Stop harassing Zhiqiu.
Xiangyang.
The real Zhiqiu is in danger right now.
You won't even investigate
and just tell me to walk away?
Are you too stupid to see it,
or do you know what's really going on?
Xiangyang.
You don't care about Zhiqiu at all.
Rachel,
you should see a doctor.
Don't put on an act with me.
Zhiqiu is in danger right now.
You won't go?
Fine.
I'll go.
I never expected this.
I just went to Korea for surgery.
She's acting like she's gone crazy.
Zhiqiu's return this time
seems really different.
I never expected
you would sing so well today.
What?
Coming to blame me on behalf of your master?
No.
I just want to have a quick chat with you.
What could we possibly have to talk about?
Don't make us seem like enemies.
I know something
about your condition.
We should go for your follow-up appointment.
Follow-up?
Right.
Once I'm diagnosed as crazy and locked up,
you'll all be happy,
won't you?
Don't you all
just want me to disappear?
Especially Ye Zhiqiu.
That Ye Zhiqiu.
Can people be fake?
Don't you feel anything at all?
First disappearing, then breaking up.
This isn't something Zhiqiu
would ever do to me.
I don't care if you all think I'm crazy or insane.
I must find
the real Ye Zhiqiu.
I still think
you should take care of yourself first.
By the way,
I heard the compensation is quite substantial.
You should accept it if you can.
Wait.
You came to see me today.
Do you know something?
Or are you planning something?
You said you have evidence. What is it?
I will get the evidence.
In this world,
everything is fake.
I don't believe in anything,
including people.
Then find some evidence.
The thing I asked you to do,
have you done it?
Good.
Did you bring it?
You brought the stuff.
Where's my money?
The stuff is correct.
There's another job.
Are you in?
Tell me.
A list of all residents at Binjiang Gardens.
Get the money ready.
Starting from September 20th.
Clothes, jewelry,
handbags,
she hasn't bought any of them.
This isn't just changing habits.
This is clearly a different person.
What you asked for,
the list of Binjiang Gardens property owners,
I've sent it to you.
Xie Yuxuan.
The owner of unit 302
is Xie Yuxuan.