[English subtitles are available]
[My Lethal Man]
[Episode 18]
In other words,
they went to arts university
to see Miss Xinyan
because they knew about the personal seal.
Not only did they know this,
they also knew that the seal
is with Xinyan.
No wonder they tried to kidnap Miss Xinyan.
In the end,
they kidnapped Shen Manning by mistake.
In this way,
we can explain
why Miss Xinyan
had such a big trouble
and why Miss Manning was involved.
If they really kidnapped Zhuang Xinyan,
then LH Star would...
It was Manning
who saved LH Star and the House of Zhuang.
Now all fingers
are pointing at Miss Manning.
Does that mean
the personal seal
is with Miss Manning?
The last person Xinyan saw
when she had the accident was Manning.
But I'm not sure if that personal seal
is in Manning's hands.
Boss,
go ask her.
I don't want her to know.
In the past six months,
she has been in this vortex for too long.
I finally sent her out safely.
I don't want her to go back to danger.
But Boss,
the seal...
I'll be with her these days.
I'll find a chance to ask her
what happened during her last meeting with Xinyan.
But I don't want her to know what we're going through
or let any danger
fall into her again.
Fang Xiang.
You continue to filter the entry and exit data of personnel from arts university
on the day of Xinyan's accident
and clues about the truck 17 years ago.
OK.
Yuan Shuai,
follow Yang.
Yang is Zhuang Jiakai's right-hand man.
If we keep an eye on him,
Zhuang Jiakai won't cause any trouble.
When I find my mother's personal seal,
there might be other solutions.
Come back then.
Okay.
[Yan Xingcheng]
Hello?
Are you awake?
I was thinking
if still no one answered the 20th call,
the next second,
I will appear by your bed.
You really called me more than 20 times?
I'm sorry.
I...
I drank too much last night.
You called me so many times.
I didn't hear anything.
You're sorry.
Are you serious?
I don't know which girl
looked at me
but drank so much.
Yesterday, someone
watched me drinking
and didn't say a word.
Didn't you have Lin Mufan by your side?
Yan Xingcheng.
When other men
see their girlfriends
being with someone else,
they will be jealous.
Look at you.
You really didn't say a word.
Impressive.
I need to be jealous of him?
You don't remember
what you did to me last night?
Last night,
what did I do?
I want you to like me.
I also want you to love me.
I also want you
to stay by my side forever.
Yan Xingcheng.
Do you love me?
What do you think?
I want you to tell me.
You remember?
I can't remember.
Neither can you.
You saw nothing.
In the future, when I'm not with you,
don't drink so much,
no matter who is beside you,
not to say Lin Mufan.
Besides,
come down.
Today,
let's date.
Mr. Yan,
you're not working today?
I skipped work.
♫I'll hug you like this♫
♫And kiss you like this♫
♫I'll cooperate with your willfulness♫
♫I want to watch shooting stars with you♫
♫I want to learn the secret of love with you♫
♫The ring finger means you and me♫
Xingcheng.
Do you know this place is very familiar to me?
I know.
That day,
we came here.
Not that day.
It was in my dream.
Dream?
In my dream,
on this beach,
you
walked ahead.
Then I followed your steps
and stepped behind your footsteps.
You turned around and held my hand.
You said
we would be together forever.
Xingcheng,
when you get back what you want,
let's get out of here.
Where do you want to go?
Anywhere.
Where there are mountains, rivers
and stars.
Anyway,
as long as I can leave these troubles
and won't get involved
in these things...
Maybe I've been too busy
and didn't spend much time with you?
No.
I just hope you won't be too tired.
I hope when you are with me,
you can be happy and relaxed,
without thinking too much.
As long as you're by my side,
it is enough.
Manning.
I...
Sorry.
Sorry
for disturbing you.
Sorry.
Let's go.
You're so naughty.
Chen.
What?
Don't you recognize me?
No.
I'm a little surprised.
Why?
Because of me?
No.
Nobody can drink
my wine so easily.
What do you want
this time?
You.
You want my design.
Tell me.
How much do you plan to pay this time?
You've made progress.
I thought saying this
would scare you away.
I'm from the House of Zhuang.
This small thing
is not enough to scare me.
It is no wonder that you are the man from the House of Zhuang.
You're also charming.
I heard
you intend to set up a personal studio.
Although my Celine is not luxurious enough,
it is also a well-known studio
in the fashion industry.
Now,
as the CEO,
I will sign a three-year contract with you to fully cooperate.
I wonder if you
would like to take the offer?
A full cooperation?
You mean...
Mine
is yours.
Tang Lin,
I know you appreciate my designs.
But you don't have to
hand over your business which you have managed for years
to me.
I've never been indirect to
the person I trust.
Mufan,
you're talented.
I'm willing to give you
all of my sources
to help you become an international designer.
If
you still willing to believe me...
Don't talk.
Otherwise,
I can't help it.
What are you looking at?
You've never seen a couple being intimate?
I'm not interested in you.
Have fun.
I was scared.
Yuan Shuai,
are you just leaving like this?
Or what?
I helped you.
At least
you should thank me.
I need your help？
I'll say it one last time.
Don't.
follow me.
I haven't eaten this mousse cake for a long time.
I heard that they have improved the recipe.
Let me try it.
It tastes even better.
Try it.
Hurry.
You have it on your mouth.
Meina.
Hey, Meina.
Manman.
What is wrong?
Take your time.
Don't...
Don't cry.
Meina is crying.
It is okay.
I'll make a call.
Stay here and
don't go anywhere.
Manman, are you there?
Yes, I am.
Go ahead.
I'm listening.
I'm really listening.
Don't cry.
Okay, Boss.
I'll visit her later.
Don't say anything too harsh.
Boss.
Why are you...
Don't hang up.
Boss.
I just finished screening the big data of entry and exit.
I have a major discovery to tell you.
Go ahead.
Before Miss Xinyan's accident,
the right-hand man of Zhuang Jiakai, Yang,
had a record of entry.
The city he went to
is far away from Miss Xinyan's arts university,
but once he entered the country,
the distance wouldn't be a problem.
Also,
Tang Lin sent someone to Dr. Tai
to take away Miss Xinyan's medical record.
Although Miss Tang returned the medical record,
at the same time, Yang also had an entry record.
So our guess is correct.
Yes.
The ones who went to arts university for Miss Xinyan
should be Zhuang Jiakai and Yang.
So they knew
the personal seal that
can influence the whole LH Star Group
was with Miss Xinyan.
So they planned to go to arts university to
take Miss Xinyan and the seal away.
But Manning's appearance
ruined everything.
Now all fingers
are pointing at Miss Manning.
This means
that personal seal
must be with Miss Manning.
Fang Xiang,
go to Rao Meina first.
Then tell Yuan Shuai,
besides Yang,
to keep an eye on Zhuang Jiakai as well.
This matter can not be so simple.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Where is the girl sitting here just now?
She was taken away by a man.
♫Tick-tock, the second hand goes♫
♫Every moment it turns♫
♫Right now♫
♫How are you doing?♫
What is wrong?
♫I always think about you♫
I texted you.
Don't ignore my calls in the future.
♫When I wake up from my dreams♫
Xingcheng.
♫All stubbornness♫
You mustn't go away alone
without telling me.
♫Broke down in an instant♫
I have...
Promise me.
♫If I give up everything♫
OK.
I promise you.
♫And take the risk♫
Mr. Yan.
You have to promise me that
you must hold me tight
♫Will you come back to me♫
and don't lose me.
♫And go back to the beginning of the story?♫
♫If I'm brave♫
♫Maybe in the parallel world♫
♫My tomorrow♫
♫No longer like parallel lines♫
Still looking?
Not enough.
Just now, Uncle Guangyi came to me.
He said
grandpa wanted to see me.
So I went to see him.
Grandpa.
You didn't raise your head
or talk.
Do you really not want to see me anymore?
No.
President Zhuang.
It is not that I don't want to see you.
I just...
I don't know how to meet you.
Yes.
You and Xingcheng
tricked me
and Lin Guangyi so badly.
When I saw you,
I thought you were my granddaughter.
Then?
I'm sorry.
President Zhuang.
I was wrong.
I...
I shouldn't have pretended to be Xinyan and lied to you.
But...
Xingcheng and I did this
for a reason.
I...
I'm not looking for an excuse.
We did
do this.
We were wrong.
No, it was not our fault.
It was all my fault.
If you are mad,
just be mad at me.
If you want to punish us,
just punish me.
After such a big accident,
he just wants to stay out of it
and shift all blame to you?
No. President Zhuang.
Xingcheng didn't mean to shift the blame.
He is...
Well, he and I...
He...
I...
You two are together, right?
I knew it long ago,
since he brought you home,
stayed by your side every day,
and didn't allow anyone to touch you.
If he didn't have this intention,
I would
have lived in vain for over 60 years.
Since you called me grandpa,
you can't take it back.
Whether it was because you used to think of yourself as Xinyan
or now you're with Xingcheng, the brat,
from now on,
I am your grandpa.
Do you agree?
You...
Are you not angry with me anymore?
You forgave us?
Silly girl.
Since you came back,
I've seen through
your little thoughts.
Although you're not Xinyan,
when I look at you,
I feel like
she is really back.
I've lived for so long.
I don't care about anything.
Xingcheng
has suffered a lot outside.
As long as he can come back,
the House of Zhuang will be saved.
It would be hard for you
to go forward with him.
It is not hard.
I like Xingcheng.
No matter what difficulties I face,
I will try my best
to keep him company.
Good girl.
Do you really think so?
Then stay with Xingcheng.
The door of the House of Zhuang
will always be open for you.
Grandpa.
[Yan Xingcheng]
That brat again?
I sent him a message.
He probably didn't see it,
so he kept calling me.
We were on a date today.
He is waiting for me.
No.
Tell him
you're having tea with grandpa.
Ask him to wait.
Maybe...
Alright.
Go ahead.
Don't make Xingcheng anxious.
When you two are together,
be good.
I'll wait for you two at the House of Zhuang.
I'm leaving.
Grandpa.
Go.
Take care of yourself.
We'll visit you when we're free.
Go ahead.
But Xingcheng,
this time I saw him,
I think he didn't look well.
If you're free,
ask the doctor to treat him more.
Got it.
Well,
tell me what happened to you.
What happened to me?
You skipped work today
and even took me on a one-day date.
Did you really miss me?
Manning.
Mr. Yan,
I know you well.
I just went out for a while.
Why are you so nervous?
What happened?
Is it about the House of Zhuang
or LH Star?
No.
Is it about me?
Don't think too much.
I just want to spend a day
to accompany you.
Here we are.
Go back and rest.
Call me if anything happens.
Don't go out at night.
By the way,
my dad saw you sending me home last time.
After that,
he kept urging me to take you home for dinner.
We're already together.
I hope our relationship
can be blessed by my dad.
So,
come to my house for dinner this weekend, okay?
I'll prepare for it.
I'm leaving.
Manning.
I want to ask you something.
Back then...
That man...
He was the thief who came to my house last time.
He is holding my backpack.
Wait for me here.
Yan Xingcheng.
What's wrong?
What happened?
I'm going to go after Xingcheng.
Can you help me?
Get in.
Xingcheng.