[English subtitles are available]
If
we never met that day,
you are not in my life...
[My Lethal Man]
[Episode 1]
[Prato, Italy]
Fio,
if you can help our family to
chase the fraud money back.
I can offer ten percent of the amount
as compensation to you and your team.
No need.
I'll get your money back.
You would need to help me
to find her.
If your investment consultant doesn't show up,
we're all dead.
Who are you?
Your safe investment consultant.
Safe investor?
Facial identified and voice unlocked.
I got him!
Done.
Game over.
Hey, what do you mean?
Aren't you an investment consultant?
My money hasn't entered your investment account yet.
You don't even want the commission?
I have never been interested in dirty money,
but it has to go back
to where it came from.
Hey, what are you talking about?
Boss, bad news!
It's him, get him!
Boss!
The Walter family just called.
The funds have been received successfully.
They insist on transferring ten percent of amount
to you.
Send Xinyan's information to him
and tell Mr. Walter,
if he can find out where Xinyan is,
no need for
compensation.
By the way, boss,
I got the information from China,
something happened to House of Zhuang and LH Star.
President Zhuang is seriously ill,
LH Star would need to have a new president immediately.
Boss,
House of Zhuang finally gave
Missie's photo and address.
We...
found her.
♫Tick-tock, the second hand goes♫
♫Every moment it turns♫
♫Right now♫
♫How are you doing?♫
♫I always think about you♫
Thank me quickly.
♫when I wake up from my dreams♫
Shen Manning.
It's from my dad?
It's from my mom.
For your dad,
she sends you a big box of packages every time.
I don't know who is her daughter.
Aren't my dad and your mom
a family?
Open it.
If
your dad and my mom are really married,
You are the legitimate daughter of our family.
I'm just adopted.
[Come home early. I'll wait for you.]
What's wrong?
What did Uncle Shen say?
Nothing.
Are you still copying professor's Geminate Rose?
I heard that once this homework is done,
you can get full marks in advance,
so that you can graduate and go home, right?
Yes.
No way. You want to graduate early?
Nana,
you know my family.
I just want to graduate early and go home,
so I can spend time with my dad.
Alright.
I forgive you
for your filial piety.
By the way,
have you heard the legend
behind Geminate Rose from professor?
What legend?
Legend has it that the rose
have been depending and growing together.
They got each other's backs for lifetime
until the flowers bloom.
Under the sunshine,
they can turn around
and look at each other.
But after one glance,
these two roses either die at the same time
or one is damaged,
and the other blooms alone.
Imagine this scene.
When you
meet
your doppelganger,
If what's infront you is
not the climax of fate,
then it is the omen of death.
Stop reading these weird comics.
What doppelganger and twin flower?
What the other me in the world?
This isn't what I saw in comic books.
It's true.
I'm leaving.
Wait for me!
Manman, Manman.
Hurry up.
Wait for me!
Xinyan,
for your safety,
I would assign someone to guard you to the Art University.
Although this is the 13th school you transferred to,
I promise you that
once the House of Zhuang and LH Star settle down,
I would take you home as soon as possible.
Grandpa, I will protect myself
and wait for you to take me home.
Hi, girl,
let's be friends.
I am half Chinese.
Do you think
I came here to make friends?
Tell me.
Who are you?
How is that possible?
It has been 17 years.
You're still alive.
Meet me
at the front gate
of the Art University.
Who is there?
Hey, what's the matter?
Someone from China is looking for you downstairs.
China?
Hello,
are you looking for me?
Yes.
President Zhuang and my father asked me to pick you up.
Let the principal know and
come back to the House of Zhuang with me.
Wait.
Who were you talking about?
Do we know each other?
Don't you remember me?
I'm Lin Mufan.
When we were young,
you often called me Lin.
Your grandfather, President Zhuang Cheng'an
and my father Lin Guangyi
sent me to pick you up.
L-Lin?
Xinyan.
Have you forgotten me
after leaving the House of Zhuang for over ten years?
When you were little, Yi thought you were too young.
I was the one who played with you.
I'm sorry.
You just said
the person you're looking for is...
I'm looking for you,
Zhuang Xinyan.
My surname is not Zhuang.
My surname is Shen. My name is Shen Manning.
I'm a senior student from the Department of Design.
I think you got the wrong person.
Wait.
Before we set off,
President Zhuang
gave me your photo personally.
I just asked that male student to find you.
I don't think I got the wrong person.
What is going on?
She looks
exactly like me.
It is amazing.
But I'm not her.
My dad and I are the only ones in my family.
My dad is just an ordinary truck driver.
And what you just said,
something about the president,
has nothing to do with me.
I'm sorry.
I really have to go.
I have encountered some trouble and
it took me some time.
I'll be right there.
Nana, I have met...
I really met
my twin flower.
She is the doppelganger
you told me before.
I...
♫Every time I look out of the window♫
♫I hope I can see you♫
♫The night breeze is cool♫
♫I'm all alone♫
♫I wish you could call my name♫
Nana.
What's wrong, Manman?
The legend of Twin Flowers you mentioned before
that once Twin Roses meet,
what would happen?
Once Twin Flowers meet,
if it is not the climax of fate next,
it is the omen of death.
Manman, Manman.
Manman, what's wrong with you?
Where are you, Manman?
Hi, girl.
Why are you still here?
I saw a man carrying you into the car.
What did you say?
I saw a man carrying you into a car.
You were wearing something different too.
What is going on?
I saw it just now...
Hey, look!
It is the person right there.
♫When the nightmare blurs the boundary♫
♫When pure white is stained by black♫
♫Me and I have finished the handover♫
♫I can't stop♫
♫Whose calmness can detect the threat?♫
♫Who has that treacherous look in his eyes?♫
♫Who would swear to risk everything?♫
♫Turmoil is deciding♫
♫a point-in-time♫
♫to drag the self-awareness♫
♫into the abyss♫
I have to save someone first.
♫His calm face♫
Wait for me.
♫The calm fraud♫
Watch out!
♫It would only make me see clearly♫
♫The real dark side♫
♫Who is swirling♫
♫Whose old trick is repeating♫
♫There is nothing can be done to change the ending♫
♫Danger coming in the fierce way♫
♫The calm two eyes♫
Hello, boss.
We have caught her.
Don't worry, no one saw us.
I will make her disappear tonight.
Nobody would find out.
Stop! Where are you taking me?
What happened?
Nothing, boss.
Something happened. She woke up. I solved it.
Then find an isolated place
and kill her.
Are you okay?
It's you.
Yes, it's me. I'm here to save you. Let's go.
Are you okay?
My name is Zhuang Xinyan.
I-I'm Shen Manning.
They came for me.
I should be the one they wanted.
But you look exactly like me.
They mistook you for me.
But don't worry.
I'll send you back to school.
Stay there and don't go anywhere.
I'll take care of this.
I won't get you involved again.
OK?
OK.
Sit tight.
Okay.
What should we do?
They...they're catching up again.
Hurry up and make a call.
Passcode is 1121.
Who should I call?
The first one on the contact list who
called me.
♫I remembered your smile again♫
♫Long time no see♫
♫I was longing for a hug in my dream♫
[Emergency Room]
♫But the dream could not be true♫
♫What I said to myself♫
♫Have you heard it?♫
Doctor, how are they?
Both of them...
This is crazy.
The driver protected
the person next to her at the critical moment,
but she broke her sternum,
and her bones pierced her lungs and heart.
She passed away.
The protected girl was severely injured,
especially her cornea.
Even if she survives, her eyes will be blind.
Fio, Fio!
There's something very important, Fio.
I'm afraid you need to go in and have a look.
During the rescue,
we found this important and magical thing.
The two of them
look exactly the same.
Fio. The girl who survived,
her eyes were pierced by broken glass.
Her only chance now
is to receive the cornea transplant immediately,
so that she can see when she wakes up.
But regarding the cornea...
I think...
since the girl who left
protected her with her own life,
why not donating her corneas
to the girl who's still alive.
[15 days later]
[Ward No. 32]
You are awake.
Who...who are you?
Why am I here?
I'm your fiance.
I...I don't know you at all.
I don't have a boyfriend either.
By the way,
do you confuse me
to that girl who looks like me?
We do look the same,
but I'm not her.
Her name is Zhuang Xinyan.
I-I'm Shen Manning.
Shen Manning is dead.
Your name is Zhuang Xinyan.
How is that possible?
I'm fine now.
I am alive here.
Why do you say so?
[Zhuang Xinyan]
I...I'm not Zhuang Xinyan.
I'm Shen Manning, not Zhuang Xinyan.
Stop chasing me.
Stay back!
-Okay.-If you come any closer, I'll jump!
Calm down, don't rush for anything.
It's dangerous there.
I'm not the Zhuang Xinyan
you are looking for.
I'm really not her.
I did nothing.
I know nothing.
I am begging you.
Stop following me.
Don't come over!
If you come any closer,
I...I will really jump.
Don't touch your eyes!
You can stand here
because someone died for you.
You can see the world
because you took her eyes.
What?
Two people in one car.
Since you are still alive,
who was the one who died?
Your encounter with her
is your destiny.
Since someone has left in the accident,
then the person who survived
doesn't belong to yourself anymore.
You must live on behalf of
the person who left.
You are Zhuang Xinyan.
You can only be
Zhuang Xinyan.
♫I remembered your smile again♫
You must live on behalf of
the person who left.
♫Long time no see♫
♫I was longing for a hug in my dream♫
♫But the dream could not be true♫
♫What I said to myself♫
♫Have you heard it?♫
♫The past taught people to grow up♫
♫I would not listen♫
Can you
go back to the House of Zhuang for me.
♫Thinking about your face If you're just hibernating♫
You must go back to the House of Zhuang
and get
LH Star back for me.
♫Give me one more moment♫
Find Yan Xingcheng.
♫Missed your face and wanted to pay you back♫
You must
live on.
♫Why not forever?♫
Yan Xingcheng,
right?
You want me to go back to the House of Zhuang
on behalf of Zhuang Xinyan?
How long do I have to be there?
One year. Is that enough?
Xinyan saved my life.
My eyes
are also from her.
Twin roses.
If only one rose can live,
I'm willing to go with you
on behalf of her.
♫Falling in love with the most dangerous person♫
♫I can't let go♫
♫Oh, forget it♫
♫Meeting the most dangerous person♫
♫I can't turn him down♫
♫This love drama♫
♫He is the most dangerous♫
♫The concern left for me♫
♫Oh, forget it♫
♫Leave the most dangerous place♫
♫But I've already fallen♫
♫He might know too♫