[English subtitles are available.]
[Episode 7]
Don't fight!
Calm down.
Don't fight.
I got it!
That brat must have fled
to the back of the hillside.
I'll take you there.
Hurry up.
-After you.
-Let's go.
Over here.
This way, please.
Tianqi.
Are you sure Lu Ping will come here?
I went to great lengths
to get this information.
That brat always trains
at the back of the mountain.
My father came to capture him.
He is definitely hiding there.
The last fight wasn't enough.
I want to kill him this time.
Tianqi. Someone is coming
from Zhaifeng Institute.
Stay hidden.
Don't make any sound.
Once they are near, we'll make our move.
Yes.
Are you guys ready?
Who did that?
Brat!
You didn't succumb
to the poison in the tower last time.
I want to kill you today!
Tianqi.
Father, how could it be you?
I sacrificed myself
to save your father.
Thank you.
Am I dead?
-Am I dead?
-No, you're not.
You're still living.
What's wrong?
Why does it not hurt?
I don't feel pain anymore.
Hang on, you're...
Get up right now.
It's retribution for my sins.
I originally wanted you two
to lead the attack
and capture Lu Ping.
Thank goodness, I walked in front of you.
Otherwise,
your son would have...
Thank you so much.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Mr. Wei, what did you mean just now?
You used poison inside the tower.
I didn't.
Cheating in the exam
and poisoning the lives
of other examinees.
What kind of crime is this?
Tianqi, don't be afraid!
My son will never
do such a despicable act.
It was so chaotic just now.
Maybe you heard it wrongly.
All of us heard it.
Your son did it.
Yes!
You guys heard it wrongly!
They heard it wrongly.
Everyone heard it wrongly!
Yes, they heard it wrongly.
We heard it, Master.
We swear.
Actually, I heard it too.
You...
How could you?
Come over here.
Well, I need a bit of hush money.
We, Zhaifeng Institute,
aren't as wealthy
as the Chan State Academy.
We don't accept payment on credit.
Cash.
Cash is accepted.
Guo Youdao.
This is blackmail.
You're blackmailing me.
They are gone.
Every single person
from the Wei family left.
I told you.
My luck is back again.
Really?
Of course.
Lu Ping.
They left and we're fine now.
Can we still go back?
I already said those things.
Going back is embarrassing.
Come, let's wait for him
at Ruyu Restaurant.
Who are we waiting for?
After he arrives,
you'll know.
Master.
Why did you protect Lu Ping desperately?
You even pretended to be a bad person.
No wonder Lu Ping always provokes you.
Now, I also feel that
your personality
is quite interesting.
Come with me.
[Ruyu Restaurant]
[From now on,]
you have nothing to do
with Zhaifeng Institute.
[Cutting ties with them]
[is the only way to save them
from all this mess.]
Lu Ping, he is really here.
[Save me!]
Mo Lin.
Su Tang is your disciple
and also my disciple.
If I die,
I'll never let her take you as her master.
Speak now if you have something to say.
You guys can either fight now
or get this done with.
Old geezer, I'm going to kill you.
Master.
Is this why you want me to come with you?
Old geezer.
I won't let you die instantly.
The Piebald Scorpion Venom on this arrow
will make you itch for 49 days.
Despicable person!
Come here if you dare...
and fight with Xifan.
Let go of Xifan if you dare.
I'll never let him go.
Lu Ping, come here.
Perfect timing.
Make that brat stop right now.
Am I not rat poop?
Assumed I farted loudly that day, can you?
Please don't, Master.
Although I'm petty,
I really want to talk to you
openly and honestly,
so that you can understand me.
Madam Jin.
Prepare some dishes and wine.
Put it on my bill.
All right.
Shi Dongchun wine?
A pot costs 52 silver taels.
One sip is worth three silver taels.
After I finish it, it's gone after I pee.
A fine wine
deserves a modest master.
If you didn't use tricks
and wrote the letter to attract Qin Qi,
I'm afraid I'm still trapped
in Chan State.
Is your head messed up
after getting beaten inside the tower?
I advise you to place your wager
on someone else quickly.
Someone else?
I invested too much.
If I withdraw halfway,
I'll lose everything.
As long as I'm still
on the gambling table,
I can recoup my losses.
Now,
we're disqualified
from the Soul Combat Convention.
Where are you going next?
I'll follow
wherever Lu Ping goes.
If we can't go to the convention,
there is always another way.
Why don't you dump
your troublesome brother?
Worship me as your master.
You're not bad,
but you shouldn't be with us.
Don't you want
to roam the martial arts world
and become the top assassin?
Actually, I think you're quite impressive.
Maybe next time when we meet,
you've become the top assassin already.
The next time we meet...
Why do you look unhappy?
I'm not.
I just feel that...
I couldn't get a disciple this time,
so I'm feeling quite sad.
Don't worry.
You still have a chance.
Su Tang.
Do you know
who is the important person
I always visit every year at Kaifeng?
Who is it?
[Chu Min.]
Tianzhao Academy's instructor?
So, you visit her every year at Kaifeng.
I can't believe an old man like you
have such an influential friend.
So you decided to stop calling me
an old geezer?
Listen carefully.
Soul Combat Convention requires
a team of four people to compete.
The tower was demolished.
Zhaifeng was already disqualified.
But if you guys worship Chu Ming
as your master,
we can use Tianzhao Academy's name
to join the convention.
Surpasses that of Beidou,
make our ancestors proud.
Both can be achieved.
Lu Ping already agreed to it.
If Lu Ping agrees, I agree too.
Fine.
I'll do this kind deed
for my future disciple
and let you guys owe me a favor.
Please forgive me for not abiding.
Master.
Is Xifan okay?
Xifan.
Master.
I saw you peeking just now.
What's the matter?
Are you feeling reluctant?
Master.
I know my own limits.
I shouldn't be going
to the Soul Combat Convention.
I'm not the one controlling your legs.
I'm not stopping you anyway.
An ambitious person needs a place
to showcase his talent.
You've stopped at Zhaifeng
for so many years.
It's time for you to go back
to the path you belong on.
I can't win against you.
I can't even win against Lu Ping.
I didn't atone for my sins.
I can't hold a blade anymore.
Even if I go to the convention,
I can't be of help.
Compared to you,
Lu Ping is nothing.
Without Zhaifeng Institute,
Lu Ping won't be like this now.
Without you,
Zhaifeng won't be Zhaifeng.
Xing Luo is dead.
The weight is off your shoulders.
Stop it, Master.
My leg is injured.
Whatever you say is pointless.
It's too early to tell.
Drink with me first.
I can tell from one glance,
that this Zhao Xifan is different
from you bumpkins.
He has high self-esteem.
This thing you made.
Could it really make him
follow us to Kaifeng?
Lu Ping.
All these years,
after Xifan join Zhaifeng,
he never returned home or went out.
There's more to this than meets the eye.
Didn't Master give you any advice?
I think Master went drinking again.
He didn't leave any message.
After I make this,
send this to him on my behalf.
I provoked Xifan many times.
It's better if you guys advise him.
All of you are here.
Lu Ping.
When Master Guo bought wine, he left this.
He said he's buying time for you
and asked me to pass this to you.
He also said,
"the person who tied the bell..."
Should untie it.
"...should untie it."
Why are you holding the boards?
Isn't this Ruyu Restaurant's chair?
Why did it become like this?
It's pretty comfortable.
Master.
I should go now.
Don't.
Don't leave me.
You completely ignored my feelings.
Zhaifeng offended
the Wei family this time.
If we don't get a placing
in the convention,
the centuries-old organization
will be ruined.
Xifan, why don't you reconsider it?
Can you?
Master, I surrendered the badge.
You should give it
to a more suitable person.
Xifan.
I have something to return to you.
Here.
I already gave it back to Master.
The eldest disciple is
Zhaifeng's role model.
Take it, God of Bandits.
Nope.
It's worthless.
-Even if it's a gift, I won't take it.
-You...
Xifan.
It suits you more.
Without you,
I won't be where I am now.
I have my past.
You have your past too.
Rather than running away,
why don't we face it together?
Yes.
You said your personal matters
are none of my business.
You can take it back now.
I never take my words back.
Let's get to know each other again.
Wait for me.
I have something for you.
Your craftsmanship is pretty good.
Come over here, give it a try.
Here.
Hold them.
There's hope
to surpass Beidou!
Move forward!
Lu Ping, push him.
Did you not eat?
Chan State reported
that you're dead.
I have important news
to inform our lord immediately.
I was heavily injured
by the people of Zhaifeng.
I only dared to show myself
after hiding for several days.
What a useless junk.
You embarrassed us!
Why don't I pluck your teeth
and make a necklace?
The person concerns our lord's grand plan.
I rushed back to report this.
I'm very sure
that the person is the Awakener,
who was kidnapped from the tower
three years ago,
Lu Ping.
Did you see him clearly?
Yes.
I also heard
that he's heading towards Kaifeng
for the Soul Combat Convention.
I'm willing to go to great lengths
to capture him,
so I can redeem myself.
It's fine.
Since he already showed himself,
he won't be able to escape again.
Nobody can walk away from Shanhai Gang.
Dying here is his destiny.
As for you,
you should know the rules of Shanhai Gang.
Take her away.
How is the arrangement at Kaifeng?
Mr. Feng has made
the necessary preparations.
Your plan may begin at any time.
Pass my order.
Don't act rashly and alert the enemy.
Yes.
The triennial Soul Combat Convention
is around the corner.
How is the preparation, Mr. Wen?
Your Majesty.
I already negotiated with General Qin
and sent invitations
to all martial arts academy
to recruit talented people
from across the kingdom,
so we can contribute to the kingdom.
Your Majesty.
In my opinion,
Mr. Wen's actions were inappropriate.
Mr. Xia, why do you say so?
The selection of generals
concern the strength,
the rise, and fall of the kingdom.
For generals of Shuo Kingdom,
we should select them
from prominent families by right.
Your Majesty,
a hero's origin isn't important.
There are many extraordinary people
in the martial arts world.
If we miss out on them,
it will be Shuo Kingdom's loss.
In terms of talent,
many disciples of Tianzhao Academy
have been enlisted over the years.
All of them are excellent in martial arts.
In terms of loyalty,
imperial relatives come
after prominent families.
Their loyalty was indisputable.
How could the martial artists
fare against them?
I think that,
General Qin has many acquaintances
in the martial arts world,
especially the people
with an unclear background
and a suspicious motive.
It's a disgrace to Shuo Kingdom.
Mr. Xia is also the headmaster
of Tianzhao Academy.
Naturally, your disciples' capability
can't be underestimated.
But in my opinion,
gathering talented people
from all walks of life
is the only root of serving
the imperial family.
If you're afraid that commoners
will overshadow the imperial family,
doesn't this goes
against the imperial graciousness?
General, you just returned.
You should take off your armor first.
While I'm absent,
Mr. Xia won't waste this opportunity.
I can't let Mr. Wen suffer alone.
My two officials,
you've been planning
for this martial arts event.
You want the best for the kingdom.
Please don't be agitated.
Your Majesty.
[Commander of Victorious Dragon Troop,
Qin Qi requests to meet.]
Summon him.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
General Qin, you must've had
a tiring journey.
Serving the kingdom
is my pleasure.
Your Majesty.
I heard the martial arts academy
are planning to send their disciples
to take part in this convention.
Shuo Kingdom's martial artists
have never been gathered together.
It's the blessing of Shuo Kingdom.
I'm afraid Mr. Xia doesn't believe so.
Does Mr. Xia still believe
that generals should be
from prominent families?
Exactly so.
Your Qin family is prominent.
They are valiant.
They have also cultivated
a talented person like General Qin.
This proves my point.
Lieutenant general
of Left Guard Corps, Li Che,
graduated from Chan State Academy.
Since he took office
to suppress the northwestern bandits,
he performed a total
of 35 meritorious services.
Lieutenant general
of Imperial Martial Artists, Fang Qiong
graduated from Xu State Academy.
This person was a genius.
He invented Horse Splitting Formation
and fought countless enemies.
Since Mr. Wen takes control
of the army selection,
many generals selected
from the commoners are talented.
But some people from prominent families
are incompetent and corrupted.
I believe Mr. Xia knows this clearly.
More importantly,
the citizens are in turmoil
over the years.
There is unrest.
The citizens are fighting
against oppression.
If we can unite the citizens
and put them to good use
through the Soul Combat Convention,
we won't have to worry about
Shuo Kingdom's prosperity and stability.
Your Majesty.
Forgive my bluntness.
During this convention,
you're not only selecting generals,
you're also raising the ambitious
and fighting spirit of the kingdom.
Nicely spoken.
This Soul Combat Convention
is to enlighten the soul power
of Shuo Kingdom.
General Qin.
I'm looking forward
to the kind of talented heroes
you and Mr. Wen will select
during this Soul Combat Convention.
We won't disappoint Your Majesty.
General Qin.
You sounded sure of yourself
in the court today.
But I still hope
that the martial artists you recommend
can be like you too,
so His Majesty won't disappoint.
Please look forward to it then, Mr. Xia.
Wenrui.
I'll send Mr. Wen home.
Find a director for a check-up.
Yes.
I'm fine, General.
It's just a relapse of my old injury.
In the court just now,
thank you for fighting for me.
But at this rate,
the hatred between Mr. Xia
and you grows deeper.
Since there's already a grudge,
leave it be if I can't resolve it.
General.
You should plan for your own future.
I'm just an ordinary guy
from the martial arts world.
Don't worry about me.
Mr. Wen.
All these years,
If you didn't discuss martial arts with me
and organize military affairs,
you won't become a thorn
in Xia Bojian's flesh.
Not to mention,
if I protect you,
I also protect the talented people
who will work for Shuo Kingdom
in the future.
Do you still remember what I said
when we were organizing
the Soul Combat Convention
back then, Mr. Wen?
I still remember.
"The Qin family conquered the world
with the previous emperor.
Knowing that soldiers
are the roots of a kingdom,
if I can bring talented martial artists
to Shuo Kingdom,
even if I have to go against
the whole world,
I, Qin Qi, am not afraid."
I'm amazed by your lofty spirit.
I'll definitely handle
the Soul Combat Convention,
so I'll live up to your expectations.
Come with me now.
After you rest well,
the Soul Combat Convention
needs you as a host.
Also,
Qin Sang...
Qin Sang has been wanting to meet you.
Did Ms. Qin create
some sort of trouble again
and you need to deal with it?
I instructed you guys.
Don't hold back.
All of you are pulling your punches.
What's the point of fighting?
Dismiss.
Yes.
You fought three people previously.
Now, you can fight five people.
It seems you've made progress.
I heard that when you were at my age,
you can fight ten people.
Why don't you train with me?
When I train the Sun Streamer Swordplay
with Ziyan,
she always holds back.
It's suffocating.
Ziyan!
You instructed me before
that I can't train with Miss.
I have crossed the line.
Please forgive me.
I ordered Ziyan.
I know the Sun Streamer Swordplay
can't be divulged,
but I need someone
to counter my moves, don't I?
You love roaming the world.
I allowed you.
The Sun Streamer Swordplay
is the Qin family's
secret sword technique.
Once it's divulged,
it disturbs our clan's foundation.
Did you totally ignore what I said?
You two, accept your punishments
based on the family rules.
Go now!
Don't get angry, General.
Let me be the mediator.
Soul Combat Convention is upon us.
Why don't we make a deal here?
If Ms. Qin wins the convention,
Ms. Ling's and her punishments
will be revoked.
If Ms. Qin didn't manage to pass,
she'll accept your punishment
without any objection.
What do you think?
-Mr. Wen...
-All right!
It's just a convention.
I'll win and show it to you.
What do you think, General?
Fine.
She won't listen to anyone,
but only to Mr. Wen.
But let me tell you.
Don't expect Mr. Wen to cheat for you.
If you want to win,
you must rely on your own strength.
If I ask Mr. Wen to guide me
in martial arts,
it's not cheating, right?
Mr. Wen, come with me.
Mr. Wen.
You're the most knowledgeable.
Have you heard of a chain
that can bind one's soul power?
Why did you suddenly ask this, Miss?
Do you know?
Do you know how to unbind it?
Indeed, there's
a blood martial art
called Soul Confinement.
But it's rare and complicated.
As to whether it can be unbound,
it depends on the person.
Have you seen this kind of martial arts?
[Why am I concerned about that rogue?]
[I must concentrate]
[to train my swordsmanship.]
[I must perform well]
[during the Soul Combat Convention.]
I heard it from a young bandit.
Mr. Wen, I'll get a cup of tea for you.
Let's continue training later.
"Preparations are made in Kaifeng.
Our lord orders you
to stop chasing after Lu Ping.
Stay in Chan State for further orders.
Failing again
won't be forgivable."
How gracious of our lord.
It's not our time yet.
The Wei family is safe for now.
What about our future?
Let's take one step at a time.
Our lives are in the hands of others.
Father.
Father, I've decided.
Father, why are you sweating?
The weather is so hot. It's too stuffy.
What do you need?
I want to go to Kaifeng
for the convention.
If I'm famous,
I'll be worthy of Sangsang.
Young Master.
Go if you must.
Wei Ming.
Let Wei Ying bring the bodyguards
with the best martial arts
to protect Young Master.
Thank you, Father.
I'll write a letter now.
I want to tell Sangsang.
Master.
Lu Ping is at Kaifeng too.
It's better to avoid him right now.
The Shanhai Gang's punishment
is hanging over our heads.
We are walking on thin ice.
Let Tianqi do whatever he wants.
The Shanhai Gang
treats Lu Ping indifferently.
Tell Wei Ying to protect Tianqi this time.
Don't let him get involved with Lu Ping.
Yes.
I can't.
I can't walk anymore.
Guo Youdao.
Didn't you take a lot of silver taels
from Wei Zhong?
Can't you hire a carriage?
How dare you.
The martial arts tower was so expensive.
I gave them to Chan State Academy.
Be thankful that we don't have
to beg for food.
Martial arts practitioners
shouldn't crave for comfort.
It's easy for you to talk.
You've been sitting.
My disciple was pushing you.
Mo Lin.
Do you want to sleep here
or do you want to sleep on a bed
in Kaifeng City with a full stomach?
Isn't this Ms. Qin's golden badge?
Lu Ping.
Let's go to Kaifeng quickly.
Stay in the most luxurious inn.
-Yes.
-No!
Using someone's name to deceive people,
how is it different from stealing?
Xifan.
Even if he's poor,
he can't give up on his principles.
Look at him.
Zhaifeng disciples must be honorable.
Master, this is what you taught us.
What should we eat?
We must eat chicken.
Yes.
Let me think about it.
One whole chicken isn't enough.
I can eat half a chicken.
Let's order two then.
[Tianzhao Academy]
Miss, it has been a while
since you return to Tianzhao.
But you refused to enter.
Don't you want to visit your peers?
Ziyan.
I was here for three years.
But I attended classes
for less than three months.
Do you know why?
Tianzhao only accepts disciples
from prominent families.
It's not about martial arts,
but one's family background.
This type of place
isn't as interesting
as Zhaifeng Institute.
Qin Sang.
Luo Ting.
Congratulations.
For the Soul Combat Convention,
you and I are selected.
I wonder if you're interested
in forming a team.
Thank you for the kind offer.
Ziyan and I will find two more disciples.
You are highly respected in Tianzhao.
I believe you have better candidates.
A slave
who become
a disciple of Tianzhao to protect you.
She's not worth it.
Plus, I heard that you returned
from experiencing the martial arts world.
You're from a prominent family after all.
Roaming among commoners
in the martial arts world
goes against the decorum.
Why don't you mingle with us?
That's only fitting for your identity.
I don't care about one's identity.
I only look at one's martial arts.
Plus, the martial artists
come from all walks of life.
There's no shortage of talented people.
Since you're going
to the Soul Combat Convention,
you'll witness it soon.
Ziyan, let's go.
Luo Ting, you're from a prominent family,
Headmaster Xia's favorite disciple.
If the Qin family didn't organize
the Soul Combat Convention,
you already joined the military
as an official.
You won't have to fight
with those martial artists.
You're broad-minded
so you chose not to argue with her.
But she has gotten worse.
She said you're worse than her maid.
[Hongfu Inn]
If I know the Qin family
is so powerful in Kaifeng,
I should've asked
for double the price
from Qin Sang back then.
At this point in time,
do you still want to kill Lu Ping?
No way.
How can I touch our boss?
Right, Su Tang.
Do you like this room?
It's the most expensive.
I have a good taste after all.
All right.
Let's keep this room for Lu Ping.
Where is Lu Ping?
If you don't change the dressing,
don't dream of walking again.
Did you cheat
using Qin family's golden badge?
Do you not need this?
I don't need it.
All right.
Lu Ping.
Don't you want
to fight against Shanhai Gang?
Can you change your bad habits
and be a good person?
Xifan.
Good people will not only die,
but they will die earlier.
This is the principle.
When you can walk on your own,
let's talk about your principles.
Lu Ping!
Master.
Lu Ping, take a look inside.
The interior is so luxurious.
Hurry up.
Looking at you,
it seems you're determined
to sleep outside.
I have never stayed in such a nice inn.
I won't accompany you.
Master!
Help me up.
Did you change your mind?
If I don't rest well
and get back on my feet,
that guy, Lu Ping is going
to be on cloud nine.
Very good.
Your provocation is working.
Lu Ping, come here.
What's the matter?
For you to succeed,
I have prepared specifically
an affordable gift for you.
You have a gift for me?
Master.
Use it when you pray
for our founding master.
I don't need it.
Since the day in the tower,
I broke one of the chains.
The usage of my soul power
isn't limited
to burning one joss stick anymore.
I think I can handle the convention.
I already taught you
most of the things I know.
Only this Kaifeng City can teach you
the remaining things.
Do you guys smell it?
The Shanhai Gang?
Shanhai Gang again.
Other than escaping,
can you think of something else?
It's congee.
The most famous congee in Kaifeng City.
Young Master.
The Soul Combat Convention is near.
Master reminded me to be wary
of your work-sleep balance.
Where do you want to have your meal today?
Not meeting Sangsang,
my heart is filled with sadness.
Let's have something light.
[Yuyangji Congee Store]
Honorable guests of the Qin family,
although our shop is small,
this crab congee
is the one and only in Kaifeng City.
Please enjoy.
River crab, Japonica rice, and parsley.
Nothing more,
nothing less.
Martial arts practitioners
shouldn't crave for good food.
Xifan.
Martial arts practitioners aren't monks.
Here.
Zhao Xifan.
I'm cultivating soul of Pivot.
Perception is my focus,
so not only must I eat,
I must eat good food.
Nobody wants to live
an ascetic life like you.
But it's odd.
In this congee restaurant,
why is there a woman who reeks of alcohol?
It ruins the congee's delicate taste.
What is that smell? It's so familiar.
Sir, I want another bowl of congee.
Excuse me.
I'm coming.
Do you have private seats?
Sir.
Our private seats are occupied.
Do you mind sitting here?
I just reached Kaifeng
and I came to your restaurant.
But you actually told me
that there's no private seat.
Don't you feel bad for all my sweat
and tears to come here?
Enemies often cross each other's path,
don't you think so?
Sir.
Do you know who my father is?
Have you heard of Chan State's Wei family?
I'm the young master of the Wei family.
This place reeks of alcohol.
How could we eat?
Sir,
Kaifeng doesn't care about the Wei family.
Not to mention, my private seats
are occupied by honorable guests.
Honorable guests?
Are those the honorable guests
you mentioned?
No matter what, I want the private seats.
Wei Hu.
Throw them out.
Mr. Wei, Master instructed us
that we must keep
a low profile in Kaifeng.
If you won't, I'll do it myself.
Sir.
Move aside!
Sir, don't smash anything. Sir!
Go!
Excuse me, this is your congee.