[English subtitles are available.]
Legend of Awakening
Episode 25
You save Su Tang for me.
I can save myself with confidence.
Okay.
I promise you.
Mr. Lu.
I’d like to go with you to rescue Miss Su Tang.
Ziyan.
You…
You have been taking care of me.
I regard you as my family.
Mr. Lu. If you still regard me as a friend,
don’t keep me out of this.
Fine.
More people, more assurance.
Okay.
I entrust Su Tang’s life to you.
What?
The Big Dipper even broke into the jail
and rescued Lu Ping.
Now how can Qin Qi take him back to
E’zhou for execution?
Yes.
It was you who proposed to the master that you’d
rob Lu Ping from the path under the mountain.
Now you are one step behind Qin Qi.
I don’t know how Mr. Xu will explain to master.
I need more time
to change the situation here.
[Bring Xu Weifeng back now.
Don’t disturb Big Dipper.]
I don’t think you have the chance.
Master wants to meet you.
General Qin.
Open the door.
Yes.
When are you going to cut off my head?
At noon tomorrow.
This is an explanation to Tan
to comfort Xu Tianbing’s spirit.
Okay.
I still have time to have a dream.
How could you
fall asleep now?
Lu Ping.
You must hate me.
I can only live until tomorrow.
Why should I hate you?
In Kaifeng, you were supposed to be
the winner of the Force Combat Convention.
But you were framed by me.
You saved me
in E’zhou.
But you are still being charged for me.
I’ve sacrificed you several times.
You have reason
to hate me.
You and I have different needs.
You did it for Qin Family,
and Shuo.
I did it for
a clear conscience.
I will do it again
for the people
I care.
In this case,
I have nothing to regret.
You are a talented person.
If I knew you earlier,
I would have taken you under my command
at all costs.
But it’s too late
to say that.
Lu Ping.
I’m sorry for you.
I will repay you in my next life.
Get ready for tomorrow.
Master.
Master Zhou was defeated by Yan Qiuci that day.
We have not found his whereabouts.
Mr. Xu.
Your plan failed.
Don’t do things
beyond your ability.
Or you’ll get everyone in trouble.
Am I right?
Master.
He is useless now,
and he knows the secrets of our gang.
It’s better
to get rid of him.
Wait.
Master.
I have an idea.
You want Lu Ping alive.
Right?
You know too much.
I could bring him back.
Master.
You won’t trust this man again.
If you want Lu Ping alive.
I can take him back.
Lu Ping will be executed tomorrow.
Qin Qi will be strictly guarded.
Now Master Zhou hasn’t come back.
Yan Xifan is too obvious.
You’ve no ideal person to take over the job.
I am the only one
to bring Lu Ping back
without being seen.
Tonight at the ferry,
I’ll wait for you until 1 a.m.
Okay.
[Breeze Mansion]
It’s hard to break through.
We’ll only alarm the guards.
Could you sneak in?
The scope is too large.
If we can’t confirm the position of Miss Su Tang,
I’m afraid that I will alarm the guards.
We can’t afford to
alarm the guards.
Xu Weifeng hasn’t been back for a long time.
Has he sent Su Tang out of the mansion?
What can we do?
Don’t worry.
I’ve been checking his gate for the past two days.
I haven’t closed my eyes for a moment.
I swear in the name of
the World’s No. 1 Assassin that
Su Tang
is still in his mansion.
Xu Weifeng did something.
He made a mess of spices
in the mansion.
So I can’t determine the location of Su Tang.
And no one came in or out
of these two days
carring a vessel that could hold a person.
And since he left the post,
he has added many guards to the mansion.
So
Su Tang must be in the mansion.
Lu Ping will be executed at noon tomorrow.
If he has ambition,
he would leave tomorrow.
It’s the only chance for us to save Su Tang
when he leaves.
So whether there’s a clue of Su Tang or not,
we need to break in the mansion.
Mo Lin.
How long since you had a good meal
and slept?
I don’t remember.
As long as you relax a little bit,
you may miss the clue.
I will take the shift.
That’s okay.
It’s about the life of my master.
I can do it.
You’re going to die first.
I know you honor your master.
She is not only my master.
She is Su Tang.
As long as she’s safe,
even if I die,
it doesn't matter.
[Breeze Mansion]
Bao Niang.
Mister.
I told you many times
you don’t need to clean the study.
You can leave now.
Mister.
You seem to be getting cranky lately.
Bao Niang.
I saved your life.
Just follow my order.
Okay?
Yes.
Hold it.
People smell from their skin.
I use the silver needle to stimulate the acupoint,
which can temporarily seal the smell,
so no one can find you.
I will be gentle.
I have candy for you,
if you feel hurt.
How about my brother?
Su Tang.
Is Lu Ping important
to Shanhai Gang?
What do you want from my brother?
I underestimated Shanhai Gang.
I wanted to use them to finish my plan.
But I was controlled
by them.
They casted me aside
like an old shoe.
Answer me.
What do you want from my brother?
Didn’t you tell me
not to give up dream?
Since Lu Ping is so important to Shanhai Gang.
Then only when I get Lu Ping first
can Shanhai Gang help me willingly.
Am I right?
Xu Weifeng.
You can kill me.
Don’t hurt my brother.
How could I hurt you?
No matter what happened to Lu Ping,
I will take good care of you for him
and will not hurt you again.
The smell can be sealed,
but the smell of blood can’t be sealed.
Brother.
I can’t save you this time.
I just hope that you won’t be dragged down by me
and you can find some way of tiding over the crisis.
Mo Lin.
Please find me.
This man has personal relationship with Qin Qi.
I am afraid Qin Qi will find one to replace him.
General Xu is from Tan.
The murderer should be taken back to Tan by me.
Mr. Xu.
I’m afraid it’s out of line.
It is the order of the Military Minister, Mr. Xu.
If you dare to violate, you may hinder
the friendship between the two countries.
Yes. Mr. Xu.
I’m dying.
Can’t I see a face that makes me happy?
Why should I see you?
Lu Ping.
I’ve told you
I regard you as my friend.
Now,
Qin Qi is going to kill you.
I am coming to save you.
[Breeze Mansion]
Mo Lin.
Ziyan will distract the guards later.
You and I go to the mansion.
I will guard and you go to find Su Tang.
We leave the rest to god.
I don’t believe the god.
I only believe Su Tang.
She is my master.
She must have a way to notice us.
Ziyan won’t have much time.
Let’s split up.
Blood.
The smell of Su Tang’s blood.
I know where she is.
Master.
I am coming for you.
You…
Master.
Master. Are you okay?
I will stop the bleeding.
Thanks.
Master.
Are you okay?
As you said, you practiced.
Shanhai Gang likes to have a partner like you.
Senior Xu.
I thought you have huge ambition.
You are a running dog of Shanhai Gang.
I brought Lu Ping here.
I want it to be the same as before.
Shanhai Gang and Tan work together
to eliminate Shuo.
Otherwise,
even if I should kill him,
I won’t let Shanhai Gang success.
Okay.
I promise you.
This Shanhai Token shows my promise.
When I return to Shanhai Gang,
I will plan this.
Deal.
Xu Weifeng.
Do you really think Shanhai Gang will be so kind?
You and I are the same
to them.
As long as you are useless,
you will be abandoned as old shoes.
Lu Ping.
You don’t have to struggle and instigate anymore.
You lose your freedom again.
Are you desperate?
I’ve said that for a long time.
No one can escape from Shanhai Gang.
You’re wrong.
Zhaifeng Institute and Big Dipper
taught me a lot these years.
The first.
I can save my life
by myself.
Yan Xifan.
You are awake.
The second thing Lu Ping and I have learned
in Zhaifeng
is that great things can be achieved,
if we all work together.
Now you are
alone.
It’s said that Shanhai Gang has a good way
to torture the captives.
I’d like to see
how many secrets you can spit out
in Longjie Army.
Get ready for tomorrow.
As long as you won’t trouble me in the next life,
I can do you another favor.
Those who killed General Xu,
colluded with Shanhai Gang
and caused disputes between Shuo and Tan
will appear tonight.
It depends on whether General Qin
would like to play a show with me.
Okay.
General Qin.
Please return my weapons
back.
Take them down.
Yes.
You and Qin Qi,
you have been designing for a long time.
Yes.
General Qin won’t come out soon,
I’m afraid I’ll steal all the limelight.
Didn’t we agree?
You let Xu Weifeng get the Shanhai Token.
I’ll clean up the mess.
Qin Qi.
It’s no use catching me.
Lu Ping killed Xu Tianbing.
It’s a truth.
You want to cover for him.
You are covering the murderer.
Is that right?
Feng’re.
Dad.
Why are you here?
Minister Xu.
Xu Weifeng colludes with Shanhai Gang
to kill the general of Tan,
with the intention of provoking a war.
Now the evidence is solid.
Minister Xu. Please make a judicious judgment.
Weifeng.
I thought you are not reconciled
because you couldn’t join the army.
I didn’t expect
you’ve fallen so far.
Minister Xu.
We will leave your son to you.
Weifeng.
No. No.
Lu Ping.
Let me go.
Or you won’t see Su Tang again.
With women as chips,
how could you talk about the country?
Su Tang.
How could they find you?
Even if I give up my life,
I won't let you hurt her.
Bao Niang wanted to tell you that,
she hoped you won’t make another mistake.
She asked me to take a word.
She didn’t understand your principle of
ending war with war.
She is just hoping that there would be no more war.
Xu Weifeng.
You thought you were helping the people,
but you didn’t know what they want.
Since you worked with Shanhai Gang,
everything has been wrong.
No.
Weifeng.
Listen to me.
If you repent,
I will save your life
even if I give up this official uniform.
Son.
Please repent.
Dad.
Don’t you understand?
I admit that I have ambition.
But I didn’t do anything wrong.
I believe in ending war with war.
I did it for our country.
The winner takes all in Jianghu.
But I will never
give up.
Weifeng.
Don’t go.
-Mr. Xu.
-Weifeng.
Don’t go.
Weifeng.
Mr. Xu.
Sang’re.
Don’t worry.
They’ve settled in the inn.
I sent some guards there.
Yan Xifan was imposed Xi Sui
by others in Shanhai Gang.
He broke through the Force of Spirit.
It took a lot of effort
and he was hurt.
Now there are the best people treating him.
He is fine.
Brother. I…
Lu Ping has been taking care of him for days.
Sang’re.
Peace talks are now starting again.
These things,
are more important than romance.
Don’t worry.
You will meet Lu Ping
later.
What’s wrong with boss?
He asked Ling Ziyan to take care of Xifan
instead of me.
Doesn’t Xifan want to see our friendly faces
when he wakes up?
Am I right, master?
Master?
In fact, in addition to our senior,
I also suffered a lot of injuries
when I went to E’zhou Mansion to save you.
Do you want to take care of me?
You looked all right.
You didn’t even rub your skin.
I have internal injury.
Internal injury.
Master.
Or,
I can take care of you.
Master.
Mo Lin.
I am a little tired.
I want to walk alone.
Master.
I can go with you.
I can even take you to fly
by my Force of Air.
I said,
alone.
Xifan.
Are you all right?
It’s just a little hurt.
Thanks for your care.
Why are you so polite?
It’s no big matter.
What are you talking about?
Senior.
Mo Lin is trying to amuse my sister.
I am tired of taking care of you.
I can’t ask Qin Sang to take care of you.
I can only ask Miss Ling here.
I am all right.
Xifan saved my life
in the breaking the force practice.
Now I am satisfied that
I can do something for him.
It’s my honor.
Thanks, Miss Ling.
You two are polite.
Who do you play for?
Speaking of play,
You two are the best.
When did you two
start the play?
Xifan.
The competition between us.
It’s barbaric to use swords.
Do you remember
when we were in Zhaifeng,
you forced me to study every day?
Lu Ping.
I have no time to gossip with you.
No?
I have to thank you.
I remember the power of six forces
rules because of you.
The power of six forces.
Air, Color, Sound, Spirit,
Heft, Temperature and Air.
Force of Spirit is powerful,
but it can be controlled by the Force of Sound.
As long as the man’s will is strong enough,
he will have the possibility of waking up.
You’ve said,
no one in Zhaifeng could fall behind.
You’re the senior.
You can’t fall behind.
Did you hear me?
Xifan.
Lu Ping.
This time it’s my turn.
Get up.
It’s good to have you back.
No matter how big the mistake is,
as long as we are all here,
we can always find a way.
I will take the charge of murder.
Shanhai Gang wants to provoke a war.
I won’t let the Gang do it.
How about Xu Weifeng?
He is very cautious.
Are you really willing to let him go?
[Peace and Prosperity]
Since Shanhai Gang thought
it has controlled you.
Why don’t you make them happy for a while?
You mean we can work in collusion,
forcing Xu Weifeng and Shanhai Gang to move?
Lu Ping.
I must make Xu Weifeng take the action.
Hold in there.
It’s dangerous.
Thanks to you two
who came up with this idea.
It’s a nightmare to think
that I was hypnotized in Shanhai Gang.
Now I am awake.
Senior.
It’s not a dream.
You can’t feel hurt in dream.
Who makes you use up your strength to be brave?
Now it’s your turn.
Method of Xi Sui in Shanhai Gang could
improve your skill.
But this short-term improvement
will definitely hurt.
As the senior,
I can’t hold you back.
Fine.
Enjoy your hurt.
I won’t forgive you for making up your own mind
next time.
Miss Ling.
I have injuries.
Can you help me to take care of my senior?
Don’t worry.
I can do nothing else.
But I will try my best
to take care of Xifan.
Lu Ping.
I don’t need the care.
Miss Ling.
You know how guilty he was
when you were shot
by Qin Qi
in Kaifeng.
Lu Ping.
Fine, I won’t talk.
I won’t talk.
I will go to rest.
[Peace and Prosperity]
Thanks, Miss Ling.
I can do it myself.
Sorry.
I forgot you are the younger master of Wuji Manor.
You are noble.
I can’t be close.
Miss Ling, don’t get me wrong.
I don’t care about the reputation given by others.
You are my best friend
in my heart.
I am glad to
see you back in one piece.
Really?
I am telling the truth.
Now.
You’re no longer a maid.
Why should I bother you to take care of me?
Since you have said that we are friends,
then I saw that my friend was in trouble,
so I should help to take care of him.
[Peace and Prosperity]
What’s that?
I am glad to
see you back from Shanhai Gang safe.
In my hometown,
the people who come back from the disaster
have to cross the fire pot and stick peach branches
to dispel ghosts and evil spirits.
Am I silly?
No.
I think it’s good.
I wish you peace and prosperity
in your life.
May you have
a bright and happy life.
[E’zhou Post]
Master Xia.
General Qin.
I have told his majesty that
everything that happened recently was
because of my rebellious son.
Now the truth is out.
His majesty still hopes to have peace
with Shuo forever.
That is wise.
It’s really the blessing of Tan.
Your son is really cunning.
I’m afraid we would be under control
by him and Shanhai Gang.
if we hadn’t taken the move.
Thanks to the two young heroes,
Lu Ping and Xifan,
this matter can be solved smoothly.
If two of them didn’t work together,
I don’t know how my son
will do irreparable sin.
Compared with them,
I’m really ashamed.
I’m not good at teaching children.
When the peace talks are over,
I will make a plea to his majesty.
Master Xia was not polite.
I hope it didn’t bother you.
You cherish the country,
and protect the people.
I admire you.
As for your son.
I am sorry for your loss.
Thanks, General Qin.
Now that the document has been exchanged,
I will order the Longjie Army
to leave your country as soon as possible.
I will also tell his majesty
to release the prisoners as soon as possible.
You can also let your subordinates
open the gate to settle the refugees.
General Qin has arranged it properly.
I am willing to help.
Yan Xifan had the crime of conspiracy,
but he was under control of Shanhai Gang’s cult.
He didn’t kill General Xu.
Besides, he made up for it later.
I hope Tan will forgive him.
Yan Jin and Shanhai Gang
had done countless crimes in Shuo.
His majesty wishes to remand him to Kaifeng
for trial.
His majesty has ordered that all matters concerning
the Shanhai Gang be handed
over to your country.
General Qin, please.
Thanks, minister.
How is everything?
The gate will be reopened in two hours.
Thanks.
Lu Ping.
You have made great contributions this time.
Do you only want to open the gate early?
Don’t you ask anything for yourself?
A high official with a high salary.
A fancy mansion.
As long as you want,
I can report to his majesty
and try my best to help you.
I’m free
and well fed now.
What do I want these things for?
I’ve protected the people in this city
from the plot of Shanhai Gang.
Watching them go back home
and have a peaceful life.
I am happy.
After the peace talks between the two countries,
Minister Xu will hold
several celebrations in the city.
At that time, people will go out to celebrate together.
I suggest you
go and have a look.
Go and see
the city and
those people you are trying to protect.
That would be fine.
But
I will be lonely
if I go alone.
Can I take Qin Sang with me?
She likes the celebration.
She must be happy.
You can go alone.
Don’t bring Qin Sang with you.
She is a Miss in Qin Family.
She is a young lady of a noble family.
How could she hang out with you?
Qin Sang wanders all day.
-How could you say that?
-You…
Do whatever I say.
It’s none of your business.
Didn’t you let me ask anything for myself?
I want this.
I am telling you,
I’ll trade my previous credit for Qin Sang
to accompany me out.
If you are worried about us,
you can follow.
I’m the leader of the Longjie Army.
I have many military affairs to deal with.
How can I idle with you?
Right.
You can’t do anything
if you let Qin Sang by your side.
You…
Fine.
For your credit,
just this time.
That’s great.
Thank you, General Qin.
Come out.
He agreed.
I have the best brother in the world.