♪If not for you♪
♪I wouldn't have wanted
to make a name for myself♪
♪Only when I have your love♪
♪Is my invincibility not in vain♪
♪The towering peaks I've conquered♪
♪Leave me♪
♪Feeling empty♪
♪I've given everything♪
♪Just to follow you♪
♪Through life and death♪
♪Could it be that love♪
♪Is the true end of this life♪
♪Why does every battle♪
♪Bring deeper pain♪
♪I never got it♪
♪You once promised me♪
♪You'd give me ordinary days♪
♪Then I'd rather♪
♪Face blades and fall♪
♪Into your arms instead of the clouds♪
♪I'll pass through layers of fog♪
♪And barriers♪
♪The world's rights and wrongs,
wins and losses♪
♪Who's to weigh their worth♪
♪Only love♪
♪Gives me a sky as wide as the sea♪
♪I only want to be your hero♪
=The Prisoner of Beauty=
=Episode 18=
Even so,
I'll agree to neither of them.
Goodbye, My Lady.
Alright.
Let's go.
Father, goodbye.
Lady Qiao left the prefect's mansion
with a big smile.
Right after,
they went to a jewelry shop,
saying they wanted to make
a full set of gold and silver
wedding jewelry.
Ask Yuan Wang to come and see me.
Yes.
General, may I ask
why you summoned me so late?
Today, I received a Go board
and a bridal hair ornament.
Prefect, please take a look.
See if they match
what Lady Qiao promised you.
General, you truly misunderstood.
Her Ladyship did stop by today to discuss
a marriage for my daughter.
Out of respect for our families' agreement
I neither accepted
nor made any promises.
Prefect, save your excuses
for simpletons.
Even if nothing came of today,
what about the silver
and gold sent late at night?
You didn't turn that away,
did you?
Silver and gold? Sent at night?
General,
what do yo mean?
Prefect,
drop the act.
I have already set guards
outside your mansion day and night.
Everything between you two
has been seen clearly.
You...
You had me watched?
I've honored our agreement
and never betrayed you.
This is how you see me?
How you guard against me?
Is this your idea of sincere cooperation?
Don't forget, my troops
are garrisoned in Rongjun,
to keep your family safe.
That's ridiculous!
Our Yuan family has been rooted
in Rongjun for a century.
Why would we need your protection?
Your so-called garrison here is nothing
more than a leash to keep me in check.
I should've seen this sooner.
But better late than never!
So, betrayal was your intention all along?
Says the one with hidden motives!
And what if I do?
Rongjun Prefect left Rongjun in the night,
heading to Wei Dian's place.
The timing couldn't be better.
All we need is one final push.
The arrows we collected
during the previous ambush
can finally be put to use.
Very good.
I'll go myself later.
My Lord?
My wound is healed.
I know my body better than anyone.
I've been stuck in bed for days now.
You won't let me do anything.
I've got it from now on.
You can't go.
I said, I'm fine.
Don't I know my own condition?
You don't.
Wei Qu, what do you say?
Am I fine or not?
So, Wei Qu,
can you really call this fine?
Just say it.
Right now,
I'm not feeling well.
Get back here.
That's enough.
No army sends a foot soldier
while the commander shows up in person.
You can strategize from this very room.
What's going on?
You...
Who are you people?
How dare you attack me on the street?
You betrayed the General.
Have you thought about
what will happen to you?
Kill him.
General Wei Liang! Save me!
Wei Dian,
I knew it was you.
That was too harsh.
Look how scared he is.
Feeling sorry for him, are you?
You almost cut my club in half,
- you know?
- Had to make it real.
Fine, you big oaf.
I'll remember this.
Alright, enough.
Let me help you!
That's not loud enough!
Stop!
General, you...
Are you alright?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Your face is covered in blood.
It's nothing. It's their blood.
Is it?
That's good.
What a relief.
Thank you for saving my life, General.
If not for you,
I...
I'd be dead.
Prefect,
who have you offended?
Who wants you dead?
It's a long story.
General Wei Liang,
I need to see Her Ladyship.
General!
Bad news!
General, Rongjun Prefect
has openly declared his support
for planting winter wheat.
He's even rallied the people.
Many have already joined him.
People are lining up for seeds
outside every house now.
General!
General,
Yuan Wang knows so many of our plans.
Do you think he'll betray us to Wei Shao?
Even if he says nothing,
Wei Shao could still
connect it to me.
All these years, he hasn't
moved against me, not because he didn't
want to, but he didn't dare.
So, how about
we strike first?
Back in the mourning hall,
I should've acted.
General,
it's not too late to decide now.
If canal construction is finalized,
we'll be held back in the future.
They came for the canal and the grain.
They don't have much manpower.
So, that's it?
Only a little force in Rongjun?
Pass on my command.
Gather the troops.
We depart at once.
Yes, General.
Wei Shao, you brat!
Once I'm armored up,
I'll have it out with you!
Why bother with a tough fight?
One slash settles it.
Have a good rest.
From this day forward,
Wei Dian's former troops
are spared from death.
They will be reassigned
to work on the canal.
Once it's complete,
all past offenses will be pardoned.
Thank you, My Lord.
Greetings, My Lord.
Prefect, you've worked hard.
Now that the wheat seeds
are in the hands of the people,
and we have laborers for the task,
the canal will surely
be completed.
Rongjun shall offer
its full strength in support.
However, this land
has long suffered from drought.
We lack experience
in building canals.
Don't worry,
I've already found the right person
to oversee it.
I've worked in flood control for many years.
Now,
the Yongning Canal has been rebuilt,
stretching all the way to Rongjun.
This is a project
for the benefit of generations to come!
Her Ladyship and His Lordship
trust me so deeply.
I will not let them down.
I'll give it my all.
Mayor,
you've been talking all the way.
You've helped with
the Yongning Canal more than once.
It's just one more trip there.
Why are you so excited?
You don't understand.
Back in my youth,
I used to debate with Zhen Zhi,
if the Yongning Canal were to go
beyond just Panyi and Xindu,
where should it lead?
Looking at your face
reminds me so much of Zhen Zhi.
The construction of Yongning Canal,
meant to bring prosperity to both our peoples,
wouldn't be the same with the wrong partner.
There'd be no joy in it.
Never mind, forget it.
I've distanced myself from Xindu
and from Zhen Zhi.
I still don't know
who I'll be working with on this task.
I'm not questioning
Her Ladyship or His Lordship's judgement.
I just want the chance to prove
what I'm capable of.
You'll see once we arrive, Mayor.
Zhen Zhi?
- Goodbye.
- But you just got here.
General, you may not know this,
but I've never gotten along
with that man.
And frankly, I don't
get along with you either.
Back then, we swore we'd never
cross paths again in this lifetime.
If not for
His Lordship's orders that I oversee you,
I wouldn't have come at all.
You? Oversee me?
Come on, Zhen Zhi.
You took twice as long as I did
to build the canal in Xindu,
and now you're going to oversee me?
What a joke. I've got nothing more to say.
General,
you truly don't understand.
I just can't work with him.
It's not that I won't serve Lord of Wei.
I'd like anyone else to oversee me.
I'm leaving.
Why are you doing?
What do you want?
Look.
Look for yourself.
Is this how you ask someone for help?
Don't waste your breath on him.
This person is pure Qiao clan
through and through,
smooth with his words,
but sneaky with his actions.
If you want him to work,
force him.
You shut your mouth.
Every time you open it,
it stinks. I'm leaving anyway.
Mayors.
Greetings, My Lord.
Greetings, Lord of Wei.
No need for formalities.
Fourteen years ago,
you both served my Grandfather.
Together with Lord Qiao,
you built the Yongning Canal,
diverting the Yang River to the Pei River,
ending the drought that struck Wei State.
Now, fourteen years later,
the canal flows again,
thanks to both of you.
But now,
Rongjun faces
the same hardship.
I seek to follow my ancestor's path
and build a new canal.
The Yongning Canal
benefited only Yanzhou and Wei State.
As Xindu and Rongjun
border Bianzhou,
if we succeed,
folk in Bianzhou will benefit as well.
This time,
we set aside borders
and act for the people.
This is a great cause for the good of all.
So, I entrust this task
to you both.
I hope you can work in unity to relieve
the people from the pain of drought.
Here and now,
you have my deepest thanks.
- I will do my utmost.
My Lord, urgent news.
Bianzhou has changed hands.
(Chen Xiang died in Danjun)
Governor of Bianzhou
(Chen Pang takes over.)
died.
(Bianzhou's border, Bianzhou)
Any women in the cart?
My sister and I are returning home
after visiting relatives.
We're just passing through.
May I ask what you want, officers?
No, officer...
Officers, is there
something you require?
Nothing.
Forgive me
for asking, officers.
There are checkpoints along the way,
and searches even stricter.
Are you searching for
someone dangerous?
Not exactly. We're following
General Xue's orders
to find Lady Yulou.
Lady Yulou?
If you see her,
report it at once.
General Xue will reward you well.
May I ask, which General Xue?
Chen Pang has seized power.
Xue Tai, General of Longxiang
in Juejun, has rebelled.
We follow our late lord's orders
seeking Lady Yulou,
to keep her safe...
No need to say more.
We have duties to attend to.
Ma'am, best you be on your way.
Thank you, officers.
Let's go.
Thanks to you both.
Ehuang, Xue Tai doesn't
accept Chen Pang's rule.
Why don't we go to him?
Maybe we can do something.
Don't be reckless again.
Xue Tai is blindly loyal.
He's only
fulfilling Chen Xiang's final wish now.
Claiming to keep me safe
is just for his own reputation.
We should go.
Alright.
Bring me some water.
I need to wipe my face.
Yes.
Ehuang...
Ehuang, don't draw that.
If they find you, they'll
send you back to Yulou Pavilion.
Once we pass Bianzhou, it's Wushan State.
They won't chase us there.
Ehuang, you know
we're arriving at Wushan State.
We have achieved nothing.
How can we return home?
The Su clan of Wushan State
has treated you well all these years.
If not by adoption,
you could at least have formed
an alliance with Bianzhou.
Now Chen Xiang is dead, and Chen Pang
has turned his back on us.
We have nothing left.
If the family blames me,
how am I supposed to explain?
At the end of the day,
you're just a woman.
Painting a penoy doesn't help...
You think I want this?
So?
Now that I've fallen,
you come to lecture me?
I wouldn't dare.
Don't you forget,
you've worked with me
away from home for years.
Whether you'll be the heir back at Su family
is still uncertain.
Pull yourself together!
We're in the same boat.
This huadian I wear
protects more than just myself.
Yes.
(Post House)
I solved you a problem, My Lord.
Is there any reward for me?
Reward?
When Wei Liang faked a marriage proposal
you made a set of gold jewelry.
It's yours now.
When you were ill,
I took such good care of you.
I even schemed to split
Yuan Wang and Wei Dian.
All my efforts were for you.
Now, you're giving me the gift
meant for someone else?
Then what do you want?
My Lord,
haven't you ever thought
of giving me something special?
What a hassle.
I'll think about it.
Why the sudden mood to take us
to the market, My Lord?
I just want to show you
local customs and sights.
As the lord, and you as generals, we should
care about such things.
Yes, My Lord.
We can also buy some local specialties.
Local specialties?
For whom?
Advisor is still guarding Yujun.
You need to wise up.
For Advisor?
A fine ink slab should do.
I suppose
Grandmother would
surely enjoy Rongjun's specialties.
We can bring Lady Xu some ginseng.
What about Yan?
Every time he goes out,
he always brings you gifts.
That's easy. Some wine will do.
Right?
But there's still one more person.
This time, Her Ladyship
played no small role.
She deserves a reward too.
Sure. Got it, My Lord.
Still buying gifts for the others?
My mother says all women love sweets.
We can't get these in Yujun,
perfect for Her Ladyship.
That's lame.
A jade hairpin,
a jingling hairpin with white pearls,
and a kingfisher-blue pin.
I swear, any one
of these would win
her heart instantly.
That's tacky.
That's jewelry!
No ladies would say no to that!
My Lord, Xiaotao told me
Her Ladyship could read by three
and recite poetry by five.
A book would be a good gift.
She could read by three, remember?
How should I know
what she hasn't already read?
I think I know what she likes.
This is for you.
What's this?
Steeds.
Five hundred of them.
(Five hundred fine steeds for Yanzhou.)
Steeds?
This canal construction
is a favor Wei owes Yanzhou.
These five hundred steeds
make it even.
My Lord, what do you think
why would I risk everything
and go through all this?
I understand your intentions.
Yanzhou truly wishes to ally with Wei.
I was too narrow-minded before.
(Five hundred)
But now,
I see your sincerity.
What do you think you're seeing?
What?
You don't like steeds?
I can exchange them.
How about weapons?
Battering rams?
Catapults? Or armor...
Enough. No need.
I like steeds.
They're good.
Horses, huh?
Right?
I can tell,
you do like them.
I really do.
Great.
I do like them.
Steeds are great.
My Lady.
Duang told me
His Lordship gave you five hundred steeds.
Is that true?
His Lordship
is so generous!
I just don't get it.
Tell me, what kind of man
gives his wife steeds as a gift?
But they're practical.
Send them straight back to Yanzhou.
Not everyone can afford such a gift.
Now that's a proper gift
from His Lordship.
Not sure if his wife likes it,
but his father-in-law
must be over the moon.
He really knows how to win favor.
Speaking of gifts,
has Wei Liang ever given you anything?
Here, this is for you.
Why bring him up, My Lady?
Xiaotao.
My Lady, please don't be upset.
It takes time.
You two just need more time together.
Chunniang,
make me some red bean soup.
Yes, My Lady.
What is that, My Lady?
I thought you might be hungry,
so I brought some sweets.
What is that?
It smells so good.
It's golden osmanthus incense.
I used it earlier.
I see, it's the incense.
I thought the smell was from the sweets.
Next time, add some osmanthus.
It'll taste better.
My Lord, you have grown thinner
working so hard on the canal.
It's fine.
This is for people's livelihood.
I can't slack off.
That's true.
Canal construction may seem simple,
but there's much to take into account.
Weather alone, sunny or cloudy,
cold or warm,
can all affect progress.
That much?
Yes.
Back in Yanzhou,
before any digging began,
Grandfather and Uncle would observe the stars
to forecast the weather months in advance.
That's how the work went so smoothly.
But Yang Feng never mentioned
any of that.
He doesn't know that?
Grandfather and Uncle must've
observed the stars themselves.
That's why the overseers weren't aware.
Luckily,
Grandfather taught me well.
I know a bit about star signs.
Shall I join you tonight
to observe them?
That's a good idea.
Let's do it tonight.
Meet me at the observatory at the Xu hour.
I'll find you when I'm done.
Okay.
My Lady, the wind's strong.
You should put this on.
I'm not wearing it.
It will hide my dress. I'm not wearing it.
Is my hair messy?
No.
I told you,
I shouldn't wear this jade hairpin.
The other one was better.
It's so dark out here. He can't see it.
Don't worry, My Lady.
It's clear enough to see.
But,
you and His Lordship have been
spending time together for a while now.
Why are you more nervous than ever?
My Lord.
You can't dress like that in this cold.
Why didn't you wear the cloak you brought?
I... I don't want to wear it.
I don't like wearing it.
You'll catch a cold.
- Put it on.
- I'm not wearing it.
I'm not cold.
Just put it on.
Listen to me.
There. Not cold anymore, huh?
Let's look at the stars.
Alright.
My Lord,
do you see that star up there?
Which one?
That one there.
The brightest one of all.
That's the Ziwei Star.
It's also called Taiyi.
Have you heard of the Five-Star Augury?
I've heard a bit.
The Five-Star Augury
interprets the movements of five stars...
Do you have something on your mind?
No, not really.
It's just that...
I'm sorry for being late.
It's fine.
Lord of Wei, My Lady.
You said we should
watch stars before starting.
So, the overseers
must know the method
to plan ahead.
By the way, where is Xindu Mayor?
You mean Zhen Zhi?
Well, let's not
bring him up.
Lord of Wei, My Lady, what can I do for you?
I've worked with Lord Qiao
for years, so I know a bit
about stargazing.
That's perfect.
Just now, Her Ladyship
mentioned this Five-Star Augury.
Do you know about it?
The Five-Star Augury?
Yes, I know a little bit.
It's about eight thousand characters long,
but it's an important text
on stargazing.
It's divided into two parts.
The first part is about augury...
What's wrong?
My Lady, I believe you've already known it,
so I won't repeat it.
Since His Lordship wants to hear it,
please go ahead.
Don't mind me.
Yes, please continue.
Lord of Wei,
I just noticed
this observatory is old, worn,
and quite cramped.
I'm afraid
it can't really fit three people.
Two would be ideal.
What are you talking about?
It's... It's not cramped at all.
I mean,
stargazing needs peace and quiet.
It can't be too noisy.
So,
two is best.
That's right.
You head back first.
I'll take... I should take my leave.
Today, you have to tell me
what exactly is Five-Star Augury?
Her Ladyship said that star is the Ziwei Star.
It's also called the Taiyi
or something like that.
What does that mean?
The Ziwei Star?
Well, the Ziwei Star...
It's the brightest star in the sky.
It's also known as Taiyi.
This Five-Star Augury
is a treatise
that uses the movement
of the five planets
to divine fortune or misfortune.
For projects like canal construction
or flood control,
we depend on the planetary movements
to decide whether to proceed,
how to proceed,
and whether the timing is auspicious.
So...
(Prefect's Mansion)
My Lord?
Please, My Lord.
Actually, I asked you here today
to request something.
Prefect, rest assured.
Wei Dian's remnants have been cleared.
No one will trouble you again.
Thank you, My Lord.
There...
There's one more thing.
Please, go on.
You know, earlier two generals
came to propose.
My daughter
has feelings for one of them.
Wei Qu is a brave and skilled warrior
in my service.
He's also quite handsome.
- He...
- My Lord,
it's not General Wei Qu.
It's…
General Wei Liang.
Wei…
Liang?
Yes, the mighty General Wei Liang.
I know of he is
your trusted right hand.
My daughter is not worthy.
We dare not dream of such an honor.
But...
But my daughter
has been crying everyday,
saying
she'll marry no one
but the mighty General Wei Liang.
My Lord, I beg of you.
This is a father's humble plea.
As for this matter,
I shall speak with
the mighty General Wei Liang.
Just asking him would mean the world.
Thank you, My Lord.
No, no, no.
- My Lord.
- I should thank you instead.
My Lord, please.
- My Lord, please.
- Please.
I'll down it.
Wei Liang, my boy.
Stop calling me your boy.
Call me bro.
I missed again.
You've got no manners.
Bro!
Look at him.
You hit me dead center.
Stop throwing at me.
I'm cutting patterns here.
No need to ask Wei Liang.
He won't agree.
How do you know?
You're the only one who doesn't know.
Why are you so sure
he won't agree?
If you don't believe me,
go ask him yourself.
Fine, I will.
Sounds like
we're not on the same page.
Let's make a bet.
Okay.
What's the wager?
If you lose,
you'll come with me
to pick out the prize yourself.
Deal.
Wei Liang.
- My Lord.
- Come here.
I've got good news for you.
I met the prefect today.
He wants to marry his daughter to you.
What?
- Isn't it good news?
- I...
I...
She...
Are you happy?
My Lady.
You're back.
No, no way. It's impossible.
Why not?
We're just not a good match.
Wait, come here.
Why aren't you a good match?
What are His Lordship
and Wei Liang whispering?
They seem quite furtive.
Look.
My Lord,
I know you're doing this for me.
- Yes, I am.
- But...
I'm talking to you here!
She's the prefect's daughter.
Why are you turning her down?
I've already given my heart to someone.
I can't love anyone else.
You have? Who's she?
I...
Remember when we took Wei Liang
to the prefect's for the proposal?
Yes.
Wasn't that just to
sow discord between Yuan Wang and Wei Dian?
But who would've thought...
What's wrong?
The prefect's daughter has fallen for him.
She begged His Lordship
to let her marry Wei Liang.
What?
But we...
Yes, I'm doing this for you.
The prefect's daughter is a noble lady.
Listen, I'm talking here.
You know what?
Love takes time to grow.
Him? Wei Liang?
Well,
that's great news.
Great news.
Great news indeed.
If that's the case,
should I go ask
His Lordship to finalize
the marriage right now,
even if Wei Liang doesn't agree?
Finalize it...
The marriage?
But my words don't count.
I'll go boil some water.
Move aside.
Heading for the city gate?
My Lord.
- Tao...
- Step back.
Wait.
We're not done here.
My Lord,
if you're doing this for my sake,
please don't make me marry her.
I'm begging you.
Wait.
At least tell me why.
You know nothing
about love.
It can't be forced.
How about letting one of them marry her?
Come back!
How did you know
he won't agree?
There's a lot you don't know, My Lord.
Fine.
You win.
So, my prize...
Alright.
Tao, let me help you.
I wouldn't dare.
Aren't you the prefect's son-in-law?
You're too important for this.
Don't talk nonsense.
So, you knew?
Of course I did.
That's great news.
The sooner I knew,
the happier I could be for you, General Wei.
How can you be happy for me?
Why not?
Look,
General Wei, right now,
you have great battle merits,
but you're still just a retainer.
Once you marry into Yuan Wang's family,
that's a whole different story.
From now on,
you'll have a beauty by your side
and enjoy a life of wealth and honor.
I'm happy for you.
You're not worried at all?
Why should I be?
Let me...
- Let me.
- No need.
Are you happy now?
You're about to get married.
Why are you still coming to me?
You only know half the story,
not the whole thing.
I've already told His Lordship
I'd never marry her.
If I'd known it'd come to this,
I wouldn't have gone to propose.
All these years,
the four of us have followed
His Lordship through thick and thin,
fighting battles everywhere.
Lost count how many times
we crawled out from piles of bodies.
By watching each other's backs,
we made it this far.
Why are you telling me this?
Alright, alright.
I'll drop it.
The four of us use different weapons.
You know that, don't you?
I do.
So what?
Ten years ago,
His Lordship had a craftsman
make each of us a miniature
golden version of our weapons.
Mine is a small gold dart.
Wei Qu's is
a pair of long and short swords.
Wei Xiao's,
a small gold bow.
Wei Duo's,
a small sword.
I'm not interested
in your man stuff.
To us four,
these miniature weapons
represent who we are.
Every time we go to the battle,
we leave them at home.
We weren't born on the same day,
and I guess
we won't die on the same day either.
But one day,
even if all four of us are gone,
burying these miniature weapons together
will mean we'll always be brothers.
So,
I want you to have this.
♪The moonlight is as silent
as the deep sea♪
♪From afar♪
♪It once lit up dreams with a breath♪
♪But vanished with a sigh♪
♪Brushing past my fingertips♪
♪My heartstrings were stirred quietly♪
♪As if we once met before♪
♪Holding back a love so deep♪
♪Love asks for nothing in the end♪
♪Leaving only obsessions♪
♪I've wandered in the world♪
♪Yet cannot have it all♪
♪We meet and part in the fires of war♪
♪Embracing,
leaving tender marks of love♪
♪With one breathtaking glance♪
♪How could I ever forget♪
♪I would cross mountains and seas♪
♪To spend time with you♪
♪When we grow old♪
♪Nothing will change♪
♪The misty rains never cease♪
♪Falling gently on your brow♪
♪Lingering in my heart♪
♪I would sever fate's ties♪
♪To protect your smiling eyes♪
♪Even if behind me lies a storm♪
♪No matter the trials♪
♪I carry this longing for the journey♪
♪This life♪
♪Will not be in vain♪
♪I would cross mountains and seas♪
♪To spend time with you♪
♪When we grow old♪
♪Nothing will change♪
♪The misty rains never cease♪
♪Falling gently on your brow♪
♪Lingering in my heart♪
♪I would sever fate's ties♪
♪To protect your smiling eyes♪
♪Even if behind me lies a storm♪
♪No matter the trials♪
♪I carry this longing for the journey♪
♪This life♪
♪Will not be in vain♪