♪If not for you♪
♪I wouldn't have wanted
to make a name for myself♪
♪Only when I have your love♪
♪Is my invincibility not in vain♪
♪The towering peaks I've conquered♪
♪Leave me♪
♪Feeling empty♪
♪I've given everything♪
♪Just to follow you♪
♪Through life and death♪
♪Could it be that love♪
♪Is the true end of this life♪
♪Why does every battle♪
♪Bring deeper pain♪
♪I never got it♪
♪You once promised me♪
♪You'd give me ordinary days♪
♪Then I'd rather♪
♪Face blades and fall♪
♪Into your arms instead of the clouds♪
♪I'll pass through layers of fog♪
♪And barriers♪
♪The world's rights and wrongs,
wins and losses♪
♪Who's to weigh their worth♪
♪Only love♪
♪Gives me a sky as wide as the sea♪
♪I only want to be your hero♪
=The Prisoner of Beauty=
=Episode 2=
Something bad happened in Xindu.
14 years ago,
tens of thousands were buried here.
No need to discuss this further.
If Yanzhou
has no sincerity,
then you may leave
and take her back.
But this marriage
is my grandmother's wish.
So,
if you want it to happen,
the wedding must be held in Panyi.
- Tan.
- Yes.
Give the gift I prepared
to Miss Xiaoqiao.
Yes.
(Panyi Annals, Yanzhou)
My Lady,
if you ask me,
the Lord of Wei does like you.
Why don't you follow their arrangement,
(Culture)
hand over the seal of Panyi,
(Introduction)
and marry him soon?
This gift doesn't mean he likes me.
It's a threat.
(Panyi)
He's long had his eye on Panyi.
Even if I don't give it to him,
he'll take it through war.
Exactly.
So,
handing it over
doesn't really matter.
The dignified Lord of Wei
wouldn't go back on his word, right?
The feud between us
was caused by a broken promise, right?
To find a way out of this game,
we must find his weakness
and figure out what he truly wants.
(Yuyang Courtyard, Wei State)
What kind of person is Wei Shao?
He is
narrow-minded
and ruthless.
Let me tell you.
(Chunniang, Xiaoqiao's wet nurse)
This is not like home.
You must speak and act with caution.
Don't worry, Mother.
Look where you're going.
Can't you see we're carrying things?
What's that smell on him?
It's not from me;
it's from the chest.
Inside is Li Su.
Nonsense.
Li Su is tall and strong.
How could he fit in a chest?
Even Li Su didn't believe it at first
until he saw his own hands and feet
cut off
and placed inside piece by piece.
Then he believed it.
Look.
Generals,
we're new here and don't know the rules.
Please forgive us.
Forgive us.
Let me tell you.
The Lord
is not someone easy to deal with.
If you don't want to end up like Li Su,
learn the rules.
This chubby little girl
even threw up.
Li Su
killed three generations of their family
and slaughtered Xindu City.
Whatever happens to him
is no surprise.
To know how broad-minded he is,
you must see how he treats the people.
He treats them poorly too.
I heard people say...
The Lord has ordered
that from today onward,
everything
like this
is forbidden here.
Anyone who disobeys
will be punished severely.
Even praying for blessings
is not allowed?
How does he treat those close to him?
Suspicious.
I heard that the Lord of Wei
kills people in his sleep.
He never lets anyone near him
while he sleeps.
I think
he's just afraid of being assassinated.
Who is it?
I'm Wei Xiao.
My Lord,
the candle inside has gone out.
Shall we add more oil?
No need.
Come here.
Are you stupid?
The Lord sleeping with the lights on
is not something
he wants others to know.
The Advisor said
we should act like we know nothing.
It must be hard on the Lord.
He was locked in that tiny wooden box.
If it were me,
I'd be afraid not just of the dark
but of the wood itself.
Say something, okay?
I can't even beat a word out of you.
Maybe if we speak louder,
the Lord won't be scared anymore.
It's like I'm talking to a wall.
My Lord.
- My Lord.
(Grain)
You haven't finished counting
the households?
Leave.
My Lord,
the people of Xindu
suffered under Li Su for years.
They're still watching and waiting.
We'll need more patience.
- Where is this place?
- Is that Mrs. Wei?
- The people say
- Yes.
this is called Tan Terrace.
You can see all of Xindu from the top.
What a pity
it's now in ruins.
Let's go up and take a look.
Mrs. Wei,
the terrace has long fallen
into disrepair.
Be careful climbing up.
You can't call her that yet.
Our lady hasn't married the Lord of Wei.
Then when will you marry?
Please marry soon.
Yes, with a wedding,
the Lord of Wei
won't slaughter the city.
These days, he's counting households
so he can kill off all the migrants
from the border regions.
- That's right.
- Yes, Miss.
Please save us.
The roadblocks are enough,
but if the arrow towers
were a little taller,
the view would be better.
Look.
There's a woman in red up there.
That's Lady Qiao, right?
Yes, that's her.
Just like the rumors say,
she's beautiful as a flower.
Do you think
the Lord of Wei will like her?
When will they get married?
If they wed,
there won't be any more war here.
Showing off.
She's just pretty.
My Lady.
Xindu is truly in ruins.
So, you'll marry the Lord of Wei
in Panyi just like he wants?
We'll marry here in Xindu.
I think I've found the way out.
- Sir, give me a little money.
- Get lost.
Are you all right?
Thank you, Miss.
There's a deep pothole on East Street.
Our lady's carriage can't get through.
Is there anyone kind enough
to help clear the road?
Each helper will receive
five pecks of flour.
I'm willing to go.
We're all willing.
We're willing to go.
We all want to help.
My Lord,
the people have gone
to repair the streets.
Why?
They say Lady Qiao paid them generously.
My Lord,
the people have gone to repair the well.
Really?
Why would they dig a well for no reason?
Come on.
Everyone, eat up.
To thank everyone
for fixing the roads,
Miss Xiaoqiao prepared a meal for you.
She's so kind.
- She's used
- She gave us food and money.
- to drinking well water.
- How kind.
But the wells in the city
have been dry for days.
It's all right. Don't worry.
We'll fix it together.
- Shall we?
- Yes.
Will we be paid for digging the well?
- Of course.
- Eat up.
We wouldn't dare
trouble you for nothing,
would we?
That's wonderful.
I heard Lady Qiao also loves flowers.
Many people picked wildflowers
to give her.
(Grain)
Lady Qiao is truly something.
Shortly after she came,
Tan Terrace was restored,
and the roads were cleared.
Even the weeds and wildflowers
along the roadside
have been mostly cleaned out.
(Yuyang Courtyard)
(Changqing)
I hope Miss Xiaoqiao likes them.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
I hope Miss Xiaoqiao likes them.
This is way too much.
Stop them from sending more.
Flowers are of no use.
People like them
because they long
for what they represent.
Are you trying to say
the people love you
because they long for you too?
I didn't mean that.
The people treat me kindly
because they long for you,
waiting to see what you want.
Everyone knows
I'm a Qiao from Yanzhou.
Compared to the people from the border,
I'm the one
you despise most.
If you can set aside past grudges
and marry me,
it means you're magnanimous.
Then the people will no longer fear you
and will follow you.
You're good with words,
twisting things around
just to get me to marry you.
This is the will of the people.
So why not go with the people's will
and hand over the seal of Panyi to me
so we can get married soon?
Xindu has always been part of Wei.
I share the people's will and purpose.
Li Su was the first to sow discord,
and now you play mind games.
You both disgust me.
Don't think for a second
that I'm as easy to fool
as my grandfather.
As for the seal,
I suggest you make your decision soon.
I have some patience
but
not much.
The Lord of Wei
really is cold as stone.
If he were so easily persuaded,
it wouldn't be trustworthy.
So,
what do we do now?
My heart is like water,
and water wears down stone.
Turns out Lady Qiao is pretty tough.
The Lord fought day and night
just to reclaim Xindu.
Those flowers should be offered to him.
The Lord doesn't care for flowers.
Otherwise, he'd be like a weak woman.
Right.
Lady Qiao has managed to do
what the Lord has failed.
That's what's bothering him.
Good for you.
You're usually like a mute,
but now you've hit the nail on the head.
Hey, give it to me.
- Whoa.
- Catch it.
My Lord, please spare us.
We didn't see you there
and offended you.
Are those flowers meant for Lady Qiao?
They are for you, My Lord.
You're a renowned
brave fighter.
I...
I heard
you'll be the new lord of Xindu,
and Lady Qiao is to be your wife.
So, I passed them to her.
Fine, hand them here.
I'll hold them for the Lord.
From now on,
don't bring useless things like this.
- Go now.
- Yes.
Thank you, My Lord.
Who says the Lord doesn't have
the people's support?
Seems to me the commoners know
who their lord is.
Then why won't they come and register
to collect their food?
Give them more time.
The thick ice didn't freeze in a day.
I've got some patience left.
Let's go.
Hyah.
Mayor.
Help us.
Wei Shao's killing people
in the streets on horseback.
They've been counting households
every day
just so they can kill
all of us border folk.
They're trying to steal our food.
Even good families can't protect
(Zhen Mansion)
their daughters anymore.
Yeah, they treat lives like weeds.
Xindu has changed hands.
I'm no longer your mayor.
Though you have reclaimed lost land,
the people of Xindu today
are no longer subjects of Wei.
You wish to win them over quickly,
but they've been poisoned
by Li Su's lies.
They may not understand
your intentions at once.
Besides,
you didn't take Xindu
just to get revenge.
You have greater ambitions
and will need the people's help.
My Lord,
governing people is like managing water.
You can't rush it.
Now, let's see who runs out
of patience first between me and her.
(People's Wall, Wei State)
Back in the battle of Xindu,
countless families
lost their sons and husbands.
After Li Su entered the city,
he forbade the people
from collecting the bodies
and burying their loved ones.
So, whenever the people
could leave the city,
they would sneak out
to the eastern battlefield
to find their relatives' belongings,
hide them in their clothes,
and smuggle them back in.
This wall
was built from those very keepsakes.
But
as the years passed,
people gradually turned this place
into a shrine for prayers,
forgetting
(Nanny Zhong, Lady Xu's maid)
its true meaning.
To the people, this wall is a place
to grieve their loved ones.
To the Lord,
it's a memorial to the dead.
I came to Xindu this time
to ensure the marriage
between you and the Lord,
so Lady Xu can be at peace.
This is a wishing plate.
May your marriage
go smoothly.
Thank you.
(Stay united as one;
do not part in anger)
(Stay in health; grow old together)
Where's Wei Duo?
Didn't I order all this cleared away?
Why is it still here?
My Lord,
the people have kept this habit
for over a decade.
It's understandable
they can't change overnight.
What are you doing here?
My Lord.
I'm praying for the people.
Praying?
Do you know what this place is
and why this wall
was built?
How can you let her pray here?
How many of you still remember
why this wall exists
and who should be responsible for it?
Come on.
Take all this down and burn it.
Burn it all.
- My Lord, please don't.
- You can't burn it.
My Lord, you can't burn it.
You're ruthless.
You're not fit to rule Xindu.
You don't deserve it.
My Lord,
Zhen Zhi used to work for the late lord.
When Xindu fell,
he surrendered to Li Su
to protect the people.
My Lord, please calm your anger.
My Lord, please spare the mayor.
Please spare the mayor.
He's a good man.
The Lord watched with his own eyes
as his father, brothers, and people
were slaughtered.
How can he let that go so easily?
That's exactly why Lady Xu
wants to forge
a marriage alliance with Yanzhou.
Lady Xu feels sorry
for the Lord.
She hopes he can move on
and live with less pain.
My Lady, what are you thinking?
I think I know what he needs.
Li Su was a thief,
and you, Wei Shao,
are no better.
Back then, Li Su's army
pillaged the city for grain.
Now, you take control of Xindu
and force the people
to offer food, wine, and women.
How are you any different from Li Su?
Yes, you're just like him.
Exactly the same.
The late lord was a righteous man.
You are
unworthy to be his heir.
My life is nothing,
but I pity...
What a pity that Xindu
has fallen into a bandit's hands.
My Lord,
kill this man now.
We can't let him confuse the public.
Yes, My Lord.
Yes. Let's Kill him.
- Kill him.
- We can't let him live.
My Lord,
if you kill Zhen Zhi,
everything we've worked for
will be ruined.
Please punish him severely.
We fought so hard for Xindu.
Was it for these people
to insult even our ancestors?
My Lady, must you go?
This could put you in danger.
My Lord,
you must execute him.
- Kill him, My Lord.
- Just say the word.
I have something to say to the Lord.
Just in time.
Let her in.
This started because of you.
Aren't you going to say anything?
I just did a divination.
The wedding date is in three days.
If we miss it,
we'll have to wait a long time.
You keep delaying the marriage
because you just took control of Xindu
and have been busy rebuilding it.
But now, the people
don't obey you
or listen to your orders.
Will you have your soldiers
spend their days
making bricks and mortar?
I have a plan
to ease your troubles.
Most of Xindu's people
are migrants from the borderlands.
Since they refuse to submit,
why not
make an example of them?
Kill one to warn the rest.
If one's not enough, kill ten.
If ten's not enough, kill a hundred.
Keep killing until they obey.
You...
You venomous woman.
With this,
we can marry sooner.
As expected
of that jerk's granddaughter.
You wicked thing.
Last night he tried to kill the Lord,
and now he dares insult me.
We can't let him live.
We don't have to slaughter the city,
but at least his entire clan
should be executed
to eliminate future threats.
How vicious.
My Lady...
My Lord.
If I follow your advice,
how would I be any different from Li Su?
Your grandfather's betrayal
brought me to ruin.
And now you try to sway me
into slaughtering a city
for your sake?
You viper.
That's right. She's a viper.
- Kill her.
- That viper. Kill her.
My Lord,
please calm yourself.
Kill her.
Please calm yourself.
I was ignorant.
Please forgive me.
I will never forgive you.
You're so cruel.
You will not meet a good end.
You won't meet a good end.
This started because of Lady Qiao.
I will never fall for her schemes
to turn me against the people of Xindu.
As for the mayor...
You only pleaded for the people.
You're blameless.
Please rise.
My Lord,
you're just like the late lord.
After 14 years of Xindu
under the enemy's rule,
at last, we are back.
The Lord is righteous
and cares for his people.
Thank you, My Lord.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
Luckily, the Lord is sensible.
Otherwise, the whole city
would've suffered for her.
So what if she's pretty?
- Get lost.
- That viper.
She's so cruel.
Indeed.
What's going on?
My Lord, you may not know.
The people surrounded Yuyang Courtyard.
Lady Qiao couldn't go back
so she had to hide on the Tan Terrace.
She's not so pretty.
It's just rumors.
I think she's just average.
Actually, she's kind of ugly.
Can you tell from here?
Why say she's ugly?
My Lord,
you mustn't marry this woman.
Send her away from Xindu now.
You may leave.
The Lord
will decide.
- Yes.
- Let's go.
Let's go now.
Let's go.
Let's go back.
You are so different
from earlier.
I know you put on that act
to help me out of trouble.
But what I hate most
is how your family
manipulates people at every turn,
always scheming,
thinking you can
control everyone.
Yet you don't know
that heaven follows rules
but people don't.
Still,
you're a bit better
than your grandfather.
At least you paid a price
for the show.
(Healing Powder)
Apply this on your neck.
My Lord.
I haven't congratulated you
on gaining the people's trust.
Nanny Zhong got this for me.
You should have it.
(Stay united as one;
do not part in anger)
What does this mean?
You're too young to get it.
It's about a couple
staying united forever.
What does it actually mean?
Say something.
(Stay united as one;
do not part in anger)
Next.
- Take it.
- Thanks.
Thank you. Thank you.
(Grain)
My Lord, thank you for the food.
Thank you, My Lord.
They'll all get some.
(Out for today)
That's all for today.
Come back tomorrow.
Out again?
It's out again?
- Don't push.
- I didn't get it yesterday.
- I still didn't get it today.
Please give me some.
There's no food left at home.
Don't push.
Step back. Don't push.
What's going on?
The food ran out again today.
- Don't push.
- It's out.
There are too many people.
My Lord.
My Lord, please help us.
Everyone, everyone.
Please listen.
To prevent panic,
we distribute a certain amount
of food regularly every day.
If it's not enough,
we'll increase the supply.
Lies. Just give us food.
Give us food.
You will get it.
Please be patient.
I promise you.
No one will go hungry.
For today, please return home.
Alright. We trust you.
Come back tomorrow.
Fine. We trust the Lord of Wei.
- Thanks, My Lord.
- Thanks.
My Lord,
we got the people's trust too soon.
They all came rushing for food.
Once we counted, we realized
there were far more refugees
than expected.
Are you saying
the grain we brought from Wei
isn't enough?
This year's drought
has left all of Wei short on food.
The disaster relief grain we brought
was scraped together
by cutting rations across every region.
It'll be hard to get more.
But I already promised
that every household in Xindu
would have food.
My Lord,
there's a city
within reach.
(Panyi Annals)
Wei Liang.
Pull.
One, two, three.
I heard the Lord of Wei gave
all the army's provisions to the people.
Maybe he's not as ruthless
or vengeful
as we thought.
Even so,
if I give up Panyi,
I'll have nothing left to rely on.
My Lady,
the Lord of Wei has torn down
the People's Wall.
That wall was built
with the lives of the people of Wei.
But now,
it's become a symbol of hatred.
Instead of letting it keep you in fear,
I'd rather take it down.
I've suffered the pain
of losing loved ones,
so I won't let you suffer it again.
So, starting today,
the grudges from 14 years ago
are erased.
Whether you're from Yanzhou,
Bianzhou,
or Liangya,
from now on,
you are people of Xindu.
That's wonderful.
We finally have a home.
The Lord of Wei is so righteous.
Lord Zhen,
you risked your life
to speak up for the people.
It's admirable.
So, from now on,
Xindu will still be
under your governance.
Wei Qu.
As you wish,
My Lord.
Thank you, My Lord.
Starting today,
the soldiers of Wei
will work side by side
with the people of Xindu
to rebuild this city,
so you can once again
live and work in peace.
Live and work in peace.
Give out the food.
(Out for today)
This can't be delayed any longer.
My Lord, please marry
Miss Xiaoqiao at once.
My Lord,
Miss Xiaoqiao is here.
Perfect timing.
The Advisor and I were just discussing
our marriage.
My Lord.
Miss Xiaoqiao, is there
something urgent you need?
On my way back from the post house,
I saw people still had no food.
But Panyi has food.
It could ease your urgent need.
You love the people like your children.
I'm sure one day
you'll treat the people
of Panyi as your own.
I'm willing to offer my entire fortune.
I only hope you'll accept me
and forge an alliance for the people.
We're not even married yet.
Why do you trust me so?
Because you're kind.
Kind?
You think I'm gullible, don't you?
Your family is far too naive.
Do you think a betrothal
can wipe out 14 years of hatred?
Do you really believe you're so stunning
that you could enchant me?
Qiao Gui is so scheming.
He planned this well.
He thinks he could send
his granddaughter here
to put on a gentle and sweet act
so I'd ally myself with Yanzhou.
Was this how he fooled
my grandfather back then?
Let me tell you.
Being fooled by your family once
was already enough.
♪The moonlight is as silent
as the deep sea♪
♪From afar♪
♪It once lit up dreams with a breath♪
♪But vanished with a sigh♪
♪Brushing past my fingertips♪
♪My heartstrings were stirred quietly♪
♪As if we once met before♪
♪Holding back a love so deep♪
♪Love asks for nothing in the end♪
♪Leaving only obsessions♪
♪I've wandered in the world♪
♪Yet cannot have it all♪
♪We meet and part in the fires of war♪
♪Embracing,
leaving tender marks of love♪
♪With one breathtaking glance♪
♪How could I ever forget♪
♪I would cross mountains and seas♪
♪To spend time with you♪
♪When we grow old♪
♪Nothing will change♪
♪The misty rains never cease♪
♪Falling gently on your brow♪
♪Lingering in my heart♪
♪I would sever fate's ties♪
♪To protect your smiling eyes♪
♪Even if behind me lies a storm♪
♪No matter the trials♪
♪I carry this longing for the journey♪
♪This life♪
♪Will not be in vain♪
♪I would cross mountains and seas♪
♪To spend time with you♪
♪When we grow old♪
♪Nothing will change♪
♪The misty rains never cease♪
♪Falling gently on your brow♪
♪Lingering in my heart♪
♪I would sever fate's ties♪
♪To protect your smiling eyes♪
♪Even if behind me lies a storm♪
♪No matter the trials♪
♪I carry this longing for the journey♪
♪This life♪
♪Will not be in vain♪