LEE SI-AN
CHUNG YOU-JIN
KIM MIN-SEOL
BAE JI-YEON
KIM HYE-JIN
KIM A-RIN
PARK HAE-LIN
KIM TE-HWAN
KOOK DONG-HO
JANG THEO
KIM JEONG-SU
YUK JUN-SEO
AN JONG-HOON
SINGLE'S INFERNO
I'd like to go to Paradise with…
Lee Si-an.
No way.
- Lee Si-an.
- What?
See! I told you.
Oh…
- She got excited too soon.
- He's solidifying it.
If he was gonna do this,
why'd he ask her in the first place?
He got Min-seol all excited for nothing.
This just means Si-an
is the one who has his heart.
- No way.
- My hands are sweaty.
- Have fun again.
- Seriously.
Whoa, that's crazy.
I've got goosebumps.
Gosh.
Let's go.
- Right away?
- Yeah, right now.
Okay.
All black.
Wow, Paradise two days in a row.
I wonder what we're doing today.
- Something different.
- You think?
- Yeah.
- I hope so.
You said I'd be the one to go this time!
- I really thought so.
- I know.
I mean, they went yesterday.
I thought it'd be me.
I was sure since they just went,
but I guess was wrong.
What's happening?
I can't wait to see
who Jeong-su will choose.
I know. Since Si-an's already taken.
Next is the second-place winner,
Kim Jeong-su.
Please choose the person
you'd like to go to Paradise with.
I'd like to go to Paradise with…
I wonder what he'll do now.
- He's gone pale.
- Who will he choose?
- I wonder who Jeong-su will choose.
- Hae-lin?
- Hae-lin.
- Hae-lin or Hye-jin.
It's Hae-lin.
Two guys went with her before,
he didn't get one-on-one time.
I'd like to go to Paradise with…
Chung You-jin.
- Chung You-jin.
- What?
- Huh?
You-jin?
Chung You-jin.
Hurry up! Just go on.
You've packed your stuff?
- Good thing you dressed up.
- Go, go, go.
- Have fun there.
- What is this?
Unreal.
Gosh, I guess Jeong-su must've thought
I was a lot of fun yesterday.
Was she that fun?
She must've been super fun
if he picked her this time.
You-jin's cheerful.
Well, if I chose Hae-lin or Hye-jin,
they might sense my uneasiness.
If I had chosen one of them,
I felt like I would've needed
to apologize to them
for being my second choice, in a way.
So I just wanna go with You-jin
'cause she's fun to be with.
- Hi.
Let's go.
Let's go, Donald Duck.
- May I?
- What? It's okay…
- The heavy one.
- It's not that heavy.
- Oh, then…
- Not too heavy, right?
- I'll still carry it for you.
- Thank you.
- This is insane.
- Wow.
You-jin must be shocked.
Like, "Why me?"
Wow, it's getting really fun.
I know, right?
Lastly, the third-place winner,
Kim Te-hwan.
I'm wondering
if he'll choose Ji-yeon or not.
And if he doesn't,
then I'll be even more curious.
I didn't think I should be the one going
to Paradise with him today.
We just went to Paradise yesterday,
so it would be better for us
to confirm our feelings for each other
by taking it easy,
rather than going there twice in a row.
I think Te-hwan will choose Ji-yeon again,
despite all that she's been telling him.
- You think?
- Yeah.
To be honest,
he doesn't have any other options.
He doesn't.
No one else
has had even the thing with Te-hwan.
- No one.
There's no one!
I'd like to go to Paradise
with Bae Ji-yeon.
- Bae Ji-yeon.
- What?
- I knew it.
- Wow.
Now this should be a good thing
for her, obviously.
- You think she'll be happy?
- Yeah. Right, she should be.
- Bae Ji-yeon.
- What?
I'm not curious about pursuing anyone here
other than Ji-yeon.
I don't think I'd enjoy Paradise
with anyone else.
- Hi.
Hi.
Oh…
Oh, thanks.
I gave it a lot of thought,
but it was just…
Go on.
Didn't wanna mess
with your head.
His feelings for her are solid.
This will seal the deal for Ji-yeon.
Choosing her despite suggesting
he choose someone else,
well, that's the cherry on top.
You think so?
Judging by what Ji-yeon said earlier,
I think Te-hwan
might've made the wrong decision.
Really? In what sense?
She needed to take a step back
to see what's she's feeling.
She say what she needed
in a roundabout way
without hurting his feelings.
But now that Te-hwan has chosen her again,
they're going to spend more time together,
which means…
she's not going to get that space
she's been needing.
This could make things
a bit uncomfortable for Ji-yeon?
As far as Ji-yeon's concerned,
I think she would've been fine regardless.
Whether she got chosen or not,
she would've been fine.
Yeah.
Anyhow, Jun-seo is going back to Paradise
with Si-an once again.
I do think today's trip
will solidify things for Si-an as well.
They might end up having
the best chemistry in Paradise today.
Yeah.
I'm concerned for Min-seol.
Imagine how whiny she'll become.
I have a feeling
she'll complain.
True.
I even picked a pretty outfit.
I'm going to lunch in this.
I refuse to change.
It really is pretty,
and it screams Paradise.
Seriously, I thought
I would be going today.
I saved this outfit for Paradise!
- Change already.
- I told you she'd get whiny.
When she speaks,
it's almost like a bird chirping.
- Oh, dear.
- She's adorable.
I saved this outfit for Paradise!
What did I ever do to you?
- I'm just talking to myself.
- Jun-seo!
Goodbye, you jerks.
Look at those
two miserable bags left on the ground.
Man, this is so sad.
- What even is this?
- What happened?
Sit down first.
- I thought he'd choose you.
- I thought so too.
Let me tell you exactly
what we talked about.
I won't embellish on any details
or leave anything out.
Okay.
The first thing he asked me
was how I was doing,
if I was getting the hang of things here.
Uh-huh.
I said I was having fun.
Then, he asked if I had any concerns.
So I said no and we just kept talking.
He then asked,
"Do you wanna go to Paradise?"
- I said, "I want to."
- You made yourself clear.
I said, "Yeah,
I really wanna go."
I asked about his trip with Si-an,
and he said
it was "just dinner and drinks."
He went there just for dinner.
He said, "I just went there to eat."
Wait, he said that?
I was like, "You promised to drink whiskey
with me on our next trip to Paradise.
How dare you drink whiskey without me?"
But he told me,
"I didn't have Johnnie Walker, though."
I read into his words again.
I thought he meant
he wanted to drink it there with me.
You've heard it all. What do you think?
Wait, did I read it wrong?
- Oh, gosh. That poor, sweet girl.
- They can't lie. They just can't.
Like when you have a crush,
you gather a couple of friends,
and you question them
until you get the answers you want.
- And it makes your friends suffer.
- Right.
They do look like they're suffering.
Wasn't that conversation hinting
that we'd go together?
I don't think…
I mean, I really enjoyed talking to him.
Hmm…
Let them do what they want.
I refuse to be played around with.
Sorry, but no.
Why would I do that to myself?
It's like he wants to…
I mean, she's saying all this now,
but if he asks for a chat
when he gets back,
she's going to say yes.
- Like, "Hold on."
- "How annoying." While putting lipstick.
"One second."
It's so cute how she can't play coy.
Seriously, she can't hide it.
- I'm not that obvious.
- You are.
- Am I really?
- Yeah.
As soon as he came,
you started adjusting yourself.
I had to since I was lying like this.
I saw you starting to smile,
and you were like, "Come in."
I really thought I was going though.
Well, in any case,
I can tell she's frustrated.
I bet she'll keep talking about it
with her friends today.
- "Guys, don't you think it's weird?"
- "He likes Johnnie Walker."
They filmed this last year.
Let's go!
- Oh!
- They're sitting next to each other!
- What's this?
- Oh…
What?
- Can you hear me?
Ah!
- Can't you hear me?
Are you insane?
Jeong-su looks bothered.
Si-an seems unbothered,
but she actually is.
Yeah, I agree with you.
She can see him
out of the corner of her eye.
Exactly.
Yeah, I still see Jin-kyung like this.
We're here.
- What?
- Wait, what?
Jun-seo's letting his guard down.
What is happening?
- Huh?
I said, have fun.
Okay, got it.
He's cute.
- He couldn't hear them.
- He heard nothing at all.
PARADISE
KIM JEONG-SU & CHUNG YOU-JIN
- Let's go.
Vroom, vroom.
- Vroom, vroom. Let's go.
- Vroom, vroom.
- Let's do this.
- You opening the door for me?
- Yeah, go on in.
- Thank you.
- But you have to close the door.
- Sure, I'll do it.
- I'm just playing.
- Okay, thank you.
Okay.
Off we go.
Let's go pig out!
Nice!
Come on!
"Let's go pig out!"
"Let the food therapy begin!"
Learn from them.
We should be able to do that.
- Come on.
- Gosh.
"Vroom, vroom."
Oh.
Wow, we're finally here.
- Food. I'm so stoked.
- Me too.
Bon appétit.
- Let's just focus on eating.
- Yeah, sure.
I'd love that.
But since you came here because you won,
the food must be like heaven to you.
- Me?
- You conquered this Paradise trip.
I needed to get out of Inferno.
Mm…
Honestly.
- My head was spinning yesterday.
- Hmm.
Having to choose
whether we like someone or not in a day,
that's really not an easy thing to do.
I know.
Right now, my number one pick is…
- Who?
- Si-an.
Mm-hmm.
So, if I had placed first today
in the game…
I honestly would've chosen Si-an.
I was hoping
to have a real conversation with her…
since it's hard to find a moment
to chat with her.
Mm-hmm.
Hmm…
But then, somehow…
you were able to help me
clear my head quite a bit.
- Is it the talking that I do?
- I mean it, seriously.
I just thought, like,
"This person's words
are wholesome and sincere."
You mean it?
Yeah, I do.
- Reason I chose you…
- Yeah?
…is because I just wanted to have fun
with someone as sweet as you
and clear my head
on this trip while I can.
Hm.
And I think I did the right thing.
I'm happy that I chose you.
Hm.
It's like…
The closer we get to the end,
the more my head hurts.
It builds…
It's hard, since this is
all about our emotions, you know?
I can put up with the physical exhaustion,
but the mental stuff
is really getting hard to handle.
Right.
Mm.
Now that we've gotten
to see him talk about Si-an,
it's pretty obvious
that he only has her in his heart.
Looks like it.
- I don't think there's space for Hae-lin.
- No one.
Feelings grow
the more you talk about someone.
He's opening up to her,
as if he's doing a confessional.
It's making him realize he's on Si-an.
He keeps missing his chances
to be with her because she's so popular,
these situations are making
his feelings for her grow even more.
I have another question.
What do you like about Si-an?
Like, what is it?
Let me be really, really honest with you.
My first Paradise trip…
My very first one was with her.
And we just…
kept having conversations
about love together.
And talking about such topics with her
made my heart race, so…
Mm.
I used to date pretty casually
and carefree.
I'd say,
"I don't have a romantic bone in me."
"Gosh, I'm just hopeless."
I used to say that.
But then, my heart raced
when I was with her, which surprised me.
I thought, "Wait.
So I still do have a romantic bone in me."
But Si-an does have
a lot of qualities that,
I would say,
most men would find attractive.
- Just like I do.
- Mm-hmm.
Like what?
She's got those slightly feline features,
but her smile is totally disarming.
She looks kind.
When she smiles, I mean,
you couldn't look kinder than that.
Yeah, I can see that.
But she's scary
when she makes a straight face.
Looks-wise, a lot of men
find that quality charming.
Mm…
When we first talked,
I felt like she really put me at ease.
Mm…
But then again, I sensed
that she could be pretty stubborn too.
Ah, I see.
That's how I feel.
So…
I wanted to talk with her more,
which unfortunately didn't happen.
But I like it this way.
Because you get time
to organize your thoughts?
No, I'm having so much fun
hanging out with you.
It's so fun.
- You're so harmless.
- Why is that?
Like an Oompa-Loompa.
I'd like to make you this small
and carry you on my shoulder like this.
This small?
- Then you'd chitter chatter away all day.
- For sure. Chitter chatter.
You'd sit harmlessly on my shoulder
and talk until I say,
"Be quiet."
- "Shh."
- Ah, that's funny.
Jeong-su sure does seem at ease.
- I'm finding this side of him attractive.
- Yeah, me too.
When he was with Si-an or other girls,
I was like,
"Gosh. What's wrong with this guy?"
But just now,
when he was talking with You-jin,
I feel like his demeanor with her
was really charming.
Yeah.
Now that I think about it,
Jeong-su seemed very experienced at first,
but maybe that was just him being nervous.
So, he was probably making a big effort
to fully focus on the experience.
PARADISE
YUK JUN-SEO & LEE SI-AN
- Wow.
- This has a unique look.
It does.
Thank you so much.
Wow.
Do I look better with my hair down?
I think you look better
with your hair down.
You give off a different vibe
with your hair up.
Let's go.
Thoughts on coming back in just ten hours?
Has it been ten hours already?
Yeah.
I thought it was less.
I know.
I'm so tired today though.
Well, you had to exert yourself.
How many matches did you have?
I only played three.
- Only three?
- Yeah.
The streets are so confusing
and there's too many cars.
Do you have a feline or puppy face?
What do you think?
Feline?
Yep, that's right.
Yes! I got it right.
And you…
You just kind of look like a beast.
Why do you keep calling me a beast?
Beast.
Oh!
- Wow.
- Gosh! This is insane.
Oh!
- No way.
- Oh, my gosh.
Seriously, what is this?
- Today's the real deal.
- It's the best one yet.
Thank you.
Eat up.
- What should I have?
- Wow.
For the winner.
- Help yourself.
- Thanks.
Some wasabi.
Do you like wasabi?
It's not bad,
and it goes well with beef.
Mm…
- Wow…
- Wow.
- Hmm. Jun-seo.
- Yeah?
- Is it radish? Radish?
- Try this.
No, well, don't…
Whoa. They've become really close.
You see, watching those two
make physical contact,
those aren't something you see with people
who are just getting to know each other.
Those two actually feel like a couple.
Spending the night together
made them close.
Even in the car earlier,
making physical contact like this is…
Oops, sorry.
A puppy.
No, I…
- Jin-kyung…
- She rested her chin on her hand.
You were so surprised.
It happened so quickly.
- These physical…
- That physical touch…
Or how he had his arm around her
while entering the restaurant.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Or how she spoon-fed him.
- That's what we see couples do.
- It doesn't seem forced.
- Like they've been dating for a year.
- I know.
How sweet is this first-place reward?
- Mm…
- I told you so.
Hm? That I'd win.
YESTERDAY EVENING
But still, don't think or worry too much.
Yeah, you're gonna come here
with me again.
Because I'm gonna win tomorrow.
I said I'd win so we could come back.
You weren't torn at all?
- I was torn.
- Um…
- Just messing around.
- Get out.
- If I place first in a women's game…
- Yeah.
I'll give you some thought.
Hey, how many times have you been here?
Is this your fifth time now?
Tell me.
I don't know.
- Count your blessings.
- There…
- What, no, I never said how many.
- Yeah.
Count your blessings.
Wow. Delicious.
Oh.
Really tasty.
- You cold?
- Mm.
Did you bring something warm?
I didn't bring much outerwear.
This bottle is nice.
Let's go if you're done.
Huh.
You can tell by that look on her face.
Jun-seo's being way too comfortable.
I mean, that's just
what he's like, though.
- True.
- Gosh.
- Oh, no.
- This is not good.
- I'm sensing a strange vibe.
- Right.
- He's not focusing on her.
- I wonder why though.
This is so nice.
What would you have done
if you hadn't placed first?
Oh.
What if you placed second
and the winner already chose me?
Yeah.
Who would you have picked?
Um…
If I placed second, I honestly think
you wouldn't have been an option.
So first off, I'd like to say
that I'm very glad that I won.
If I placed second
and you had already been chosen,
then I would've chosen the second person
I went to Paradise with.
- Min-seol?
- Min-seol.
- Oh…
- Wait.
Oh…
Why? Can I ask you why?
- Why her?
- Mm-hmm.
She intrigues me.
- Oh, does she really?
- Yeah.
Oh! Did you see her clenching her jaw?
- Like, "Oh, does she really?"
- I saw it. Yeah.
That put a damper on things.
But isn't Si-an a bit interested
in other guys as well?
But it's a different story if you say
that out loud to the other person.
- Oh, does she really?
- Yeah.
- I had no idea.
- Honestly.
- No one does.
- Well…
- Hm?
- In Paradise…
- Mm?
We definitely talked a lot.
We were cracking jokes
over 90 percent of the time.
Mm-hmm.
- It was fun.
- Mm.
- She's very funny.
She's a bit of a tease too.
But then I…
Then, we came back the next day…
And I've been seeing her
around Inferno since.
But she just seems pretty down,
unlike when she was with me.
She tells me that she isn't down,
but the Min-seol I got to know in Paradise
isn't the one in Inferno.
I was even rooting for her.
And I told her that I thought
she'd be pretty popular in Inferno.
But, yeah, she hasn't been the same
for a while now.
Hm.
I guess I do sort of feel sorry for her.
I can't help but look out for her.
Mm…
Okay, I get that.
I didn't know all that.
I had a lot on my mind.
I have been interested in Min-seol
without even realizing it.
I really just wanted
to be honest with Si-an.
So I told her
that I had Min-seol on my mind.
That's why I couldn't focus solely
on my date with Si-an.
You seem to be thinking about her a lot.
Are you going to act on it?
I'm not sure.
Are you considering talking to her
when you get back?
Dunno.
Hmm…
- Why?
- What?
Why do you ask?
No reason.
- Why are you asking me though?
- For no reason.
Okay.
Man, why are you being so cold?
You know what?
I have something to say too.
Let me be honest,
you're being too cold right now.
- Me?
- Mm.
Why?
- Could you be a bit sweeter?
- Seriously?
- Mm.
- Was I being cold?
Can't you treat me more gently?
How so?
You're getting comfy too quickly.
- I am?
- Mm.
I'm not comfortable.
What I'm saying is…
Forget it.
I'm really not comfy though.
- Do I seem comfy?
- Yeah.
I'm just a little…
Or am I?
Am I not being gentle?
I think you're just a bit tired today.
I feel normal.
This has nothing to do
with me being tired.
- You're usually like this?
- Yeah.
Okay. Got it.
Am I doing something wrong here?
Hmm.
I suddenly had a lot
to think about.
I'm not so sure what he's thinking.
Well, it's just that
he said a lot of reassuring things to me
during our first date.
I was excited about our date
in Paradise the next day,
but he was just there to eat.
He finished eating, and then said,
"If you're done eating, let's go."
I was seeing something very different
from what I'd seen on our first trip.
It caught me off guard a bit.
- Playing mind games?
- Why are they playing mind games?
- What's wrong with them?
- A little odd.
I think things moved too fast
so now his feelings have waned.
Si-an could be sensing this from him.
They became too close too quickly.
Jun-seo definitely seems like
he has a lot on his mind.
- He does.
- Yeah.
And inevitably,
Si-an has a number of choices right now.
So I think…
Si-an unconsciously keeps sizing him up
a little this time around in Paradise.
- A lot of guys like her now.
- A lot.
If I were him, I'd be annoyed.
I'd feel that way more over time.
- Jun-seo is annoyed.
- That's the vibe I'm getting.
I'd already be pretty annoyed.
Like, "What's wrong with her?"
He doesn't want to put up
with everything she has to say.
I'd be thinking, "I have feelings too.
Why I only cater to her?"
But when Si-an said,
"Can't you treat me more gently?"
Jun-seo should've
swallowed his pride and said,
"Oh, I'm really sorry.
That's not what I meant."
He should've pulled her back in like that.
Instead, he just went, "Was I like that?"
That won't fix anything.
Or maybe he really is exhausted?
He said he had a hangover
from all the drinking yesterday.
I think Jun-seo
just has too much on his mind.
He's like, "This is how I usually am.
I'm not being like this because I'm tired.
This is what I'm like.
This is Yuk Jun-seo. This is me."
This is tricky.
Yeah, the vibe's gotten weird,
we didn't expect that.
It's a bit nerve-racking.
Should we go?
- You cold?
- Mm.
- Should I look for a blanket?
- It's okay. Mm-mm.
Maybe this could warm you up a little.
Yeah, put it on me.
Let's cover you up.
- Do you wear cologne?
- No.
- Then, what am I smelling?
- I don't wear any.
You have your own unique scent.
What scent?
I guess how your skin smells?
- I notice when you pass by.
- Really?
Yeah. You have this distinct scent.
- This feels warmer now.
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I'm warmer.
- I'll cover you more.
- Mm.
- She's satisfied.
- Is this what she wanted?
- Things like that?
- She's all better now.
For goodness' sake.
- Oh, come on.
- He's sweeter now.
How did it turn out this way so suddenly?
With you.
- With me?
- Yeah.
- I think we have good timing.
- Mm.
It was good yesterday,
and it still is good today.
Mm-hmm.
When we first got
to our hotel room yesterday…
- What?
- …you were all soft and gentle.
- Me?
- That's the vibe you had.
Can I ask why?
- Soft and gentle?
- Were you sleepy?
What do you mean by soft and gentle?
You know, your eyes were looking drowsy.
You kept giggling while you were picking
at those rose petals.
- Yeah.
- Remember that?
- What? What about it?
- Huh?
What about it?
Did it give you butterflies?
Yeah, I liked seeing that side of you.
You just being there and doing nothing.
That casual side of yours seemed natural.
And it was nice to see.
I was mostly looking forward to all
the conversations we'd be having today.
- Are they holding hands?
- Are they?
- Hold my hand properly.
- Hm?
Hold my hand properly.
You held it just fine yesterday.
Did I?
I like it when a guy is expressive.
- You want me to be expressive?
- Mm.
Should I go take some classes on it?
No.
Oh.
What's your idea of expressive?
- Hm?
- Saying "I love you" and stuff?
Just as an example.
Oh, you love me?
I've barely used that word in my life.
Dang.
You don't really need to say it
if you can show your feelings
through actions.
No.
It's better to say it
and show it through actions.
You think?
Is that so?
So you've hardly said "I love you"?
Right.
Well, this proves the situation early on
was just a lovers' quarrel.
- Is that right? I see.
- That's all it was.
We took it too seriously.
- Like, "Jun-seo, just be nicer to me."
- "Be nicer to me already."
- A quarrel to fall deeper.
- Exactly.
- We got worried.
- They like each other a lot.
- Just needed a push.
- I get it now.
Geez.
Oh…
Wow.
- Nice.
- They have everything.
- Hmm…
- Hmm, dart machines.
How do you play that?
It takes pictures.
Do we move back?
I didn't think
we'd come to a place like this.
Awesome.
It's so nice.
- Wait. Are they going to meet? Here?
- What?
- Wait. What?
- Wait.
- Wait, what?
- Wow.
- Whoa, what?
- This is insane!
- So glad to see you.
Jeong-su, my love.
- You-jin, my love.
- What took you so long?
Geez.
Do we finally get to drink now?
- This awkwardness was driving me nuts.
- Why were you awkward?
- Is this yours? Can I drink it?
- Yeah. Drink anything you want.
- They made them meet up like this?
- Ah…
In this case…
- Ah, this could be really dangerous.
- Well, this is entertaining.
Right, this is no ordinary double date.
- It's not.
- Jun-seo wasn't being sweet.
But now Jeong-su can use
some of his sweetness on her.
- He could sway her.
- A déjà vu moment?
Yeah.
- Might shake things up.
- Right timing to get swayed.
- It's good to see you guys.
- I know. It's crazy to see you both here.
- Do you remember, on day one?
- We all came here day one.
- We're here again.
- Is that right?
Something's different.
It is. Then, should we switch seats?
- Diagonally.
- What do you think?
Let the diagonal talks officially begin.
What is this? A social experiment?
You both placed first and second last time
and today as well.
How do you two feel?
- I lost again.
- You lost again?
- Oh, right.
- I lost again.
He kept saying that he'd never move up
from being a runner-up.
He's no match for me.
I wanted to beat you at least once.
I'm shaking.
Anyway, I had no idea
that you'd choose You-jin.
- You didn't?
- No.
- Mm.
- You had her in mind?
She's my Oompa-Loompa.
Why's that?
- He wants to carry me around in a jar.
- Uh, what?
What? Is that some pickup line?
He must have
found me entertaining yesterday.
Oh, really?
I guess I was funny.
You're unbelievable.
Thank you. I'll take that as a compliment.
- You're charming.
- Right.
You're infectious.
Cheers.
- This is better than I thought.
- So refreshing.
Mm…
You wanna try some?
Is it sweet?
If so, I'll try it.
Oh, right, you like sweet food, don't you?
- Is it sweet? If so, I'll try it.
- I don't like sweet drinks.
I guess it's yours now.
I'll just have a Coke.
Mm…
- Like it?
- It's not quite my taste.
- I'm good.
- Oh, it's not?
- Si-an's not liking that.
- He's being too sweet.
Right, she just said it with her eyes,
"Watch and learn."
- Like it?
- It's not quite my taste.
- I'm good.
- Oh, it's not?
How is being with
the same person two days in a row?
- Si-an is looking…
- Stop eating, Jun-seo.
You've been eating all day.
Come on. Please stop eating.
How is being with the same person
two days in a row?
- Now that you've been here twice.
- What do you think?
Is the communication better?
Are you more comfy with each other?
Yeah, it's definitely flowing.
Or maybe not so much.
Just kidding.
We're communicating as best as we can.
It's been fun.
I definitely feel more comfortable
being with her for the second time.
- Good at pool, Jeong-su?
- Let's play.
Let's play in pairs.
I've only played it
three times in my life.
Three?
Oh…
Good job.
You did fine.
- Try it.
- Do I hit the white one?
- Shoot the white ball to hit this.
- I'll give it a try.
- Like this?
- Know how to hold the cue?
- She knows how to hold the cue.
- Only three times, huh?
- It's true, I swear.
- You got into position right away.
Only three.
- Don't take her word for it.
- What?
Try to aim slightly left of center.
- Yeah.
- Oh, no. It's getting tough again.
I know, right? This one makes it tricky.
This move is going to be tough to do, huh?
- Strike here to scatter these.
- Sounds good.
Ugh, it's getting stuck.
Do it this way.
- Like this? That's new.
- Yeah.
Use the bottom one here
to help choose the direction.
- The direction?
- Place this here, shoot in that direction.
- There you go.
- Got it.
Oh…
Right, you've just gotta
teach her like that.
- How sweet are they?
- They are.
Good job.
It barely touched the ball,
but I still got it.
Can you shoot this one over there?
Let's see…
You might make it.
- Hey.
- You're so strong.
Don't do it halfheartedly
even if you'll mess up.
He's speaking like some coach.
He sounded like one just now.
- He's Mr. Coach.
- Oh, dear. This is not good.
What should I do? Look, the yellow stripe.
- Like this? Not too bad?
- It's doable.
- I'll go again…
- Yeah, but…
Wow.
- Ah.
- Wow, you did great.
I guess I'm good at stuff
that requires physical skills.
- I knew it.
- I have a good eye for detail.
- You do?
- Don't I?
A dance major's eye for detail.
No?
Can you quiet down a little?
We're trying to focus here.
Whoo!
Shoot however you want.
Whoa!
- Ah.
- Ugh, that girl really is…
I have to say,
I guess I do have a sharp eye for detail.
You're incredible.
- Just hit it hard?
- Try to shoot it that way.
Good.
"Good."
Is Jun-seo in a competition right now?
Unbelievable.
- He's competitive.
- They're different.
What's the score?
- I'm getting competitive.
- We're crushing them.
We're winning.
- We are.
- Really?
I better beat Jun-seo in this, at least.
Right, you have to. Go for it.
Let's get you first place. We can do it.
Maybe I used up
all my luck earlier.
Okay.
I don't see any good shots.
- Look at that row.
- I'm getting competitive.
- Break them?
- Yeah.
- Should we aim here?
- Go for it. Let's go. We can do it.
Losers write their names
with their butt.
It's a little off. Hey, hey.
- "Hey, hey."
- He's way too blunt.
He should stop addressing her like that.
He keeps saying it.
- It honestly doesn't seem okay.
- Why does he do that?
- Annoying.
- Her buttons have been pushed.
- She's annoyed now.
- No, I… I mean…
- Can't let that go.
- It's the way he speaks.
Hey, can't you discuss
your move with me first?
- This is our chance.
- This is a tough one.
- Don't be nervous.
- That's not it.
Tricky to shoot from here.
- Go get that bridge stick.
- Bridge stick?
No, I don't want to get any help
for the final shot.
- Want to write your name with your butt?
- Okay, go already.
- Let's end the game here.
- Think and look before you shoot.
- Hey.
- Call me Si-an.
- Stop calling me "hey."
- Oh, Si-an. Si-an.
I want you to come a little to this side.
Uh-oh. Conflict is brewing.
- Fight, fight.
- Let's use it to our advantage.
Good job.
- Geez, they're like con artists.
- They are.
It was fun.
- Where should they do their punishment?
- Fun game.
- Hey.
- Likewise.
You're good.
Yeah, I guess I am.
The difference keeps showing.
Si-an can't stand
how he's treating her in front of them.
Ugh, this is so bad.
How does second place feel?
Fine, as long as we do well
in the official games.
- It's fun to be on a double date.
- I was dozing off.
- But this woke me up.
- Mm.
- Did we make you mad?
- A little.
Ah, my blood pressure.
Gosh.
- Still, it was fun. We were neck and neck.
- Right, it was a close game.
- Ladies are so good.
- They're good.
Why are you so good?
I'm a bit of a perfectionist,
maybe a bit controlling.
That's my Oompa-Loompa.
Gosh, You-jin really is crazy.
You're the real deal.
Thank you very much.
It's good.
Anyway, are you in a bad mood?
No.
- From coming in second.
- Come on.
Gosh.
- Cheers for the last time.
- Cheers.
- Bye.
What's with the "bye"?
Um, to be honest,
I was already feeling disappointed
by Jun-seo.
Maybe that's why…
Jeong-su's sweet behavior
drew my attention even more.
His actions really reminded me a lot
of my first date in Paradise
when I came with him.
So, it's definitely given me
a lot to think about.
- Did you have fun?
- Mm.
That's good.
Did you?
Mm, it was really fun.
I think that Paradise is…
actually a super important place to be.
Paradise?
Yes, it's so important.
- Yeah.
- So, so much.
It's super crucial.
- Interesting words.
- She keeps bringing it up.
What do you think she meant by
"Paradise is an important place to be"?
She wanted Jun-seo to hear that.
Right.
"Now I'm more certain about my feelings
from spending time in Paradise."
I guess that's what she meant.
It sounded like
she was giving him a warning in a way.
"This is an important place,
so you better behave and listen."
What?
"Come to your senses
before it's too late."
But I doubt he noticed
that warning at all.
Yeah, that seems to be the problem here.
You have to make an effort to change
for the person you like.
She's mentioned it multiple times.
But his behavior is just…
Is he looking down on her or what?
- It's the way he speaks.
- It's just out of habit for him.
He's been like this for 30 years,
so that must be why.
He got so competitive.
This means they don't click well.
They should just part ways here.
Da-hee, that was so direct.
What? I mean, isn't it obvious
what their future will look like?
They're incompatible.
They should end it here.
What if he's like "I can fix this habit"?
Never. He can't change how he speaks.
- Are you empathizing with Jun-seo?
- I'm just heartbroken.
He's like, "It's a habit of mine
for 28 years. I can't help it.
I don't want be like this. I don't."
- How long you need to fix it?
- "Give me time. At least three months."
If Jun-seo said, "Give me time."
She would've said, "Sure."
But that's not how he's handling it.
He's more like,
"You don't like it? Take it or leave it."
It was a double date!
That makes it embarrassing to hear
your partner keep calling you, "Hey, hey."
Seeing the other being sweet doesn't help.
It was a stark contrast.
This is why you shouldn't do double dates.
Gosh, these double dates.
This double date
will bring about some huge changes.
I know.
This one was actually pretty pivotal.
PARADISE
KIM TE-HWAN & BAE JI-YEON
Ooh…
This is so private.
- Shall we go in?
- Okay.
Yeah!
It's nice, actually. It's not too bad.
- Really? It's not bad?
- Yeah.
Ooh.
- Feels nice.
- Does it?
Yeah.
This feels good.
You know what? You look cute in this pool.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Hiya!
You look like a puppy.
- Having my feet in feels nice.
- Mm.
I know.
This is fun.
- Is it?
- Mm.
Usually, it's the other way around.
I guess he doesn't wanna get wet.
- Ji-yeon is taking initiative.
- Yeah.
- You asked me about my dream.
What's yours?
Well, the thing is, the work I'm doing now
is truly about creating
a whole new culture.
I want to nurture
and grow this new culture
into something incredible.
I want it to be
over a thousand times bigger
than what it currently is right now.
I want everyone to know that it was me
who fostered its development.
Mm…
So, becoming someone who can be respected
by those who love that culture
is my dream.
Mm…
Mm-hmm.
Whoa, he's got a big dream.
- He wanna go down in history.
- "Go down in history."
- I've never even imagined such a dream.
- Right?
I believe that Koreans
are deprived of chances
to expand their tastes and perspectives.
- Right.
- It's such a shame.
But fortunately, there are already
a lot of people these days
who started to seek out their own
unique professions.
- That's great.
- That's true.
You know?
Te-hwan seems to like
talking about his work.
He likes to talk about
the work he's doing quite a bit.
But the problem is,
he only ever talks about himself.
He never says,
"Okay, this is me. What about you?"
So I always work really hard
to introduce good music to everyone.
"I'm this, I'm that."
He just talks like that all the time.
As the night went on, I became tired of it
so I didn't respond much.
I only want to be known
by those who actually see my worth.
I only want to be recognized
by those individuals or groups
that are on the same wavelength.
Hmm.
- Yeah, to put it lightly, that's my dream.
- Hmm.
That's putting it lightly?
I didn't know
his self-esteem was high until now.
He's odd, that's for sure.
What's your non-work-related dream?
I definitely wouldn't say
I'm against marriage.
But you could say
I lean towards that idea.
I just wanna be with the culture I love.
What is he, some future culture president?
- Minister of Culture.
- President of Culture.
That's what he is.
I wanna be with the culture I love
for the rest of my life.
Living happily
with friends I connect with.
I'd say that's my dream.
Happiness first.
A happy life is the ultimate goal.
- Okay.
- Mm.
Usually, when you like someone,
do you tell them you're not into marriage?
I'm sorry, but I also think
it's too early to even mention marriage
when it comes to Te-hwan.
The point here is I said that my dream
was to create a happy family of my own.
What's your dream?
Right, you asked me about my dream.
My dream is to become a caring wife
and a devoted mother.
- That's my lifelong dream.
- Sounds hard.
Yeah, it is.
I mentioned to him I wanted to get married
and create a family of my own.
So I was a little confused
about his reaction to that yesterday
as well his answer today.
When we should be walking together,
he just walks ahead
without thinking about me.
- I'm getting the hang of it now.
- Oh, are you?
When we were skating,
he was having all the fun by himself
without noticing me at all.
Who knew there's a twist to that scene.
Seriously.
He only focused on skating, huh?
THIS MORNING
Yeah. Um…
- You're so focused on eating.
- Mm-hmm.
- I've got to eat a lot to stay healthy.
- Oh, okay.
THIS EVENING
Wanna ask me anything else?
Hmm…
- I'll ask if I think of anything.
- Huh?
If I think of anything.
"I'll ask when I think of any"?
Most men are simple-minded,
but they don't answer like he does.
Exactly!
I'll ask if I think of anything.
If I think of anything.
- You're putting me on the spot.
- Am I?
Yeah, I'm drawing a blank.
I wonder
if he really does have feelings for me.
He keeps on telling me
that he likes me this much,
but it only feels like this much.
I'm trusting my gut here,
and it's telling me
that he's not being honest with me.
So I'm a little confused.
This is like
a Sixth Sense level plot twist.
That's why
she didn't want him to choose her.
Ji-yeon meant it when she told him
to go to Paradise with someone else.
She wanted to stay in Inferno,
give it some thought.
He could've used the time
to get to know someone else.
But Te-hwan didn't get the message
and chose her.
If you like someone,
you never say you'll ask questions
if you end up thinking of any.
- It's just not possible.
- You wanna know everything.
If you can't think of one right away,
you wouldn't say it like that.
Come up with something, like,
- "I have many to ask."
- "What's your favorite color?"
"There's so many questions. Hold on.
What should I ask first?"
- That's how you come up with things.
- Right.
Te-hwan seems to have a strong sense
of who he is as a person.
But I think he's behaving
and speaking within that strict standard
that he's holding himself to.
He could've gone in the pool with her.
- But instead, he just…
- Did he not go in?
- He's already made up his mind.
- Didn't he go in later?
He just didn't want to get wet.
His stubbornness came through.
Maybe it isn't good to go to Paradise
with the same person twice in a row.
It isn't a good idea.
This trip could be important
because now they really know each other.
I guess it really is important.
- All couples aren't working?
- Nope.
Seriously, this sure
wasn't Paradise today.
- Everyone looks somber.
I'm just…
Why are you down? Tell us.
I've been stuck in Inferno
that I don't know what it's like outside.
I won't go tomorrow either.
Why don't you think so?
We'll help you out.
- With what?
- Dong-ho!
- Just stay put.
- She wants you to stay put.
- Why?
- Look at you chuckling.
- She can fend for herself.
- Yeah, I'm good. I'm doing great.
You might get to go tomorrow.
Don't stay behind.
I have no choice.
I'm saying it's okay to be more forward.
You know?
Are we not allowed to share
who we voted for and interested in?
No, that's up to us.
If you're being cautious,
you can keep it to yourself.
I've been careful.
I thought we needed to keep it a secret.
Be honest
with us now, then. Go on.
- What?
- Who?
- Who did I pick?
- Who you have in mind?
Jong-hoon.
- Oh…
- Mm…
Jong-hoon.
- Oh…
- Mm…
What?
- What's happening?
- What is this?
Whoa, Hye-jin.
- That was great timing.
- She nailed that.
I also picked Jong-hoon.
Man,
you're pretty clueless, Jong-hoon.
- This time? Even before that?
- Amazing. You're awesome.
- How cool is that?
- I will…
Pat on the back.
- Should we swap seats?
- I'll keep choosing Jong-hoon.
I can't stop cringing.
Why?
I'm just telling you.
I'll do that for sure.
Oh!
Nice move, Hye-jin.
It wasn't cringy at all.
It was really cool.
- I'll do that.
- I had no idea. I didn't know.
How could you not sense?
- That's my fault.
- Why?
I've hardly expressed my feelings
since he got here.
He was kind to me at first
and I sensed it.
I was really grateful.
- I haven't followed through.
- She's shaking.
Geez, I am shaking now.
I saw quite a lot of Polaroids of you two.
- Let me go talk to Hye-jin alone.
- Okay.
That was fast.
I love that they're acting quickly
on this. Good for them.
This is healing my soul. So cathartic.
Hye-jin's so honest.
I'm grateful and touched
that you have feelings for me.
It's a nice feeling.
You know, every time I see you…
you're so pretty.
And you give me butterflies
every single time.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- You mean it?
- Mm.
- Because I believe what I hear.
- Mm-hmm.
- So tell me the truth.
- I am.
Don't be like Jeong-su.
Why, how is he?
Never mind, it's nothing.
Okay.
I just couldn't bring myself to tell you.
Even today, you were wearing a scarf
or something, right?
A scarf?
- You had it wrapped around your neck.
- Yeah.
It looked so great on you.
- Really?
- Yeah.
That outfit
and the yellow outfit.
Okay.
You know, it's not a big deal to say,
"You look pretty in that."
But it was hard to build up
the confidence to say that to you.
Hmm…
I found it so hard to talk
and tell you that.
- Mm.
- Yeah.
That's understandable.
Then, I'll keep approaching you first.
- It's okay. Now, I will…
- It's okay now?
Yeah, it's fine.
I'll approach you first from now on.
I really hope we…
go to Paradise together.
- Us two?
- Yeah.
Wow.
I will absolutely keep choosing you,
that's for sure.
Jong-hoon, Jong-hoon, Jong-hoon.
An Jong-hoon.
Let's take a picture
to remember this.
- All right.
- Yeah.
I'll stretch my arm as much as possible.
♪ Let's take up the cloud
Till I hold you ♪
There.
Nice, I like it.
- Oh!
- That happened fast.
I never expected to see this in Inferno.
I just felt so troubled by everything
I was seeing in Paradise.
Right. Hye-jin was actually
really cool just now.
- So cool.
- It might work out between the two.
- These two will make it to the end.
- Yeah, they'll go to Paradise next.
Does anyone wanna have a chat
with someone here?
We can do what we want, so feel free.
- Yeah, I wanna have a chat.
- Huh?
Who do you wanna talk to?
- Dong-ho.
- Go ahead.
Three of us can chat.
I'm going to go bed
after we talk.
- You're not gonna stay and talk to us?
- We should talk.
I'll be back after I grab some lip balm.
The female contestants take charge.
- A-rin is looking upset again.
- Yeah.
I wanna stroll.
- Do you like walks?
- Let's walk.
What about you?
- Do you have a lot on your mind?
- Curious.
Well, I just…
I could be completely wrong,
but he gave me enough reassurance.
I'm roommates with Hae-lin and You-jin,
so it's just a little tricky.
- That's why you're quiet in there?
- It's hard to say anything.
I'd like to talk about what I did,
what I liked, what we discussed.
But I can't even share that with them.
Right, you shouldn't.
I don't know how things are going.
I haven't talked to Dong-ho
since we came back today.
- Talk to him later.
- I'm sure those two talked today.
So I'm wondering
if she's just pursuing him
even after he gave her a clear answer
and turned her down,
or if he gave her mixed signals.
- We just came back from Paradise.
- You really lose track of time here.
Gosh, and we had Americanos yesterday.
In the morning.
- You're right.
- Did you get one?
- I did.
- I'm so envious.
- Are you craving coffee?
- I'm dying here.
Those good old times.
Why "good old" times?
Those good old times…
Well, these are better times, of course.
If the girls compete
for Paradise tomorrow,
is it okay if I kidnap you?
- I'll choose you anyway. No question.
- Yeah. Okay.
For sure.
I'm definitely gonna win first place.
What?
- What?
- You're really determined.
I really need to go to Paradise right now.
Let's go, together.
Let's go together.
You're doing that smile again.
Smile? What smile?
You're doing it again.
No, It's just awkward.
I smile when I feel like that
but I look more awkward.
Mm.
There it is.
He can't pull it together.
He only smiles like that
when he's hanging out with Hae-lin.
- I didn't tell you this?
- Tell me what?
- When I talked about my ideal type…
- Mm.
…I didn't mention
that I love when people blush, did I?
- I don't think you did.
- I wonder why.
In my interview, my ideal type
was someone who blushes when they get shy.
Then, you showed up.
Oh, oh…
- I wouldn't say I'm being shy.
- Are you flustered, not shy?
Well, it's just that I have never met
anyone like you before,
someone who's so straightforward
with their feelings.
I hope we get to choose tomorrow.
I'll let you sleep in the big bed.
At this point,
I just get a kick out of teasing you.
- She's coming in full force.
- "Full force."
- She is no joke.
- Yeah.
Doesn't know what to do
every time she acts like that,
but Hae-lin finds that so amusing.
She's enjoying it.
Yeah, and she likes him.
Right, this feels like
a comic book situation.
There's this very shy male lead.
And suddenly, the bubbly female lead
shows up and gets all cute with him.
Like in school,
there's always that it-girl
who's friends with everyone,
like, "Hey, did you sleep well?"
I keep picturing it like that.
The male lead gets drawn
to the female lead
before he even knows it.
Yeah.
They're taking so long.
- I'm nervous.
- Hae-lin and Dong-ho?
I'm sure they talked
with each other earlier.
Oh, that's true. They did talk earlier.
Yeah, they did, right?
I saw them walking around.
They had a one-on-one conversation.
Hmm.
What really got me…
was finding out
that we work in the same building
and that we even live
in the same neighborhood.
Also…
Both of our parents
live in the same neighborhood.
- Crazy, right?
- What?
Plus, we were born in the same month.
Sounds like fate.
Yeah, that's honestly
why it was so shocking for me!
And the surprise of it all
made me feel butterflies in my stomach.
I thought, "What? What even is this?"
- Could it be fate?
- Oh!
That's how I felt.
When he told me about himself,
it all hit me.
That's why my feelings grew so quickly.
I bet they all went inside.
They haven't.
- Still here.
- Yeah.
Do what you'd like.
I'm gonna get some water.
Oh.
They're back!
- Hey, hey. Hey, hey.
- How was the talk?
You talked for, like, two or three hours.
- The sun might come up.
- What?
What time is it?
Come on. You're so mean.
Did you two have a drink or something?
- No. My eyes are feeling dry.
- Really?
I thought you'd keep going till morning.
I almost went to bed.
Ah, you guys are scary.
I'm so tired. I almost went to sleep.
I know.
I don't want to wash up…
You're talkative considering
you only slept two hours.
Uh-oh.
Ah, this is so entertaining.
All the fun is in Inferno.
The two of you can go talk.
We couldn't wash up
since we were waiting.
We can talk another time if you're tired.
Let's go.
Sneeze alert.
Do you just wanna sleep?
He's feeling cold,
so he wants to go inside.
He's even cold in the summer.
Let's go. It won't take long anyway.
Shall we?
Okay.
Let's go.
I said we could talk tomorrow
if you were tired.
You're being super obvious.
You're yawning.
- I'm not.
- Why ask if I was gonna sleep?
Let's make it quick and go to bed.
I'm so tired.
Well, I…
- Didn't you two talk earlier today?
- We did.
So I was just wondering why you needed
to talk to her again tonight.
And you guys… talked for so long.
I'm curious what you talked about.
She just wanted to talk with me.
Oh.
I mostly just listened.
I listened to what she had to say.
I pretty much listened the whole time.
Okay.
I was just curious,
but I used it as an excuse to talk to you.
Plus, you played that game earlier.
But we didn't get to talk afterward.
Oh, yeah, you're right.
I thought I'd have more time
to spend with you today.
- The other girls kept approaching you.
- Yeah, the others…
We were talking,
You-jin asked if she could talk to me,
so I had to talk to her right after.
That's how they do things?
Hmm.
Well, honestly, I'm not curious
to know exactly
what you guys talked about.
It's just that…
I wanted to let you know
that I'm thinking about you.
I really don't care
what you guys talked about at all.
Because we talked a lot before that,
and even in Paradise.
That's where I'm at.
That's all.
What? What is it?
Bedtime?
No, no. Let's just stay a little longer.
You want to?
I was worried
you'd get the wrong impression.
- I didn't!
- I wanna stay.
- Yeah.
- You know that, right?
Just sleepy.
- Ah, you're sleepy?
- Yeah.
Dang, let's go then.
We really didn't get much sleep.
- These two are feeling iffy.
- Feeling off.
This love triangle
revolving around Dong-ho.
But given the evening conversations
we just saw,
I believe there's no need for confusion.
I'm certain
that he's more drawn to Hae-lin.
But do you remember
what A-rin mentioned earlier?
We wondered
if A-rin wasn't taking initiative enough.
But from their conversation earlier,
I sensed that she wasn't feeling
the need to approach him
because he'd given her enough reassurance.
But wouldn't that be
a major miscalculation on her part?
This must be the first time Dong-ho
has experienced anything like this.
I don't think he will show
how he is actually feeling.
- A little…
- Even if he's drawn to Hae-lin.
PARADISE
YUK JUN-SEO & LEE SI-AN
Gosh, the air's so crisp tonight.
I love it.
This sure is Paradise.
Do you agree?
Don't you think?
Mm.
- She turned her head.
- Stop talking to her like that.
Please stop being so rude.
This is because we're tired, right?
Wanna shower first?
Yeah, after we talk a bit more.
You wanna talk?
Should we talk after the shower? Or…
I think that's best.
How's your second time
in Paradise with me?
- My second time with you?
Yeah.
- You sleeping?
- "You sleeping?"
- Ridiculous.
- You're kidding.
There's no way.
What if he is asleep?
- What?
- They're so done.
- It's over, for sure.
- Is he asleep?
You asleep?