(Only For Love)
(Episode 14)
(It's been a busy day.)
(Now I'm craving some late-night snacks.)
Busy?
What has she been up to?
Yue, what's wrong?
I'm trying to contact some industry experts.
Is it still about that article you were working on?
Yu Ling suggested we get some big names to endorse it.
But I think the experts you found before should suffice.
Yue,
when we write an article, we're sharing our insights
and communicating with our readers.
It's not just about regurgitating others' viewpoints.
A good article isn't a mere jumble of technical terms.
You shouldn't rely solely on others
to lend authority to your work.
But Yu Ling said...
You've been working for a while now.
You should learn to make your own judgments about what others say.
I reviewed your initial outline.
The structure looks fine, and the information is thorough.
What you need to do now
is enrich the content based on the initial draft
and adjust some wording.
Look, show me your initial draft.
We'll go over it together.
If there are any unclear points, we can seek further confirmation.
Hello.
I'm Kong Nan, a journalist from Financial Introduce.
Is Mr. Qin still on his way?
It's okay. Let's chat for a while first.
When Mr. Qin arrives, we can formally begin.
Miss, I think you've mistaken me for someone else.
Aren't you Mr. Chen Sheng?
I'm sorry. You've got the wrong person.
Miss Kong.
I'm sorry. I got the wrong person. Sorry.
It's okay.
Are you Chen Sheng?
Yes, I am. Hello, Miss Kong.
Nice to meet you.
How old are you?
I'm 25.
Did you start working right after graduating?
Yes, I joined Yunchuang right after graduation
and started working with Mr. Shi.
The way you talk to me on WeChat doesn't seem like
someone from the post-90s generation.
Well, I might come across as more mature when I'm at work.
You're a really fast learner, Yue. You're getting there.
Thank you, Shu Yi.
It's getting so late. Let's call it a day.
You should go home now.
Tomorrow, go through it again and check it thoroughly.
Yes!
(Have you had dinner?)
(How was your day?)
(Today was great.)
(Shu Yi is back. She's been mentoring me closely.)
(Your beloved niece here is a fast learner.)
(We managed to finish our work just before midnight.)
(Shu Yi is amazing, so professional and patient.)
(She has so much on her plate, )
(yet she stayed with me to work this late.)
Shu Yi, I'll head out now.
You shouldn't stay too late either.
Go home now. Stay safe.
- Bye. - Bye.
Shi Yan hasn't contacted me all day.
(Yes, I'm not alone.)
(Can someone help deliver a bed to the magazine office?)
Perfect.
(Come downstairs.)
(Coming!)
Miss Zheng.
Did you just finish work?
Yes, I had to work late.
It must be tough for you.
It's not easy for you either.
By the way, I guess you probably haven't eaten anything
working so late.
These egg tarts are freshly heated for you.
Would you like to take them with you to eat on your way home?
I reserved them just for you.
If you don't want them,
I'll have to throw them away.
Thank you. How much is it? I'll transfer it to you.
It's fine.
My supervisor has already settled the accounts.
Are you waiting for a ride?
It's quite cold tonight,
and it's not safe to wait alone.
How about I stay with you for a while?
I...
Let's go.
Have you paid him?
Show me your QR code.
Thanks.
Haven't you chatted enough with him?
We're done.
What brings you by?
It's on my way.
Miss Zheng, you seem quite popular.
Just average.
About as much as you, Mr. Shi.
Are you hungry?
Would you like to have some?
It's late. I'll pass.
If you don't sit in the front seat,
you would make me look like your driver.
- Easy there, Mr. Wang. - All right.
- Bye, Xu. - I'll wait for your confirmation on the interview time.
Good night, Mr. Wang. Bye.
Zheng Shu Yi?
Shi Yan!
They really are dating.
Who's talking behind my back?
(The dangers of late-night snacking)
Where are we going?
Late-night snack.
Didn't you say we shouldn't have late-night snacks?
Given your routine, this meal can't be considered a late-night snack.
It's just a late dinner.
Can we really do that?
Can I choose what to eat then?
I only want noodles.
Do you know the way?
Turn right at the next intersection!
Thank you.
You're really not going to try some?
Their signature seafood noodles are incredibly delicious.
With every bite, you'll taste the freshness,
and it leaves a lingering flavor.
No, thanks.
Their noodles are really good.
You'd be missing out if you don't try them.
They're best when served fresh,
so they don't do takeout.
If you want to enjoy them, you have to dine in.
It gets crowded during the day,
and sometimes you have to wait for a table at night.
I rarely eat here after starting work.
Back when I was in college, I used to come here often with...
Here you go.
Thank you.
Xing Zhou, let's have dinner here tonight.
Sure. Let's go.
Excuse me, I need to use the restroom.
Five bowls of seafood noodles, please.
You got it.
- Let's have a drink, guys. - Sure.
It's been a long time.
Xing Zhou, we've been classmates for so many years.
You've got to be honest with us.
Why did you and Zheng Shu Yi suddenly broke up?
- Tell us. - Yes, tell us.
We're just incompatible.
So, who initiated the breakup?
She did.
That's normal.
She's interacting with a different crowd now,
and her standards have risen.
When she's surrounded by CEOs and CFOs every day,
how could she still be interested in
a small tech company employee like you?
You guys enjoy dinner. I've lost my appetite.
Xing Zhou...
- Xing Zhou! - Xing Zhou!
- Where are you going, Xing Zhou? - Xing Zhou!
Xing Zhou!
(Need me to go and pick you up?)
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Zheng Shu Yi, look up.
What?
Do I have something on my face?
Nothing there.
Still as beautiful as ever.
What's going on?
With such big eyes,
yet why do you have such bad taste?
Why are you suddenly attacking me?
(Could he have guessed something?)
(That couldn't be. He doesn't know Yue Xing Zhou.)
Yes, you're right.
I used to have poor taste before,
but it has improved a lot.
Now your standards are too high for you.
It's like playing the lute to a cow.
Pardon me?
I said you're like a cow.
Zheng Shu Yi.
I'm sorry.
Still want to finish your noodle?
No, I've lost my appetite.
He's a cow who has no sense of romance,
with no self-awareness at all.
(Nothing good ever happens when I meet that cheater.)
(I couldn't even finish my noodles.)
(Now I'm hungry and tired, )
(with an unhappy cow beside me.)
(Why is he in such a bad mood?)
We're here?
I should go home then.
Drive safe.
Zheng Shu Yi.
What?
Don't eat before going to bed.
Sleeping on an empty stomach not only causes low blood sugar
but also affects sleep quality.
Mr. Shi, take care of yourself,
and I'll take care of myself.
Bye.
Why is it empty?
Forget it. I'll just order a food delivery.
I'm not going to listen to you.
You're not the one who's starving.
I'm hungry.
How long till my food gets here?
Coming. Give me a minute.
I didn't order this.
(Open the door. Get your food.)
He's actually pretty considerate and sweet.
He even delivered Jiuwei's noodles to me personally.
Maybe he does care about me.
(This is so good.)
(You don't eat green onions?)
(Yes.)
(Are you this considerate with your ex-girlfriend too?)
(I'm just like you.)
(Could it be that he found out?)
(Why did I bring up his ex-girlfriend?)
(And I sound jealous.)
(He's probably mocking me.)
Zheng Shu Yi,
why do you care about what Shi Yan thinks?
There is no way I'm jealous.
If anything, it should be his ex-girlfriend who's jealous
that I can have food delivered by Shi Yan himself.
(Don't starve yourself for someone unimportant again.)
Nan Nan, pour me a cup.
I just bought it. I haven't had it yet.
You can have it.
Morning, Yu Ling.
What's wrong with her?
Do I look like I know?
It's not poisoned, is it?
Let's begin the meeting.
Shu Yi, go turn on the lights.
I'll go.
Today's class is interesting.
We're going to talk about a favorite topic of ours,
money.
Of course, we will primarily discuss the supply and demand for money.
Before we begin,
let's first review the monetary system in our country.
New Year's Day is approaching, and the holidays are coming.
Before the New Year, make sure to wrap up your work.
Additionally, Guan Capital is hosting a thank-you dinner.
Yu Ling, Guan Capital is your client.
You should attend.
Editor, I've scheduled other interviews on that day.
Shu Yi should go.
What did you say?
I have other arrangements on that day. Shu Yi going is more suitable.
What's wrong with her?
Is she under a spell?
I've been busy with a feature on new energy vehicle batteries recently,
so I might not have the time.
How about sending Kong Nan instead?
Me?
Okay. It's settled then.
Now, let's talk about the interns' work.
Both teams of interns have been doing well.
They've made great progress.
We are about to begin their internship assessment,
so keep up the good work.
What are your plans, mentor?
Bei Er has been working diligently.
I will continue to guide her
and help her secure a job here.
And you, Shu Yi?
Shi Yue has already developed the basic writing skills.
Next, I plan to work with her on a special feature article for Yunchuang.
No, thanks, Shu Yi.
Thank you for valuing me so much,
but the special feature on Mingyu Yunchuang is a crucial project.
I've only made a little progress.
I don't want to weigh you down.
There is still so much I need to learn.
However, I can assist you with some other tasks to lighten your load.
Professor Yu, you want to talk to me?
It's the first time you've called me. I'm so happy.
Miss Qin, please stop sending someone to record my lecture.
I...
I'm sorry.
I've been very busy lately, so...
The course you're taking is a foundational one.
If you don't have time,
you can study at home.
(If you have any questions, come to school next time and ask me.)
But please stop sending someone to film my class.
It distracts my other students.
I understand. I won't do it again.
I'll study at home by myself.
I'll try my best to attend your lectures in person.
Thank you.
Yu You called me
and even said I can ask him questions in person
if I don't understand.
Does this count as him inviting me to see him?
(You treated me to noodles a few days ago.)
(It's my turn to treat you to dinner.)
(Okay.)
(I'll decide what to eat.)
(So, pick me up after work?)
(Okay.)
Are you just going to "okay" me?
If you don't talk, no one can know what's on your mind.
(Are you in a bad mood now?)
(Yes.)
(It's like that night, )
(when you left, you seemed to be in a bad mood.)
(But later, you went to buy noodles for me, )
(and it seemed like you were in a better mood.)
(Don't you have other things to do?)
(Whether you're happy or not is a top priority for me.)
This article...
What do you think?
Is the criticism too strong?
After all, they're our advertising client, Shi Yue.
I know.
Before I wrote it,
I double-checked all these facts.
Please tone it down and make it more polished.
Editor,
the media is the voice of the public
and the conscience of society.
Journalists cannot speak against their conscience.
I can't and I won't write an overly exaggerated piece.
It's really like mentor, like disciple.
You're just like Zheng Shu Yi.
Shu Yi taught me to be truthful and objective.
Have an opinion and an attitude.
We can't write based on how the interviewee wants it.
Fine.
Go and call Zheng Shu Yi here.
I didn't expect this intern to be so insightful.
Some of it is what I taught her before,
but I didn't expect her to actually apply it in her PR piece.
Our editor asked her to go and make revisions,
but she stood her ground,
using the journalistic spirit I told her earlier.
Now our editor is having an headache.
This intern of yours sounds really interesting.
(Now you're praising her.)
(I don't usually hear you praise me.)
Yes, her taste and aesthetic are on point.
Lately, she's been very motivated.
She's been attending Professor Yu's lectures
at University of Finance and Economics.
Getting a spot in Professor Yu's class is no easy feat.
She's determined
and hasn't let anything stop her.
I've attended a few of Professor Yu's classes in the past,
and they were so captivating.
He's an excellent speaker.
If I had a charismatic and interesting finance lecturer
like Professor Yu during my college years,
I would've definitely pursued finance.
The world of financial journalism would have missed out on a rising star.
Really?
(Now he's getting jealous of Yu You.)
(Shan Shan was right.)
(Men like what they can't have and want to conquer.)
Absolutely.
When you think about it,
Professor Yu is three years older than you.
But I've seen him a few times.
He looks like he's younger than you
and has a more cheerful personality.
I almost forgot,
Professor Yu was quite famous in Qing'an.
I heard he skipped two grades in school.
He was already in college when I was in middle school.
Later, he went on to excel even more,
graduated from Harvard on a full scholarship,
obtained a dual degree from Cambridge,
and published numerous papers in the Science Citation Index.
I also heard he's really into sports.
Oh my, a genius professor who's young,
handsome, and interesting like this,
what student wouldn't like him?
Do you like him too?
Come on, who wouldn't like someone like that?
Where are you going?
Weren't we supposed to have dinner?
Since you enjoy classes so much,
I'm going to give you extra lesson.
Extra lesson?
Instead of having dinner, he is showing me these.
What is he trying to do?
I just thought
that you should broaden your horizons a bit
and understand the universality of the human world.
Otherwise, you might mistakenly think
that some people and things are unique.
Where's the universality in this?
(He's doing this because I praised Professor Yu.)
You not only excel academically
but also know so much.
You're truly outstanding. Now I feel inadequate.
How do you manage to excel in your studies
while having so many hobbies?
2015, 2016,
2017, 2018...
Why isn't there 2019?
Why are there no more medals after that?
In 2019, I left Mingyu and founded Yunchuang.
Later, work became very busy. I didn't have time for running or fitness.
So, why did you leave Mingyu at that time?
I'm just curious.
You don't have to answer if you don't want to.
During my postgraduate studies, I was very interested in investment.
After graduating,
I wanted to work in a related field.
However, after graduation,
I ended up joining Mingyu as per my father's expectations.
By that time, Mingyu had already grown quite large,
and it had many employees.
Many of the children of long-time employees
also joined Mingyu after they graduated.
To outsiders,
Mingyu looked like a massive carrier.
However, its management
lacked modern and scientific practices.
A company overly reliant on scale and capital
could lack flexibility
and fail to keep up with the times.
I noticed this issue back then
and made several suggestions.
However,
Mingyu was the result of a lifetime
of hard work by my father and his close friends.
It's difficult to make significant changes to things like that.
If we wanted to preserve my family's legacy,
my brother-in-law was a better fit.
That's why you handed it over to your brother-in-law?
I didn't hand it over.
My brother-in-law also put a lot of effort into Mingyu.
He rightfully deserved it.
Besides, I had my own aspirations.
I wanted to help entrepreneurs who wanted to make society better.
I wanted to explore more possibilities.
Shi Yan, I think you're very brave.
It takes a lot of courage
to break away from the established framework
and pursue your own dreams and visions.
Especially considering what you gave up, which many people would envy.
Throughout this process,
you had to withstand pressure,
endure people's criticism,
and quietly work hard.
But you did it,
and you did it very well.
You really think so?
Do I have a reward then?
Hello.
(Mr. Shi, your business trip has been arranged.)
From now on, there's no need to call me for such trivial matters.
(Zheng Shu Yi, what were you doing?)
(Why did you...)
I'm going on
a business trip in a couple of days.
Will you come with me?
I'll need to check my schedule when I get back.
I might have a business trip too.
I'll go back and check on it right away.
(Attention passengers traveling to Ancheng, )
(the flight will begin boarding in ten minutes.)
(Please proceed to gate 23.)
You may leave.
Mr. Fan is already in Ancheng. I've asked him to pick you up.
Mr. Shi, what a coincidence.
What are the odds.
I'm going to Ancheng on business too.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
- Hello. - (Why haven't you been answering my calls?)
I'm on a business trip.
(So sudden? Does Shi Yan know about it?)
It's with him.
With Shi Yan?
(Yi, good for you.)
But listen, no matter how much fun you have,
you'd better not go as two and return as three.
I got it. I have to go.
Hello.
Hi, Shi Yan. Have you landed?
I've sent the information about other battery companies to your email.
If you need any additional details, just let me know.
Got it.
I'm on a business trip with Miss Zheng.
She's sitting right next to me.
Who were you talking to?
It's that excellent Professor Yu you mentioned.
(You mustn't let him have it too easy.)
(I got it.)
Miss Zheng, you seem to excel at multitasking.
You're on a business trip with me
and chatting with Professor Yu at the same time.
Well, Mr. Shi, aren't you also looking at Zhanlan
and thinking about other battery companies?
We're quite the perfect pair, aren't we?
Mr. Shi, the hotel is just up ahead.
Mr. Fan, please take me to Kanglan Hotel.
Get off.
What are you doing?
I'm taking a cab to my hotel.
This is your hotel.
Zhanlan is nearby, so I booked a room here.
You also need to go to Zhanlan and do some follow-up interviews,
so you're staying here with me.
Staying with you?
What's wrong?
Don't you want to?