(Only For Love)
(Episode 1)
Yu Ling.
Do you need any help?
No, thank you.
Let me help you.
This way, I can say I've been part of a major interview.
I heard the editor highly recommended you.
You're the ace journalist of our magazine.
It has to be you doing this interview.
Yu Ling, the sales for our next issue will surely skyrocket.
The editor has given me such an important task.
I'm going to give it my all.
You've lost your chance to interview Shi Yan.
Why are you still reviewing your interview outline, Zheng Shu Yi?
Shi Yan is probably an unconventional man.
I just took another look at my outline.
Some questions seem too conservative.
They can definitely be improved.
I'm going to refine it further.
Are you okay?
Did losing the interview opportunity turn you insane?
Even if you have the perfect outline,
Shi Yan won't turn back to you.
I heard the editor-in-chief made a call to Mingyu Yunchuang
and highly recommended that person.
So, tactics matter more than competence.
There are plenty of important figures. Even if I've lost Shi Yan,
there will still be other opportunities.
Having tactics can only get you one interview,
but competence can help you produce excellent articles.
Since I lack tactics, I'll keep honing my competence.
Too bad you can't help me see what Shi Yan actually looks like.
Is he handsome or not?
Mr. Shi, the interview with Financial Introduce
is scheduled for 7 pm after dinner.
Journalist Xu Yu Ling will come to the office to interview you.
I don't think I picked Miss Xu as my interviewer.
She was strongly recommended by Financial Introduce's editor-in-chief.
She said she has extensive experience in various aspects,
and her writing quality is quite consistent.
If it's just a straightforward Q&A interview,
there is no need to see me in person.
Sending over the answers should suffice.
An interview should be an enlightening conversation and reflection.
I like Miss Zheng's interview outline.
My apologies for being empirical.
I'll rearrange it.
(Zhu Xing Guo on the Currency War)
Ms. Yi, you wanted to see me?
Okay, bye-bye.
You don't need to comfort me.
I understand, I'm fine.
Understand what?
I know you wanted to talk to me about the interview with Shi Yan .
I understand.
Yu Ling has more experience than me.
Though there's a tiny bit of disappointment,
my interview outline does have room for improvement.
So, there's no need for regrets.
I'll prepare more thoroughly next time.
You're dressed so nice today.
It's my boyfriend's birthday.
I want to look pretty for him.
Looking at it from another perspective, if I were to interview Shi Yan,
I wouldn't be able to celebrate with my boyfriend tonight.
So, this works out fine.
I see.
What's the matter, Ms. Yi?
The staff of Yunchuang just called me.
They said for tonight's interview,
Shi Yan has designated you
to conduct it.
It's a shame that you're celebrating your boyfriend's birthday tonight.
I suppose you don't have time. Right?
Shi Yan designated me?
Yes, he picked you in the end.
It's for tonight.
Are you okay for tonight?
Yes. I can do it.
You sure?
Great, tonight at seven.
Shi Yan's assistant will talk to you about the details.
Okay, I'll go prepare right away.
Hang on.
What about your boyfriend?
Birthdays come every year,
but the opportunity to interview Shi Yan is rare.
I'll wrap things up as quickly as possible,
maybe I can still celebrate with him before midnight.
This is so you, Zheng Shu Yi.
Mr. Shi, the details for the exclusive interview have been arranged.
Shall we schedule the interview in the main conference room?
Wasn't the representative of Le'an scheduled to come
for a meeting in the afternoon?
Dept. 1 had reserved the main conference room for the afternoon,
but they canceled it later.
It seems they've rescheduled the meetings
with representatives from Lieying and Le'an to the morning.
Both in the morning?
Yes, the system shows that it was personally
rearranged by Mr. Feng from Dept. 1.
Fan, drop me off somewhere.
I need to go back to the company.
Understood, Mr. Shi.
What about Miss Qin?
Go pick her up and take her back to the Shi family's mansion.
Yes, sir.
Impressive!
You've already secured the cover story for nine issues this year.
It's unprecedented in our magazine.
Even the editor's record is only eight issues in a year.
You're still having coffee? Do you even want to get better?
Drink this instead.
But why do you think Yunchuang
suddenly changed the interview journalist?
It shows their boss has a keen eye.
You mean Shi Yan?
Shi Yan must have a keen eye indeed.
Otherwise, he wouldn't have turned Mingyu Yunchuang
into such a success in just a few years.
But he's a bit strange too.
When Mingyu Group was facing its toughest times,
he left his family's company
and went out to start a new one.
What was he thinking?
You don't know how harsh the rumors about him were,
people calling him the runaway prince,
a selfish coward, and more.
There's also that girlfriend of his, the actress Bei Lin.
They say she dumped him immediately.
I actually think he's pretty brave.
Despite all the doubts,
he still chose that path.
That takes a lot of courage, you know.
It'd truly be an honor for us if we can
establish a partnership with Lieying.
Mr. Feng, you're too kind.
- We're practically family, after all.   - Yes, yes.
Exactly. We've been friends for so many years.
Yes.
Mr. Shi.
Get me two cold Cokes from the pantry.
Yes, sir.
I've been working on an article about Lieying lately.
They said that Yunchuang is considering an investment.
You know about Lieying, right?
They've been gaining a lot of momentum in the last couple of years.
Many companies want to invest in them.
There isn't a single clear picture of Shi Yan anywhere on the internet.
He became even more low-key after starting his own venture,
never appearing in front of the press.
If we could get him to record an exclusive video or audio piece
for our digital magazine,
it would surely attract a lot of readers.
You're still thinking about upgrading the digital magazine?
Financial information is closely related to everyone.
If we don't revamp it
and just stick to the same content as the print version,
without effective interaction with the readers,
we'll only grow further apart from them.
You make a good point.
But our magazine doesn't currently have the manpower or finances
to carry out this digital magazine upgrade.
Even if you convince the editor-in-chief,
she'll surely ask you,
who's going to do it, how are they going to do it,
and where will the money come from.
I'll do it.
I want the highers-up to see
that I have the capability to lead the upgrade of the digital magazine.
Then, by monetizing the content,
we can meet the manpower and financial needs
of the upgraded digital magazine.
That's bold!
Go for it. You got my full support!
You should drop by our place more often.
Sure, I'd be happy to.
- Hi, Mr. Shi.   - Hi, Mr. Shi.
It's cold.
Thank you, Mr. Shi.
By the way,
I looked at the data and information you updated on my way here.
- The progress is impressive.   - Yes.
Yes, we just finished it last night.
Lily, please take Mr. Chen to the adjacent meeting room.
I'll join you in a moment.
Okay, Mr. Shi. Mr. Chen, please come with me.
Mr. Shi.
Mr. Shi Yan, if you have any requests, please don't hesitate to ask.
After all, we have a deep relationship with Mingyu.
Over the past two years,
we've had business dealings with your father as well.
Of course, given the circumstances at that time,
we certainly wanted to help.
So, I believe
we'll have a great time working together this time.
Mr. Shi, do you have any questions?
Thank you.
I've already reviewed the situation with Lieying,
but what I'm more interested in
is the future direction your company is focusing on.
Our company is among the top-ranking ones in the industry.
As for Le'an Technology,
they used to be one of our suppliers.
This is unrelated to industry position.
According to the information,
if your company's ultimate goal is to serve a broader public,
there must be further technological advancement.
However, so far, I haven't seen a solution.
Mr. Shi, here's the thing.
Lieying is an established company.
Investing in them will help us enter the industry quickly.
Besides, Lieying has a close relationship with Mingyu.
We've been through thick and thin together.
That's right.
Yes, I understand.
My father holds Lieying in high regard.
However, business is business.
The essence of investment is buying future value.
If Lieying wants to collaborate with Yunchuang,
you should present a plan to enhance your core technology.
After all, we are an investment company,
not a charity.
Wouldn't you agree?
Thank you for your valuable time today.
Mr. Feng, please see Mr. Li off.
Mr. Li...
- Mr. Li...   - Mr. Chen, this way, please.
Technical breakthroughs take time,
but once achieved,
they will be a revolutionary boost for our domestic chip production.
So, keep up the good work
and create our own patents.
I have high hopes for you.
Yunchuang will provide you with the maximum support.
Thank you, Mr. Shi.
If we can resolve the R&D funding issue,
I'm very confident we can make significant progress.
I'll pay another visit to Le'an tomorrow.
- We can discuss it further then.   - Okay, I should get going.
Mr. Shi,
I'll be straightforward.
Lieying's owner, Mr. Li, is an old friend of your father and Mr. Tian.
If you insist on choosing Le'an,
I'm afraid it won't be easy to convince the board.
Meetings are a fundamental part of investments.
If you can't even manage the meeting schedule with potential partners,
how can I trust your judgment on the project?
Mingyu's investments are based on future trends,
not personal connections.
Mr. Tian,
Mr. Shi suddenly came during our meeting today.
Hi, Mr. Shi.
(Uncle, didn't you promise to come pick me up today?)
Something came up last minute.
(Uncle, do you not love me anymore?)
Mr. Shi.
I have to go. Talk later.
I've dropped off Miss Qin.
She's been complaining that you didn't personally pick her up
and asked me to convey her frustration to you.
Is there anything else?
Yes, Mr. Guan Ji said he hadn't been able to reach you on your phone.
What does he want?
Mr. Guan Ji is hosting a dinner tonight at the Warner Estate.
He insists on your attendance.
I'm busy.
Mr. Guan Ji anticipated you'd say that.
He said he has an important person he'd like to introduce to you.
(Yu You)
All right, tell him I'll attend tonight.
What about the interview with Financial Introduce this evening?
Explain the situation to them and reschedule it.
Understood, I'll do that right away.
(Babe, you won't be working overtime today, right?)
Xing Zhou,
do you remember the interview with Shi Yan I told you about?
The editor just informed me
that they've switched the journalist
for Shi Yan's interview, and it's me now.
(But we only celebrate my birthday once a year.)
I'm sorry, Xing Zhou.
I've been preparing for the interview with Shi Yan for over two months.
It really is a rare opportunity.
He specifically requested for me to do it.
If I don't go, we won't have a cover story for next issue.
You know how many stories he has.
He hasn't done any interviews since founding Mingyu Yunchuang until now.
This will be his first exclusive interview.
(Fine. I guess we can celebrate a little later.)
(I'll wait for you downstairs at the office after I finish work.)
I'm sorry, Xing Zhou.
It was so sudden.
(It's okay, I understand.)
(You've put in so much preparation for this interview.)
(You have to make the most of it.)
Thank you, Xing Zhou.
You're the best.
The interview starts at seven.
I'll try to wrap it up within two hours.
There'll still be time for me to join you, blow out candles, make a wish,
and have birthday cake.
(I'll come pick you up after you're done.)
I'll send you my location later.
You're amazing.
So, your boyfriend is completely fine with it?
Yes, he said he understands and even offered to pick me up.
Your boyfriend seems overly understanding.
Unlike mine, he's extremely possessive.
If I were to stand him up just once,
no matter the reason, he'd get mad at me.
Let's go.
(Hello, Miss Zheng, This is Chen Sheng from Mingyu Yunchuang.)
Hello, Mr. Chen.
Miss Zheng, Mr. Shi has to cancel
the interview tonight due to personal reasons.
We will need to reschedule.
(We are very sorry.)
When is Mr. Shi planning to reschedule?
(How about the same time next week?)
(Or are there any convenient times for you next week?)
If we reschedule for next week,
we won't have a cover story for the next issue of our magazine.
Can Mr. Shi spare some time in the next two days?
No matter how early or late.
We can even split it into two sessions.
I'm afraid that won't be possible.
(Mr. Shi's schedule for the next two days is already fully booked.)
Then...
How about setting aside two hours tonight?
Even one hour is fine.
Mr. Shi has a personal commitment tonight.
He can't free up any time.
(We're really sorry.)
Hang on...
Shan Shan, you're beautiful and well-connected.
Can you help me find out where Shi Yan will be tonight?
Hello.
Shi Yan?
I don't know him.
But you're in luck.
(I do know that Shi Yan's good friend, Guan Ji, )
(is hosting a private banquet at Warner Estate tonight.)
(I reckon that most people in Jiangcheng)
(who have connections with Guan Capital will be attending.)
(I'm not sure if Shi Yan will be there.)
I'll try my luck then.
(Wait a minute.)
(Aren't you supposed to celebrate)
(your boyfriend Yue Xing Zhou's birthday tonight?)
(You're just going to bail on him?)
Well, I can't bail on Shi Yan, can I?
(Very well.)
(A career-driven woman is the most charming.)
Thank you for your kind words.
Warner Estate...
Please enjoy.
Come see me.
Mr. Chen, good evening.
I'm in Warner Estate now.
(Miss Zheng, how did you...)
I'm sorry for showing up uninvited,
but it was a matter of urgency.
Could you please let Mr. Shi know that I can wait for him here?
I hope he can sense my sincerity
and spare some time for the interview.
Tell you what, find a place and wait first.
I'll go talk to Mr. Shi,
(but I can't guarantee he'll have time to meet with you.)
(There's a good chance you might end up coming here for nothing.)
Understood. Regardless, I'm very grateful to you.
I think Guan Ji organized this banquet
just to get everyone together for a meal and some drinks.
It can't be that simple.
I heard that Yu You
was specially recruited by Guan Capital from abroad.
He's a professor at University of Finance and Economics.
Only Guan Capital could have
the clout to hire him as a consultant.
I saw that Shi's son is here too.
Shi Wen Guang's son is so unreliable.
When Mingyu was in trouble, he went off to start his own company.
Shi Wen Guang had no choice but to entrust
the company to his son-in-law and those outsiders.
That's outrageous.
From what I see, the two young men from the Guan and Shi families
are quite ambitious.
Bringing in some professor from abroad,
they're probably planning to make some waves.
One is timid, and the other likes to have fun.
What waves can they make?
Just puffing themselves up. Let's go.
Is Guan Ji running late again?
Mr. Guan Ji said he's stuck in traffic,
but he'll be here in ten minutes.
Is there anything else?
Miss Zheng from Financial Introduce is also here.
She said she's waiting for you
and hopes you can spare some time to do the interview tonight.
Zheng Shu Yi?
Didn't I ask you to reschedule with her?
I did inform her,
but she said if the interview isn't conduct as planned,
the next issue of the magazine will be left without a cover story.
I'm not sure how she found out about your private schedule.
I have a meeting at Le'an Technology tomorrow,
so I definitely won't have time for an interview tonight.
Since she came all the way here, she probably hasn't eaten.
Arrange some food for her and a car to take her back.
It's not easy to get a taxi here.
Yes, Mr. Shi.
Graduated from Harvard University on a full scholarship.
A dual Ph.D. in economics and finance from Cambridge University!
Soon to be the youngest professor at University of Finance and Economics.
What an impressive resume.
- Thank you.   - You're welcome.
Excuse me.
Are you Yu You, Professor Yu?
You know me?
I've been reading some of your papers.
Fintech, technology-driven financial innovation,
it's not just impacting the macroeconomy
but also has the potential to bring profound changes to our everyday lives.
I feel a close connection to this field
because it's so relevant to our daily lives.
That's right. That's also why I chose this research direction.
In the past, finance and capital seemed like lofty concepts,
but now we're exploring
how they can transform our lives to what extent.
If I ever have the chance,
I'd really like to return to my alma mater
and attend some of your lectures, Professor Yu.
You're a graduate of University of Finance and Economics?
Yes, I'm currently working at Financial Introduce.
I'm a journalist.
Professor Yu, may I add you on WeChat?
- Mr. Shi.   - Of course.
- I'll scan your code.   - Okay.
That's Zheng Shu Yi from Financial Introduce.
Done.
Zheng Shu Yi. I'll put "journalist" on Note.
Thank you.
Zheng Shu Yi?
The winner of the annual Person of the Year interview
is the journalist of the article
"Zhu Xing Guo on the Currency War,"
Zheng Shu Yi.
I'm so sorry. I'm late.
Guan Ji, it's been a while since you rode horses with me.
My bad.
I heard you went to Qionghai, so I was waiting for your return.
Well, I'm back now.
Then I'll await you at the riding club tomorrow.
From what I know,
tonight's banquet isn't open to the media.
Yes, I'm here privately to wait for an interviewee.
Work is important, but so is your health.
You don't look very well.
It's nothing, I'll be fine after taking a pill.
We'll go in first.
Okay.
I should get going.
Let's go in.
Mr. Shi!
I'm sorry, Miss Zheng. Mr. Shi really doesn't have time tonight,
but I'll arrange for you to do the interview at the nearest available time.
You haven't had dinner, right?
Go and have something to eat first,
and I'll arrange a car to take you home.
It's fine. Someone is coming to pick me up.
I was so close.
At least let me see what you look like.
- It's been so long.   - Yes, indeed, Mr. Zhang.
- It's been so long.   - Nice to meet you.
Mr. Wang, how have you been?
Hello, Professor Yu.
Welcome back to China.
Hello, Mr. Shi. Thank you.
I read your research
on the impact of financial constraints
on the financing behavior of listed companies.
It differs from many domestic perspectives.
That was last year's thinking.
It got a bit lengthy.
My thoughts have evolved this year.
Embracing change is the right way.
I'm glad that Guan Ji recruited you.
There should be many opportunities
for us to seek your advice.
Mr. Shi, you're flattering me.
The future of Yunchuang is limitless.
We can learn from each other.
By the way,
a while ago, I read an article titled "Zhu Xing Guo on the Currency War."
The viewpoints are sharp.
The writing is both insightful and warm. It was quite inspiring.
You might want to take a look if you have time.
I vaguely remember that article.
It was well-written.
Cheers.
Ladies and gentlemen, may I have your attention, please?
Today, we have gathered here,
and you are all long-standing friends of Guan Capital.
As the year comes to a close, I've organized this appreciation banquet
as a token of gratitude for the sincere cooperation we've shared.
At the same time, we'd like to formally introduce a new friend,
our strategic advisor,
Mr. Yu You, a finance professor.
Thank you.
Cheers.
Enjoy yourselves.
- Allow me to introduce...   - We can skip that.
Yu You, you have no idea
he's been eager to meet you for a long time.
I haven't even seen him this infatuated with girls.
You flatter me, Mr. Shi.
All right.
We've got this major task sorted out,
and I've secured the great expert for you.
My dad supports us, that's for sure.
So, the next step is to win over those old-timers at Yunchuang.
As for your dad, do you want to...
There's no rush, let's take it slowly.
Right.
We can now consider ourselves three stooges...
I'm not a stooge like you.
Right. We're like the Three Musketeers of Jiangcheng,
unstoppable with our sharp wit.
Cheers.
Xing Zhou, where are you?
(Traffic is really jammed. Give me a bit more time.)
(I'll be there as soon as I can.)
Okay, I'll be waiting on the roadside
so you won't have to look for me.
Miss Zheng, long time no see.
What are you doing here?
Long time indeed, Mr. Zhang.
I'm here for an interview.
I haven't had a chance to properly thank you
for the fantastic article you wrote for me last time.
How about I give you a ride?
Mr. Zhang, you're too kind.
It's your rich experience
that gives me room to shine.
My boyfriend will be here soon.
No need to trouble you.
All right then, take care.
Miss, are you alone?
Would you like me to give you a ride?
It's pouring rain, and it's not easy to catch a cab.
Thanks, but no need. My boyfriend will be here shortly.
Why are you standing here alone if you have a boyfriend?
Who says having a boyfriend means you can't stand here?
Why is Miss Zheng still here?
Didn't you arrange a ride for her?
She said someone was coming to pick her up.
How much longer, Xing Zhou?
I'm freezing.
Could it be that her ride can't make it?
At this time, on this stretch of road,
and with the rain,
it's difficult to get a cab.
Get the car over.
I know it's raining, but I'm waiting for my boyfriend.
That's right. I have a boyfriend. Thank you and bye.
It can't be him, can it?
Drive.
She really was waiting for her boyfriend.
I didn't expect that
she really has a boyfriend.
I had several phone calls with her today,
and I felt like she's quite easy to get along with.
Maybe it's because she didn't succeed in the interview today,
and there were people trying to strike up conversations with her all day,
plus the weather was so cold,
so she was a bit impatient.
You seem quite concerned about whether she has a boyfriend or not.
No.
I just think she's very good-looking,
and she's competent in her work.
It's perfectly normal for her to have a boyfriend.
So, you think she's good-looking
and competent in her work?
Definitely. And internally, they have high hopes
that she will skip ranks
and secure the position of deputy editor.
- Chen Sheng, I've noticed something.   - What is it?
You seem to have more talent
for being a gossip columnist than being my executive assistant.
I'm sorry, Shu Yi.
It was pouring today, and the road conditions were bad.
I got stuck in a traffic jam just as I was arriving.
- You must be freezing.   - I'm fine.
How was your birthday today?
Did you have a good time?
My girlfriend didn't even spend my birthday with me. How could I be happy?
I'm sorry.
Who celebrated with you today?
Who else could it be?
Xu Feng?
He even wears cologne now.
It has a light and unique scent.
His taste is not bad.
The next time you see him,
ask him what cologne he's using.
I think it would suit you too.
How did the interview go today?
Long story.
Let's not talk about that. It's upsetting.
Okay, don't be upset, babe.
Why aren't you answering?
I'm all yours after work.
No work calls allowed.
Come over later.
I'll make you a bowl of longevity noodles.
It's fine. It's already so late,
and you're not feeling well. Get some rest.
There will be plenty of chances for you to make it up to me.
Why are you so considerate?
Well, it's because I love you, silly.
It's still your birthday.
Happy birthday, Xing Zhou.
Thank you, babe.
I'll go home now.
Hello. What's the matter?
What?
I need to inform the editor.
Where's my phone?
The hospital?
How did it end up at the hospital?
Was it stolen?
I was definitely holding my phone when I got in the car.
What is Xing Zhou doing in the hospital?
Is he sick?
Did he have a car accident?
He really is here.
License plate with repeated digits.
Better not mess with them.
She's probably his friend.
It's perfectly normal to visit a friend in the hospital at night.