(Only For Love)
(Episode 6)
Have your meal. I'm going back.
Are you going home to wait for Miss Zheng?
Did I say something wrong?
Didn't you say you didn't want to discuss personal matters at work?
Will this be too abrupt?
Will he get angry and make things even more difficult for me?
What's the situation now?
Zheng Shu Yi, you can't lose.
Who cares if he will get angry or not?
I must get specific feedback today.
Miss Zheng, why are you coming to see me at this hour?
(I'm stuck on my draft. Don't you know what this is about?)
I just felt that you might want to see me, so I came to you.
Tell me.
Why do you feel that I want to see you?
Otherwise, why would you reject my drafts three times?
I see.
Not bad, you're confident and resolute.
Your logic flows smoothly.
I almost think so too.
Even my editor and editor-in-chief,
the most critical duo in the financial journalism industry,
couldn't find any faults in my drafts.
Yet you rejected it three times without giving any specific feedback.
Is there any other reason aside from wanting to see me?
My reason is that
I'm not satisfied.
Not satisfied? What are you not satisfied with?
Point out each issue, and I'll revise it until you're satisfied.
If you can't point out what's wrong, that proves that you want to see me.
You deliberately used this method to attract my attention,
so that I would come to see you.
In the first draft, there were too many overly flattering words.
I believe an excellent personal interview
should be different from ordinary corporate PR materials.
The writing should be more rational and objective.
Journalists can have their preferences,
but they shouldn't affect the readers' reading and thinking.
You should've realized this problem.
So, in the second draft, you changed it into an objective article.
You didn't miss out on any contents.
However, because you cared too much about its completeness and objectivity,
it lacked emphasis.
The focus of this interview should be the future of Yunchuang,
not Mingyu Group, and certainly not my personal development.
What about the current draft? What's the problem?
You put a lot of effort into the draft, and many issues have been improved.
But I think there should be room for discussion.
I remember I said this in the car that day.
I believe a company's technical capabilities and innovation
to a certain extent determine its core competitiveness and development.
I expressed this viewpoint to facilitate discussion,
not to draw a conclusion.
Thus, I think when you're producing the official article,
it should more faithfully represent my expression and true attitude.
I humbly accept your opinions.
This statement is indeed not rigorous enough as written by me,
but everyone has a different interpretation.
You can't ask me to rewrite the entire article just because of one issue.
The draft has been delayed for so long.
If I don't submit it soon, we'll have a blank space in the magazine.
I really want to write this article well.
Please help me.
Yunchuang is a very reputable company that has always pursued rigor.
Due to different interpretations,
you have put my words in a more absolute manner,
representing my personal views and judgments.
But what I really want to explore is the potential of this industry.
The meaning is completely different,
and the impact it generates will certainly be vastly different.
I understand your point now.
Then I will amend it now.
Come here.
Don't you need to revise the draft?
Amend it inside.
(Wouldn't it be inconvenient to amend the draft at his house at this hour?)
What if I run into his niece again?
Mr. Shi, is it convenient for me to go to your house this late?
You were lying in wait for me in front of my house.
Now you're starting to worry if it's inconvenient for me?
I'm just eager to revise the draft.
Don't worry, no one can disturb you.
You can definitely revise it until I'm satisfied.
(She's really here to revise the draft.)
Yue, are you sure this will work?
Why not?
This gift is rare even for my uncle.
It's good wine.
But I advise you not to have high hopes.
If he finds out you give him this wine to ask him not to let you work,
I don't know how he'll react.
Why not give the wine to me instead?
Don't waste it.
Don't even think about it.
I'm counting on this to save me from this desperate situation.
You don't want to help me, even Grandpa won't help me.
This bottle of wine is my only lifeline.
Do you want some water?
Lemon water, thanks.
Thank you, Mr. Shi.
(He has a good memory.)
What's wrong?
Did you encounter any problems?
No.
What's the matter then?
I want
to drink the one you're holding.
Thanks.
(He didn't even look at me.)
(It seems that this lipstick color doesn't work.)
Hello?
I'm very busy. It's inconvenient.
(No, Uncle!)
(Mistress?)
What's wrong?
Is anyone coming?
No.
Is your niece coming back?
You seem to be very interested in my niece.
No, why would I?
I don't even know her.
He said he's very busy and it's inconvenient.
He said the same thing the last time I called him.
Why inconvenience a man could have?
Unless he's with a woman.
I think your uncle must be hiding a woman in his house.
Hiding a woman in his house?
It's been three years.
My uncle is finally seeing someone.
Have you met that woman?
Shi Yan won't let me see her. How could I possibly meet her?
Have you ever seen him bring his girlfriend home?
It's done. Take a look.
How is it?
Too wordy.
Fine.
I don't believe I can't get it done.
I've simplified it.
Mr. Shi, please check if there are any problems.
That's not what I meant when I said this.
What did you mean then?
Figure it out yourself.
How about I write it for you directly?
Okay.
Really?
Is there really nothing to amend?
It's about there.
If you're satisfied,
does that mean we can take it a step further?
Take a step further?
Take a step further
to explore the possibilities of a special coverage.
Since you're satisfied with my draft,
I'm sure you'd be satisfied with my revision service as well.
So, can you consider the special coverage I mentioned before?
If I take a step further with you,
what benefit does that offer?
If you accept my proposal,
I'll definitely complete the articles for this series well.
I guarantee you'll be satisfied.
But...
I have a small request.
I hope these articles can be published
in the digital magazine of Financial Introduce.
Is this how the journalists in Financial Introduce do business?
I haven't even agreed to your interview for special coverage,
and you're already making additional demands.
Sorry for my lack of consideration.
I should have taken it step by step
and discussed this with you after completing this interview.
(Did I say something that offended him?)
(Mr. Shi said)
(he doesn't like discussing personal matters during work hours)
(and at the workplace.)
(Right.)
(He doesn't like discussing personal matters)
(during work hours and at the workplace.)
(He probably wouldn't like discussing work)
(during personal time and in a personal space either.)
Mr. Shi, please consider my proposal.
Also, can you send me an email confirming the draft now?
According to the procedure,
this should be confirmed by our company's PR Department.
I'll go through it again tomorrow.
Sure, Mr. Shi.
If you have any issues tomorrow, just let me know.
I have no problem. I can cooperate and further amend it.
Are you sure there's no problem?
I'm sure there's no problem.
You stayed for so long at a strange man's house at this late hour.
Your boyfriend doesn't have a problem with it?
I don't have a boyfriend.
It's true.
On the day I first met you,
I broke up with him after I went back.
It was the day of Guan Capital's banquet, outside Warner Estate.
You still remember, right?
So?
So...
Can I pursue you?
If I say no,
will you stop?
No.
Then why are you asking me?
I'm just following the procedure
to show you some respect.
Thank you for respecting me.
The draft is done. You can leave now.
Mr. Shi, good night.
I'll add you on WeChat when I get back.
I can chat with you when you're bored.
I'm very good at chatting. I have a lot of stickers.
Let me remind you one last time.
Your uncle won't be happy if you show up at this hour.
I don't care.
I want to see who that woman is.
My uncle never brought his girlfriend home before.
I want to see who the amazing woman is.
Maybe if my uncle is in a good mood for dating, he won't let me go to work.
That's weird.
Shouldn't she be busy revising the draft?
What is she doing here?
Who is it?
What?
My uncle won't let me reveal my identity.
Everyone knows that you're the young master of the Guan family.
I don't want to get involved with you.
Who is this?
She's the senior I told you about. She's very critical of me.
Is the threshold for journalists so high now?
I advise you not to have any evil thoughts on her.
My uncle doesn't like her.
He's been rejecting her drafts multiple times.
Of course, it's mainly because Uncle loves me so much.
Where is she?
Where's the woman?
Lipstick?
There was really a woman.
What are you doing here?
Didn't I ask you to go back to Grandpa's house?
I came to deliver this wine to you.
Such a good thing should be delivered to you as soon as possible.
What if you get too busy and don't have time to have dinner at Grandpa's?
Leave it here and go home early to rest,
so you don't have trouble waking up for work tomorrow.
You should have some sense of being an employee now.
Uncle, why don't you ask the woman to stay?
What woman?
The one you just had a drink with.
It's so late, why didn't you ask her to stay?
Is it because she's not pretty enough?
Or did she reject you?
Or
maybe you haven't dated for so long that you're scared now?
What's wrong with Shi Yan?
I know, right?
It was the first time in my life that I confessed to someone,
and he just kicked me out after hearing it.
Is this reasonable?
Is Shi Yan even a man?
Now I'm sure he's a man,
but he's a childish one.
Shi Yan is childish?
Yes.
Boys will be boys.
When they aren't being honest with themselves, women don't stand a chance.
Haven't you read those novels about domineering CEOs?
The more a man likes you, the less he admits it.
The more he likes you, the more he wants to bully you.
Shi Yan is exactly like that.
Qin Shi Yue.
What nonsense is running through your mind?
You invited her to have a drink at your house at this late hour.
After having a drink, you immediately told her to leave,
without spending some time together.
Oh my God.
Uncle, are you a pervert?
You're talking about a pervert.
That's roughly the idea.
Try to understand it.
Otherwise, why would he keep rejecting your drafts?
Because
there were some issues with my drafts.
Of course, that's part of the reason.
But the most important thing is he wants to attract your attention.
He must be interested in you.
I really admire your inexplicable confidence.
This is a conclusion I've drawn through countless practical experiences.
As the saying goes, experience is the best teacher.
Though the tactics are old, they work.
But why did you suddenly confess to him today?
Do you really have feelings for him?
How is that possible?
I did it for the sake of my article.
Didn't you tell me to...
Then why do I feel like something is off?
You two were alone and there was a sense of attraction in the air.
And you suddenly confessed to him.
Could it be that you've unconsciously developed feelings for him?
Think carefully about what I said.
I won't argue with you anymore.
I'm heading back. I have to work tomorrow.
Honestly, I think he's interested in you too.
If both of you are interested, what are you waiting for?
Strike while the iron is hot.
- Goodbye.   - Bye.
Finish the food, don't waste it.
When it comes to dating, you have to learn Guan Ji.
Don't be so insensitive.
If you really like her, you have to take the initiative.
If you invite her over, you should strike while the iron is hot.
You still have time to talk nonsense here.
It seems that the job at the magazine is indeed very easy.
How about this?
Straight away come and work at Yunchuang. Stop dawdling.
No, thanks.
Uncle, you should rest early.
Working at the magazine is not easy at all.
I didn't get off work until after eight o'clock today.
It's been a long day. I worked hard and took it very seriously.
I have to go back and get some rest.
Don't act pitiful in front of me.
It won't work.
Also...
Save your money on wine.
(Silence)
Shi Yan didn't say I couldn't pursue him,
so he implicitly agreed.
What am I waiting for?
Mr. Shi, how afraid are you that others will find your WeChat account?
(I'm home.)
(Mr. Shi, are you sleeping already?)
(I think you must be very busy.)
(You just need to read the first three words of the previous message.)
I saw this online.
It can express my feelings without being too cheesy, which is just right.
(It will be cloudy with light rain tonight, )
(with temperatures ranging from 5 to 12°C.)
(Tomorrow will be cloudy turning to partly cloudy, )
(with temperatures between 3 and 10°C.)
(There will be continuous rainy weather in the coming days, )
(coinciding with the workweek. )
(Please remember to plan your travel accordingly.)
(Make sure to stay warm.)
(Uncle.)
(When it comes to dating, you have to learn Guan Ji.)
(Don't be so insensitive.)
(If you really like her, you have to take the initiative.)
(If you invite her over, you should strike while the iron is hot.)
(Actress)
Unsubscribe?
Shi Yan, what is wrong with you?
Mr. Shi, I just got a call from Le'an Technology.
They said they have reviewed our funding pool plan.
Mr. Chen said while the funding pool provides some assurance
for their future research and development,
there is still a considerable gap compared to Lieying's acquisition price
at the current stage.
So, they are very concerned about the solution
to the technical issues you mentioned last time.
Mr. Shi, our last offer was already the highest price we could give.
Although there's an increase, it cannot match the acquisition price.
If we continue to deadlock here, will it lead to changes?
I understand. Go get busy first.
(Do you have time? Let's meet and talk.)
Shu Yi, good morning.
Morning, Shi Yue.
What's the matter?
No, nothing.
Your lipstick looks really nice.
Take it.
I...
It's not that.
She seems to never use that shade normally.
Zheng Shu Yi seems to have had her drafts
rejected several times by Yunchuang.
She had never been in this situation before.
How do you know she didn't offend anyone?
Encountering a client who rejected drafts without giving feedback
is really tough.
(So to say, Uncle is indeed my biological uncle.)
(But Zheng Shu Yi is probably not the woman.)
(Who could bear to intentionally make their crush suffer?)
(Is that even humane?)
(But...)
(My uncle might like this.)
(I feel like he's capable of doing such a thing.)
Zheng Shu Yi.
Can you stop being so hardworking?
At least let us take a breather.
(Securing Guan Capital is a crucial step for Mingyu Yunchuang.)
(Guan Capital invited Yu You back to the country at this moment.)
(And Shi Yan went to his welcome dinner.)
You're already choosing the next topic.
You're not giving us any chance.
Why? Have you settled Shi Yan?
Basically.
(Yu You's opinion should be essential to Guan Capital's decision.)
(Talking to him will surely provide many clues.)
(Actually, it's not hard to guess what Shi Yan wants to do.)
(But the key is how he will proceed with each step.)
(Readers must be very interested in this.)
That's good. It's all 10 rings.
Last time it was rock climbing. This time, it's shooting.
You really don't seem like a college professor.
You don't look like a rich second-generation either.
Actually, Bruce is also a bit different.
How so?
The domestic market is vast,
and the conditions you offered Bruce are very attractive.
Many people would consider this a great choice.
But Bruce is just like me.
He likes excitement, adventure, and challenges.
So, salary and conditions are not his primary factors for consideration.
So, don't try to predict or judge him with fixed thinking.
He's coming next week. Have you figured out how to convince him?
Do you have any suggestions?
We both enjoy doing interesting and challenging things.
Actually, so does Bruce.
Interesting and challenging, both are indispensable.
Then why are you willing to return to China?
In fact, the academic environment is getting better here.
And I also get to meet friends like you and Guan Ji.
Speaking of which, you're very interesting.
What you do is also very challenging.
You could've accepted Mingyu Group's offer and made everyone happy,
but you chose to start your own business and establish Yunchuang.
Isn't it fun working together with you?
So, I'm that annoying, huh?
But I believe if I could attract you back to China,
I can certainly attract Bruce too.
And I'm confident that Bruce will be impressed by Chen Kang's spirit.
Sorry, I have to take this call.
Hello.
(Professor Yu, I'm Zheng Shu Yi.)
(I don't know if you still remember me.)
Miss Zheng, of course I remember you.
(Here's the thing, )
(it was too rushed last time, and I didn't get to talk to you.)
(I would like to schedule a time with you next week)
(to ask you some questions about the industry.)
Okay, sure.
Let me check my schedule, I'll get back to you later.
(Okay, thank you very much.)
Okay.
Can I pursue you?
Come on, one more round.
Ms. Yi, I've proofread the article of my interview with Guan Ji.
It's ready for layout and printing.
Ms. Yi?
Ms. Yi, Mr. Shi has already verbally confirmed.
Yunchuang will respond officially soon.
This version of the article should be fine.
Shu Yi, we understand you've worked hard this time,
but we have to consider the overall situation.
Can we rely on verbal confirmation?
The front-page content is not child's play.
If something goes wrong, the responsibility will be significant.
I have confidence in my article.
And Mr. Shi also promised me he would give me email confirmation today.
What's the use of your confidence at this moment?
If something goes wrong, how will you take responsibility?
Will you resign?
Since he agreed to reply by today, let's wait until midnight.
If there's no response or it's not approved by Yunchuang,
then Yu Ling's article will be on the front page.
I'm fine with that.
What about you?
That's fine with me.
You seemed out of sorts just now.
It's not like your usual standard.
(Mr. Shi, it's urgent.)
(You confirmed my draft yesterday.)
(Please send me a confirmation as soon as possible.)
Is that so? Let's have another round.
(Miss Zheng, Mr. Shi isn't with me today.)
(He must be busy. I can't reach him either. I can't help you.)
It's so late now.
So what if it doesn't get approved?
What are we waiting for here?
What can we do? We work in the news business. We have to be rigorous.
We agreed to wait until 12 am, it has to be 12 am sharp, not a minute less.