(Only For Love)
(Episode 10)
(Unsubscribe)
(Morning)
Oh, right. We can use WeChat now.
(I have a date today. So, I won't see you.)
(I also have a date today.)
(I won't see you either.)
(Morning! Sending you a heart.)
(Don't forget the concert tonight.)
(Want to have dinner together?)
Well, maybe not. Better not overdo it.
I don't want to push my luck.
Please line up and enter in an orderly manner.
What a coincidence.
Coincidence?
Weren't you the one who invited me?
I invited you?
The one I invited is...
(Hang on.)
(Shi Yan.)
(SY.)
(It's Shi Yue?)
I was just joking.
I was about to urge you, and here you are.
That's quite a coincidence.
That's what I said.
Shall we go in?
Sure, let's go.
What's wrong?
This song is really sad.
It makes me feel so sad.
So sad.
Shu Yi, did you just go through a breakup?
Is that why you're feeling emotional?
We broke up a month ago.
He totally cheated on me.
But I'm not emotional because of that.
I'm just thinking,
when you experience a breakup,
it shouldn't be women feeling devastated,
the scumbags should go screw themselves.
You're absolutely right.
But, Shu Yi, with your looks,
I can't believe you got cheated on.
You're very beautiful.
I know, right?
But it still happened.
It's because that guy was blind.
He cares more about money than appearances.
The rich girl he's after has a very wealthy uncle.
Shu Yi,
you're handling this so gracefully.
I really admire you.
However, after getting along with her uncle,
I'm starting to realize that he is actually quite nice.
So now, I'm kind of torn.
What are you waiting for then?
Let me tell you, don't overthink it.
You've already lost your ex,
don't lose this new guy too.
But he's not immoral like his niece, right?
No, he's nothing like his niece at all.
Shu Yi, I'm going home.
- Okay, drive safe.   - Bye-bye.
(Professor Yu?)
(Is he a fan of Mom too?)
Mom, can you give me
some of those limited edition albums from when you debuted?
The limited edition ones. The kind you can't find in stores.
Shu Yi?
What a coincidence.
Professor Yu, what are the odds of running into you here?
Shi Yan gave me the ticket, so I came to chill.
You've seen the interview outline.
Can we set the time for the interview this week?
No problem. How about next Tuesday at 3pm?
Sounds good.
Let me give you a ride home.
It's fine. I've called a cab.
Okay then. Stay safe.
Bye.
(Since you came to me, )
(I might as well take the chance and stage a little accident.)
Mr. Shi, I sprained my ankle.
It's all because of you.
You should take responsibility.
Why should I?
Because every time I see you, I can't focus on the road anymore.
(Miss, where are you?)
Stay there. I'll go to you.
Shi Yan! Are you serious? Shi Yan!
Oh, heavens, why am I so unlucky?
Shi Yan, you heartless man.
You are uncaring.
Am I not beautiful?
Am I not pitiable?
Your eyes aren't just nearsighted.
They're designed to avoid good-looking people.
Someone like you should grow old alone! Without...
Go on, what else?
Someone like me should what? Without what?
Mr. Shi,
I think I can explain to you in the car. Don't you think?
You haven't come up with an explanation yet?
What's the rush?
Even a test gives you ninety minutes to answer.
Ouch.
I'm sure I've injured my bone.
It hurts so much.
Yet you can still talk so much.
(Outpatient)
Get out. Let's get you to the doctor and have your bone checked.
My foot hurts.
I can't stand up, and I definitely can't walk.
If it weren't for you, I wouldn't have sprained my ankle.
You should take responsibility for this.
Zheng Shu Yi, stop exaggerating.
I'm not exaggerating.
Can't you be a bit more considerate?
Is your heart made of stone, Mr. Shi?
No.
- Then...   - You said it yourself, I don't have a heart.
Why are you so petty?
Try wearing these shoes and spraining your ankle.
It's as painful as having your ankle broken.
Excruciatingly painful, okay?
You've never worn them, so you wouldn't understand.
Did your ex-girlfriend ever tell you
that you look handsome from this angle?
Did your ex-boyfriend ever tell you
that you're heavy?
No way.
Nobody has ever carried me like this.
But I think you have the potential
to be the first boyfriend to say that.
Ouch!
Does it hurt that much? I didn't apply much pressure.
I'm really sensitive to pain. It hurts so much.
Hello, Sister.
So, it was just an act to make him feel bad for you.
Well, not exactly.
I knew it, it couldn't have hurt that much.
When you get home, put ice packs on it for 48 hours.
If it still hurts,
apply some medicine to improve blood circulation.
Try not to move around. Got it?
Thank you, doctor.
I must say,
your boyfriend, although quite handsome,
seems a bit unromantic and stony-hearted.
Don't say that, doctor.
He's not stony-hearted.
Young lady, you're quite protective of him.
He simply doesn't have a heart.
What's taking him so long?
He must've gone to pay the bills.
He wouldn't have left, would he?
I still can't walk.
A medical miracle.
The doctor did a good job.
Can you get in the car by yourself now?
(Guan Ji)
(Shi Yan, are you still in touch with Bei Lin?)
(Your ex, that actress, the really pretty one.)
(Here's the thing, )
(I have a friend who wants to cast her in a movie.)
(If you don't mind, could you help introduce them to each other?)
(Hello, can you hear me?)
Her?
I think her acting skills are just average.
The one in my car right now is a much better actress.
(Seriously?)
(In your car?)
(I won't disturb you. Bye.)
So, his ex really is that famous actress.
His ex...
When he said I'm a better actress in the car,
can I interpret it as him thinking
I'm better than her?
Anyway, she's just his ex.
I've come so far now.
I can't give up now, no matter what.
You're doing this on purpose.
You knew your uncle doesn't like hotpot.
How do you know...
Shi Yan.
Uncle, we're almost done eating, and you just arrived?
I had some things to take care of.
You told me not to forget, and then you arrived so late.
Yue,
I haven't seen you in such a long time.
I don't want to see you being scolded by your uncle now.
Carry on with your story. What's going on between you and your superior?
Oh, Uncle knows about this too.
I misunderstood her.
I sent her a friend request on WeChat to apologize to her.
Unexpectedly, as soon as she accepted it, she greeted me passionately
and even invited me to your concert.
I was so surprised.
She invited you to the concert today?
That's right.
But she acted a little strange,
like I wasn't the one she invited.
But it doesn't matter, we had a great time.
You misunderstood her,
and then went to a concert with her without feeling guilty?
Uncle, why are you so sarcastic?
Always holding grudges.
Sister, here's to your successful performance.
- Cheers.   - Cheers.
(I almost forgot.)
(I haven't paid you back for the medical bills.)
Mom, Uncle is dating an actress again.
Don't talk nonsense.
Guan Ji said you had an actress in your car.
I just saw her sending you a message.
Shi Yan, who is it?
Do I know her?
Sister, they are making things up. Don't mind them.
I clearly saw it just now.
Okay, don't believe rumors so easily.
Gossip spreads this way.
Your uncle knows what he's doing.
But when it comes to relationships,
you can only keep them if you cherish them.
Shi Yan,
if you meet the right girl,
make sure to cherish her and don't lose her.
Oh right, isn't Uncle Cheng having a family banquet tomorrow night?
If you don't have a date, let Yue go with you.
It's fine.
Uncle, I'd be happy to go with you.
Not anyone can be my uncle's date.
Tone it down now.
Sister, enjoy your meal.
I need to use the restroom.
Okay.
There's something going on with him.
All right now. Just eat your food.
(He seems to be in love.)
(I have to find out which actress it is.)
(Are you Shi Yan?)
(Who else could I be?)
(How much was the medical bill?)
(I'll transfer it to you.)
What kind of hospital is this? It's so expensive.
(Can I use medical insurance?)
(How kind of you.)
(Consider it today's paycheck.)
For my Oscar-level performance,
you're only paying a little over 2,000?
What a stingy character you are.
(For my Oscar-level performance, )
(you're only paying a little over 2,000?)
(How much do you want?)
(I want you to have dinner with me tomorrow.)
That's quite a thing to ask.
(Sure. I'll pick you up tomorrow at 5pm.)
(What are we going to eat?)
(Which of these should I wear?)
(Which outfit looks nice on me?)
(The red one.)
Red?
Where did red come from?
Is he just humoring me,
or is he colorblind?
He couldn't possibly mean that red one, could he?
Xing Zhou, is this dress nice?
It looks pretty nice.
(What is he doing here?)
- Hello.   - (Hi, Shu Yi.)
(What are you doing? Want to go shopping with me?)
I'm already out shopping.
I even saw that cheater and his girlfriend.
What bad luck.
(Really? Where are you now?)
I'm at Guojin.
I have the worst luck.
Every time I see them,
I have to wash my eyes for days.
(Guojin...)
(Wait for me, I'm coming.)
This dress feels a bit too plain, doesn't it?
It looks like something for middle-aged people. It's not for me.
Your choice isn't good either.
A turtleneck sweater can easily smudge my foundation.
Pick another one.
"It smudges my foundation."
Isn't this dress a bit too simple?
It lacks any design flair.
Not at all. Simple tailoring makes it look elegant and attractive.
See, the bright red color complements your complexion.
Chinese New Year is coming up,
and this would be perfect for visiting relatives.
But I still feel there's something off about the shoulder area.
Xing Zhou.
Xing Zhou?
Do I look good in this?
Yes.
Forget it. I'll try something else.
Miss, this outfit is absolutely perfect for you.
Your skin is so fair.
This bright red color seems tailor-made for someone with your skin tone.
You look even better than magazine models in it.
Thank you.
I'd like to take a photo to show my friend.
Solid-state batteries have become one of the key bottlenecks
restricting the development of the new energy vehicle industry.
The industry is about to witness
the emergence of semi-solid-state batteries.
Zhanlan is the most likely company to be the first
to mass-produce semi-solid-state batteries.
This round of financing holds great significance for them.
Zhanlan's semi-solid-state batteries have very mature technology.
Currently, they are considered leaders in the new generation
of high-performance power batteries.
All right then. You've all done your homework.
I can only respond to the call
and contribute to the national dual carbon goal.
(Is it nice?)
(Give me a one-word response.)
Are you smiling?
Why are you smiling?
Nothing.
So, do you have a date for the evening?
I can go with you. I don't have a date.
I'm not going with you.
That's interesting.
You don't have a date tonight,
and he unexpectedly does.
Yeah.
(Acceptable.)
(Couldn't he have added a few more words?)
(Would it kill him to say "you look beautiful"?)
So ugly.
Get me something else.
Honey, I like all of these. Buy them for me.
Hurry up, we have to go to dinner later.
Miss, do you want all of these outfits?
They look great on you. They suit you well.
Shu Yi.
Have you made your picks?
Don't overthink it. I'll help you choose.
Ma'am, excuse me.
Your taste is really on point.
You've picked out the ugliest pieces in the store for me.
You've saved me from wasting time.
Are you really going to buy them?
Of course.
- I don't feel right about it.   - What's not right about it?
It's my uncle's supplementary card. It's fine, don't worry.
That's even wrong. I don't even know your uncle.
You said you wanted them. You can't change your mind now.
You have to maintain your pride at times like this.
Consider it a return gift for taking me to the concert before,
and compensation for some other things.
What other things?
Nothing, forget it.
Shu Yi, consumerism will never betray you.
The clothes you buy are yours, forever yours.
Much more reliable than certain men, for sure.
Miss, it's done.
Thank you.
Ma'am, thank you.
What the hell is wrong with you?
That's enough.
These few pieces really aren't that nice. Forget about them. Let's go.
They aren't nice?
Your eyes were practically glued to them
when she was wearing them just now.
She's nothing!
Shu Yi,
put on the one you like.
Shu Yi, do you have plans for later?
How about dinner together?
Sorry, I've made plans with someone.
I see.
That's why you're out shopping for clothes.
Smart.
You should head off then. What are you waiting for?
Go on, good luck.
This outfit seems a bit too much.
Zheng Shu Yi.
Where are you going?
I'm going home to drop these off and change my clothes.
No need to change.
You look great in this.
He was holding my hand and praising me before getting into the car,
but now he's silent.
Men can be so fickle.
(Langyuan)
This courtyard has quite a distinctive charm.
Let's go inside.
(I didn't know he could be so good at choosing a place for a date.)
What are you looking at?
You.
What about me?
You look different today.
You look very beautiful.
It's time to join the banquet.
The banquet?
This is a family banquet hosted by one of my elders.
There should be quite a crowd later.
Aren't you supposed to have dinner with me?
Isn't this considered having dinner with you?
Okay.
This is not the kind of dinner I had in mind.
After this meal,
you can invite me for a private meal, just the two of us.
Let's go.
(Shi Yan is seeing someone again.)
(How long has he been single?)
(Why did he break up with Bei Lin before?)
(Who dumped whom?)
- (Who's she?)   - (Is this his new girlfriend?)
(Judging by her look, she's probably a celebrity too.)
- (I've never seen her before.)   - (I think she's as pretty as Bei Lin.)
Shi Yan, it's been so long.
Yes.
I haven't been paying much attention to the entertainment industry lately.
Who is this?
I remember now.
Aren't you the lead actress
from that web series "Princess Qin Lan"?
It's really you! I used to say that the lead actress was very beautiful,
but you look even more stunning in modern attire.
Sorry, guys. You got the wrong person.
I'm a journalist.
Oh, we're sorry.
Let's go.
(He just spent the night with an actress yesterday, )
(and today he's with a beautiful journalist.)
(The runaway prince is quite the ladies' man, isn't he?)
What's the matter?
You're still thinking about her?
That's nonsense.
You know it's not nonsense.
I saw it clearly today.
You've never looked at me that way.
She and I are past tense. It's not what you think.
You didn't even buy me clothes.
I think you just don't love me.
You're reluctant to spend money on me, aren't you?
That's not true.
I was just saving up for our future.
Look, once you talk to your uncle
and get me a job at Yunchuang,
I'll buy you whatever you want, okay?
Let's have a drink.
Cheers.
Thank you.
(Shu Yi, are you busy?)
(I'm sorry about today.)
(I want to talk to you about something.)
(Shu Yi, are you busy? What are you doing right now?)
(I'm baking a cake.)
Is she okay?
She's fine.
She's probably craving for desserts.
(Some people are alive, but they are dead inside.)
Hi, may I know who ordered this?
Here.
Well, someone here wants cake.
(Shi Yan, )
(I can't believe you're subtly mocking me in front of so many people.)