Try to do something, huh?
Why isn't Han Jae Hoon coming?
Chief Han! Quickly, come here. Hurry.
Doctor Park.
Aigoo, what is all this, Master?
Park Hoon.
Let's change players.
Isn't that Doctor Park Hoon? Doctor Park Hoon came.
Oh, Doctor Park came.
- Really?
- Let me see. Yes, really.
Needle holder. Forceps.
It's done.  The patient is alive.  The patient is alive, rascal!
It's not finished yet. Don't relax.
I understand.
Why are you back?
Did Professor Moon handle it?
No, Park Hoon came.
Episode 17
Doctor Yang Jung Han.
This is Yang Jung Han.
You didn't forget what I said, right?
This surgery, Park Hoon absolutely cannot win.
Make him lose at all cost!
I understand.
Septum and valves are a mess.
Even the arteries are damaged.
I know.  There isn't a part that's not damaged.
What are we going to do? This really is a major construction.
What do you mean? We have to suture prettily and super fast.
Now, then we'll start with the ventricular septum.
You're blocking my vision.
I'm sorry. I was trying to make it more visible...
Please continue.
Instead of agonizing, move aside.
This is where my patience ends.
Master, please change to first.
- Why me?
- Quickly change!
Cut.
Please turn off the pump.
Anesthesiologist!  What are you doing?
His vitals are unstable. They're fluctuating too much.
- Focus!
- We have to call a cardiovascular anesthesiologist.
I'll do it.
You really… Do you really have no thought of becoming my adopted son?
Your wife won't like it.
I can leave the rest to you, right?
Okay.
Doctor Park.
You can laugh?
I should laugh since I am here anyway. Should I cry?
Hoon.
Stop it.
Why did you come? I told you not to.
I told you that I'd never send you into any operating room alone.
Are you being like this because you don't know what kind of operating room that is?
I know. It is dangerous, so let's go together.
It's not too late yet so go back.
I'm not leaving you alone.
Go! Please.
If you're really thinking of me, then don't do this.
At that bridge in Budapest, when you let go of my hand,
I really hated you.
The time I spent without you was too painful.
I really hated myself for not being able to fall into the river together with you.
Don't do that again.
The last competition,
I will win no matter what. So let's go together.
We're going to make the surgery team you first thought of  and will go in together.
I will win so that you can meet the President.
And Han Jae Joon is a good doctor.
We can't ruin him by getting him involved in this conspiracy.
Do you have time to worry about others?
In fact, there are mountain loads of my worries too.  So I'm wondering,
can you take one of those away?
What?
Mom.
I'm begging you.
Yes.
It seems Park Hoon went back.
Even so, he is going to be left out of the plan.
I will be on the surgery team with Chief Han.
Should I wash it in the washing machine?
Hyung!
What about Mom?
Whose mom?
Mom.
Hoon, you're back?
Where did you go?
I was looking for you.
I'm sorry, Hoon.
I'm really sorry.
No, I was wrong.
Who are you?
It's me, Hoon.
My Hoon is only 8 years old.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I just thought that you had abandoned me, so
I resented you.
I didn't even know you became like this.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Should I keep taking care of her?
- I'm counting on you.
- I'm scared.
I'm not saying your mom is scary.
Jae Hee is acting like that too. It must mean that there are people looking for her if you're hiding her here.
That's why I'm asking you, the person I trust the most in the world.
- Stop saying nonsense.
- Then the second?
You can joke around right now?
The jokes are coming out well.
I'm going.  Take care of her.
It's unexpected for you to come here personally, Chairman.
Park Hoon, that jerk... I heard you said he wouldn't be able to come?
I know.
Fine, what exactly is this?
It should be the end of the story if you get your surgery by the doctor you want.
Park Hoon or whatever, why are you being so fickle about him?
I'm thinking about withdrawing Myeongwoo now from Prime Minister's surgery altogether!
The heart that'll be getting the surgery
isn't mine.
It's not for mine but the person above me.
Coul...d it be?
Yes, it's the President's.
But why?
Wouldn't the President's health be a top secret?
There's nothing good if it gets known
when his approval rating has fallen already.
Then, when the surgery ends...
Yes, well, you'll receive support funds from here and there,
and the fact that the hospital is in charge of the President is a bonus.
I really thought I was dying, crap.
It's because you haven't held a scapel in a while.
Why did Park Hoon tell you to move from being First?
He must have thought that you were much better than me.
Come to think of it, you left during the last surgery for good.
The day that Park Hoon hurt his hand.
Anyway, what's going to happen to this match?
The match?
It must be a tie, right?
Of course!
Chairman hasn't come back yet.
I will contact you when he comes back.
Chief Han.
We tied, right?
Am I right or wrong?
It is something that Chairman will decide.
Geez, the answer is right in your expression, as being tied.
You came?
It's constriction of the mitral valve.
I think the valve has arterial plaque (been calcified) a bit.
Let's go with that patient this time.
Isn't this too simple?
It's just putting in an artificial valve.
What is this?
Chief Han's patient is much easier.
As with the twins, the one who  finishes the fastest will be the winner.  We'll look at the prognosis too.
Chairman this is too lopsided.
For us, it's a man over 40, and Chief Han's patient is a young lady in her 20s.
It's much harder for us because the valve has plaque.
If you don't like it, speak now.
- Of course I don't like it-
- Then,
just end the competition as Chief Han being the winner.
- Chairman.
- Prime Minister is telling us to select a surgery team quickly.
Until when are you going to keep talking about the competition?
- Even so-
- What?
Say it!
Let's just do it.
What? Hey!
Should we not do it?
Hey!
Have we ever had the advantage?
But this time, he's too blatantly helping the other side!
- I will win so don't worry.
- Really?
Yes. But I need to organize my team first.
Tell me now.
Exactly what happened.
I definitely told you.
If you ever do anything strange in the operating room, I wouldn't just let it pass again.
What strange thing did I do?
Are you going to keep lying?
That's fine. Doctor Yang, don't enter my operating room from now on.
Doctor Park.
It's not only about money.
I hate your arrogance.
Jung Han.
Someone like you would never know how an ordinary person like me has to make
a desperate effort to survive in this world.
That cashier's check you threw at me saying it was to pay for the patient's hospital fee,
it was from Professor Moon, right?
That money you can have if you so wish it,
I have to make an effort for months.
Or do dirty work.
Jung Han.
I have actually done many dirty things myself too.
Because I know well how painful and regrettable that is,
I'm telling you to get out of my operating room.
Also, you are absolutely not an ordinary person either.
Just the fact that you have a doctor's gown on,
people willingly put their life in your hands.
Let's not disappoint those people anymore,
Doctor Yang.
Doctor Park's words are right.
Jung Han… if you stay here any longer,
you'll end up losing everything.
Just do the surgery.
Will the Prime Minister acknowledge it?
You don't have to worry about that.
I got it.
You, after the surgery team is chosen,
you will have to be an acting chairman.
I'm telling you in advance since you'll win the competition.
How can I...
You don't need to worry too much since Sang Jin will help you with the things you don't know.
Complaint
Just wait and see. I will do whatever I can do get revenge on you!
I will get revenge on you!
Complaint
I'm there. Almost there.
Do you have time?
What's the matter?
The tie was a shame.
Did you come here to say that?
No, it's not like that.
Since you're busy, I'll keep it short.
I would like it if you'd take your hands off of this match.
I think that I at least asked you to take your hands off while offering some money.
If your life as a doctor is at stake, then don't you think it's a stronger reason than money?
You're saying things I can't understand as time goes on.
Also understand how I feel for not being able to say everything.
My answer is "no."
Do you understand?
Taking your hands off from the Prime Minister's surgery team...
I'm sincerely saying it for your sake. Trust me.
If you care about me,  then you should take your hands off of it.
Don't be like that, and can't you just say yes for this one?
Honestly,  the Prime Minister's surgery team is brimming with  dirty things.
Is it as much as your father?
Why are you bringing up that story here?
Let's just say it's the process of  association.
Anyway, if you're done talking, please leave.
Come to think of it, you seem to have a lot of interest in my father.
- How did you know?
- About what?
About him going to North Korea. Honestly, I don't think I ever told you that.
Out of the friends I've met at Harvard,
there was a friend named Lee Seung Hoon.
How are you...
That friend asked me to do a favor.
If I go to Korea, to find out definitely what happened to Park Chul.
Because of his desire for fame in performing surgery on North Korea's greatest leader,
the person who abandoned his father and family.
If I find him, my friend wants definitely to repay him.
It seems like that person has the story wrong.
Has it wrong?
My dad didn't go to North Korea for fame.
He went there to block a war... no,
he went because he was deceived by Chairman Oh Joon Gyu and Jang Seok Joo.
Lies.
Do you think my friend will believe an excuse like that?
I want to make him believe it, so I must contact him.
The director of this hospital has also gone to the States because of him.
I haven't talked to him recently.
Hey, Quack.
Where are you running away to like that?
What do you mean I'm running away?
- Then, why are you in such a hurry?
When did I?
I thought I was dying catching up to you. What do you mean you weren't!
What?
Don't you have anything to tell me?
There isn't.
Then, I'll do it.
First, I'm really sorry.
Second, you don't have to concern yourself with what your father did.
It's not something you did, anyway.
Third, are you doing your hair loss prevention exercises?
Stop!
- Why?
- What are you trying to do here?
- I'm trying to get along well with you.
- You think we can get along well?
- Of course we can!
- Stop it!
- Stop!
Stop!~
Seriously, you rascal!
Aigoo!~
In order not to infuriate Chairman,
I can always make it appear that nothing is wrong between us.
But it can't be Park Hoon.
I know.
When you know, you were like that with him earlier?
We're just trying to be comfortable with each other.
He's a person for whom there is no one except Jae Hee.
I'm sorting my feelings out too, so
you don't have to worry about me like that.
That day, I was really out of it.
I didn't have the confidence to handle it either.
Honestly, I was embarrassed towards you too.
I'm sorry for deceiving you.
Then tell me.
Doctor Han--no, Jae Hee, did you come from North Korea?
By any chance, is there an ulterior motive behind trying to operate on the Prime Minister with Doctor Park?
Doctor Oh.
If it's like that, even if you're Jae Hee, I won't stay still.
Don't put Doctor Park in danger.
It's true that I met Hoon in North Korea.
But strictly speaking, I'm a Japanese citizen.
After separating with Hoon I got moved to Japan.
I received medical treatment there, and also finished medical school.
Then why did you pretend not to know him when you met him?
Honestly, I didn't have the confidence to meet him.
What are you saying? Doctor Park only has you.
- You've seen the picture of my kidney, right?
- Yes.
That kidney...
belonged to my father.
The person who did the transplant surgery was Hoon.
He was trying to save me, but, Hoon...
made my father pass away.
So I had no confidence.
If we met again, would we be able to love each other like before?
No. Doctor Park loves you.
I hoped that he would.
But the emotions that  Hoon feels,
I think they might be out of guilt or obligation.  Especially,
moreso when he is with you.
No, I...
I will return to Japan soon.
Japan?
Hoon...
no, Doctor Park
likes you, Doctor Oh.
Not out of guilt or obligation,
but genuinely.
What are you talking about?
If he hadn't made my father pass away,
and if he had no past with your father,
Hoon would choose you.
No. Doctor Park only loves you.
When I go back to Japan, please wait little bit.
If you wait by his side,
you will also know Doctor Park's heart.
You've also done some part-time jobs at restaurants, right?
Of course.
But, why?
That's good then.  That's good.
I thought you worked at a restaurant before?
I've only watched them making the food.
My specialty is delivery.
In any case, go on and eat, Mom.
See.  She only eats a bit if I make porridge.
Do you think she'd get an appetite by looking at this, you idiot?
I really did my best making it. Are you seriously going to be like this?
What can we do?
Eat. Eat your food.
I will eat well.
Kim Min Joo's blood analysis still hasn't come out yet?
It came out. I really made a fuss!
You did well.
Everyone, hello. Quack, hello!
When I go to Japan, wait for awhile.
If you wait by his side Doctor Oh, you will also
come to know Doctor Park's feelings.
Did you two fight again?
Even so, you should accept his greetings, Doctor Oh.
Don't call me a quack.
My patients really think that I'm a quack.
Sorry, Quac... Aigoo.
What can I do when it has become a habit?
Hey, Qua-
Oh my.
Forget it,  just forget it.
I'll let it go because I'm kind.
Over there... we've got to go.
Joking around like we used to is a bit hard for me now.
Please be careful.
I'm doing it so we can be comfortable with each other.
Is that possible overnight?
Aigoo, that girl...seriously...
That Unni... she likes you, Beanpole, right?
What is the relationship between you two? Do you two have something going on?
Who are you?
Me? "Flaming Skewer" from Moonamdong.
What? What is burning?
Oh right, a patient who has settled that and is trying to live beautifully.
You know, that everyone has a past that they want to hide.
A patient can't be doing this here.
Here, hurry and go back to your room.
Good luck, Beanpole.
What is she?
What is it?
You little wench!  Why did you tell Mom about her?
I told her because it was necessary!
What's wrong with a girl who delivers water?
It's not about what she does. It's because you hit on every girl out there!
Did you not hit on every guy, too?
But I settled down when it was time to settle down.
Didn't you know? About my wedding next month?
Wow, does that man know? That many guys got crushed with the backs of your heels?
You are an ex-con!
Wow, seriously, you are really again firing up the extinguished "skewer!"
You (informal)? How dare you say "you" to your older brother?
You have to act like an older brother to be one!
Hey! Come, come!
This is a hospital!
Hey!
This is a hospital. This is a hospital.
Live properly.  Live properly!
Stop it... stop!
Hey.
Chief.
What are you doing with the patient?
Ah, right, she is a patient but...
Hello. I'm this delinquent doctor's younger sister.
Oh, the chief is really cool!
- You, really...!
A valve surgery?
Yes.
You have a disease called mitral valve stenosis.
You mean mitral stenosis?
Yes.
If you leave it alone, it might lead to a left atrial aneurysm and even atrial fibrillation.
You're talking about auricular fibrillation of the left ventricle.
How do you know that? Are you preparing for medical school?
Everybody knows that except you.
The reason why you're out of breath and dizzy is because blood didn't flow to your left ventricle properly, so
it resulted in left ventricular failure.
Enough of that, but is there any other method besides a surgery?
Can't I take medicine?
You have to have the surgery.
Explain to her well.
Goodbye.
Hey, what is this? Are you really preparing for medical school?
You try going to over 10 hospitals, too.  You end up memorizing it automatically.
Why did you go to 10 different hospitals?
I don't want to have the surgery. Why?
Simply put, there are 4 chambers in a heart where the blood flows through.
In the wall between the left and right chambers
and in the wall between the upper chamber and the lower chamber, there is a door on each side.
That wall is a septum and the doors are valves, right?
Oh, you know it well.
I studied because it's my illness.
If that's the case then it'll be easy to understand.
One of those doors broke in your case.
When that happens, because the blood doesn't flow properly,
the upper left chamber has enlarged and it causes stress on your heart.
It's dangerous because your heart is beating erratically.
I'm going to do a surgery that changes out that door.
It's not a difficult surgery so don't worry too much.
Okay.
Get some rest.
Hello, Beanpole.
Hello, Skewer.
Why are you bringing up my past?
You're good at explaining it.  It's really easy to understand.
Oh, it's nothing.
Can I ask you something too?
What?
So what you are saying is that there is no other way except surgery?
Right. You must get a surgery for constriction of the mitral valve.
Got it?
Do you by any chance know a person named Han Jae Joon? I heard he's a chief who graduated from Harvard.
- Why?
- Is he trustworthy?
His skills are good.
I will ask one last time.
Are you sure there isn't any other way?
There isn't.
Really?
Why? Are you afraid of the surgery?
That is true too, but I'm getting married next month.
I found my destined mate.
Well, if I say this you might mock me, but our heartbeats even beat at the same time.
Want to see? Look.
It's pretty.
These... they seem similar yet different.
And then they seem different, yet they're similar.  They're like that.
Do you know how many days I agonized to pick one that's pretty?
I wouldn't know.
I really want to live happily with this person.
I want to live a lovey-dovey life with him and with our baby.
So then  I heard I can't get pregnant if I have this surgery.
Well, it's not always but it's just a bit difficult, that's all.
My fiancé is saying who cares if we don't have a baby?
He said that our happiness is the only thing that matters.
But I really want to have a baby.
I bought baby clothes already.
I'm going to put them on our junior.
So, do you think I want the surgery or not?
I know you don't want it, but since it's a necessary surgery, get it.
That door… show it to me too.
What door?
The door to heart's upper left side. The door that needs to be fixed.
Why?
I'm so angry that I want to curse at it to my heart's content.
Your name?
Kim Ah Young. Isn't my name pretty?
Kim Ah Young.
Where is it?! That damn door!
Here-
Hey! Because of you, my dream is shattered!
I'm going to destroy you soon too, you bastard!
Thanks. I feel a bit better now.
Hold on.
Did you see it, too?
What are you talking about?
This patient's aortic valve.
Marfan Syndrome. I saw it, too. So what?
An inherited disorder than affects connective tissue.
What do mean "So what?"
A patient with Marfan Syndrome can have the surgery at same time as an aortic aneurysm anyway.
I'm saying you don't have to do a surgery right now.
The width of the mitral valve has constricted to a point where it needs surgery. Can't you see it?
It's still at a state where she can certainly withstand it
as long as she doesn't exercise too vigorously. On top of that,  she says she's getting married soon.
After the surgery, she needs to take Warfarin but it could be deadly to get pregnant.
So?
- I'm saying you can delay the surgery-
- Are you telling me to give up on the competition or what?
Once pregnant, an aortic aneurysm progresses quicker.
Then if an aortic dissection occurs suddenly  and a blood vessel ruptures, she dies immediately.
It's not that severe yet.
You want to bet her life on luck?
You also know that this surgery doesn't need to be done right away.
After getting married and giving birth to a child... it's possible to go without it for over 10 years.
A patient's life could be completely changed by this.
After the surgery, she just needs to regain her health. Who cares what she does after that?
If possible, you should also think about a patient's life after surgery.
You can do that kind of thing. I am going to do a surgery on this patient.
Is it because of the competition? We can call it a tie then.
There is no tie. This is the last time.
If you really want to pretend to be a good doctor, then we can change the patient.
- What?
- We can exchange our patients.
You can't do that, right? You will lose if you don't do the surgery.
Tell me anytime if you change your mind. I'll exchange with you.
Is it true?
I heard it all. Water Bottle, is it true what you just said?
Yes. Why?
Kim Ah Young is my younger sister.
Is it true?
In my judgment, yes. It's true.
So, you don't want her to have the surgery?
It's not that.
I just want to hear your honest opinion.
She needs to have the surgery.  Because it's gotten so narrow, it'll be too much to lead a normal daily life.
Of course, it is.
That girl, because she doesn't want to have the surgery,
she must have been to every hospital.
When the wedding is next month, she's worried that she might ruin it,
and she's worried about possibly not being able get pregnant if she has the surgery.
She was such a play girl  in the past, but I guess she's a woman.
When the right time comes, they must all change like that.
If you understand, you can leave.
But Hyungnim,
Water Bottle says that she doesn't have to have the surgery.
Are you really a thug?
What are the symptoms of MS?
Marfan Syndrome
What are they?
That is...
uh... breathing difficulties and...
Atrial fibrillation, sleep apnea, chest pains,
aortic aneurysm, or a stroke!
You said the condition wasn't that bad.
- Then, when does it get worse?
- Pardon?
Does it give you a notice and get worse?
I'm saying to have the surgery because we don't know when she'll get worse.
By chance,
are you doing this because of the competition?
She came here with the same diagnosis from all the other hospitals, too.
My diagnosis is the same as theirs.  MS needs to be repaired.
I understand, Hyungnim.
Even after surgery, if she tries, she could conceive.
Your sister can
live the desired married life.
It's a judgment I made as a doctor who'll do the surgery.
My judgment and Water Bottle's judgment.
Consider carefully which side you should believe.
Hey, I heard this patient has Marfan Syndrome.
Who said that?
What do you mean "who"? Kim Chi Gyu did.
He's going around asking this person and that person.
This is an opportunity from God... you know that, right?
What is an opportunity from God again?
You need to tell his younger sister.
"You can do this surgery later!"  Something like this.
Then discharge. The competition is over! We win.
Chief Han is saying he's going to do it so don't tell the patient yet.
I already did.
She's here.
Hey, Beanpole.  I really don't need the surgery?
Talk.
Talk or I'll put a hole in your head.
That's my opinion.  Later,
you can do it together when you see signs of aortic aneurysm.
Water Bottle, shut your mouth.
You heard it too, right?  He said that I don't have to have the surgery.
I can be discharged.
I told you that you need the surgery.
Beanpole said that I don't need it!
You just trust his words?
He is this hospital's doctor.
How can you trust this Wattle Bottle bastard?
Do you know where he went to medical school?  He graduated from Pyongyang.  Pyongyang!
So what?  He is still a doctor.
Hey, our chief who graduated from Harvard said that you need to have the surgery.
And you said that you've been to other hospitals too.
You said that all the doctors there said you needed to get surgery, too!
So you want me to have the surgery?
I also looked into it.
If I have the surgery and a valve is replaced, they said that it's too hard to conceive a baby.
If something goes wrong, there are cases where you have to give up getting pregnant.
They say you could conceive if you try.  Then you can have a baby.
Why do I have to be the only one who has to try when everyone else just does it?
I just want to live like other people, that's all.
If I have the surgery later like Beanpole said, I can live like that.
Then tell me.  I'll do what you tell me to do.
I will do as you say.
Should I get the surgery?
Should I not?  You tell me!  What am I suppose to do?!
Accept it.
Get the surgery.
Do you have something you need me to hold onto?
Take the call if I get a phone call.  I told the wedding hall that I was going to cancel it.
Okay.
Okay, let's go.  Go.
If it's a tie again here, what's going to happen?
Then it's been decided that the hospital will select the doctor.
Who will?
That's something... that the Chairman there has to do.
I trust you with the anesthesia.
Why? What's wrong?
I'm going into Chief Han's operating room.
What are you saying all of a sudden?
You really don't know?
Think hard. About what you did to me.
What do you mean what I did to you? Tell me so that I can understand.
Let's talk after the surgery.
What are you doing? You should get ready quickly.
Why is Doctor Han going in there?
She did that last time, too.
Don't worry about it, and focus on the surgery instead!
If we win, I'll do whatever it takes to bring her back.
Hurry.
Chi Gyu, you can stay out.
Will that be okay?
Yes.
Hyungnim.
- Ah Young… please take good care of her.
Okay.
Tell them we are ready.
Myeongwoo University Hospital
00:00:00
Hey, this was over after the twins' surgery.
Think hard. About what you did to me.
I cancelled the reservation for the wedding hall, Ah Young. .
Kim Ah Young
LINE
Home
They said they're finished with the preparations.
I trust you with the vitals.
Yes.
Master, you stay focused, too.
I'm nervous since it's the last one.
Myeongwoo University Hospital
00:00:00
Hey, Water Bottle.
I… Ah Young… I told her not to cancel the reservation for the wedding hall.
That time… Chief Han
said that you can change patients, right?
Kim Chi Gyu, what are you doing?
After my sister marries, please make her live a normal life like everyone else.
Hey, Water Bottle.
Aren't you going to get out!
Just once...
Just once, please help me act like her older brother.
What are you doing? Take him out!
Hey! Wait!
Hey, Water Bottle! Hey! Water Bottle!
Water Bottle!
Hey, Park Hoon! If you listen to him, it's game over.
We're going to lose!
Scalpel.
Grasp the scalpel!
Hoon… From now on…
never forget the fact that …
you're a doctor.
The final competition... I'll do whatever it takes to win, so let's go in together.
Just like how you thought initially, let's make the surgery team together,
and we'll go into the same surgery room together.
What is this?
What are you doing, Doctor Park?
What? Doctor Park...
The scalpel...
♬  Will someone tell me please  ♬
♬  I cannot see a single place to rest  ♬
♬  Every time I open my eyes, there's not a single light  ♬
What is it?
What do you think it is?
♬  Every time I open my eyes, there's not a single light  ♬
♬  At the end of this road. At the end of this strange road,  ♬