- Did you find it?
- It's hard to see, Chief.
Calm down.
- But Chief...
- I said calm down!
Keum Bong Hyun.
Please take me in.
Why do you have your heads lowered like people who've committed sins?
There is nothing that you people have done wrong so lift your heads.
The ones who should have their heads shoved down are up there.  Look.
That's right, let's become confident.
Because the only real doctors in this hospital are just you people.
Okay, since our necks hurt, let's stop looking and let's hurriedly do it.
Please find the area that's hemorrhaging first.
Because the hemorrhage is severe, we can't stop it.
Since we are in the middle of surgery, we can't do a CT scan or an ultrasound.
♬ Because of this will, because of heart's will ♬
Suction.
Needle holder.
Forceps.
I don't think there is a surgery Doctor Park Hoon can't do.
What's the point?  It seems like they're all going to be fired now.
- What about the vitals?
- They're  good.
I don't think we need to worry anymore.
Of course, since we have a great First. Right?
♬ Just wait a bit longer ♬
What are you doing here? Didn't you hear me say  to open a disciplinary committee  and to prepare for a lawsuit?
Yes, I understand, Chairman.
I can understand the disciplinary committee but what is this about a lawsuit, Hyungnim?
Episode 13
This is a surgery that's revealing that the surgical procedure was done wrong.
That's why we have to prepare for the lawsuit.
Geez... Another problem that's going to be tiring.
Hyungnim, can we convince the Cardiology Department,
so that we can avoid the lawsuit?
How can we persuade them?
Have you ever seen a doctor in this world that says, "I did wrong"?
I will finish it up.
Yes, please.
You've worked hard.
Jae Joon!
I clearly warned you.
If you do surgery on that patient, it's clearly over.
I'm prepared for it.
A sincere apology?
Okay. Let's see if you can stop the medical malpractice lawsuit with that.
Doctor.
Don't worry, the surgery went well.
Thank you, Doctor!
I apologize instead of the hospital for making you worry.
Why are you like this when you have no reason to apologize?
If anyone should apologize, the cardiology department's doctors should.
Are you going to pursue the lawsuit?
I don't know.
If you need anything, please contact me.
Shouldn't we at least make plans when we're all about to be fired?
Didn't you see the laser coming out of Chairman's eyes?
There won't be any use even if you make plans.
Except for one person.
What are you doing, not moving the patient?
I will follow soon.
Doctor Keum!
What is this?  This lonely and lonesome feeling.
Are you worried that you'll be fired?
- No!
- Then why?
I am Chief's First,
but I didn't do anything during the twin's surgery and today's surgery!
It's my first time seeing Doctor Keum getting mad like this.
Don't feel so distressed.
Naturally, kids all make mistakes as they become adults.
Do I look like a kid to you?
No, what I mean is...
Somehow, Dr. Keum's innocent charm is...
Stop treating me like a child now!
I understand.
Then,
from now on,
from now on... I will treat you like an adult.
Mom!
Your mom will get better.
Thank you, Doctor.
I am a fake, but Doctor Oh here is the real one.
Right?
Yeah, that's right.
I'll call you when your mom regains consciousness so wait a little bit.
Yes, Doctor.
Thank you.
Doctor Oh?
Isolation Ward
What are you looking so intently at?
Did you say Doctor Oh?
- Did I say that?
- You said that in front of Jae Cheol earlier.
Well, I guess I briefly had a slip of the tongue.
Come on, it wasn't a slip.
Why are you like this?
You said to become confident.
That the only real doctors in this hospital are just us.
That's why you called me Doctor Oh. Isn't that so?
I didn't know the quack was in there.
- Really?
- Of course.
How can I know who is who when everyone is wearing a mask and has a surgeon's cap on.
You even talked to me.
That was after the surgery had finished.
Do you not like calling me Doctor Oh that much?
Is that really that  important?
That's why your hair keeps on falling off because you concern yourself with those things.
Think about your own hair. What kind of hair is that for a doctor?
- What about my hair?
- Trim it a bit.
These days patients like tidy doctors, not weird perm-haired ones.
Stop talking nonsense and go put in a good word to your father.
About what?
Won't everyone get fired because we did Jae Cheol's mom's surgery?
Seeing today, Chief Han seems like a decent guy.
I don't know about the others, but
ask him to do something for that person.
Complaint
I'm sorry,
Father.
The patient woke up.
Okay.
You're were really cool today,  you know that right?
Thank you.
Don't worry too much about Chairman.
If I leave the hospital, I'm going to go back to America.
America?
But I don't want to go alone.
Let's go together. I'll look for a spot at Harvard.
Thank you,
but you won't be leaving the hospital.
Because I'll try to persuade Father somehow.
Cheer up!
Why did you go into the surgery?
Let's talk later.
I said to to do it later.
Hoon.
Go, I want to be alone now.
You don't like competing with patient's lives.
So, I thought if I let this competition be, I thought it would end.
So, are you telling me to ignore a patient who was going to die?!
There were other people in the operating room.
Jae Cheol's mom was dying.
And they were asking for help in the operating room!
So how could I stay still?
Don't do that to me.
I'm really
confused whenever you do that to me.
Truthfully, when I first met you here,
I was really ashamed.
During the time after I lost you, I did a lot of horrible things.
But I gained courage.
Now that I've found you,
because my dream came back,
I thought I could really return back to myself, when I put that bracelet on your hand.
However,
how could that Jae Hee
do that to me?
How can you tell me to
ignore a dying patient?
That son of a bitch.
Move aside.
Stop it.
Get your mind together.
I said to stop it!
Stop it.
Please, stop it.
Right now...
You can still wait now.
I'm saying you can wait a little bit.
Whether my decision is wrong,
don't you judge it by yourself.
You want me to forgive them?
The thing you are worried about is the medical malpractice lawsuit.
A lawsuit is like a disease.
If you ignore it thinking it's nothing much, it will spread throughout your body instantly and
ultimately, it makes a person die.
It will kill our Myeongwoo.
Then, Father,
what if the guardian doesn't proceed with the lawsuit?
That patient's guardian already requested the records of the surgical procedure.
It means he has already started preparing for the lawsuit.
So I'm saying,
if the guardian doesn't proceed with the lawsuit, will you forgive all of us?
What's the reason? Is it because of Han Jae Joon?
Of course.
Why are you talking like this now when you said you needed time when I told you to get engaged?
I only have that person.
If he gets kicked out, I'll have to live by myself forever. Can you let that happen?
What horrible thing are you saying?
So then, Father, promise me.
If the medical malpractice lawsuit doesn't happen, forgive all of us.
Fine then.
But the medical malpractice lawsuit will start for sure.
In this world, there aren't any guardians or doctors that Han Jae Joon talked about.
I will look for one this time.
Thank you, Father.
How can that be a meal?
Do you know how tasty this is?
You have to make it right to make it a meal.
Why did you come here?
I have a favor to ask.
What favor?
He'll forgive us if we just stop the medical malpractice lawsuit?
Yeah, so that's why I'm asking you to help me.
If he's going to forgive us, he should just let it pass.  Why is he being so petty by putting a condition on it?
Anyway, an opportunity is available for Chief Han.
You will help right?
Forget it.
If you stay still, you'll get kicked out too.
If he kicks me out, I'll just leave.
Don't you need money?
I can earn it here, and if it doesn't work out, I can steal too.
Are you going to be keep being so twisted?
You said Chief Han is a decent person.
And there are those who you said were real doctors.  Are you going to just watch them get kicked out?
Well, that's true.
Why is it me?
Why do you talk so much when you can say that you'll help?
Why the temper when you're asking for help?
Fine then. I'll do it alone.
Okay, I'll help you.
Other people's lives and deaths are on the line. Can't you be more serious?
You don't die just because  you take off the gown.
Hey, Park Hoon!
Sorry, sorry. What do I have to do?
First of all, we have to persuade the guardian.
Aigoo, it's expected of a quack.
How can that be the first?
Just do as I say.  Huh?
Okay, I got it.
I'm sorry, Doctor.
I can't just let it pass when those people tried
to hide what they did wrong.
Dad.
We can promise monetary compensation for a mistake made during the surgical procedure.
Money is important.
However, what I want to know is what went wrong during my wife's surgical procedure.
Also if they did something wrong, I believe a sincere apology for what they did wrong is more important.
I doubt those people will ever apologize...
Doctor Park...
I got it.
Then we will go first and try to talk to them.
Apologize?
What apology? What are you?
If we didn't do the surgery, we would have been in trouble.
Cardiology Department's treatment was good enough.  Did you know that?
You guys were the ones who over-treated the patient.
Let them do the lawsuit if they want to.
We are not even going to blink our eyes.
Now what do we do?
What do you mean?  If begging doesn't work then we need to threaten.
Threaten?
Jae Cheol's mom's surgical procedure was done by the cardiologist's third year resident.
I heard about Doctor Kim, too.
I called the branch just in case.
They said he's on vacation. He's not answering the phone either.
If so, we should go find him.
How?
- Do you have some money?
- Money?
Why money?
We need to find Doctor Kim.
Hyungnim is doing well, right?
Of course, he's been well.  Thanks to you.
In very good health.
- In prison.
- Oh no.
- I really had my mouth shut tight.
- It's okay.
During the 10 years Hyungnim isn't here,
I am the Hyungnim.
Congratulations.
Ah, well, there's no need to congratulate.
- Well, then, work hard.
- Where are you going?
Oh, yeah.
Here.
- You should endorse it.
- Ah... Right?
- Of course.
- Of course I have to endorse it.
My kids really had a difficult time trying to catch this guy.
Guys, count!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten,
eleven!
11!  That's a freakin' lot of kids, isn't it?
I should feed them beef. 10 for each head.
Wow, your memory is really good!
Let's feed them some beef.
Who is this woman?
It just keeps coming out. Is this an ATM or what?
Here. That's enough, right?
- Give me 500 more won (50 cents).
- What's with 500 won?
I don't know. You asked for it too, hmm?
Oh!
Here!
Okay!
You've suffered through a lot!
Okay, let's go now.
Thank you.
Call me if something comes up again.
What are you here for?
I have something to tell you.
It tickles, Doctor.
If they use a kid to record me, did they think I'd fall for it?
Recording? What recording?
Don't play dumb. If I say that I made a mistake,
you are going to record it and use that as evidence in the lawsuit!
I don't know what you are going to say but we have done nothing wrong.
You're right, my father was the one who made a mistake.
You were trying to make my mom better when that happened. A lawsuit...
I don't think we need to do things of that nature.
Since you are a doctor, even if you are really mad because of my dad,
- I wish you'd understand.
- Is that so?
Tell your dad exactly what you just said.  Got it?
Professor!
Aren't you being too much to a kid?
A fist is closer than the law, hmm?
Hey.  Hey.  Hey.
- Let's settle this peacefully. If you don't apologize...
- Doctor!
Look here, Ahjussi,
I'm telling you that even if this goes to a lawsuit, there is nothing you'll gain.
Have you heard of beating your head against the wall?
You are doing just that right now.
There is nothing else I want.
If a mistake was made during the surgical procedure, really acknowledge that fact,
and all you need to tell me is, "I'm sorry," and "I've made a mistake."
Just so you can record it and submit it to the court if we apologize like that?
Ah seriously, do you think you can we're that easy to fool?
You little... That's enough, you bas--
What is this?
Watch from over there if you are curious.
I'm sorry.
Our professor should have done the surgical procedure. But while a resident was performing the surgical procedure,
there was a mistake.
Above all, the fact that we did not tell you the truth from the start,
I'm sincerely sorry.
We've done something so shameful as doctors.
I'm sorry.
Was it that difficult?
To say "I'm sorry, I made a mistake!"
"I'm sorry, I made a mistake!"
Was it that difficult to say that?
I'm going to sue all of you.
All of you...
Don't do it, Dad.
Even so, they're people who tried to make Mom better.
They will also heal me, too.
They will heal you, too, if you get sick later.
Thank you.
Buy me at least a meal if you are thankful.
Tae Sung!
I told you not to pick up things rashly. Give me that.
Why? It's dirty.
Just because.
Son.
I'm sorry, Son. You've waited a long time, right?
Is this your son?
You can't go around like this.  Come this way please.
I think it's because we are near the Psychiatric ward.
What's wrong?
I don't know.
Hey, Park Hoon.
It's all over.
It's  all  over.
After a diversified screening,
out of the three candidate hospitals, the chosen hospital to perform the surgery on Prime Minister will be
Jaeil University Hospital.
What were the specific criteria for your selection?
When is the surgery date?
Why was Myeongwoo eliminated...
Yes, Jaeil University Hospital,
not only secured the best medical team,
but it was especially highly assessed in the area of ethics.
Anyway, since there weren't any clear differences in the overall evaluation in all 3 hospitals...
The final decision is Jaeil University Hospital.
Jaeil University Hospital.
Then what is going to happen to us?
What do mean 'what happens to us'?
Competitions or whatever, it's all over now.
This situation is exactly what you call, "It's pie in the sky."
Isn't that right, Water Bottle?
It was a subjective decision...
Why are you so happy when he says our hospital has been eliminated?
That's why I'm happy.
- Do you want some?
- Give it.
So dirty.
Because of Soo Hyeon's plea, I'll let it go for now.
Thank you, Chairman.
Then, you forgive all of the other doctors too, right?
Except one.
Who?
Park Hoon. That guy can't be here.
Dr. Park is the one who suffered the most in stopping this lawsuit, but why?
No means no!
- My Master, you suffered a lot all this time.
- Yeah.
You also suffered a lot.
I hope you fulfill your father's wishes.
Hey, wait.
What did you do with the ₩50 million that I gave you?
You probably can't use that.
Why not?
Because I only have half of each one.
Okay, since they're useless anyway, I'll get rid of them.
You worked hard.
I'm sorry.
You take it.
Can you throw this away?
Hey, Quack,
If you keep doing just as much as you're now, you'll become a useful doctor someday too.
Take care.
By chance, if you want to stay here longer, tell me.
I'll try talking to my father again.
Forget it. Your father will never be able to take me in.
Why?  Father was the one who said he'd accept you in the first place.
That was when he didn't know who I was.
What are you saying?
There is something like that.  Anyway, take care.
Thoracic Surgery Department Park Hoon
Tell me what I need to do now.
Alright.
Doctor Park!
Just in case, take it.
Thoracic Surgery Department Park Hoon
Help me.
Thank you.
♬  I'm going to meet you right now. Let's meet again.  ♬
♬  When we meet again, we'll be really happy.  ♬
♬  Me, without you, I can't do anything.  ♬
Did Patient Kim Cheul Seo's blood test in room 25 come out yet?
The directions to that injection has to be done by a doctor.  Just a minute please.
♬ Let's meet again. ♬
Yes, it's the nurses' station.
Hey, you quack.  Since you can't even do that right, that's why you are being called a quack.
Ouch. Let go.
- When will you come to your senses?
- Ow, it hurts! It hurts!
When will you? When will you come to your senses?
♬  I am missing you. I want to be together.  ♬
♬  I won't let you go the second time.  ♬
♬  Now let's go and meet. I won't let you go again.  ♬
♬ If we meet again, ♬
- Hello? Hello?
Are you not going to pick up the phone?
♬  If you are not there, I am nothing.  ♬
We need to wait for Patient Kim Cheol Seo's blood results.
Doctor Oh...
Doctor Oh, are you crying?
Me?
Is something wrong?
No, it's just... I think something went in my eye.
♬  I'm going to meet you right now. Let's meet again.  ♬
♬  When we meet again, we'll be really happy.  ♬
Why?
Just for a minute.
♬  Me, without you, I can't do anything.  ♬
♬  Let's meet again.  ♬
♬  Let's meet again right now.  ♬
Why aren't you eating?  This is all expensive food.
Please explain something to me.
What do you mean Jaeil University Hospital?
Ah... About that...
I put Myeong, Mingook, and Jaeil,
these 3 items for approval.
It was an agenda the President had a lot of interest in too.
In that case, he wanted to make the decision.
But, by reading his countenance,
it seemed like he was going to reject the hospital I chose.
If I chose Myeongwoo, he seemed like he was going to choose Mingook or Jaeil.
So, I purposely chose Mingook, but,
of all places, he chose Jaeil at that moment!
I did not come here because I wanted to hear those words, Prime Minister.
Of course.
The words that you want to hear should be in here.
Do not worry too much.
Our work will progress well.
It's an awesome place.
Aigoo. As you can see, there isn't much here.
The cup is not important as long as it tastes good.
Out of all the coffee I've ever tasted, it's really the worst.
Jeez, I did my best yet you're complaining that it's not tasty. Really, this person.
Is this rotten? It's gone bad.
Your skills in brewing coffee are totally different from your skills in surgery.
Well, you didn't come here to taste my coffee.
What brings you all the way here?
I have two things I want to ask you.
Two?
My surgery. Why did you help?
Why did you do that surgery?
It's because of the patient.
Ultimately, was it because of the same reason?
I'm sorry. If I had done it in the first place, you wouldn't have been in a difficult position from the beginning.
I heard from Doctor Oh.
Thanks to you... Thank you.
It's not like I did anything that great.
Did you stop the lawsuit because you were worried about me?
This is the second question I want to ask you.
A little.
It's unexpected.
It's unexpected for me, too, that I'd be worried about you.
Why?
Why were you worried about me when we were uncomfortable with each other?
You really have an unique hobby.
This is getting embarrassing. Do you really have to hear this?
Yes.
You know already.
I need to hear it personally from your own mouth.
This is really...
I thought you were an okay doctor. Satisfied?
Let's have a drink. It'll be my treat.
This is hard.
Have you never made curry before?
Since I don't like it all that much.
Why did you make so much of something you don't even like?
Wow! You're really good.
Aren't you going to eat?
I wonder how long it takes to get to Dr. Park's clinic from here.
- Why?
- It seems like he likes curry.
Since it looks like there would be a lot of leftovers, should we invite him here?
Is that why you made so much?
No.
It looked like he just adds instant curry on top of rice.
How do you know that?
I just... Is that okay?
- Aiyoo.
So we fervently fought to do the Prime Minister's surgery but then BAM the hospital's been eliminated from the outside!
Not even knowing it'd turn out like this, do you know how fast my heart was racing when I failed the first patient's surgery?
Even the sky turned yellow (feeling devastated).
Your words are becoming a little short.
(It means that he's starting to speak informally.)
Did I?
I'm very sorry.
It's okay. You've aged a lot more than me anyway.
So that's why I was curious.
How did you get such amazing skills
at such a young age, and on top of that from North Korea?
My father was a doctor.
Then is he still there?
He died.
That's unfortunate.
Then what about your mother?
Let's stop talking about gloomy stuff.
I need to pee.  I'll go pee and come back.
Hey! Why aren't you answering the phone?
You haven't eaten dinner right?
I was making some curry and I have a lot of leftovers.
So come here and handle the leftovers.
Are you mad?
Well, I was a little sad after you left like that.
I have something to tell you, so can you come over?
Doctor Park went to the restroom.
Jae Joon!
I'm having a drink with Doctor Park.
Ah, I see.
Why Doctor Park?
No.
Doctor Han made some curry, I mean food, and there are a lot of leftovers.
I'll call you back after I ask him.
Okay.
What happened?
Jae Joon picked it up.
I think they are together.
But why are you so flustered?
I am not.
Then, tell Chief Han to come over, too.
Oh, should I?
What do you think about Dr. Oh?
Dr. Oh...
At first, I thought she was a quack with only a sharp hand.
But after seeing her awhile, she tries hard, too,
and because I think she is slowly becoming a real doctor,
she's also cute.
When I keep looking at her, I get reminded of Jae Hee sometimes.
Does Jae Hee look like Dr. Oh?
That's not it.
Just, I wish Jae Hee would be more like Quack.
As a doctor.
How is Dr. Oh as a woman?
Hey you... Do you think I like Quack or something?
It can be the opposite.
Wait, by chance, are you concerned Quack would like me?
My goodness... This person is so...
Oh, this is...
This person was worried that I would like you.
How can you pick up someone else's phone?
You kept calling so I picked it up, thinking it might be urgent.
Did you perhaps say you like me over the phone?
Stop sprouting nonsense.
Stop and please eat.
Hey, Quack. Honestly, we just can't be.
I'm sorry when your beloved man is here, but
the people I hate the most are ones with a bad temper.
On top of that, your violence, vanity, and whoa...
Hey, did I say I like you?
I was trying to act kindly because I took pity on you for getting kicked out of the hospital. You're seriously...
Relax.
How can I relax?
I called you because I thought you weren't even eating properly, but your words are too harsh.
The one being too harsh is you, Soo Hyeon.
- Stop.
- How am I being too harsh?
I'll go.
You were too harsh.
It's okay.
You got along well at the hospital.
How did you know I liked curry?
I'm curious, too. How did Dr. Oh know that?
Quack did?
Forget it.  Just eat.
Are you okay?
What a jerk! Can he disregard a person's good will like this?
- Do you, by chance, like him?
- What?
It's not like Dr. Park has acted like that for only a day or two.
It's something you could've just laughed over.
So, are you saying I'm overreacting?
First off, calm down a bit.
I get it, so can you leave me alone for a bit?
Okay. Once you calm down a little, come downstairs.
Jerk!
I guess there won't be a reason to see each other in the future.
I guess so.
They are my parents.
Are your parents in the US?
You can say so.
You must be sad since you can't see them often.
It's not so bad for me compared to others.
In North Korea, Dr. Park's father was...
Then is your mother still there?
You are asking me many strange questions.
Did I?
Would you mind if I ask your father's name?
I want to know who he was.
In truth, there aren't that many skillful thoracic surgeons even worldwide.
If he's someone who raised someone like you, I was wondering if per chance I might know him as well.
His name is Park Chul.
Is that enough?
Who?
Yeah, you arrived?
Am I a call taxi? Why do you call me out when I'm busy?
Sorry, sorry. I'll be out soon.
How is Park Hoon's mother here?
I am soon going to let her meet with Park Hoon.
Why?
It's the Prime Minister's order.
Why was he so curious about someone else's family history?
Family history?
Who?
It's nothing, so just drive.
How was your father's wedding?
Not bad, but now I have a stepmother who is two years younger than me.
I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
It's about Professor Park Chul.
Didn't you say he went missing?
Find out if he went to North Korea, by any chance.
North Korea?
Work pertaining to there is costly...
I'll compensate for it.
Compensate?
Okay. I'll find out and call you back.
Are you still waiting for Professor Park Chul?
Did the professor still not return?
Just go home.
The trial was cancelled because Professor Park didn't show up.
No...
Please open the door. Professor, answer me.
You said you would tell them that my dad died a wrongful death.
You said you would testify!
- Seung Hoon.
- You heard it too, Mom.
Professor said he would testify!
Seung Hoon. I am...
Mom, Mom!
Mom, come to your senses! Mom!
Help! Mom!
Come to your senses!  Come to your senses, Mom!
Help!
Mom, Mom!
Are you waiting for someone?
My son...
There is no one here. I will escort you to your room.
Dad.
I will go to school.
Mom  001-1-949-2419-25
Hello?
Are you perhaps Hoon?
Yes.
I am Hoon.