[Please Remember Me
Episode 21]
Nian.
Trust me.
I will come back.
It's a deal.
Deal.
This is strange.
Why hasn't Nian come here yet?
Maybe Nian is reluctant to see Qi off.
Looks like she won't come.
I'm leaving.
Qi, goodbye.
Take care, Qi.
Take care.
We will miss you.
-Goodbye.
-Qi, take care.
-Take care.
Take care.
Goodbye.
Goodbye, Qi.
Take care.
Qi, take care.
Qi!
Qi, wait!
Nian is finally here.
Qi!
Luckily, she made it in time.
Nian!
Qi!
Nian.
You still came.
You're finally here.
Zisu.
This is a half piece of Bixi.
Grandma,
you told me
a living water guest will come to Sushui.
When will he come?
Sushui is not an ordinary river.
It's said that the River God let Meng Po down, the keeper of memories.
His tears flowed
and formed Sushui.
So ordinary water guests
can't come in.
Even if they can come in,
they will forget everything here
when they leave.
Only the person with the totem can come in.
The person with the totem?
Who is that?
The great hero who can take us out of Sushui.
Great hero?
When will the great hero come?
High Priest said
he'll come after I die.
After you die?
Then I don't want him to come.
I want Grandma to live forever.
Nian, remember,
when he shows up,
you must tell him
to remember us.
With it,
you can find the way back to Sushui.
Bixi is such an important thing.
How can you give it to me so easily?
Although you're from Lin State,
you're also one of us now.
Since you'll defend Ji people,
you can't forget us.
Sushui's mist is poisonous.
If you don't take this half piece of Bixi,
you won't be able to find the way back to Sushui.
It's said that when Bixi is complete, lovers can be together.
If not, they'll forget each other.
If you give me a half piece of it,
will you forget me?
No.
Seven days.
As long as you can come back within seven days,
we won't forget each other.
It's Grain Buds in seven days.
I will come back by that time.
Remember,
on Grain Buds,
you have to come back.
Grain Buds.
Morning, Brother Qi.
Morning, Nian.
What are you doing?
The smell is so strong.
I'm making maltose.
Qi taught me.
I'll deliver it to you when it's ready.
Okay.
Good morning, Grandma Jiu.
Morning.
Charge!
Warriors!
It's your duty to protect Sushui.
Ready to fight!
Add some firewood for me.
Sister Nian, he hasn't come back yet.
Why do you come here every day?
You know nothing.
What if he comes back in advance?
I want him to see me first.
I'll accompany you.
I promised Qi
to be the bravest warrior of Sushui.
Did Brother Qi teach you that?
No.
I just learned it from you.
She's getting married!
Sister, you are so beautiful.
I'm beautiful every day.
Nian, do you think Qi will come back?
Today is Grain Buds.
Qi will definitely come back.
I trust him.
Qi is back!
Brother Qi!
Qi is back?
Qi!
Brother Qi is back!
Slow down.
Qi!
Qi is back.
Qi.
Brother Qi is back.
Qi is back.
Qi!
Over here!
Qi, here!
Qi!
Here!
It's really Qi.
It's Qi.
He's back.
Qi.
Qi!
He's back. Qi is back.
Here!
Qi!
-Qi!
Brother Qi!
Here!
Qi!
We're here!
Qi, here!
Qi!
So this is the Qilin Armor.
Brother Qi is so handsome.
Qi!
Qi is back.
It's Qi.
High Priest, look!
There are so many of them.
Brother Qi!
Their armor is so cool.
Brother Qi is so handsome,
Sister Nian.
He's coming.
Uncle, have some candies.
What's going on?
High Priest,
what's going on?
Jiuye, come back!
They even killed kids!
-Jiuye!
Jiuye.
Jiuye!
They're bad guys!
All men, attack!
High Priest, be careful!
High Priest!
Attack!
Sister,
I'm fine.
I just tripped.
I'm a warrior.
Jiuye!
Let's go!
Nian!
Let's go now!
Let's go!
Jiuye.
Nian.
Jiuye!
Let's go now!
After them!
-Yes!