[City of Romance]
[Episode 11]
Senior,
you moved so many things today.
You must be tired.
It's nothing.
I'm going to be the pillar
of the comic club.
Why do I feel...
the lines sound so familiar?
They're classic lines from The Great Quest.
Yes.
You like The Great Quest?
I love it very much.
You could say
it was my entire childhood.
But
you know what?
I didn't really understand it when I was little.
All I knew was it was incredibly exciting.
It wasn't until I grew up that I realized
how much it actually influenced me.
Whenever I face a tough situation,
I think about
staying true to my original aspiration
and moving forward bravely.
I'm sorry,
The joys of boys
can indeed be somewhat trivial.
Not at all.
I think you're like
the male protagonist in a shonen comic.
Really?
But actually, I'd rather be
the male lead in an idol drama.
What?
You... You... You've arrived.
See you tomorrow.
So embarrassing.
You're here.
I've been looking for you.
You know what?
I did something big this afternoon.
I haven't had a chance to share it with you.
What is it?
This afternoon, I was chosen as a lucky audience member
to go on stage and interact with him.
I even got his autograph.
The only one
[Mr. Owl and Miss Flying Squirrel, Blake]
in this world.
I even hugged him.
Well, what's that reaction?
Not interested.
You haven't stopped being a fan, have you?
No.
Then where did you go this afternoon?
I had something to do, so I went out.
That's a shame.
You missed a lot of iconic moments.
You know what?
This afternoon, I was standing in that crowd.
I was jumping up and down.
Then Blake, dressed as an owl,
said, "You!"
"You little mouse, come up here!"
And the crowd was like...
Then I went on stage and hugged him.
Alright,
I'll stop talking about it.
Otherwise, I'll just make you jealous.
Here, take it.
[I hope today can become your beautiful memory]
Don't you...
want this?
Of course I want it too.
But one can't be greedy.
I've already hugged him,
and our relationship is pretty good.
So, I'll...
give this to you
to make up for what you missed.
I don't want it.
Don't be polite with me.
Take it.
Just take it.
Next time when I want to see it,
you can just show it to me.
Do you like it?
Since you've given me such a precious gift,
should I give you something in return?
What do you want?
You've already given it to me.
When did I give you a gift?
That owl on the sticky note
is just as precious.
What's wrong with you?
Are you feeling unwell?
You're having a fever?
It's not hot.
[Episode 11: Xiaoduo on the Offensive]
I'm fine.
Look.
They're so alike, right?
Xiaomiao,
you look amazing in that Hanfu today.
Thank you.
I'm going back to the dorm then.
Senior He Rui, I'm back.
Xiaomiao, you're back.
How was the exchange conference today?
There were so many people. It was really lively.
I saw on social media
Blake was a surprise guest.
Did you see him?
Yes.
Bai even went on stage to interact with Blake.
Xiaoduo must be very happy
to meet Blake.
She was absolutely thrilled.
She immediately went to show off to Senior Su Yancheng.
Is that so?
They really are close to each other.
[In the flower of youth]
[Mr. Owl and Miss Flying Squirrel]
Senior,
why are you so serious today?
What's wrong?
You know Tian Chuan from Xue City University, right?
I heard
he's always been a problem student.
He was
also like this in high school.
Is that so?
I'm not implying anything.
It's just that he's been pestering you.
I think there must be a reason for it.
Once upon a time,
there was a girl
who was used to walking alone to and from school.
One day,
in the alley she often passed through,
a whistle sounded.
You're from No. 1 High School?
You must have a lot of pocket money.
Give me some.
Don't touch me!
What's wrong with touching you?
Do... Do you know what the grade director's surname is?
What's his surname? Bai?
Yes, Bai.
[Bai Xiaoduo, Rao City No. 1 High School]
He's my uncle.
That time, she protected herself with a lie.
But who would have thought
from then on, the bully would keep harassing her?
Remember me?
Is the grade director your uncle?
Do you think lying is fun?
Do you think I'm a fool?
I didn't mean to lie to you.
I was so scared that day.
I lied to you to make you leave me alone.
It's okay.
Let's wait and see.
Please tell that girl
that from now on,
no matter what happens in the future,
her friends will always stand by her side,
firmly choosing her.
She's no longer afraid of that bully.
Because now she has many friends
who will be with her,
accept her,
protect her,
and always stand by her side.
[Don't stop drinking]
Check, please.
Fan-made comics.
Xiaomiao always blushes when she sees me.
Could it be because...
Senior Xiao Yang,
what are you doing here?
You went to buy something?
It's rare to come to an exchange conference,
so I bought some comics and merchandise.
Are they comics with lots of handsome guys?
[Don't stop drinking]
Just some ordinary shoujo comics.
Right, Senior Xiao Yang,
this is for you.
The Great Quest?
I remember
you like The Great Quest, right?
I saw this figurine over there just now
and thought you might like it.
Consider it a thank-you for always taking care of me.
I didn't expect you to remember
something I said casually.
As long as you like it.
I like it.
Xiaomiao, let's go look around some more, okay?
Frog, frog, jump!
Frog jump, frog jump!
Be careful with the board behind you.
Stop fooling around, you guys.
What happened?
There's a pervert in the bathroom.
A pervert?
Yes.
Look at this.
A hook?
Someone installed a camera
in the bathroom.
Fortunately, He Rui noticed it early.
We can't tolerate such a thing!
Let's go!
Put it down.
We need to stay calm now.
I'm going to the surveillance room and see if I can find anything.
You stay with He Rui.
Rest well.
I'll go too.
This is really terrifying.
How could something like this happen?
[Public Lavatory]
There are blind spots.
It's hard to see clearly.
The surveillance footage shows it was around 9 a.m.
At that time, the exhibition hall should be closed.
Could it be someone on the inside?
What are you implying?
Are you suggesting it was an inside job?
I didn't mean that. I apologize.
[Public Lavatory]
Can we go in and take a look?
Don't worry. We've assigned people to investigate.
Why don't you...
go back and wait for news?
Okay. Thank you.
Okay.
Let's go.
So,
did you find the suspect?
The surveillance footage is unclear.
The security guard said they're investigating
and asked us to wait a bit longer.
How long do we have to wait?
I might have a way to catch that person.
That person must have been familiar with the environment beforehand,
installing the camera
when no one was around.
I'm sure he'll retrieve the camera
when there are few people around.
That is, on the evening when the event will be over.
Right?
So what we need to do is...
Waiting for that person.
That makes a lot of sense.
But that's not enough.
We need to make a plan.
So what's the plan?
Since that person is so familiar with the environment,
he must know
the best way to...
Well...
can I join you?
[Ladies' Room]
What are you doing?
It's really you.
You went to the bathroom in the middle of the night.
That's strange.
Am I not allowed to use the bathroom?
The evidence of your crime has been recorded.
Give it to me.
Don't expect to escape!
You pervert!
I'm gonna slap you!
Why did you slap me?
Why were you standing there?
You're so stupid! He escaped!
You're so stupid! I can't believe you!
So stupid!
Alright, stop. He's already gone!
Enough.
Let's go help them.
Let's go.
[College Manga Exchange Conference]
Why hasn't he come here yet?
He's here. Watch me.
Help!
Catch the pervert!
It's you again, brat.
You want another beating?
Come and get me.
I...
You guys want to gang up on me, huh?
Isn't that your favorite thing to do?
Watch out!
Pervert!
Give me the DV!
Watch out!
Get out of the way!
What are you doing here?
It's in the middle of the night.
All of you, go back to school.
Leave the rest to me.
Go!
What you did is against the law.
Security guards,
go arrest him
and take him to the police station.
Okay.
[He violated the relevant provisions of Article 42 of the Law of the People's Republic of China on Penalties for Administration of Public Security]
[Tian Chuan placed a camera in the bathroom to secretly film others' privacy]
[to detain him for ten days and impose a fine of 500 yuan]
[The public security authorities have decided]
♫In this bustling world♫
♫Amid the crowded sea of people♫
♫Every time I toss and turn♫
♫It's all because of you♫
♫I wish I could tell you♫
♫Every boy would like you♫
♫My humor and charm♫
♫All belong to you♫
♫Perfectly♫
♫I follow your path♫
♫I'm very cautious♫
♫Keeping the longest memories♫
♫Of me and you♫
♫The sea breeze♫
♫The rain from the eaves♫
♫I still like you after all this time♫
♫I'd give you all my best memories♫
♫I didn't tell you♫
♫Because I was hesitant♫
♫Don't worry♫
♫That I'll leave without saying goodbye♫
I like you.
♫I'll give you the best♫
♫I'll give you♫
[The 10th College Manga Exchange Conference]
Is...
♫I just want to give it all to you♫
what you said true?
Can I... see your face?
♫I'll give you♫
♫I'll give you the best♫
[The 10th College Manga Exchange Conference]
Are you surprised?
Are you amazed?
Bai Xiaoduo,
you're dreaming of me.
Do you like me?
Su Yancheng.
How come it's you?
[The 10th College Manga Exchange Conference]
Impossible. Impossible.
How could Blake be Su Yancheng?
And why would he like me?
Xiaomiao.
You scared me,
Bai.
Do you know who I dreamed of yesterday?
You dreamed of Blake.
How did you know?
You've dreamed of him like 800 times already.
That's not true.
Bai,
have you really
fallen in love with Blake?
I like him.
But
you don't even know what he looks like.
I mean
it's more than just a fan's love for an idol.
I don't know.
Detective Su!
Come quickly!
Come.
What's wrong?
Quack plasters.
What quack plasters?
These are the Bai family's heirloom plasters.
They're very precious.
They're still plasters.
Are you going to use them or not?
I'm fine.
A-Actually, my injury is almost healed.
Almost healed, huh?
I used to think you had slender arms and legs.
I didn't expect that you're capable of doing a shoulder throw.
I thought you were useless.
Done.
I'm useless?
That's not what I meant.
What I wanted to say is...
actually...
you are the spiritual pillar of the comic club.
And I think everyone is great.
In the past, Blake gave me strength.
But now, I think it's so good to have friends.
So it doesn't matter anymore whether Blake
is in MCUSOM or not.
From now on, let me, Vice President,
assist you.
Wait.
You just said
it doesn't matter anymore whether Blake is in MCUSOM or not.
What does that mean?
It just doesn't matter anymore.
Because I've already met him.
I'm very happy.
It doesn't matter?
You're not looking for him anymore?
No, I'm not.
How could you just stop looking for him?
You're the one who said you wanted to find him.
You're also the one saying you're not looking for him.
Can you at least be a little...
persistent in that?
What's wrong with you?
Listen, stop trying to pressure me
with your president's tone.
I see.
Are you jealous that I've met Blake?
If you want to see him, go find him yourself.
If I could find him...
Hello, Dad.
Don't worry. I'm fine.
Listen, I did something big recently.
[Comic Club]
Thank you all for your hard work at the exchange conference.
We won
the first place in the creativity competition.
We also won the popularity award.
And we caught the pervert in the bathroom.
Therefore, the organizers
gave us a special award.
Although the funding isn't a lot,
it's enough for our comic club's expenses.
Great!
Friends, long time no see.
Yu Chi, you look great today!
When did you come back?
Why didn't you tell us earlier?
Who is she?
I don't know.
You heartless girl, you didn't contact us.
Yeah.
But they seem to be very close.
How could I not miss you?
Su Yancheng,
you're still the same as before.
You wouldn't even pretend to be surprised.
Wow.
Yu Chi, come and sit over here.
Have some water.
Thank you.
You must be Bai Xiaoduo.
Hello, I'm Yu Chi.
You know me?
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
Su Yancheng.
Why didn't you answer my calls?
Check your phone.
Hi, Yu Shubo.
Long time no see.
I like you.
Well, the professor wants to see us. So...
come to me once you're done.
I'm going first.
Got it.
I'm leaving, everyone. Bye bye.
Bye bye.
Well, let me introduce her to you guys.
This is Yu Chi.
She was also a member of the comic club in the freshman year.
Later, she went abroad as an exchange student.
When she was in the comic club,
she and Su Yancheng had
a remarkable rapport.
Let's welcome her with a round of applause.
Su Yancheng,
can I join the comic club again?
You're very familiar with this place. Feel free to do whatever you want.
Welcome back.
Thank you.
You deserve it.
Today is a good day.
Our comic club has won awards.
And Yu Chi has come back.
Let's find a place to celebrate.
Good idea!
How about... going to a scary escape room?
Okay, I know a place.
If Xiaomiao will go, I'll go too.
Bai Xiaoduo.
Let's go together.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
Why does she keep calling me?
She...
She likes you.