[English subtitles are available]
[The Flowers Are Blooming]
[Episode 9]
It doesn't hurt, right?
Luo.
Recently I have to
to draw draftings for Architect Li.
Let Meng Yuanxu push your wheelchair.
Do you have any places you want to go these days?
Tell Meng Yuanxu.
He will take you there.
Jing Ci Temple?
Go to Jing Ci Temple first.
Luo was badly injured in that house.
There must be evil spirit on her.
We must worship Buddha no matter what.
For safety.
Don't bother.
Mr. Lin's medicine is very effective.
In a few days,
I'll be able to walk again.
I think
it'll work.
But you can go to Lingfeng Temple, Shaoxing Temple
and Faxi Temple.
Why do you go to the remote Jing Ci Temple?
Master, you don't understand.
Jing Ci Temple is located on the hillside.
It's hard for people to go up or down the hill.
So it tests the sincerity of the people worshiping Buddha.
As the saying goes, if you wish really hard, maybe you'll get what you want.
Since we are going to pray for Luo’s safety,
we should let the Buddha see our sincerity.
Since it's so inconvenient,
maybe Luo doesn’t need to go there in person.
Master is right.
Luo should stay in the yard.
You and I go to pray for her.
Luo.
You can rest at home.
But Miss...
Mr. Li also got minor injuries.
I’ll invite them to come with us.
I...
No.
Mr. Luo.
Sincerity.
We've climbed the mountain and offered the incense.
If this is not called sincerity, it's not worth it.
Let's go.
Please bless Luo.
Luo will recover soon.
Bless Luo to recover soon.
I hope that everything goes well in Wood Feather House.
Wood Feather House can be safe and smooth.
Bless Luo to be able to jump soon.
Bless everyone healthy. Very healthy.
Bless the wellbeing of the people of the Xiao Dynasty.
Bless His Majesty healthy.
Please bless us.
Sir,
please keep these eight amulets.
Thank you, Master.
I'll ask for another marriage amulet.
Marriage amulet is also called mandarin duck amulet.
There are two of them.
One for the man. The other for the woman.
They'll love each other after wearing it.
I have never heard of it.
What?
Xu said
his was from Jing Ci Temple.
Only your temple has it in Lin'an.
Some folk warlocks
like to give away this kind of amulet.
But Jing Ci Temple doesn't have any of it.
Xu was cheated.
Since you mentioned it,
I’ll say one more thing.
You are all lovers.
It’s fate and man’s will.
Your marriage will come true.
Take care.
Be careful.
Be careful. Be careful. Mr. Luo.
A little further.
Move forward.
This stone is stable.
Be careful.
Wait.
Take care.
Be careful.
This stone is stable.
Stand still.
Stand here. Don’t move.
Meng Yuanxu, help Miss Zhao.
Come on.
Be careful.
No, I can walk by myself.
That's right. She can walk by herself.
She doesn't need any help.
Take care.
Be careful.
Miss Zhao! Miss Zhao! Miss Zhao!
Are you okay?
Are you alright, Miss Zhao?
Miss Zhao.
Leave me alone.
I told you to leave me alone.
Miss Zhao.
We are not...
Be quiet! Snake!
I...
Snake! Be careful!
Miss Zhao, don't move.
Miss Zhao! Miss Zhao! Miss Zhao!
Li Qingfeng.
What should I do with you?
[Wood Feather House]
How is Miss Zhao?
Niaoniao has sent her back.
Don't worry.
Qingfeng.
If anything happens again,
even the Heavenly King is here,
I'll quit the job in the evil Liao Mansion.
Luo.
It was just an accident.
No need to think about it.
You go back first.
Smile?
Are you blaming me for sucking poison blood for Miss Zhao?
I know that you are a righteous man.
If it were me,
I would do the same.
But...
But..
You think Miss Zhao and I
touched each other.
♫The wind stopped in the story of flowers♫
I don't know.
♫Waiting for people to listen♫
♫The moon hidden in the boundless night sky♫
♫Looking for its dreamboat to find♫
It was made a long time ago.
It's useful now.
♫I'm trapped in an endless universe♫
What is this?
I always make you angry.
♫You are the starry night sky♫
But I don't know what to say to apologize.
I can only use it to help me.
♫Every single word♫
♫Is never heard but familiar♫
Then call it Xiao Qingfeng.
♫Like we have been in chemistry since we were born♫
Do you expect it to do the work for you?
Xiao Qingfeng.
♫The wind chased the moon for a thousand miles♫
It’s a nice name.
♫Write the most romantic poem of my life♫
Xiao Qingfeng looks so greasy.
And it seems to have some evil thoughts.
♫You are my unexpected scenery♫
♫It's the first time I feel my heart flip♫
It seems that
♫Not knowing why♫
it can't help much.
♫Just let it pass by♫
♫The moon has seen my hair get lifted by the wind♫
♫It also knows what I hope most for the lengthy life♫
♫I have no courage to guess our ending♫
♫From dark night to dawn♫
♫Stars have sunk into the sea♫
♫And I only want to belong to you♫
Let's assume you were poisoned, too.
My sister.
No. Look at you.
You came out to get some fresh air in the middle of the night?
Brother.
I really can't let it go.
What? What?
If you really
If you really can't let it go,
just cry.
Here.
I made all these.
And give everyone one of them.
Li Qingfeng is so arrogant.
It's easier for him to be targeted by evil spirits.
Master is always with him.
It's too dangerous.
Sir.
You're still the same as when you were young.
When I was young?
Yes.
Have you forgotten
the time you and Miss in the Ministry of Works?
Yes. Together with you.
You followed Master the second time she came here.
At that time, you treated me as your enemy.
In order to play with Master,
I fought with you a lot.
I still remember it clearly.
Although you don't stop me now,
Li Qingfeng is between us now.
It's done.
Look.
Arrange the order and mark.
We can notify everyone to return to work tomorrow.
Brilliant.
If you take out every part separately,
it seems to be traditional.
But when they're combined, it's harmonious and unified.
It's so neat and beautiful.
This design is my own style.
Your style?
I remember you said
the Gold Building does not match your style.
And you criticized it as worthless.
I don't understand.
If it's not your style,
whose will it be?
You've seen it.
Me?
The gambler of the Gold Building?
My father.
Uncle?
What kind of misunderstanding is there between you two?
No misunderstanding.
But I don't want to see him.
I don't want to see his work.
Listen to me.
Father and son can't be strangers.
You should
go back to see your father more.
What if he
wants me to take you back to see him?
Again?
Luo.
Master, Miss.
Why are you here?
Sit down.
Master. Why are you blushing?
You...
It's because it's too stuffy in the room.
So I went to Luo for some fresh air.
Really?
What are you doing?
We're making a peach wood sword.
I'm making a copper cash sword for him.
I told you to find the craftsman.
But you're still here
and doing all this.
Architect Li has drawn the drafting.
We can return to work tomorrow.
You can't do this anymore.
Okay.
Miss Chen.
Miss Zhao! Miss Zhao!
Luo. Sit down.
Miss Zhao,
you've recovered?
I've recovered.
Thank you for your concern.
Li Qingfeng just finished the drafting and you came.
Your nose is so sharp.
But you are
always around Miss Chen.
It must be very convenient for you to frisk.
Why does it make me feel uncomfortable
when hearing what you just said?
No, little girl.
You mean I'm a dog?
She was just kidding.
Don't take it seriously.
I was not just kidding.
What do you mean?
Of course I envy you since you're in a favored position to get close to her.
If you're jealous,
you can move in.
This proposal is quite good.
Then you can move in.
Today.
Do you need my help?
Miss Zhao, you must be kidding.
Our Wood Feather House is so shabby.
How can you get used to living here?
Miss Chen is used to living here.
I can get used to it.
I was joking.
I'm busy with my family affairs.
I can't just
move in the Wood Feather House and ignore other affairs.
By the way, where is Li Qingfeng?
He's at Wood Feather Pavilion.
I'm leaving.
Why are you still here?
I told you to find the craftsman team.
Luo,
I'll leave the rest to you.
OK.
Tell me.
What's wrong with your face?
My face?
You should care about your legs.
You.
Goodness.
If you can't do it, don't force yourself.
Tomorrow is the first day of returning to work.
I'll do your job.
You don't need to go.
Just because it's the first day of returning to work,
I should go.
Besides,
after Mr. Lin's treatment these days,
I almost recover now.
Look.
Take a good rest today.
Okay?
We'll see how is your leg after we get there tomorrow.
If your leg still hurts,
just don't force yourself.
I won't agree.
Okay.
All right. You're the best.
Why are you back?
Miss Zhao,
Miss Chen said you've finished your drawing.
What are you doing?
I'm having fun.
Having fun?
You call this having fun?
Wood mechanism has nothing to do with work.
It's my hobby.
It's just for fun.
OK.
Let's not talk about this.
I heard you're returning to work tomorrow.
That Liao Mansion is so evil.
I can find some masters for you
to help you with your work.
If so,
the rumors of Liao Mansion will be getting worse.
We can't do this.
Right.
But as the owner,
I have to do something at this moment.
Miss Zhao.
Leave it alone.
Actually, I'm here to thank you.
Thank me?
If it weren't for you,
I would have died.
You're welcome, Miss Zhao.
I would do that
for anyone else from Wood Feather House.
I hope
I've never heard the noble words you just said.
Do you feel uncomfortable
because of my presence?
A little.
I really envy Miss Chen.
Miss,
I have something to ask you.
It may be a little disrespectful.
But I still want to ask.
We are on good terms.
Tell me what you don't dare to ask.
Don't scare me.
You...
Are you in love with Architect Li?
Why do you ask that?
Keep your voice down.
Recently, your relationship with Mr. Li
is different.
Besides,
when Miss. Zhao said she would move in,
your reaction was...
You're asking for a beating.
Do you want to be beaten? Please spare me.
I dare not.
All right, let me tell you.
I only tell you.
Don't tell anyone else.
I'm afraid other people than Mr. Meng,
everyone can see it.
Is it so obvious?
It's not obvious.
Just a little.
Hush. Hush.
[Liao's Mansion]
Come. Be careful.
Wait, wait, wait.
Come on.
One for each.
Here, Luo.
Thank you.
Miss Han.
Well.
Give me one.
Come on.
The more the better.
Wang Sheng.
I don't need it.
Forget it then.
Don't think you're great because you're good at martial arts.
No matter how great you are, can you be better than the hostess here?
Mr. Meng.
Let's not talk about it.
Li Qingfeng, you don’t want it, do you?
OK, master.
This is yours.
Take it.
Don’t be like Wang Sheng and Li Qingfeng.
Look.
Look what?
Are these the craftsmen you found?
Yes, they are.
What's wrong?
No.
I've found 18 people.
Why are there only three?
What about the others?
Yes. Where are the others?
Wake up.
Get up.
The officer is here.
What about the others?
Yes. Officer.
Yesterday, you took 18 of us
to see the scene.
Yes, but...
It went well, didn't it?
You all said yes.
What's going on now?
Nothing happened in the first place.
But on our way back,
Zhang, who was telling jokes,
suddenly had a stroke and fell on the ground.
After we took him home,
Zhang couldn't get off the bed.
His wife hired a few doctors.
Later, she invited another doc to check it out.
They can't tell anything as well.
Ridiculous!
So they don't want to take this job anymore.
They asked me
to return the deposit,
and to apologize to you.
Do you think
I care about the deposit?
It's about credibility.
Credibility. Do you understand?
Qingfeng.
What should we do now?
Just let the three do it.
I never believe
the existence of ghosts and gods.
What are you looking at?
I did all these
just for you
cowards.
I want you to have some confidence.
I didn't expect it to be like this.
You really let me down.
Do you believe that
no one would dare to
hire them anymore in Li'an city?
You three, contact them now.
I need to
see them all in 2 hours.
Except for the one who had a stroke.
Let him use the money to get treated.
I'll investigate this matter thoroughly.
Officer.
We are not familiar with them.
Please don't make it difficult for us.
No need.
The initial renovation scale is not large.
Only the main house.
These three people
and us
are enough.
Besides,
thank you for coming as scheduled.
After the work,
I'll pay you another wage.
Thank you. Officer.
Only the three of them. And us?
Is it enough?
Yes.
Get back to work.
OK.
Let's go.
Although we don't have enough people,
but we have to work.
Because only in this way
can we stop the public from spreading rumors.
Then we can recruit craftsmen.
So I hope you can understand.
Everyone should work hard.
Stop nagging.
Just tell me.
What should I do?
Officer.
Luo and you take the craftsmen
to repair the walls and mow the grass in the yard.
All weeds, bricks and stones
should be cleared away.
Luo, take care of yourself.
Thank you for your concern.
Don't worry.
I'm here.
I won’t let Luo get tired.
Be careful.
Don't worry.
Master, if anything happens to you,
call me immediately. I will protect you.
Luo.
Thank you for helping me.
Be careful.
You two.
The rest
is the renovation of the main hall and the bedroom.
This is the renovation draft.
Everyone,
today,
members of Zi Yan Opera House are here to congratulate
the returning work ceremony of Wood Feather House.
After a moment,
our leading actress Su Huanjing will
perform Love of Butterfly by Shang tone.
If you want to enjoy it,
you can go in the mansion to watch.
Free of charge.
Everyone, please.
Good morning, everyone.
Let me introduce.
This is
the leading actress of Zi Yan Opera House, Miss Su.
I invited her to perform for you as my congratulation.
She'll perform Love of Butterfly by Shang tone in the courtyard later.
While you're working,
you can take a look.
So it wouldn't be so boring and exhausting.
Zhao Yi'ning.
Good for you.
You managed to invite Su Huanjing.
I’m the boss of Zi Yan Opera House.
Why can't I invite her?
OK.
Half Lin'an City is almost yours.
It's the first day of work. The more the merrier.
Miss Zhao, I know what you want.
But when we work,
we need to be very focused.
So, please ask them to go back.
Look, this is our architect.
See? He’s hard to serve.
Li Qingfeng, I’m being kind.
You see,
there were supposed to be 18 people today. Only three are left.
We can't afford any more accidents.
Otherwise, the rumor about the mansion getting worse
is exactly what the spreader wants.
On the contrary,
with so many people working with us,
I believe that the person who spread it
dare not to act rashly again.
OK. It's the first day of work.
It's good to have fun.
Fine.
Miss Su, please perform in the front yard.
How about that?
You only listen to Miss Chen.
Come on. Please.
Don't go. Don't go.
Let's go. Let's go.
Be careful.
Put it there. Put it there.
Let me do this.
After tiding it,
this mansion is getting more and more clean.
Rumors will be scotched.
Am I right, Mr. Liao?
Yes.
I really appreciate that.
Thank you.
The preliminary
is done today.
Right, Qingfeng?
This is just a preliminary plan.
The follow-up is the key part. Don't slack off.
At least we're safe these days.
Nothing happened.
If we need more people,
we can hire some to work.
That's great. That's great.
But the sooner it is done, the better.
It might be tiring these days.
It's too early to say finishing it.
Miss Zhao, what do you mean?
The Zhang who had a stroke on his way home
fell asleep safely after the treatment last night.
But he didn't wake up this morning.
Dead?
He's not dead, but it's almost the same.
What happened?
He became a living dead.
He can still breathe.
But he's unconscious.
Did other doctors go to see him?
I asked all famous doctors in Lin'an.
They all said that unless a miracle happens,
otherwise, he will never wake up again.
This disease, in the medical literature,
I remember it's called
catalepsy.
But not everyone
is as knowledgeable as Miss Chen.
Now it's all over the city.
They said Zhang saw the white shadow in the mansion.
He was so scared that his body was stiff,
and can't wake up again.
Now,
the story is getting more complicated.
So now, let alone hire new craftsmen,
I'm afraid the three of them wouldn't come here again.
Well, Mr. Li,
what should we do?
If he really saw the white shadow...
I mean
if someone dressed up as the white shadow,
Zhang was probably murdered by him on purpose.
Murdered on purpose?
Why did the murderer want to kill Zhang on purpose?
If all the previous things were done by humans,
the purpose of killing Zhang
is to confirm
the rumors of this mansion.
From the result of the discussion on the street,
that's possible.
But what is his purpose?
Why did he hurt an innocent man?
Mr. Liao, have you offended anyone?
I...
He may not offend anyone.
Maybe it was because someone with ulterior motives
wanted to lower the price of Mr. Liao's mansion.
That's why he did this.
No.
Not a human.
It's "she".
It must be her.
It's Miao Hongdou. It's Miao Hongdou.
Mr. Liao.
Miao Hongdou, it must be Miao Hongdou.
Miao Hongdou.
Come out!
Come out if you dare!
Mr. Liao, calm down.
How can I calm down?
I can't stand it anymore.
We'll figure out the truth.
But we still need your cooperation
to complete the "play".
How can I cooperate?
Yes, Wang Sheng.
Can you finish your words in one go?
I see.
Now you understand again?
If we want to scotch all kinds of rumors,
the landlord's moving back is the most effective way.
Yes.
I'll move back?
No, no, no.
I can't move back.
Yes.
If that person wants to prove the rumor,
Mr. Liao's moving back
is what that person cannot tolerate.
He will definitely show up.
Then we’ll wait for him.
That's a good idea.
I'm afraid it's not a human.
Did you hear me?
I can't move back.
Mr. Liao.
If you want us
to keep doing this work smoothly,
then we must solve the problem.
What are you doing?
Mr. Liao, do you trust us?
I do.
OK, then listen to me.
Just move back.
Don't be afraid. It'll be fine.
Miss, no one would come, right?
Relax. So many people are here.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Coming.
Oh my god, it's really a female ghost.
Did you see that?
That's qing gong.
Whose qing gong is as masterly as that? It's... flying...
If you don't believe me,
let's make a bet.
Well...
Fine, I'm not afraid.
Come on.
Excuse me.
Where is the ghost?
Are you mistaken about that?
How could it be?
How could we mistake it at the same time?
Maybe she's already inside.
Impossible.
Around the house,
there are small bells put by us everywhere.
Unless he opens the roof directly.
Oh no, Li Qingfeng.
Liao Shisan.
Give me back my life!
Don't let her run away.
Qinghe.
How could it be you?
It's you, little lady, who acts like a ghost.
Do you know how many people you've hurt?
It turns out
you're scaring other people in this mansion.
It's me.
Why did you do that?
I want revenge!
Revenge?
Which one of us has a grudge against you?
It must be Mr. Liao.
Luo! Miss Han!
I'm sorry.
Your injuries were
caused by me.
It's really you.
What about the bookshelf? You did that too?
I designed it, but I didn't do it.
I didn't expect you to come at night.
Who else could it be?
Maybe it was an accident.
But..
What about the carpenter Zhang?
I didn't do that to him.
It was just a coincidence.
I didn't mean to harm anyone.
I just want to create some small accidents
to make them shrink back.
As for Miss Han and Miss Luo's situation,
I didn't control it well.
I still feel guilty.
Qinghe, I don't blame you.
Since the first time I met you,
I felt very close to you.
Although you don't talk much,
But I can feel that you're not a bad person.
Thank you. Luo.
Tell us if you have any difficulties.
We will help you.
Luo is right.
Miss, if you really have your reasons,
you can tell us.
All of us will help you.
Yes.
If you feel wronged,
I will make it right for you.
But don't make up and lie to us,
or I won't forgive you.
I was planning to pay with my life tonight.
But unexpectedly...
Pay with your life?
Yes, my sister.
My sister was killed by Liao Shisan.
How could this happen?
My sister suffered a lot.
She was pregnant several times but miscarried.
Liao Shisan thought my sister as a jinx.
He abandoned her and had an affair with Jiang.
You jinx!
Making a fuss, huh?
Making a fuss?
I must be blind.
Why did I marry you?!
Let me tell you. Miao Hongdou.
I will marry Jiang,
no matter what you do.
Are you going to divorce me?
You're right.
I want to divorce you.
If it weren't for the property
you inherited from your dead parents,
how could I marry
a willful woman like you?
That doesn't matter.
If you can bear a baby boy for my family,
maybe I can bear to spend more years with you.
But you can't.
If you can't give birth, you can only blame yourself.
Jiang can do it?
Let me tell you.
Even without Jiang, I will divorce you.
OK. We can get a divorce.
But you won't get my money.
I won't give it to you even if you kill me.
You won't? You won't?
You...
You won't?!
You won't?! You won't?!
Liao Shisan
beat my sister up every few days.
He also had an affair with Jiang...
He also had an affair with Jiang
in front of my sister.
One day, my sister can't bear it anymore.
She argued with them.
Liao Shisan was so angry.
Then he killed my sister.
Where are you going?
To your heart.
Yes, go to my heart.
Go to my heart, go to my heart.
What are you doing here?
Why I'm here?
Go to hell!
Didn't I tell you?
As long as you give me your property,
I can divorce you.
Otherwise, I'll beat you every day.
As I said,
you can't get my money.
Fine.
I'll sell the mansion and the inn.
By then, all the money will be transported back to Jinling.
You'll never get the money.
What did you say?
Beat her!
You jinx! How dare you hit me?
Give it to me. Give it to me.
Give it to me. Strike her to death.
Give it or not?
He wanted to occupy the inn and the mansion.
No.
Liao Shisan said the mansion and the inn
were earned by them together.
He's shameless. He lied.
But you came to Lin'an
after Hongdou passed away.
How did you know that?
Liao Shisan's evil deeds
were written in the letters from my sister.
As for his murder of my sister,
I learned it
once I eavesdropped on his conversation with Jiang.
If you know the truth,
why didn't you report it to the police?
Yes, just call the police.
I'll put him in jail.
If what you said is true,
I'll behead him.
I'm afraid there's no evidence.
Yes, I have no evidence.
That's why I came up with this idea.
Firstly,
the mansion and the inn won't be sold,
so their wedding will be canceled.
Secondly, I wanted to scare him to death.
Even if I can't scare him to death,
I will find a chance to take revenge.
I'll kill him for my sister.
After my parents passed away,
she was the only family I have
in the world.
But Liao Shisan
lied to her.
She took the property left by our parents
and went to Lin'an with him.
But she didn't know
Liao Shisan is a scumbag.
He hung around in brothels and casino every day.
My sister was really blind.
So she ended up like that.
Do you think I should take revenge?
Should I?
So in order to take revenge,
you learned martial arts.
When I was nine,
she planned to take me to Lin'an.
But Liao Shisan thought I'm a drag,
and left me to the neighbors.
Uncle used to be a martial artist.
They raised me and taught me martial arts.
My sister sent me some money every month,
but was beaten by Liao Shisan because of this.
Liao Shisan is so cruel.
How about this?
I will ask my father to
arrest Mr. Liao.
He will confess after being tortured.
I've heard that Mr. Meng is an upright man.
He will never allow
you to torture him.
What should we do?
We can't arrest him without evidence.
Do you want him to be at large?
Miss,
your sister has passed away for over a year.
It's a bit difficult for us
to find evidence.
But we can find another way.
Let him confess himself.
[Hanyuan Hall]