♪Blame no one and nothing♪
♪Even if fate goes against us♪
♪Our love and faith remain unaltered
despite any adversity♪
♪Sun and moon, mountains and seas
as our witnesses♪
♪My thought follows you wherever you go♪
♪To attend the grand final meeting
in the mortal world♪
=The Dawn to the Night=
=Episode 17=
You still can't learn it after so long?
What do you mean?
Still can't learn?
Did you teach me?
You just gave some words.
Didn't even demonstrate!
Are you doubting my teaching skills?
Yes.
This is how the greatest sect
teaches its disciples?
Kneel.
What do you want me to do?
I don't want anything.
Can I just leave?
Kneel.
Don't blame me.
Blame my Master, Tian Lantern.
The point is
we don't have
the power of celestial beings
to get rid of Master's control.
Work harder.
My freedom depends on you.
I'm going to eat.
Good luck!
You!
I must get out of here!
Cross this stream,
head west, and then...
Where are you going?
To the restroom.
Why are you carrying a bag?
Senior, I'll be honest.
I want to leave.
You'd better stay alive first.
Guyue Sect
is downright banditry!
Not convinced?
Convinced.
I'm convinced.
Senior,
if you let me go tonight,
I will do anything to repay you!
Why can't you accept it?
My brother is waiting for me
down the mountain.
Without me, he can't survive.
Without me, Zhaoyang
still lives well.
That's different.
I have to find him.
Ye Tian,
do you know why
I'm the one stopping you?
I know.
Because you are the most reliable,
responsible,
and admirable one.
Thank you.
But the truth is,
Zhaoyang has other plans.
She is here.
Kneel.
My dear disciple,
where are you going?
Hua Zhaoyang.
You haunting pest!
Even if I kneel till my bones break,
I'll go find my brother anyway!
I know.
Don't worry.
We are reasonable.
What do you want?
I...
Ye Xun?
Tian.
Why are you here?
Touched?
I...
I brought your brother here
the same way I first met you.
You've gone too far!
We just came here to gather materials!
Why won't you let us go?
Innocence gets blame
when holding treasure.
Blame the Celestial Flower inside you.
Celestial Flower?
I don't even know
what it is.
I don't get it.
Guyue Sect provides food and shelter.
Why do you keep trying to flee?
You know nothing.
A true man has great ambitions.
I need to finish my book.
My readers are waiting!
You write books?
The popular Collection of Fish and Birds
is my work.
Just the final part left.
My readers are waiting.
That trash was written by you?
Trash?
You're so impolite!
I've read it too.
The Celestial Flower
is just like the Flying Herb
in your stories.
Flying Herb?
The Celestial Flower
is like the Flying Herb.
Then...
Wait, that's not the point.
Why does a copied book have readers?
Copied? Nonsense!
Which part?
Prove it!
I can't remember clearly.
Anyway,
in your stories,
every plot felt familiar.
You must've copied.
Baseless accusations.
Well, I'm tired today.
I won't argue with you.
Rongyue, how about making Xun
your disciple?
Don't make me suffer alone!
Focus!
Eyes forward!
Steady stance!
Watch your back.
Disaster.
Enough.
Dismissed!
Not bad, Ye Xun.
You've grasped the key.
Thanks to you.
Let's practice mental cultivation.
Seniors, please.
Ye Xun, you're doing great.
See?
How different are you!
What's up?
Xun is just smart.
Jealous?
No.
Rongyue teaches better than you.
Upset?
Kneel!
At this rate,
when will I ever get to leave?
I'll talk to Master.
Keep practicing here.
Why stay here?
Senior asked you to practice,
didn't you hear?
I heard. I just don't want to.
You dare disrespect Senior
over some dubious Celestial Flower?
I'll teach you a lesson!
Is this all you got?
Teach me?
You...
Shut up!
If you breathe a word
about my swordsmanship,
you'll
regret it.
Pretending, huh?
Master, what's up?
This is Guyue Sect.
We value most
propriety!
Ugh!
Master, please don't...
Kneel!
Master,
it really hurts.
If this continues,
I'll need metal knee pads.
Keep pretending.
What are you saying, Master?
I don't understand.
You're skilled at martial arts,
yet pretend to be weak
and clueless
before me, huh?
I don't understand
what you're saying, Master.
Master has told me.
With a little training,
you could become a Celestial candidate.
But you
just play dumb.
Don't you think you're despicable?
Despicable?
Me?
A Celestial candidate
sounds tempting.
Then why refuse?
You just fear staying here, right?
Ye Tian,
you want to escape the sect
more than I do, right?
Master, I really don't understand.
Well,
let's make a deal.
Go ahead.
Listen.
You just
show off your skills publicly
and become the Celestial candidate.
And then,
take my place as the Celestial.
Then, I'll be in big trouble.
Let me finish.
And then,
I'll go travel the world,
studying mystic arts
and gathering treasures
to rescue you.
How about it?
Master,
becoming a Celestial
or traveling around
freely,
which one sounds more feasible?
How about you?
I think...
Definitely,
me sneaking away is the easiest.
You're really good at pretending!
It's a pity
only we know it.
♪Sun chases moon to barren vows♪
♪Never meet even once♪
♪Cicadas dash at frozen dawns♪
♪Autumn's dirge♪
♪She buried blossoms with brocade♪
♪Love's needle
sews addiction into flesh♪
♪Shadows drink from my shattered cup♪
♪To drown till this torment cease♪
♪Moon-drunk, wind-cradled♪
♪Why deny the storm its feast♪
♪Years of dreams, she never came♪
♪Is there no cure in the world♪
♪Regardless of the past or the future♪
♪Vowing to go on
until time itself unravels♪
♪Daring to conspire with heaven♪
♪I steal heaven's script,
rewrite my end♪