♪Blame no one and nothing♪
♪Even if fate goes against us♪
♪Our love and faith remain unaltered
despite any adversity♪
♪Sun and moon, mountains and seas
as our witnesses♪
♪My thought follows you wherever you go♪
♪To attend the grand final meeting
in the mortal world♪
=The Dawn to the Night=
=Episode 24=
As you killed the Asura,
your merits are immeasurable.
Walk the Celestial Path
and you will become a true Celestial.
I thought I became a Celestial
the moment
I came out of seclusion.
Everything is as it was written
in the ancient scroll.
Asura is born from the darkness.
After you slay the Asura,
this Yin-Yang Jade
will split into two pieces.
Once you piece it up,
you can step onto the Celestial Path
and become a true Celestial.
(But it was)
(already in two pieces when I woke up.)
Is this jade a gift from you, Master?
How come I don't remember?
You have forgotten many things
in the past five years.
But it doesn't matter.
Walk the Celestial Path.
Is this the staircase to the heavens?
Hua Zhaoyang,
you've completed your cultivation
and taken down the Asura.
But if you want to
ascend as a Celestial,
there is one more trial.
What is it?
Satisfy the strongest obsession
in the mortal world
and save the one who most needs saving.
Asura?
Look for him
in the cycle of reincarnation.
Remove the root
of his suffering in the past.
Transform the flower
bred by the darkness.
The jade pendant in your hand
is born of heaven and earth.
It is the only thing
that can escape reincarnation.
Your celestial power
will be sealed into the spiritual jade
and follow you into reincarnation.
Your memories
will be sealed deep within your soul,
waiting to be awakened.
Asura is born from the darkness.
After you slay the Asura,
this Yin-Yang Jade
will split into two pieces.
I have a question.
How many times
has this jade been split up
throughout the reincarnation?
Have I been trapped in a loop,
going over the same things?
This jade
seems to carry some burdensome memories.
You two are always so troublesome.
What happened?
This is a world of constant ebb and flow
where yin and yang
complement each other.
All previous celestial beings
slew the Asuras.
All previous Asuras sought revenge.
The light and darkness
achieved balance in this universe.
But when it came to you and Ye Tian,
everything went wrong.
You had to fall in love
with each other in every cycle.
I gave you 3,000 chances.
But it was always like this,
forming an eternal cycle.
The end becomes the beginning.
The beginning becomes the end.
But isn't it good
that I've woken up?
I will remove your memory again.
Even if you reincarnate 30,000 times,
you have to reach the destined end.
What if I refuse to comply?
(No one can defy the heavens.)
Do you know what Ye Tian would say?
Heavens, my foot.
Do you remember me?
I haven't forgotten you for a moment.
(I'm a cultivator.)
(Call me Taoist Master Hua.)
(You can have)
(whatever you want
for meals three times a day.)
Deal.
(If it's possible,)
(I hope I can)
(gather herbs
in the mountains with you.)
(I can't afford to pay you.)
(The herbs don't sell that much.)
(I don't need wages.)
(Just let me tag along.)
♪Sun chases moon to barren vows♪
(You won't let others touch you)
(because you're afraid)
(that people will get infected?)
(But I don't want you
to go through that pain.)
♪Autumn's dirge♪
(I have already)
(made my choice.)
(If I were you,)
(I might make the same choice.)
(But we have to admit,)
(the one who remembers suffers most.)
♪To drown till this torment cease♪
♪Moon-drunk, wind-cradled♪
(You kept calling my name
in your dream.)
(And I have always)
(had feelings for you.)
(On the surface,)
(I came here to collect materials.)
(But now, it seems)
(it is fate that makes us)
(meet again.)
(I have no choice)
(but to seal all your memories of me)
(in this piece of jade.)
♪I steal heaven's script,
rewrite my end♪
(You always want to leave here, right?)
(Let's leave together tonight.)
You've crossed the line here.
What happened?
The heavens want to erase our memories
and make us start over.
Heavens, my foot.
Never mind.
No matter how things change,
we will always be together.
(Ye Tian,)
(we have gone through
so many lifetimes together,)
(drowning in the vortex
of love, hate, and enmity.)
(In those years,)
(we wandered through time's misty veil.)
(In the end,)
(we found each other.)
(This kiss)
(will be a closure)
(to everything we've been through.)
(Zhaoyang,)
(let's end the cycle of reincarnation)
(and find our happiness.)
(After this kiss,)
(our hearts)
(will be filled
with nothing but peace and love.)
(This is the end of our legend.)
Tian,
she is just a fraud who's been applying
to be the Imperial Preceptor.
She just won't give up.
Let's meet her.
It's an important position.
We can't be reckless.
Of course not.
Come in.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
You're the one who wants to be
the Imperial Preceptor?
It depends on the wage.
If you want to talk about the wage,
why not consider another position?
Hua Rongyue.
Tian.
Hua Rongyue,
control your temper, okay?
Shut up.
Ye Xun,
just bear with it.
I'm only bringing
someone here to apologize.
Is this how you apologize?
I'm not the one apologizing.
Leave me alone.
Ye Tian.
Long time no see.
What are you doing?
How about it?
It's the new spell I learned.
Isn't it impressive?
Impressive, my foot!
Let go.
Master, do you feel
that you need to learn another spell?
What spell?
The spell to make me obedient.
Is that so?
Let's try it.
- Kneel...
- Wait!
Don't you love the novel I wrote?
I will finish it tonight
and let you read it first, alright?
Let's keep things separate, alright?
Kneel.
No.
Come back.
- Come back, Ye Tian.
- No.
Come back.
Come here.
- Don't run.
- Come and get me.
This novel is quite in demand.
Get all three books for a discount.
At dawn,
when the sky isn't fully bright,
it's the only time
night and day can merge.
This preface is quite cheesy.
That's the vibe.
I will give you
an extra discount.
It's the perfect read for you.
The Dawn to the Night.
At least, the title isn't that cheesy.
♪Sun chases moon to barren vows♪
♪Never meet even once♪
♪Cicadas dash at frozen dawns♪
♪Autumn's dirge♪
♪She buried blossoms with brocade♪
♪Love's needle
sews addiction into flesh♪
♪Shadows drink from my shattered cup♪
♪To drown till this torment cease♪
♪Moon-drunk, wind-cradled♪
♪Why deny the storm its feast♪
♪Years of dreams, she never came♪
♪Is there no cure in the world♪
♪Regardless of the past or the future♪
♪Vowing to go on
until time itself unravels♪
♪Daring to conspire with heaven♪
♪I steal heaven's script,
rewrite my end♪