- We're taking this car?
- Mm, let's get in.
You finally get to drive a car.
It won't be a good ride.
What did you say?
Wait, what do I do now?
Because that was the
first time I drove this car.
- Oh, you drove this car already?
- Yeah.
I see.
I was with another girl,
but I'm with you this time.
(Speechless)
So funny.
There was another girl
in that seat yesterday.
Mm, now I understand
why you look so nervous.
(Nervous)
I...
I'm easygoing.
I think I am.
I get a mild scent of Seoyeon.
- Really?
- Yeah, probably her perfume on the seat.
It might be the scent from her hair.
We were just talking about that.
(Trying to lower the window)
Should we lower the windows a little?
- I knew it.
- To take in the Jeju Island's air.
But the weather today is gloomy.
Is that a good thing?
It's really bad.
(Mirang and Dagyo's first exciting drive)
So it's good that we drive around.
(What does a double date really mean?)
Yes, let's just drive around Jeju Island.
Honestly, I didn't look
at the view yesterday.
- Did you drive and talk like this too?
- Yeah.
Really?
I kept comforting her,
'Why are you crying?'
Oh, the sun's out.
I've already seen a bit of this.
Really? You went on a date yesterday?
- No, no, no.
- Really?
(Stuttering) (Embarrassed)
I saw it yesterday, but I went out alone
just to take in the view.
(Acting innocent)
Because it's outside
so you don't see it.
Probably.
Yeah, that's why I'm saying this.
I saw this when I first got here.
Back and forth... around Jeju Island.
It's not the first time
someone comes here with me.
Eh?
I guess I'm the second
woman who gets to sit here.
Is the first time so important?
(Embarrassed)
You're the second one.
The second girl in this seat.
Is being the first one so important?
I wanna get some air.
I'm gonna lower my window.
- So nice.
- Mm.
Let's follow the wind.
Mm.
- But this place is really beautiful.
- What?
(Their second date
starts at an emerald sea)
(Their second date starts at an
emerald sea) The color is so beautiful.
Very beautiful.
(What kind of memory will they make today?)
It's the prettiest today.
So beautiful.
Me?
(Embarrassed)
What?
I'm so embarrassed.
Wait a minute. What should I say today?
Today looks pretty good.
(Staring)
You're flirting with me again.
Don't you think?
Yeah, you look good.
You're always beautiful.
I already went for a drive
with Ms. Seoyeon.
To be honest, I really wanted that date
to be with Ms. Dagyo.
So I volunteered to drive her around
because I wanted to score a few points.
(Where are they heading?)
(The place where the
ocean and the fields meet)
Awesome. I want to cut through this.
The weather is really good.
(Mirang and Dagyo's first trip date)
Yes, I had to stop by for this view.
It's a must-see.
- Beautiful, right?
- We came up here just to see this view.
Who would take more beautiful photos?
Let's take some.
- To make memories.
- No.
(Both enjoying the sweetest date)
I'm not confident in this angle.
- Then I'll take some from behind.
- Fine.
Maybe from the side. How's that?
- Did they turn out good?
- Mm.
She was the date I
wanted to go on a trip with.
And I had fun getting to visit new places.
I hope she has more memories
with me than with someone else.
That would be nice.
Let's go.
But you're wearing high heels.
That must be difficult.
Maybe it's better to go down this way.
Looks like going down this way
is even more difficult.
- It's pretty steep.
- Then let's hold hands all the way down.
(Mirang tends to Dagyo
who wears high heels)
- I look good because I wear high heels.
- I know.
(Where is their next destination?)
An outdoor date is fun too.
Are you playful?
- Playful?
- Yeah, playful.
I'm not very playful.
How do you show it
when you're like someone?
Facial expression?
I just tell them.
You just do that without any planning?
That's the secret I can't reveal.
Oh, the secret?
(Hehehe)
Are you aggressive?
Tricking me into trusting you.
You have to figure it out by yourself.
But you didn't flirt with me, right?
(Shocked)
Why do you think that?
Did... did you do it?
- Did you?
- Don't know.
I think I find you cute
every time you flirt with me.
That makes sense.
I saw a cute side.
But I really think
if the other person keeps acting cute,
that would be the best thing.
If you fall for my cute side,
then it's not the answer.
Have you ever dated someone cute?
Don't know.
You're so evasive.
So do the people you dated
have different personalities?
They do.
But all my friends agree that
they must have this one quality.
I revealed my secret yesterday.
My reason for keeping this a secret
even though someone's interested in me,
is because I have a very specific type,
so they may not approach me.
I see.
- That's true.
- And even if they like me,
I may not feel the same way.
"Dagyo said she used to date
someone like that." Something like that.
Yes.
Saying that really reminds me of you.
(Disappointed)
That's why I laugh when I talk about it.
Because I'm keeping it a secret.
Now you're here and you're exactly my type.
So I don't know how to act.
But 'why is it a secret?'
I couldn't figure it out.
- There might be someone else.
- What did you expect?
I didn't. I just thought,
"I had to ask Dagyo about it." That's all.
From what you're saying right now,
you just have to keep it a secret.
(Correct)
I'm just really curious.
What's your type?
You can't tell me, but that's
what I'm curious about the most.
"What kind of person will you date?"
Because you said once that
there were two people you liked.
Because I...
have short hair. The
other person has long hair.
I don't care about that.
I was like, "Huh? What?"
When did you start keeping it short?
- When I was 23.
- 23?
- I'd love to see that.
- When I had long hair?
- When I had long hair, people said I was pretty.
- I would think so.
(Embarrassed)
(While getting to know each other, they arrive
at their destination without realizing.)
- What's this?
- What?
(What is this place they arrived at?)
What do you think it is?
Probably a double... a double...
Probably the last thing we expect.
Will there be another pair on their date?
No idea. We'll find out soon.
What's this?
(What is this place they arrived at?)
What's going on?
(The place that feels
luxurious and comfortable)
(What kind of date they
will be having here?)
(Looking around)
(What did they find?)
(A special occasion is given to
Ms. Kim Mirang and Ms. Park Dagyo
(who chose the keyword "double"
to doubly enjoy their 1:1 date.)
(A special event for Mirang and Dagyo)
- Eh? What?
- It's too much.
What's the matter?
(Getting to have a cozy night alone)
The "double" card that you two...
(Embarrassed) (Confused)
All day and night... All
day and night... Mm...
A cozy night?
Didn't expect to come in and find this.
I didn't expect it to
convey like that at all.
That sentence...
Right now I'm so surprised I can't speak.
A cozy night?
Cozy.
Let me sit.
As soon as we walked in,
we found a note on the table.
The two of you will be
doubly satisfied on this cozy night.
The writing was that explicit.
That sentence sounds to be very seductive.
I was like, "Is it really okay?"
I like going out to places and having fun.
But now if I can stay in,
I don't have to care
what other people think.
And there are still many things I can do.
That's why I like going on dates at home.
This house is huge.
First of all, there's another room.
- Shall we check it out?
- Where is it?
Wow.
Is this the bedroom?
(Embarrassed)
It's okay.
We won't be able to sleep.
Of course I didn't expect to sleep there.
I thought no matter what we'd go back.
I never thought we'd have the whole day
together like that, so I was shocked.
(The room both will be
enjoying their cozy night.)
- A bathroom.
- But it's kind of strange.
(Both trying to find what "double" means again)
But if you think about it, why is this place...
There are two bathrooms here.
So maybe another pair is coming here.
But it says, "Just you
two will be staying here."
What should I do now?
Oh, there's a projector.
What else?
This looks fun.
(Love Test)
- What book is this?
- If assuming that we.
(Getting to know each other) If we
do this all day, we won't get any sleep.
(through the first couple test)
The only thing we can do. - Yes.
Okay.
Because we're not dating yet,
I hope we won't find difficult questions.
(How much skinship do you allow?)
Skinship.
Wait a sec. A question like this...
(Embarrassed)
I'm gonna write it down.
Just answer based on our own standards.
I should do that, right?
My hand's shaking so much I can't write.
(A love test that seems to shake them)
(The most nervous moment,
equal to their first date)
What did you write? I
wrote down everything.
(Hahahaha)
- Damn it.
- What?
- You're brave.
- Am I being too forward?
Everything.
Everything I want.
(Bang)
Oh, it's so funny.
Damn it, this is so embarrassing.
It's suddenly hot.
I felt embarrassed even though
there was nothing embarrassing.
The whole time.
"This is when I'm excited about you."
Mm...
What is there to not feel excited about?
I know.
(Both thinking of the moment
they were excited about the other person)
- You're done.
- Mm.
When you don't confuse me.
"Just don't confuse me."
She writing that made me feel very good.
I was thankful she wrote that.
You're very beautiful
every time I see you in the morning.
When you almost touched me,
you were clearly flirting with me.
Yes, I was.
Oh, really?
Oh, now what?
I was flirting.
How did you not know?
I'm a reserved woman.
Oh.
So what else?
- Let's do this one.
- What?
"How do you help relieve
your girlfriend's stress?"
Comfort her and tell her to meet up.
Comfort her and set up a meet.
We're similar.
We have to meet whenever
one of us is stressed.
- Yes, when stressed.
- When stressed, it's best to meet up.
Exactly. If I see my girlfriend's face,
my stress will be gone.
I get to comfort her too.
(Two people trying to find common ground)
Right. What if you're stressed
because of your girlfriend?
Like about what?
If I...
If I told you a big lie
while I'm out and having fun.
- I'd probably be pissed.
- Yeah. Would you go out and find me?
- I wouldn't.
- What would you do?
- Just acknowledge you were out.
- Would you sulk?
If you're out, I'd just go to sleep.
Just sleep. You wouldn't do anything?
When I wake up the next day,
once she's sober, I'd bring it up.
It's pointless to talk while she's drunk.
Drop the bomb when she's awake and sober.
But lying is what I hate the most.
- Lying?
- Mm.
If that happens to you, what would you do?
I'd probably go there first.
- Really? You'd follow her there?
- Yes.
- I'd go to the end of the earth...
- So scary.
I'd follow her as far as I could.
Then I'd probably get her home.
Oh, really?
After that, I'd wait for the next day
for her to be sober as well.
"Were you crazy yesterday?"
There are only three chances.
I'd casually say, "I'm not going."
You'd say, "I'm going there right now."
Because I'd had some questions
I'd wanted answered from the beginning,
so I had time to get to know Dagyo better.
But after the show,
if we get a chance to date each other,
it would be nice if we could add to
what we lack and exchange those things.
Okay.
If we get to date. If you choose me.
Whatever happens next
from now until the end of the show.
Don't think I'm a sure thing.
I'm not thinking that.
Are you thinking that
because I called you yesterday?
- I don't know.
- Where are you going?
- Gonna find food?
- Yes.
(Both getting closer in their
private space) But where?
Losers! Come eat!
- Don't call us that.
- I'm a loser too.
Ah...
Done.
Should I eat this pork belly?
Yeah, that's what I'm eating.
Shall I grill it?
- Yeah? You're probably better at it.
- No tongs.
- You're a good griller.
- Use these instead.
First of all, I'm glad
everyone's comfortable with me.
Right now peace of mind is the best thing.
And yesterday Ms. Minwoo showed
how determined she was.
That was really cool and attractive.
Today I'm gonna try talking to her.
I can do that because
there are people around.
I want to create
the feeling of being taken care of
when I'm with Ms. Heeyoung.
The two of us enjoy being alone.
I'm someone who creates
an indirect comfortable vibe.
I'm not someone
who would make an effort to go out.
So I think staying in is good.
I think the person who's
practiced the most is Seoyeon.
Yes.
But despite having some practice,
I listen to other people.
And I've been very
surprised by what others do.
Those people usually think very deeply,
so I often get it wrong.
I somewhat understand their actions...
(Teasing)
Then I resolve things I got wrong.
So it's a very meaningful moment.
So you're often the one who gets it wrong.
You always say that you can't adapt.
Why do you agree?
Why do you always act older?
Because you still look very young.
Yes, yes.
I almost forgot, then I remembered.
Why do you keep forgetting?
Because you don't care.
That's not true.
- You don't care about me.
- Not true.
(Uncomfortable)
(Even when we all eat together)
(Subtly putting the vegetables close by)
(Carelessly taking care of Heeyoung
but still getting her meat)
Thanks.
Honestly,
Because she has short arms. Hard to reach.
So I helped her.
(Embarrassed)
Actually, there's a reason
I wear an open-shoulder top today.
Because she has a moon tattoo
on her shoulder too.
I wanted her to see mine.
As for the moon tattoo,
I don't think someone like Ms. Heeyoung
would get a meaningless tattoo.
So I wanted to show my tattoo.
I wanted to create the
feeling of connection
through the same big picture
and let her absorb it organically.
(Minwoo comes for the second time
and prepares to go outside.)
Ms. Heeyoung, let's talk outside.
- Be right back.
- What's going on?
- I'm gonna go talk.
- You said you were gonna make kimchi stew.
- She'll come back and make it.
- Yeah, go.
It's cold outside.
I think Ms. Heeyoung's
aware that I like her.
I wanted to know what she thought about
the fact that I had feelings for her.
And I wanted to know
what'd exactly happened with Ms. Jinah.
I already heard it from Ms. Jinah,
so I went to Ms. Heeyoung.
And I wanted to hear the rough story.
Because there's not much time left,
so I want to open up in the last stretch.
But I feel that...
I don't want to be a burden.
What are you talking about?
It will help me get a
really good night sleep.
Well, I have some questions.
I wanna talk about what happened back then.
Of course.
"Since I'm here, I have to do this once."
That was my thinking.
I liked that she was brave enough
to invite me for a walk.
However,
I was hoping to see
the other side of Ms. Minwoo.
To see if I could see it now or not?
(Minwoo prepared a warm tea for Heeyoung)
Here you go.
Thanks.
- Huh.
- What is this?
(Slurping)
(Mm)
- Is it good?
- Yeah.
(Peeking)
(Hahahaha)
I don't know what it is.
I don't know what it is, but it's good.
It's so obvious on your face.
I'm not a good liar.
I just haven't had a chance to speak.
You're right.
To tell you the truth,
I don't want to ask how you feel
or anything like that.
Because I'm not the kind to pry.
But what I want to know right now.
What happened with Ms. Jinah?
And would you mind telling me
what the most important reason was?
(Nodding)
And I'm curious if you like or dislike her.
Mm.
Ms. Jinah and I
talked a lot about marriage...
and our future seriously.
That's crucial to me.
I just wanted to know,
"What are you thinking?"
But that was our first date.
And I felt that our timing wasn't right.
I think that actions
matter more than words.
Others told me differently.
They kept not choosing me.
Different from what she said,
but they said they liked me.
I became the second choice by default.
It's not that I like this person that much
or anything like that.
That's why I came here.
I was shocked and surprised
to hear it with my own ears.
It was very unexpected.
It's just difference of opinions.
We don't have the same intention.
We're a little different personality-wise.
So you ended up sharing
a room with Ms. Seoyeon.
I think Ms. Seoyeon is interested in you.
Not me.
Because I don't think
you would call someone
just to give emotional support.
I knew my sexual orientation pretty late,
when I was a senior in high school.
But I was also a senior.
We've lived very different lives.
But I felt uncomfortable
and went through some difficult times.
But I never had that
experience with anyone.
I just wanted to give support
when she said she'd
just discovered herself.
That was the biggest reason.
Of course, at the time I
was extremely worried.
I was grateful she'd been
caring for me and talking to me.
I was thankful from the bottom of my heart.
I think it was very different
from making a phone call.
That's why I like you.
You're not the type to text
just to say thanks or apologize.
I don't do that.
I think it's fortunate.
If you were the type to
send thank you messages,
I would have been even more confused.
I see. That's your thinking.
That's good.
I feel like you're helping
me figure this out.
I'm actually not one
to understand other people's feelings.
So I'm not good at empathizing.
But for the people I like,
I tend to empathize with them.
I want to know and understand first
what their intention is
for saying certain things.
What they feel calling up someone.
And how they feel about me.
What they like or hate.
We probably wouldn't get to talk.
What do you want to know about me?
I always wanted to know you.
Thank you.
So...
(Teary)
Hm?
Feels like there's something in my eyes.
- Are you okay?
- Me? Yeah.
- What's wrong?
- Me?
I usually don't show it.
If we weren't opening up like this.
I'll probably feel this way
on the last day of selection.
That my efforts have been in vain.
That's about it.
When I wasn't aware...
Come to think of it.
- The invisible efforts...
- The view is so beautiful.
- To make me feel comfortable.
- Yeah.
But I really don't know
if you're the only one
who thinks like this.
I think there are a lot of people
like me in this world.
If you say nothing,
almost no one will know.
Because it's not easy
to speak out and express yourself.
- I wouldn't know if you didn't tell me.
- You really wouldn't.
That's why I gathered the courage to speak.
I really didn't know. I found out just now.
Previously, she showed her interest
in a subtle way or straightforward.
Did her actions at the time
"give me some assurance?"
I really got that feeling from her.
But when she expressed herself
in a serious conversation,
I felt really grateful.
And I thought, "So people like this exist."
And I felt much better
than I had felt before.
I think once we're closer,
opening up is just a cute way to complain.
When I talked about that,
she looked so surprised her eyes widened.
So I thought of
"the best aspect of Ms. Heeyoung."
Like, "She may be a softie."
(Heeyoung and Minwoo
are one step closer to mutual sincerity.)
Feels so good right now
because it's very warm.
You prefer summer or winter?
- Summer.
- Summer?
- I don't like winter.
- I loathe the winter.
(Relaxing during their at-home date)
I probably wear each one just once.
Because you hate it.
(Surprised)
Mm. Wait.
(The bell suddenly rings)
What's that?
(Surprised) (Surprised)
Wait. - What's that?
It comes from there.
- Who's there?
(Mirang walking to the door carefully)
Eh? Who is it?
Who are you?
- Hello.
Hello.
- Oh, hello.
- No one held the door for me.
I have lot of things.
- Hello.
Some gifts.
(Who are their unexpected guests?)
Oh, so nice.
(The couple Mimi and Vivi
making their first appearance)
(The calm and feminist Vivi
and the cheerful and lively Mimi)
(The appearance of a couple of five years
who have many followers)
I was shocked.
I really didn't expect it
that someone else would show up.
I thought, "Oh, this is why"
"it's called a double date."
What were you doing?
(Embarrassed) (Embarrassed)
Wait a minute. I had no
idea you two would come.
I had no idea.
A successful surprise.
They're very close to me.
- They're dating each other.
- Oh. I see, I see.
- We've known each other for about 10 years.
- Oh, really?
- For that long?
- Almost. We go way back.
I can't remember how we met.
I think we met through a mutual friend.
Because I had a shop,
so we saw each other a lot.
(Mirang and Mimi are acquaintances.)
Have you known each other long?
Longer than with me?
When I started dating
you, you introduced us.
I didn't know her initially.
But I went to the shop
and greeted each other.
- I just found out about this.
- But I didn't think you'd come.
- I had no idea.
- I don't think you'd come here.
I thought it'd be just us today.
- Oh, we're imposing.
- No, no.
- You're like, "Why are they here?"
- Not true.
Not at all. I'm very glad.
First of all, we have something for you.
- You read.
- What's this?
We've gotten a lot of surprises today.
"Today's date is a double date."
"You will enjoy this double date
with the couple Mimi and Vivi."
- I told you.
- That's why you brought a lot of stuff.
"Why is this house huge?"
- They have better reactions than I thought.
- So nice.
(Happy)
So let's see what we can cook.
- Let's see and cook together.
- I want to know.
You said you were a good cook.
- Oh, I'm not at all.
- You can trust Mirang.
Put on an apron first.
Do we have to wear one too?
- No, no.
- Yes.
We have to cook together.
(Let's go)
Looks like everyone has to wear one.
- Turn around. I'll tie it for you.
- Okay.
- Is this okay?
- Yeah.
Perfect.
(Putting on aprons for each other)
I'm fine.
Please tie it for me.
And do it like this.
(A double date with two couples
who are expecting sweetness)
This is what we brought.
First of all,
(Curious)
what's all this?
I'll unload everything first.
Please help unload it on the side.
Don't just watch.
It was out of reach.
Don't scare her.
Get it out gently.
There are steaks and pasta in tomato sauce.
- And canapés.
- Canapés.
- So you make something simple like canapés.
- You got it.
Please tell me how to make it.
Cooking does sound fun.
- Yeah.
- Right?
Yes, I was thinking of making dinner today.
I planned to eat dinner here.
Oh, you're right.
So do the two of you cook at home a lot?
We almost always cook at home.
I do most of the cooking.
She barely cooks.
Not that I can't. I'm just not good at it.
(Ah-ha)
I wash the dishes and clean the kitchen.
But I think that's important.
So I have to do that.
Are you moving in with me?
No, no.
I got you. Are you moving in with me?
Figure of speech.
Now add mayonnaise.
And add cream cheese.
Then plate them in a heart shape.
Okay?
(Mimi kindly shows them)
Do it together.
(how to make canapés)
Okay.
How many should we make?
- Let's make a lot.
- A lot?
A lot.
- How many?
- We'll probably eat a lot today.
You usually eat a lot.
What do you mean?
This looks very strange.
(All over the dish)
You're probably hungry.
- Mirang said to make a lot.
- What do you mean?
- "Let's make a lot"?
- Mirang said
- to make "a lot."
- What do you mean?
(Acting oblivious)
It's because you eat a lot.
Can I eat this?
She just sneaked one.
Butter. Is this butter?
Oh, this is a margarine, not butter.
Not bad at all with the onions.
Put the onions on it?
- Just one.
- Yeah, you eat it.
I made it for you.
No, I'll pass.
- Don't you trust me?
- It's not that. I can eat onions.
Try the one with onions.
It's really good. Try just one bite.
Good, right? Not bad at all.
(Indifferent)
Failed.
- I failed, right?
- Usually,
I don't like raw onions.
Why didn't you tell me? Why?
You should have told me.
I ate it because you made it.
Eat this then.
Honestly, I hated that piece of onion.
If it were someone else,
I would have said no.
But what did you say you didn't eat?
Caught red-handed.
We should keep it a secret.
- You're slacking off and sneaking food?
- We just tried some.
Please us cook first.
Because you asked me to eat with you.
Spit it out. Try again.
We're almost done.
The canapés look so good. Great job.
This is almost like a housewarming party.
(Looks very yummy)
Not finished yet, right?
We have to add chicken
stock. Won't take long.
- What's that?
- Season it with chicken stock.
Add chicken stock.
What's that?
(Looks like she does a lot.)
(Mimi's a skilled cook.)
We usually add it.
Try it.
(Vivi's in charge of tasting.)
It's a little too bland.
Try it and let me
know. I'll make this dish.
A little bland? Then
add more chicken stock.
(Both have clear duties.
(They really are a couple of five years.)
Try this.
Thanks.
Let's cut it and put it in.
(Two couples who cook and feed each other)
Dagyo said she wasn't a good cook.
And I'm not good at cooking western food.
But Mimi and Vivi came
and showed us how to cook.
I wanted to see Dagyo's food once.
I'm glad I got to see it this time.
It's really good.
It was funny that she ate so much.
Even while cooking,
she kept putting something in her mouth.
Even though her doing that
was funny, it was cute too.
Because she took really good care of me.
It was very memorable.
(Because they cook together,
the food is doubly delicious.)
- Looks delicious. I'm so hungry.
- Great job, everyone.
(The double date's home-cooked dinner)
Should we light the
candle on the cake and eat?
Wow, what is this?
We prepared this to
celebrate the double date.
And this is our 2,000-day anniversary.
Today is our 2,000-day anniversary.
- Today?
- It's today.
Today is a really good day.
(Surprised)
So let's celebrate together.
(The double-date commemorating cake)
Now let's all make a wish.
Yay, congrats. So let's start.
- Should we sing?
- Happy the 2,000-day anniversary.
Thank you.
I wished to be able to face Mirang
even if we break up.
That was my thinking.
I wished to get another date with Dagyo.
May this wish come true.
(The girls making wishes
while pressing hands together)
One, two, three.
- Yay!
- Congratulations!
Let's eat.
Let's clink glasses first.
- Cheers.
One shot.
Oh, the wine tastes good.
- Bon appétit.
Eat this.
(Giving food to each other)
- So much food.
- This one is good.
Would be even better with wasabi.
So much food.
Very delicious.
But how did you two end up here together?
Yesterday...
I got a phone call privilege.
- Oh, to call the person you wanted to talk to?
- Yes.
So only those who called
each other came here.
Yes.
Because there were "single" and "double."
"Double" probably had an edge,
so I picked "double."
Is Ms. Mirang your type, Ms. Dagyo?
What do you think?
I'm curious too.
My type?
Her ears just pricked up.
- She's probably curious.
- When curious, her ears will prick like now.
She is.
Her overall image matches my type.
So she's your type.
You're talking about appearance,
or personality too?
Her appearance matches my type exactly.
As for her thoughts, I want
her to show them more.
Something like that.
Did you want her to be make clearer
gestures since the first time you met?
I didn't initially care about Vivi.
But did Mirang showed
some signs of interest?
Honestly, since we got there,
this is the first time this has happened.
But she could be a womanizer
or just a nice person.
(Agreed)
Women can't separate these two types.
You don't know if she's nice to everyone
or just to you because you guys just met.
So I feel maybe it's all in my head.
So when we had our first date,
- I asked her everything that day.
- What did she say?
- I just asked...
- "You're interested?"
Were those gestures flirting?
- She said, "Yes."
- Wow, that's a very brave question.
If she said no...
- No.
- It'd probably end that day.
You must like her at first sight.
Honestly, there are very few people
I like at first sight.
But her appearance really got me.
She was the one on my
mind all night that night.
- Cheers.
The wine is very good.
You guys are living together, right?
We live together.
And we've now been
dating for about five years.
But we've never separated even one day.
Every day since the day we started dating.
- Hasn't been a day we're not together.
- It's true.
It's true. She's always been with me.
I've been by her side.
No matter where I
go, I'll take her with me.
- We're attached at the hip, right?
- Mm.
- How is that possible?
- When you're on a date,
is there something that
you don't want to do?
Like your expectations.
- I want to do everything.
- Still want to do it all.
Everything is perfect.
Do you guys think about that stuff?
Like getting married.
Or do want to wear a wedding dress?
I want to have a wedding
and wear a wedding dress.
And do you want to invite everyone?
Or just a small wedding?
- Everyone, but won't be that many.
- And all the reporters?
Reporters?
- I'm tired just thinking about that.
- Won't work.
Because the reporters will be there.
If I can, I will have a wedding.
I want to get married.
You would have to invite your parents.
Parents? Of course
we have to invite our parents.
Because older close friends
around me are getting married.
They say they won't invite their parents.
They will invite only their friends.
There are many cases like that.
Their parents probably won't come.
But it would be great to let them know.
- And will they come?
- If they're told, they'll definitely come.
I don't know. They may not come.
- But you think about marriage.
- Yes.
I have so many friends who say
they don't think about marriage.
What's the point of getting married?
Because it's not legal yet
and it's not legally binding.
But this is totally different.
Opposite-sex couples
have clear goals in marriage
and having children.
And there's a link between them
through a legally binding document.
It lasts a lifetime. But
we don't have that right.
- That's the biggest problem.
- Yes.
But the way I see it,
this is not ideal,
but we must keep trying.
Because without this thing,
it's harder to live as a couple.
I'm trying to take care of myself too.
You're doing that?
(Hahaha)
Is it lacking?
You're right.
We come to Jeju Island
about half a year ago.
Or was it one year ago?
And we took wedding photos.
(Wedding photos?)
This is our third time on Jeju Island.
We took pictures wearing
evening gowns by the sea.
I think it's the place where
brides and grooms go to take pictures.
We were the only lesbian couple.
Everyone there was staring at us.
You both were wearing the gowns?
We both were.
We had to walk down that street
for more than five minutes.
I was really embarrassed.
There were a lot of lights.
And we brought a lot of props.
Even a bed.
It was perfect.
Shockingly perfect.
While we were shooting,
cameras were following us.
And another camera.
I asked, "Why are the
cameras following us?"
Despite many couples there,
we were the only lesbian couple.
And people kept looking at us.
We couldn't flee either.
(Both still being watched) And some
wanted to take pictures close to us.
I actually liked it
but her face was so red
like it was gonna exploded.
In other countries,
they don't care about that at all.
Mm, exactly.
Then we were walking together,
holding hands,
and we sang together.
(Singing while shooting to relax)
Trying to act natural.
T's here, so it's not allowed here.
- Did I sing?
- I sang something like, "Tan-tan-tan."
At the time it felt
a bit like a responsibility.
People were looking
but pretending not to see anything.
At the time we pretended
there were just the two of us.
That moment is very meaningful to us.
A lot of memories.
That's why Jeju Island
is a very meaningful place for us.
If everything goes well,
this place will become very meaningful.
Like with us.
I really want that moment.
The moment to hear
that kind of story from someone.
So I could get answers
about things I'm curious about.
It's great to learn about these things
while getting to know someone.
They told us how they dated
and how they overcame various issues.
And they helped us cook dinner
and prepare a place like that.
I'm 100% satisfied with the double date.
Shall we cook?
What are you doing?
- Cooking.
- Where's Dagyo?
- She's on a date.
- They're not back yet?
Let's cook together.
Today's menu:
pork kimchi stew,
grilled fish and rolled omelet.
Today I was assigned to cook with Dagyo,
so I didn't feel too good about the date.
But I probably expected too much.
Because it would be the first time I got to
do something one-on-one
with someone I liked.
That's why I...
feel strange in the way I can't explain.
(Hangyeol just returned from the date.)
- Oh, you're back.
- Hello.
How was it?
Hello.
- Your hair's still pretty.
- Hello, all the princesses.
- It's very cold.
- Is it very cold outside?
- Yes.
- You must be tired.
How was the date today?
Okay?
No complaints. It was fun.
That's good.
We come back from our date
and other people in the
house ruined my mood.
I wanted her to come to my place,
but I was terrified
of running into Ms. Riwon
because I went on a date
with someone both of us chose.
"Why did I have to be so careful?"
Honestly, I'm scared.
It was practically the first time
we went out to talk.
So I wanted to talk more
on a walk after dinner.
- Wow.
- What?
Awesome.
"The two of you who chose
the keyword 'double' today..."
(your date will be twice longer.)
(You will have a cozy overnight stay.)
Twice longer.
(The rest will have dinner at
the guest house.) Oh, wonderful.
"Double" must be good then.
Double is always good.
Wow.
The rice is all mushy.
I'm low-spirited again.
Although both of us are already roommates,
but there's a phrase "overnight stay."
They're on a trip for
two days and one night
in an unfamiliar setting.
I really don't want to imagine it.
Yes, I really don't want to imagine it.
(The two of you who chose the keyword "double"
today, your date will be twice longer.)
(You will have a cozy overnight stay.)
Oh, now I'm mad.
(The rest will have dinner at
the guest house.) What is this?
(Shocked)
Wow, damn it.
I'm speechless.
We're alone here too.
- This is basically a matrimonial home.
- We... Sorry. We have to stay here alone.
- Eh?
- We have to stay here alone.
They probably go out to eat
and have a well-rested night.
- Eh? So they're sleeping somewhere else?
- Yeah.
- Look.
- Wait.
"You will stay at another place alone"
"and spend cozy time together."
"The rest of you..."
So we'll have dinner over there
- and eat together.
- We'll...
We'll do that and we'll sleep here
on our own tonight.
- I see.
- So we'll be alone here.
Unbelievable.
- Oi, how could they?
- I'm so mad.
Honestly, I thought we'd be going out.
An overnight stay is crazy.
- Hi.
- You're back.
- What's for dinner?
- You're back?
Yeah.
Kimchi stew.
- You're back.
- I'm back.
Wow.
Such a big pot.
(Pork collar kimchi stew)
It's pork kimchi stew.
(and grilled hairtail)
Smells great. - I did my best.
(Butter omelet and a
dessert made by Seoyeon)
Let's eat.
Bon appétit.
(Minwoo gives Heeyoung the fish first.)
Eat this.
You gave that piece to Heeyoung?
Why?
I can't see it.
Because she can't reach it.
Thank you.
I can't see it.
(Riwon gives Hangyeol the deboned fish.)
Oh, I already got mine.
- Here.
- Then give me a little.
These are clean chopsticks.
Thank you.
My God.
The kimchi stew is so good.
Delicious.
Very good. Great job.
- Is it good?
- Mm.
Mirang and Dagyo are staying
somewhere else tonight?
I guess so.
While we were eating,
I thought a lot about Mirang and Dagyo
and I was in so much pain.
What did "single" do on the date?
Single.
We went to a cafe. An LP cafe.
- LP cafe?
- LP cafe.
Do you want more hairtail?
Have a bit more.
I must look like a pig.
You don't. You're growing.
You're growing.
Because you're growing emotionally.
You need energy.
There are some growing pains.
Ms. Riwon takes care of
Ms. Hangyeol like a baby bird.
She kept giving her food
and deboned fish for her
while taking care of other things.
I was so unsatisfied with myself.
For not being brave
enough to show my feelings.
I'm someone who's very
confident, clear, brave and honest
in terms of what I'm interested in,
what I feel good about,
what I like and love.
But I'm getting smaller and smaller here.
It's been...
a very difficult time for me.
(It's a painful dinner due to
their feelings for each other.)
What should I do if I really can't do it?
I will ask people around me
and definitely introduce myself.
Really.
Do you like foreigners?
There are many good-looking ones.
Well, do you like Koreans?
For my first time, I'd like a Korean.
- So cute.
- So Asians in general.
My first... My first time...
Oh, it's so crazy.
- But it's true.
- Really unexpected.
This is really unexpected.
Aww, don't cry.
- So cute.
- How should I comfort you?
What should I do?
(Time to comfort Seoyeon)