BLOOD FREE
"What kind of meat would you like?"
I asked you all this question
just four years ago.
"What kind of meat would you like?"
But I don't need to ask you this anymore.
Because BF successfully commercialized
cultured meat for the first time
in 2022.
Consumers worldwide showed
an overwhelming preference for our meat.
And that was our solution.
But I did ask a similar question.
About what kinds of clothes you preferred.
Killing. Slaughtering.
"Is there no way to enjoy meat
without sacrificing animals?"
BF SUCCEEDS AT CULTURING FUR
Fifteen years ago,
BF was founded
on the basis of this question.
And thanks to you, we were able to achieve
a phenomenal market share of 72%.
We can now confidently say
that what we put on our tables
is more transparent and safe than ever.
Meat that requires slaughter
is in the past now.
This is a remarkable achievement
made by you and BF,
a biotechnology company.
BF 2025 UNPACKED SHOW
Ladies and gentlemen.
Let me introduce the individual
who achieved the impossible.
Ms. Yun Jayu, the CEO of BF.
Hello, I'm Yun Jayu.
First, I'd like to thank you all
for attending
BF's new product presentation
on Christmas Eve.
How are you all doing?
Last year, a news channel picked me
as the greediest woman on earth.
It's okay.
You can agree with them.
It's true that I'm greedy.
I'm never satisfied.
Did you know?
Cell culture requires only 1% of the land
originally needed
to raise and feed livestock
to produce the same amount of food.
You already knew this?
Then what about this?
Did you know that one cow
produces more greenhouse gas
than a car does?
Why would I mention something
you already know?
KIM SINGU
BF RESEARCH TEAM 3 LEADER
Because I wanted to brag.
I'm extremely proud that BF contributes…
SEO HUI
…to the prevention of global warming.
But we're not perfect just yet.
"BF."
"Blood Free."
Some people pronounce it as "beef."
Well, it does befit a company
that produces meat.
However,
perhaps it is time
to change our company name.
We have expanded our territory
to include underwater production.
We refuse to be complacent
and only culture what's on land.
Ladies and gentlemen.
We'd like to introduce
our new masterpiece for the end of 2025.
How does our new product taste?
All of these dishes were cultured?
That's correct.
Not only did BF succeed
in culturing livestock,
but we also succeeded in culturing
the four most consumed seafood items,
tuna, salmon, mackerel, and shrimp.
All the fish in the ocean are dead.
I can't catch a single one.
Oh, no.
JEONG HAEDEUN - BF
LEGAL ADVISER, PLANNING DIRECTOR
I need to tell you something.
Our seafood doesn't include three things.
Parasites, microplastics, and mercury.
Not only are our products blood free,
but they're danger free as well.
Enjoy, everyone.
We can produce an unlimited amount.
I have a dream.
There's something I need to achieve.
The very day when we don't need to destroy
this world for food.
My company and I will bring
that day closer.
I promise you all.
In six months' time,
we will succeed in culturing
all types of grain and food crops
such as rice and potatoes,
and even palm oil, which destroys jungles.
We will succeed in culturing them.
I give you my word.
In six months,
I will see you all again right here.
Please welcome
Professor Kim Singu from BF Laboratory.
Hello.
I'm Kim Singu
from BF Laboratory.
I'll take a peek at this
only when I'm stuck.
I will be
retiring soon.
As a doctor of biotechnology…
They've already surrounded
the entire building.
We demand an apology from Yun Jayu,
a murderer!
The government should actively support BF!
Support them!
Yun Jayu is innocent!
- We support her!
Yun Jayu is…
Yun Jayu is innocent!
-We support her!
The government
-should actively support BF!
-Support them!
The government should actively support BF!
A GLOBAL COMPANY FOR A REASON!
MURDERERS, BF
BF CARES ABOUT
OUR CHILDREN'S FUTURE
YOU DON'T HAVE TO WEAR
ANIMAL FUR ANYMORE
A COMPANY THAT SAVES THE EARTH
BLOOD FREE
This was the only route
to the highway, but there's a traffic jam.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
What did you say?
This was the only route to the highway,
but there's a traffic jam.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Well, it's the end of the year.
Ms. Yun.
The door is stuck!
-One, two, three!
Move!
Don't touch her!
You could injure her spine.
You have to wait for the ambulance.
Hang in there for a bit, Ms. Yun.
Who are you? Do you know him?
No.
Is he alive?
Yes, until a while ago.
As of now…
I'm not too sure.
-Enjoy your Christmas.
-You too, sir.
Did they identify him?
He was a stockbreeder in his 50s
who went bankrupt because of BF.
He was spotted on CCTV
hanging around the overpass
for an hour and a half.
I believe Ms. Yun was his target.
He died in the ambulance.
How did he know she'd be there?
BF asked the detective in charge
the same question.
The detective said
that was the only road
leading out from BF's venue.
Plus, traffic jams are common there.
He said it would've been the ideal spot
to jump and land on a vehicle.
How's Ms. Yun?
Thankfully, she only got a few bruises.
Gosh.
Schedule a visit to the funeral home
and send some flowers under my name.
-To the other side too.
-"The other side"?
-Ms. Yun.
-Yes, sir.
Do you have to watch that?
He waited for the best moment
to break your neck.
Ms. Jeong went to the police
to ask about the deceased.
ON SAN - RESEARCH DIRECTOR
& TEAM 2 LEADER
Whether it really was suicide
or something else,
we'll have to see.
Is the cause of death ruptured organs?
That's what they said.
Ruptured organs.
What a shame.
Had he fallen right on top of you,
you would've gotten ruptured.
Don't you think so?
He must've failed
to correctly calculate his fall.
I heard he went through a lot.
Even his final moments
didn't go as planned.
Who is he?
Beats me.
Can you not make me watch that?
I brought some clothes.
Don't tell me you're working right now.
What did the police say?
I asked them to look into things
such as the possibility
of him being incited to do this,
his call records,
how many times he had visited the spot,
and whether he was alone or not.
But the police want
to speak with our bodyguards.
What for?
What if the bodyguards
leaked the route
Ms. Yun was planning to take today?
I'm sorry, ma'am.
This was the only route to the highway,
but there's a traffic jam.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Only the driver would've known
the exact route she'd take.
I always felt uneasy about that.
Should we get a full-time bodyguard?
That could be even more dangerous.
She doesn't like
being escorted all the time.
We should be thorough
and find someone who best suits the job.
We can't always hire private security.
You think so?
To be honest, it has been a nuisance
to contact new services every time--
Actually, no.
Um, we just don't know whom we're hiring.
Did they hear us?
Gosh.
Check out these flowers.
Guess who sent them?
"Wishing you a speedy recovery.
Prime Minister Seonu Jae."
Who is he?
He said
he was just passing by.
- Do you know him?
- No.
Is he alive?
Yes, until a while ago.
A passerby who's willing to intervene?
And touch a bloodied man?
I don't think I could ever do that.
He did seem like a paramedic.
I think I've seen him somewhere.
I was so out of it during the incident.
Where in the world did I see him?
I'm curious about that too.
He just happened to pass by.
He just happened to be a paramedic.
And you recognize him.
What's the chance of that, Ms. Jeong?
I'll make sure I remember
where I saw him, ma'am.
Mansik.
CONTROVERSY BEHIND BF'S CULTURE
FLUID BEING FULL OF GERMS
CURRENT NEWS HEADLINES
BF'S CULTURE FLUID CONTROVERSY
30 MINUTES AGO
Hello, Ms. Hong.
TEAM LEADER OF RESEARCH TEAM 3
KIM SINGU
Don't worry about it.
I can do it by myself just fine.
I'm sorry. I should be helping you.
Ms. Yun is at the hospital,
and I'm still home.
Please put aside
the things you need to move.
I'll move them later.
All right then.
What?
What's the matter?
What is this?
Professor Kim,
all the files have been encrypted.
I think the computer got hacked.
They told us to follow the directions
to decrypt the files.
So I opened the description file.
And I got this.
They want 80 billion won in Bitcoin
within the next 48 hours.
Only then will they unlock
our lab's computers
and files.
CitizenX is a ransomware organization.
They target companies
and government agencies,
then render their files inaccessible.
No one, to this day,
has successfully decrypted any files.
We got hacked?
How?
One of our security staff
is coming from home.
We'll have to ask him.
Is only our lab hacked?
How about HQ or the Seoul branch?
They're both unscathed. It's only our lab.
Are the hackers behind the article
claiming how our culture fluid
was full of germs?
I just arrived at the newspaper agency.
I'll ask them
where they got that information
and report to you right away.
What we know so far is that
there's been an anonymous tip
about how our research has been illegal
and how the culture fluid
for the cultured meat was full of germs.
That is all.
I'm on my way,
but the traffic is terrible.
Everyone must be going somewhere.
I'll be there soon. I'm hanging up.
Me too.
Me too. Goodbye.
How does this make any sense?
I can't open the files I made
on my own computer.
That's what ransomware is.
Imagine someone
changing the passcode to your house
and demanding a ransom in exchange
for the new passcode.
What about the culture fluid?
I made those serums myself.
Who in the world…
This makes no sense.
Yeongsil, look up articles about BF germs.
There are 1003 related articles.
I see.
That's a hell of a number.
If you want me to read them, please say,
"Jang Yeongsil,
read articles about BF germs."
No, it's okay. Just get lost.
Ms. Jeong,
you need to be kinder with your words.
Had we been the only ones
who received the tip-off,
we would've confirmed with you.
"Rumor has it that your research
is illegal and your culture fluid
is full of germs. Is that true?"
After all, you and I are acquaintances.
How did you know
that every news agency got this tip-off?
Because there were dozens of recipients.
They were all news agencies.
It was sent through email?
I debated deleting it
because I was worried I'd get scammed.
But it was sent to pretty much everyone
in this line of work.
I didn't want to be left out.
"Most would think culture fluid is clean
since it's fed to the meat,
but that's not true.
BF's culture fluid is full of germs.
Simply put, it's bacteria.
BF had been selling meat
that had been fed bacteria."
Is it true?
Whoever said that made a mistake.
So it's not true?
As Korea's biggest portal site,
I'm sure you could find out who sent it.
They even sent it anonymously,
but I guess they'll get caught soon.
I traced the IP address on KISA
and Googled their email address.
And?
It was in Canada,
but the address didn't exist.
As for the email address…
"Schrosky"?
That was their name?
The IP address and the name…
directed me to this.
So I opened the description file.
And I got this.
Can you forward the email to me?
So are the rumors true?
Come on. This isn't your first rodeo.
Only BF is worthy enough
to be set up every single day.
Right.
What did Ms. Yun say
about the stockbreeder's death?
Thanks for your cooperation.
Hold on.
Shouldn't she be vehemently denying
the allegations?
They're the ones behind it.
The ones who hacked our lab.
I see.
This is how they got in.
They hacked us remotely
using the router on the fourth floor.
They got in this afternoon at 4:19 p.m.
How do we send the money?
This is their account number.
They want us to send the Bitcoin
within the next 48 hours.
That's their account?
Then can't we catch them?
We can track them down.
Right? There must be a name
behind that account.
It may be a false name,
but if we keep digging--
You don't need
to verify your identity when making
a cryptocurrency account.
And it's probably not
an official exchange.
So we can't track them down.
How is this possible?
Forget about this.
Can we catch those bastards
who treated my culture fluid like trash?
Sir, they didn't say that.
They said it was full of germs!
Then the news reported that
and people believed them!
They're all the same!
I devoted my entire life to this.
They're practically bad-mouthing me.
Those bastards.
How could they only give us two days
to prepare 80 billion won?
They happened to hack us
right when we presented our new product.
Do you think they knew
we'd be at the event
and the lab would be vacant?
It only took them 20 minutes
to hack our system.
Who knew our lab was this unprotected?
We can't block the ransomware
unless we cut off
our external network entirely.
Shut down the lab for the next two days
and don't let anyone in this weekend.
You want to do this covertly?
We need to report this to catch them.
Reporting this won't guarantee
that we'll catch them though.
Ms. Yun, what's your plan?
Will you really pay the ransom?
Eighty billion won
is pretty cheap if you think about it.
Due to these allegations,
the market cap of the third market
transactions is dropping.
What do you think
you should do right away?
We need to find out if anyone used…
…the external network.
But we told the employees numerous times
to only use the company network.
Isn't it crucial to find out
if they only locked the files
or if they actually read them?
The computers contain
the core technology of our lab.
Ransomware rarely opens the files.
But we can't guarantee it.
Then we need to assess the damage
and see how much work
we can do without opening the files.
Then do that. And set up a new firewall.
Deny all allegations
and threaten to take legal action.
Request a culture fluid analysis
from food safety organizations
and report the results.
As for this hacking incident…
let's keep it among ourselves.
Sir.
Right, Ms. Yun.
It's about that man
I said looked familiar.
Chairman Park Daeseong of Sanghwa.
You had a meeting with him previously.
I saw this man when I was waiting outside.
He had been standing guard at that time.
That's why he looked familiar.
Standing guard for what?
He's Chairman Park's bodyguard.
I asked Sanghwa,
and this man no longer works there.
As in he quit?
Or got fired.
They didn't elaborate.
Well done.
I only did a simple background check.
Should I dig further?
Are you okay, ma'am?
He'd be perfect
if he wasn't fired from Sanghwa.
Perfect for what?
- Yeongsil.
- Yes?
Give me a list of all the companies
and organizations attacked by CitizenX.
There have been seven
that were attacked by CitizenX.
July of 2025.
Maypal, a pharmaceutical company.
January of 2025. Pacific Bank.
-September of 2024--
-Jang Yeongsil.
-Yes?
-Did any of them pay the ransom?
I'm sorry. There are no related articles.
Any cases in Korea?
The Naval Intelligence Command in 2022.
The navy?
Read me some related news.
I'm sorry. I can't find any.
They're all covering it up.
The Intelligence Command?
He worked at the NIC
from 2020 to February of 2023.
- Jang Yeongsil.
- Yes?
When did CitizenX attack the NIC?
It was in September of 2022.
OCTOBER 2020
NAVAL INTELLIGENCE COMMAND
"Chaewoon."
It all makes sense.
But why?
Is he a resource that I should use?
Or should I avoid him?
It's nice to meet you. Please sit down.
LEE MUNGYU
FORMER PRESIDENT
It's been years.
I should've visited you sooner.
I apologize, sir.
Don't be sorry.
You must be curious
as to why I suddenly contacted you.
I am. What is this about, sir?
Did you attend BF's presentation?
Were you the one who sent me the invite?
Yes, it was me.
You know why, right?
No, sir. I'm afraid I don't.
Captain Woo.
The reason why you accepted the invite
from someone you didn't even know.
The reason why you quit
even when Chairman Park dissuaded you.
Or, from the very start,
the reason why you decided
to work for Chairman Park.
Did you identify the terrorist?
Not yet, sir.
You asked me
when I had told those I was with
about visiting the troops.
And you said it was
seven hours prior.
I did.
Because it was the truth.
JANUARY 2024
It was normal
for me to be accompanied by CEOs
on overseas trips.
But it was a last-minute decision
to visit the dispatched troops.
So I explained to them that
I wanted to make a surprise visit
to those who were abroad.
The area was still a former battlefield
despite the war being over.
So I told them in advance.
After all,
they were all influential individuals.
I said they could wait in the plane
since I wasn't going to take long.
They were all delighted to hear this
and wanted to accompany me.
It all happened within 30 minutes.
The two ministers died,
so it couldn't have been them.
Or my attendants who retired
due to severe internal injuries.
In that case,
Chairman Lee Namjin of STL.
Park Daeseong of Sanghwa Group.
Han Giho of Tech Games.
Yun Jayu of BF.
It was one of them.
Even the dispatched troops didn't know
I was coming due to security reasons.
One of them violated the orders
to keep it top secret.
If someone was trying to kill me
in the explosion,
it was one of those four.
You thought so too.
That's why you approached Park Daeseong.
The fact that you left him
means it wasn't him.
You have changed your target.
So the next target is BF?
Thus the invite?
It was Yun Jayu. I'm sure of it.
May I ask why you think it was her?
Are you also insinuating
that I have no proof?
You wouldn't have called me if you had it.
Yet you're convinced it was her.
I'd like to be sure as well.
I want to be assured
that the person behind bars is innocent.
I want to be assured that
my time spent
after the military wasn't wasted.
Why do you think it was her?
As soon as I took office,
she requested a meeting with me.
She wanted me
to abolish the law
requiring cultured meat to be labeled
as genetically modified foods.
She said both the US and France
finally accepted cultured meat
as normal meat.
She wanted me to follow suit.
That brazen woman tried to slyly coax me
into changing the law.
And she got what she wanted.
Because I had to step down.
After losing my legs.
Do you know
how big BF got after that incident?
They grew exponentially.
Do you know how much BF
is helping the incumbent president?
I've kept an eye on you
ever since you visited me at the hospital.
From the moment you asked me
when I had told the others
about the surprise visit.
You pursued this matter
despite receiving no help.
You were tenacious despite the individuals
you were up against.
Captain Woo.
It's my time to aid you.
Let me support you.
Even if it's too late
to bring up the past incident,
I'm certain that
she's still committing illegal actions.
Find out what it is.
Then we can bring her down.
Sir.
I'm not trying to bring anyone down.
You failed to protect me.
It was your duty
to protect the head of state.
Don't make the same mistake.
That should never happen.
Go to Yun Jayu.
Become her right-hand man.
Gain her trust.
PRESIDENT LEE MUNGYU
BLUETOOTH AUDIO
Yun Jayu of BF
is currently facing a lawsuit
against USMEF…
"And NCBA, and is receiving
many death threats."
"She's building a safe house
with state-of-the-art security.
She seems to be staying
at different hotels until it's complete.
Her younger sibling succumbed
to a degenerative brain disease.
She doesn't speak to her family.
Other than those affiliated with her work,
she doesn't seem to have
any acquaintances."
Do you think he'll believe it?
He wouldn't be a soldier if he doubted me.
Obeying the commands
of one's superior at all times.
That's what a soldier does.
Hmm.
I hope he's a soldier to the bone.
"There's a rumor that On San,
the research director and alumnus
of her school,
got a divorce because of her.
If the two are indeed lovers,
he could be her only relationship in life
and weakness."
BF will be hiring a bodyguard.
I can help you get in.
How will you do that?
You think I don't have
that much power because I'm disabled?
No, sir.
I apologize.
Many filed for bankruptcy
and even committed suicide
after BF expanded.
But Yun Jayu didn't bat an eye.
She was only interested
in making even more money.
I tried to stop her.
And that's why…
she got rid of me.
Captain Woo.
Isn't it a soldier's duty
to protect the people?
Have you already forgotten
the humiliation you felt that day?
Salute!
At ease!
I will catch you
no matter what.
Hello.
This is Woo Chaewoon.
Translated by Kim Sooji