BLOOD FREE
PREVIOUSLY
Let me introduce the individual
who achieved the impossible.
Ms. Yun Jayu, the CEO of BF.
I have a dream.
I promise you all.
We will succeed in culturing all types.
We will succeed in culturing them.
Don't make the same mistake.
That should never happen.
Go to Yun Jayu.
Become her right-hand man. Gain her trust.
-What is this?
-They told us to follow the directions
to decrypt the files.
I'd like you to be someone we need.
You know CitizenX, right?
Someone is pretending to be them
to hide their identity.
-Jang Yeongsil.
-Yes, ma'am?
Search for Woo Chaewoon.
Why did you hide it from me?
I didn't see the need
to bring up the past.
I don't even know
if our reunion is favorable.
A mole shouldn't be tight-lipped.
The ransomware
could've been an inside job.
Is Professor Kim going somewhere?
Locate Kim Singu right now.
We go back 20 years. Could he have…
I kept going back over it in my head.
"Was everything he said afterwards a lie?"
I finally managed to fool her.
Ms. Yun from BF called.
She found out who was behind it.
What are your thoughts
on the rumor about you poisoning him?
Damn it.
Did you kill someone?
We're dealing
with more lunatics now.
But I don't plan to do that.
I have no intention of stopping.
I regret it. But now,
I'm going to do something about it.
I'll protect you.
I'll be by your side. Do you hear me?
Breathe. Keep breathing! You're okay!
Mr. President,
we have a bigger problem.
Activate the basement at HQ.
We're not ready for this just yet.
You were culturing human organs
in this laboratory.
On the first day we met,
I asked you not to experiment with me
as if I were cultured meat.
Don't tell me you really think
there's another terrorist at large.
You don't have the power.
There's no way you can turn the tables
regarding that case.
Then do you, sir?
Are you saying there's a spy?
I wonder who it is.
I said I couldn't stop you
from leaving.
Thank you for saving my life.
Thank you for keeping me safe.
Even a conglomerate's bodyguard like you
can't beat a stray like me.
Kim Hoseung!
Hoseung. Stay awake. Breathe.
-A scar…
-Don't talk. It's okay.
-Jang Yeongsil, call 911!
-Yes, sir.
Hoseung, wake up.
You're okay. Breathe. Hoseung!
Over here!
Stop right there!
Right there! Hey!
The culprit is still nearby.
He couldn't have gotten far!
Stay still!
Are you okay?
Yes.
We're ready to culture grain.
The issue is
if we can make a profit or not.
I just got a call from the police station.
One of our bodyguards died,
and another one was arrested
at the scene as a murder suspect.
Make sure you meet them in person.
Tell them we'll cover the cost
of his funeral and everything.
Send our sincere condolences.
Yes, ma'am.
Yun Jayu's bodyguard died.
No, not him. Someone else.
Has the Engineer called you?
He should've reported in by now.
Was it his doing? Are you positive?
What did he say?
Don't tell me you can't reach him.
Hold on.
- Find him at all costs.
-Yes, sir.
-Damn it. That bastard must've run away.
-Hey.
-I'm going to flee now.
-No.
Jayu isn't an idiot.
She'll wonder how the culprit knew
where her bodyguards would be.
It'll only be a matter of time.
Do you think
she won't be able to find you?
The Engineer disguised himself
from the get-go. But what about you?
Running away will just prove
that you tipped him off.
What if she catches me?
Deny it at all costs.
There won't be any proof
of your involvement.
All she can do is guess.
So don't run away and just deny it.
I'll find that jerk,
so stay there and keep me updated.
Yes, sir.
These bastards are all the same.
-It's my favorite restaurant.
-Yeah?
-I'm going there.
-Me too.
-Follow me.
-I doubt it'll taste good.
-It's really good.
-I agree.
-It's delicious.
-Really?
He's gone already.
What should we do?
What do you think?
Find him at all costs and bring him to me.
This is why I told you
not to hire someone from the outside.
An internal hire would've made it worse.
It can't get any worse than this.
He went into hiding. You could be
charged for conspiring with him.
So find him before the police do
before it's too late.
Why should I? This is your mess.
It's obvious what they'll say
if the culprit claims
the DORSON Group made him do it.
"This is why the prime minister
stepped up for a bodyguard's death.
He had something to do with it."
So catch him first
instead of complaining about it.
Why do you think
I helped you become prime minister?
He's skilled
at putting the blame on others.
We must find him
before he's caught and questioned.
You need to find him first.
Are you listening?
I am. I'm hanging up.
That's no way to talk to your father.
How am I supposed to find him quickly
if you won't stop talking?
As if I talked more than he did.
Call the chief of police.
Yes, sir.
Hello, sir.
You see…
…I just heard some bad news.
I heard there was another casualty at BF.
Was the gang behind it?
Do I have to make another public apology?
Hold on.
This means your men were after
someone else when they lost the culprit.
Why are you so incompetent?
How could a single man
fling three police officers in the air?
Who was he?
He had superhuman strength.
He was unbelievably strong.
He was dangerous,
so we had no choice but to arrest him.
Superhuman strength.
Unbelievably strong.
Ms. Yun.
You're making
all my childhood dreams come true.
BLOOD FREE
Why did she have to send me here?
Good night.
I'm okay. This is nothing.
I scanned the entire house once more.
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
That damn bastard.
Why did he have to kill an innocent man?
EPISODE 7
God, this is annoying.
-Who is it?
-Hello, I--
Is this Mr. Kim Hoseung's house?
He's not here right now.
I'm his coworker.
Can we talk?
There's something I need to tell you.
Do I have to open the door?
What the hell is he saying?
My name is Jeong Haedeun.
What's your relation to Mr. Kim?
He's my parents' son.
-Sorry?
-He's my older brother.
It wasn't then.
Everyone had left by then.
Who overheard us?
Who knew we were headed
to the welfare center?
Let's go now
since Ms. Yun isn't going out.
Ma'am. Ms. Jeong said
-I could go to the police station today.
-Excuse me.
Sir. Excuse me.
He injured one of our men
and caused a scene
before getting arrested.
I cleared your murder charges.
I'm sorry.
As for Mr. Kim, there was nothing…
we could do.
I shouldn't have sent you.
I should've ignored it.
Can I get out of here?
You didn't murder anyone,
but you assaulted the police.
What happened?
Why did you assault the officers?
They said you flung their men.
I don't know what happened.
My body suddenly felt hot…
in that moment.
I'm not sure.
Do you mean your arm?
I think so.
Get a checkup
as soon as you get out of here.
After catching that bastard.
Right.
But we need to sort something out first.
How did he know?
He could've approached
Professor Kim,
disguised as a cancer group member.
He would've given a fake address too.
But why was he there today
when he doesn't even live there?
He knew we'd be there.
Did anyone else know
you were going to the welfare center?
No, I only told Mr. Kim.
Hey, do you want to come with me
to the welfare center?
It was just us two.
No one could've heard us.
Then was it one of my people?
Hong Saeip? Seo Hui?
Saeip knew
about Professor Kim's cancer group.
Ms. Yun said that?
Mr. Seo gave me the address
to the welfare center.
Saeip wouldn't have told me
about the group
if she were the spy.
And she wouldn't have drowned.
That leaves one person.
If Hoseung didn't tell anyone,
then it was Hui.
Do you think he hired the killer?
The killer called himself a stray.
Did you speak with him?
I heard him from afar.
By "stray," he must've meant he was hired.
He didn't attack Kim Singu or BF
due to personal reasons.
Let me know if you need anything.
Ms. Yun.
We wouldn't have found out about this mole
without Hoseung's sacrifice.
And this just proves
that Kim Singu could've been murdered.
Is that supposed to comfort me?
Because we got something out of it?
Even so,
do you regret sending us there
and not sweeping this
under the rug?
We must hunt down the traitor.
I shouldn't have sent you.
I should've gone instead.
I need to tell you something once I'm out.
You're giving me a heads-up.
You were shot once,
and you lost your colleague today.
You don't think
you can continue working for me.
Is that it?
In conclusion, I guess you could say that.
I'm sorry.
I failed to protect you.
Even now.
Wait.
It won't take long. Please.
Hey, are they done?
Yes, they are.
Okay. Let's go.
Goodbye then.
-I need you to get me something.
-What is it, ma'am?
Hello, Ms. Yun.
I'm Lee Daesik, chief of Euljung Station.
I'm sorry for what my bodyguard did.
I asked to see you
so I could apologize in person.
Don't worry about it. It's okay.
Please come this way.
Our dashcam recorded
the culprit running away.
That's the suspect.
We had all rushed to another site,
so we weren't present at this time.
Right.
This dashcam footage was
retrieved from your late bodyguard's car.
Weren't we only able to retrieve this
because we swiftly reached out
to the control center?
Correct, sir.
-Jang Yeongsil.
-Yes, sir?
Show me the route that our vehicle took
20 minutes prior to Kim Hoseung's death.
Connect to the CCTV cameras
that recorded said vehicle.
Rewind ten minutes.
Stop.
Rewind four seconds.
Two seconds forward.
Combine the footage
from 60 seconds before and after.
Yeongsil, remove his glasses.
I got his face.
I'll send it to you right now.
AGE: LATE 30S TO EARLY 40S
Even the control center
couldn't locate where he went.
So we're doing our best to track him down.
We got his license plate number.
But the car is a lease
that he used a fake ID to get.
Is there a photo of the victim
when he was first found?
Yes, of course.
Didn't the body cam record him?
Yes, it did.
Let me show you the photos first.
As for the autopsy photos…
Please.
…we don't have them yet.
We're currently looking for the vehicle,
so we'll find it soon.
I hope so.
But I doubt he fled in his car
simply because he needed transportation.
I guess you could say that.
He'll probably get rid of it first
since his DNA is all over it.
-Yeongsil.
-Yes?
Were any Travelers scrapped-- No.
Did any Traveler
go up in flames, explode,
or go underwater after 11 a.m. today?
Did my bodyguard tell you
about the welfare center
and the post office?
The suspect must be on their CCTV cameras.
We're currently trying
to get our hands on the footage.
I heard that my bodyguard
unintentionally hurt an officer.
I apologize.
It's okay, ma'am. It was nothing serious.
Please take your time
to investigate this case.
We'll cooperate as much as possible.
By the way,
your bodyguard is unusually strong.
He's a bodyguard after all.
Yes, that's true. But still…
I located his vehicle.
A vehicle was reportedly set on fire.
Sorry?
The Gangbyeon Fire Station got a call
about nearby repair shops and the car
going up in flames,
fueled by the inflammables.
But I think it's the same model.
Clean Repair Shop in Gangbyeon.
That's where the fire began.
How did you know that?
-Look into it.
-I should get going. Goodbye.
Have a safe trip back, ma'am.
How did she know that?
KG LOW TO MID 70S
LATE 30S TO EARLY 40S
What?
-I sent it, ma'am.
-And the earphones?
I passed them on.
Mr. Seo, could you deactivate this?
It popped up.
Is that him?
Yes.
He's something else. A total professional.
He subdued our bodyguard.
No, the sensor suit-- Never mind.
What is it?
What is it? Did Mr. Kim die
because of the sensor suit?
That's not why.
-Yeongsil, the crime scene photos.
-Yes, sir.
He was stabbed through this small opening.
Pick a suit that fits you.
Am I getting one? For free?
Yes, it's free.
Gosh, this is amazing.
Mr. Seo, this is amazing.
-Why did I have to design it like that?
-It's not your fault--
What?
That's all the help I needed.
I'm sure you're busy.
It's great to have connections.
He's walking free
after assaulting police officers.
That's enough.
Ms. Yun asked us
to give this to you before you left.
May I go now?
Yes, you may.
-Sorry about everything.
-That's okay.
Where are you? Are you out already?
I thought you got me out.
It wasn't me.
But the officer said I had connections.
Hello?
-Yeongsil, locate Woo Chaewoon.
-Yes, ma'am.
Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep?
I thought she just saved your life,
not turned you into an android.
What did BF do to you?
I'm afraid I don't follow, sir.
No, you do. You definitely do.
So quit playing dumb.
I don't understand
what you're talking about, sir.
I heard you easily subdued
a group of police officers.
I heard you flung them in the air.
It was this sensor suit.
BF gifted me with this sensor suit.
It's bulletproof
and makes the wearer stronger.
But I can still feel things,
-so please don't throw anything.
-How dare you
act cheeky in front of me?
Then how about this for a serious topic?
Kir.
You know him, don't you?
His family left AZORAN
with Special Immigrant Visas
right after the explosion occurred.
They're enjoying
a comfortable life abroad as we speak.
You're not surprised to hear
that a terrorist's family is living well.
I can't believe
you thought I wasn't aware of that.
That's fascinating.
Had you been aware of it,
you should've been doubtful like I was.
And you wouldn't have thought
I was purely delusional for thinking
there was a mastermind behind the attack.
It must've upset you a lot
when I said that.
Have you been holding a grudge?
You're the one
who should have reasonable doubts.
But you concluded that the culprit
was caught and that it was over.
It just doesn't make any sense.
There must be a reason.
I've always been curious.
Getting a Special Immigrant Visa in AZORAN
back then was almost impossible.
So how did his family get it?
And one more thing.
How could the Korean embassy
issue the visas?
Was it you?
Do you think I'd use my power for that?
No, sir.
I'm asking if you attempted
to murder former president Lee Mungyu.
He was against all forms
of synthetic biology.
Had he been in office
for a few more years,
he would've shut down BF,
a company you're very much interested in.
You've gone insane.
Do you think I would've harmed
my own grandfather? My own blood?
Then it must've been someone higher up
who's not related to him.
Someone above you.
Was it a coincidence
that Chairman Seonu Geun
got a divorce soon after
the incident at AZORAN?
His ex-wife put up with him for decades
despite his countless scandals.
Did the lady of DORSON Group…
ever explain the reason to you, her son?
You weren't lying.
That sensor suit is well made.
Water!
Water.
You have hemophilia.
Shut up.
What is it?
Okay. I got it.
Get lost.
I said, get lost.
Why now when I'm in this condition?
If he cared so much about his appearance…
Where is he?
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
The prime minister knows a lot, ma'am.
And he has no intention of hiding it.
So the rumors were true.
About your relationship.
What kind of relationship
could we have when we're not even related?
You came to his rescue.
And much sooner than I expected.
Sir, I never pegged you
as the romantic type.
I've known you for many years.
You were never interested in others,
let alone men.
So why did you rush over here?
To protect the company's secret.
Because that man is your walking secret.
You've found a way to prolong life,
haven't you?
You succeeded in culturing organs,
Yes, I have.
Just show it to me. Only me.
I won't even tell my father about it.
It's simple if you want to know.
Please revise the bioethics law.
Then we'll make an announcement.
"BF has successfully cultured human organs
that can be commercialized now.
Humanity will suffer no more pain--"
No. Not all of humanity.
Why would you announce that?
What'll happen if everyone
is granted immortality?
Those people outside
won't be able to handle it.
They'll become extremely reckless
because they can live forever.
"Those people outside"?
What about our natural resources?
They'll still reproduce.
We can always produce more meat.
But what about land?
Natural resources? Jobs?
Generations must be replaced, Ms. Yun--
"Life may be unfair, but there's one thing
that everyone will face.
Death.
Culturing organs will take away
that remaining fairness from us."
I've heard this countless times.
And I made this decision every time:
"I will create a future
that is equal for all."
But this is a first.
You think everyone else but you
should get sick and die?
You gave me other excuses,
but are you actually worried about them?
Is it not that you, the high and mighty,
don't want to be like the rest of them?
We can't be the same.
It's impossible.
Let's say your dream came true.
Let's say purchasing organs becomes
as cheap as buying over-the-counter drugs.
Let's say everyone can live for centuries.
Regardless, the poor will remain poor.
We'll only be prolonging their pain.
Then who will suffer their fury?
Us. The rich.
There's only so much wealth,
but they can live forever.
Don't you think that'll cause a riot?
Just look at those commoners.
They think the rich are evil.
And you were their biggest victim.
Side with humanity.
Which side do you think I'm on?
You're on your own.
Achieving it together would be
considered human evolution. But alone,
you'd just be a mutation.
You're the wealthiest
and most powerful individual I know.
You've lived comfortably all your life.
And despite it all,
what you've always wanted
is to become a mutation?
To be different from the rest?
That's rich coming from someone
who created a mutation herself.
I heard he has superhuman strength.
He should be dead right now,
but he has superpowers.
If that's not a mutation, then what is?
I see. He was your first subject.
Fine. He was your lab rat.
You said we had to do this together.
That's why I'm volunteering
to be the next subject.
Or I'll just dissect that lab rat.
I have the right to order a search
and seizure for the illegal acts
committed by BF.
I'll confiscate all evidence
and related technology.
Is this your only way of threatening me?
What more do I need to say?
Frustrated, aren't you?
Ms. Yun.
I care…
about you.
Grab onto me before you lose everything
and regret it all.
This is your last chance.
I can see that.
You're about to reveal your true colors
and challenge me.
I can see that.
You did a good job
pretending to be someone useful until now.
Yes, sir.
Okay, I'll go right now.
I'll drive.
It was Ms. Jeong.
Did you catch her?
Did you tell Hoseung
about your plans this morning?
Ms. Jeong knew as well.
He said we should head out now
because you didn't have plans today.
Ma'am, Ms. Jeong said I could go
to the police station today.
He must've asked Ms. Jeong
about your plans like he did last time.
MS. YUN
JEONG HAEDEUN COULD BE THE MOLE
"Why do you want to know
about Ms. Yun's plans for the day?"
Ms. Jeong probably asked him that.
We need to know what she did afterward.
We found out.
-Hello?
-Are you still outside?
Go to Nakyeon-dong. The suspect is there.
Did he get caught?
Go to Corner Motel in Nakyeon 1-dong.
SISTER
ENGINEER MIGHT GET CAUGHT
What was that? Give that back!
What's your problem? Let go of me!
What's wrong with you?
What's your deal?
-Who was she texting?
-They can't track the recipient.
Any records of them communicating?
-Not at all.
-Damn it.
You have it all wrong.
Aren't you embarrassed
now that we got you?
Aren't you upset?
"Why did San tell me
to go see the suspect?"
I bet you were in too much of a hurry
to consider that.
Who is this "sister"
that you hurriedly texted? Tell us.
Ms. Yun.
How could you do this to me?
Look. You were the one
who asked me to quit my job as a lawyer
and work for you instead.
How could I have possibly killed anyone?
Ms. Yun, it's me! Jeong Haedeun!
Get your damn hands off of me.
Not only were you a spy,
but you killed a man.
It wasn't me.
How many times must I tell you?
Call the police.
And tell them I'm a spy.
Let them interrogate me and find out
what classified information I leaked!
How much is DORSON paying you to do this?
If it's not money,
are you secretly dating Seonu Geun?
Or is it Seonu Jae?
Maybe it's both of them.
Ms. Yun.
How could you--
How could you let him say such a thing?
Damn it.
Professor Kim's wife died
in our laboratory.
The ill woman died
after visiting her husband's workplace.
Seonu Jae must know that.
It was probably the first thing
Professor Kim told the killer.
But Seonu Jae didn't mention it
when he threatened me.
He had to play dumb.
Even a prime minister
couldn't have known that
unless he was the one
who sent the spy or the killer.
Exactly.
He knew it would've been
my biggest weakness
both legally and socially.
But he remained tight-lipped
to protect himself.
He would've been confessing to his crimes
had he mentioned it.
What about Ms. Jeong?
She was their spy.
So will she confess?
This is unlawful imprisonment.
You know I'm a lawyer, don't you?
Did the prime minister
say that you'd live forever as well?
Damn it.
Are you trying to jump on the bandwagon?
Who do you think you are?
Just hit me.
I'll add assault to the charges.
You put me on the interview list.
That way, I'd become her bodyguard,
and DORSON would send me here.
Seonu Jae didn't send me here to find out
who was responsible
for injuring his grandfather.
We're hacking BF.
Infiltrate their security system now.
Shut down their system completely
and get the data in the next two days.
He was using the disabled, old man
to swallow BF whole.
However…
I guess he has no plans
to protect his spy.
Let go of me!
I'm not like the rest of these people.
-Who killed Hoseung?
-Damn it! Let go of me!
Who killed him?
Ms. Yun, please help me.
You should all leave.
Ms. Yun--
How long have you been working for him?
-Since the terror attack?
-What are you saying?
What are you talking about?
Ms. Yun.
Ms. Yun, help.
Translated by Kim Sooji