BLOOD FREE
EPISODE 8
You don't have to explain anything to them
since they're all bereaved families.
I just thought it'd be nice
to have some people
you could talk to once a week.
No.
You just came to mind when I heard
about that support group.
MURDEROUS COMPANY
BF
Please help me.
Let her go.
She can take that much.
She's responsible
for Professor Kim's death,
as well as Mr. Kim's.
I'm sure she knew the risks involved.
Give her what she deserves.
She's already dragged down Professor Kim.
Let her go for your sake.
Don't even bother.
No. You heard what he said.
He just admitted that Seonu Jae sent him.
Tell them the truth.
It was you! Tell them!
Jang Yeongsil, strap her down!
Don't I deserve an explanation?
Damn it.
Does that mean he's also…
You're doing that?
Only if Ms. Yun allows it.
Did Seonu Jae send you here?
It was my choice.
Were you just trying to bait her
by saying that, then?
Had I not already decided
to come and look into it,
I wouldn't have listened to anyone,
not even the prime minister.
Look into what?
Whether or not you were behind
the terrorist attack
at AZORAN in January of 2024.
Yeongsil, locate Woo Chaewoon.
You came to his rescue.
And much sooner than I expected.
It was all a show!
-You and Seonu Jae are trying to frame me!
-No.
What did you tell him? What did you leak?
Nothing.
And you suspected me of doing that.
You scumbag!
You're the worst.
You're the worst kind of all.
I didn't know you back then.
I didn't know how much pain
you were dealing with
or what your dream was.
It wasn't a coincidence
that we were both at AZORAN.
No.
What about being my bodyguard?
Also not a coincidence.
What about when you came
to our event in the very beginning?
And the ransomware?
That wasn't a coincidence either.
I don't know which one it is.
Whether the prime minister included me
in his ransomware scheme
or if he decided to use me
after finding out I was connected to it.
So he underhandedly requested information
but didn't explain why he needed it?
I never gave him information.
Of course you'd deny it.
I have only one goal.
To find out if my men died at the hands
of our own people and not a foreign enemy.
But I couldn't find
any related information here.
There were no leads.
You should've given him something.
If you did as Seonu Jae asked,
you would've been useful to him.
"Haedeun got caught. I'm all you have."
You could've had the upper hand.
Will you give me…
one last chance to be of use?
Let me catch Hoseung's killer.
Why bother asking for my permission?
You don't listen anyway.
Because this is my final mission here.
I'm going back to the welfare center.
At least one person there
has to remember the killer.
I'll tell you what I found out
once I come back.
Don't bother.
Also, don't bother resigning.
You're fired.
Jang Yeongsil.
Tell Ms. Jeong to pack up
all my belongings from Woo Chaewoon's--
Yes, ma'am?
This is what she's looking at right now.
The images are being sent
through brain waves.
And this is what comes to her mind
after seeing the images.
What is she thinking about?
I don't understand.
She's resisting psychologically.
That's why we're not getting much output.
God, she's obstinate.
The photos of her victims are showing,
but she's still resisting.
The output images
are gradually getting clearer.
Is she becoming psychologically weaker?
Bullshit. I'm not getting weaker.
Should I cover her ears?
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay. Damn it.
What?
It's him. The man who jumped
and fell on Ms. Yun's car.
Wasn't Haedeun there too?
She witnessed it up close.
All the blood we're showing her
is prompting her
to recall an image
she most closely associates with blood.
Ms. Yun, we're running an experiment.
Should we continue?
Jeong Haedeun.
Careful. She bites.
You are torturing me.
I won't let this go quietly.
Report me if you think I'm a spy!
Call the police!
I already did. I reported you as missing.
An industrial spy
who infiltrated BF has run away.
My bodyguard got murdered while trying
to find her. The killer and the spy
both vanished.
DORSON will find you at all costs.
People will find out that
the disgusting Seonu family planted a spy
in someone else's company,
but they won't abandon you.
They will save you no matter what.
Dream on.
Things will never go
according to your plan.
As you already know,
this building is quite complex.
And we have many freezers.
Make sure she eats three times a day
until she confesses.
Shove the food down her throat
if you must.
Don't you even think about dying.
I don't see the other spy.
Did you let him go?
What if he intended to reveal
his connection to Seonu Jae all along?
He and Haedeun could've plotted this
so at least one of them could go free.
He came here to find out
if I was behind the attack on AZORAN.
That's the most creative excuse ever.
But how can we believe him?
What if it's just a random excuse?
-Did you want to believe him?
-You think I did?
Can we control
the electronic chip in his ears?
What do you want to do with it?
I'll tell you
if he turns out to be a spy
and we have to do something about it.
Theoretically speaking,
we can cause a vibration in his ears.
We can cause a sharp pain
by affecting his inner ears.
So the noise cancellation
won't work either.
Hello.
Let's do that.
Get it ready.
-I'm sorry.
-About what?
I thought he was trustworthy.
After all,
I conducted his test and interview.
I promised to check for any side effects.
What?
Jang Yeongsil, send Woo Chaewoon an alarm
as soon as BF's app turns off.
- Yes, ma'am.
-I trusted Ms. Jeong too.
The minister will arrive in five minutes.
"We the farmers have protected our crops
even in the face of heavy rain.
When our country was plagued
with foot-and-mouth disease…
SEONU JAE, PRIME MINISTER
…mad cow disease, and the avian influenza,
the government ordered a massacre.
And being uneducated, we obeyed them.
We thought it was providence.
But now,
a monster called BF roams our country.
Providence is dead.
Has this hopeful world abandoned us?
Or should I,
a useless farmer, abandon this world?"
The USDA expressed their concerns
about BF's monopoly
of the market this morning.
They threatened us and said BF
could create diplomatic issues.
BF no longer feels like a major company
that's focused on a shared interest.
I'm concerned about this farmer
who left behind this letter
before taking his own life.
This company is burning
an entire industry to the ground.
How long will we just
sit and watch under the guise
of putting the economy first?
Actually,
I met with the CEO of BF
right after the culture fluid incident.
Nothing could be worse than people
questioning your product's safety.
Yet the CEO of BF,
who is an influential individual,
was only focused on making a profit.
It made me reflect on myself.
"This is really one of our leading CEOs?
Was I also like her in the past?"
Sir.
Can we begin an investigation on BF?
Yes, sir.
We can open a case whenever you wish.
There are already
several cases pending against BF.
But if we carry out an investigation
when Ms. Yun has already been charged
with poisoning a man,
it might seem like the government is
endorsing the accusations.
That's exactly it.
I don't think it's normal for a company
to be suspected of staging
an attack on their CEO
or the death of a company executive.
This investigation must be
more than just showing
that we are trying too,
or that we don't side with a corporation.
We must be thorough.
That way, BF will correct themselves
and self-reflect.
I need you leaders to help BF
become a company that serves this country.
The National Human Rights Commission,
Ministry of Trade, Industry and Energy,
Ministry of Agriculture,
Food and Rural Affairs, and the rest
must aid the prosecution.
-Can you do that?
-Yes, sir.
BLOOD FREE
I'm from a nearby real estate agency.
What? Is she the new owner of this house?
That young man should've told me
if the house was sold.
He never gave me an update.
Is this house on the market?
Why do you ask?
I heard you talking
to the real estate agent.
I wasn't meaning to eavesdrop,
but I could hear you so well.
Why? You want to move to an apartment?
No, to pay
for my niece's studies abroad.
What? You're selling the house
to pay for her studies?
Where does she go to school? Harvard?
She's in elementary school.
-She's still a kid.
-Yes.
Why are you footing the bill
instead of her dad?
Gosh, I'm in no position
to worry about others.
I need to buy a house
before I can get married and have a kid.
Are you seeing anyone?
Do you seriously think this handsome face
and hot body is single?
Geez, you're only 26 years old.
Even I'm still not married.
Why is that open?
Exactly. Ms. Yun.
Have you ever heard of an uncle
who financially supports his niece?
This isn't my house.
My entire family used to live here.
Look. I know it's none of my business.
But what you're doing is meaningless.
She'll only be fluent in English
and not give you anything in return.
You've been very nosy all day.
Do as you wish.
You'd have to work like a dog
to get a house like this again.
I've always wanted to study abroad.
You can go now.
My parents could only send one of us.
Ma'am, I can't believe there was a time
when you couldn't afford something.
All parents want to do
as much as they can for the children.
I have no choice.
She has a dairy allergy.
She can't have
any kind of milk whatsoever.
That little girl was taken to the ER
countless times when she was here.
Sellers would claim that their products
didn't contain any milk,
but her throat would swell up
and she couldn't breathe.
Guess what those people said every time?
"We didn't know it contained milk."
Some said we should feed her milk
to help her overcome her allergy.
Is she being treated in the US?
It's incurable.
What's interesting about the US is that
people there have all sorts of allergies.
One of her classmates has a water allergy.
Some do have that.
Your niece's parents
must be so devastated.
Her dad gave up on her.
He said he couldn't support her.
He expressed his resentment toward me
before filing for divorce.
Why would he resent you?
It's not your fault she's allergic.
Because I told my sister to come.
I was training long-term in the US.
She constantly called me in tears
after her daughter went to kindergarten.
Why did she cry
after her daughter went to kindergarten?
They had birthday parties every month,
and the kids would get cake.
Goodness. Your niece must've wanted some.
She never eats cake.
Because she knows
how painful it is better than anyone.
But her classmates were offended.
They were upset
that she didn't eat their cake.
Then they started to bully her.
Geez, I hate bullies.
It probably had to do with her race.
But she's never gone to the ER in the US.
Even if you had 100 kids,
I bet you could send them all abroad.
What's wrong? Was that too many?
He was 26.
I wonder how his girlfriend is holding up.
KIM HOSEUNG
Did Ms. Jeong spill anything?
Does Ms. Yun look like a terrorist to you?
It's likely…
that Mr. Kim Singu was brainwashed
in a short amount of time.
-By the killer?
-Yes.
He never opened up
during the group meetings.
And he only attended
two or three times in total.
But this guy sat next to him every time
and talked to him.
There was a time when they skipped
a meeting and went to that café.
He said the two never attended
any meetings after that day.
Professor Kim fell victim
to a heinous bastard.
How do you think he knew he could meet
Professor Kim at the welfare center?
Haedeun must've been busy tipping him off.
He was heinous enough to stab someone
and set an entire neighborhood on fire
instead of doing it
in a vacant lot. What a lunatic.
If you find out anything,
you don't have to tell me, but--
EULJUNG POLICE STATION
Don't worry.
Right. Did you tell the police
that we have Haedeun?
No.
How did they set up
so many explosives so quickly?
On a military base, at that.
Ms. Yun and the rest of us
once suspected that it could've been done
by a professional hit man,
not some extremist.
All you did was talk about it?
What could we have done?
But she was a victim too.
She looked familiar.
Did you find anything?
My God!
You could've given me a heads-up.
What?
Call me when you're done.
I won't stop until she talks.
You should eat.
No.
Are they worth starving yourself for
in order to remain loyal?
I don't want you to see this side of me.
What?
Let someone else do it.
Not you.
I'm not asking you to understand me.
I've already been caught anyway.
But I'd like you of all people
to only have good memories of me.
Please grant me this much.
Are you messing with me?
You won't trick me by suddenly acting
this way. What do you take me for?
How would you know if it's sudden or not?
You only set your eyes on Ms. Yun. You…
You never gave me a chance.
Ms. Jeong. You shouldn't have talked shit
to me a while ago if that were the case.
I swore I would hide my feelings
every time I came to work
since I knew I couldn't have you.
I guess I did a good job.
Did you really not notice?
Tell me the truth if you want me
to remember you in a positive way.
What happened to Professor Kim?
Who and where is Hoseung's killer?
What did DORSON ask you to do,
and what information did you leak?
"A colleague of mine died.
He was murdered on the street.
How is that possible?"
I told my friend that
because I was so distraught.
Stop talking about this friend
we can't even trace--
It's driving me crazy too!
She was like a sister to me!
Mr. On, how could I have possibly known
that her phone wasn't traceable?
Mr. On, I…
That friend of yours…
Fine. Tell me how you two met.
Jesus. What am I saying?
It was at a swimming pool.
We met at a pool.
She approached me first
and treated me well.
It's likely that Mr. Kim Singu
was brainwashed in a short amount of time.
We met at a pool.
She approached me first.
This is just unbelievable.
-Hey, are you done?
-Yes.
Are you going home?
Yes. See you tomorrow.
What about the images
Ms. Jeong was seeing?
I'll turn it back on before I go.
I told you to tell me when you were done.
Never mind. You should go.
What is it?
You must think
I really don't know anything
just because I'm staying quiet.
What are you staying quiet about?
You wanted to see if the traitor
was me.
You thought I was behind Hoseung's death.
-It's not your fault--
-What?
That's all the help I needed.
I'm sure you're busy.
Look. It's not like I don't understand.
Even I wondered how the killer
found our bodyguards.
But now that we found our mole,
don't I at least deserve
an apology from you?
-Deserve?
-But instead,
you look at me as if
I'm a professional torturer.
I can't believe what I'm hearing.
When did I look at you that way?
Just now.
I was going to say
that the woman looked familiar.
Woman? What woman?
The woman Ms. Jeong recalled.
The one she remembered
alongside the man who fell.
She looked familiar, but I stopped talking
because I couldn't remember.
And you suspected me?
Could it just be your insecurities?
No one accused you.
Maybe you already know
that you're torturing her.
That's why you feel guilty
when someone looks at you.
He doesn't have the balls to confront
the person who gave the orders.
Everyone thinks I'm a pushover.
Goddamn it.
-Jang Yeongsil.
-Yes, ma'am?
Send a letter to the stockholders.
"We foresee a hostile M&A attempt
by outside forces.
The company will issue stocks
that are relatively cheaper
and allow the stockholders
to purchase them first.
We're only doing this
to prevent illegal mergers
resulting from short-term profit fixation
and market failure.
We believe the outside forces
will attempt to purchase
the cheap stocks in bulk.
We urge our wise stockholders
to join hands with us
and protect the company."
Replace "urge" with "ask."
Okay. I have revised it.
"In addition…"
Seonu Jae sent me here
so he could swallow BF whole.
Grab onto me before you lose everything
and regret it all.
Jang Yeongsil.
What's the difference
in the company values of DORSON and BF?
Based on the figures of 2025,
DORSON's total market value
is 1.57 quadrillion.
BF's is 260 trillion.
It's not even one fourth.
Ms. Jeong vehemently denies
any involvement.
We'll only be accused
of keeping her hostage.
Let's just hand her over to the cops
if we're not putting her in the freezer.
And what if she dies like Professor Kim?
Freezer, it is.
I don't expect her to admit
that she was working for DORSON.
But we need to find out who the killer is.
Even if she admits to it,
how can we put up a fight
against Seonu Geun and the prime minister?
This is your last chance.
This is my last chance.
Yes, ma'am. Mr. Yeo.
Wouldn't there be more people in Haeundae?
Especially at nighttime.
We already set everything up there.
We're in Nampo-dong now.
It won't be real-time.
They'll send us an edited version.
How about the other areas?
Yes, we're ready too.
Hello. I'm Yun Jayu, the CEO of BF.
-Look at that.
-Gosh!
There's something I must tell you all
who live in this day and age.
I apologize for the sudden appearance.
We at BF have been
conducting a secret project.
Organoids.
Simply put,
we've been culturing human organs.
With our top-notch
cell culture technology,
we strived to copy human organs.
And as a result,
we were able to culture muscle fibers,
osteocytes, blood,
hearts, livers, kidneys, lungs,
- pancreases, stomachs, small intestines…
-Hey, look.
…large intestines, and bladders.
We successfully cultured all human organs
- except for the brain.
-No way.
However,
our project isn't perfect just yet.
We need to run some clinical tests.
That's why I'd like to ask you for help.
Those who have terminal cancer.
Those who are suffering
from incurable diseases.
We are looking
for clinical test volunteers.
We will cover the entire cost of surgery.
We'll carry out a suitability test
on the volunteers.
The first batch will consist
of 60 patients.
The second and third batches
will consist of 150 patients.
I have a great deal of respect for BF
for their wonderful achievement.
But I am enraged
as the prime minister of this country.
What gives Ms. Yun the right
to stir up the entire country
by using our people's health as bait?
What you just witnessed
is an advertisement.
As the CEO,
she is merely advertising her products.
However, there is heartbreaking news
that I must share with you
prior to carrying out this project.
Two years ago, our researchers carried out
a clinical test. However,
we failed.
Even though
the patient had consented to it
and the cancer cells had metastasized,
we must not and can't
deny the fact that she passed away.
I would like to take responsibility
and promise you two things.
I do not doubt it.
I believe our people are wise.
BF will not get what they want.
I understand that her words
may have given some of you hope.
However,
the government will do their job.
We will absolutely not allow
a private company to make
this large-scale gamble
while putting lives at risk.
First, I will take legal responsibility
for carrying out medical treatment
outside a medical institution.
Second,
I volunteer to be the first test subject.
Are you insane?
Were you aware of this? Mr. On.
Mr. On, were you aware of this?
Did you guys agree on this?
Are you crazy?
Then…
I won't use people's desperation
for my project.
So this is her own crazy idea.
I will replace all my organs
- with our cultured ones.
-My dear citizens whom I respect.
Please remember this.
You don't need to approve of her,
let alone respect her,
just because she's sacrificing herself
to prove something.
The entire procedure will be open to all.
We will see if I suffer
from any complications,
infections, or rejections
over the next three months.
Hi, honey.
We'll only select new test subjects
once that's been cleared.
Is that true?
BF's cell culture technology is
currently the highest point possible
that modern humans can reach.
The surgery will be carried out by AI
that is absolutely precise
and top-notch researchers who have been
working on culturing human organs
- since the beginning of BF.
-Yun Jayu is advertising her products!
BF is advertising a product
that is far from being complete.
This isn't a reckless attempt.
And that is only because
many of you are desperate
to live in a world free of disease.
I trust your courage and determination.
I, alongside BF, a biotechnology company,
will be waiting for those
who will join us in changing humanity.
Ms. Yun.
If you still have an ounce of conscience
or good sense in you,
don't try to profit
from our citizens' lives.
Instead, you should repent
and give your sincere apology
to all the innocent lives
that fell victim to your company.
You will be redirected
to voicemail after the beep…
-Why isn't she picking up?
- Your call will be charged.
MS. YUN
Yun Jayu,
are you seriously out of your mind?
What do you take us for?
Hey, even someone whose organs
are completely damaged wouldn't do this.
It's not like you're being forced
to fall off a building or something. I…
All he ever did was work hard.
Hold on. Jang Yeongsil.
Yes, sir?
Find the name of the farm
owned by the man who jumped off
the Maesan Overpass on December 24, 2025.
Okay. I'm searching news articles.
The name of the farm
is Yangju-ri Gwanghyang Husbandry.
MS. YUN
The prosecution was already notified
of BF's illegal surgery
and the patient's death.
The fact that
Ms. Yun mentioned this incident right now
shows that she knows
she'll be interrogated soon
and is trying to save face
by pretending to be
a conscientious individual.
As you just heard,
the prosecution will be conducting
- an investigation on BF.
-Leave it running.
-Yes, ma'am.
-We will update you
on any new announcements
made by the government.
Let's see what the citizens thought
after hearing Yun Jayu's announcement.
I was utterly shocked.
I wonder if she'll actually do it.
Let me be your proof.
What did you find out
after leaving to find the killer?
"I was on the brink of death,
but BF saved me.
What better proof
could there possibly be?"
Whom should I tell this to?
I'll tell them that I got stronger
and can hear much better now, so…
Don't go through with it.
Why take a longer route
when there's a shortcut?
There's no better solution than this.
Why are you going this far?
Because I must subdue them.
There's no other reason.
I've faced countless obstacles until now,
and I've overcome them all.
This one will be no different.
I will show them
that I can't be subdued.
Was there ever a time
when you had to sacrifice your body?
Do you even want to live?
I'm doing this so I can live.
And I will.
I understand.
What do you understand?
Where are you going?
You won't need the best solution…
if the second-best one succeeds.
What are you planning to do?
I also have something I can't give up on.
My mission…
isn't over yet.
It has been a while
since I've taken a night stroll.
You know, don't you?
It's not just about
replacing the organs, is it?
You can become lively again.
You must've seen it firsthand.
You could've worn a prosthetic leg
if you wished to walk again.
Captain Woo, be careful what you say.
Did you tell your daughter?
You said it was a surprise visit,
but a visit from the head of state
couldn't have been spontaneous.
You must've planned the visit
even before you boarded the plane.
Did you tell your daughter about your plan
before boarding the plane?
What if I did?
I'd like to meet with her.
Why?
Ms. Yun wasn't behind the attack.
So we should move on.
Just like how we moved on
from Chairman Park to Ms. Yun.
You want to move on,
yet you want to see my daughter?
To be precise,
I'd like to meet Chairman Seonu's ex-wife.
Leave.
Will you ask her yourself?
Leave!
CHAIRMAN OF DORSON AND HIS WIFE
It's nice to meet you.
My name is Woo Chaewoon.
I have something to tell you
regarding a request
made by the prime minister.
What is it?
You'll request to go abroad
just to pay for your niece's studies?
I'm also sick and tired of everyone
blaming each other for the ransomware.
Look at you.
You must've heard about how beautiful
the women are in that country.
You're a lunatic.
You know what? I'll also go
and stop you from marrying one of them.
You're coming too?
They'll think all Korean men are ugly
if you're the only one they see.
Don't tell me
you already did the interview.
I will catch him…
at all costs.
Translated by Kim Sooji