I like you!
Hey...
Yes?
You're a pest, an eyesore,
and I'm not interested.
He's right.
Of course, she is.
-Oh, Moe, you did it...
-How'd it go?
It didn't go well, did it?
Seems it did not.
Moe... Hey! Where are you going?!
You're in my way.
Do you know how much courage it took
for Moe to tell you how she felt?
And yet, you just went off on her.
You're unbelievable.
Only the most inhuman--
Who are you?
I'm Moe's best friend, Aoi Nishimori.
Moe?
The girl who just professed
her love to you!
She's actually serious about you!
What?
So you...
want me, too?
Not even in your dreams!
Oh, no!
It hurts...
My foot hurts.
Sorry.
The signal's turning red.
What?! Hold on.
Wait...
I made it.
Go left here.
Gosh...
Okay, okay...
-Shusei Kugayama?
-Yeah!
There he is!
On the left? Right?
The right, of course!
He's so cute!
Is he that popular?
Where have you been?
He's not just a handsome face.
He's a top student
and a talented athlete, too!
He's just so cool!
Go up here.
What? Wait a minute.
Ouch!
Try walking on your own--
No way.
Climb on.
Here we go.
You know, if it hurts that much,
maybe you should see a doctor--
Nope.
Why not?
I hate doctors.
That's not a reason not to go...
Hey, can't you do it right?
Sorry.
Okay.
Over there.
What?!
-Huh?
-Hey!
Don't just drop me here.
What?
Why here?
This is where I live.
What? This is where I live!
What?
Are you serious?
What room number?
Room 202.
Right next to me? Since when?
Since a week ago.
You're kidding me...
How did I end up having to do this, too?
Ow! What are you doing?
That's your...
Oh. You want to look at them?
No, I do not.
Dinner ready yet?
I'm still cleaning.
-Besides, you didn't mention dinner--
-Oh, it hurts so much...
I'm starving.
What a pest!
ROOM 203 NISHIMORI
ROOM 202 KUGAYAMA
Wow. I'm surprised you know how to cook.
I've been living alone for a year now.
Why are you living alone?
My dad transferred to China
for work last year.
My younger brother
and my mom went with him,
but I have entrance exams.
Our high school is affiliated
with a university. Just move on to there.
Wait, maybe you can't
because you're stupid?
That is not the reason.
To be honest, I wanted to stay in Japan.
Because...?
I didn't want to change schools,
and go abroad on top of that.
Plus, I didn't want to leave Moe behind.
Moe?
-The girl who said she liked you!
-Oh.
You know, Moe's a really nice girl.
She may not look it,
but she's got a deep personality.
Back in junior high, she stood by me
even when my other friends didn't.
She was always there for me.
Oh, that looks good.
Don't scare me like...
Put some clothes on!
Whoa...
My goodness, what happened here?
Ah, it's cold!
You guys made a real mess of this place.
Well, I've called someone
to handle repairs,
and the insurance will cover it.
No worries.
I am so sorry!
Um, how long will the renovations take?
They said they're currently busy
with other orders they've received,
so it could take up to a month.
What? That long?!
What'll you do until then, Shusei?
None of the other rooms are available.
I guess I can have you
stay with me, but...
That's okay.
I'll stay at a friend's place.
-Really?
-Yes.
Right?
Huh?
"A friend's place"?
Your room.
What?!
Are you serious?!
UNDER RENOVATION
VISITORS PLEASE GO NEXT DOOR
Come--
How did it come down to this?
Hey, are you really planning to stay...
Ah... that hurt!
Did you see anything?
I'm gonna take a bath.
Red polka dots.
What should I do?
I've never dated anyone before,
and now I'm living with a guy
I don't even like.
Are you a nudist or something?!
Put some clothes on!
It's fine. I live here.
It is not fine. I'm a girl, and...
Oh, I see. You have dirty thoughts.
You pervert.
No! If we're going to live together,
we need to establish some rules.
You can't just walk out here
looking like that.
-This is good.
-Think first and--
This is really good.
Really?
Nishimori.
Is my class boring you that much?
No! Not at all.
Not at all. I'm sorry.
To continue,
-What are you doing?
-...let's talk about the Renaissance.
In French, the word means "rebirth."
"Rebirth."
So doesn't that make you wonder
what was reborn?
Right? What do you think?
What?!
What happened to your injury?!
He's completely fine!
I was tricked!
Nishimori?
Tricked by what?
I'm sorry.
What's with your lunch?!
That's not like you. Did something happen?
Why'd you move my bed?!
There wasn't enough space for me.
Enough space for you?!
Give me back...
my spot!
He just does whatever he wants...
Okay.
Oh, no!
Darn it!
Today's recycling day!
You're gonna be late!
I'm skipping first period.
Oh, no!
You shouldn't let the trash pile up.
Well, I've had a few eventful days.
Living alone does seem
to have its difficulties.
-Hey, Moe.
-Yeah?
You know that guy, Kugayama...
I think I've fallen even harder for him!
What? Why?
Even after he said those awful things?
He's just a prince
with a hot-cold personality.
All the more reason I like him.
I... see...
Hey! Did you hear the bad news?
Manami in class two
might get kicked out of school.
-Kicked out?!
-Why?
The school found out
she was living with her boyfriend.
Well, that was stupid of her!
She should've hid it better.
You can get kicked out just for that?
It's bad for the school
if the parents found out.
Our school is surprisingly strict
on stuff like that.
I see.
Reina! We have to be careful, too.
That's right, Hama.
You two don't live together!
Oh, no...
Share your happiness with me, you jerk!
I'd never share with you!
I bought this yesterday,
but I've no clue how to use it...
Moe, look! It's Shusei!
No way. I should say hi to him!
But you were rejected just yesterday...
The real struggle begins now.
That's what it means?
Yes!
He's coming this way!
What do I do?
Go for it!
Hey...
-Yes?
-I'm talking to her.
Huh?
Me?
Your key.
Hey! Stop it!
I forgot my key.
Will you knock it off?!
If the school finds out we live together,
we could be kicked out.
We live together?
Simply put, yes. It looks like that.
So if we get busted for it--
Do you need it or not?
Give it back.
Hey... I said give it back!
Where's my "Thanks"?
Hey, get away from me.
It's bad if we get busted, right?
Thank you.
I can't hear you.
Thank you!
So you can say it.
Oh, yeah! What's with your leg?!
Since when did it heal?!
I dunno.
You're unbelievable!
Shusei!
-Hi, honey.
-Are you my girlfriend?
Oh, you must be in a good mood.
You came back at me with a perfect
straight-man response.
Not really.
No, something good happened, didn't it?!
Last night's dinner was good.
That's about it.
Really? Where at? Saizeriya?
You know, that place is...
Hey, Aoi, what was that?
Are you and Shusei--
My key! I dropped my key.
He was just returning it.
Isn't he so kind?
Right?
That's great.
Wow, he's so amazing!
YAMATE APARTMENTS
NO WALKING AROUND NUDE!
NO STEALING FOOD!
KNOCK WHEN ENTERING BATHROOM!
NO USING OTHERS' TOWELS!
I wish I didn't have to lie to Moe...
Okay.
All done!
I've got my own space again!
Man, I'm hungry.
Now, to put him straight.
So, this is your new place?
What?
What's he doing?!
What should I do?
It's so old.
There's dust everywhere.
Is it open?
This place is nice!
It's comfortable enough for one person.
What the...
Hey, what is this?!
This is a girl's!
-Oh, that belongs to the girl next door.
-Huh?
Sometimes her laundry flies over
off her clothesline.
From next door?!
Like her red polka dot underwear.
The neighbor girl's?
What's she like?
Ordinary.
Does she go to our school?
-Yeah.
-Who?
What was her name again?
Did you hear something strange just now?
No.
Really?
But it must be nice here.
What's it like living next to her?
It's whatever.
"Whatever"? So nothing's happened?
Like she doesn't come over
asking to borrow soy sauce?
Or ask you to come over
to switch out a light bulb?
Or come over to give you a message?
Nothing like that?
Nope.
Hey, stop it!
Huh?
What?
Didn't you just hear a girl's voice?
Next door. The walls are pretty thin.
Seriously? So, can you
hear her taking a bath?
I dunno.
Hello?
What?
What are you doing?!
Ouch...
What's wrong?
Who's she?
She came from next door
to get her laundry.
I'm Aoi Nishimori.
I'm a third-year from class three.
Ryosuke Sato, class one.
I went to junior high with Shusei, too.
I'm not sure if I'm a good friend
or a bad influence.
He's giving me a house-warming party.
Yeah, you should come too.
Oh, that's okay. I--
Yeah, she can't. Bye.
Maybe next time then.
Sure.
I'll be on my way now.
Wait.
You forgot this.
Thank you.
I'm so fed up!
That was my room in the first place!
Ooh, a sale!
Welcome!
Hello!
Wow, they've got some good deals today.
Oh, olive oil.
Would you like to try our new products?
Oh, Sanjo!
Welcome to the store, Aoi.
We just got this olive oil in today.
Wow.
-Would you like a taste?
-Yes!
That's delicious!
Oh! Seems like this will be a hit.
-Huh?
If it puts a smile on your face,
then it'll definitely sell well.
-Really?
-No doubt about it.
By the way, you know that marinade
that the landlady made...
You're wearing such thin clothes.
No, I didn't mean to--
Do you have an umbrella?
No, but I'll be okay.
Hold on.
I'm sorry for the trouble.
Who is that girl?
I think she lives
in the same apartment building.
What? Really?
I'm coming in.
Hey.
From now on, no inviting friends over.
That goes for both of us.
Why?
I told you.
If we're busted,
then we might be kicked out of school.
What's with the sweater?
Sanjo let me borrow it.
You've got a fever.
Do I?
Hey, you're standing too close.
You've never been around a man, have you?
Why are you asking me that now?
You haven't gone on a date either?
That's none of your business!
Why are you looking at me like that?
I don't need your pity.
And I don't need a man
when I've got plenty of friends. I--
Good luck!
Wait.
You hide over there!
Hi, Sanjo!
Here's the marinade recipe
you wanted.
Thank you so much!
Your drawings are so cute.
These would be good enough
to be in a cookbook!
No way.
Do you have a guest over?
No, of course not.
Oh, it's next door!
I often hear voices next door.
Oh, you mean the high school boy?
I think so.
You should be careful, Aoi.
Sometimes you forget you're a girl.
Yeah.
I'll return your umbrella
and your sweater once they've dried.
Don't worry about it.
No, please let me do that much.
You really saved me.
-Really?
-Yes.
Alright. Goodnight.
Have a good night.
How cute.
"Thank you so much!"
I didn't say it like that.
Does he live here?
Sanjo lives on the floor below us.
He goes to Keio University.
I'm going to work.
Work?
See ya.
Ouch!
What was that for?!
Good morning!
Morning, Aoi!
So how is it, living with a hunk?
I can't take it anymore.
It's rough being young, isn't it?
Huh?
Make sure you use contraception!
Oh, my God! Landlady!
Shusei isn't your average man.
He's solid.
He works a part-time job
to pay his own rent.
"I decided to leave home on my own.
Of course, I have to pay it myself."
That's what he said.
Mom!
I changed my shoes, Mom.
Oh! Well done.
Good morning, Kota.
Good morning, Aoi.
You're coming to the barbecue, right?
What barbecue?
Next Sunday.
We're having a welcome party for Shusei.
You're coming too, right, Shusei?
Yup.
Oh!
Moe, it's not what you think!
This isn't how it looks!
Moe, I swear this isn't how it looks...
Okay.
Are you okay?
No, I'm not...
Well, just do your best.
Alright.
Can I put this here?
Oh, actually can you put it over there?
That looks heavy.
What are you making for us today?
Some paella, spare ribs, and stew.
I knew we could count on you, Sanjo!
Won't you come be my bride?
Your bride?
-Yes.
-Can I be your bride?
Huh?
Who said that?
Me! I'm over here!
Oh, it's just you?
Hurry up and get to work! Open that.
What?!
Don't just sit there. Get the fire going.
Quickly!
I was so surprised
about Shusei being your neighbor!
It's such a coincidence, isn't it?
And that he goes to your place to brush
his teeth because his sink's broken.
-Amazing, right?
-Right!
Throw it!
I'm glad Shusei can smile
like a normal guy.
Catch, Shusei!
At any rate,
why do you have so many
good-looking guys at your apartment?
You've got Shusei and Sanjo, too.
Sanjo?
Sweet, handsome, mature,
and a fantastic cook.
He's perfect,
though I still prefer my hot-cold prince.
-Moe.
-Huh?
Well...
What is it?
You should join them.
-What?
-Yeah.
Kota, Moe said she wants to play, too.
-Is that okay?
-Yup.
Go on, Moe. Join them!
O-Okay!
Can I throw the ball with you guys?
Sure.
Here I go!
Okay!
It's behind you.
That's too close, Kota.
Shusei!
I missed you!
Mom! There's a man hugging another man!
This is my older brother.
-What?
-Huh?
Hello!
-Welcome!
-Oh, Kazumi!
Here, I brought this.
Really?
Soju! It's been a while.
Oh, Ryosuke! You look well. Hey!
Shu!
"Shu"?
It's so good to see you, Shu.
Why are you here, Satsuki?
I thought you'd be missing me
right about now.
Who is she?
This is Satsuki,
a childhood friend of ours.
A "childhood friend"?
It means we lived
in the same neighborhood as kids.
I guess she's like family,
or someone who's always with us.
Oh?
Were we just childhood friends?
More like just an ex-girlfriend.
-Shall we eat?
-Yeah!
-Let's go!
-Okay!
Come on.
So, there are girls at Shu's apartment?
I'm Aoi Nishimori.
I live next door to him.
And I'm Aoi's friend, Moe Shibuya.
Hello.
Let's go, Shu.
Thanks.
Shall we?
I've got a bad feeling about her.
A real bad feeling.
-Wow!
Amazing.
That looks yummy!
Eat it while it's hot.
-Alright!
-Thanks!
-Let's eat.
-Looks good!
Please help yourself.
Hey, Moe. Can you get me some of that?
Delicious!
-Is it good?
-Moe!
Glad you like it!
Woo-hoo! Boat time!
Here.
Thanks.
He must be popular at school.
-Huh?
Shusei.
Oh. Yeah, it seems so.
"Seems"? You're not interested?
Yup. Not interested
in that heartless prick.
Really?
Then we're the same.
I'm not interested in you, either.
Don't eavesdrop!
I want to eat that.
Get it yourself.
My hand hurts.
That lie again?
You two get along well.
-No way!
-No way.
You match too well.
It doesn't seem
like you're just neighbors.
I'm a little jealous.
Then why don't you take her home?
Huh?
Wait a minute.
What are you talking about?!
This is tasty.
I'm sorry about that.
-He's just weird like that.
-Don't worry about it.
Okay, here we go!
-Ready? Rock, paper, scissors!
-No!
-Yes!
Why do I have to carry this
both to and from here?!
I'll take the yogurt!
Then I'll take strawberry milk.
I'll take strawberry milk, too!
Why are you copying me?
I'm not! I just want to drink this, too!
Here.
Shu.
Yeah?
You remember your promise, right?
How could I forget?
That's good.
You'll catch a cold wearing that.
It'll just aggravate it.
I can handle this much.
I've been doing well recently.
I don't really catch colds either.
I need the bathroom.
Hey.
Don't play games with Aoi, alright?
What?
For the last year,
I've been watching over Aoi
like an older brother.
If you do anything to hurt her,
I won't forgive you.
An older brother?
Huh?
That's cool.
He's overreacting.
It's not that cold out.
They've both always
been protective of me.
Is that so?
Your name's Aoi, right?
Yes.
Shu won't commit to anyone.
Huh?
Don't waste your love on him.
I don't have any feelings for him...
YAMATE APARTMENTS
What's wrong? It's just a little thunder.
Y-Yeah, I guess you're right.
It's nothing to be scared of.
Of course.
I'm fine.
Morning!
Good morning!
That was some thunder last night!
It sure was! I was so scared.
But at least Shusei was there with you.
What? No, it wasn't like that...
Oh, yeah.
Do you want to go to an amusement park?
I got two tickets from my friend,
but they expire this month.
I'm too busy to go.
Then I'll go with Moe--
-We'll go.
-Huh?
Thanks for the tickets.
See you after school.
What? Wait, what just happened?
Wait a minute!
Give that back!
Three, two, one!
Ta-da!
He's late.
That roller coaster was so fun!
It's been a while
since I've been to a theme park.
Where should we go next?
Wait, this isn't a date...
Ow! Huh?
Hey, wait!
Oh, that's right. I'll practice with you.
What?
Dating.
Never done it, right?
Wh--
What are you doing?
I think I like it when you're embarrassed.
What?
-That suits you perfectly.
-Shut up.
Oh, what?
You suck at this.
-One more time.
-I'm way better than you.
I did it!
Yes!
Alright!
Wow! That was awesome!
I did it! It went in!
Yay!
Hey, let's ride the roller coaster!
No, thanks.
Let's ride that instead.
Oh?
Are you scared?
I just don't like to hear
a bunch of girls screaming.
-You are scared!
-No, I'm not!
How is it? You nervous?
No.
Really? You're definitely scared.
I'm beat.
Look at your hair!
Shut it.
Wanna ride it again?
No!
Hey, do you know about this?
The Tanabata Fireworks Festival.
"Seven hearts filled with wishes."
What is this?
At the end of the fireworks display,
seven heart-shaped fireworks go off.
If couples kiss during that time,
they'll be together forever.
You believe that?
It's not a bad thing to dream.
Dream?
I shouldn't have told you.
Why don't you give it a try?
Someday, I will.
"Someday" is next month.
This year, I don't have anyone...
Then you wanna go with me?
-Huh?
-If you can't find someone first.
Why you?
It'll be fun.
Hey, I'm being serious, you know!
It's not a joke.
If I went with him...
Huh? Where did he go?
They're gone.
Do you think that was Shusei's girlfriend?
They were holding hands!
Who was it? A third-year?
Let's go see.
There she is! That's her!
-She's running!
-Seriously? It must be her!
She turned the corner!
Where is she?
Huh?
W-What are you doing--
Shh!
Where is she?
Where did she go?
I wanted to see who she was.
She has to be his girlfriend.
They held hands.
What do we do?
That's awful.
I know, right? The worst...
Sorry about that.
But... I wanted to go out with you.
You're so tense.
Save it for the right guy.
What was that?
YAMATE APARTMENTS
FIREWORKS AT 7:30 P.M.
Oh, morning!
Hey, Aoi!
Are you waiting for someone?
Really? Did you get boyfriend?
Of course not! Just go to class!
You're being suspicious!
Which class is he in?
Totally suspicious!
Morning, Aoi.
Morning.
Listen,
Moe...
Yeah?
You have a boyfriend?
Huh?
No...
So, you're going out with Shusei?
No! We just live together.
He doesn't even think of me as a girl.
How do you feel?
At first, I kind of hated him.
But now you... like him?
Kind of...
Even though I like him?
I'm so sorry.
This pisses me off.
We promised each other
back in junior high,
that if we liked someone,
we would tell each other first!
-I know.
-I've always done that.
I'm sorry.
You better tell me everything from now on.
Huh?
Don't you know who you're dealing with?
It's Shusei, remember?
You can't possibly do this alone
with no experience in love.
But Moe, you...
I thought it'd be nice
to be his girlfriend,
but since it hasn't happened by now,
I don't think it ever will.
Besides, I told him how I felt
just for the sake of doing it.
It's about time that I moved on.
Really?
Have I ever lied to you?
Moe!
-What?
-I love you!
I know that, sheesh.
Hey! Moe, wait!
Hey!
Oh, no! You're so fast!
STAR JEWELRY CO.
Oh!
It's so cute!
Buy it.
No way. I don't have that kind of money.
I see.
Do you really need this?
Huh?
Five kilos of rice.
We're going to eat it!
Besides, if we don't finish it,
we can just stick it in the fridge.
Eating five kilos of rice
will fatten you up.
I'm not eating it all by myself.
Though I ate three kilos alone--
Satsuki.
Is it true you're living with her?
Yeah.
Until repairs are done.
It can't be helped.
You could've come to my place.
It's too far.
Besides, we just live together
for convenience.
What's that supposed to mean?
My hand's gonna fall off holding this.
Wait, Shu!
You must be happy with this.
Living with a guy in your class.
That's just how things worked out--
I told you, didn't I?
Not to waste your love on him.
Well,
you guys broke up, didn't you?
Shu hasn't told you...
what happened two years ago, has he?
No, he hasn't.
He and I have an unbreakable bond.
I'm the only one who can make Shu happy.
Maybe you should try to pick up on that.
Satsuki went home.
I see.
Hey...
What?
Never mind. It's nothing.
What's up with that?!
S-Shibuya!
Do you have a complaint about my class?
Uh, no. Not at all.
-What?
-What was that?
Nothing.
What is it?
-Be quiet!
-To continue,
From the end of the 15th century
until the mid-16th century,
I DON'T BELIEVE IT! I'M SO MAD!
WHAT'S WITH THAT EX-GIRLFRIEND?
Italy was intermittently embroiled
in war for 50 years...
THERE WERE CIRCUMSTANCES...
What kind of circumstances?!
S-Shibuya!
I'm sorry.
Yeah, I'll go. Aoi, you're coming, right?
I'll pass today.
No, sorry.
-See ya.
-Bye!
Later!
Aoi!
Hello.
Where's Shusei?
I don't really know...
But you live together, don't you?
What? No! I mean...
I heard from Satsuki.
She can barely contain herself.
Can I ask...
what kind of relationship
does Satsuki and Shusei have?
Do you like Shusei?
Uh... no! Not at all!
You're easy to read.
My dad always had
a lover on the side,
and my mom tolerated it by not having
any interest in our family.
You could say it was a loveless household.
That was our family.
Satsuki knew about all of that
since we were kids.
So, when Shusei started
getting into trouble,
and my family basically gave up on him,
Satsuki would make sure
he made it to school.
She'd bring him home too,
from even the sketchiest places.
Really?
Well,
that's a pretty standard
childhood-friend story.
Do you want to hear more?
Yes.
It'll cost you.
Huh?
How will you pay me?
-Um...
-I know.
What are you doing?!
Oh, was that your first kiss?
Seriously?
Well then, why don't we just go out?
Don't mess with me!
Very nice!
-As adorable as ever.
-Really?
-Last three shots. Let's get a close-up.
-Okay.
Here we go. Yes!
Very cute!
Okay, that's perfect!
-Yay!
-Nice shot.
-It's good, right?
-Yup.
Good job.
Everything's okay!
Did you make me look good?
Of course. These are the best shots yet.
Please change costume.
-Okay!
-Thank you!
Oh, Shusei!
How was school?
What did you want?
You could at least
make some small talk first.
Here. This is from Mom.
I don't need it.
Working part-time isn't enough.
Just take it.
Take it back.
You can never have enough
money or women.
Then you keep it.
I'd gladly keep Aoi instead.
Why are you bringing her up?
That girl seems a lot like Satsuki.
How?
She's clumsy, but honest.
The straight-forward type.
Why are you making that face?
Well,
she's quite a tough one.
Huh?
I kissed her.
But I think it was her first
because she cried--
I haven't seen you angry in a while.
-Bastard!
-Stop!
What are you doing?!
Nothing!
Prepare for the shoot.
What are you doing?
Looking at the sky.
You're crying.
No, I'm not.
You are.
I said, I'm not!
You look awful.
Why are you taking a picture?
Don't just let anyone kiss you.
I told you to save it
for the right guy.
You're an idiot.
Sorry...
You've been reset.
-What--
-It's fine now.
Just keep quiet.
-But--
-With my kiss,
his kiss is canceled out.
I've decided it.
What?
-Off you go.
-Huh?
Wait!
Wait a minute!
That's pretty scary.
I thought I was gonna die!
You're laughing too much!
Maybe I just want to laugh with you.
Me, too.
I want to laugh...
with him.
Um...
Cut about this much.
Okay.
Actually, cut it this much.
Welcome back.
Thanks.
But...
somehow...
when we're together...
It's good.
What is?
I think I like it.
Hey...
Your cooking.
Gosh.
...it's always me...
whose feelings get all mixed up.
Thanks for waiting.
Welcome.
Hey, Kugayama!
Break time.
Okay.
It's so pretty!
Oh, that's a very cute lunch
you've got there.
Are you a married man?
That must be great
having a wife who can cook!
-Let me have a bite.
-No way.
-Me, too!
-No!
Hey!
That's my toothpaste!
Sheesh.
The next thing you know...
Here.
What's this?
It's nice, huh?
...you're wanting more and more.
You've got some guts to cut it that short!
You must have a boyfriend, Aoi.
No, I don't.
I told you, that's not it!
You're different somehow.
Yeah, you must be
to have cut your hair so short.
He's so cool!
X equals 6, Y is 6 minus twice root 6.
The maximum is 6 minus twice root 2,
minimum is 1. Got it?
Stupid.
If you want me to teach you, then listen.
You could be a little nicer, you know!
But sometimes,
there's a voice inside that says,
"Don't come any closer."
I know that.
So things are good the way they are.
I want to cherish
this space we have between us.
I'm having the plumber fix it tomorrow.
Do you two take baths together?
Of course not!
-Do you want to take a bath with me?
-Yup!
Then I guess we're married, huh?
Okay, I guess we'll be
naked together, Kota.
Oh, stop.
Rather than say "I like you"
and lose what we have,
NIGHT OF JULY 7TH
SEVEN HEARTS FILLED WITH WISHES
we will just stay like this...
-Let's go with that.
-Okay.
Wait!
Aoi!
Hello.
Because of you,
Sanjo will find out about us!
Is that a problem?
Of course, it is!
I don't care if people
find out I'm with you.
Huh?
Being with you isn't so bad.
Always like this...
forever and ever...
Ready? Rock, paper, scissors!
I want it to stay like this...
for as long as it can.
Ready? Rock, Paper...
That's so cute!
Hello.
Oh, hello.
Isn't it beautiful?
If you wear one of our yukata on a date,
your love will become true.
Really?
Try it on.
Okay.
It'll happen, right?
Okay. I understand.
It's fine. I'll be right over.
Stay at home.
What's wrong with Satsuki?
I'll be back.
Shu.
You said you'd protect me, didn't you?
It's open.
Welcome back. Is Satsuki okay?
Yeah.
That's good.
You didn't have to wait.
The expression on your face when you left
made me worried.
Sorry.
She gets very insecure.
I had to be there.
What happened...
two years ago?
It's got nothing to do with you.
Besides, don't even ask. It's annoying.
Why did I have to go and say that?
I'd say you've done well
to have held back for this long.
What should I do? What if he leaves?
It's okay.
I heard that he seems
to like living with you.
Huh? Heard from who?
Actually...
I have a boyfriend now.
Oh, here he is.
What?
This is my boyfriend.
Yup!
What? Since when?!
I asked him about Shusei to help you,
but one thing led to another.
From the first moment I saw you,
I thought you were great.
Really?
That's wonderful. Congrats.
Thanks.
We should double date with Shusei!
No, that's okay.
-Oh, what'll you do for him today?
-Today?
It's Shusei's birthday.
What?!
I hope it bakes well.
It's rising nicely!
Okay.
Why did you suddenly want to play catch?
Why? It's normal
for two guys to play catch.
I've never heard that before.
Hey, Shusei.
What?
Isn't it time that you stopped?
Stop what?
With Satsuki.
It was two years ago.
You've been holding yourself responsible--
Hey! You threw it too far!
Geez.
Ryosuke.
What?
Why'd you start dating that girl?
Isn't it obvious?
Because I like her.
I can't remember anything
I used to think about
before I met Moe.
Sex, right?
What kind of answer is that?
Throw it here!
SATSUKI CALLING
Hey.
Make your relationship with Aoi official.
It's unfair to keep
leading her on like this.
Aoi must be uneasy--
So, hovering around her
like a big brother...
isn't unfair?
Then I guess I'll make her mine.
Go ahead.
I made it just in time!
He's so late.
He's not working today either...
SHUSEI KUGAYAMA
Hello?
It's Satsuki.
I don't think Shu
will be coming home tonight.
He and I are even physically well-matched.
Oh, I guess you don't know
what that means.
He's back now.
See ya.
Welcome home.
Are you okay being up this late?
Just seeing your face
makes me feel much better.
Go to sleep.
Don't want to make things worse.
I'm sorry. I know it's your birthday, too.
That doesn't matter.
Shu.
Yeah?
Come live with me.
YAMATE APARTMENTS
Welcome back!
You're still awake?
Did you make all of this?
Yeah.
Can I eat it now?
Yup.
Thanks for the food.
I hope it's good.
It's delicious.
Why are  you crying?
Sorry.
What?
Say what you wanna say.
I...
just...
want to laugh with you.
What a pain.
What are you doing?
Stop it! This isn't what I want!
You want to laugh, right?
Why...
No!
Wait!
This isn't what I want!
I love you!
I love you.
I love you...
I want to be with you.
I...
don't have that kind of feeling.
Not just with you.
I just don't understand...
what it means to love.
I'm sorry.
It was a short time...
but it was fun.
I'm glad it was with you.
No, don't go!
I don't like it!
I don't want to see you hurt...
because of me.
That promise...
about Tanabata...
I'm sorry...
I can't keep it.
Okay. Turn, turn.
Hey, Kota!
What did you write for your wish
for Tanabata? Tell me.
It's a secret!
What? Just tell me, please?
No!
What? Are you serious?
That's crazy!
No way! I mean, this is how it is!
Like I said, it can't be helped!
I know what you mean. This is how it is.
Aoi's been acting weird lately.
Shusei, too.
Really?
Hello.
The fireworks festival is coming up soon.
Yeah.
Oh, yes. Here.
If you write your wish on here,
it will certainly come true.
Actually, I just made that up.
But wishes come true
more often than you think.
So, that's the last that you saw him?
Yeah. But I just wanted
to tell him how I felt.
Hey, Ryo,
is this because
of that ex-girlfriend of his?
-Huh?
-What's with that chick?
Why does she still hang around Shusei
even though they broke up?
Satsuki is kind of
an important presence in Shusei's life.
What?
When he had it the toughest time,
she was the only one who stood by him.
But that's not the same as love.
When they first started dating,
I told him it wasn't going to work out.
She had just been dumped,
and Shusei just couldn't watch
Satsuki be alone.
So, when she asked him to stay with her,
he said he'd protect her.
Satsuki...
Shu!
What's wrong?
You didn't answer my calls.
Oh, sorry.
Are you avoiding me?
No.
Really?
Yeah.
See you.
Oh, okay. See ya.
Shu, we'll always be together, right?
Yeah.
But it didn't last.
He couldn't be what she wanted.
I'm sure Satsuki realized that.
She became more demanding,
until all they did was fight in the end.
So, they eventually broke up.
But then that day...
two years ago on Christmas night,
Satsuki said she wanted to make up.
I'm waiting for you
in front of the big tree.
I'll be here until you come, Shu.
Shu, why won't you come see me?
You said you'd protect me, didn't you?
I... don't want to live anymore.
Shusei?
Shusei! Hey!
Where are you going?!
Coming through! Please make way!
Shusei!
Coming through!
Excuse us, please move aside!
Where is she?
Over here! It's this girl.
Excuse me, what happened here?
That girl seems to have collapsed.
Can you hear me?
Can you tell me your name?
Satsuki?
Heart rate 90. SpO2...
Excuse me!
-Please move!
-Excuse me!
One, two, three.
Blood pressure is 110 over 60.
How's her breathing?
It's quite shallow.
-Do you know her?
-Yes.
-What happened?
-Satsuki!
-Wake up!
-This girl collapsed.
What's wrong? Satsuki!
-Shusei, stop.
-Satsuki!
Satsuki!
The doctor said to expect the worst.
Shu blamed himself.
He stayed in front
of the intensive care unit for three days.
Miraculously, she woke up,
but then Shusei told Satsuki,
"I'll always be with you
until you are happy."
He's trying to keep that promise
no matter how long it takes.
I understand he feels responsible...
but hasn't he done enough already?
It's not fair for her
to tie him down like that.
I guess...
the two of them are special.
Even though it won't turn into love?
It seems they're destined
to stay together.
So, does that mean
you're just giving up on Shusei?
To love another person
isn't always just fun.
But it's okay to love someone
because they bring your life joy.
That's what I did.
Why?
Maybe I just want to laugh with you.
Coming through.
AOI NISHIMURA
Kugayama!
After you're done cleaning,
can you set the tables?
Okay.
It's so good to see a hard-working youth!
Hey there, heartbreaker.
Hey!
I get about ten emails a day from Satsuki.
Long ones, too. Give me a break.
Sorry.
What are you gonna do?
Until she's happy,
I'm going to stay by her side.
Even though you're not dating?
That's ridiculous.
That just makes you smug.
There's no substance to this--
I...
If it's not making you happy,
then put an end to it.
I can't do that.
Don't you get it?
The reason Satsuki is after you
is because she's stubborn
and wants to control you.
And you are using that as an excuse
to run from commitment--
I already know all of that.
Satsuki knows it, too!
All of that.
Leave her to me.
I'll take care of her.
I'm sick of her complaining anyway.
Is it time to go?
No more running.
Later!
I'm so hungry!
Oh, I know! Moe, do you want
to eat at my place?
I'll make you something really good.
Aoi!
Wanna go to the festival with me?
I know you're not busy.
No, you should go with Ryosuke.
You bought a yukata, right?
Don't let it go to waste.
It's fine. I'll wear it next year.
We should invite another guy.
Then, it'll be a double date!
Moe, it's okay.
Unrequited love is such a waste of time.
Really, I'm fine.
Where can we find a good guy?
Uh, Moe, are you even listening?
Oh!
I know!
Huh?
Sure, I can go.
I don't have work that day.
-But I don't want to be a burden--
-That's great!
Look foward to seeing Aoi in a yukata.
What?!
I certainly will.
Excuse me, Sanjo?
Sorry, I gotta go.
We'll meet you at the event on the 7th!
Sounds good.
Welcome!
Okay!
Hey, Moe. You're putting me
in an awkward spot.
Why? Is Sanjo not good enough?
That's not it. I--
You can't say there's someone you like.
Hold onto your unrequited love
and you'll end up all alone forever.
Wear this year's yukata
during this year, okay?
Okay.
Welcome to the 12th annual
Tanabata Fireworks Festival.
Thank you very much!
Ten thousand fireworks
will shoot up into the night sky
starting tonight at 7:30 p.m.
JULY 7, 2014 AT 7:30 P.M.
10,000 FIREWORKS WILL LIGHT UP THE NIGHT
You look so cute, Aoi!
Sanjo is going to love it!
Don't say that!
The bus is here.
Okay, get on!
Driver, please go ahead.
What?!
Ryosuke and I are taking his scooter.
Say hi to Sanjo for us.
You better come later.
See you later!
Hopefully, our plan will work out.
Well, if Sanjo pushes her,
I'm sure Aoi will do something.
The next stop is
Yokohama Cosmo World.
Due to today's fireworks event,
please expect the next stop to be crowded.
Please watch your step as you exit.
Aoi!
-Good evening.
Where are the other two?
Oh, they're coming a little later.
I see.
Shall we go?
Was there traffic?
Just a little.
Hey.
You!
What?!
Ow...
This isn't right!
-What?
-You've changed!
You enjoyed being with Aoi.
You wanted it to stay that way,
didn't you?
Isn't that what love is?
But what are you doing?
You're just making excuses
and putting on an act!
Leave me alone.
Shusei, you--
Stop it!
I don't care about how you feel.
But...
this.
She put this away
because it makes her think of you.
Maybe I should sell it for her.
Aoi is with Sanjo
at the amusement park right now.
I made her go.
I don't want to see her stuck
on unrequited love for her whole life.
Shusei!
You don't have time.
Thank you.
Hurry, Shusei!
You're slow!
Yeah, he is.
Wait, how are we getting there?!
What were you thinking?!
Thanks for the gift.
Now that I think about it,
we didn't spend much time together.
But I had a lot of fun.
I think it might have been
the funnest time in my whole life.
But...
I wanted to talk with you more.
I wanted to know you well.
If only I hadn't said I loved you...
I thought maybe we'd still be together.
But...
I can't erase what already happened.
Even if we can't be together anymore...
even if you hate me...
I am in love with you, Shusei Kugayama.
That feeling just won't go away.
I don't want it to go away.
Aoi.
Wanna ride this?
Sure.
Please proceed slowly.
Lane restrictions are in effect
due to the fireworks display.
We ask for your cooperation.
It's so pretty.
Please proceed slowly.
-Please follow the directions.
-Damn it!
Lane restrictions are in effect
due to the fireworks display.
Excuse me!
Please let me through! Excuse me!
Let me through!
Look out! Stop!
I need to get through here!
The lanes are restricted!
Hey, you can't go through!
Hey! Get back here!
No parking here!
Let me through! I'm coming through!
The heart-shaped fireworks
should be starting soon.
I'm sorry you're stuck with me.
Huh?
Next year, you can
take your girlfriend here.
I'd like to come again with you.
Huh?
Excuse me! Make way!
Sorry! Excuse me!
I love you.
I always have.
I wouldn't make you cry.
I like seeing you smile.
Excuse me!
I'm sorry.
Wow!
Aoi!
Hey, that hurt!
I'm so sorry!
Aoi!
Why are you here?!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry for everything!
I...
I thought I didn't know
how to love another person.
But that's not true.
I was scared.
I was scared of how direct you were.
But I'm done running.
I...
want to laugh with you.
I want to know you well.
Please be my girlfriend!
You're so selfish!
You closed yourself from me...
and decided alone that's how it would be.
Share it with me!
No matter how much grief...
no matter how much it hurts...
no matter how many tears are cried...
no matter what,
I will never leave you.
I want to be happy with you.
I'll always be by your side.
Yeah.
A face waiting for a kiss.
Hey, you're seriously making me mad!
Give that to me!
Huh?
The fireworks are over.
Not quite yet.
WE WISH TO ALWAYS LAUGH TOGETHER.
AOI AND SHUSEI
Subtitle translation by Krysta Uyekawa