Episode 36
During the Trinity,
him, as his realf hat isn't Kyawari,
becameboard himself over Taizu outside Gong force.
But he's got the virtue and the life of his country.
I've been there.
But we seem to never meet each other.
I was not surprised by your kindness.
I've been taught for ten days.
Of course you don't recognize me.
Fine.
Fortunately, I have a letter from Li.
I'm here. I'm Li Dangbangbang.
But I've seen you for ten years.
It's true that you're from the court.
You were in the capital and were taken away.
You were so full of your anger that you didn't turn back.
I wonder if you really agree with me.
I was so impulsive back then.
But I don't know how to speak.
This is how I learned from you.
I was thought that everything is true.
But it's not.
It's not because of the forest.
It's because of the temple.
As long as it's pure, it's not a theory of thought.
It's not a matter of the past.
Why do you think it's true?
I wonder if you know the meaning of Li's legacy.
It's a story of the dead.
It's a long story.
It's a story of the truth.
It's a story of the past.
I didn't expect that I would see Li's great master again.
Yu'an is enough.
Bring the body of the body here.
It's such a rare opportunity.
You're not good at it.
You're going to be a monk in the future.
I'm very grateful.
Seeing this, I can walk the capital city.
I'll let you do whatever you want.
All right.
I've done my best.
I should go back to the temple to rest.
I'll take my leave.
Take care, Mr. Zhou.
I'll see you in the temple.
Childishcore again.
Delicious.
Chinese TV劇心
Chinese
A talent like me is too far back.
What a pity.
Now this person won't see us again.
So this didn't happen?
Hurry!
Something is still there!
Quickly jaunty!
Song Chun, are you okay?
He's here.
I don't know why.
Ni Huang has been working hard lately.
He's been chasing after me.
He's been trying to get me out of here.
I'm afraid I can't keep it.
If Ni Huang has been in this mess,
I'm afraid it will be inappropriate.
Ni Huang has a son.
He's different from others.
If he can't keep it,
let me persuade him.
Chief.
It's not right to be a rich man.
We've been working hard lately.
If we can't keep it,
we will have to go back to the same place.
You're not afraid of me?
I'm afraid that I will keep it.
Do you think it's a deal?
I don't think so.
I'm afraid it will be inappropriate.
Why do you come here in person?
You're also a good person.
I'm from the East.
I'm willing to marry you.
It seems that Jiang Zomeng's strength is really beyond imagination.
Jiang Zomeng is just a matter of time.
I'm willing to meet my brothers.
I'm always the first.
I don't ask about my birth.
I don't ask about my future.
I just had a few days.
Are you trying to tell me
that the person who sent you to help me practice water battles
is also a person who doesn't know his identity and doesn't know where he is?
That doctor,
from Jiang Zomeng,
you don't know him, do you?
If you don't know his origin,
then it seems that I know him more than you do.
What else do you know?
Although he changed his name
and became a good person,
I still recognize him.
Don't you want to know who he is?
Who is he?
He's not lucky.
His name is Wei Zheng.
He was the vice general of the Cheyenne Army
and the general of the General's Army.
He's a courtier.
He's a wolf-eared man.
Jiang Zomeng is a wolf.
You're the first wolf in the world.
And Wei Zheng is under your command.
If you don't know his identity,
how can I believe you?
How to believe?
How to not believe?
Then please tell me,
is there only Wei Zheng and a Cheyenne rebel in Jiang Zomeng?
Do you also believe that Cheyenne is a rebel?
I don't know.
I was still young then.
But I believe
that those people I know
won't betray me.
Since you're so kind,
why do you ask?
Now you're talking about what's the point of betraying and not betraying.
The peace is fixed.
Crown Prince and Prince Yu won't rebel for the Cheyenne Army.
Because this case
is their most important solution.
That's right.
Who would order Crown Prince and Prince Yu to rebel?
There's only one way to achieve it.
Prince Jin?
So you've always wanted to help him.
It's really Prince Jin.
Your Highness, the weather is cold.
Please be safe.
Okay. You should go and rest.
Yes, Your Highness.
Sister Chen Fei,
I've decided to take a road of danger this year.
The world is in danger.
The future is in danger.
If you have the power to do so,
please protect me.
Yes.
Only Prince Jin can do it.
But it's too hard.
If you don't be careful,
you'll be in trouble.
You'll never be able to go back.
Who would have thought I'd go back?
Have I thought I'd go back?
Wei Zheng is different.
Wei Zheng is a Cheyenne savior.
He wants to take his own fate.
But you...
Who are you?
I've just arrived at the capital.
Many people asked me
who I am.
Someone asked me in person.
Someone asked me in secret.
They soon got the answer.
Has anyone ever asked you?
No.
No one has ever asked me.
Who am I?
I didn't expect
you'd ask someone like that.
How do you want to do it?
To save people
like Wei Zheng.
If you're a Cheyenne savior,
why don't I recognize you?
You've always recognized him.
But I recognize Wei Zheng.
He's the deputy commander of the Cheyenne army.
He can listen to you.
I don't believe you're a commoner.
We're just trying to kill him.
Wei Zheng is not good at this.
Moreover,
he can't be exposed.
Do you know Uncle Lin?
I know him.
He's really dead.
Yes.
Where is he?
The Meiling.
Where is the dead body?
The soul of the seven souls.
The world is a dream.
No one knows his body.
He's still alive.
The war is tragic.
The enemy is like a mountain.
Who can recognize who is Uncle Lin?
I know what the battlefield is.
But if you're a Cheyenne savior,
why didn't you call me
a Cheyenne savior?
Why did you call me that?
It's just a nickname.
Whether it's Uncle Lin or Cheyenne savior,
or any other important thing,
it doesn't matter.
There's a letter here.
The wind is cold.
I know that
you are my Uncle Lin.
What am I claimed to?
In the red eyes the ordinary people are optionals.
Interrogate myself forever.
Woman always thinks I'm so unreasonable.
Tired.
No fear nor hatred ever.
As far as I know,
No wonder why I cry
I take courage toNow I move
the flower of theектор
inụo
for your drama
and my love
Don't leave me again.
You will never leave me again.
But I'm no longer the same Lin Shu.
I've been taking care of you for a long time.
I should have taken care of you.
I thought I could take care of you all the time.
You've been taking care of me.
Ever since I was in Nanjing,
I've been their support for Qing'er and Yunnan.
But every time I meet any difficulties,
you are my support.
I believe you are by my side.
I believe you will come back.
Just like when I was little,
I couldn't run away from you.
My Lin Shu brother will always be taken by me.
But before the accident,
I'm afraid I'll never be able to come back.
How could you be like this?
You were never afraid of cold.
You were a little boy.
What have you been through these years?
What kind of cruel thing is it?
Can you erase all the traces of someone?
To make you look like a piece of paper?
Don't ask me first.
I'll tell you the truth.
When I come back,
I'm in danger.
I can't expose my Lin Shu brother.
I know.
Especially Dong Jie and Jing Yan.
They can't know.
I understand.
But why can't you tell me?
When I come back,
I can't let the past be my own.
Not you.
What can I do for you?
From now on,
I'm still a Suzhe.
You're still a princess.
I can't let the death be my own.
Okay.
I can wait.
Wait until you turn back to my Lin Shu brother.
Mother is back soon.
Don't let her see you crying.
It's not good.
I'm leaving.
Brother Lin Shu.
I can still go to Suzhai.
To see you.
If you really want to see me,
then come.
Master.
Come.
Doctor Yan.
How is he?
He's not feeling well.
He's having a cold.
He's in a critical condition.
He needs to be relieved and rest.
Is he a medical doctor?
What is a medical doctor?
He can't live until tomorrow.
If he's always so unwell,
and lights up the room,
he'll be fine.
But he's not well.
If he's always so unwell,
and lights up the room,
he'll be fine.
He won't be fine this time.
Next time.
We know that.
But the princess is so lucky.
Luckily you're here.
If we were to be alone,
I'm afraid we can't stop him.
Your Highness.
Master Shen.
You just took care of the Ministry of Revenue.
You should be busy.
Why are you still out?
I've been cleaning up the Ministry of Revenue.
I found something wrong with the grass.
So I'm here to help you.
I'm sorry.
I'll go to the dock to check on the wood.
The grass is good.
Brother Zhang.
What's this?
Why is the fruit so heavy?
It's like a metal skin.
It's sealed.
Why are you asking so much?
I'll give you a lot of money.
The brothers are divided.
My Lord.
According to the Ministry of Revenue,
the ship should be the sacred fruit.
Let's help them.
Okay.
Hurry up.
Although the weight is not related to the weight of the goods
that are reported by the official,
it's not that heavy.
It's not that heavy.
I'm afraid I'll be hungry.
Good.
It seems that the secret of the
grass-dried fruit is hidden in the coffin.
No matter what the secret is,
the old man in the building
is not very concerned with the official.
You have to be careful.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of it.
If you need help,
I'll ask His Highness to come and see you.
Okay.
Let's go.
Brother Zhao,
two official ships are about to enter the port.
Keep an eye on them.
Brother Zhao,
these two official ships are also wearing black.
Six official ships are wearing black.
My brother is not like that.
Who is Xiao Yu?
I don't know.
What is the place where these black goods are in the last place?
They must have chased after me.
The black goods are in the capital.
It's absolutely not a good thing.
The chief is now in the capital.
Hu De.
Yes.
Be careful.
Master Zhao, you're back.
Is His Highness back?
Yes, His Highness is back.
You have to take the goods back to the capital.
Be careful.
Don't let it get in the way.
Father.
You're back.
Go and do it.
Yes, Your Highness.
I'll send someone to pack up the stuff.
No need.
The officials are still going to be here for a few days.
I'll pack up some things when I'm back.
I'll be going now.
Master, everything is packed up.
Okay.
Father.
It's good that you're here.
But the sand is really hard to eat.
What do you know?
Yijin.
Father.
Do you still have enough money in your house?
Master Li.
What is it?
Prince Yu sent someone to bring some gifts.
He's already returned it twice.
Why is he still sending it?
Is he still annoyed?
Give it back.
This time it's not something expensive.
It's some kind of trick.
It's for the concubines.
Leave it.
I'll go and pack it.
Yes.
Prince Yu.
You've lost to me this time.
You've lost to Suzai?
Okay.
The court has changed.
The imperial court is in great danger.
We have to help each other.
I can't thank him.
But the gold, jewelry,
and the ancient words are still not familiar.
Or do you have a way
to let Prince Yu's Li Xiang enter his door?
I just know that he has to do it.
Suzai's unfulfilled child
has a weak sense of security on the surface.
But in fact,
like his younger brother,
he's not easy to get away with.
But he can still get away with
and move on with his feelings.
Don't be modest.
I still have that word.
Thank you for your help these years.
Come on, get in the car.
Yes.
Are you going out?
Although your gift is a good one,
it's still a toy.
It's too light.
I heard that Mei Changsu is sick.
I'd better go and visit her.
You're really thoughtful.
What's going on?
The brothers have been following us all the time.
But they lost the gun after they got the gun.
Where did they lose it?
The Shizi Street.
Hurry.
They lost it?
Sixth Su船 was sent here.
It was so much fire.
How could they lose it?
What fire?
Someone killed the suspect.
The fire was not in the government's house.
According to the court's law,
only those who don't know
can get out of the house.
The fire is made by the fire
that is used by the fire department.
The rest are the only black fire.
Brother Zhao,
how much is this piece of fire?
Not much.
But the Sixth Su船 is really a waste.
The fire department is not clear.
I sent people
to look for the black fire.
Who knows
if they lost it?
I don't know.
But they lost it.
Didn't they say
there was a large group of fire
that was not aware of the direction and the purpose of the city?
The fire is dangerous.
The chief always walks around the city.
Mr. Shi San,
I can't rest assured.
You must find out where the fire is.
You don't have enough people.
I'll send a companion to help you.
Yes.
We need to report this to the chief.
We need to make him more careful.
Now that everyone is in the big house
you can probably find your companion when you go out.
I'll catch him when I get home.
Greetings.
ゲ 二 三。
Your nastiest day
Back in our days,
I'm a little bit worried about the harem.
I can't take care of it alone.
Consort Xu.
I'm here.
You're the only one in the palace.
Sister Yue and Sister Yuan are three different concubines.
Your age is the longest.
You should be more respectful.
Help me to do some things.
Yes.
Do do. Hurry up and join us.
The first lady of the palace, Yu Le Cheng 94466. Come.
What's wrong, Empress?
Is there something wrong with the title?
You're just hoping I'm wrong, right?
I don't mean that.
Mother.
I used to be a good person.
I was a good person.
Your Majesty is so dissatisfied with this.
From now on...
Your Highness.
How do you feel?
I just got a cold.
Thank you for coming in person.
I'm really sorry for your visit.
I don't like the outside.
I can't take it seriously.
I'm in a big trouble.
Please take care of yourself.
Your Highness.
Something bad has happened.
Go and check.
Yes.
Fei Liu.
Let her go.
Your Highness.
Something bad has happened.
What's bad?
The palace is in a mess.
Empress...
Empress is sick.
What?
Don't worry, Your Highness.
Just go and check.
Go.
Take care of yourself.
Please.
The capital is so big.
At first, there was no way to go.
Then we went to the same road.
We went to investigate the recent
transport of the Cao Yun.
From the clear view,
the ships are all fresh,
fragrant, and rare.
The new products of Guihuan family.
The types are very diverse.
The direction is also very bad.
Many households have a prediction.
Who can find out who has the biggest suspicion in the world?
But the normal people
can't do the transport.
There should be a royal official involved.
You're right.
But most of the ships are old.
People with a big suspicion are not fully recovered.
It's hard to find out at once.
I didn't expect that there is no small mistake.
I actually...
You just said the result.
I didn't have time to listen to you.
Yes.
We found that there are four firewoods
and they were transported to the north side.
One of them was trapped in a big yard.
There is a private kitchen.
A private kitchen?
The annual government will hold a price explosion.
The private kitchen is sold and the goods are carried out.
But the private kitchen of the official
will be in the stock.
The Ministry of Revenue will stay.
So the top-ranked building
will secretly open the private kitchen.
They will transport the goods and sell them.
All the income is a little bit less.
The crown prince will be the one to take the lead.
I understand.
Although the building is closed,
the crown prince won't let go of this package.
So the private kitchen is still in operation.
These black goods
must be transported to the capital
to make the firewood.
At the same time, we found out
the new minister of the Ministry of Revenue,
Mr. Shen,
and sent people to investigate.
This is a small case.
We should report it to the governor.
Mr. Shisan, let me go.
I can do it.
I bought a piece of vegetable garden in Xi City.
The same road is now
responsible for sending vegetables to the house.
The governor has ordered
that there is a direct message
that the same road is responsible for it.
Once we find out the information
about the private kitchen,
we can send it to Mr. Shen.
I understand.
We will cooperate with Mr. Shen.
Go.
Chief,
the news from the imperial hospital said
that the Empress is not in a serious condition.
Not in a serious condition?
Yes.
Then why is the person in the Prince's Mansion
in such a panic?
It's because of the illness.
The symptoms at first
seemed to be very serious.
So it caused a panic.
But according to the doctor's statement,
it's indeed not serious.
Please ask the princess
to investigate the name of Wen'an.
I can figure out a way
to get a prescription for the doctor.
The chief suspects that
the Empress is infected.
Who is it?
It's a coincidence.
I'm not worried.
If we want to kill the Empress,
then the most possible thing
must be the princess and the crown prince.
It's because they can kill the Empress.
So it's not easy to get a prescription.
The Empress and the princess
fought in the palace for so many years.
They were very careful about her.
When the princess was in the middle of the day,
she couldn't do anything to the Empress.
It's impossible for them to get a prescription now.
The Noble Consort of Yue just recovered.
Moreover, she has experienced the court's trial.
I'm afraid the primordial spirit
hasn't fully recovered yet.
And the Empress is not in a good mood.
If it's really the crown prince and the Noble Consort,
they won't be so close.
They will get a prescription,
but they don't know the Empress is dead.
This is definitely not their way of doing it.
What you mean is
that the Eastern Palace is innocent?
Now, any conclusion is still on the line.
Maybe the Empress won't attend the memorial.
I didn't expect anything good to happen.
Maybe the Empress is really just sick.
But there are no more days left until the memorial.
If the Empress can't recover in time,
it will be a disaster.
So we must hurry up and investigate.
Yes.
I always have a feeling
that there is a deep doubt behind this.
Did I ignore any of the concerns?
I'm sorry.
Empress Yan.
Empress Laofan is here to say hello.
Empress is not in a good mood.
But the imperial doctor said
that Empress needs to recuperate for several days.
She can't get tired.
Please go back to your room.
If so, we won't disturb Empress to recuperate.
Wait.
Miss Qi Hong.
Is this the tea that Empress used for the past days?
Yes.
It's so delicate.
Your Highness.
Are you okay, Empress?
The imperial doctor said that she's fine.
Her Highness is also recovering.
She should be fine.
Then she's fine.
I'll go back to the room.
I'll go to the room.
Thank you, Your Highness.
But no matter what illness,
there must be a reason.
Your Highness.
I'm sorry.