See you later.
Your Highness.
What is it?
The balance report of the Ministry of Revenue
and the absence of the selection list
have been reported.
But it hasn't been approved yet.
And
the increase in the price of the year
should be settled.
Now the Ministry of Revenue
is full of people every day.
Who will go to see them?
It's all about the Ministry of Revenue.
Why don't you ask the Minister of Revenue?
Since Mr. He's son was sentenced to prison,
his spirit is less than one day.
He can't get up in a few days.
He's sick?
Yes.
All right.
I know.
I'll give it back to you in two days.
I'll give the two leaders of the Ministry of Revenue
the result of the selection list.
I'll give them a list of the advantages.
Yes.
If you're fine, you can leave.
Is He Jing Zhong really sick?
Is it because of the selection list?
I went to see Mr. He in the morning.
He's really sick.
His son is his son.
He's going to be taken away.
He can't bear it.
But the Ministry of Revenue is the most busy time.
All the connections have to be used in this period.
The people and the people
can't be relaxed.
If the Crown Prince is in trouble,
we can't just laugh at him
and follow him.
I'm afraid that the Ministry of Revenue
needs Mr. He to take care of himself.
I'm afraid I forgot.
I'm not in danger for that case.
But it's better to be careful than to be careful.
It's not good to be in a hurry.
But it's not as good as the water in the mountain.
Do you have any good ideas?
Wen Yuan Bo wants a life.
Then let's give him a life.
I'll tell you about it.
I don't understand it at all.
We only know Gu's disease.
Why my father didn't call you?
I'm so sorry.
Bo во phishing,
the current Apparently,
you're not as good as Mr. He is.
Bo,
Okay.
I just came in to ask them to bring in some.
Fei Liu.
How's your tiger-ball shape?
It's so comfortable to soak in hot spring.
I should go.
It's good for your health.
Here.
This is thin and thin.
It's not sweet.
I'm sure you'll like it.
I'm going to take these fruits.
He's in his own yard next year.
He's also in his own place.
This is a very rare and rare game.
It's called the game of the north.
If it's really in your house,
I'm afraid it's a bitter melon.
You're right.
This game is very fresh.
It's actually made from the silkworm.
It must be made from the official ship.
That's right.
It's from the official ship sent directly from the Linnan Manor.
It's a common ship that doesn't need to be cut off in the middle of the river.
It's faster than a normal ship.
It's a rich family in the capital.
They all like it.
It's a real ship.
They can't even grab it after a long time.
Luckily, my father made a reservation early.
That's why we have this kind of food.
So that's how it is.
It's really your favor.
You're welcome.
Just eat.
I'll give you a gift when you're done.
Mr. Wen.
Mr. Bin.
Thank you for your hard work.
Don't worry.
I've re-watched the game
and revised the game's location
according to the new year's plan.
I'm sure
I won't be able to forget the old days.
Mr. Wen is a great cook.
I'm really grateful for
the preparation of the new year's day.
You're in a good health.
I'm really enjoying
this food.
You only ate one.
You didn't eat one.
You ate several.
Are you going to
finish this dish and go back?
It's delicious.
If you like it,
I'll give you a gift later.
Why are you here today?
Her Highness the Empress is sick.
You're not going to the palace to visit her.
Her Highness the Empress is sick?
How come I don't know?
I have to ask her.
If Her Highness the Empress is sick,
I have to inform my father
to let her come back soon.
What's wrong?
Is the Empress not in the capital?
She went to the Xuan Tian Temple
and called for her.
You know my father
is a good cook.
He only wants to ask for the
Daliantan.
Without my son,
our family would be in trouble.
Her Highness the Empress
doesn't care about her.
They're always close.
My father likes to take care of her.
If he didn't have to
take care of her in the capital,
she would have moved to the mountains.
Uncle Yan is innocent.
He's like a fairy.
But why are you
so passionate
and so eager to do things?
I think
you're like a wild cat.
Fine.
You're so generous.
You're a family cat, okay?
I haven't heard you
say that in a long time.
Brother Su.
During the New Year,
are there only these people in Suzhai?
Most of them are.
But when it's the third or fourth,
I'll invite some friends.
How about it?
Are you coming?
Of course.
But there are few people in Suzhai.
It's cold outside.
It's not cold.
Brother Su,
he doesn't like to make fun of people.
Besides,
I think there are many people in this family.
Unlike our family,
after we finish the homework,
there's only me in the whole mansion.
Where's your husband?
He usually goes to the unit to practice.
You should find something.
You should take good care of yourself.
Brother Su.
Do you want to go to the
Qing House in Luo City with me this year?
Look.
This is not a good time
for you to stay.
Okay.
Come here when you're done.
Let's drink some wine together.
Then you can take me to play.
I'm sick
in Langzhou this year.
I'll feel uncomfortable.
Okay.
Xiao Fei Liu.
You're in charge of me this year.
Greetings, Your Highness.
My Lord.
Where are you going?
It's a few days.
I can go to the Palace to greet my mother.
What?
Can't you go to the Palace
and meet the Imperial Concubine?
I can go to the Palace at any time.
That's the Prince's specialty.
I'm just a Prince.
I'm not that bad.
I don't know how many
of you have fought in the Palace.
You even gave me a chance.
Are you still investigating about Cao Yun?
I'll take my leave.
I found a manga
about the suppress
in Cao with Please.
Do you see it?
I found this
in Cao Yun's gunfire.
Gunfire?
uphold the gather in the Qingyang
But because of other reason,
you said the Crown Prince and the Ministry of Revenue
were trying to get the private room out of the way.
What is all this?
Your Highness, please calm down.
I have some evidence that I haven't checked.
When the investigation is over,
I will cut off the private room.
No more questions!
Your Highness, Prince Jing is here.
Huh?
exchange
It'slie
Come on,
Break down the critical information quickly
notions
Alright
Have something to tell you
Right.
I have beenATHING
to you
And staying overnight
Because of all the trouble
Going into the corner
Right.
If you haven't ihnamed me
Why am I here?
What do you think I should do?
You'll squeeze my back
That's not it.
I can go home
I am so do!
It's another kind of brain.
It's a thought in mind.
You can listen to it if you want to.
You're a very smart person.
You should understand the truth
that the loss is too long.
Yes.
I also want to spend more time with you.
I just want you to be more careful.
I'm here to take care of you.
But you've been gambling with someone.
I know
you won't let me lose.
Let's go.
You're sick.
Take it easy now.
Don't worry.
No one sees me.
Mr. Huang,
what happen?
Can't I come for a visit?
But
there's something nice in thebolt.
Later.
Your Highness.
The Empress suddenly got sick.
I'm sure you're concerned about the cause.
What news did Your Highness get?
The Empress got poisoned by soft grass.
Soft grass?
This kind of grass
helps people to recover from the cold and the cold.
It's easy to recover.
But it can only last for six to seven days.
Why are you so sure?
When the Empress was sick,
my mother was with Consort Zhong
好像 один着
causing spots
to hub against her.
I'm sure
they just makegtz
Lord Yu was at大廁
to search for a woman
This is the harem's case.
I'll be in a hurry.
Let Prince Yu investigate.
It doesn't matter if we can't find out.
The final result is that the Empress can't attend the ceremony.
There's nothing.
When Mr. Su is thinking about something,
will he be able to hold on to something unconsciously?
I often feel like this.
Even if I'm alone,
my fingers will move.
Many people have this habit.
Yes.
There's someone I know like this.
I'll be in a hurry.
Everything is arranged.
Don't worry.
Okay.
Thank you for helping me in this big thing.
After the ceremony,
you'll have to stay away from the world.
I understand.
Mr. Jiang's gang is out of the air.
There should be some more people to guard.
You have a point.
The Ministry of Revenue is investigating a case.
I'm afraid it'll be dangerous.
Even the case of the private kitchen has been told by you.
Your relationship is getting better and better.
You know the private kitchen?
Yes.
Mr. Shen is the one who asked me to be his friend.
Of course, I'll keep an eye on him.
Are these friends worthy of a hand?
You're right.
The ones he chose are all smart and smart.
It's even more pleasant to be friends with them.
Unfortunately,
I can't be sincere to them.
I always feel uncomfortable.
It's not comfortable at all.
You should bear with it.
I'll take a good look at them.
I'll make them some trouble.
I'll ask you to help them.
You can also give them some more love.
If there's no true love in love,
what's the use of it?
I think
the two of us are too close.
As long as we're together,
why should they feel bad for us?
There's a thing that
a man can only know.
Only a sincere person can't be a man without a hand.
If it's something like a foe,
it's just sincere and kind.
It's not easy to be honest.
You're just a little man now.
You can still be a man.
Once the Crown Prince and Prince Yu notice you,
there's no more love.
I understand what you mean.
I've already walked this path.
I'm not that naive.
What you just said is just a man.
I'm afraid that
I'll be more anxious and not get it.
It's not easy to be honest with a man.
I have my own way
to deal with the strategy of the Prince.
Your Highness, you're right.
I'm a man of wealth.
Sometimes, I'm more dangerous.
Sometimes, I'm more important.
This is to see
when and where you're using it.
Your Highness, go and see the man in the yard.
He's Tong Lu.
He's the one who's responsible for
the foreign exchange.
I'm not that lucky to have him.
But his mother left me
in Langzhou by Jiang Zuo Meng.
I'm the only one who's important to Tong Lu.
I'm not afraid of anyone.
This is my sincerity.
Just leave him
carefully
I'm done with it
in the answer is check with someone else.
I was just a woman's fierce spirit.
It only blows out trees when I gather,
because I've never
put myself at risk.
I believe in that.
But do you know that if you treat people like this,
people will treat you like this.
You are so smart.
You don't understand this, right?
I understand.
But I don't care.
You can use any means to test me and test me.
I don't care.
Because I know what I am in my heart.
I have never thought about betraying.
Wrong!
Here!
Here is a chess piece.
It's wrong down there.
Here!
You come here.
You can do it.
I will do it.
I bow to Your Majesty.
You are right.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
You come here.
I haven't seen you for days.
Have you lost your weight?
Your Majesty is busy with the court affairs.
Her Highness the Empress is unwell.
I am incompetent.
I can only pray for you.
You are thoughtful.
Here.
Come sit here.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I am here to see you.
What's the matter?
The year is coming.
Her Highness the Empress is unwell.
To make the country better,
I have invited Consort Xu
to bring the Empress to the memorial.
She is a gift from the Empress.
Your Majesty, please.
Consort Xu?
You and you
are the birth mother of the Crown Prince.
I am the birth mother of the Crown Prince.
But the year is far from Consort Xu.
Besides, Sister Xu has a princess,
and she is the eldest.
She is here to bring the Empress.
I am very happy.
It's rare that you have such a brother.
Good.
This time, the court's judgment
was not only caused by my words,
but also caused Your Majesty to suffer.
Your Majesty, although you did not punish me,
I really can't bear to do it.
You can stop.
Jing Huan is too much.
I feel sorry for her.
I can't bear to do it.
I am too much.
I am not happy with it.
But the truth is that I am a righteous person.
I can only do it in my own way.
From now on,
you should be more careful
in front of the Empress.
I am sorry.
The private kitchen has been using the official ship
to send the firewood to the temple.
It has been here for a long time.
The firewood that is used every year is fixed.
But this year, there are more firewood.
But the firewood in the temple
has not entered the private kitchen.
And the spirit doesn't know
that the ghost is gone.
Maybe...
Maybe what?
Someone else is missing from the firewood.
That is to say,
there is still a group of firewood hidden in the capital.
I don't know where it is and what it is useful for.
If we don't make the firewood to be fixed,
if it is not for the sake of the firewood,
what is it that we want to do?
The private can use the official ship
and also know how to use the salt-shrine method
to make the sword-picking arrangement with the private kitchen.
He must not be a normal person in the world.
Is he trying to kill people or destroy something?
Is there any important occasion
in the capital this year to become his target?
The year is not over yet.
It is from the official ship that Lingnan Manor used.
It is not necessary to stop the journey to the middle of the world.
It seems that the Empress' illness
really has nothing to do with the Noble Consort Yue.
I'm going to leave the carriage.
Dr. Ye,
I really have something very urgent.
I must go out.
Look at how warm I am wearing this.
Moreover,
Feiliu and Li Gang will follow me.
Don't worry.
Look, the wind and snow have stopped.
You should be fine.
I said I would be fine.
You are just a cold-hearted person,
but your body is different from the normal person.
If you come back with a grudge,
isn't this clearly the sign of my demolition?
Dr. Ye, look at this.
As long as you let me out today,
I will listen to you when I come back.
No.
I said no, but it is no.
What are you doing?
Let me out!
You are not allowed to go!
Brother Su.
Why are you here?
I have been here for so long.
I have never been to your house to visit.
I am really sorry.
Is Dr. Ye here?
You are here to see my father?
He came back late today.
Are you playing the horse game?
Yes.
He has been playing the ball outside the yard.
Jin Rui, please help me to call Brother Su.
Okay.
I will go back when I am back.
Why haven't you found him yet?
Sir, you can't go out.
Your horse game was hit by a car that was hit by Ye Qing.
He is looking for you everywhere.
He is playing the game.
My horse game is more important.
Is Yu Jing alone at home these days?
I think so.
I haven't seen Marquis Yan for a while.
Even if he is in the capital,
he is always in the coffin.
Brother Su, I am back.
Is something wrong?
Nothing serious.
I just hit their horse with the car that Ye Qing gave you.
That's good.
You didn't see the Ye Qing's official
looking so dirty.
He was so mean at first.
But then he ran away.
He was not angry at all.
Although Ye Qing is a small country in the country of Daliang,
he is also the leader of the whole country.
He should choose some people, okay?
What kind of person do you think
can be a member of the country of Yi?
I feel that
the most important thing is that
when the letter was in the letter,
when the tiger's flesh was red,
it could suppress the whole nation.
It could really kill the army.
It could even prevent the rule of the country from becoming a military.
It is really bold and bold.
It is not as good as it is.
You have a good taste in your eyes.
You don't have to envy me.
In fact, in Daliang,
there was once a minister like this.
Really?
37 years ago,
the three sides of the North and East Sea
were united to fight against Daliang.
The enemy used a five-time army
to suppress the army.
When the minister was 20 years old,
he knew that the king was in the middle of the war.
He was so stubborn.
He was so brave.
The enemy's power was so strong.
He was so weak.
He was so strong.
The army of the King was so strong.
If you don't mind,
I will not be as good as you.
How could a person like me
be so brave?
I don't know anything.
When I was young,
I was not mentioned by anyone.
I was a few years older than you.
I was also told by my elders
when I was young.
37 years ago,
20 years ago,
I was 57 years old.
Is he still alive?
If he is alive,
I really want to see his talent.
Of course he is alive.
That person is your father.
Do you think
that the position of the King
is based on Yan Taishi's son?
With the identity of the King,
he can easily get it?
But my father is now...
He...
He has been a king for 40 years.
He was a person who killed Feng Yun.
It's a pity that the world is not normal.
Now, he can only fight with his husband alone.
Why do you come to my father's room today?
What is the reason?
You take the things in.
Yes.
Marquis Yan is back.
Father, you are back.
Go ahead.
No need to go.
Father,
I came to visit you
on the topic of Mr. Su.
I am Su Zhe.
I have met Marquis Yan.
I am so glad to meet the King,
ask you to talk to him.
My father is the second son of the King.
He just wants me to be with him.
Punish the father.
Pray that he also experienced death like now.
Yeah.
Lord Jiang gel is bothering me.
Mom, go and ask advice.
Little girl, hurry and get up the just genau.
Where's King Ma Tou Dan?
His home.
LiuIGNAN needs a sense of hosting him himself.
岂能受父的观解,
do NederL보请。
What did you say?
Say it!
I won't say it!
Who did it?
Your Highness.
How is it? Did anyone call?
All the things that can be used in the palace are used.
But they still say they don't know anything.
I think...
What do you think?
The poison that Empress Dowager sent,
maybe it really has nothing to do with them.
It reminds me that this whole thing
is indeed not like what happened in the Palace of the Zhao.
I understand. You may leave.
Yes.
It's not the Palace of the Zhao.
Who could it be?
You have hidden all the black fire under the roof.
Right?
You can not stand it now.
But I have sent someone to check.
The evidence is very accurate.
The past is a matter of time.
You are so clever.
Aren't you afraid of getting hurt?
The surgery is fixed.
Why bother?
I just want to ask my husband.
We will arrive at the Palace of the Zhao in the future.
You have made up your mind.
Everything will be fine before you appear.
The poison is hidden in the roof.
The ashes are hidden.
As long as His Majesty is with us,
he will be able to throw the imperial edict into the prison.
The entire base will be covered.
Indeed.
When His Majesty was in the prison,
the Empress was about to take over.
Although His Majesty and His Majesty have been together for many years,
they are still very close.
The plan is to make him poisoned.
He cannot take part in the ceremony.
Although he is a serious criminal,
he is my sister.
Sir, you are so strange because of his illness.
Did you find out about me?
The Empress is unwell.
She is very ill.
The imperial edict I sent to me has made me more anxious.
The edict?
His Lordship won't even go to the Palace for the ceremony.
This time, it was for the anniversary of the execution.
It was specially set up to prevent the execution.
Isn't it for the sake of bringing the black fire into the capital?
Your time has been chosen very well.
The black fire of the Ministry of Revenue is reliable.
Even if someone is suspicious,
the spy will surely take the Crown Prince's private room.
Although I have lost my way into the Zhou family,
you still have me.
His Lordship is willing to take the risk of killing the imperial edict.
What exactly does His Majesty want to do?
I want him to die.
What is the big deal?
It is the crime of the imperial edict.
I don't care.
As long as he can die,
I can do anything.
I can bear any crime.
Is it for Consort Chen?
You...
You actually know Consort Chen?
It is a matter of time.
Prince Qi died in a deep grudge.
Consort Chen is still in the Palace.
Although no one is mentioning it now,
after all, it has only been 12 years.
I know what is strange.
12 years.
It has been a long time.
Who else will remember
except me?
Since His Lordship is deeply in love with Consort Chen,
why did you look at her in the Palace at that time?
Because that person is the Emperor of Liang.
He is the Emperor who we risked our lives to help him
become the Emperor of the throne.
I heard that
His Lordship is the eldest son of the Yan State.
When he was young,
he used to be the Emperor.
Is that so?
He and I...
We have a great relationship.
And we have a great brother Lin Xie.
We studied together.
We were very close to each other.
We shared great peace and security.
We once had a marriage.
We were together in a difficult time.
We never met each other in life and death.
But when the Emperor was born,
there was only one son left in this world.
The Emperor of the Yan State.
When he was in the second year of the throne,
he took Yue Yao away from me.
Yue Yao was left with Jing Yu.
She was divided into Consort Chen.
I thought...
I could give up.
As long as she was alive in the palace,
but as the Emperor of the Yan State died,
Yue Yao died.
And Brother Lin Xie was in a difficult time.
If I hadn't...
trained Yuan Dun Hong Chen,
I would have been in the Ninth World.
So you've been drawing a long time.
You just wanted to kill him?
Such a generous Emperor.
He deserves to die?
What happened after he was killed?
The Emperor died.
He left a piece of the evidence.
The Crown Prince and the two internal conflicts
were all over the border.
Who was the most loyal one?
The people of Meng Yuan's body
were all scattered around them.
Yishan was in their body.
I hope Yishan is a traitor.
And Yishan is a traitor.
And Consort Chen,
she was a ghost who was killed by the Yan State.
She was innocent and innocent.
You made the Emperor of the Yan State feel so sad.
But in the end,
you just killed someone.
I don't know why,
but this is the next time.
But look at the chaos in the imperial court.
The whole country
doesn't have the same kind of
as we wanted.
This person
was the one who supported him
to leave the Emperor.
Now, Brother Lin Xie is no longer here.
This situation
should have stopped him from coming here.
My Lord,
you're not here to revenge,
but to thank me.
His Majesty is dead.
Xuanjing Bureau must investigate it.
You're here to kill me.
But have you ever thought about Yu Jing?
Yu Jing?
Yu Jing's mother passed away
after she gave birth to him.
I've never cared about her since I was a child.
It's hard for her.
She's my son.
Maybe this is her fate.
My Lord,
although Yu Jing is not the one you love,
she's your biological son.
Are you really willing
to let her be a pig's face
when she's young?
Yu Jing is a good child.
Maybe
we can't make up for her.
If you're still
guilty of Yu Jing's love for Yu Jing,
you can't go back soon.
Commander.
Is the memorial site ready?
Don't worry, Commander.
The memorial is ready.
The brothers are very careful.
Okay.
I'll go check it out.
Go ahead.
Yes.
Yu Jing.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa