Episode 13
Among the people I am here with,
these are the best in the Qing Palace.
They are also the masters of drug addiction.
Chief Mei,
you can do whatever you want.
Thank you, Master.
Have a good rest today.
I will give you a detailed review
of how to do it tomorrow.
Thanks lot.
Yes.
Soldier- tastes is great,
you should guess it as just one egg.
Cut it out,
you shouldn't had tried...
What are you talking about?
This is not a simple action.
If we don't take it seriously,
I'm afraid that we'll be in trouble for a while.
I've thought about it.
Such a dangerous action
could be done by someone.
If someone gets hit that day,
you'll say that it's the person who's the King of the Valley.
Don't involve anyone else.
Anyway, I'm the King of the Valley.
I'm the King of the Valley, the King of the Heavenly High.
I'm the King of the Valley.
I can afford it.
They can't afford it.
Why are you here, Fei Liu?
How did you come in?
Burn it.
Fei Liu, are you sure that you're going to burn it?
Why don't you let me open it and see what's written inside?
You're so cute.
The King of the Valley, the King of the Valley?
Then you have to think of a way.
Look.
I've burned it.
Where did you go?
I wanted to go to Xuanjing Temple to see Wei Zheng.
But Xia Jiang blocked me.
He seemed to be unhappy with me.
I think at this time,
Xia Shou Zun wouldn't let anyone know
that he and the King are connected.
Especially his three disciples.
Xuanjing Temple is a secluded place.
You don't want to be a pawn.
Each of them is very independent.
Although Xia Jiang is the King of the Valley,
he can't be so bold and bold.
So what news do you have to tell Xia Shou Zun?
It's better to tell him through the four seasons.
Second HD.
Make it quick.
Enter theلي JuliaSichung994466 throat젎ㅋㅋ
How did you break into fourth sister?
Is she not willing to help me?
All she says is that we shouldridge the tenet of kowtow loyalty.
If he hadn't mentioned that to Xia Jiang,
he'd only been mentioned in the Japanese media bubble.
I'd put such a Hawker in the hands of him already!
I know that you have a lot of troubles.
But Xia Jiang is too much of a person.
I'm no longer a bad person.
I'm also an old man.
Even if he leaves, he won't betray me.
So please forgive him.
I'll give him another chance to follow my path.
But remember, it's all because of you.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Miss Qin is here too.
We are all sisters. We don't need to see each other.
I don't know that you have business with Miss Qin.
You came in here so well.
I hope you don't mind.
You are the princess. You can come to my study anytime.
Who will blame you?
If there's nothing important, I'll leave first.
Please forgive me.
How is the palace today?
Her Highness said that Consort Jing got a gift from the banquet.
She has been giving gifts these days.
But since the first day, she has been in the palace for years.
She has been in the palace for three days.
I don't know why.
What else can be wrong?
You are busy with your own affairs.
There's another thing.
Your Highness, let me tell Your Highness.
What is it?
Her Highness the Empress got a secret report from the palace.
She said Consort Jing is in her bedroom.
She has set up a place for Consort Chen.
She has been in the palace for decades.
A place for Consort Chen?
This is a big deal.
Consort Jing is really on her own.
She is the most important assistant of Prince Jing.
Prince Jing must be very upset with her.
She is no longer in the position to be a law.
What is the plan for Her Highness the Empress?
Her Highness the Empress knows that she is very resourceful.
She is afraid of being caught by the snakes and not being able to catch them.
So she ordered me to tell you
that we must meet outside the palace.
We must meet at the right time.
Good.
You don't need to worry about Her Highness the Empress.
I think Consort Jing will be in trouble if she doesn't die.
This woman is really like her son.
She is so silly.
Young Master Yan.
Is Prince Ji here?
Yes.
Prince Jing is in a hurry. Please.
That's great.
I have discussed all the details about the operation.
I have discussed it with everyone repeatedly.
To ensure that everything is fine,
I want to save the route of the operation
and recommend it to everyone.
The operation will start at 5 o'clock tomorrow.
Xuanjing Temple is the most secure place to stay.
After we meet outside the palace,
she will take you to the main gate.
Prince.
Yes.
You take the food.
Stay outside and prepare the reception.
Yes.
Zheng Xuting.
You take the food and leave the place at 3 o'clock.
Yes.
Tomorrow,
Xia Jiang, Xia Chun and Xia Qiu
will not be in Xuanjing Temple.
You will be very successful in the beginning.
But even if the young master is slow,
you can only rush to the outskirts of the dungeon.
The palace will start from this moment.
Remember,
Xia Dong will not help you.
He will only watch over you.
What you want to do is to take everything
and rush to the inner courtyard
and reach the corresponding location.
Finish the mission and then rush out.
Did the poison we prepared
work at this time?
That's right.
At this time, I thank all the brothers of the Demon King Valley.
Xuanjing Temple has many soldiers.
The terrain is relatively narrow.
The poison can be used to make a huge difference.
You are all good at choosing the right one.
Once the other has the Song Xie,
you will have the opportunity to be able to attack.
Little Yu Jin,
you finally come to visit me.
You all go down.
Yes.
I only have good things to show you.
Well.
How is it?
It's a new moon.
Where did you get it from?
Sit down.
Listen to me.
The Empress Dowager and the Empress Dowager
almost all the rooms are closed.
I found some top musicians
who came to my house.
They also came out of the county.
I thought that
you are the only one who can meet the Empress Dowager.
Your Highness, you always praise me.
You are a wonderful person who knows the music and the wine.
Come, come, come.
Come on, drink.
Of course, I know.
Your ears are always raised by the Miaoyin House.
The better the music is,
the more obvious it is to you.
What's wrong with the royal court?
I'm afraid that the one who has the music
in her hand is not just me.
Miaoyin House, Miaoyin House.
What a pity.
How did they steal it?
You believe it too.
You mean that Miaoyin House didn't steal the bandit?
Steal the bandit?
Which bandit did they steal?
Is there a name?
Is there a crime in the Ministry of Justice?
Who is the main person?
Is there a根據?
There is no need to have a father.
Since they have wronged me,
why did the people in Miaoyin House
have to make a promise to avoid the crime?
It's simple.
It's a fake.
It's true that they offended people.
They offended people who couldn't afford to offend them.
If they don't run away, they will be killed.
No way.
Who dares to be so arrogant?
Your Highness, who was the one who went to arrest them?
Who was the one?
Your Highness, you don't know, right?
I heard it from the first and second.
It was a military officer who used the Dali Temple.
The one who ordered it was the little old man named Zhu Yue.
Did that Zhu Yue
hurt any other people?
Now you understand.
Zhu Yue's heart is all over the city.
Miss Gong just can't stand her.
You should hide for a while
and find a way out.
That's not right.
Miss Gong's heart...
Why do you seem to be in a hurry?
Xiao Yu Jin,
did you hide it?
I...
I didn't.
Your Highness, don't talk nonsense.
I'm so happy.
To be honest,
how is she now?
I really miss her.
When the time comes,
we must act quickly.
Once we get out of here,
we'll be fine.
When we get out,
the place is empty.
It's just right in front of Xuanjing Temple.
How can we say we'll be fine?
Tomorrow,
at the Taekang Da Dao,
the security guard will be near Xuanjing Temple
to show up.
When you get out,
Xu Fang Yin will also
catch her in front of Xuanjing Temple.
When the two teams are together,
the scene will be chaotic.
You can imagine.
The scene will be very chaotic.
I hope everyone here
can leave tomorrow.
Don't leave any of them.
Understand?
Yes.
Your Highness, don't think too much.
Actually, I didn't hide Miss Gong Yu.
It's just that after she escaped,
she was in a difficult situation and asked me to help her.
I was already a guard.
But she's doing well now.
She even made a new song.
When I gave her the gift of the New Year,
she listened to it quietly.
Take me to see her.
How can we say that we're old friends?
When she's in trouble,
I can't go to see her.
But...
But what?
What are you afraid of?
You're afraid of that pig?
That brat can't be put in my eyes.
Even if Prince Yu knows,
he can't be turned over because of this.
After all, I'm his elder.
Your Highness,
actually,
there's nothing to take you there.
It's just that Miss Gong Yu is in a deep state of depression.
I'm afraid she doesn't want to see you anymore.
What are you talking about?
What kind of person am I?
Can I be like those people?
I can't go on like this.
Let's go.
Let's go now.
Your Highness, don't worry.
It's already late.
Alright, alright.
I can't stand you anymore.
I'll just take care of Miss Gong Yu.
I'll take you there tomorrow.
Let's talk.
Master,
the Marquis of Yan's mansion just sent someone to send a letter.
He said that he needs to know about it.
Look.
It's Yan Que?
Yes.
Master, what's the matter?
Yan Que asked me to come to the city tomorrow
to have a meeting with the Marquis of Yan.
Tomorrow?
Marquis of Yan and you
haven't been here for years.
But now that you're here,
I'm afraid that's not his purpose.
No matter what his purpose is,
I have to go.
Why?
He said that he has the most memorable news of me.
Master,
does Yan Que know about the Marquis of Yan?
It's been more than ten years
since he's been here.
I'm afraid that's not his purpose.
It's not his purpose.
I have to go.
I'll go with you.
Are you ready?
Yes, Master.
Yu Jin.
Father.
Are you ready?
Yes.
We can leave now.
Let's go.
Yes.
These days,
I'm impressed
by the way you played the military tactics.
I really admire you.
Actually, there's no difference
between this battle.
I know the bottom line
of the enemy
based on the terrain of the battle.
And I can play the military tactics
in the process of battle.
I'm sure that
you can play the military tactics
based on the terrain of the battle.
These are the basic methods
of using troops.
Do you dare to ask
if Master Mei has ever been to Dagozhang?
It's a pity
that you can't
lead troops like this.
Brother.
It's the first day of the day.
You're going to Mount Gu today.
I've only seen him once a year.
I don't want to lose him.
You know
what your intention is.
The mountain is big.
I'll add more.
By the way,
there's something
that I want to trouble you.
What is it?
I'm sorry.
I just found an important witness
in a case.
He lives in Chizang Town,
North Street.
His name is Jiaxi.
I'm afraid that he'll be around
in the future.
So,
can you please
take care of him
and bring him back to me
to be safe
and sound?
Leave this matter to me.
Don't worry.
I won't be wrong.
Thank you, brother.
I'm sorry.
I'll leave now.
Let's go out together.
Okay.
Your Highness.
Everything is ready.
Thank you, brother.
What did brother and sister say?
Let's have a toast
for Nie Feng.
My Lord.
I didn't say that you'd come today.
It's a big day.
I didn't prepare anything.
It's okay.
I just need to find a room
and prepare some hot tea.
I need to bring an old friend.
Yes.
Brother Xia.
I can't find the Hanzhong Temple.
There are many places to go.
Brother Xia is coming here
and he's even more late
than my car.
Yan Zhi is not Yan Hou.
You should go first.
I brought you here
to kneel.
Why are you following me?
Hurry up.
Father.
Are you really going to kneel?
I'll kneel for two days.
My Lord.
I'll take my leave.
Father.
The baby got into a bad condition.
It was a little bit bitter.
I think Yu Jin is fine.
He's quite similar
to Yan Hou when he was young.
Brother Xia.
There aren't any toys
like this when I was young.
But the children
always grow too fast.
If Brother Xia's children are still alive,
I'm afraid that the three of them will be similar to Yu Jin.
Did you ask me to stand here and talk?
How dare you!
Brother Xia, you're too much.
Your Highness.
You're orderly.
Please find a source to enter the palace today.
And stay with His Majesty.
Enter the palace?
Is there anything you're afraid of?
Since you want to have his help in the palace,
I'm sure you'll have his help.
Is it today?
Yes.
The tea in the coffin is called Yi Jue.
I'll have some tea.
Brother Xia, please have a taste.
Marquis Yan said that
knowing the way I've been thinking about
is like having a child.
Back then,
you were so eager to marry the princess of the Hua Clan.
You were so eager to marry her.
As for your wife,
you were so eager to marry her.
Although you've been married for many years,
you're still your own son.
You're still your own son.
You're not the wife of the Hua Clan
who's been married to the same family.
This is my family business.
Marquis Yan, please take care of it.
If you really don't need me to take care of it,
why do you have to come here?
I just wanted to ask you something.
Since you didn't tell me
where my son was,
why did you say that today?
I thought
we didn't want to tell you the truth.
Actually, you're wrong.
Since Madam Sun left,
she didn't tell anyone about his whereabouts.
Really?
Yes.
I think he must be very anxious.
Think about it for him.
He saved the palace of the kingdom
because he was kind at that time.
He loved the family and loved the family.
But he didn't want to have
such a person who would be so willing to give up.
He didn't have a heart to give up.
Later,
he realized that
you two didn't have a chance.
But you didn't want to give up.
That's why he took the son out of the palace.
He hid his whereabouts.
I think
we should talk to him.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Eunuch Gao,
how are you feeling today?
I'm fine.
I'm not feeling well this year.
I'm a little nervous.
I'm happy to see
the new piece of chess in Nanzhou.
Since that,
why did you invite me out today?
Please listen to me.
When Madam Zun left,
she didn't tell anyone about her whereabouts.
It's true.
But
just five years ago,
she still brought me some news.
Why did she give it to you?
I'm afraid you were kicked out
because of the old people in the capital.
I'm the only one left.
Did you forget
your own handwritten letter?
What did she say?
She said she was seriously ill.
I'm afraid she didn't have much time.
I think she had a problem with her health.
She was so ill that she could only take one or two days off.
What else?
And Ling Lang was still in a bad mood.
He was still young.
Do you think I'll believe you?
No.
Brother.
The letter is here.
Do you believe it?
You two are brothers and sisters.
Even without the couple's feelings,
you should still recognize her.
I have one last thing to say.
You can keep on thinking.
Why didn't you tell me at that time?
The letter was written to me.
She didn't let me tell you on the letter.
So
did the content on the letter tell you
when and when
I decided to do it?
When I got the letter,
I didn't want to say anything.
But I suddenly wanted to say it today.
That's it.
Master.
Calm down.
Master Yan.
If I'm not mistaken,
Prince Jing is going to jail us today.
Master Bang, Shanghai maintaining master
Rebecca Lee, Shanghai
noodles,
to the Young Master.
It's Young Master Kang and Young Master Tang.
Go and bring them to Dongyue to see me.
Yes.
After you.
Go!
The most exciting game online is
Ma Jiang Hu Le
Ma Jiang Hu Le 2
The Queen of the Rally
The King of the Rally
The Rally?
Of course, it's the Rally of the Rally
The one who saved the King of the Rally
What do you mean?
The King of the Rally is not a bad person
If you hadn't taken me away from the King of the Rally
I wouldn't dare to do it
It's been a long time since I came here
I've been thinking about you drinking a cup of tea
I don't know when Marquis Yan started to do things for the King of the Rally
You've been pretending to be the truth these years
Even I really thought you had been disobeyed
Brother Xia
Since you thought you were a few-fold ill, you still haven't changed
I think for you, maybe in this world
You haven't decided the crime yet
Only the crime you didn't think of
But the crime of holding the crime of being a traitor
You have no reason to be at fault with a King
Xia Jiang
Don't you think your idea is a bit crazy?
Did I wrong her?
Did she dare not to seek justice?
To be honest, I was really afraid she would go back to the Rally
To be the father and the son-in-law
But I believe in the King of the Rally
But I won't let her down
As you said, the King of the Rally
She will
But think about it, she's not a fool
Your idea of the Rally is like a dragon's talk
I'm afraid she would be too much to do it
So you're the one who asked Lord Yan to leave me?
Maybe it's not just me
Master, Dong'er has already asked Xia Qiu to help him
I believe that these two are not helping him
If Xia Chun doesn't come with me today
You guys should have a way to lure him out of the city
Gao Jie is not here
The King of the Rally is alone
Maybe there's a chance of winning
I remember it was many years ago
You just made a mistake
Not like now, you always bring your imagination to reality
Why are you suddenly like this now?
Are we too late?
Or are you changing too quickly?
Is it really just my imagination?
Chun'er, explain to Lord Yan
Yes
Lord Yan, Lord Jing has already taken the Daoist
But these two days, Lord Jing has added two times
The amount of military supplies he has set up in my side
What a pity, Lord Jing has won a battle
I'm actually encouraging him
I'm going to fight him and give him a chance
To strengthen his confidence
To make him feel that he has the hope to save the people
Especially when he has an inner strength
Why did Xia Dong suddenly start to suspect me?
I still don't understand
But this time he's helping me instead
Did he help you?
I was originally worried that Lord Jing's confidence
I was originally worried that Lord Jing's confidence would not be enough
If Xia Dong had it, he could have helped him
I'm not fighting in the dungeon's position
To defend the military supplies
If Lord Jing wants to know something, I will tell him through Xia Dong
If I had a secret ally like me
Lord Jing would definitely feel that the plan is very smooth
The success has already been held in his hands
Are you saying that?
Xia Xun's words just now
Isn't it too exaggerated?
The dungeon of Xuanjing Temple is indeed a high-level strategy
But now, the main point of the progress is no longer there
If there is a hidden reason for Xia Dong's actions
There is a possibility of a breakthrough
Aren't you really not afraid that your own disciple will take someone to the dungeon
And put Wei Zheng away?
That's right
You are talking about a difficult topic
I know the disciple I taught
He indeed has the ability to take them to the dungeon
But Yan Hou
You think that if you break through the dungeon, you will find Wei Zheng?
No...
They must be알 Kolubel's otherwise
What to do
I can only wait like this?
You have your own battlefield.
It's a pity that I'm a good dungeon.
There's no place to hide today.
I'm just not satisfied with the fire.
I'm not satisfied.
As long as you hide from the next door.
Master, you haven't said that there's a fire.
Because you can't let this matter know.
Of course, I won't let you know.
Because in his heart, he doesn't care about that person anymore.
Maybe at this moment, you still care about him.
Xia Dong, since you were a child,
your west side,
your church, your work, you are rich.
But when you were caught by the fire,
you didn't care about where he was.
You didn't care about him at all.
Maybe he's standing at the door.
The wind is blowing.
The clouds are falling.
The world is chaotic.
The sky is blue.
Snow is melting.
Who believes in the fire?
The fire is burning.
The love is eternal.
The sword is cutting the red smoke.
No need to say.
It's not easy to throw away.
The cold heart is broken.
The night is falling.
The year is passing.
The wind is blowing.
The world is chaotic.
The water is not sweet.
Snow is melting.
The year was yesterday.
The shadow is back.
The wind is blowing.
The world is chaotic.