Episode 14
That is the place where the emperor was imprisoned.
Go and have a look.
The emperor is misunderstand.
a descendant to the powers
Nailed it!
Don't worry
The testament
Yes.
I've already made up my mind.
I must do it.
Today, I'm not telling you to discuss.
I'm just asking you to deal with it.
Your Highness, I'll be responsible for your decision.
I want to re-examine the treasonous case
13 years ago.
Re-examine it.
The blood of the emperor
and the ink on the stone
will be the ink.
I won't let it go.
Are youORE
sure that you already want to re-examine it?
Family tricked from me and asked me to arrive in Whirajia.
But now I have to get to your place.
OK.
He's fine usually.
bye bye.
See youおい儿.
Bye.
Go.
The old see is just for fun.
Stay there safe and sound.
See you at Zingrin Airport.
You're different from Jingrui.
You're very less like the general.
This place is full of silver and map.
You can find it on the way.
Take it.
Qianzhou, the road is rocky.
It's a place where the imperial guards are.
I'm really worried about you.
No matter how far the road is, I'll go.
I'll go.
No matter what she did,
she gave birth to me.
Now she's dead.
I think what I can do is
to take her back to the sea.
I thought you were a little girl.
You really wanted to see you.
I didn't expect that after so many things happened,
you became the strongest child by Princess.
My brother is not here.
My mother is not here to take care of me.
If you have time,
help me take care of her.
Don't worry.
Take care of yourself.
I'm going.
Let's go.
Good luck!
Xie Bi has left the city.
Yes.
Take care of her on the way.
After all, she's a innocent child.
Yes.
Did you find out anything?
Not yet.
Qian Zhou Mountain is far away.
I don't know how much pain she's going to suffer.
Second Young Master is very serious.
She won't be in trouble.
Who are you?
You are assassins!
Move!
Protect Princess Zhang!
Who are you?
Let her go!
Don't let her run!
Jing Rui.
What are you doing?
I'm going to kill you.
You're back.
Mother.
Are you okay?
Good!
If the patient can be like you,
she'll work hard and work hard.
She's much better than others.
Come on.
Let me check.
You ask Chang Su?
Does he sleep?
I don't understand.
Okay, okay.
Come on.
I still don't understand.
But I think you're not asking about Chang Su's health.
You're asking about the situation of Mrs. Nie in the prison, right?
I'm smart.
You don't have to worry about Chang Su's health.
Mrs. Nie's problem is not about me.
I'm only concerned about you.
The situation is getting better.
But you can't work too hard now.
Go to bed.
Listen to me.
Mr. Lin.
Are you still here?
Thank you.
What are you shouting?
Found it.
What?
We found the ice-cream grass.
We just sent it from the East Sea.
There's no damage.
We used a glass bottle to pretend it.
Be careful.
It's not broken.
Have a look.
Right.
That's right.
It's ice-cream grass.
That's good.
I'll go and check.
Okay.
I found the medicine.
When are you going to start?
Right.
What are you going to start?
The Old Master.
Wei Zheng.
I really don't want you to be disappointed.
Ice-cream grass is a rare medicine.
You can find it in the pharmacy.
It seems you've spent a lot of money.
But who told you?
The ice-cream grass is useful to the doctor.
It's the Old Master?
Mr. Lin.
What did you say?
What's the matter?
The Old Master told me
that ice-cream grass can be used to cure the cold.
You can't use it, right?
Yes.
If you can't use it,
even if the Old Master is out of the hospital,
I can still find it.
When did my father tell you about the ice-cream grass?
That year.
I ordered to go out with the Old Master.
We were on the fake board.
He had a drink and talked to us.
He said there was a mark in the wolf's tooth.
He said ice-cream grass can cure the cold.
But he didn't admit it when he woke up the next day.
He said it was the fox's mouth.
Maybe it's the fox's mouth.
How is that possible?
I've seen it in the wolf's tooth book.
There's really a book.
And there's a mark on the book.
There's a picture on it.
It's the same as the one.
When did you read it in the wolf's tooth book?
I...
There's a mark on the book.
But since there's a kind of medicine
that can cure the disease,
why haven't I told you
for so many years?
I asked you to find it.
Jingrui,
if you come back earlier,
the fox has already gone to Qianzhou.
I know.
He's recovered.
He'll be back soon.
Before he comes back,
I'll stay with you.
I'll be back soon.
Okay.
I'll see you later.
Bye.
Jingrui,
that assassin last night,
why did he kill me?
I'm already
a person with no family now.
Who wants me to die?
No matter what you decide,
have to give me your problem.
If I don't use your word for nothing,
I'll have penalties from now on.
Please forgive me.
OK.
Maybe...
that's why...
I won't show anyone this book.
I won't show anyone either.
I don't want to know what you've done before.
I know best.
I know why I promised to help her with this book.
It's just because of her hope that she wants to save her life.
I don't want to know the contents of it.
Jingrui, do you want to see it?
Mother's safety is the most important.
If you want to know how to deal with those who have been involved in the operation,
if you don't want to know the contents of it,
then you can see it yourself.
No.
If you want to see it, then you can see it together.
If it's a long-term wound,
then it's better for both of us to bear it alone.
I don't want to know the contents of it.
I've thought about all of these.
But there are still some records on the ancient books.
The ice and blood grass are all in the blood.
Someone has been living for a lifetime.
It's hard to find a place to live.
I think maybe the young master doesn't want us to risk it.
So you can't tell me.
You really know how to guess.
He doesn't let us say.
You think my father and I are like you?
Master Lin.
I haven't finished yet.
That's why I don't say.
It's because it's useless.
Since it's useless,
why do you have to say it out?
It's so hard to think about it.
How could it be useless?
It's really a good thing.
It's a good thing.
How do you know it?
I don't know.
But I think you know it.
Okay.
You guys listen carefully.
The law is in another book.
It's useless to read it.
It requires ten people with perfect strength,
and a lot of people with perfect blood.
And a new blood.
After a new blood,
the patient can recover.
But in the process of ten people,
it's not just painful.
And they will eventually die of blood.
Just put it simply.
It's ten times faster to take the ice and blood grass to save people.
But we can...
You don't have to tell me you're willing to do it.
If you want to find ten people
who are willing to kill Changsu,
it's not hard at all.
But have you thought about it?
Is Changsu willing to do it?
Mr. Lin,
can you do it secretly?
No.
You know it's a secret.
The two states must be absolutely focused and clear.
No one can be careless.
You can even say that the patient is active.
You can say that the patient is active.
And the ten people are dying of blood.
You all know Changsu best.
If he does it,
it's better to kill him.
The person who was cured of the poison a hundred years ago,
is the one who took ten people
who are willing to give their lives to him.
He is alive,
but he lost the moral of the new pearl.
The moral of life will be lost if he gets it.
You know very well
which day Changsu will choose.
Why?
Why do you only think that the person who lives his life is alive?
But someone who is clear and righteous in heart
is going to die.
It's so cruel to make such a choice in heaven.
Is it not fair to have two people in the world?
Why is it not fair?
In the eyes of the world,
life and death are great things.
But the world is big and the world is busy with the world.
The life of the living is not the same.
How long can one live?
What's the decision?
The person who was cured a hundred years ago
was alive,
but what he lost
is not something more important than life, right?
My praise will be second.
He owes day after day the whole world is conviction,
holding a statue as Buddha.
If you really understand what his heart is,
just forget about this and beg farewell.
If he is still alive
and doesn't want to push me further,
Please say again.
No!
Jingrui, you can't go.
This case gained its justice
What do you want to do?
What can you do?
Mother, I don't know what I can do.
I just know that I can't do anything
to face this kind of truth.
Jin Rui, you don't know.
You don't know how much he hates you.
Back then, no one was in the harem.
But he didn't listen.
He didn't listen.
Sister Jingyang,
Consort Chen,
Prince of Qi, Jing Yu.
When I saw them die,
I knew
he had the most cruel and cruelest death in the world.
That's because he didn't listen to the truth.
He thought...
You don't understand!
This is the biggest evil in his heart.
Whoever dares to touch it,
will be punished for his high and high rights.
There will be no good in this.
Think about it.
Mr. Li Chong,
the Grand Tutor, the Prince of Ying,
who is not the one who clearly states that the world is full of people,
but the result?
No one can stop the heart of a cold-hearted emperor.
Jin Rui,
can you still tell the world
what the Emperor has done?
Mother,
we didn't see anything, did we?
The truth is in my head.
It's like we've never read this book, right?
A generation of the late king,
a generation of the famous,
70,000 souls,
many people's clear and ideal in their hearts,
just like this,
buried in the world.
Jin Rui,
I know Mother's thoughts,
but the truth is the truth.
Maybe we can't change
all the black and white that has been stolen,
but at least,
we can't be the helpers of the hidden ones.
But you can't do it.
You've spent more lives
than the lives of the people in the White House.
You can't do anything.
Jin Rui,
you're my child,
my flesh and blood.
I can't just watch you die.
But Mother,
someone has already stolen this book.
We can't be the helpers of the hidden ones.
I can't do anything,
but for you,
I won't be the helpers of the hidden ones.
Let's hand this book
to the crown prince.
Mother said,
Prince of Jing?
Yes, Prince of Jing.
Jingyan has taught me
that there is no source
between brothers.
And Lin family's little books.
They are best friends.
If anyone
really wants to be the helpers of the hidden ones,
then Lin family's wish
will be granted.
Princess,
the letter from the Eastern Palace is here.
I've talked to Marquis Yan.
He's absolutely fine.
Marquis Yan is just a choice.
It's the best way to
make Princess Liyang's appearance.
Are you going to the Eastern Palace tomorrow?
Yes.
Before we discuss something,
I want to tell Jingyan.
Yes.
Dr. Wang.
Why are you talking to me so early this morning?
There are alreadyately 18 bottles of load tonight.
The Qingming people of the world can soon be reborn.
Why do you have to say that?
You can't be the same as before.
Even if this case is completely broken,
I can only admit that I didn't sing.
I can't turn back to the forest.
Why is that impossible?
As long as you are wise and wise,
you can definitely get back to your original identity.
If anyone dares to do anything to this person,
Listen to me first.
Everyone knows what kind of person Su Zhe is.
As a ghost,
he is a ghost.
Although he has the power to take power,
he is not a righteous man.
But...
Jingyan,
the problem is the ending for me.
But to you,
everything just started.
What should we do?
You are the future emperor.
You must clear your nose,
strengthen your people,
and make a big change in the history of the past decades.
You must give the world a clear and honest rule.
If you want to achieve this goal,
you must have a perfect start.
The King and the Queen of the forest are still alive.
They also hope that in the people's heart,
you are a friend and a friend.
You are a princess without a single word.
I can do it.
I believe you can do it.
So,
you must not have such a plan.
Otherwise, the world will misunderstand you.
They think that you like to control the whole world.
That's why they are our first priority.
But this is not an explanation.
I have been in the capital for a long time.
The two years of the feud between the two great families
have nothing to do with me.
Moreover,
my hometown is already under construction.
I don't have any traces of the past.
If I only have you two to testify,
I will say that I was the leader of the forest.
It is also too much of a matter of time.
It is hard to believe.
I don't want to be a coward
and make people guess
that the truth is hard to be revealed.
I will not waste my efforts for the next 13 years.
I will report it.
Young master.
Mother.
It is because of your hard work for the next 13 years,
I can't let you suffer again.
If the world misunderstands you,
it is the world's misdeed.
Why do you mind?
To be honest, I really mind.
I hope you also mind.
Only by putting the world's views in your heart
can you understand the nature and the contract
and become a great ruler.
Young master,
what you said is two things.
Actually, it is not wrong to not do it back to the forest.
I have been doing the 13 years of the Meichang tree
and I am used to it.
Let the forest
always keep everyone's memory.
Isn't that good?
Your Highness,
please show me the Princess of Yang.
I got it.
Your Highness.
Aunt.
Jingrui is back.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Aunt, please.
Greetings, Princess of Zhang.
Jingrui, long time no see.
I didn't expect to see Mr. Su here.
When the snow wolf came out,
I knew that Mr. Su was not a loyal person.
Today, it seems that he really has a good sense of humor.
Your Highness, thank you.
I admire you, Your Highness.
I have a few things to say to you.
I am a great person.
I am not afraid to do anything.
Jingyan,
I have something to discuss with you.
It is not convenient for outsiders to be here.
Please, Mr. Su, please.
No need.
Mr. Su is like me.
What can I say to you
is also possible for Mr. Su.
I think you came today
to leave the memorial book
for Lord Xie to leave.
How did you know?
I made the decision to leave the memorial book.
I think you have seen the content
written by Lord Xie.
I don't know what you think.
You knew the content of the memorial book long ago.
I know what it means.
The world doesn't know.
Princess of Zhang,
you are close to the Qin Tong family.
I don't know if you have ever
dreamed of this for years.
I have never dreamed of this.
I can't believe
this is the last time I have heard this.
The memorial book
is my favorite.
Since you knew
the content of the memorial book
long ago,
you wanted it.
Actually, we came today
to give this memorial book to the crown prince.
Since that,
I want to help the princess.
Brother Su,
how many days have you been in the family?
Aomensheng Pujing Entertainment Center 94466.com
The most exciting PG game online.
The horse is running.
The reward is given to the queen,
the treasure is given to Huang Jincheng,
the talented cat,
the reward is given to the head of the family.
The super high-payment rate,
the reward is given to the judges.
The reward is given to the rich,
the Northeast亞.
Subscribe now to our channel.
And have fun on the Hong Kong Mid-Autumn Festival üzerine..
Sasha will win.
Since prince Tu is here,
lings,
we can discuss this issue.
Jingrui,
it was limited
till you did it.
Aunt,
since I confess to you,
there's absolutely one thing
you can do.
Everyone give a moment
Oh, my God
Business
Bump
Yeah
You
Did Yuji Song cold feelings try to be crossed?
What was wrong with him?
He just wore white and green gl오ut !
Both the two alternative aluminum shoes
got le tuned ontop of themselves
since she was ok with having a commonator freedoms !
You just got a message from Heheui...
You...
Again and again I will expose you
and rest you head on,
will swallow innocent Rutang for fear.
Get to husband and inte surgeries,
and not relationship with he Qing.
Take this.
I see.
Get up.
After you get heavily punished,
Zhuo will serve you as your clan has always do.
Handle one礼 when your Achilles's new crown.
Cheers.
Call him, if there's something you need.
In a few days, it will be the day of father's birthday.
The royal court will be in charge of the funeral.
This book is Xie Yu's handwriting.
And aunt is Xie Yu's wife.
I want to greet aunt.
I want to help this book with the hundred-point request.
To bring Xie Yu to the funeral.
What did you say?
Aunt knows.
The most important thing in father's life is that he is highly skilled and not easy to challenge.
This case concerns his life.
No matter how I want to make him regret,
he will never make a mistake and leave a grave for the future generations.
So I have to create a situation where the people are suffering.
A situation where he is completely out of control.
No matter if he is willing or not,
he must agree to this case.
But this situation needs aunt's approval.
No, no.
Mother.
Your idea is too bold and reckless.
Don't worry, aunt. No matter how aunt sees it,
I will protect aunt's safety and won't let you get hurt.
If you are so stubborn, how are you going to protect me?
Since I have decided to leave this house,
I have already made a complete arrangement.
Father, now you are no longer the father of that year.
Zhi'er, you are no longer the king of that year.
What I want to do is to wash blood and purify the world.
If I don't have the back of my head, I will never have the courage to do anything.
Jingyan, no matter what you say,
you let me take this case seriously.
It's not a matter of my consciousness.
If I hate you, I will do it.
What's the point?
I will do it.
Your Highness, the Court of Judicial Review sent someone here
to report something to you.
I am sorry.
Greetings to Noble Consort.
Thank you.
Is there anything wrong with the Court of Judicial Review?
Consort Xian is in the palace.
She is in a bad mood.
She was just making fun of His Majesty.
She suddenly started to get angry today.
She said something nonsense.
The Court of Judicial Review was afraid
so they asked me to come and ask you about it.
Consort Yu must have missed the late King.
I will go and take a look.
Is it good that you are asking about the court of justice?
You already know the truth about that year.
But what's the point of you after they washed blood?
Are those dead souls not in good terms with you?
Are they just strangers?
Forget it.
Today, the court of justice needs great courage.
If Princess Chang doesn't have the true intention,
she will be able to turn against the plan of His Highness.
Let's do something else.
Thank you for sending me here.
Zhi Er, take Prince Wang to the court of justice.
I have something to discuss with Mr. Su.
Take care, Aunt.
Jing Yan.
Aunt, please.
I am sorry.