=Ex-Wife Stop=
=Episode 21=
I'll take my leave.
Shaoyan,
come and get me
out of the hospital tomorrow, okay?
Nanfang,
I'm sorry.
Look how rude Su Shaoyan was.
Xiaoya was just so angry that she...
Stop.
Think about what she did.
Why are you still defending her?
Check it carefully.
Mrs. Sheng, Xiaoya,
how's Nanfang?
Tianwei,
I didn't expect you to do that.
You really let me down!
Mrs. Sheng, what are you talking about?
Mom,
say no more with her.
Let's go.
Here we are.
Get in on your own.
Won't you get in?
No.
I have a bad impression of this house.
What are you doing?
Put me down.
What do you want?
Put me down!
This is for you.
Boorish.
Shaoyan, later I got to know
that the language of lavender is
waiting for love.
I'm sorry.
Say no more.
Hello, Mickey Mouse.
Hello.
Let's have fun together.
Wait a second.
What's your name?
I don't know.
I don't have a name.
Mom, why are you crying?
Did anyone bully you?
No.
I'm just reading Dad's diary.
Mom,
do you still like Dad?
I'm not sure.
Mom,
there was a singing contest
in the kindergarten today.
I won the first prize again.
You did?
Oh, my sweetheart.
Tell me.
What award do you want?
Mom will satisfy you.
Anything I want?
Mm.