=Ex-Wife Stop=
=Episode 6=
Grandpa.
Let me flog you,
you ridiculous son.
Grandpa.
Shaoyan.
Grandpa,
I don't know what exactly happened.
But times have changed.
Nanfang made sense, too.
Why don't you put away your biases
and listen to him?
Today,
for Shaoyan's sake,
I'll let you go.
You idiot,
think about
who you should truly cherish.
(Hello, Shaoyan.)
(My company asked me to return to work.)
(They not only apologized to me,)
(but also gave me a pay rise.)
(So, it's not Sheng Nanfang
who tricked me,)
(but Zhang Tianwei.)
I blamed you wrongly
for Xiwen's problem.
It's okay.
I just don't allow anyone
to take reckless action
in my name.
Anyway,
thank you.
This ointment is effective for healing.
You can hardly apply it by yourself.
Let me help you.
If you don't answer,
I'll take it as a yes.
Did I hurt you?
I'll be gentle.
You...
Go out.
Take the ointment with you.
You're wounded, too.
Apply it.
I think
Nanfang appears
to be insensitive.
But actually,
he's very gentle.
I believe
as long as I'm true to him,
he'll feel my love.
Yes, yes.
Anyway,
your husband is perfect.
Sheng Nanfang
must have done great things
in his previous life
so that he has such a good wife
this life.
Don't exaggerate.
Anyway, if he dares to bully you again,
I will...
Nanfang,
why did you ignore my calls?
Tianwei?
Why are you also here?
Tianwei, calm down.
Stay with me tonight, will you?