=Ex-Wife Stop=
=Episode 20=
Xiaoya,
how's your brother?
Mom.
Ah?
Oh, Mom,
he's all right.
He just had minor injuries.
According to the doctor,
he can leave hospital in a day or two.
You freaked me out!
Tell me
what on earth happened.
What kind of guy hit him?
Mom,
it was...
It was me.
You?
What a girl!
Is there anything on my face?
Then why are you staring at me?
Because you look pretty.
I guess you're all right now.
I've been quite busy lately.
I'm going back to my office.
Ouch.
My head...
What's wrong?
Come on.
Let me check.
I feel much better.
It's Xiaoya's bad
for last night.
If you want to blame her,
I'm definitely on your side.
Do you know it was
very dangerous last night?
Why did you save my life?
I made a mistake five years ago.
I'll no longer leave you
in danger alone.
But aren't you and Zhang Tianwei
- already in a relationship...?
- She and I are in no relationship.
In my life,
I've loved only one woman.
Her name is
Su Shaoyan.