[English subtitles are available]
[A Different Mr. Xiao]
[Information: Ouyang Yu Gender: Male Age: 22]
Xiao Jing.
Why are you here?
Is it appropriate to make a girl drunk like this
at night?
You are
in a girl's house at night.
Do you think it's appropriate?
Meeting.
Not clouds.
How about
going inside?
[Episode 9]
Both of you. Stay.
It's my treat today.
Leave the rest to me.
You can go out now.
I'm her teacher.
I don't want to have a class.
Shouldn't
a teacher be in the college?
What?
Do college students need tutors now?
Her grandpa asked me to take care of her.
Then I'll take care of her with you.
After all,
she drank wine at my place.
It's good that you've realized your mistake.
Don't take her to drink so much next time.
Maybe Mr. Xiao is old.
You can't remember some things clearly.
At our age,
drinking is for celebration,
not for getting drunk.
Is there anything that is worth celebrating?
She can't even get enough credits.
Or in the eyes of delinquents like you,
everything is worth celebrating. Huh?
That makes sense.
After all, you are a college teacher.
You deal with so many students every day.
It's normal that you don't understand students.
I'm different.
I draw with Orange alone every day.
Then please don't harass her.
Can you take the responsibility if she can't graduate?
Sure.
You can't.
You are still not leaving?
Do you want to wake her up?
If you don't have money to take a taxi,
as a teacher,
I can give you some pocket money.
No need.
[Taxi Occupied]
♫I wonder if there is a way♫
♫To let me gradually get closer to him♫
♫Should I pretend that I don't care at all?♫
♫Looking at the book in my hands and lowering my head♫
♫Oh right, he can play guitar and let me think♫
♫I learned a song and let him accompany me with music♫
Your heart is beating so fast. What's wrong?
♫Want to ask him about weekend plans♫
♫Facing him, I become tongue-tied♫
You two...
♫Afraid he might reject me♫
What nonsense are you talking about?
♫I cried my heart out by myself♫
♫No, I've been listening to hip-hop recently♫
♫Being cool is just a façade♫
♫Actually, I can't help it♫
I'm not talking nonsense.
Look, it's thundering.
♫Hiding my love for you♫
If your heart rate is over 160 beats per minute,
it will rain.
♫I want to know if what you said is from your heart, so agree♫
Be careful. People of the Time Management Bureau may come after you.
♫Otherwise, I can't focus on class♫
♫Give me a surprise quickly, don't always give me blind boxes to open♫
♫I searched for clues to get closer to you♫
Get lost.
♫The hints are too subtle, and I can't contact you♫
Goodbye.
♫I received a message, waiting for your response♫
♫I know I'm thinking of you, and you're thinking of me too♫
What day is it today?
You made so much for breakfast.
The day of you getting sober.
Mr. Xiao.
Take in some protein.
Here.
I specially made this
hangover soup for you.
Well. Is there nothing I can eat?
Why is everything so bitter?
What?
You think it's bitter no matter what you eat?
It's because of the hangover.
If this continues,
your bile will flow backwards.
But I only drank a little
last night.
The aftereffect is too strong.
So
do you know when you came back?
23:30.
It's indeed a bit late.
A man sent you back.
A man?
You mean Ouyang Yu?
Good. He has a conscience.
Professor Song asked me to take care of you.
So during this period,
don't cause me any trouble.
Okay.
Okay. Mr. Xiao.
I'm going to get changed.
Come downstairs in ten minutes.
Okay.
Mr. Xiao.
You're really a good helper at home and during travel.
It's good you're awake.
I was so worried that I didn't sleep all night.
I'm going to get some sleep.
Okay.
Do you think...
You can be with him.
It has nothing to do with me.
But I'm worried about your taste.
Xiao Jing.
It's fine you criticize me
for my study.
But now you are
criticizing me for my taste.
What do you mean?
I mean you have a bad taste in men.
Men?
You mean
Ouyang Yu?
He is not an ordinary person.
Do you know OY?
He is OY,
the first Chinese who can
exhibit his works at Saatchi Gallery at the age of 20.
And he
has never encountered any creation bottleneck.
You can never know
what is in his head.
If
you still don't feel anything for him,
it must be because
you haven't seen his exhibition.
As long as you go to his exhibition once,
you will definitely fall in love with him.
What's wrong?
Get off.
I'm asking you to get off.
Xiao Jing,
if you apologize to me now,
I can reluctantly forgive...
Three times.
Three times!
I will change my family name if I ride in your car again.
Did you get up on the wrong side of the bed?
Why do you care so much?
I think
Ouyang Yu is a nice guy.
Besides,
if Song Yiju is with Ouyang Yu,
we can stay away from her, right?
You get off too.
Xiao Jing.
How am I supposed to live without you?
Do you want some water?
I'm going to get you a glass of water.
Bye.
Actually, I think
we should
talk.
What's there to talk about?
We both are adults.
It's normal.
No. No. No.
Actually, I am
a man of virtue.
Although
I can't compensate you
physically or mentally,
if you need anything,
just come to me.
Who asked you to be responsible?
Why should you compensate me?
I was heartbroken yesterday and used you to relieve my boredom.
Think about how I should compensate you.
Well. It's a deal then.
No one should compensate anyone.
Xiaoxiao.
Orange, what took you so long?
I was dropped off again.
Xiaoxiao. Come on.
I've saved a seat for you.
Excuse me.
Do you have your student ID card and ID card?
My student ID card. My student ID card.
Really? I reminded you.
I...
I used it to borrow some books from the library the day before yesterday.
And then...
I forgot what happened yesterday.
Think if it's somewhere else.
I'll get it for you.
I don't remember.
Where is your student ID card?
I...
Madam, what time is the deadline?
12:00.
-12:00.
-12:00?
[Sign-up Site]
How about this?
You queue here.
I'm going to the counselor. I'll help you.
-Don't worry.
-Okay.
Please move aside and keep looking, okay?
Okay.
Come on.
So handsome.
Okay.
It's almost the deadline.
You guys, come here.
Okay.
Xiaoxiao.
Have you found it?
It's almost the deadline.
No. Think again. Where did you put it?
I really don't remember where I put it.
Song Yiju from Department of Traditional Chinese Medicine.
Thank you.
Madam. I'm coming to sign up.
My handsome boy belongs to someone else.
You must try this dish.
It's my favorite.
And this.
It's Xiaoxiao's favorite.
You can try it too.
This one.
It's vegetables.
But in our canteen,
it has a special flavor.
Do you eat mutton?
The stewed mutton
in our No. 3 canteen is quite delicious.
I'm going to get it for you.
I can't taste all the delicious food in one day.
I'll come to you and taste it next time.
Deal.
That's too little.
I'm going to get you more.
Excuse me.
Which department are you from?
The galaxy.
The shredded potatoes are really good too.
Orange.
This is your extra meal.
Xiaoxiao, let me introduce.
This is my friend, Ouyang Yu.
This is my best friend, Gu Xiaoxiao.
Hello.
Xiaoxiao.
Sit down and eat with us.
No, I have a part-time job.
You guys eat.
Eat more.
Fine.
You know what?
You really impressed me today.
You were like my savior.
I impressed you?
A lot.
Oh, right.
Why did you have my student ID card?
You dropped it on the ground when you left that day.
I picked it up for you.
I wanted to deliver it to your house that day.
But
I found a man in your house.
He said he is your teacher.
Xiao Jing.
What kind of teacher is he?
He just gives classes for my grandpa.
What my grandpa did is unnecessary.
He's been on a business trip recently.
He asked his student to take care of me.
I think
he just wants to supervise me.
And he always plays tricks.
I've been having a hard time these days.
Did he bully you?
It's not that serious.
He's under 30 years old.
Every day,
he eats nutritional supplements
for health preservation.
It's like he wants to live to the age of 100.
And the soup he made
is so bitter.
Next time, throw it away.
Good idea.
Eat.
Okay.
Okay. Eat.
Here.
Chicken feet.
Yes.
Does their food
taste better than ours?
You don't have to eat if you don't want to.
Look, they are laughing again.
Can telling jokes
make food taste better?
Why don't you enable it on me?
Your mouth is unnecessary.
And your eyes too.
What a pity.
[The Hippocratic Oath]
Have you signed up?
Yes.
Then start reviewing.
Sit.
[The Hippocratic Oath]
Don't always think about
things that have nothing to do with your studies.
And don't have contact
with anyone who has nothing to do with your studies.
I...
Do you still remember the content of the previous class?
The Hippocratic Oath.
[The Hippocratic Oath]
[The oath under the sycamore tree]
Any kind of art and form,
through
countless setbacks
and repeated practice...
Good morning, Drizzle.
[Mr. Smart: Good morning, Drizzle. You got up late today.]
You got up late today.
[Drizzle: It's not late. We usually start chatting at this hour.]
It's not late.
We usually start chatting at this hour.
[Mr. Smart: Now I feel my life is full of you every day.]
Now I feel
my life is full of you every day.
I also find us congenial.
[Drizzle: I also find us congenial. So I want to ask for your opinion about something.]
So
I want to ask for your opinion
about something.
I'm all ears.
[Mr. Smart: I'm all ears.]
When do you think I can start a new relationship
[Drizzle: When do you think I can start a new relationship after being crossed in love?]
after being crossed in love?
[Mr. Smart: I think anytime.]
I think anytime.
Really?
[Drizzle: Really? Anytime?]
Anytime?
[Mr. Smart: Yes. He has become your ex-boyfriend. What's use of thinking about him? To celebrate Chinese New Year?]
Yes. He has become your ex-boyfriend.
What's use of thinking about him?
To celebrate Chinese New Year?
Then
[Drizzle: Then how do I deal with the pain caused by the previous relationship?]
how do I deal with
the pain caused by the previous relationship?
Use your new relationship to forget it.
[Funny things]
[Very sharp eyes, a strong sense of security]
Is something of lowbrow taste
[Mr. Smart: Is something of lowbrow taste the only thing that can make you laugh now?]
the only thing that can make you laugh now?
How do you know?
[Drizzle: How do you know?]
I have an ace up my sleeve.
[Mr. Smart: I have an ace up my sleeve. Haha.]
[Drizzle: Thank you for making me not heartbroken when I'm sad.]
Thank you
for making me not heartbroken
when I'm sad.
I can record my laughter for you.
[Mr. Smart: I can record my laughter for you. Hahaha.]
[He's your friend.
I'm handsome. I want to know you. Pretty.]
Hello, Miss.
Do you
need a bottle of red wine?
No, thanks.
[Mr. Smart: Drizzle. What are you doing? It's a cool night. Suitable for drinking alone. Drizzle. Have you started drinking?]
I think
you should try Astrale Rosso from Italy.
[Drizzle: I was drinking alone. But someone came to harass me.]
If you think it's not bad,
in my house,
[Mr. Smart: What? Ridiculous! I'm sending you a voice message. Play it to him.]
I have other products
[Mr. Smart]
under the same brand.
[Ridiculous! I'm sending you a voice message. Play it to him.]
Dear Drizzle, what are you doing?
I'll pick you up right away, okay?
Okay.
Sorry to disturb you.
[Drizzle: Good for you. He believed it and left.]
Good for you.
He believed it and left.
Of course.
[Mr. Smart: Of course. I'm tall. I'm smart. I'll be your boyfriend in your phone from now on.]
I'm tall.
I'm smart.
I'll be your boyfriend in your phone from now on.
Bro. Bro.
My bad.
I made a mistake just now.
Can we stop and talk?
I thought you didn't want to study hard.
Now I think that you have low IQ.
That's not what I want.
I have used
every method
for memorizing
Xiaoxiao
taught me.
But I just can't remember these.
What can I do?
Look at you.
Not everyone has a strong heart like me
to stand your harsh words.
Who asked you to come out?
I'm a ball anyway.
She won't see me.
What are we eating tonight?
All you know is eating.
Eat your graphite battery.
Xiao Jing
doesn't want to help me with my study at all.
He just wants to make fun of me.
It's here.
I'm going to catch you this time.
You thief! I caught...
you.
Hi.
Why are you here?