Yun Jae?
Still?
Are you
Gyeong Jun?
Yes, Ms. Gil Da Ran.
Let's go back to the hospital.
[Episode 2]
This is the hospital's fault.
It was medical malpractice,
so if we go and tell them,
they'll switch you back.
What do we tell them?
So you'll say
your student's soul is now
in your fiance's body?
That they should put the right soul
in the right body?
They'll tell us we're crazy,
but they'd figure out a treatment.
They'll lock us all up
in a mental institution.
My body won't be going anywhere.
It will be at that hospital.
You can go alone. I don't
want to go back there.
But you can't just hide from the problem.
Stop being childish.
But I am a kid.
I'm only 18.
Then you should listen to your elders.
Let's go, Kang Gyeong Jun.
Don't treat me like a baby.
Look at my old dude face.
This is no time to be joking around.
And this is no time for you to be
stubborn like a stuffy adult either.
Why doesn't it occur to you to ask me
the details of what happened?
Fine. Tell me.
I, Seo Yun Jae, got into an accident.
Crash.
When my life was teetering,
my soul left my body.
Seo Yun Jae's soul, thinking
his body had died,
slyly slipped into my body.
Huh?
But Yun Jae is not the sly type.
He'd never take what isn't his.
Whatever.
So my soul had no choice but to slip
into Seo Yun Jae's body.
This is all Seo Yun Jae's fault
for slipping into the wrong body.
But Yun Jae always thinks things
through very carefully.
He's the not the type to make
a mistake like this.
Whatever.
Seo Yun Jae's soul has to wake up
before we can do
anything at all.
Yun Jae,
how did this happen?
Why did you have to slip into
his body of all things?
Of all things?
I don't like being in this either.
Yun Jae doesn't drink soda.
Please drink something else.
What?
This isn't your body. It's Yun Jae's.
Please treat it with care until
you can return to your own body.
With care? How?
Do what Yun Jae always did
and drink water instead of soda
if you're thirsty.
And it's still a bit chilly.
This is too thin.
Don't you have anything warmer?
You should've gotten all the tests
done at the hospital.
There's a scratch.
Oh, no.
Hang on.
I would like my soul to be elsewhere
when you're poring over his body,
but I can't do that.
At this rate, I might have
a nervous breakdown.
Kang Gyeong Jun,
please take good care of Yun Jae's body.
He's very important to me.
I'm going back to the hospital
to see how your body's doing.
Let me see your phone.
My phone?
Who're you calling?
My maternal uncle.
Ask them what the situation is.
Hello?
Is this Gyeong Jun's uncle?
I guess they must have already
contacted the school.
We moved Gyeong Jun to Hanguk Bath Hospital.
Oh...
If Gyeong Jun wakes up,
please let me know.
Okay.
They moved your body to a hospital in Seoul.
I heard. This dude has good hearing.
So do you live alone here?
What if your uncle and aunt come over?
You can't be here like this.
I live alone.
They'll never come by.
You should go.
Will you be okay alone?
You were in a major accident,
and you're not yourself either.
This must be overwhelming.
Are you sure you'll be okay?
You're pretending to care about me,
so you can watch over his body.
I'll be fine. Go.
I'll give him a good night's sleep.
Only sodas and frozen foods.
Is this all he eats?
He's huge.
Too big.
I don't have to go to school.
Yes!
Oops.
All for his precious body.
"Please take good care of it."
I won't eat any of this.
You're in there, right?
Right?
Are you cold?
Your hand's so warm.
Maybe it's because I was holding
the coffee with it.
They say your hand temperature mirrors
the temperature of your soul.
Your hand's super warm because
you're a warm person.
I bet you have the warmest
hands in the world.
It's warm.
There is only person
who has such warm hands.
And here you are.
[Gil Family Dumplings]
Da Ran just got in.
She spent the night out.
I bet she was with Yun Jae.
It's our daughter we're talking about.
They'll be married in a month
anyway. Who cares?
I was actually worried something
might be wrong with Yun Jae
because he always brought Da Ran
back home so early.
But no more worrying.
Should we ask Yun Jae over for grilled eel?
Don't make it so obvious.
You'll embarrass the kids.
You're right.
You have to do it less blatantly.
How can we make him eat eel
without his knowing though?
We can make dumplings with eel.
Eel dumplings.
Should I grow facial hair?
It's not my body anyway.
Why am I itchy all over?
Does this dude have skin problems?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Da Ran,
he looks like Yun Jae.
Hang on. Hang on.
Gil Da Ran!
Yun Jae...
Give me some money.
- Just $10.
- What?
Hurry up. Hurry up. Hurry up.
Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry.
- Oh my gosh.
- Go.
Go away.
I'm going to lose it. I'm burning up.
What?
Help me.
Look at me. My body's on fire.
You're nuts.
Come. I'll show you.
Who is he?
Da Ran's fiance.
What's wrong with him?
- Hurry.
- What happened?
It's itchy and hot. It's driving me mad.
Oh my goodness. What's going on?
Something's wrong with this dude.
Is he sick or something?
Look.
The legs, too.
Hold still. Hold still.
And the butt.
What are we going to do?
- How did this happen?
- I don't know.
Please.
Oh, mother. Oh, father. Oh, please.
Oh geez.
Oh, yes. Right there.
Oh, please. Geez.
Such a vile act on school grounds!
It's mushroom allergy.
You'll be fine once you take the medication
and put the ointment on.
I should have asked you about his allergies.
I feel dizzy.
Is our school infirmary a free clinic
or a public hospital?
I'm flabbergasted.
Is he mentally challenged?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I spent all the money I had
on the cab fare yesterday.
His body was acting up, but I
couldn't go to a hospital.
I came to you because I was worried
something would happen
to your precious fiance's body.
Did you get chewed out badly?
Do you feel better now?
Yeah.
This dude must be really healthy.
The medication is working wonders.
Go home and have some lunch.
And don't forget to take the medication.
I wouldn't have had to bother you
if I only had my wallet.
I'll pay you back once I get my wallet back.
Did you get yelled at?
I'm just upset.
Yun Jae is smart and has great manners.
I don't want people thinking
he is mentally challenged.
I feel so bad as to what this has done
to his reputation.
Go home and stay put.
Don't go out and cause trouble again.
I'll bring you whatever you need.
Bring me what I need?
I'm all set.
Don't worry about me.
I can take care of myself.
Head straight home.
Don't go anywhere else.
This is a cool shirt.
It looks awesome on my real body.
It looks stupid just because
it's on this body.
I can dress like this
once I get my wallet back.
[Gil Family Dumplings]
[Donate to Hanguk Bath Hospital]
Yun Jae,
it'd be nice to see you.
The caller you're trying to reach...
What room is Kang Gyeong Jun at?
Room 560.
Thank you.
Dr. Seo seems very different today.
I'm sorry to bother you.
What floor is the Pediatric and Young Adult
Medicine Department?
Yun Jae?
Yun Jae.
Y-Yun...
Yes, dad.
I came by the hospital to see Yun Jae,
but he must be busy.
Pardon? Yun Jae is at the hospital?
Um...
I'm leaving a bag of dumplings for him
at the information desk.
Tell him to pick them up.
Ignore me?
Gyeong Jun doesn't know
Yun Jae works at that hospital.
Darn it.
Vice Principal Kim, I... Umm...
What is it?
What?
Nothing, ma'am.
Ms. Gil Da Ran!
Put that file down this instant.
Pardon?
I was looking at it. Put it down right now.
Were you looking at it?
Yes, Vice Principal Kim.
I don't want Ms. Gil touching my files.
I'll look it over and process it.
Okay.
Since you don't want her touching it...
Leave it there and go.
Da Ran.
Da Ran!
Really?
What's up with her?
Something's going on
between her and Yun Jae.
It's your doctor. Say hello, Jae Hyeong.
- Hello.
- Hello, doctor.
Hello.
Hello, doctor.
Hello, doctor. Have you had lunch?
What's going on here?
I have a feeling I shouldn't be here.
Oh, geez!
Seo Yun Jae?
Oh my gosh!
Oh, man.
This is his home turf.
Darn it.
Geez.
He must be a star here.
Would this work?
Do I have to do this?
Geez. I look like a dork.
Hi, Yun Jae.
Seo Yun Jae.
Pigs will fly. I can't believe
you're playing hooky.
We couldn't get a hold of you.
Did you just get in?
You came dressed like that?
Are you not feeling well?
Ow. My head.
- See you...
- What's going on?
Is something wrong?
You look sick.
I had mushrooms.
Mushrooms?
How?
It must have been pretty bad then.
Yeah. It's been very bad.
I need to rest.
Yun Jae,
you still have what I gave you, right?
Huh?
Oh, that.
I gave it to you for a situation like this.
Don't be bashful and just
do as I tell you to.
Why is that lady all touchy-feely?
Yun Jae.
Hi, Da Ran.
Hello.
I came to see Yun Jae.
How can you come here alone
without telling me?
I didn't know he was a doctor.
And I only came to see my body.
Your body?
I'd like to know how it's doing.
And there's something important
I need to retrieve.
Then come with me.
Put this on.
By the way, Gil Teacher,
this dude has a female colleague, right?
She's odd.
She touched his body in a strange way.
You're making people think
Yun Jae is mentally challenged.
Don't make them think
he's a pervert as well.
What? A pervert?
I know boys your age
are very sensitive to a woman's touch.
I know. I'm a high school teacher.
But you can't be like that
around Yun Jae's friend.
What will she think?
You're being delusional again.
I'm sure you also know that
the more you nag boys my age,
the more we want to rebel,
don't you, Ms. Gil?
Mentally-challenged, perverted,
and incompetent...
Stop provoking me
if you don't want me to add
delinquent to the list.
I'm at a very emotional age.
Lying there on Yun Jae's bed
in Yun Jae's clothes
and in Yun Jae's hospital
makes it seem you really are Yun Jae.
Yeah, so...
Don't say anything for a second.
Give me your hand.
It's not warm.
The temperature of your soul is different.
You're not Yun Jae, so your hand
isn't as warm as his.
I'm relieved.
I like being cool.
Let's go.
I...
I took his hand.
What?
In the water...
I thought I was going to die.
I saw him holding his hand out to me.
I knew that was the only chance at survival,
so I took his hand.
Maybe that's how my soul
slipped into his body.
If you and Yun Jae switched bodies
by holding hands,
wouldn't you switch back
if you held hands again?
What if I don't wake up?
You will. Hurry up and hold his hand.
Da Ran.
It's me.
Yun Jae.
I was so worried.
It felt like this happened to you
because I complained.
It seemed like it was my fault.
I was so worried.
I'm sorry about what I said.
I'm sorry, too.
I'll say what I was going to tell you.
I'm sorry.
It didn't work.
I'm still Kang Gyeong Jun.
You look very disappointed.
Hello.
Gil Teacher, snap out of it. Where are you?
Does this seem like a joke to you?
Is this funny to you?
Do adults cry over a kid's joke?
It's my fault for being fooled by you.
It's not my fault we didn't switch over.
Why is she lashing out at me?
Where's my stuff?
Doctor.
You're here.
How's Gyeong Jun?
Hello.
He's still in a coma.
But they say he's not hurt.
Why won't he wake up?
He won't be comatose forever, will he?
He's not hurt, so he should wake up.
I heard that some people
stay like this for years.
Then do we have to keep taking care of him?
He'll wake up, right?
If he doesn't, what will you do?
We're not his guardians per se, doctor.
We're just relatives looking after him.
You shouldn't be asking us
what we'll do about him
if he remains comatose.
Gyeong Mi.
What?
Excuse us, doctor.
Good grief.
If worse comes to worst, can we
send him to the States?
Who'll take him in?
He grew up there. I'm sure he knows people.
He doesn't have anyone.
That's why he came to Korea.
Excuse me.
What would you like us to do
with his personal effects?
- Gyeong Jun.
- Leave me alone.
Gyeong Jun.
Just leave me alone.
- Gyeong Jun.
- What?
Are you worried people will think
your precious fiance is a maniac?
Are you welling up again?
Then leave me alone before
I make things worse.
I'm sure you're upset about what
you heard. I can't just take off.
Don't pretend to be concerned.
You're just like my uncle.
You're just worried I'll be inside
your precious fiance's body forever.
I'm a hindrance to you
just like I am to my uncle.
Stop acting concerned.
Gyeong Jun.
I'll only get worse if you keep this up.
Da Ran.
Yun Jae,
did you just push my sister?
Why were you yelling at her?
Chung Sik, this isn't your concern.
Just go.
He came to school this morning
and was acting strangely,
so I came to ask him what happened.
I'm glad that I came.
I thought you were a good guy,
but I must have been wrong.
Yun Jae.
I'm not your brother-in-law, okay?
Wouldn't your husband be
my brother-in-law?
I'm confused.
Stupid.
Stupid?
Did you just insult me?
Chung Sik, Chung Sik. Stop it.
Hold on.
Yun Jae.
Stupid.
Don't meddle and just go home.
He's treating you badly though.
Just stay out of it.
The more you meddle, the more
complicated things will get.
Go home. Just do as I say. Go.
Drink water instead of soda
if you're thirsty.
There's mom's inheritance,
so they won't abandon you just yet.
You shouldn't worry.
Huh?
But they threw these out.
Dumplings?
Gil Family Dumplings?
Gil Family?
Gil?
Gil Da Ran?
Da Ran,
did Yun Jae break off the engagement?
He said he wasn't my brother-in-law.
Is that why he didn't answer my call?
You see,
Yun Jae's going through a rough patch.
He insulted me, too.
He called me stupid.
He acted like he didn't even know me.
He completely ignored dad.
It wasn't Yun Jae.
Then
who was it that I saw earlier?
And who was the guy who
pretended he didn't know me?
That was Yun Jae, of course.
He broke it off.
Yes, he did.
It's you, Yun Jae!
Did you like the dumplings?
Guess what was inside.
Pardon?
Just guess.
Meat?
Nope.
- Shrimp?
- No.
I'll give you a hint.
It's slimy, and it wriggles
when you try to catch it.
It wriggles like this.
It's long.
Long?
Yup. Long and slimy.
Long and slimy...
Eel.
That's right. How did you know?
Let's go in.
Hon, hon, hon,
Yun Jae guessed what we
put in the dumplings.
Mom.
Mom? Hon?
So she's Gil Da Ran's mother?
Then she's Seo Yun Jae's mother-in-law.
That guy is her husband,
so he's Seo Yun Jae's father-in-law.
And he's Gil Da Ran's brother,
which makes him
Seo Yun Jae's brother-in-law.
Hello, sir.
Hi, Yun Jae.
- Hi, Chung Sik.
- Hi, Yun Jae.
Hello, ma'am.
It's been so long.
Hi, Yun Jae.
Surprise!
Why did you come here?
What were you thinking?
I came to see you, right?
But then this lady suddenly
showed up and asked me,
"Guess what was in the dumplings?"
"Wriggle, wriggle."
"You got it."
And then she dragged me inside.
I don't believe this.
But thank goodness I was quick on my toes.
What if I had said, "Who are you"
to your mother?
I was smart and said my proper hellos,
so you take care of the rest.
Bye.
Where do you think you're going?
You came here as Yun Jae,
so you need to do your part.
What?
I guess the engagement is still on.
He was a bit loopy because
he was in a car accident.
I shouldn't have taken it the wrong way.
Talk things through with Yun Jae over beer
and some spicy dumpling stew.
Chung Sik. Chung Sik.
Get a few bottles of beer
from the store fridge.
Beer.
Why's he all excited?
Get some soju, too.
You deal with it.
I don't want to be involved.
Then should I tell them
your soul's in Yun Jae's body?
They'll drag you to a mental hospital.
You need to cooperate if you
don't want anyone to find out.
It'll become more obvious with time anyway.
Yes, but we should at least try to hide it.
Hide what?
See? It's happening already.
What are you two hiding?
You don't need to know. It's adult stuff.
Let's go, Yun Jae.
It's adult stuff.
You're too young.
Wow.
Take a seat.
Da Ran. Da Ran.
Yes, mom.
Something wrong?
Would you like a pair of socks?
No, thank you. This is how I like it.
I heard you were in a car accident.
Are you okay now?
As you can see...
So you're okay?
I'm good.
It's itchy.
This body has an allergy.
You sure have a lot of stones.
My viewing stones? I collect them.
I didn't know people collected stones.
Ouch.
You shouldn't touch...
These here are my family.
The large black one is me.
The pretty white one is Da Ran's mom.
This smooth one is Da Ran.
And this tiny one is Chung Sik.
You're literally the Flintstones.
Daddy Flintstone,
Mommy Flintstone,
and Baby Flintstones...
Yeah...
Since you're now part of the family,
let's pick one for you to place
right next to Da Ran's.
No thanks.
It's ridiculous.
I mean, should we look
for the son-in-law flintstone?
So this is where it'll go, right?
Yes. This is your place.
So what are the standards
you use to pick out a stone?
Standards?
I can't figure it out.
If size was your standard,
then this should be Chung Sik
as he's the biggest,
followed by Mrs. Gil, Da Ran, and then you.
But if beauty were your standard,
this one should be Mrs. Gil
as she's the prettiest,
then Chung Sik, then Da Ran, then you.
You need to tell me what your standards are,
sir.
That's right.
Despite being the smallest
and ugliest member of this family,
I picked out the best stone for myself.
You must not be happy with that.
Oh, no no no no.
I just wanted to know which stone
would best represent me
according to your standards.
The standard you should focus on
is compatibility.
That is, how your stone can fit in
with the rest of the stones here.
Compatibility.
That's what you should focus on.
You don't have to pick out a stone
if you don't want to though.
That's what adults do when
they don't have the answer.
They give you an abstract,
long-winded sermon.
Compatibility?
What is that?
Plus, this is Seo Yun Jae's spot, not mine.
The oh-so-perfect Seo Yun Jae
should figure it out.
You're making so much noise.
I can't eat food this hot and spicy.
It won't kill you.
Keep it down. Keep it down.
The stew must be too spicy for you.
How about a nice, cold beer?
Alcohol?
Why not? Sure. Sure.
It won't kill me.
Dad, Yun Jae has to drive.
My car was wrecked in the accident.
You shouldn't drink.
You're still recovering.
One glass will help me
get a good night's sleep.
Please, sir.
Dad, dad. Me too.
You're only 18. No drinks for minors.
You're too young.
No.
You really are a teacher
through and through.
That's right. I can't let any
student of mine drink.
You don't have to take me home.
I can manage just fine.
You drank though.
I have to make sure you get home safely.
I had one sip.
Don't tell me you're that naive,
Gil Teacher.
You don't suppose that was
my first drink ever, do you?
Regardless, I can't help but feel
responsible for your safety
as you're my student, Kang Gyeong Jun.
I'm sorry
I made you pretend to be my fiance.
And thanks.
You don't have to be sorry.
You got this back for me.
And if you're really thankful,
fill this with some cash, will you?
With this face, I have to pay
the adult bus fare.
And get me some clothes.
His body might rip my clothes.
And I keep getting a wedgie.
You're right.
I can't have Yun Jae dressed like this.
Let's go.
Shopping?
No. We're going to his place
to pick up some clothes.
Hey, hon.
Didn't Yun Jae seem different today?
I don't know where his manners went,
and he was so brazen around us.
He wasn't his usual overly courteous self
to Da Ran either.
Right?
You noticed it, too, right?
Yeah.
I was so happy.
He must feel at ease with us.
He finally feels like our son-in-law.
It makes me so happy.
It's a good thing if it's a sign
that he feels comfortable around us...
All set. Come.
Come in.
Does Yun Jae live alone, too?
His parents live abroad.
Don't touch things.
Let's quickly get what we need.
Hey.
Don't touch anything! Come on!
Here are his clothes.
Pick out a few things.
Geez.
You startled me.
Cover yourself up.
You probably see this every day.
What's the big deal?
Hurry up and change.
Why are you sneaking a peek?
Go ahead and look.
I wasn't peeking.
What's wrong with you?
You embraced this body when
he was completely naked in the hospital
and wailed, "I thought you were dead."
Those were extenuating circumstances.
And I didn't get a good look.
Oh my gosh.
So you and Yun Jae
haven't... You know...
You're about to get married
in a month. That's crazy.
What do you know? You're a kid.
Hurry up and pick out what you want to wear.
Gil Teacher,
do you want me to show you?
He has a great body. Look. Look.
See?
This isn't something you can
achieve in a month or two.
See? This dude even has a six pack.
Stop it.
He's hairy too.
So why didn't this guy show you
his well-toned body?
He must have put a lot of time
and effort into it.
I assumed it was to impress you.
Yun Jae's disciplined, which is why
he likes to work out.
That's right.
He had to have worked out at least
2 hours a day, every single day.
Does it really take
2 hours a day to buff up like that?
Definitely.
Why didn't he use that
time to see you instead?
He kept standing you up,
saying he was busy.
Maybe to him, his muscles were
more important than you.
So I guess he had time to work out.
Was he just making excuses?
Maybe he just didn't want to see me.
I doubt that.
He was on his way to see you
when he got into the accident.
Yeah. And he was going
to tell you something, right?
Do you think he was going
to tell me he loved me?
But what if it was something else?
Gil Da Ran,
I love you.
I'm sure that's what he was going to say.
Yeah.
You're probably right.
Right?
I don't know why I got so worried.
I'm an idiot.
That's right. You're an idiot.
Let's pick out clothes.
This color looks great on Yun Jae.
This one, too.
And so does this one.
Here.
Hold on to them.
I'll get a bag.
I don't know how she can like him so much.
These are so ugly.
Is this the key to this apartment?
No.
Maybe it's the key to our marital home.
Oh, no. What now?
Keep it short and natural.
What?
- Hello?
- Hi, Yun Jae.
It's Se Yeong.
- His colleague.
- You were home.
I was so worried because no one
could get a hold of you.
I heard you were in an accident.
I only found out because they sent
your stuff over to the hospital.
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm okay now.
No wonder you didn't seem
like yourself earlier.
I'll bring your stuff over to your place.
I'm nearby, so it won't take long.
Okay.
She's coming here.
That's great.
She must be bringing Yun Jae's
personal effects.
What about Yun Jae's work?
Do I have to start working at his hospital?
You can't do that.
Why don't we request a leave of absence?
What about the wedding? Do I have to
walk down the aisle with you?
I'm sure he'll return by then. He has to.
If he doesn't, I won't do it for you.
Should we tidy up until Se Yeong gets here?
I'm doing my part by keeping his body clean.
I'm not cleaning his place.
I'm all set with that.
When Se Yeong gets here,
be polite when you say hello.
Don't look at her with lustful eyes.
I'll look at her with pure
and innocent eyes.
Where's the vacuum cleaner?
Here it is.
This thing's heavy.
It's not empty.
Huh? Yun Jae had packed this.
Where was he planning to go?
He never told me about a trip.
Where was he planning to go
without my knowing?
Yun Jae.
Hi.
I was so worried.
I should've been the first person you called.
Hey.
What's wrong with you?
Yun Jae,
I love you.
Yun Jae.
Seo Yun Jae, you bastard.
[Big]
He was cheating on you,
playing you for a fool.
Yun Jae's not himself.
You got yourself into a pickle, didn't you?
Kids run away from home
when they get into trouble.
I need to find evidence
of his two-timing ways.
Who's he?
Someone Gyeong Jun knows.
I will
get you
to marry
me.
You're very pretty.
Yun Jae,
you're in there, right?