[Episode 6]
I'm sorry I'm late.
Hurry over.
Congrats on passing the exam.
- Congrats.
- Ready.
1, 2, 3.
[Gil Da Ran]
Meal ticket please.
The groom's friends are amazing.
We have to go to the post-wedding bash.
I'm hungry. Let's go eat.
Who cares about food?
Look at the groom's friends. They're so hot.
I didn't have breakfast.
I'm starving. I'm going.
Huh?
Is that Yun Jae?
Gyeong Jun.
Kang Gyeong Jun.
Yun Jae?
Ms. Gil Da Ran,
long time no see.
Are you getting in?
Pardon?
Um... Yes.
You're Gyeong Jun, right?
You confused me.
Did you pretend to be Yun Jae,
because there are other people here?
Why didn't you call or write me?
When did you return to Seoul?
And why are you here?
Because my friend's getting married.
Is that you, Yun Jae?
It's only been a year,
but you've really aged.
I see a lot of fine lines.
You're not that pretty anymore.
So it is you, Gyeong Jun.
I fell for you the first time I saw you,
because you were so pretty.
Yun Jae?
I must have changed a lot.
You don't recognize me.
I threw you for a loop.
It's Kang Gyeong Jun.
Da Ran. Da Ran.
Da Ran, guess who I saw?
I think I saw Yun Jae.
Do you think he's back?
Yeah...
You must have seen him, too.
There he is.
He's changed a lot.
Yeah.
He's become devastatingly more handsome.
He's looking this way.
Are you okay, Da Ran?
I'm fine. Hold on.
She must still have feelings for him.
You're Kang Gyeong Jun, right?
You must have been really confused.
You used to know when to shoot
your love beams and when not to.
I was so worried about you.
It's good to see you.
Let me see you. Have you been well?
Yes. Apart from the fact
that I'm still in this body,
I'm doing well.
I didn't think it would last this long.
This place is teeming with friends
of you and Seo Yun Jae.
Is it okay for us to to be this friendly?
You used to cajole me into playing
your precious Yun Jae.
You must have forgotten what
transpired between you and him.
To me, you're Gyeong Jun,
but to everyone else, you're Yun Jae...
What are we going to do?
They're watching the couple
that broke off their wedding.
In a situation like this,
the person who gets up first
gets the upper hand, right?
Yes.
To avoid any one of us looking pathetic,
I'll count to 3, and we'll get up together.
Okay?
1, 2...
3.
- Are you okay, Da Ran?
- I'm fine.
- What's going on?
- What happened?
It's nothing.
- Did he dump you again?
- Um... No...
You're okay, right?
It's not that...
I'm counting to 3.
1...
You're not getting up?
2...
This is your last chance.
3.
Let's go.
Oh my goodness.
Da Ran.
What a relief. I would've
been so humiliated.
You're relieved?
Of course. I was the talk of the town
when we called off the wedding.
Now, they'll be gossiping about
how we might be back together.
Get with the program.
The moment we got up together at
the count of 3, we got back together.
You came with me, holding my hand.
Oh, right.
It didn't occur to me.
You showed up out of the blue
and caught me off guard.
Why did you show up here
of all places anyway?
To get you back.
- Me?
- Yup.
Something's come up. I need you.
What's come up?
Yun Jae's mother wants me to get married.
I'd be grateful if you could
stay by Yun Jae's side.
I just don't get why he's being
so cold though.
I have to win him over again.
You've known him since college.
Please be more aggressive and win him over.
I'm sorry to be asking so much of you.
When Yun Jae said he was getting married,
I pretended to okay with it.
Frankly, I regret it.
I don't want him to slip
through my fingers again.
Yun Jae's mother keeps pushing me
to see Lee Se Yeong.
She thinks I'll return to being the old
Yun Jae if things go well with her.
I'm in a bind.
Yun Jae's mother doesn't know
you're but an 18-year-old nursling,
so of course she wants you to get married.
Correction.
I'm a 19-year-old nursling.
What a pickle.
That's why I've come to get you back.
Me? Why?
You're the only one who
knows who I really am.
So if I have to get married,
it has to be with you.
Don't tell me you still like me...
Things have changed.
I was very young then.
You're still young.
I'm not proposing that we really get married.
Remember how I played
the part of your fiance?
This time, you can help me out
so that Yun Jae's mother
doesn't try to set me up
with Se Yeong or any other woman.
No. I can't.
There are too many people here.
Let's continue this discussion
somewhere more private.
Are you serious?
- Really?
- No way.
Why are you back? Go.
Geez.
Da Ran, where are you going?
He said he'd drop me off.
Don't get the wrong idea, though.
What's going on?
You little twerp.
Showing up at the wedding
was part of your scheme.
I told you I've come to get you back.
You never listen to me.
You need to see girls your age.
In this body? Wouldn't that be a crime?
I suppose I wouldn't have to
get married if I went to jail.
That's not what I meant.
What are we going to do?
See? You're the only way out of this.
I still can't help you.
You have no idea how difficult
it was for me to get over Yun Jae.
I can't keep being reminded of him again.
Do you still love him?
Does it still pain you to see this face?
It's a wrap for today. Get off.
In any case, I can't help you.
But you're welcome to call
if you need help with anything else.
After all, I'm the only one who knows
you're Kang Gyeong Jun,
not Seo Yun Jae.
How's the dumpling business?
You can't do what you did
at the wedding with my family.
You're Seo Yun Jae,
the guy who broke my heart,
so if they see you, they'll
mince you into meat stuffing.
Gil Teacher,
call me by my name.
Kang Gyeong Jun. Kang Gyeong Jun.
Kang Gyeong Jun.
That's good. Get off.
Bye, Gyeong Jun.
I missed you.
You're the only person who
calls me "Kang Gyeong Jun."
Have some more. Vitamins are good for you.
I'm back.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Did you have a good time at the wedding?
Yes.
Da Ran must be doing a lot better.
She's started seeing her friends again.
That's good.
She'd be a fool not to get over
that irresponsible jerk.
Should we set her up with someone?
After she passed the exam,
many people seem interested.
Bring it up with her when you can.
My only condition is that the guy's
family name is not Seo.
I never want to hear that name again.
Have you fully recovered?
Not fully, but I'm a lot better.
So you're coming back to work?
Soon.
I'm almost ready.
I'll be ready soon.
Doctor, the patient in room 802
is hemorrhaging.
I have to go.
I have the knowledge, but I still
can't stand the sight of blood.
Mister,
you're really back.
Yes, I am.
I shared classified intel with you,
so you need to give me
intel about Gyeong Jun.
Gyeong Jun wet his bed until he was 7.
Really?
That's so cute.
First kiss was not with Amy.
Confirmed by Amy.
Did not date Sally.
Taught Sally a lesson
for spreading a false rumor.
Why don't you put that kind
of effort into school?
Do you even go to school?
I have to be here in Korea
to stay by Gyeong Jun's side,
so I'm putting up with going to school here.
Do you like Gyeong Jun that much?
Gyeong Jun lost his beloved mother
because of my love for him.
That's why
I've decided never to stop loving him.
Wouldn't most people give up
given the extenuating circumstances?
That's what traitors do.
I'm going to keep loving him
and become the person he holds most dear.
So your love for Gyeong Jun
is a form of loyalty, isn't it?
You seem to share a very
special bond with Gyeong Jun.
Are you his father by any chance?
No way.
Seo Yun Jae's only 12 years older.
Seo Yun Jae would have...
Never mind.
Mary, you never make any sense.
That doctor isn't Gyeong Jun's father,
so who can he be?
He brought up the inheritance. He's a
relative on Gyeong Jun's father's side.
He wants a cut of it.
Gyeong Jun's birthday's coming up.
Do you think he'll wake up by then?
Maybe the doctor is Gyeong Jun's uncle.
There's no way we'll know
until he wakes up though.
There's nothing wrong with him,
so how can he be in a coma for a year?
If he doesn't wake up, how will
we collect his inheritance?
I'm sure it's a sizable sum.
If I could open a few more
restaurants with that money,
I'd take great care of Gyeong Jun
for the rest of his life.
Huh?
Why are you here? Go.
You go.
Where are you going?
Is it wrong of me to want to
see my old school?
Geez.
- Hang on.
- Huh?
Yun Jae...
Is that...
That's Da Ran's ex-fiance.
What's going on?
You go ahead.
Kang Gyeong Jun's been
put on extended leave.
How many days does he have to make up
to avoid being held back a year?
Hold on.
Yun Jae isn't here to see you?
Didn't you say you guys
talked things through?
Don't worry. Plus, what's there
to talk through anyway?
- Are you sure?
- Please take good care
of Kang Gyeong Jun so that he can
return to us sound and healthy.
Excuse me.
You are
Ms. Gil Da Ran's ex-fiance, right?
You came by here a few times.
- Yes.
- Oh...
I was confused, because you didn't
seem to acknowledge her.
Oh...
It's not that I wanted to ignore her.
She told me to act like we're strangers.
Ms. Gil asked you to do that?
I see.
But then again, I'm sure she was very hurt.
It was me who was more hurt.
I don't think you know what really happened.
Ms. Gil was the one who
called off the wedding.
I had much to work to do
to become a better man.
Although I'm back new and improved,
she turned down my proposal again,
saying it was the funniest thing
since "Dumb and Dumber."
I see.
What's "Dumb and Dumber" anyway?
I should get going.
Of course.
Bye.
Ms. Gil wasn't dumped? She did the dumping?
But why?
I don't know. This is news to me, too.
Kang Gyeong Jun!
What are you doing?
Checking your registration status
was just a front, wasn't it?
Yup.
You've gotten smarter.
Did word go around that it was you
who had been dumped by Seo Yun Jae?
That doesn't concern you.
I have to build you up for
when we get back together.
Why are you so stubborn?
Let's eat first.
You need to eat if you're to go up
against Seo Yun Jae's mother.
Why would I see her?
I asked you for your help.
We need to get back together.
And I said no.
What am I supposed to say
to Yun Jae's mother?
She won't be your mother-in-law
anyway, so what do you care?
Say whatever you want to.
Tell her you want her son.
Mind your manners. You're just a kid.
I'm not a kid in anyone's eyes but yours.
Be careful.
They might drag you to the funny house.
That's why you need to reason
with Yun Jae's mother.
She won't listen to me.
Then go against her wishes.
That's not easy. I'm living
in her son's body.
I suppose it can't be easy for you.
Honestly, it didn't sit well with me that
I sent you off with Yun Jae's mom.
Your just a nursling after all.
Why's your stuff still at the house?
They said I wouldn't even get
half of what I paid for,
so I kept them there for when
I eventually move out on my own.
This works out well.
Since your stuff is still there,
we can play newlyweds at that house.
It's a great excuse.
No!
Then move your things out right away.
I can't help you. Move everything
out before I return home.
By the end of the day?
He's become so mean.
Do you have to stay at that house?
If you want to stay there, would you
like me to move in with you?
I'd rather stay alone.
I don't know what happened that my own
son feels uncomfortable living with me.
I'm sorry.
Will you be returning to the hospital?
I've worked hard to fill in the gaps,
so I should start working again.
Then you should hang out
with your old friends,
especially Se Yeong.
She'll help you return to your old self.
I'm trying to reconnect with my friends.
I'll take care of it.
I should've just sold all these.
I'll put them in the master bedroom for now
and move them out over the weekend.
You won't help me out, and yet
you expect me to help you?
Is that what an adult should be doing?
When a kid acts up,
an adult has to be stern with him.
If you're going to be stern,
make sure you clean up here
after you remove all your stuff.
There are no cleaning supplies though.
We can get that.
I'll go get them, so make sure
you clean up before you leave.
He's as mean as can be.
All set.
What do you think?
Everything looks good on you.
One pizza down.
This one.
Okay.
- And this.
- Okay.
- This.
You can carry them all, right?
Sure.
One more pizza down.
I'm almost done paying off my debt.
Are you happy?
When I pay off my debt
and I'm no longer your slave,
I want to tell you something.
I thought Gyeong Jun would've woken up
before you paid off the 300 pizzas.
I'll take you to the arcades today. My treat.
You don't have to deduct a pizza for that.
Did you hear anything about Dr. Seo
returning to the hospital?
Why do you ask?
I heard that he's returned.
Dr. Seo...
Oops.
Should I remove the bathroom slippers, too?
You won't need these, right?
Why are you here?
I'm here
because of my things.
Did you meet up with Yun Jae?
Yes.
Seeing that you're here, it must be true
that his mother is trying
to set you up with him.
Which cleaner keeps the dirt and grease on?
Do you really want to marry him?
Why should I tell you?
You and Yun Jae are now history.
I don't want to help you in the least
but I do want to tell you that marrying
Yun Jae won't be a good idea.
You're 31 years old, right?
What do you see when you look
at a 19 year-old kid? A man?
Pardon? What do you take me for?
You see, inside Yun Jae
is an immature little kid.
They do say a man is forever a child,
but in Yun Jae's case,
it's more than just figurative.
I know Yun Jae has changed
since the accident.
But I still like him nonetheless.
Unlike you, I won't give up on him.
That's not fit for a young kid.
Get up.
This is my couch.
What?
Get up. This is my couch.
Why are you being so childish?
All the furniture in here belongs to me.
You can't come here until
I remove everything.
- Go.
- Ms. Gil Da Ran.
Just go.
And don't ever come back here at night.
I'll beat you into a pulp.
What's going on?
Gil Da Ran's at your place.
She said she was moving her things out
and kicked me out.
Really?
What's going on?
What's wrong with her?
She told me you've become a child
and that I should give up on you.
That's right. I'm a child.
I'm very immature.
Will you be able to handle that?
You were never childish or immature.
She may have given up,
but I'm going to wait until
the old you returns.
Fine. When he does return,
he's all yours.
Happy now?
I heard you kicked Lee Se Yeong out.
You're not as wimpy as you used to be.
Gil...
She brought Yun Jae's things.
These could probably go.
Stop it.
I'm putting them in that room.
Don't throw them out.
Have you really been studying medicine?
You read all of these?
You must be really smart.
I told you I was skipping.
It's not that bad. I didn't
have to waste time.
I got to where I am in the blink of an eye.
But getting married is a different story.
Yeah.
Seeing that Se Yeong came over
this late at night,
the problem is serious.
I've been telling you it was serious.
All alone with a sexy woman like her...
On the inside, I'm a young kid
with raging hormones.
When she finds out about the nursling inside,
she'll no longer be chasing you.
Really?
This kiddie bed speaks volumes
about your childish mental state.
So that means
you will
never ever
be attracted to me, right?
Of course not.
That's why you're the only one
who can help me.
Please let me hold onto the boy
in this body who likes toy beds.
Poor Gyeong Jun.
I can't just turn a blind eye.
Those love beams in her eyes
were still there.
You've wasted so much time.
You wasted 6 months
denying that you like Da Ran
and another 6 months worrying
that you'll make her uncomfortable.
You might lose her again
without having done a thing.
Ms. Lee Ae Gyeong,
what do you think I should do?
What do you think you should do?
I can run 100 meters in 12 seconds.
But it's been a year, and I still
haven't been able to start
my sprint toward Ms. Gil.
Please pull the trigger on the gun
so that I can start my dash.
Bang.
Shoot it right here. Bang.
Okay.
Bang.
I've started the race.
Please help me.
Shoot the gun one more time
so that I can get a better start.
Bang.
Good grief.
That male and female are
shooting love bullets
on sacred school grounds.
This isn't a battleground.
Geez.
This could be war.
I could get hurt.
- Aren't the dumplings delicious?
- Yes.
Guess what's inside.
It was so good. Thank you.
Do come back soon. So long.
She's the scariest.
This is it.
Geez.
What would you like, sir?
Dumplings, please.
Coming up.
I should just do it. They'll go easier on me
because of the customers.
Hon, where's the pork?
Inside. Right in front of the fridge.
Here?
I don't see it.
Where can it be?
Oh, right. It's in the small fridge.
The small fridge? Okay.
I'll be minced up like meat stuffing.
Sir, your dumplings.
Sir.
It's to go.
Okay.
Hi, Mary.
Dumplings, right?
They were holding weapons.
You would have been made
into dumplings if they caught you.
They make good dumplings,
so imagine how well they would
have diced and minced me.
Mister,
it's one pickled radish per dumpling.
I only make an exception
to the rule for Gyeong Jun.
Then make an exception for me, too.
Mister,
you're taking 2 radishes to be
like Gyeong Jun, aren't you?
I normally have 3 at a time.
I was just being nice.
In any case, thanks.
You can have the rest.
Even if they make dumplings out of me,
I have to go and talk to them.
There's nothing left.
You toss all that into a trash bin.
Are you following me? Don't follow me.
I told you not to follow me.
I can't open my eyes.
Are you okay?
Don't touch your eyes.
You'll be fine once they start watering.
Fine. I'll deal with the trash.
Please get your things
out of Yun Jae's house.
I'm going to sell the house soon.
The house?
But there's someone who
wants to buy it later on.
The house means a lot to that person.
How is that your concern?
You want the house and
the furniture left as they are?
You must still be hung up on Yun Jae.
Please move you things out
as soon as possible.
Dr. Seo Yun Jae's gotten even more handsome.
Yun Jae was at the hospital?
Yes. Right here.
Here?
How does Yun Jae know this patient?
There was no external trauma.
I don't know why we won't wake up.
I've never seen anything like this before.
This patient was in a car accident, right?
Yes.
He's a celebrity around here.
The Sleeping Hottie.
Kang Gyeong Jun.
He was first taken to Yangpyeong Hospital.
Wasn't Yangpyeong where
Yun Jae got into an accident?
The patient who was brought here
with Kang Gyeong Jun
was Seo Yun Jae?
You're sure, right?
That's why mom bought me this house.
This house
is all I have left.
Hi, Ae Gyeong.
What?
You're at our dumpling place with Mr. Na?
We'll wait for you. Hurry over.
So you went to the same college
of education I had gone to, Mr. Na.
Yes, sir. Please call me Hyo Sang, sir.
Well...
I don't know...
Hyo Sang? Na Hyo Sang.
I like the family name Na.
He's certainly sprinting fast.
He did say he could run
100 meters in 12 seconds.
Come on in.
As a former teacher, Min Gyu has always
wanted a teacher for a son-in-law.
Right?
Of course.
I'd like it too if my brother-in-law
were a teacher.
It would be perfect.
Da Ran's on her way, right?
Yes.
Let me pour you a glass, sir.
Bottoms up. No stopping.
What's going on here?
What's up with the gym teacher?
And what do your parents do?
They're both civil servants, sir.
- Wow.
- How wonderful.
This is great.
Are they thinking of setting
him up with Da Ran?
I'd like another glass, sir.
If Da Ran shows up,
they're pressure her into dating him.
Huh?
What are you doing here?
I need to talk to you. Let's go.
I have guests. I have to go.
You said I could come and talk
to you if I had any problems.
You know you're the only one I can talk to.
Fine. Go on in then.
It's not easy reconciling the gap between
the subject I see in the mirror and myself.
I don't know if I need to come to terms
with having two identities
or destroy my old self and create
a new identity altogether.
That's what has been bothering me.
It's a problem that's probably unique to you.
I don't know what to tell you.
You said you had guests.
- Did the gym teacher come by?
- Yeah.
Have you two gotten closer
while I was away?
No.
No?
What should we eat?
I can't decide.
What you said earlier, Gyeong Jun...
Never mind.
So you're confused as to who you are, right?
I don't know
what I could do for you,
but you're just Kang Gyeong Jun.
Don't forget that.
You came up with a short answer
to a very big question.
So don't forget that you're still young.
Don't go to places where adults drink,
and don't smoke, either.
I know you have a license, but
I worry about you driving, too.
Yes, ma'am.
I have faith in you.
Don't touch your eyes.
You'll be fine once they start watering.
How can
two people be so similar?
Hello, Mary.
Do you know how Gyeong Jun
got to know Dr. Seo Yun Jae?
I was wondering whether you knew
anything about their relationship.
I don't know anything, either.
All I know is that they shared a special bond
and that Dr. Seo knows
a lot about Gyeong Jun.
I know.
He even bought Gyeong Jun's house.
They must have shared
an exceptionally strong bond.
He bought the house
Gyeong Jun used to live in?
Yeah.
Gyeong Jun's mother had bought
the house for when Gyeong Jun
would attend college in Korea.
After Gyeong Jun's accident, we didn't
want to leave it empty, so we sold it.
And the person who bought
the house was Dr. Seo.
Dr. Seo bought the house
Gyeong Jun used to live in.
Isn't it weird?
Yeah.
They were planning to get an apartment
but suddenly changed their minds.
It was probably Dr. Seo.
Really?
Seo Yun Jae used to be a gentleman,
but he became really weird
after the accident.
Accident?
Yeah. A car accident.
When?
Um...
It was probably right before you got here.
Really?
Here's your orange juice.
2 Americanos.
Ow.
2 Americanos, right?
Please wait.
You bring the coffee.
Why?
I can't stand seeing blood.
How did he study medicine then?
Look at him sitting askew
with one hand in his pocket.
That's how he used to sit in class.
He's so hot.
- Isn't he handsome?
- Yeah.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry. Did I get it on your shirt?
She's making a move on him.
I'll pay for the dry-cleaning.
Why don't we exchange numbers?
Spilling a drink to get the guy's number.
Classic schemes always work the best.
She's getting his number.
He's really giving her his number.
He's really easy, isn't he?
2 Americanos.
Thank you.
Are you just going to watch?
Aren't you going to stop her?
You said you'd take care of me.
Are you his girlfriend?
Pardon?
I... Uh... Well...
Sorry about your shirt.
I... Uh...Well... Is that a yes or a no?
Well... Uh...
So Gyeong Jun used to live here?
So what do you say?
You're going to help me, right?
I need to think about it.
The more you think, the more
delusional you get.
Just make up your mind.
Kang Gyeong Jun's the bait.
Take it.
You're the only one in the whole world
who really knows me.
This isn't fun for me. I'm not out
to lure all the fishes out there.
There's only one fish for me,
and I'm begging her to take me.
It's a sad situation.
So Gil Teacher,
please take the bait.
That's Gyeong Jun's bed.
They're all Gyeong Jun's.
They were in the same accident.
One's in a coma,
and the other one lost his memory...
If I'm with you like this,
people will think
I've gotten back together
with Yun Jae, right?
That's why we can't just meet up like this.
Either we keep seeing each other
or we don't see each other at all.
Gyeong Jun,
I...
I really want to stay by
your side and help you,
but I don't want to
see Yun Jae's face.
It wasn't easy for me to get over him,
and I'm not sure I can keep myself
from falling for him again.
Will I be
able to hold myself back?
So...
You've made your decision.
Let's not see each other again.
Why are you here?
And why are you here?
Why are you in Gyeong Jun's house?
Because I bought this place.
Why didn't you tell me
Gyeong Jun used to live here?
You're a doctor, right?
I have a cut.
Could you take a look at it?
Are you scared of blood, too?
Just like Gyeong Jun...
You're not a doctor, are you?
You're not Seo Yun Jae,
are you?
Are you Gyeong Jun?
Gyeong Jun.
Is it really
you, Gyeong Jun?
Gyeong Jun!
Gyeong Jun.
[Big]