Why didn't you move away?
[Episode 4]
Were you planning to go for it?
For crying out loud.
No matter how much you want it,
there's an 18-year-old inside this body.
It would have been a catastrophe
if I hadn't stopped.
How irresponsible can you be?
So this is how I would have felt.
This is how it would've felt
if Yun Jae had leaned toward me.
What?
So you two never even got this far?
No way.
We did,
but I didn't get to see it.
I was asleep when it happened.
I had pulled an all-nighter
for a school event,
so I dozed off when Yun Jae
went to get me coffee.
When it happened,
I was so startled that I did wake up,
but I couldn't open my eyes.
I should have opened my eyes right away,
but I lost the window of opportunity,
and I didn't know anymore
when I could open my eyes.
So?
So I kept my eyes closed all the way home.
Why couldn't I open my eyes then?
If only I had,
our relationship would have moved
forward at lightning speed.
Don't be too sad.
You might be mistaken.
You tend to get the wrong idea easily.
I was not mistaken.
But you said you didn't see.
How can you be sure it was
his lips that touched yours?
How can anyone mistake that?
Is she sleeping?
Maybe this is what happened.
It didn't feel like a quick pat like that.
Then...
She's drooling.
Maybe this is what happened.
It didn't feel like that either.
But then again, I didn't see anything.
This?
Was it like this?
Yeah.
Huh?
You jerk.
You jerk!
What?
Why did you hit me?
I was just trying to help because
you seemed so confused.
You can't help me. You're a little kid.
How dare you?
Why would you help me? Huh?
Stop. Stop. Stop.
If you keep kicking me, I'll plant these
on whoever I see.
They're not yours. They're Yun Jae's.
Precisely.
So why are you mad at me?
It was your precious Yun Jae's lips
that landed on yours.
Think of it as a rerun of a show you missed.
You had your eyes wide open this time.
So you didn't miss a thing, right?
Was it good? Was it?
You're not Yun Jae. You're Kang Gyeong Jun.
Since you know that,
stop making me play Yun Jae again.
I told you I'd rebel if you kept nagging me.
Where are you going?
Home.
To Kang Gyeong Jun's home.
So you didn't know Gyeong Jun was hurt.
Didn't my sister tell you?
Your sister?
You were talking to my sister
at school earlier.
Ms. Gil Da Ran is my sister.
I suppose you also met my brother-in-law.
Your brother-in-law?
They're getting married next month.
My brother-in-law's a doctor
at this hospital.
He's a doctor at this hospital?
You can go now.
How do Da Ran and Yun Jae know her anyway?
Why did they lie to me?
What now?
There's something I forgot
to give you earlier.
Come in, Ms. Gil.
Won't that give you indigestion?
It's so late at night.
Plus, it's very high in calories.
It's probably not healthy.
This dude's going to gain weight
and have an upset stomach.
Make sure you eat slowly. And brush
your teeth once you're done eating.
Just give me what you forgot
to give me earlier.
You may not like this,
but I think this is very important.
What now?
What do I have to do in Seo Yun Jae's stead?
This is what you've missed
at school since the accident.
You're a student.
You can't go to school, but you should
still keep up with your studies.
I'll help you.
Whose class notes are these?
The best student in your class.
Once I return, this kid will
become second best.
Why? Because I'll be the top student.
I did hear you had done quite well
back in the States.
Not just well. My grades were excellent.
I was beyond compare.
And if you want to keep that up,
you need to keep studying.
I will. I'll go to Seoul National University.
SNU?
I could go to Harvard if I wanted to,
but I promised mom I'd go to SNU.
That's why mom bought me this house.
I see.
I bet your mom is very proud of you,
given your good grades
and given how well you're doing for yourself.
I'll help you go to SNU, okay?
Really?
Then help me with this for starters.
It's math.
I specialize in Korean history...
This is integral calculus.
Gyeong Jun's fine. There's nothing
for you to worry about,
so go back home.
I'll tell him to get in touch with you.
He won't be able to call,
but I'm sure he'll text you.
Gyeong Jun's in a coma.
How would he have been able to text me?
Gyeong Jun, I'm waiting for you
to get in touch with me.
I want to know how you are.
At least text me before I leave.
She won't leave if I don't
text her, will she?
[Take care. Bye]
Take care.
Bye?
But she came all this way.
Was the message too succinct?
Darn it.
Where are you going?
You're Gyeong Jun's uncle, right?
Yes.
Are you Gyeong Jun's friend from the States?
Is is true what you told me over the phone?
Yes.
I'm going to take Gyeong Jun to the States.
If she's that close a friend,
why don't you just tell her the truth?
You don't know what Mary's like.
I doubt she'd cause you trouble.
Yes, she will.
Gil Teacher, Mary will now
try to stay by my side.
Gyeong Jun,
I'll be right here by your side, okay?
If she finds out I'm in this body,
she'll follow me around
24-7, day and night, around the clock.
No matter what I tell her,
she won't listen to me.
You can't reason with her.
Really?
Then she shouldn't know.
Let's go.
So there was someone who
was willing to take Gyeong Jun.
I know.
We'd need his doctor's authorization
to put him on a plane, right?
If the doctor's still around,
we could get Gyeong Jun
discharged tonight, right?
I'm sure there are morning flights to L.A.
He's in a good mood. He must have
decided to send me to the States.
What should we do?
How will we talk her out of it?
She already has your uncle's permission.
Like I said, you can't reason with her.
We need to shock her
and take her down by surprise.
It seems like you're just sleeping.
In fairy tales,
the princess awakens when
she is kissed by Prince Charming.
I told you to go home, and yet here you are.
Thank goodness I found out.
Mister,
why did you lie to me?
You're a liar, a quack, and a fraud.
I'll tell the hospital you lied
about your patient.
I never lied.
As you can see, he is being
well taken care of here.
I'm taking Gyeong Jun to the States.
I bet that's what he'd want, too
because no one here cares about him.
I bet he'd want to stay here
because the woman Gyeong Jun likes
is here in Korea.
Someone he likes?
But Gyeong Jun's not interested in anyone.
Oh, yes he is.
She's right here.
Ms. Gil.
Gyeong Jun likes Ms. Gil Da Ran.
Gyeong Jun
likes her?
Gyeong Jun likes me?
Sure.
He fell for her the moment he saw her
on the bus, so he got off with her.
Really?
He did get off the bus with me, but...
He then followed you around
and pretended to have accidentally
run into her at the furniture store.
That's not true, right?
We did run into each other
at a furniture store, but...
No way.
Gyeong Jun's not the type to follow
someone around like a stalker.
I caught him following
my fiancee around.
I met with him to talk some sense to him
when he told me this and that about his life.
You're lying.
No way.
Then how else would I know
so much about him?
As you said, I'm not the type
he'd normally befriend.
But she's not the type
Gyeong Jun would like, either.
He said he liked women who were
charismatic like Angelina Jolie,
so I've been trying so hard
to work on my charisma.
She's anything but charismatic.
He can't possibly like her.
But she's pretty.
He said she grew on him
because she was so pretty.
So the one Gyeong Jun needs isn't you.
It's her.
Your name's Mary, right?
I'll take good care of Gyeong Jun.
I'm his teacher after all.
She loses.
Game over.
Go, go!
It must have been a real shocker to her
that you like someone else.
Once I return to my body,
I can explain to her.
What you said isn't true, right?
You made up that whole thing
about how you like me, right?
But of course.
Don't tell me you were worried.
Talk about delusional.
All you had to say was that it wasn't true.
Mind your manners.
Yes, ma'am.
You tend to flatter yourself, Ms. Gil.
Why did he have to say he found me pretty?
That's what Yun Jae said.
I should have known.
You're not the type to take pictures
of someone you don't care for.
We got her good. You saw, right?
I must be a genius.
I'm so proud of myself.
But you don't feel the same way, right?
You don't like Gyeong Jun, right?
No.
I'm about to marry Yun Jae.
Be that as it may,
Gyeong Jun's much hotter than him.
That's not true.
In my eyes, Gyeong Jun's just a kid
who doesn't know better.
I'm not the type who'd play
childish games with my students.
Were you worried?
Talk about delusional.
You can never ever change your mind.
That will never ever happen.
You seem like a good person.
Gil Chung Sik's your brother, right?
Tell him I'm deducting
10 pizzas from his debt.
10 pizzas?
Excuse me.
This is Gyeong Jun's.
It's mine.
This is Gyeong Jun's favorite sweatshirt.
No. This is my favorite sweatshirt.
You want to be like Gyeong Jun, don't you?
No. He wants to be like me.
Stop copying me.
I wasn't copying you.
I did this, and then you copied me.
I did it like this.
What's the difference?
Did you just copy me? Stop copying me.
You're a super copycat.
Then you're a super duper copycat.
I told you not to copy me.
I said "super duper copycat,"
not "super copycat."
Then you're a super duper ultra copycat.
And you're a super duper ultra
copycat to the infinity power.
Infinity power to
the infinity power to you.
What you said times a 100 to you.
We'll have a lot of paperwork
to do to get him on a plane, right?
Probably.
Mary,
we just spoke with his primary care
physician, and...
We're not going.
Are they Seo Yun Jae's parents?
Yeah. They're both overseas.
What a relief. I don't have to
play the son at least.
Oh, right.
I think he called his mother often.
She must be worried.
What's the number?
Yun Jae?
I was worried because your phone
had been turned off for so long.
You're okay, right?
I've just been busy.
You can still make time
on that day though, right?
I'll be in Korea soon.
I'm sure your father
hasn't forgotten, either.
We'll discuss your marriage
when we get together, okay?
Okay.
Alright.
You seem to be busy,
so we'll talk again later.
Take care.
What's that day?
I don't know. It must be some kind
of a family gathering.
When could it be?
Doesn't Seo Yun Jae have
a planner? Look for it.
He must have the date saved
on his cell phone.
What's Seo Yun Jae's birthday?
I know his password.
You do?
I saw him type it in by accident.
I swear it was an accident.
Then why haven't you
checked his phone?
He had it password-protected.
He wouldn't like it
if I went through his phone.
He'd think I had no manners.
Gil Teacher,
are you going to make me
do all the dirty work?
I just told Mary a ridiculous lie.
That's how low I had to go.
I won't cooperate anymore
if you're going to be like this.
0624.
The password is 0624.
His password is 0624?
Yeah.
So it is.
0624... Is his birthday June 24?
No. Why?
Because my birthday's June 24, 0624.
It is a good number though
as it stands for the date
yours truly came into being.
Let's see.
Huh?
I think the family gathering
is on June 24.
There's no subject listed
for the date though.
I wonder what the special occasion is.
We'll find out.
He might have gotten urgent messages.
I should check to see if there are any.
Look at that.
His car insurance company
sent him a message.
Thank goodness I saw this.
[Lee Se Yeong, Car Insurance, Realtor...]
[Lee Se Yeong: Okay, let's eat together.]
[Yun Jae, want to grab lunch?
Then how about dinner? / Let's eat.]
Why is she always asking him
to eat with her?
She has been texting him
at least 2, 3 times a day.
There's nothing special though.
Did you see what I included
in the box of your favorite black tea?
With that, we won't have to
split tea anymore, right?
What did she give him with the black tea?
Seo Yun Jae...
Da Ran, you looked tired.
You came home late last night.
Did you not get enough sleep?
No.
When can you guys move
into the new apartment?
We're closing the deal today,
so we'll be able to start moving
things in next week.
The furniture and appliances
will be delivered next week.
You also have the wedding shoot,
and you have to pick up
the wedding gifts you ordered.
It's going to get very hectic for you.
No matter how busy things get.
don't fall behind on your studies
for the certification exam.
I won't.
May I be excused?
Why are you nagging her about
the exam? She looks so tired.
Da Ran,
are you not feeling well?
Pandora's Box was opened yesterday.
Pandora?
Is she from the States, too?
Say, how do you and Yun Jae know
Mary, the college girl from the States?
College girl?
No. She's your age.
That's not what she said.
She lied to me?
I should get pizza off the ledger for that.
Oh, right.
She told me to tell you she's deducting
10 pizzas from your debt.
What's that about?
Really?
Should I not bring up the whole college lie?
Insurance company. Bank.
Real estate agency.
Why are there so many places
we have to go to?
I'm not feeling well.
Tell them I'm sick and reschedule
everything for tomorrow.
We have to go today or Yun Jae
will sustain huge losses.
Fine.
$100 for each place.
I'll get this fixed when I get the money.
Oh, man. Why are they here?
We should.
It's so dusty in here.
We should clean this whole place.
Let's see. The kitchen's...
Clean?
At least they think I will be returning.
Ow, my neck.
What are you thinking about?
You've been like that all day.
Black tea...
Black tea?
No. We managed to close Pandora's Box.
Ms. Gil Da Ran,
I'm visiting Kang Gyeong Jun
at the hospital today.
Would you like me to give you a lift?
Look at how considerate you've become.
Thank you very much,
but I don't have to go to the hospital today.
You don't?
What a relief that I don't
have to give you a lift.
Geez.
He's always so snide.
Mr. Na, I have an engagement
near the hospital. Could I get a lift?
Bye.
It smells funny in here.
I can't smell anything.
I have a sinus infection.
[Incoming Call: BIG]
Hey.
Did you meet with
the insurance agent?
Everything went well.
The insurance company
hooked me up with a rental car.
I picked up a sweet ride.
It's awesome.
And I've come to pick you up.
A car?
You drove this?
Do you suppose I would have carried it over?
Are you nuts? You're too young to drive.
I have a license. I used to drive
back in the States.
This is Korea. Give me the key.
- No. It's mine.
- Give it here.
- It's mine.
- Hey!
You're too young.
Stop it. It's mine.
Hey!
No.
How do you do, ma'am?
It's nice to see you again.
So you're back.
It doesn't look like you're here
for your cab fare.
Do you need gas money today?
I apologize for the ruckus I caused.
I'll treat you to a nice lunch
to make amends.
Please don't.
I'm busy nourishing my mind
that I don't have time to nourish my belly.
If that's the case,
please allow me to treat you
to some literature.
"My son, fear a woman’s love,
fear that bliss, that poison."
Wow.
You know by heart
the most famous passage
in Turgenev's "First Love."
I only
know a few lines.
Your pronunciation is excellent.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
So long.
Where did you learn Russian?
There was a Russian chef who worked
at my mom's restaurant.
Give me the car key.
No.
Give it to me. The vice principal
is watching us.
So long.
What a relief. It's the same password.
Wow. This dude sure has a lot of money!
Luck you, Gil Teacher.
I can close the deal on
our apartment with this.
I thought we were going to lose
the deposit. What a relief.
I should stay at that apartment.
- Why?
- I almost got caught this morning.
My uncle came by to clean the house.
I guess he's decided to keep me around.
But that apartment will be our marital home.
I don't know about letting you move in.
Should I have Yun Jae's precious body
sleeping on the streets?
Fine.
I'll let you use the smallest room.
But my bed won't fit if the room is small.
Your bed? You're bringing that, too?
I can only fall asleep in that bed.
Didn't you say we had a lot to do?
These don't look like Gyeong Jun's clothes.
Hon,
whose shoes are these?
They certainly don't look like Gyeong Jun's.
Has someone been coming by here?
Oh my goodness!
Maybe Gyeong Jun's been
in touch with his father.
His father?
Even I don't know where he is.
How would've Gyeong Jun found him?
Maybe his mother told him, and he's been
seeing his father behind our backs.
No way.
Plus, Gyeong Jun's father has no right
or say in anything involving Gyeong Jun.
Once we get that bed
he dragged from the States
out of here, we'll be good to go.
How are we going to dispose of it?
It's too old to sell.
Who'd buy that junk?
We'll just have to trash it.
Having a car does make things
a lot easier though.
Look at the colors on that comforter.
That's so gaudy.
And the pajamas...
These are what newlyweds get.
This will look so cute on Yun Jae.
I hope it fits.
I can try it on.
Don't you dare.
What?
I don't mean to be rude,
but these are matching pajamas
and matching socks.
Yun Jae and I will wear them
as a married couple.
It's a bit weird if you were to try it on.
I wouldn't try it on even if
you begged me to.
So rude.
We'll move these in once we pay
for the apartment and get the keys.
But there's nothing there.
Where will I sleep tonight?
This isn't going to the apartment.
I'm keeping it in my room.
I'll find you a futon and a comforter.
Never mind.
I'll get my own bedding.
Where are you going?
We have to go get the bowls
and plates I ordered.
I'm not coming.
I can't use them anyway,
so why should I help you?
I'm off to get my own things.
Once you're done,
meet me at the realtor's.
You have to be there, okay?
Is he really mad?
But these are for Yun Jae and me.
Talk about exploitation.
All she cares about is this body of his.
We can let it go for lower than market value.
We need to sell it ASAP.
It's very clean. We should be
able to sell it for you very quickly.
Please make sure
all this trash is collected.
Sure thing.
Thank you very much.
I'll be in touch.
- Thank you.
- I'll see you soon.
The seller is almost here.
Your husband-to-be
will be here soon too, right?
Yes.
It's raining.
They say it's good luck if you
buy your house on a rainy day.
Thank you.
The person you're trying to reach
is unable to take your call.
He's running very late.
They say they're on a tight schedule.
The person you're trying to reach
is unable to take your call.
You're ignoring my calls?
You're dead meat.
Kang Gyeong Jun, where were you?
And why didn't you answer the phone?
What are you doing?
Were you moving your bed?
I'm not feeling well.
I'll come to the realtor's with you
some other time.
It wasn't something you could blow off
just because you were not feeling well.
I had told you many times over
just how important it was.
Please do me a favor and go.
Stop being a baby.
What...
What's the matter?
Why are you soaking wet?
I got rained on.
You should get changed then.
They threw everything out.
Uncle Hyeoksu had come by
to clean the house
because he wanted to sell it.
He threw all my stuff out,
so I was dragging them back in.
But it started raining, so I got wet.
Are you okay?
I told you I wasn't feeling well.
You never listen to me.
Let's go to your room.
I'll make you something warm.
Get changed, okay?
Drink this. I'll get you medicine.
Are you up? You should eat
and then take your medicine.
Come and sit down.
Finish that and then take the medicine.
You must be upset
that I ended up using what
you were saving for Yun Jae.
It was going to get used anyway.
You feel too sorry for me
to stay mad, right?
Let's go to my house.
I'll tell my parents I brought you over
because you're sick.
Do you want to sleep in Chung Sik's room?
No.
I'm sleeping in my bed.
I'll finish this and take the medicine.
You can go now.
You're still running a fever. Are you sure?
I'll make sure to take good care
of Seo Yun Jae's body, so don't worry.
Do you really think that's my only concern?
I know.
Right now, you're concerned about me.
How can you tell?
Your eyes aren't shooting love beams.
There's so much I want to do with you.
Please come back soon.
You missed an important exam because of me.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay. You don't have
to keep apologizing.
Are you going to take the teacher
certification exam eventually?
Yes.
I was quite confident this time,
so it's a shame I couldn't take it.
I'm not saying it's your fault.
But I think it is, and I should be
held accountable.
Pardon?
I have to take care of you
for the rest of my life.
Da Ran,
I kept you waiting for so long.
There's a surgery though. I'm sorry
I have to cancel our date again.
Oh...
It's okay.
We can go to the movies some other time.
Thank you for coming to see me though
despite how busy you are.
I'll get going then.
Da Ran.
Oh?
This seems to be a bigger
emergency than the surgery.
I'll call you after the surgery.
Okay.
You're going to withdraw everything?
- It's not spicy, right?
- No.
Is it Yun Jae's?
[Account withdrawal: 914,440 dollars]
A withdrawal has been made...
Wait a minute...
What?
That's him.
He wants to buy the house right away.
You were here.
I was scared you had run off
with Yun Jae's money.
Where would I run off to? This is my home.
Why did you take out so much?
Where's Yun Jae's money?
Oh...
I bought something.
What did you get?
What's this?
I bought this house in Seo Yun Jae's name.
This house is Yun Jae's now.
Gil Teacher.
But you said you had to buy a place.
This house is great.
I got it at an amazing deal.
I'll pay him back when he wakes up.
Gil Teacher. Gil Teacher.
I'll pay back the deposit you blew.
Come inside and take your medicine.
We'll talk when you get better.
I'm sorry.
I know it's your marital home,
but this house is all I have left.
I wanted to save it, but there wasn't
anything I could do,
so I used Yun Jae. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
You're done for if the housing value drops.
You need to take your medicine.
The realtor said the housing value
around here is bound to shoot up.
This area's going to get a subway station.
That's probably just a rumor.
I swear. Don't you feel better now?
Here?
No. Here.
This way.
Please place it here.
It's that bed.
Don't touch it.
I haven't gotten it repaired yet.
The gift from the radio station
for Ms. K of Dongjak-gu, right?
Let's see. Open it.
No.
I'm not opening this.
I don't care for this couch.
Couldn't you put it somewhere else?
Then don't sit here.
You can stay in your room.
- Are you okay?
- Ow...
Stupid.
Why you...
Let me make this clear.
This home now belongs to me and Yun Jae.
And you, Kang Gyeong Jun,
are just a lodger.
So you'd better do what
the landlord tells you to.
Why are you putting
Yun Jae's stuff in my room?
This isn't a storage shack.
I brought you over because you said
you'd deduct 50 pizzas,
but I still don't know why you insisted
on coming to my place.
Where's your sister's room?
It's the size of my bathroom.
Once Da Ran gets married,
this will be my personal fitness room.
She's definitely marrying that guy, right?
Of course.
She's crazy about him.
I don't like that guy one bit.
He's so similar to Gyeong Jun.
He's a Gyeong Jun-wanna-be.
My brother-in-law is
nothing like Gyeong Jun.
He's a great guy.
So are you saying Gyeong Jun's
not a great guy?
No.
I like Gyeong Jun, too.
See? I brought these
class handouts for him.
I'll deduct one pizza.
I can come by often, right?
Sure. You deducted 50 pizzas.
So aren't you going back to the States?
Nope.
I'm going to learn all there is to know
about your sister until Gyeong Jun wakes up.
I'm trying to find the education channel.
My parents are coming by,
so go and get some juice and fruit.
[Incoming Call: Lee Se Yeong]
So what did I leave behind
when I inadvertently
spent the night at your place?
I found this on the floor by my bed.
Huh? This...
Yun Jae,
are you returning this to me
or did you lose it there because
you were hung over?
Please don't confuse me.
Just give me a straight answer.
Are you going to hold on to
the key to my place or not?
It was the key to your place?
What?
I thought it was the key to the place
Da Ran and I were moving into.
Never mind.
I had given you the key to my apartment,
and because you held on to it,
I thought you were going to call off
the wedding and come to me.
If I was mistaken, let's just end this.
Oh, man...
This house is amazing.
But I thought you had gotten an apartment.
It's a long story.
This came from Yun Jae's place, right?
Yup.
We should put these away.
Here you go.
What could Se Yeong have put in here?
Hello.
Come, come.
- Where have you been?
- Yun Jae.
- Come eat.
- Yes, sir.
- Come and eat.
- Coming.
What took you so long? Where have you been?
You took the car, didn't you?
I told you not to drive.
Give me the car key.
Huh?
This is the key we saw
at Yun Jae's apartment.
Yeah...
I thought it was for our apartment,
but maybe I was wrong.
The realtor hasn't asked for it back.
It's probably to another place.
So what's this key for?
Why did Yun Jae have this?
Gil Teacher...
Actually, the key...
What about this key?
It's broken.
It doesn't work.
Really?
It's useless, so I'll throw it out.
It's Yun Jae's. You can't throw it out.
But it doesn't work. Why keep it?
I'll take dispose of it,
so don't worry about it.
We should come back tomorrow.
There's still more to do.
Your mother sent us that nice kimchi.
We should split that with the kids.
Yun Jae's there alone. He needs food.
But if he comes by our place often,
there's no need to split it.
With that, we won't have to
split tea anymore, right?
We won't have to split anything
if he comes by often, right?
That's right. He can have the kimchi
whenever he comes over.
He's closer by now.
Tell him he's free to come over
whenever he wants to.
Mom,
what do you give someone if you want him
to feel free to come over whenever?
Should we make Yun Jae a copy
of our house key?
He can come by and eat
even if we're not around.
Dad...
Could you pull over? I have to go somewhere.
Da Ran.
Da Ran, where are you going?
Hello?
Yun Jae, is Da Ran there?
No. Why?
She asked dad to pull over
all of a sudden and then took off.
It was odd.
She's not picking up.
I'm sorry to bother you,
but Se Yeong lives near the hospital, right?
Could I have her address?
Who is it?
Let go.
[Big]
How can you sit there
so brazen and shameless?
When Yun Jae crashed into you,
who do you suppose
he was in a hurry to get to?
It should fit perfectly.
The gentleman who ordered the ring
said he had the exact measurement.
They're hiding something
so it doesn't show.
They were arguing about whether
or not to go to the hospital.
The patient who was brought here
with Kang Gyeong Jun
was Seo Yun Jae?
If you're going to take him down,
should I keep watch for you?
No.
I'm going to feign ignorance
and just keep chugging along.