♪In a sudden instant♪
♪Dreams shattered and then recovered♪
♪Babylon's youth♪
♪Fearlessly living their lives♪
♪They keep moving forward♪
♪The noisy coastline in June♪
♪Reminds me of midsummer nights♪
♪The subtle emotions between you and me♪
♪No longer ordinary♪
♪Seasons come and go, steps never cease♪
♪Leaving behind evidence of existence♪
♪Watching time flow away♪
♪Anxiety gradually grows♪
♪Don't want to miss the scenery along the way♪
♪The scenery along the way,
evidence of existence♪
♪Dazzling you in my dreams♪
♪Are the source of my courage♪
♪The scenery in the air is amazing♪
♪Turn around to see the girl I miss♪
♪And the familiar nice wind♪
♪When this story reaches its conclusion♪
♪Perhaps it will be moving♪
=Young Babylon=
Huang Qing is really a jerk.
He has no humanity at all,
abandoning even his own woman.
He won't come.
You are just wasting your time.
You will surely be useful.
Although Huang Qing abandoned you,
there's still Lu Xiaolu.
What's Lu Xiaolu's phone number?
Lu Xiaolu and I
parted ways a long time ago.
Don't pretend with me.
I've got your phone.
What's the password?
I'll find it myself.
- I deleted his number.
- Boss Hu,
are you looking for me?
Lu Xiaolu, I knew you would come.
Release her first.
Let's talk about money.
I don't trust anyone now.
Because of the trouble you caused,
I gained nothing.
Huang Qing has fled now.
You give me the 300,000 yuan
he promised me,
and you can take her away.
Okay.
Release her first,
and I'll get the money for you.
Are you trying to pull a fast one?
I'll release her when I get the money.
Don't tell me
you don't have 300,000 yuan.
You are a big boss.
You have two hours.
Go back and get it.
If I don't see the money,
your little lover will suffer.
Don't touch her.
What?
Want to fight?
If you don't want to be disabled,
go back and bring me the money.
My wife's paralyzed because of you!
Nobody moves!
Don't move!
Li Guangnan!
How dare you attack me!
- Hit him!
- Come here if you wanna die!
Don't move!
Xiaolu!
Boss Hu,
your old friend is here to see you.
I've been waiting for this chance.
Dajiang,
why are you here?
Boss Hu and I are old friends.
Of course I should bid him farewell.
You came by yourself?
Are you also here
to play the hero and save the beauty?
You voluntarily came here.
Don't blame me for being heartless.
I didn't come here to fight.
I'm here to apologize.
Let's talk things out properly.
Just release them.
Apologize, huh?
Leave your fingers behind.
One finger for one person.
Let me cut off three,
and you can take them away.
Fine.
No problem.
Dajiang!
Boss, here is the chopper.
Lu Dajiang,
I admire you.
Dajiang!
Go!
- Hit him!
Dajiang, the chopper!
We've called the police.
You can't escape.
Xiaolu,
take them and go.
Xiaolu!
Let's go.
Dajiang,
the police are here. You should go.
Go find Ms. Tao.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine, I'm fine.
I'm really fine.
Take care of her.
Have a safe journey.
- I'll come visit you soon.
- Sure.
=Episode 26=
=Young Babylon=
(Dajiang,)
(just like in Fucheng,)
(there's a beautiful dock here.)
(The only difference
is that it snows in May.)
(I hope one day)
(you'll be able to see it too.)
(Yours, Tao.)
(Public Security)
(Hu Dafa)
(has long organized
and led a criminal gang,)
- (engaging in activities)
- Get in.
(such as kidnapping,)
(intentional injury,
and provocation of troubles,)
(which seriously disrupted)
(the economic and social order
of Fucheng City.)
(Hu Dafa has been lawfully arrested)
(and charged with organizing
and leading a criminal gang)
(and kidnapping, among other offenses.)
Looks like
it's really time to say goodbye
to this place.
Are you surprised?
No.
Bi and Huang Qing have been
brought to justice.
Since the government promised
to reimburse the workers
with the land sale proceeds,
this outcome is inevitable.
You can't go back to your company.
So what are your plans next?
I plan to study abroad
to see the world.
And you?
I plan to
continue the milk tea business.
If it goes well,
I'll open a chain store
and hire all the workers.
You haven't changed
after all these years.
Don't you think about yourself?
(Not selling land, abstaining, selling land)
The world is yours now.
You are the morning sun.
Master! Master!
We promised you
a grand retirement ceremony.
- Come on!
- Let's go!
Honorable retirement!
Today is our master's
honorable retirement day.
Let's wish our master peace.
And prosperity.
And have grandchildren soon.
Everyone, look here!
Go! Go!
♪Fearlessly living their lives♪
♪They keep moving forward♪
♪The noisy coastline in June♪
♪Reminds me of midsummer nights♪
(With the assistance of
Fucheng City People's Government,)
(Golden Peacock Food Factory)
(fully considered the opinions)
(of the workers' congress)
(during the enterprise restructuring
and disposal of land assets.)
(Matters like workers' placement
and compensation plans,)
(which directly affected their interests,)
(were subjected to democratic voting)
(by all the employees,)
(ensuring workers' legal rights and interests.)
(Consequently, the compensated workers)
(bid farewell to the food factory)
(Gongyuan)
(and entered into the wave of market economy)
(with the support from government policies.)
♪The scenery in the air is amazing♪
♪Turn around to see the girl I miss♪
♪And the familiar nice wind♪
(Blue Road)
This way, please.
I really didn't expect that
you would choose to
have your final meal here before leaving.
Remember when we used to
talk about coming here to eat?
Then we never had the chance.
Today, we're making up for it.
Do you remember
that time
we had dinner with our classmates
from the postgraduate class?
You ordered an eighty percent well steak.
Of course, I remember.
You protected my dignity.
But in the end,
neither of us got to eat.
Yes. What did we end up eating?
Fish balls?
Fish ball soup?
Right.
Fish ball soup.
So, do you want to
try an eighty percent well steak today?
Give it a try?
- These two appetizers.
- Okay.
- This Burgundy wine.
Plus two eighty percent well
sirloin steaks.
Eighty percent well?
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
Okay, let me check with the kitchen.
- Okay.
- Please wait a moment.
Do you think they can make it?
If the chef won't make it for us,
we'll do it ourselves.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Sir,
no problem, it can be made.
Two eighty percent well steaks,
right?
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
It's my duty.
Just now, our chef told me that
he makes eighty percent well steak
at least once a year,
so he's very skilled.
Please rest assured.
It looks like someone shares our taste.
What a coincidence.
Let me tell you some good news.
Just yesterday,
a big customer called me.
Guess who it was?
Afang.
How did you know?
Since the last time
you gave her the milk tea powder,
I had a feeling.
But if it were me, I would also
be willing to cooperate with you.
I believe that before long,
everything will get better and better.
Will you
come back then?
Who knows?
Yeah.
No one knows
what will happen in the future.
The next reunion,
who knows when it'll be.
♪I'll be on my way♪
I wish you
good luck.
And I wish you
success in everything.
Cheers.
Thanks for coming. Take care.
(Blue Road)
Let's part ways here.
♪The story is unclear♪
Farewell.
♪Don't even know how to cry♪
♪Be it anger or bitter♪
♪Take it and board a train♪
♪But I still have expectations♪
♪This kind of emotion,
it makes me uncomfortable♪
♪Indecisive♪
Sir, please wait.
Are you Mr. Lu Xiaolu?
That's me.
We're very familiar with your name.
There are messages for you
at the counter.
According to our service records,
it's from a lady.
She leaves you a note every year.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
(Today is my birthday.)
(I came alone and)
(ordered an eighty percent well steak.)
(The chef refused to make it,)
(and we argued.)
(I insisted,)
(and the steak wasn't delicious.)
(Blue Road)
(For Lu Xiaolu)
(I don't know if you'll come.)
(I'll leave now.)
(Best wishes.)
♪Fearing too many what ifs♪
♪Memories never seem to cease♪
♪Staying in the day we met♪
♪Vaguely, we've neglected it all♪
(Today is my birthday.)
(I postponed an important meeting,)
(came alone,)
(and ordered an eighty percent well steak.)
(The chef recognized me)
(and was very friendly.)
(He made it quite well.)
(I don't know if you'll come.)
(I'll leave now.)
(Best wishes.)
(Today is my birthday.)
(I have a slight fever,)
(but I had to come here to eat
their eighty percent well steak.)
(Because other places don't make it,)
(or they might not make it well.)
(The chef was delighted to see me)
(and offered me a cocktail.)
(He asked why I came every year)
(on this day
to eat an eighty percent well steak.)
(I said I couldn't help it.)
(I only love this kind of steak.)
(He advised me to forget the past
and start anew,)
(but I told him I couldn't forget.)
(I don't know if you'll come.)
(I'll leave now.)
(Best wishes)
(to)
(all those in love.)
♪Every restless night♪
♪Expectations grow a little more♪
♪Perhaps we don't understand♪
♪Always yearning for what's right in front♪
♪Right or wrong, we were never decisive♪
♪Fearing too many what ifs♪
♪Memories never seem to cease♪
♪Staying in the day we met♪
♪Just let it be vague♪
♪Mirage is all over the heart♪
(One year later)
- Congratulations, Master Niu!
- Thank you. Thank you.
- Come on.
- Cheers.
- The groom is here.
Come on, let's go say hello.
- Let's go.
- Hey, don't move!
I'm the father-in-law.
He needs to come and greet us.
We are the bride's family,
he should respect us.
- Absolutely.
- Yes, yes.
But we are also the groom's friends.
You are closer to the bride.
Yes, yes, yes.
- Xiaolu.
- Master.
What did you call me?
Dad.
You brat.
Did you prepare
what I asked you to prepare?
Don't worry, Master.
He prepared it wonderfully.
If it doesn't make me satisfied,
he won't be allowed
into the bridal chamber.
Master.
Okay.
- Guangnan.
- You two are here too.
Come on.
Be careful.
You are fully recovered, huh?
Just another month,
and I'll be able
to get rid of this wheelchair.
- That's great.
- Fantastic.
If I were you,
I'd pretend not to recover
and have Li Guangnan
take care of me for life.
Wouldn't that be nice?
Who cares about him?
He annoys me every day.
I can take care of myself.
Oh, Big Feet, congratulations to you.
I wish you a great married life.
And congratulations on
finally being able to stand up.
Where is Bai Lan?
She should be here soon.
She said she would come.
I'm handing Xiaoying over to you.
Don't mistreat her.
Of course.
Don't worry, Master.
Sorry, Dad.
Be careful.
Next up, let's welcome our groom,
Mr. Chen Guowei,
to deliver a speech.
Bravo!
Come on. Be confident.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Chen Guowei.
Today is
the wedding between Niu Xiaoying and me.
Thank you all for coming.
Great!
My father-in-law,
also my most respected master,
has asked me to give a wedding speech.
I've written a lot of
heartfelt words for Xiaoying,
but there are too many words
and I can't remember them all,
so I brought notes.
Oh, I forgot to take it.
As you all know,
I'm
not very good at speaking.
- No, we don't know.
- We don't know that.
We really don't know.
You do,
and Xiaoying does too.
And,
I've always
wanted to be a singer.
Even though I failed,
I've always felt that
I sing better than I speak.
So today,
at my wedding, I want to
sing a song
for Xiaoying
and all our family and friends.
Great!
This song
is a tribute
to our shared youth.
The song is called
"Young Babylon".
♪Stop searching and fleeing♪
♪I'm back here after the journey♪
♪Memories with mixed emotions♪
♪Close my eyes, I see our past♪
♪Factory chimneys spewing smoke♪
♪In the sweltering summer♪
♪We were young and didn't dream of tomorrow♪
♪Laughing heartily, joyously♪
♪Running through the heavy rain♪
♪Washing away all troubles and happiness♪
♪Stop searching and fleeing♪
♪I'm back here after the journey♪
♪Memories with mixed emotions♪
♪Close my eyes, I see our past♪
(Lu Xiaolu,)
(will we always be together?)
♪In a shattered, broken garden♪
♪On the coldest winter night♪
♪The youth fades gradually away♪
♪The empty backpack♪
♪The train ticket in hand♪
(Li Guangnan is my brother!)
(Come at me!)
♪There's still light♪
(Pass with Flying Colors)
(Gongyuan Golden Peacock Food Factory
New Year's Recognition Ceremony)
♪Stop searching and fleeing♪
♪I'm back here after the journey♪
♪Memories with mixed emotions♪
♪Close my eyes, I see our♪
♪Past♪
Thank you all for your applause.
I've finished singing.
If I
must say something,
I'd say,
Xiaoying,
I love you.
I'm incredibly lucky
to have met you in this lifetime.
Lu Xiaolu,
why are you crying?
What are you saying?
Who's crying?
I recorded it all.
Where did you go?
What took you so long?
I've been here for a while.
You didn't answer the phone.
Take a look.
♪In a sudden instant♪
♪Dreams shattered and then recovered♪
♪Babylon's youth♪
♪Fearlessly living their lives♪
♪They keep moving forward♪
♪The noisy coastline in June♪
♪Reminds me of midsummer nights♪
♪The subtle emotions between you and me♪
♪No longer ordinary♪
♪Seasons come and go, steps never cease♪
♪Leaving behind evidence of existence♪
♪Watching time flow away♪
♪Anxiety gradually grows♪
Look at them.
Big Feet,
can't you be more thoughtful?
You're walking so fast with the bride.
Can't you see Little Pouter
has trouble walking?
- I'm happy.
- She has you, right?
Stop saying that.
♪Are the source of my courage♪
Come on.
♪The scenery in the air♪
♪Turn around to see the girl I miss♪
Ouch! Oh my goodness!
What's wrong?
Come quickly.
- Go check.
- Come here.
- Come on.
- Be careful.
- Go take a look.
- Wait for us.
- Just go.
- Okay.
Be careful.
What's going on? What happened?
Speak up.
Xiaolu,
music!
Little Pouter,
since I first saw you
in junior high,
I've started to like you.
I, Li Guangnan, have liked you
for fourteen years!
What fourteen years?
Just thirteen years.
You've always been exaggerating.
Juan,
I love you.
Great!
Do you remember?
The first day we met,
I was holding that tape recorder
helping Li Guangnan confess.
Then we got into a fight,
I saw you
and took your suitcase.
Of course I remember,
you used my suitcase to fight
and broke it.
Later, I testified against you
to the police,
causing you
to miss the college entrance exam.
It was a chaotic day
but also the most
unforgettable one for me.
Me too.
Look,
who are those coming over there?
I miss them so much.
Beer, peanuts, melon seeds, mineral water.
Excuse me,
where are we?
Do you have melon seeds?
Yes.
I'll take a pack of them.
This is the train
from Fucheng to Shanghai.
What year is it now?
You are not totally awake?
I feel like I had
a very long dream.
Yes,
you were smiling
in your sleep just now.
We'll reach Shanghai station
in thirty minutes.
Shanghai station
is the final stop of this train.
Please prepare to get off.
♪Especially when it comes to love♪
♪But facing this loneliness♪
♪I realized my♪
♪Melting coldness♪
(The 1990s passed in the blink of an eye,)
(and my nineteenth year)
(felt like an endless maze.)
(My love is neither on this shore)
(nor the other,)
(but within the river itself.)
(Drifting with Bai Lan,)
(we passed through vast mountains)
(and expansive grasslands.)
(The water flowed swiftly.)
(Sometimes we drew close,)
(other times
unable to see each other's traces.)
(But I know,)
(no matter where or when,)
(as long as we both)
(strive to surface)
(and prevent the river)
(from engulfing us,)
(I will surely see you)
(and boldly shout your name,)
(for we are)
(forever in our youth)
(in this river.)
(And this river)
(is our eternal home.)
♪Memories constantly come to me♪
♪The story is unclear♪
♪All diaries are locked♪
♪Don't care♪
♪Don't even know how to cry♪
♪Be it anger or bitter♪
♪Take it and board a train♪
♪But I still have expectations♪
♪Stop searching and fleeing♪
♪I'm back here after the journey♪
♪Memories with mixed emotions♪
♪Close my eyes, I see our past♪
♪Factory chimneys spewing smoke♪
♪In the sweltering summer♪
♪We were young and didn't dream of tomorrow♪
♪Laughing heartily, joyously♪
♪Running through the heavy rain♪
♪Washing away all troubles and happiness♪
♪Stop searching and fleeing♪
♪I'm back here after the journey♪
♪Memories with mixed emotions♪
♪Close my eyes, I see our past♪
♪In a shattered, broken garden♪
♪On the coldest winter night♪
♪The youth fades gradually away♪