(Yuri) "That's only while I'm looking into your eyes."
"The power to hear the voice of the other person's heart"
"One day the girl"
"I met a boy with a kind heart."
"The boy conveyed a lot of love to the girl."
Unlucky…
What's this…
(footsteps)
(Theo) I'm home!Welcome home, Yuri
Are you hungry?I will make rice
You know... Theo-kun
Um... what did you do?
No, it's nothing, it's fine
It's 5 minutes
Out of print...
Unlucky…
The fate given to me...
Just a coincidence?
No, but...
Yeah?
＞
＜A new bakery has just opened there＞
Yuri-san doesn't seem to be feeling well.>
＞
(Mahiro) I'll sort it out once...
A picture book about the same abilities as Yuri
For some reason, Theo-kun had it.
And coincidentally, the story is →
Somehow it's linked to the memories of our love
Yeah... well
Furthermore, this is also strange
For some reason, Theo-kun
I had the author Min Ha Na's business card.
What do you think? Just by chance...
It really overlaps too much.
That's right. I don't know what...
There's more to this, right?
Yeah... I wonder if I'll understand if I read to the end?
Hmm...
No, I guess not?
After all, it's just a picture book. It must be a coincidence.
Yuri-san is worrying too much.
That's true…
(Thunder starts to rumble)
(thunder)
(Iiyama) Is this... for real?
(Lightning strikes)
Wow!
What's wrong!  ?
Mr. Turtle! ? (Kamei) Or… thunder… thunder.
Ita ta ta ta ta…
(Aihara) Kame-san! Are you okay?  ? It hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
(Nishina) Um... I was surprised by the thunder earlier.
I feel like my back is strained.
Eh!  ? Please wake up once and once!
I might not be able to do it anymore... Lightning? turtle…
Ha! Yuri-san! eh!  ?
＞
＞ Huh?
＞ Ha!
turtle!  ? it hurts!
Mr. Turtle! Tightly! Don't hit me! No no...
That picture book is no coincidence.
eh…
Yeah?
Isn't it good to talk normally?
Let me, the chocolatier, solve this mystery.
Solve the mystery after the chocolate
(chime)
Yes
Hello... Hello
I'm sorry you came to me
It's okay, I heard from Yuri.
Please, I apologize for the inconvenience.
Something… I’m sorry, it’s okay.
I'm happy because it's delicious when we all eat together.
Please excuse me
Is this...
Oh... are you hungry?
It's okay, the food is already done.
a little bit…
Please sit and wait
＞
＜OK？＞
Hey, Oppa, would you like to go to the convenience store?
I forgot to buy alcohol.
I'm not an oppa, okay?
Come on, let's go. Oppa isn't feeling well.
And there's plenty of alcohol.
I'm in the mood for wine today
wine? For Korean food?
Already... I'm going anyway! Oppa!
＞
Let's go!Take care
Chukanman... Hurry, hurry
Senpai, have you finally come?
Ha...
(Mahiro) Why, why did you come?
I'm trying to get in... Wait, no!
(Onoda) Hello hello
Why onoda-san?
Ah, I called.
It's delicious when we eat together
Please (Onoda) Thank you →
Excuse me
So no, I'm not an oppa.
(Mahiro) Well, Oppa means older brother, right?
(Onoda) If I remember correctly, in Korea, women →
When you call an older man, do you say oppa?
Yes, but Mahiro is older than me.
It's okay, I want to call you Oppa.
Let me call you!Is useless
Absolutely not! Why, stingy! Oppa!
Oppa Oppa Oppa!
Yes, this wine is delicious.
Thank goodness Mahiro-san is drinking wine.
I wanted to drink it, right?
Huh... oh well
Do you like wine?
Well... in its own way
(Onoda) Favorite alcohol is wine
Where is it produced? teeth?
How often do you drink? Alcohol may be strong or weak→
Also, behavioral patterns when drinking too much
Please also tell me how to deal with it...
Wait a minute...
What is it?
I want to research Mahiro-san.
Ha!  ? the study…
That doesn't make much sense... I'm sorry.
But... I don't know unless I know
After properly knowing and understanding →
I want to verify it again.
in my life
The existence of you
How does it work?
eh…
Yuri-san?
Let's go buy ice cream now!  ?
It's now
Eh... no, but...
hurry, hurry
Eh, no...
Yuri-san, this is where you read the atmosphere.
air?be careful
Yeah? Ah... ah!
Ah!
question
Can I continue?
yes…
Yuri-san
What if it's a little cold?
Ah... Yeah, just a little bit.
That's big issue
Whoa, my hands are cold
(Blows into hands)
It's an exaggeration, it's no good
It's still cold
(Blows into hands)
Theo-kun... you know.
Yuri-san?
Try closing your eyes
Yeah?
Wow hahaha...
Does this make you feel warmer?
Thank you Nikuman?
No, it's not a meat bun, is it?
So here's a quiz.
yes
What's inside this?
Hmm...
If it's not a meat bun, how about a steamed bun?
Ten which one?
That's different!
Curry bun
Pizza cunt
What else happened?
A special tip
Please try this
I'll enjoy having this
Hmm!  …Yeah?
Is this... a crab?
Ding dong den fufufu…
That's correct. It's my favorite Kananiman.
Hmmm
Theo-kun likes crab comics.
I did not know
Yeah
That's what I thought when I saw Mahiro and the others earlier.
I still have a lot
What Theo doesn't know
What is Yuri's favorite meal?
The best... hmm?
Maybe omelet rice
Is it omelet rice?Yeah
My father was a chef
When I was little, I often had them made at the store.
Ah... later
coffee and chocolate
I always had it served with food.
Yeah?Hmm
So our company is chocolate.
It's coffee, right?
But well...
Coffee from my company for dad
I've never had anyone drink it though.
I have one too
There are many things that Yuri doesn't know.
So I'm more
I want to know a lot
but…
Even if you don't know
It doesn't change
well…
Both the kind Yuri-san and the angry Yuri-san.
Any Yuri-san
This is my favorite Yuri
that's why…
I'm very happy now
Yeah
(Korean heart voice)
Me too... Thank you hehehe
Are you going back soon?Yeah
Ah…
Well, I'm here.
Do you want to send it?
Mahiro-san!
I will contact you again
eh?I still have questions left
(Onoda) I will send you a list later.
Well then
Onoda-san is a little different though.
You're seriously thinking about Mahiro.
is that so?
I'm more than a love interest
I feel like it's a research subject.
Fufufu…
Ha!That's right, Yuri-san.
I read that picture book!
eh!  ? I really read it!  ?
Mr. Onoda helped me understand my appropriate alcohol intake.
I only read 2 pages while I was concentrating on calculations.
I made progress and took some photos!
Thank you. What did you write?
that is…
If that power
If I could erase it...
(Mahiro) Do you want to erase it?
``The girl asked God.''
"Tell me how to get rid of this power."
"Then God told me."
"it is……"
《I am very happy now》
The most important thing...
(knock) Yes
Yuri-san, sorry to bother you.
Are you worried about whether to erase that power?
Won't you erase it? Yeah…
It's not so easy to decide
Yes, but if we don't hurry, it might get into trouble...
No, it's a picture book after all.
Is it true? Please...
(Hard knocking) (Kamei) President!
yes! Ta ta ta... It's hard!
Aitatata... Are you okay?  ?
Venture capital partners →
That VCP went bankrupt!
Yeah!  ? Oh my!
Ah…
(Hanaoka) That's a lie...
Venture capital partners...
A company that was planning to invest in our company
Isn't this pretty bad?
I don't think it's that bad.
The planned investment amount of VCP is
70 million bye! Itta... 70 million!  ?
If this continues, our cash flow will be short-circuited.
Is it possible to negotiate an increase with another company?
Let's give it a try.And also to the individual investors I know.
Please try it from all sides.
Again...
(Vibrator incoming call)
Sorry for a little bit
yes…
☎(Oki) Is it Yuri Motomiya calling?
☎Your father's condition has suddenly changed...
Huh... ☎I'm calling the teacher right now.
☎Motomiya-san, please come here soon!
Ah, President, thank you for your hard work, sorry!
Trouble will appear again soon!  ?→
It's tough being the president after all.
(Aihara) Yeah? Theo, what's wrong?
Lie... lie... no
This is not it
Absolutely not!
(Doctor) His breathing is stable now →
I don't think there will be any problems if things continue to recover smoothly.
Thank you very much
father…
good…
It was really good...
I'm really sorry. How is your father doing at a time like this?
Inflammation of the bronchial tubes
I feel like I'm having trouble breathing.
I've calmed down now so...
☎I will go to work after completing the formalities.
You don't need to worry about this for now.
☎Even if you stay by your father's side...
It's okay, I'll do something.
thank you…
I don't know if it's true but...
If it were true...
Maybe it's my fault that my father is like this...
＞
eh…
＜If it goes well, it will really give you strength＞
＞
That's true, but...
Because...
If I really run out of power...
And then with my dad...
but…
＜3 2…＞
＜1…＞
Yuri open your eyes
Yuri, listen first.
Thank you for being born as my father's daughter.
thank you
Just stop...
She was really small when she was born →
My father is →
When I touched that small hand →
I swore in my heart→
No matter what happens from now →
He will definitely protect Yuri.
So that day...
I was able to protect Yuri with my own hands.
Dad was proud
but…
Because of that, my father...
Yuri, are you misunderstanding something?
Dad is very happy now
And this too
Yeah...smells nice
Sigh... delicious
Yuri's coffee is the best in the world
(Sound of the second hand advancing)
I refuse…
As expected...
father!
After all, it's like this!
sorry…
Dad... I'm sorry.
I love you dad
Eh!  ?   ?＞
why!  ? Dad  Eh, oh >
＞
I can hear it! I hear you, Dad!
I wonder why>
＞
I don't know... I don't know though
good!
Ah, that was good!
It was really good!
That means >
＞
That's right, it's a picture book.
Why did I believe it was 33 seconds?
Ahaha... sorry
Ah, sorry!
Sigh...
I am hungry
Theo-kun! what happened?
Welcome home, is your father okay?
Yeah, it's okay now
relieved
Sorry for making you worry...
Umm... Did you eat rice?
Yeah?
It's delivery!
Wow! Ahaha...
please
Omelette rice?
Because it's Yuri's favorite food.
thank you
Delicious food
It's the best energy charge
That's why I'm happy and sad days
I will definitely eat rice
If I do that, someday
It will be a day when you can eat deliciously.
Thank you itadakimasu
Yeah? Yeah?
Hmm!
delicious!
Of course I made it
Yes Yes!
Theo-kun
Actually...
My father was in an accident a long time ago...
I've been bedridden ever since.
Yeah…
but…
Always the same and kind
Be positive...
That's why I have a father like that.
I've loved you forever
It's wonderful that Yuri takes care of her family.
Were you able to charge your energy?
Yes, ah...
Energy... Chunjo
Energy chunjong! Ahaha...
Chunjong!Yes, Chungjeong
bring dressing
(Vibrator incoming call)
(door opens)
gentlemen
I'm sorry for calling you so suddenly.
There's something I want to talk to Theo-kun.
That was 12 years ago at the field work.
This is when I visited Cape Kiritappu in Hokkaido.
I witnessed a fishing boat accident.
"Ah!  》
So he jumped into the sea to save the sea otter.
It was Yuri Motomiya.
Yuri-san?yes
But at that time
Trying to save Motomiya-san who was about to drown
her father...
I'm really worried about you two...
《Nice to meet you at Sochi University》
《Researching endangered animals》
《My name is Iiyama》
《Mr. Motomiya tried to help us》
《The sea otter was safely rescued》
"I'm really thankful to you"
(Iiyama) But... your father is →
His body became incapable of conversation.
I was worried about my condition, and since then I sometimes
I went to visit my father.
That's why I also talk about Yuri Motomiya.
I know unilaterally
your lover is so brave
I think he is a wonderful person with a kind heart.
But for her...
There's still a secret you don't know
Theo-kun
this is…
I thought it was my request as a father.
please listen
With her... with Yuri Motomiya...
please break up
If I have another chance
Thank you for your consideration.
Yes, please excuse me
Sigh...
Hmm...
(Vibrator incoming call)
yes
(Female) Are you Ms. Hanaoka from Dolce & Chocolat.?
☎(Hanaoka) Yes, that's true.
(Hana) This is Min, whom I met at an exchange event at Lake Akan in Hokkaido.
Mr. Min... Ah, what about that part?
☎(Hana) Actually, I watched the VCP news.
I'm a little concerned...
I would like to help if it's okay with me.
really! ? ☎Yes
I am interested in your company's activities.
Let's meet and talk sometime
I'm just going to Japan next week.
Thank you very much.
I will contact you again
Dad, how are you doing?
Was anyone coming? acquaintance?
Yeah?
《It's been a while. It's Iiyama.》
《I can hear you... right?  》
《If you could hear my voice》
《Even if you reply with a blink of an eye》
"is this good?  》
《Thank you →》
《Actually, I have something to ask Mr. Motomiya》
《Your daughter》
《About Yuri Motomiya's secret power...》
Eh... what do you mean?
Why is that...
《Before, my daughter and you》
《I noticed this when I saw you talking here》
《She... can hear the voices in her heart》
《(Iiyama) Isn’t that so?  》
《Is that so?》
《Actually, there is one other person besides me》
《There is someone who knows her secret》
《The person's name is...》
《(Iiyama) Yoon Tae-oh》
《(Iiyama) I am her lover》
《Please read this picture book first》
《There's no need for that》
《Theo-kun, I didn't expect you...》
《Do you already know? her secret
"yes i know"
"but…"
《I have already decided》
"I…"
《Be prepared...》
《Are you done?  》
《You… the ending of this book》
《You know, right?  》
"gentlemen"
《I am Yoon Tae-oh》