ISAMU NISHIZAWA AKA YANBOH (30) - RAPPER
BLOOM OR WITHER,
I LIVE LIFE ON MY TERMS
EVER SINCE WE MET,
I HAVE NO REGRETS IN LOVE
I'LL WALK MY OWN PATH.
NOBODY CAN TELL ME OTHERWISE.
FOR MY BELOVED,
I'LL MAKE THE FLOWER OF LOVE BLOSSOM
IF I'M FATED TO FALL,
IT'LL BE IN A BLAZE OF GLORY
THE PURE LOVE
IN MY HEART WILL BLOSSOM
LIFE IS SHORT,
BUT I'LL STAND TALL TILL THE VERY END
IF I MUST FALL TO RISE,
MY LIFE WILL PROVE IT
MY LOVE WILL GO ON
EVEN AFTER I'M GONE
Yanboh.
Unfortunately, you made a statement that
constitutes a serious breach of contract.
- It's something you said
- Okay.
- two days ago, in the home economics room.
It is unfortunate, but,
as of today, you will be expelled,
and you'll have to leave the facility.
What did I say?
You made a statement
that suggested drug use.
Huh?
No, I didn't.
I didn't talk about drugs.
I freaked out when I saw
the damage clause in the contract.
It sobered me right up, for sure.
I'm gonna stop doing illegal stuff.
- All of it.
- Uh-huh.
That's why I'm gonna stop lighting up
after the 17th.
Wait, hold on.
As you know,
it clearly states in the contract
that if you do something
that raises suspicion…
I know I said I smoked on the 17th,
but I didn't. That's the truth.
But you said something
that raised suspicion that you did.
And, of course, we have a responsibility
to protect the other people on this show.
I swear I didn't do it.
It was a poor choice of words.
I was just saying that I want to be
a better man from now on.
Maybe I said it differently
because I was drunk.
I don't know.
It was just me kind of bragging about
the things that I'd done in the past.
Those past stories got mixed up
with what I was gonna do,
and it just came out like that.
Oh, man, this can't be happening.
Yanboh, you're expelled
from the school, as of today.
I understand.
Mmm, I'd like to apologize,
if you don't mind.
I know you gave me
a great opportunity on this show,
and I'm responsible
for how this all turned out.
And like you said, I'm an adult.
But I was weak and I allowed alcohol
to cloud my judgment.
I probably just wanted
to make myself look cool.
Honestly, the fact that you had high hopes
for me, but now I have to leave…
I'm totally ashamed.
Yeah.
Once again, I realize
it's ultimately my fault.
I feel like I haven't grown at all,
making stuff up while I was drunk.
It's the lamest thing ever.
I'm sorry for causing trouble for you.
Excuse me. May I have a word?
Yanboh would like
to speak with you, individually.
I'm sorry. Could we have a moment?
HIKARU - AKA TEKARIN (21)
This is making me super nervous.
Can you stop filming for a second?
Why do we have to go one by one?
Stop filming for a sec.
I can't believe
this is happening. It's crazy.
Mmm.
Are you okay?
I want to talk for a bit.
Can you take a seat?
Mmm-hmm.
YURIA AKA BABY (25) - PAINTER AND TALENT
I got myself into some trouble.
Something I said while I was drunk,
violated the contract
we signed for the show.
Because of that, the plan to be here
for the next two weeks until the end…
I can't.
I feel terrible about it. I'm sorry.
Come on. Don't feel bad.
Hold your head high.
I can say, honestly,
I've been interested in you.
I think you're so pretty.
And I…
When you told all of us about your past,
I felt like I wanted to protect you,
to help you move past it.
And for me, when I have those feelings
for a woman, it usually turns into love.
I wish I'd had more opportunities
to talk to you.
I wanted to protect you.
Yeah.
But I ended up making you cry.
Can you promise that you're making sure
- to always protect yourself, also?
- Hmm.
Thank you.
I guess I'll go.
I'll be back.
May I sit?
Why so far away?
Let's sit closer.
I don't want to talk from that far away.
Wait a sec.
I need to calm down a little first.
Well,
so I'll get straight to the point.
I'm leaving this place today.
I got expelled.
So, I'm not going to be here
for as long as we all expected.
And honestly, I just want to, you know,
hit myself.
I was ready to turn things around today.
Everyone could tell that you were trying.
And also…
I mean,
I knew what was happening.
I saw how others reacted.
I could have guessed
this was happening, but…
Honestly, on the first day,
I looked at everyone and thought,
"I'm here to find love,
but I might not have
the confidence to do it."
But then, I don't know,
when we were in the sauna yesterday,
and I got to talk with you one-on-one,
and that's when I realized
that, deep down,
you're such a thoughtful person.
I don't know.
I'm sad, but,
I'm feeling a lot.
Like, I feel sad, but there's also
nothing I can do.
This is just so tough.
I liked your personality a lot, seriously.
And so, I hope you keep doing your best.
I don't think I can move on
from this right away.
But…
I don't want you to be expelled.
Well, me neither.
You're the cheer squad leader now.
You're kidding, right?
- Really?
- Here. It's a good luck charm.
- Hmm.
- That's truly all I can do.
- Look at it when things get hard.
- Hmm.
I hope it reminds you of me.
- Well… I'm sure.
- Are you sure about this?
- It's a symbol of our friendship.
- Mmm.
Please, look after everyone for me.
I'll do my best, squad leader.
I'll do my best.
I'm happy to have met you.
Goodbye.
I'll miss you.
This sucks.
- So much. I'll miss you.
- I know.
I'm so sad.
Bye-bye.
This is painful.
I trust that you won't
make the same mistake I made.
It'll be fine.
No one else has a problem
running their mouth like I do.
But, just in case,
you should maybe keep it in mind.
Even the small stuff
might get you kicked out.
So, you know,
I just hope you can learn from my mistakes
and do your best.
You've got this.
That's straight up.
I'm in this to win this, bro.
You better.
I mean it, for real.
- Count on me.
- Nice.
- I'll be in touch. Yeah.
- Okay. Can't wait, man.
We'll miss you.
- We're brothers. So close in age.
- Yeah.
Hit me up. Visit me in Kansai anytime.
- Dude, of course.
- I'll do the same.
- I'll do my best for you.
- Yeah, you better.
You got this. Don't get all sad.
Too late.
- Pissed off, actually.
- All good, man.
Do Kyoto proud for me. All right?
Well, I'm out.
See ya.
I thought maybe I would finally
fall in love, you know?
It's like,
so shocking, but it's also super sad.
I'm just gonna miss him.
Sorry to barge in!
Wow.
Here, look at this.
- You wanna be "it"?
- If you move, you lose, right?
You're done for, saying stuff like that!
This generation of kids, man.
They don't get me yet.
So it's up to me
to make sure that they do.
I know, it sounds crazy, right?
- It's wild.
- Not so crazy for you maybe.
But they were so cocky,
they'd never back down.
- Even if I hit them.
- So cocky.
So cocky, they'd be like,
"I don't even care if Isamu hits me."
"I'm doing it."
That's the level they'd be at.
I thought it was awesome.
What is happening?
I don't know myself anymore.
I tried so hard not to cry.
I mean, I just don't even know
what to do anymore.
Can I be alone for a bit?
NAGANO
- Oh, gosh.
- What was that?
- Right away.
- That was so intense.
- How long have they known each other?
- I know!
- How many days has it been?
- Three years?
Three years.
You'd think they've known
each other forever.
- Three days.
- I felt like sobbing too.
Honestly, I think it's only been
three or four days.
Time is irrelevant.
I think people, you know,
find a strong connection
when they're
in these heightened situations.
- That's what it is.
- Very intense.
When I first got the call about it,
I thought the show would totally be over.
- Ah.
- Let me explain.
In order to protect the cast members,
we can't tolerate
the use of any type of drug.
As soon as we saw suspicious behavior,
we had to expel him, of course.
- Yeah.
- Especially since he has a record.
- Right. Yeah.
- That's how society works.
- Just the way it is.
- That's how it is.
If you choose to break the law,
you'll lose your chance
at possibly finding love.
- That's right.
- Coming from the world of the yakuza,
he's got to know,
he has to take responsibility for that.
- That's true.
- It's a shame though.
- A real shame. I wanted him to keep going.
- Such a good guy.
And his romance with Tekarin
was just getting started.
It sure looked like it was about to start.
Tekarin was probably already
head over heels in love with him.
For sure.
Maybe when he said he stopped lighting up,
he meant lighting up her bed.
He was probably just talking dirty.
He's going abstinent till it's over.
I didn't hear anything about marijuana.
Enough of that.
- We can't forget about Tenten.
- Oh, right, Tenten. I forgot.
- Yanboh was such a shock. Seriously.
- Oh, man.
Tenten will bounce back.
- Yeah, think so.
- It's gonna be hard for her now.
Everyone was hugging each other.
It got deep right away.
But I've got high hopes.
Let's see what happens.
I wonder where all
their romantic journeys will go from here.
- It's quiet without Yanboh.
- Mmm.
- He didn't talk much, though.
- True.
MILK (22)
TSU-CHAN (30)
TACKLE (24)
Morning.
- Good morning.
- Hey.
- Morning.
- Good morning.
That's not milk, is it?
Is there milk in this?
Wow, Yanboh's stuff is still here.
- You're using Yanboh's cup?
- Mmm.
YANBOH
And you're in his spot.
- I've got to.
- Mmm.
We're from the same town.
What about the necklace?
- I put it on.
- Not on your neck?
Thought it'd be too visible.
I told her that it'd be
too much of a reminder.
I thought about it,
but they told me not to.
It's better to wear it here
than not at all.
Yeah. Yeah, okay.
I bet the transfer student
is gonna show up soon.
- For sure.
- Oh, he's coming.
- That's why we've all got sunglasses on.
- Hmm. We're ready.
- He's here!
- Oh!
- Tenten!
- Nice to meet you.
Hello. My name's Tenten.
I'm the transfer student.
Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Been a minute.
Feels awkward all of a sudden.
- Of course.
- Of course, it would be awkward.
Come on.
What were they expecting?
The guys are all pretty tense.
Oh. Got it.
Should we introduce ourselves?
- Sure.
- I mean, the girls already have.
So let's have the guys do it.
- I'm Tackle. Nice to meet you.
- Okay.
- You too.
- Be good or I'll tackle you.
Okay. Got it.
- Next is Nisei.
- I'm Tackle.
- Tackle?
- Scary.
- Another one.
- Next.
- What?
- That's harsh.
That's it?
- Your age?
- What do you wanna know?
- Well--
- I'm 27.
- 27? All right.
- So scary.
- You're giving bad vibes. My opinion.
- Bad vibes?
You know, in my experience,
guys like you are cocky.
- That's tough to hear, right out the gate.
- Yeah. Tough.
I don't get why a host from a nightclub
would come on this show.
- I'm a host, but--
- If you get a girlfriend here,
would you give up your job?
Yeah, of course, I'd quit.
Yeah, that has to be the plan, right?
I get a girlfriend and quit.
What's with that?
Tsuu's back to bullying.
Tenten, the transfer student,
is a little behind the others.
He'll need to catch up.
So we've prepared a date for him.
Hold up. Bad play, bad play.
That's going too far.
I haven't gone yet either!
Please choose one girl
you would like to talk to.
He's got it good.
Wait, that totally changes the game.
But he got here later.
- I'd like to talk to…
- This is special treatment.
- …Oto. I choose Oto.
- Yeah?
- I'd appreciate it.
- Let's go then.
But seriously, that's great.
She hasn't gone on a date yet.
- Yeah? Great. Let's go.
- Have fun.
This is crazy.
- Take care, you guys.
- Off we go!
- Watch your step on the stairs.
- Okay.
You can't climb
these stairs without sneakers.
- Wait, that's a real horse.
- There's a horse?
They're kind of cute.
Sorry I scared you.
There's more over there.
- Wow, there are so many horses.
- I know.
I've ridden horses for a long time.
Wait. You can ride horses?
- Yeah, I can ride.
- That's cool.
My dad races horses.
He works as a jockey,
so I've been riding for a while.
He thought I'd be a jockey too,
so he made me ride horses
for years and years.
I've ridden horses more formally
for horse shows.
And I've raced them, as well.
- He went to juvie?
- He went to juvie.
- I wonder why.
- Yeah, I honestly have no idea.
Like a member of the royal family.
He can ride horses.
- He's got a bourgeoisie vibe about him.
- He does.
I wonder what turned him
into a delinquent.
Take a ride?
- That okay?
- If you want.
- I want to.
- Sure.
What's this horse's name?
- Juju.
- Oh, Juju. I like that.
- Juju is a cute name.
- I know, I love it.
- She's a girl, yeah?
- She is.
I'll get on. Okay.
She had a fall three years ago.
She's a mom.
- Ah, I see.
- Oh, wow! Amazing.
Crazy. How do I look?
- You look good.
- Thank you.
- You look like a prince.
- Yeah?
- You're going so fast!
- She's such a fast girl.
- Look at you! You're a natural!
- Yeah!
- The girls were talking…
- What?
How it'd be nice
if you showed up like a prince
on a white horse.
- It looks like you're the real deal.
- That's right, I am.
- So fast!
- This horse likes to show off.
That's amazing!
- This is easy. Don't worry, I got this.
- That's so cool!
Let's ride.
- I don't know if I can.
- Let's ride.
- I got it.
- It's like getting on a bicycle.
Oh, look at that.
- Nice, she's getting on.
- She's doing it!
- There you go.
- Prince Charming.
- Are you on?
- I'm on.
This is so special.
There's a new romance in the air.
Oh, wow!
When I first talked to you, I thought
you seemed a bit wild, but pure-hearted.
- Yeah?
- In a good way.
You could sense that right away?
- That's the impression I got.
- Wow.
Just from talking to you.
- That makes me happy.
- So, that's why
- I wanted to talk more. Yeah.
- Mmm.
- When was your first love?
- High school.
- First or second year.
- Seriously? Pretty late.
- Strict parents.
- Oh.
My parents were strict too.
That makes kids act up.
- I went wild at one point.
- Yeah.
- Super strict?
Same here. Yeah.
- Have you ever been arrested?
- Overseas.
- Abroad? You're wild!
- Yeah.
Quite the conversation.
"You've been arrested? Wild!"
- Right?
- That's not a normal question to ask.
"You've been arrested?"
It's a great icebreaker, I think.
"Ever been locked up?"
No, no. Never been arrested.
I was raped in my first
or second year of high school,
and so, that's the reason
I started acting out.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
When I was 16,
I went to a Juvenile Assessment Center.
- Really?
- Then Juvenile Training School.
The reason I ended up
in Juvenile Training School
was because my girlfriend at the time
was assaulted by some bad kids,
and I went too far in my revenge.
How did it feel
going to the Assessment Center?
Were you mad at your parents?
I felt a lot of things towards my parents.
After the Assessment Center,
as soon as I was assigned to juvie,
they started crying.
- Both of them. Yeah.
- Ah, yeah.
I thought, "Why was this bad?
It was for my girlfriend."
But, in the end, I realized that
making my family sad
was not good for anyone, you know?
So I thought I'd get my act together.
- It's crazy when I got arrested.
- I bet.
Like, I felt so relieved
when I got caught.
- Relieved? Oh, why is that?
- I had been acting out.
I'd been bad for a while,
but my parents never found out.
- I was good at hiding that from them.
- Right.
Part of me felt like I was never
going to fit into normal society
because of the way I was.
Then the arrest…
I felt super relieved after that.
- Got you.
- I felt liberated.
Right.
I thought,
"Now I don't have to hide anymore."
I decided not to hide anything
from my mom, you know?
- So it was a good thing.
- Yeah, that's why it was great.
I don't think many people feel relieved
after getting arrested,
- but that's why I'm a special case.
- Yeah, that's unique.
I was a little scared, at first.
- Just because you're a host, you know?
- I get that. Understandable.
So if we can both get past that,
I think we could get along great together.
- Know what I mean?
- Uh-huh.
- But our pasts are so similar.
- True.
So I feel like, "What should I do?"
- I get it. Confused?
- I'm confused, you know?
Tenten's a great guy, right?
He seemed like kind of a jerk
when he first showed up.
Mmm.
- He protected the person he loved.
- To protect her.
That's why he got in trouble.
He hurt the people around him
and ended up in Juvenile Training School.
- You know?
- But Oto, she's super honest.
Yeah.
Most people would find it hard
to say what she said,
but she came right out and said it.
- Mmm.
- Yeah, I like that.
- That's a great quality, right?
- It's pretty wonderful, I think.
Let's work on the children's cafeteria.
We're gonna use this
to paint the hoop toss game.
And then, after that,
we'll get to workover there,
do what needs to be done.
The cooking team should start cooking.
- What are you doing, Tackle?
- I cook.
- Can you help?
- I'll do it.
Tackle asked Kii to help with the cooking.
- You know we got this. Yeah.
- For real?
Baby, you want to cook?
- No way.
- Me neither.
- I'll work with Baby then.
We'll make the cotton candy sign.
Are you guys fighting over her?
Don't you think
it'd be better if he cooks?
Rock, paper, scissors!
Show her what you're made of.
- She knows what I'm made of.
- Let's go! Rock, paper, scissors.
Give it everything you've got.
You got this.
- "You got this."
- Here we go.
- Let's do it.
- Bring it on.
- Tsuu, start us off.
- Ready?
One, two, three, and shoot!
You're a loser!
That's how the world works.
- It is what it is.
- Nisei's good at winning.
Okay, so, Tsuu,
you're in charge of sign making.
- Sure.
- The chief.
- Are you changing?
- Yeah, for sure.
Let's meet up after.
I don't need to change.
These are work clothes.
BADLY IN LOVE
Is it just you and me, man?
Get that desk out of the way.
- Better keep an eye out.
- For what?
- You better watch out.
- I might fall for her too.
I'm watching you. You got it?
Better do a good job.
Shut up, loser. You're a wuss.
Can he give him the finger?
- "You're a wuss."
- Right to the camera.
He talks too much.
Okay, okay, I got this.
Is this the paint?
I sanded it,
and I think I'll use purple, for sure.
- You like purple?
- My favorite.
My university school color is purple.
- Oh, really?
- I wear purple when I box too.
Oh, yeah? I bet purple looks great on you.
- You think so?
- Yeah.
- Then I'll wear purple every day now.
- Purple from head to toe.
They'd arrest me, or expel me.
- Do you girls talk about love?
- Sure we do.
Oh! Wish I could hear it.
But the guys share stuff too, right?
We do.
About love?
- Yeah. About lots of stuff. Love included.
- Oh, yeah?
Like what? We can't figure out
who you like, Tsuu.
- Me?
- We think you don't like anyone.
Do you think you know mine?
- Who's mine? Mmm.
- Your crush?
It's always been you.
- Oh! Look at that.
- Really?
He just went ahead and said it.
Straightforward is nice, right?
- Definitely.
- Mmm.
Look at me. I'm serious.
You can see it in my eyes. I'm for real.
- Your eyes always look like that.
- Come on. No way.
I think you're the cutest.
But I don't quite know you yet.
- Oh.
- You know?
But you don't quite know me either.
Yeah, since we've only talked a little
while we smoked.
Which guy made
the best impression on the girls?
I think the new guy
made a big impression on everyone.
- Today?
- Yeah.
The new guy, huh?
FOLK CAFE HARENOYA
Back in the day, I wasn't as…
I have had some work done on my face.
I wanted to look as good
as any handsome guy I might be with,
so I got some plastic surgery.
- I wasn't confident in my looks.
- Got it.
- That's not weird for you?
- That you got plastic surgery?
- Yeah.
- That doesn't matter at all.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
Honestly, I'm self-conscious about it.
Because I got plastic surgery,
I, like, worry
whether it's okay with the guy.
I'm still not confident.
When it comes to plastic surgery,
- I don't judge it.
- Mmm.
I like people
who want to better themselves.
Plastic surgery is just one way
to improve yourself
and make yourself more beautiful,
so I don't mind at all.
- Honestly, no.
- Really?
It doesn't bother me.
- I feel a little better now.
- Do some people judge you?
- I want kids, you know?
- Mmm.
So, sometimes, I worry
- that my kids won't look the same as me.
- Oh, right.
Oto is super open about this stuff.
I think it's wonderful.
If the guy you're with
is super handsome, it'll be fine.
I've got strong genes, no doubt about it.
Worry not, they'll look like me.
- All good.
- For sure.
Whether it's a boy or a girl,
they'd have my face.
You know, it's rare to find someone
whose background is a lot like mine.
We were able to have
a super deep conversation.
He's such a good listener.
He was open to what I had to say,
and he's super kind and such a gentleman.
My impression of him has changed a little.
He's so cool.
Looks great.
- Good?
- Nice.
Yo, Kii. Let's make takoyaki.
- How do you make that?
- Takoyaki?
Five hundred grams of takoyaki mix,
that can feed five.
Oh, that's close.
- How much water, then?
- For the water…
Two thousand milliliters.
Really?
- Two thousand milliliters.
- Not 200?
Got to be 200.
Is it supposed to be this sticky?
- Should we make 'em chewy?
- We're going for doughy.
Too late. Just pour the batter in.
- They're vibing right now.
- Cute couple.
- Maybe we didn't add enough water.
- It's all gooey.
Why is that?
They're supposed to sink
when you add them.
I thought so. Maybe we push 'em in?
And turn them over?
They'll end up looking like pancakes.
Okay, let's just keep
turning these over like that.
They're coming along. Looking good. Yeah.
- Looks great.
- You a master chef?
- Looks like cheese to me.
- Yeah, it totally does.
That doesn't look quite right.
Looks good. I'm getting hungry.
- All done.
- Okay, give one a try.
Not my fault if it's bad.
Isn't it hot?
It's hot?
That's so cute.
Pretty good, actually.
I mean, they look delicious to me, anyway.
Yeah, totally.
- We're home.
- Welcome back.
What are they holding?
- What? Flowers.
- We got flowers.
- Yeah. We arranged them.
- So cute!
- Real flowers?
- Yeah.
- They're real.
- They're pretty.
First, we went horseback riding.
- Horses?
- Rode horses?
- I've ridden horses.
He's like a prince, riding in on a horse.
You're even dressed in white.
No way.
He's hilarious.
A horse-riding prince?
Dressed in all white?
There's some leftovers.
- Help yourselves.
- I want some takoyaki.
- Go ahead.
- Takoyaki's good.
It was, right?
- I'll try.
- One bite.
Okay, let's see how it tastes.
- Tastes like takoyaki?
- It tastes like takoyaki.
- But?
- No octopus.
- No, there is.
- It's got octopus.
Mmm.
It's not that good.
- It's kind of bad.
- Come again?
- It's not very good.
- One more time?
It's kind of gross.
- Go for it!
- Get him!
- Get him, Tackle!
- Oh, my gosh!
- Whoa, crazy.
- Oh, my God!
That was a serious tackle.
- For her.
- He likes her, so…
Holy shit!
Amazing!
- Way to go!
- Incredible.
- First tackle.
- Why'd you tackle him like that?
Because he insulted the food we made.
- What?
- So cute.
That's sweet.
Of course, he'd get mad at that.
- Kii looks so happy.
- Makes sense.
That's the first tackle we've seen
since we got here.
He tackled him like, "What are you doing?"
"Are you disrespecting my girl, Kii?"
I love it when guys do stuff like that.
I appreciate that he's so loyal
to one person.
I could be happy with someone like that.
He should've just lied
and said it was good.
I mean, Kii made it.
Truth is, it was pretty bad.
It didn't taste like takoyaki at all.
I want to confess my love to Kii soon.
I hope she feels the same.
Then I want to tackle her.
A love tackle.
Getting tackled was, ultimately,
a good thing for Tenten as well,
because, you know,
guys were annoyed with him.
- But with that tackle,
- Yeah. Yeah.
he looked like a loser for a second.
It helped them blow off some steam.
Yeah, they were thinking,
"This guy's a jerk."
It's a rite of passage
to give newcomers a beating.
Oh! Is that so? I see.
- That makes sense.
- They were initiating him.
- It could have been worse.
- Yeah.
- It wasn't that bad.
- I see how it is now.
- Time for the sauna.
- Sauna time.
This sauna date
should be chosen by the boys
after discussing amongst themselves.
- Nice! Hell, yeah!
- Me, me, me!
Tsuu, step up. This guy wants it.
No way I'm backing down on this one.
- I ain't backing down either.
- How do we choose?
Whatever you want.
Let's throw a dart.
Closest to a bull's-eye wins?
- Nice idea.
- That'll work. Yeah, yeah.
Good idea, pretty boy.
I'm totally going with Kii.
- Thought so.
- So much confidence.
- He's so sweet.
- I'll help you out, Tackle.
- He's adorable.
- I'm going with Kii, for sure.
- Rock, paper, scissors.
- It'll decide the order.
They're getting right to it.
- Tackle is asserting himself.
- He's making a move.
Here I go.
- Okay!
- Look!
- Good.
- Nice.
- Who's next?
- Me.
If you win, you'll go.
I'm out.
- No way I'm losing this.
- It's not over yet. Come on.
- Anything could happen, right?
- Both out.
- We're tied.
- So lame.
- Yeah, but…
- It's so close.
I'm so pumped for this!
- Give it all you've got!
- I'm gonna crush this!
- What?!
- No way!
- Such a wimp!
- My turn.
Ah!
Man, I've already won.
What the heck? Hold up!
This is my big chance.
- Can't believe it.
- Too funny.
You can do it.
- Wow, that was amazing.
- Yay!
- Amazing!
- Nice shot.
- Whoa! What a shot!
- He's finally getting some action.
Tsuu's feelings are still
a mystery, right?
- A total mystery.
- I wonder who he wants to go with.
I don't know.
You did it!
- Nice shot!
- Nice one.
- Happy for him.
- I'm happy.
- Tsukahara's got game.
- Congrats!
- That felt incredible.
- What a shot.
Sorry, guys. I'm headed to the sauna.
No one has any right
to complain after landing
- such an incredible winning shot.
- No way, it was the best.
- Let's go.
- Ah!
- Looks like we're going.
- Let's go.
Whoa!
- So it's Kii.
- That's who it is.
- Good luck, man.
- Sorry, guys. I'm out.
Go on, get out of here.
- I did win.
- Go on, you big winner.
From now on, I'm number one.
Oh, is that so?
- Tackle does not look happy.
- See you all soon.
REFRESHED
NATURAL HOT SPRINGS & SAUNA
Hold up. This looks so wrong.
- What's happening?
- Like a yakuza movie.
Is this normal for a dating show?
This is still a dating show. Don't worry.
- Damn! That's cool.
- What?
- Oh, so cool!
- Awesome, huh?
- Crazy, huh?
- Amazing!
No wonder they were all so impressed.
- This is my first time seeing it.
- Are these Jacuzzis?
- Jacuzzi, or a cold bath.
- Oh, separate tubs.
So cool! You want to jump right in?
- In we go.
- Finally got picked first.
That last throw was fun, right?
So crazy.
It was a good thing you went last.
- For the best.
- Yeah.
- Yay!
- "Yay" is right.
- "'Yay' is right"?
- That was some sick teamwork.
- I was shaking, for real.
- You were shaking?
The sauna is great.
We could pour water on stones
in here, no doubt.
Are you sad?
She's in a swimsuit, you're missing it.
I wanted to be the first to see it.
Totally. Of course.
- Swimsuits are sexy, right?
- Mmm.
- I'm getting marbled skin.
- Amami?
Is that, like, sweat that's sweet?
It's when your blood vessels
get super blotchy, like this, here.
You see it?
- And here. That's amami.
- I see it.
I thought your skin was turning sweet.
- That's not it.
- Like honey for bees.
No, no, that's what it's called, amami.
Really? Amami?
I still don't get it.
When your skin turns red like this,
it means the sauna is a good temp.
- That's what that means?
- Yeah.
- I've got it too. Look at that.
- Look, you've got it good.
That's good amami going on.
Damn, I'm gonna lose it.
Tsukahara,
he's seeing Kii in her swimsuit.
We're already halfway through.
Damn it.
That's crazy.
I think you should give love
a real chance. You know?
- Oh, yeah?
- Maybe it'll be wild, you'll feel younger.
I'm not made for it.
You said you broke up
with your last girlfriend,
but you still loved her,
because you didn't want her to move
- and put her kid in a new school.
- Exactly.
My ex had her own house,
and her kid was getting older.
Her family had settled down
and were happy where they were.
I decided to move back to my hometown
so I could open a bar.
When I told her,
she said she'd come with me,
but she had a house
and her kid wasn't little anymore.
They had friends in the neighborhood,
and at school.
I didn't want her to move with the kid,
so I said, "We got to break up."
I totally loved her.
Even though we loved each other,
we still broke up.
- That's hard.
- It was tough.
- I bet it was.
- Yeah, really tough.
A relationship after that sounds hard.
You haven't dated since then?
There was no one else?
Still hung up on her?
No, I mean, I decided not to date anyone
until she was happy.
What? What do you mean?
Well, it'd make her feel betrayed
if I pushed her away,
- and then I dated someone before she did.
- That's sad!
- She should be happy first.
- Seriously?
Yeah, that was why.
But I heard she's happy now.
- Oh, word got around.
- Kind of recently.
- Through mutual friends, right?
- Yeah. Right.
Then you came on the show?
You should have told us that sooner.
It's so cool.
- It's not that big.
- I got chills.
- Really? Chills?
- I've got even more amami now.
Are you sure that's not the sauna?
- It's both you and the sauna.
- Yeah.
But, seriously, that's the real story.
- Wow. So cool. That's so deep.
- Yeah, so…
It'd be messed up if I moved on first.
I've never met another guy like you.
- I mean, well…
- My heart skipped.
- One beat? That's great.
- Oh, boy.
Skipped one beat. Nice, nice.
Anyone would have done that.
Look at you.
You're feeling pretty good, aren't you?
You're gazing up to the sky.
It's nothing special at all. Seriously.
You gotta walk the talk, you know?
He said he wouldn't fall in love
until his ex-girlfriend was happy.
Not a lot of people
would do something like that.
That was a classy breakup.
- He had her best interests in mind.
- For sure.
He has such a good heart.
The question is,
what does Kii think about it?
- Right.
- Yeah.
I always wonder about
what women prioritize.
It's about more than just looks, right?
Depends on the person, I guess.
When I was younger,
I cared about looks a lot.
But as I got older, I started to care more
about what's inside.
You know, whether he's kind.
I think more women find kindness
attractive as they age.
He's got such a great personality.
He's so kind.
A straight-up good guy, for sure.
Definitely.
- There you are.
- Hey.
Welcome back.
- Hey, you.
- Welcome back.
- I think that belongs to Baby. For sure.
- Oh, it's Baby's?
- I'll give it to her. Thanks.
- Okay, and that…
Yeah?
How was it? You have fun?
Yeah, it was nice, you know?
- We talked about love.
- Hmm.
He's so incredibly nice.
- He told me about his ex.
- Yeah, I get it. Hmm.
He said,
"I decided to wait until my ex
found happiness before I dated anyone."
That's why he came on the show.
- That's deep.
- It was deep.
- I was like, "For real?"
- Whoa.
I was feeling a bit jealous,
but I can't after that.
He's great, right?
- Let's talk tomorrow?
- Yeah, I'll bring my A-game. Battle's on.
- See ya. Good night. See ya.
- See ya. Good night.
- Ta-da!
- Oh!
- You're looking refreshed.
- Just like that.
So, how was it?
When I asked him
why he hadn't dated for so long,
he said, "I broke up with someone I loved
because I knew she'd be better off."
"I didn't date anyone because I thought
I shouldn't find new love until she did."
- What the heck?
- That's deep.
- That is so deep.
- Yeah.
- Your heart flutter?
- But, you know…
- I was like, "No way." Yeah, it hit me.
- You felt it?
- Who wouldn't?
- My whole body felt it.
I wanted us to share more
about each other.
I wanted to hear more about him.
So far, I'd say it's easiest
to be myself with Tsuu.
He's great. Tsuu is the best.
I couldn't see Tackle's reaction
when Tsuu asked me to join him.
I'll tell you, it was crazy.
- I thought a fight was gonna break out.
- Yeah, for real.
Tackle was there
at the bottom of the stairs.
- We were all hanging out, he disappeared.
- Really?
He was like, "Kii's not here."
"I'm gonna go tell her
how painful it feels."
He said, "I'll wait for her."
So, that's why he was there.
He never came back to the living room.
Really?
Yeah. I mean, you know Tackle.
It was so sad.
I kept telling him, "Don't hold back."
"Tell her how you feel."
When I told him, "If you want to go,
you should go, right now."
He was like, "Yeah, you're right."
- And then he left for the sauna.
- It was sweet.
Like he might barge in.
You know, I'm gonna tell him tomorrow.
What? Tell who?
- Tackle.
- Tell him what?
- What will you tell him?
- Yeah, what?
How I really feel.
Which is what?