♪The whole world is lit up♪
♪Because you exist♪
♪You're always♪
♪Somewhere close, flying with me♪
♪Go to where the wind blows♪
♪Hold tight♪
♪To the ray of light that belongs to us♪
=Wild & Fiery=
=Episode 24=
This auction's
success
is largely thanks to Ms. Mu.
As for me, I've always been a layman
when it comes to auctions.
From now on,
(Moser International)
I'll leave the company
entirely in your hands, Ms. Mu.
(Moser International)
Mr. Shen, when did you start
moonlighting as a masseur?
So, how is my technique,
Ms. Mu?
It's just so-so.
Ms. Mu,
do you remember what you promised me?
I'm not sure
which matter
you're referring to, Mr. Shen.
Find some time
to get married.
What if I back out?
Back out?
Then I will
tie you up and take you away.
Zhiyu! Boss is coming to pick you up soon.
How big a red envelope
should I ask him for?
Ask for a lot.
Take a hit on his wallet.
Zhiyu, I knew you loved me the most!
What are you doing here?
Move.
I haven't settled the score with you
for tricking me last time.
Why are you here?
Yu.
You look truly beautiful today.
You are not welcome here.
Please leave.
Yu,
don't you want to know
the real cause of your adoptive father
Mu Chenzhou's death?
Zhiyu,
don't listen to his nonsense.
Today is the big day for you and Boss.
He's just here to sabotage it.
(The cause of my dad's death?)
I'll go with you.
We meet again,
Miss Mu.
You two are actually
in league with each other.
Well, we both have a grudge
against Shen Jibai.
Boss Shen,
it's time we settled our account.
Shen Jibai!
Don't move.
You'd better do exactly as I say.
Xu Mingzhu, I'm warning you,
don't do anything reckless.
Xu Mingzhu,
what do you mean by this?
Didn't we agree to only use her
to threaten Shen Jibai
and not to touch her?
Take one more step,
and I won't be polite.
Don't you dare touch her!
Stay back.
Do you think Mu Zhiyu
will treat you any better
if you do this?
I'll give you
however much money you want.
Let her go.
He Group can barely
save itself right now.
How much money could you possibly have?
I should have known
you were this kind of person.
You are burning bridges.
I should never have trusted you.
Xu Mingzhu,
a person like you
who does nothing but evil,
will not come to a good end.
Well, haven't you heard
that the good die young, while the wicked
live for a thousand years?
Shen Jibai won't let you
get away with this.
You're still thinking
about Shen Jibai coming to save you?
I was the one who killed his parents.
You killed Ye Li too?
That's right.
It's not too late to find out now.
At least you can die knowing the truth.
This face of yours
is so beautiful
that it's absolutely annoying.
- I'll slash your face first.
- Zhiyu!
No!
Don't come any closer.
Xu Mingzhu,
let Zhiyu go.
I'll give you whatever you want.
If you want to save her,
stab yourself.
Don't listen to her.
I'll give you as much money as you want,
just let him go.
Shut up!
Boss Shen.
I want to see
if you actually have any guts.
No.
No, Shen Jibai.
No!
I didn't expect Mu Chenzhou to
raise such a sentimental fool like you.
It's quite a surprise.
I know you're in good shape,
but
if you don't stop the bleeding in time,
I'm afraid you won't make it.
How about this?
Let's make this quick.
Tell me the code to the safe,
and I'll let you both go immediately.
I really don't know the code.
But if it's money you want,
I'll give you any amount.
Don't lie to me!
You're the sole heir to Mu Group.
How could you not know?
I'm telling you,
I want both the money and the code.
Xu Mingzhu,
there's no need for us
to lie to you at this point.
If you keep dragging this out,
all you're going to get
are Shen Jibai's and my lives.
Don't threaten me.
Ms. Xu.
- Protect the Boss.
- Shen Jibai!
♪Ten years of the past
have turned to smoke♪
♪I close my innocent eyes♪
Go.
♪No more parting by life or death♪
- Take them.
- Let go of me!
Shen Jibai,
don't fall asleep.
Don't...
Don't fall asleep, Shen Jibai.
I'm okay.
I thought you...
♪From now on, no one can break it♪
Don't cry.
I'm fine.
Why were you so foolish?
You stabbed yourself
just because they told you to.
If you had just now...
I promised you
that I would protect you
for the rest of my life.
♪The green flower breaks in two♪
It's just a minor injury.
♪Our hearts will be together at last♪
It's fine.
♪Waking up between our dreams♪
♪Drawing a circle of falling blossoms
to record your book of poetry♪
♪If destined souls must part,
the broken mirror shall mend again♪
♪In this life, one life given
in exchange for a lifelong bond♪
♪And a promise of safety for a lifetime♪
The code to the safe...
♪The fragmented, peaceful♪
♪Tiniest dream♪
♪Slips through the window by chance♪
For the rest of my life,
♪Shines into my life♪
I will use my life
to keep you safe.
♪That light is you♪
♪Because you appeared♪
♪My world becomes hazy♪
♪Advancing while retreating♪
♪Guessing how you feel♪
♪You'll never understand♪
♪These random emotions♪
♪Are controlled by you♪
♪I want to ask♪
♪Will you care about
my feelings once more?♪
♪Will you let me walk
into your heart in the deep of night?♪
♪Not daring to think too much♪
(Shen Jibai,)
(this time,)
(I believe you unconditionally.)
(From now on,)
(there will be no evasion or doubt)
(between us.)
(We will hold each other's hands.)
(Just like this,
we will keep walking forward together.)
(The 8th China Auctioneer)
The winner of this year's Golden Hammer Award
(Golden Hammer Awards)
is Miss Mu Zhiyu.
Let's give her a round of applause.
(Police found the remains
of Mu Chenzhou in an abandoned factory.)
(Forensics confirmed Mu Chenzhou died of
multi-organ failure)
(caused by long-term sedative injections
by Zhao Ye under Xu Mingzhu's orders.)
(Xu Mingzhu created the illusion that
Ye Li "died of depression" to cover up her murder.)
(Xu Mingzhu was sentenced to death
with a 2-year reprieve.)
(He Min was sentenced to five years in prison.)
(Zhao Ye was sentenced to nine years.
Scarface Jiang Hu was sentenced to twelve years.)
(The End)
(Thank you for your company)
(May you find your own love and care in life)
(and be tightly surrounded
by tenderness and warmth.)
♪Will you let me walk
into your heart in the deep of night?♪
♪Not daring to think too much♪
♪To see if you like me♪
♪Will you occasionally
wait for me by your phone?♪
♪Will the music you share be about me?♪
♪Not daring to say too much♪
♪Perhaps you already
understand my heart♪
♪Will there be a day
when your eyes are full of me?♪
♪Will you think of calling me first
when you pick up your phone?♪
♪My rainbow starry sky♪
♪Is painted entirely with your smile♪
♪If you could stop dodging me♪
♪If I am becoming
a better version of myself for you♪
♪No need to say too much♪
♪I think I already understand your heart♪