♪The whole world is lit up♪
♪Because you exist♪
♪You're always♪
♪Somewhere close, flying with me♪
♪Go to where the wind blows♪
♪Hold tight♪
♪To the ray of light that belongs to us♪
=Wild & Fiery=
=Episode 6=
Yu,
I booked your favorite restaurant today.
How do you like it?
Captain Shen,
there's no need for you
to keep standing there.
As Miss Mu's personal bodyguard,
protecting her at all times
is my responsibility.
Looking at it that way,
Captain Shen,
you are indeed very dedicated.
I see you everywhere.
You just couldn't stay away.
I also see you quite often, Mr. He.
Speaking of which,
you are not on the security team,
yet you are more
dedicated than a bodyguard.
How about
you sit down and join us?
No problem.
Miss Mu,
I suggest
you eat more carrots.
Captain Shen,
there's something you don't know.
Yu hasn't liked carrots
since she was a child.
I've always been the one
to eat her carrots for her.
So the reason her night blindness
hasn't been cured yet
is that you've eaten all her carrots.
Night blindness?
Yu,
is your night blindness
still not better?
What night blindness?
What's wrong with you today?
Why are you so distracted?
Earlier,
I gave my word
to Xu Mingzhu and the board.
I said I would definitely
hold an exclusive auction with Hong.
(So she's worried about this.)
But
there's very little official
information disclosed for Hong.
He rarely attends any events.
And I even ruined his painting before.
No matter how I look at it,
this is on "Heck Mode."
From the sound of it,
Hong
seems like a hot potato.
Do you really have to work with him?
What would a layman like you know?
Hong's paintings
are undoubtedly the best
among Chinese-style art today.
For someone like him,
it's normal to have
a bit of a personality.
Now,
I need to consider
how to establish contact with him.
Yu,
I can help find
the address of Hong's studio
and send it to you.
You can pay him a visit.
With your talent,
you might have a chance.
(What a "genius.")
(Hong Art Studio)
Are you sure this is the right address?
I'm sorry, Yu.
Something very important
came up at the office today.
Otherwise,
I would have definitely come with you.
It's fine.
I'll keep looking.
He Min,
thanks for the address.
I've already found Hong's studio.
♪The breeze gently stirs my heart
that longs for you♪
(Such a familiar scent.)
(It's been a long time.)
(He really is
a Chinese-style art master.)
(The studio
has such a strong artistic vibe.)
(I really hope I can meet Mr. Hong.)
♪Flowers bloom many times♪
Miss,
♪The rain falls silently♪
can I help you?
Hello.
I'm Mu Zhiyu, the Business Director
of Mu Group.
Do you have an appointment?
As far as I know,
Mr. Hong doesn't accept appointments.
That's why
I came directly.
That's true,
but we also don't accept
visitors without an appointment.
This is a private area.
Unauthorized people
aren't allowed to enter.
Bo...
Miss,
are you talking to me?
It's such a hot day.
Miss Mu, right?
Please come in.
Please have a seat, Miss Mu.
My name is Yan Muqing.
I'm Mr. Hong's personal assistant.
Since Mr. Hong is on vacation overseas,
all studio matters
are temporarily being handled by me.
I'm not sure what brings
you here today, Miss Mu.
I'm very sorry for the intrusion.
The reason I'm here today...
First, because Mu Group
accidentally damaged
Mr. Hong's painting,
I've come specifically to apologize.
I hope
Mr. Hong can forgive us.
This is our group's
new Head of Security.
Today,
he's accompanying me to visit Mr. Hong.
(Head of Security?)
(Boss, you really
know how to play along.)
These gifts
were prepared by Mu Group.
Please accept them.
Thank you, Miss Mu.
Second,
I'd like to make up for the
previous mistake on behalf of Mu Group
by collaborating with Mr. Hong
to hold
an exclusive auction.
An exclusive auction?
I can't make the decision on this.
But
I'll inform
Mr. Hong of the Mu Group's proposal
and wait for his reply.
Thanks, Miss Yan.
When I was coming up,
I noticed the decor here
is quite interesting.
Could I have a look around?
No problem.
Please feel free.
Miss Mu.
What are you doing?
I'm staying with you.
Shen Jibai, what's wrong with you?
What could happen if I just look around?
That's hard to say.
After all, a certain lady
tends to have a lot of accidents.
What if I lost my job because
I took my eyes off you for a second?
After you.
Thank you for today, Miss Yan.
If there's any news from Mr. Hong,
please let me know.
Will do.
Pardon me,
I'd like to ask
this gentleman for some help.
Oh, it's like this.
Our studio's surveillance system
seems to have developed a small issue.
Since you're
the Head of Security for Mu Group,
I assume you're quite knowledgeable.
So I'd like to ask for your help.
Well...
It's just a small favor.
Helping Miss Yan shouldn't be a problem.
Then, I'll wait for you here.
This way, please.
Boss,
I was about to burst.
What's going on with you?
You're the president
of the Security Group,
and yet you're on vacation
acting as a bodyguard for Miss Mu?
You haven't fallen for her, have you?
Don't talk nonsense.
I obviously have
more important things to do.
Does she know that you're Hong?
Boss,
can you give me a heads-up next time?
I almost blew it just now.
Alright,
I'll explain everything to you later.
Right now,
look into
this for me.
Boss,
you're hiding behind so many layers
when you're with her.
Don't you find it exhausting?
♪Light comes beaming in♪
♪Landing on my skin♪
♪Warms the space you left behind♪
♪Shadows move around♪
♪Awake, racing thoughts♪
♪Try to keep the memories safe♪
♪Don't slip away♪
♪I'm all yours, all yours♪