=Assassin Lovers=
=Episode 5=
If you
finish this wine,
the money is all yours.
Is that okay?
Wanxiu.
Feng Xiao hasn't come back yet.
Maybe you shouldn't wait.
Go to sleep.
How can I sleep if he doesn't come back?
Wanxiu.
Since you met Feng Xiao,
you've changed completely.
You used to be so carefree.
But now,
you're always worried about him.
That's because you haven't met someone
worth your love.
Once you meet him,
you will understand me.
I'll see if it happens.
Oh, right, Wanxiu.
How did you meet Feng Xiao?
I remember I was on a mission
when I met him for the first time.
You are the notorious burglars,
Three Worms of the Shi Family?
Nonsense!
We are the Three Dragons
of the Shi Family.
Young lady.
Are you looking for me?
Do you want to have fun with me?
You are so tough.
Stop!
Let go of that girl.
Who do you think you are?
Where are you from?
Buddies.
Beat him up.
Stop.
That's it?
Wanxiu.
You're too gullible.
Isn't he just a reckless young fool?
Stop it.
You're so ignorant.
True courage is not
about being unbeatable,
but about trying to protect those
you want to protect
even if you know you'll get hurt.
From that moment on,
I made up my mind
to protect Feng Xiao.
After all, I rarely saw people
like him now.
Drink to your heart's content.
Maybe someday
you want to drink,
but you can't.
(Butler of the Qian Family)
Who is it
at this hour of night?
Open the door.
Hurry up.
(Lu Hang, accountant of the Qian family)
- What's going on? - Don't ask.
Take the kid, pack your stuff,
and go with me.
Where are we going?
You go first.
We'll hold him off.
Come on.
Go.
Mom.
I can't run.
Are you okay?
You have to run.
If he catches up, we will die.
Who have you offended?
I'll explain it to you later.
Get up. Let's run quickly.
Don't kill my dad.
Sir.
The things Qian Dahai has done
really have nothing to do with me.
Don't be afraid.
I...
I'm just an ordinary accountant
and know nothing but bookkeeping.
I beg you.
I have a family to take care of.
Please spare my family.
Are you sure
you haven't done anything bad?
Yes.
If I ever did something
against my conscience,
I may get struck by lightening
and get killed.
You're awake, Mr. Feng.
Mr. Feng.
How did you sleep last night?
It's alright.
The bed is too hard.
Really?
I don't think so.
You drank too much last night.
The hangover soup is ready for you.
I bet that after you have it,
you'll feel better right away.
Thank you, Mr. Feng.
Mr. Feng.
Come again.
Huangying's belly upset me.
You're back.
Tell me.
Did you not sleep all night?
I couldn't sleep without you.
Come on.
Sit.
I took care of something for my father.
No need to worry about me.
But I'm worried.
You didn't come back,
so I was worried about you.
(I can't let her be worried.)
(It seems I have to)
(tell her the truth later.)
Alright.
I'm back.
Don't worry.
Did things go smoothly last night?
What's wrong?
Well,
if you did something wrong
out of good intentions,
what would you do?
If it happened to me,
I would try to make up for it
as long as the intentions were good.
What's wrong?
Did I say something wrong?
No.
You're absolutely right.
I know what to do now.
Thank you.
Honey.
You've been out all night.
You have a sweaty smell.
Take it off, and I'll wash it.
You've been up all night.
Let's go to sleep.
The laundress will wash the clothes.
I'll do it.
How can I let them
wash my husband's clothes?
Anyway,
I'm not sleepy right now.
I'll do it.