(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children and adolescents were
filmed under production guidelines.)
Say that again, Oh Seong.
How dare you tell her to leave?
She's my guest.
I invited her to stay here.
Yun Hee!
This is driving me crazy.
You invited her as your guest?
She needs to leave this home,
so is it my fault for saying it?
Have you lost your mind?
What is this nonsense?
Don't just stand there
and tell her yourself.
Am I the one at fault?
Have I lost my mind?
That's enough.
Why are you
suddenly making this scene?
You're really bad, Little Grandpa.
Have you always treated her like this
whenever I wasn't around?
And what about you?
You should stop him
instead of just standing there.
Come on!
If you want anyone to leave,
you can go.
Stop picking on the wrong person!
Uncle Oh Seong!
Mom, you should've calmed him down.
Why would I do that
after what he did?
- I'll go after him.
- Leave him alone.
He has nowhere else to go.
He'll get some air
and come back to sleep.
I should probably leave.
Don't say that.
You don't have to mind him.
He had been acting strange
with a frown on his face...
since this afternoon.
Just think that he's venting on you
after something else happened.
He's usually not like this,
but he's acting weird today.
Ms. Kang, stay with us.
Don't go anywhere else.
What?
I'm having a drink.
I'm not a kid, Yun Hee.
Don't worry about me.
Don't worry, and go to sleep.
Darn it.
Hey, Bo Ram. You were still up?
Yes, may I sleep here?
Of course. Come on in.
It's nice to sleep here next to you.
Your uncle says it's nothing,
but I know something is going on.
He's not someone
who'd say such harsh words.
I kept asking him,
but he just wouldn't tell me.
Did something go wrong
with his business?
I doubt that.
I became furious
and got mad at him back then,
but I became worried.
I'll ask him
when I see him tomorrow.
I'm sure it's not a big deal.
All right.
Let me know if anything is going on.
Of course.
You should go to sleep. It's late.
(Husband)
Are you not going to pick it up?
Hello?
Why did you pick up my phone?
You didn't, so it kept vibrating.
I was annoyed.
Even so, how can you pick it up?
Have you got any manners?
I don't think
there's enough oxygen...
to share with you in this room.
I feel stifled.
Isn't that so?
Why don't you go home
and sleep comfortably...
instead of staying
in this tiny room?
Why are you here
instead of your huge place?
It must feel uncomfortable.
It's my dad's place.
Why would it feel uncomfortable?
I'm at ease.
If you feel uncomfortable,
you can sleep outside.
Outside? Where?
There are only two rooms
in this house,
and I'm staying here.
You can enjoy your space in peace
in the living room.
Darn it. Jeez.
- Did you sleep out here?
- Yes.
I told you to quit drinking.
Are you
still not in your right mind?
Cut it out. I don't want
to hear you nagging this early.
You'll end up making
another drunken mistake.
Don't go anywhere near Ji Ho.
This is my warning.
It was you, right?
You did it.
Yes, it must've been you.
I kept thinking about it,
and it had to be you.
You told Se Ri that I was the one...
who kidnapped Eun Ho.
Why are you bringing that up now?
It's nothing to brag about!
Exactly! You knew
it was nothing to brag about.
Why did you tell her
and make a mess out of my family?
My wife left home
because of you. Okay?
- Yu Gyeong is gone?
- Yes, you punk.
Why would you go around telling people
about your brother's mistake?
How do you call yourself
my younger brother?
How can we
consider each other brothers?
I never told her.
Then, how did she find out?
My wife never speaks ill of me,
not even to my father-in-law.
Se Ri said Yu Gyeong told her,
but that had to be a lie.
It was you.
You're why my wife got berated by Mom
for having a big mouth.
You need to bring her back!
I said it wasn't me!
Why would I share anything
that'd humiliate my family?
Did I tell you?
It wasn't him, Gi Man.
Then, what?
Are you saying it was my wife?
Well, I somehow ended up
overhearing you and her...
in a quarrel.
I didn't eavesdrop on purpose.
You two were in the kitchen.
In the end, it was you.
Darn it. I told you
to be careful with what you say.
Why are you telling me this now?
- What?
- What's with you?
Did you get us into a fight
on purpose?
Back then,
you said it was Yu Gyeong!
I did?
I don't remember saying that.
I must've been confused
at that moment.
Darn it.
The person you have reached
is unavailable. Please leave...
Come on.
Mom, I'm leaving.
Wait, I need to talk to you.
Why? I have to go.
I set up a blind date for you
this Saturday.
What? I don't want to go.
Why not?
He's from a great family.
Mom, I'm not interested.
Is it because you...
and that punk hit it off?
Was that why you said
you'd marry before me?
Mom, don't call him a punk.
He's a doctor. A doctor in medicine.
Who is this guy?
You'll get sick
of a good-looking guy...
in less than a year.
It's not about a guy's looks.
It's all about his money.
That's the real deal.
What about you?
Is the guy you like ugly?
No, he's unbelievably handsome.
Hey, you and I are different.
I only have
one-half of a life ahead of me,
and I'm made of money,
so I'm allowed to want good looks.
That's not fair.
Then, I'll go against you.
Stop dating that guy.
You little...
Mother, Ji Ho is still asleep.
Don't say anything weird
when his tutor gets here.
Please let her focus on him.
All right?
Fine.
So... Tu what?
Tutor. Do you get it?
I'm leaving.
Bye, Mom.
All right. Bye.
Tu... Tu?
Tutu?
These darned English words are
giving me a headache.
So, he found out
after seeing me with my aunt.
I think I'm only causing disruption
in your family.
He feels...
more betrayed by me than you.
I've been thinking about it,
and I think I should leave.
Give me some time...
to deal with Mom and Bo Ram.
And my uncle isn't that heartless.
He's only mad at me,
so let's keep an eye on him
for a while.
One second. It's Hwang Na Ra.
She must be calling
because I told her you quit.
Let me have that.
I'll talk to her and end it.
I'll get rid of the number, too.
Hello?
- Hey, Na Ra.
- Geum Ja.
Why didn't you pick up your phone?
I was worried about you.
Why did you quit?
It's something personal.
Then, do you want
to meet up for lunch?
Where are you?
I'm at home.
You're home? Where do you live?
Hello?
What was that? Was it disconnected?
Why are you here, Jae In?
She was here for a consultation.
You should go.
Okay.
(Geum Ja, Hwang Na Ra)
No way.
You were Geum Ja?
Na Ra, it's...
It's her, right?
She was Geum Ja, right?
Yes, it was me.
And you knew about this?
You two deceived me?
I had no idea and was happy
that I found myself a good friend.
I really liked Geum Ja!
You're so awful!
I liked you, too.
It was a good friendship.
And I had to go out of my way
to find the ticket to the concert...
because you liked the artist.
You're lying!
- Na Ra.
- And you're the same.
You should've been honest with me.
Get away from each other!
I hate both of you!
What do we do?
She'll tell Hwang Gi Chan all about it.
It doesn't matter.
What could he do to me
even if he found out now?
Don't worry about it.
(Bo Ram's Fried Chicken)
If you're up, don't just sit around.
Come and eat breakfast.
That feels much better.
I know I'm opening late today,
but you can't sleep here
at my business.
You're a rich man.
Why didn't you go to a hotel?
I had to chug down alcohol
to soothe my turbulent heart,
so I wasn't in my right mind.
What is it? Hey.
What made you do these things
you've never done before?
What's wrong?
Is your business not going well?
- Yun Hee, it's Ms. Kang.
- No.
You need to leave.
Yun Hee.
Why do you want to kick out...
that poor woman who lost her son
and is now alone?
She's a stranger. Yes.
She's a total stranger.
How is she a stranger?
We're family if we eat together
and sleep under the same roof.
I'm sure you also felt that
our home became much warmer...
ever since she moved in.
Above all,
Bo Ram adores her like a mother,
and she doesn't seem
depressed anymore.
She shows such a big smile.
Aren't you grateful for her?
I also feel like
the emptiness of losing Do Hee is...
slowly healing,
thanks to her presence.
She needs a place to live,
and we need her.
Jeez.
She's not overly sensitive
or particular.
She's gentle, kind, and friendly.
When I first met her,
I even wanted her as my daughter-in-law.
I understand what you want.
Are you sure you understand?
Understanding and accepting are
two different things.
Will you be like this, Oh Seong?
You should get ready to open.
I have to be somewhere, too.
Will you come home tonight?
I'll see.
Bye, then. You should get to work.
What's he going to do now?
I need two cups of cold water.
I've been too busy,
but I meant to ask you...
about your aunt.
You said you didn't have any family.
She isn't my immediate family.
We stayed in touch from time to time
after my mom passed,
but we had lost touch
after I went to America with you.
You and Ji Ho are...
my only family.
Of course, Mother, Gi Man,
and Na Ra are technically family,
but that's what I think.
Anyway, even Kang Seung Woo is...
making my life harder
after Jae In came.
He gets even more furious
when I make her get my coffee.
They're half-siblings,
but blood is still thicker than water.
The same would apply
to Director Kang Mi Ran, too.
She may be on our side now,
but she can always change her mind
as Jae In's aunt.
We're working together
only for the time being...
because we're after the same thing.
Na Ra! We aren't at home.
If you're going to be my secretary,
do your job right.
Whatever. I'm annoyed to death.
You still can't do this
even if you're annoyed.
Quit right away
if you don't want to work.
You don't even know anything!
It's her first time working.
Na Ra, is something bothering you?
Did someone say something?
You can talk to me
if something's bothering you.
Well, it's...
Gi Chan, do you remember Geum Ja?
How would I know her?
Geum Ja? The employee
who worked at the clinic?
Yes, the thing is,
she was Jae In.
What are you talking about?
I'm saying Geum Ja wasn't Geum Ja.
She was really Jae In. Kang Jae In.
She disguised herself
and deceived me.
I knew something was odd
the first time I met her.
Do you remember what I said to you?
My gut feelings were right.
I was happy that I made a friend.
Darn it.
Na Ra, did you say anything
to Geum Ja...
No, I mean, to Jae In?
Like what?
About you two?
I don't know anything
to share with her.
Get out.
Go out and do your job.
Dang it. Jeez.
Jae In had been
keeping her eyes on us...
in this company.
Dr. Kim must've known
she was Jae In.
They already knew each other,
so he had to know.
Don't you think so?
I don't like how Dr. Kim works here,
and I think it's fishy
that Jae In is...
siding with him.
Will you let them do this?
Give me some time.
Please, Father.
Please let me
talk to Yu Gyeong just once.
She's at your place, right?
She won't see me at her office
or pick up her phone.
This is killing me.
She's never been like this,
so she must have a reason
for acting like this.
What is it?
Why did you two get into a fight?
Well, it's...
It wasn't a big deal.
That's the thing
with a married couple.
Everyone gets into a fight
over how you take off your socks.
That soft-hearted girl
wouldn't have left home...
if it was that trivial.
You can't do away with this
just by evading my question.
This is between you two,
so you two must
resolve the situation first.
She won't even pick up my calls.
You can't even tell me
why you two got into a fight,
so what can I do?
I had to leave shortly
during the busy hour. Bye.
Father.
Come on!
- Thank you.
- Please enjoy.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Here's your food.
- Enjoy.
- We'd like to pay.
Yes, coming!
Just take it easy.
- Let me ring you up. Thanks.
- Please.
- Here's your change.
- Thank you.
Ma'am, you gave me
more than you owed me.
I'm so out of it.
Thank you. Come again.
Another bottle of cola, please.
Coming!
More beer, please.
- Sure.
- A bottle of soju, too.
Soju, beer, and cola. Okay.
Goodness.
That was like war.
Good work.
I've made so many mistakes
in calculation. I never do that.
I also got the tables confused
many times today.
Something must be bothering you.
It also seems like
something is on your mind.
It's my grown younger brother.
He's not acting like himself,
and I don't know what he's thinking.
My daughter is
staying with me right now.
She must've gotten into a fight
with her husband.
I asked, but she wouldn't tell me.
My daughter was never like this, either,
so I became concerned.
They're still a young couple.
They're bound to fight
many times at that age.
It may be better for her to blow up
than to keep it all inside.
You should trust her
and give her time.
I'm sure your brother
also has a good reason.
Men are like that.
Actions come before their words.
You should give him some time.
Yes.
We're the good ones,
so let's stay patient and wait.
I've been thinking
for the last few days...
about hiring another part-timer.
The business is going well,
so we're facing lots of rushes.
I'm away at times
to look after Bo Ram,
so I thought we should have
another helping hand around.
Then, may I recommend someone?
Darn it.
I'm sick of eating takeout food.
It's full of MSG.
There's no point
in trying to lose weight.
It's all coming back.
Mom, look at my face.
I'm breaking out badly
after eating just instant food.
I told you to hire a housekeeper.
I can't just throw money away.
My precious son, the chairman,
worked so hard to make that.
And we all have a very classy taste.
No one can make something
good enough for us.
Why not, Mother?
You just have to look.
I know
you just don't want to do chores.
You don't care
about wasting your husband's money.
Mom, so when is
Yu Gyeong coming back?
I miss her food.
She was a shrewd girl
who did a great job...
at cooking and housekeeping.
Yes, that must be
why she's a family physician.
Hey, my wife didn't get certified
only to make food for you.
So, your mighty wife,
who's a doctor,
still ignores your call
and refuses to see you?
She read my message today.
She didn't even read it
until yesterday,
but today, she left me on read.
And you're proud of that? Jeez.
Anyway, that means
she also wants to return soon.
All right, then.
I'll escort my daughter-in-law,
who's a doctor, back home.
I reviewed everything on the file.
(Managing Director Kang Mi Ran)
Good work. You may leave.
Did you want to see me?
I need you to find something.
The employee who died in an accident
was named Kim Do Hee, right?
Can you find the contact information
and address of her bereaved family?
Yes, ma'am.
I'll find out and report back.
Also, do you know where
Director Choi Ja Young is staying?
No, ma'am. Should I find out?
No, it's all right. You may leave.
Yes, ma'am.
Right. CEO Patrick Jung
of DH Holdings is here.
- The CEO came here himself?
- Yes, ma'am.
He's in a meeting with the chairman.
As you already know,
I can't make a reckless investment.
So, the process is
quite complicated.
Yes, of course, it should be.
I'm not sure if YL Group would be
able to meet our conditions.
We'll do our best to do so.
Just the fact that we received
an investment from DH Holdings...
would give a renewed image...
to YL Group within the industry.
Now, this is
a draft of the contract.
I believe you need...
flexible thinking and spirited drive
for a corporation to make a leap.
You wish to participate
in our overall operation,
including strategy planning
and even the design?
It's an outdated idea
to want to see an outcome...
just by investing money.
I've been hiring experts
in many different fields.
I plan to implement them one by one
as soon as our deal is sealed.
It'll provide a way...
for us to handle risks
as soon they break out.
I apologize,
but I can't make this decision alone.
Why don't we set up another meeting
after I discuss this with my board?
Let's do that.
However, time is money to me.
I'm not the type
who waits patiently,
so I may end up finding
another gold mine.
I'll return with an answer
as soon as possible.
I heard the CEO
of DH Holdings was here,
so I came to meet you. Hello.
Then, goodbye.
He doesn't like
to make himself known,
so he avoids meeting outsiders
as much as possible.
Please do understand.
You can meet him
once the investment is sealed.
I tried to call you many times,
but I couldn't.
I'm so sorry.
I don't plan to return home...
until you leave that place.
Do you understand?
Is that all?
Please give me...
just a little more time.
I considered leaving immediately,
but I was concerned
about Bo Ram and Ms. Jung.
I don't want to hurt them even more.
I'll explain myself before I leave.
Stop saying something
you don't even mean.
You practically hurt them already.
What if they find out
who you really are much later?
Who's going to deal with that?
I'm sorry.
I don't need your apology.
Just thinking about the fact...
that you came and stayed at my place
as if nothing had happened...
gives me the creeps,
so leave the place. Please.
You already know...
how precious Yu Gyeong is to me.
Is that so?
Of course.
I treat her like
she's my biggest treasure.
And what else?
Like flowers in a vase...
No, that's not it.
Like a bird in a birdcage?
No, that's not it, either. It was...
Well. Yes.
Like she's an overly sheltered girl.
I support her
like she's an overly sheltered girl.
You won't let them
get divorced like this, right?
Yu Gyeong always does
everything you say,
so please talk to her
and send her back home.
They're both adults.
I don't think
the parents should meddle with this.
They should figure this out
by themselves.
Thank you for the tea.
Mr. Do!
Darn it. That uptight man.
Yu Gyeong is also uptight
because she took after him.
Hey, I don't think
Yu Gyeong will come home,
so come home early and make dinner.
Mother, this is bad.
Jae In is going around at work...
speaking ill of Gi Chan.
She called him shameless
for having an affair...
and that he doesn't deserve
to be the chairman.
She even demanded
that he stepped down now.
What did you say?
I'll destroy that brat.
Mother, did you think
I married him to do chores?
I'm not Do Yu Gyeong.
Gosh, this is so heavy.
I brought everything you asked for.
Hey, I guess thieves
break into just about any place.
My place was robbed, too.
It must've been shocking.
I mean, there's nothing to steal.
I don't have anything
like jewelry or money.
The thief
only made a mess out of my place.
How am I going to clean that up?
Are you sure you don't have
anything else that belongs to me?
Yes, I'm telling you.
If you want to keep getting pocket money,
don't ever return here.
Okay, girl.
Why did you want to see me?
I wanted to apologize.
I wasn't trying to deceive you.
I found someone to work with me,
and it turned out to be Ms. Kang.
I just thought it'd be awkward...
for you two to run into each other
while she worked here.
Let me treat you to a cup of coffee
as an apology. What do you say?
Fine. I want caramel macchiato.
All right. By any chance,
did you tell the chairman...
about Ms. Kang?
No, nothing at all.
Let's get the coffee.
I couldn't believe it,
but you were really here.
- Have you been well?
- No, I haven't been well.
How dare you gossip
about my precious chairman?
An affair?
You two were divorced
and had become strangers.
How dare you yap about him?
You should know your place
now that your family got ruined.
Why are you acting up like this?
How dare you go inside?
How dare you come here?
- What are you doing?
- You can't get past me.
- Mom!
- Let go of me!
Mom, you need to stop!
Please!
Hey, let go of her!
How dare you pull out
my precious girl's hair?
Let go of her now!
I won't let go of her
if you don't let go of me first.
Mom, help me! That hurts!
- Let go of me!
- Hey!
Come on, Jae In!
Darn it.
I'm going to sue you.
Go ahead.
I'll counter that.
What? Darn it.
Have you lost your mind?
I have nothing more to lose.
But it's different for you,
Ms. Noh Sook Ja.
You just went on a power trip
because your son was the chairman.
This will have an impact on him
if the word gets around.
That's exactly what I wanted.
You little...
Who are you?
Do you know who I am?
How dare you meddle with me?
Get away from me.
Mom, you need to stop.
You must be the chairman's mother.
Your behavior seemed irrational,
so I had to step in.
What are you all doing?
Goodness, Mr. Chairman.
This brat and this punk are...
trying to kill your old mother.
- Mother.
- My son. Mr. Chairman.
- This is an injustice.
- Please calm down.
Take her with you.
- Mother, let's go home.
- Mom.
What's with you? Let's go.
Let's go.
Goodness! It's her fault!
Is this fun for you?
That's what I want to ask.
Does it look like I'm having fun?
All right.
Go ahead
and continue to act up, Jae In.
No, should I call you Geum Ja?
You and Kim Do Yun
made a fool out of me.
I should return the favor, right?
Look forward to it.
(Queen's House)
I'm sorry.
Forget it. Get up.
If you tell me to go die,
I'll kill myself.
Yu Gyeong, I can't live without you.
It wasn't Jae In's fault.
It's not even her fault,
so why are you harsh on her?
I'm disappointed in you.
Did you send this?
Se Ri, is Chairman Hwang Gi Chan...
your second husband?
Or are you two-timing him,
just like your current husband does?