(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children and adolescents were
filmed under production guidelines.)
I'm not sure if you remember her.
You two had met at our wedding.
I told you that
I recently met one of my friends.
It was her, Se Ri.
Hello.
Yes, hello.
It's great to meet you.
Anyway, you must've been
quite surprised to see me.
Have a seat, honey.
I didn't tell him
this was a couples' night.
He doesn't like to meet
lots of new people.
Honey, you must be hungry.
Excuse me.
You're home early.
I am.
I haven't been feeling well lately.
Should I call Dr. Park?
No, it's all right.
It's just business.
I was just too concerned.
Is something bad going on?
Well, it's Director Do.
Never mind. It's just business.
You don't have to ask anymore.
Where's Jae In?
She went out with Gi Chan
for an engagement.
Is Seung Woo home?
What did he say
about his life at work?
Did he say anything to you?
Do you want Seung Woo
to succeed as the chair of YL Group?
Why not?
I'm against it.
I thought you'd be for it.
It's different
when it comes to work.
He doesn't know anything.
He has no idea how this world works,
and all he cares about is partying.
How can you leave behind
your huge business to him?
That's why I'm telling him
to start learning.
If he could learn this quickly
in a short while,
I wouldn't have been against it.
There's too much responsibility
in that position.
Seung Woo doesn't have
the mental strength to handle it.
He's only like that
because you overprotect him.
It's not too late for you
to bring him up as a strong man,
so just ignore everything
and keep an eye on him.
How can I do that?
If the company takes a toll,
Seung Woo would break apart
before the business.
I don't want my son
to live such a difficult life.
Also...
What else?
Well, actually,
he spent a night out a few days ago,
and I got worried.
It turned out that
he had slept in his car.
It seemed like
he drove under the influence.
What did you say?
This punk
still isn't in his right mind.
Call him
and tell him to come home now.
Pretend like you never heard it.
I already had a talk with him.
How can I pretend like
I never heard it?
What if he had caused an accident?
Forget that
he would've hurt himself.
He could've hurt an innocent life!
That's not all!
If his case got covered
on the front page of the newspaper,
it could've brought
my business down with him!
Don't get mad at him.
I can never tell you anything
because you always react like this.
Wouldn't it be better if Jae In...
took over your position?
And not Gi Chan?
I haven't accepted him
as a part of our family.
Do you still disapprove of him?
He's our family now.
He'll be a stranger
if she divorces him.
How can you trust him enough
to hand over your huge business?
It's because I'm still uncertain.
You watched him closely...
as he dedicated his life to Jae In.
You wouldn't know.
What?
Anyway, whoever succeeds YL Group
must be one of the Kangs.
It would've been great
if your husband could join us.
It's such a shame.
I really wanted to meet him.
He forgot that
he had a previous engagement.
He said it was something important,
so he took a rain check on us.
We should meet together next time.
I want you to meet him, too.
All right.
Honey.
- Yes?
- He must be bored.
Oh, my. Se Ri.
I have that necklace, too.
My gosh. I just realized that.
Where did you get it?
Well, he gave it to me as a present.
Really? Mine was
also a present from my husband.
Goodness, really?
It was because
he did something wrong.
He tried to avoid talking about it
by giving me a gift.
Did you also do something wrong?
There's nothing like that.
Jeez.
- My gosh.
- Goodness.
I'm sorry.
What do we do?
It's awfully stained.
Please excuse me for a moment.
What do you think you're doing?
She wanted to do a couples' night,
so I came.
Is this your idea of a joke?
It's not funny.
It's not funny for me, either.
My husband is...
sitting with another woman
like he's her husband.
Do you think
that's easy to deal with?
You must've forgotten,
but we got married in America.
I'm also your wife.
Don't forget that.
It was such an unsatisfactory meal
without any dishes I liked.
Bring me some fruit
to refresh my appetite.
Yes.
Didn't you hear what I just said?
Bring me the fruit first
before you wash the dishes.
Mom, your favorite soap opera,
"My In-Laws' House" is on air.
You should go and watch it.
I'll bring it over soon.
Yes, I almost missed it.
I didn't get to watch it yesterday.
The female lead's mother-in-law is
the most evil woman in this world.
She keeps going after
her daughter-in-law.
My gosh. Something like that
only happens in dramas.
There can't be a mother-in-law
who's as evil as her.
- It's about to begin.
- Yes, right.
You can give those to me.
I'll do it.
Forget it. Your mother will
get mad at me if she sees you.
- If I catch you...
- Look at her.
Jeez. She's dying to make
her daughter-in-law miserable.
My gosh. A woman like her...
deserves to get her hair
pulled out. Jeez.
Hey, bring me water.
Was it you?
- Did you talk to my wife?
- Look at them.
I must've gone crazy
for a little bit.
I was out of my mind.
I'm so sorry.
Take this to her.
If I do something like that again,
I'll call myself your son.
She can't even have kids.
How can you be her son?
Mom.
Why? What I said wasn't wrong.
A man needs to have children
to get more attached to his family...
and start acting like a decent guy.
But your husband got
addicted to alcohol...
and began to talk
about foolish dreams.
Do you know whose fault that is?
It's yours.
Mother, what kind
of absurd reasoning is that?
It's not convincing.
How shameless.
You're about to put an end
to this family's heritage.
Absurd reasoning?
My second daughter-in-law
had no trouble having a son.
Why can't you have one?
Mom, that's enough.
Why are you taking out
your anger on her?
Yes, Mom.
You need to stop minding them.
These days, many married couples
choose not to have kids.
It's tough to raise them.
- It's better for them to live...
- Stop talking nonsense.
What kind of crazy talk is this?
Of course, they need to have kids
once they get married.
Are you trying to ruin our family?
Mom, let's talk outside.
We can talk outside.
What's with you? Let go of me.
I need to listen to what she says.
- Let go of me.
- Goodness, let's talk outside.
Yu Gyeong, you saw that
I was on your side, right?
I got this for you.
It's really delicious.
You can have it.
I'm tired, so I need some rest.
Darn it. What is this?
My mom ruined everything.
I got this to ask her...
to set me up with Kim Do Yun.
He was surreal.
Surreally handsome.
Come and have some fruit.
Come out, everyone.
- What about Bo Ram?
- She's asleep.
Gosh.
My goodness.
Do your legs hurt?
My business was booming today,
so I must've overworked myself.
I'm feeling some throbbing pain.
Gosh, I told you
not to overwork yourself.
You need to consider your age.
Mom, you should try this.
What's that?
It was recommended
by a professor I know,
and I thought of you.
Someone who must
move around busily at work...
must look after themselves
before anything happens.
Okay.
I'll keep it in my room
and take it every single day.
Thanks.
What are you waiting for? Dig in.
- Okay.
- Yes.
When will you two move out?
You should get married.
Instead of us,
why don't you set an example first?
Bo Ram would love to have a grandpa.
You're not getting any younger,
so you should find someone nice.
Don't you think so?
Yes, I totally agree with him.
Mom, there's someone I know.
Should I set you up with him?
Good grief. Forget it.
Stop worrying about me,
and worry about yourselves.
I could always get married
if I set my mind to it.
Why are you two laughing?
There are many guys
who try to hit on me.
It's just that
I don't care for them.
My standards are as high as my nose.
Do Yun, I don't think
her nose is that high.
It's pretty low.
Is it? Let me take a look.
It is. Her nose job will cost a lot.
What? What's with you two?
Who do you think you took after...
and were born
with those pretty faces?
- Who?
- Your DNA is...
all right in here.
Why? It's true.
- Here?
- Yes, it's true.
You're right. Thanks.
Mom! Good evening.
Be quiet. Your father is asleep.
Don't wake him.
- Have you had dinner?
- Yes.
Hey, Aunt Mi Ran.
Hey, welcome home. You're late.
You haven't been drinking again,
have you?
Sniff me.
You can't smell anything, right?
Don't make me so concerned.
Do not take your car
if you plan to drink.
If you do that again...
I won't make you worry, Mom.
So, that's the end of the nagging.
- Go upstairs and wash up.
- Okay.
That was such a lovely moment.
I'm jealous.
This is why people say
we should have children.
But people also say
your life is easier without them.
I have only two children,
but I'm always facing trouble.
Don't you hate them for it?
I would, if I were you.
You can't bring up children
with that kind of attitude.
They're all my children.
Thank you, Ja Young.
For what?
You've gone through lots of trouble
after you married the Kang family.
My mom and dad
would've thanked you...
if they were still with us.
- Hey.
- We're back.
- Mom, what about Eun Ho?
- He's asleep.
You should tuck him in again.
I need to see you, Gi Chan.
Gi Chan.
Do you remember
the promise you made me?
It's great to meet you.
My name is Hwang Gi Chan.
(Cashier's Check)
You don't have to mind me
and put down a small amount.
I'm pretty much paying you
in return for my daughter,
so you may write down
however much you want.
In return,
you will leave her
without another word.
How much...
do you think Jae In is worth?
That's a foolish question,
but let me answer that.
I can't put a price on my child.
I feel the same way.
I can't put a price on Jae In.
You can get an amount
you'll never make in this life.
But I could enjoy even more...
if I took Jae In.
I'd be lying
if I said I didn't care about money.
But I never wanted
to win the lottery, either.
I may seem like
just another prosecutor,
but I can make a living by myself.
Don't be deluded into thinking
we're all equal just because...
we live under the same sky
and breathe the same air.
People are
all born into their places.
And Jae In is...
too good for the place you're in.
You need to give up
while I'm still nice to you.
May I ask you a question?
Do you believe it is right...
for a parent to commodify
their child...
without regarding...
that child's emotions and opinions?
My parents always prioritized
their children's happiness.
I want to show Jae In...
that kind of world.
I allowed you to marry her
because of what you said then.
I didn't care about anything...
except for my daughter,
Jae In's happiness.
Do you still feel the same way?
Yes.
My priority is Jae In's happiness.
I never forgive anyone...
who makes my daughter miserable.
And you aren't an exception.
That'll never happen.
I'll take your word for it.
But remember,
if that was a lie,
I'd never forgive you.
Yes.
Please do not forgive me.
What did my mom say?
The same thing she always says.
She told me to be good to you.
She overreacted again.
You must've felt offended.
She says that for our sake,
so I need to understand.
After all,
she's crazy for her daughter.
(Catherine)
Aren't you going to pick it up?
No, it's one of our subcontractors.
She's in America,
so she probably forgot what the time was.
Can you grab my underwear?
I need to shower.
Sure.
You were appointed as of today,
so put together a planning team...
and show me
what you can really do this time.
I've been
getting ready for it already.
You can look forward to it.
I'll also look forward to it.
I heard Director Do resigned.
Did something happen?
I must've been too trusting.
Don't ask anymore.
It'd feel reassuring without me.
I also considered putting
both of you in charge.
What do you mean?
I want to retire
within the next year.
It felt sudden when you mentioned
you'd retire within 2 to 3 years.
What do you mean next year?
You're still in your prime.
I agree with Aunt Mi Ran.
My wife is the most important to me,
but I was always too preoccupied.
I've done some wrong things, too.
It's my turn
to make up for everything.
Please do your best so that I can...
put you two in charge and retire.
We'll run into each other
from time to time. It's nice to meet you.
Sure.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Sure.
She looks a lot like Catherine.
Is she not her?
Who are you?
She's a new designer
for the Planning and Design Team.
He's the director
of the Strategy Planning Department.
Hello.
My name is Kang Se Ri, a designer.
It's nice to meet you.
Sure. Keep up the good work.
Please excuse me, too.
- Thanks for the coffee.
- Sure.
Hello?
What do you think you're doing?
I'll meet you at the hotel at noon.
I'm sorry.
I have a previous engagement.
Let's talk again later.
Goodbye.
Redo your report
by the end of the day.
What?
It took me so long
to do this. Again?
The price, unit, and items
all do not match.
It's a complete mess.
Check everything thoroughly
and have it redone.
Wouldn't it be faster
if you did it yourself?
Mr. Kang, you said you wanted to be
the chairman someday.
Then, you need to figure out
how the business actually works.
This department is...
YL Group's brain and heart.
Remember that with your head
and heart as you work.
Yes.
Brain and heart.
Yu Gyeong.
I must've been out of my mind.
I'm sorry
for misunderstanding Gi Man.
Yu Gyeong, please take the flowers.
I forgot everything,
so you should do the same.
It's nothing good to remember,
so let's just forget everything.
Thank you, my sister-in-law.
Thank you so much.
These flowers are beautiful.
Thank you, Jae In.
Do you want to eat dinner together?
Sure.
One second.
Hey, Mom.
Aunt Mi Ran is
having a guest over tonight?
I'm sorry.
I wanted to eat dinner with you.
You can't help it
if you're going to have a guest.
Let's do it next time. Bye, then.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
By any chance,
may I borrow your lipstick?
You look wonderful.
Do I?
I didn't want my children
to see me looking so sickly.
They'll also take pictures,
so I want to be remembered
with a lively face...
when they pull those out to see me.
That way, they won't feel as sad.
Thank you.
Sure.
Have a wonderful time
with your family,
and please stay strong.
You're a mother.
Thank you.
Wait, aren't you the man
who saved my son?
Hello.
How's your son doing?
Great, thanks to you.
Right. How's your arm?
How's the arm injury?
Wait, are you here because of that?
No, I'm fine.
Then, what brings you
to the hospital?
Well, it's...
It was great to see you.
Good luck with your son. Excuse me.
What?
Goodbye!
Goodness, welcome.
Welcome.
What should we eat?
And two colas, too.
Why does he keep staring at me?
This is why life can be tiring
when you're too pretty.
Do you have something to say?
You can stop staring and say it.
Well, it's...
No, I'm not interested.
So, please stop staring at me.
No, it's not that.
I'm a bit of a fashion geek, so...
That line is so ancient.
Are you saying my clothes
don't match my pretty looks?
Forget it. I've heard it all.
Your top is inside out.
I can see the labels
behind your neck and on your side.
Oh, no. My goodness.
Hey, Se Ri.
You were our guest?
I wanted to surprise you.
I invited her to dinner in secret.
Do you know her?
She's the designer I hired
for the Planning and Design Team...
and Jae In's friend.
Nice to meet you, Ms. Choi.
I see. Hello.
Is it because you're her friend?
You seem familiar.
She came to my wedding.
She's a friend from university.
Really?
So, she went to your university.
It's nice to meet you.
Ma'am, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Please forgive Jae In
just this once.
Please, I ask of you.
"Jae In?"
How dare she...
copy my daughter's name, too?
(Kang Jae In)
Come on in.
I haven't cleaned up my room.
It looks clean.
I thought it'd be fancier.
I like things
that are natural and simple.
This is where I get my rest.
I was worried
your mother would recognize me,
but she didn't.
It's been many years.
She probably doesn't remember.
Really? I still remember it
like it was yesterday.
- Hey, honey.
- Hey.
You're home.
You remember Se Ri, right?
- She was...
- We met at the office.
We're meeting quite often today.
Aunt Mi Ran
invited her over for dinner.
- Mommy.
- Yes?
Dinner is ready.
We have to go downstairs.
Okay.
Where's Seung Woo?
He had another engagement.
If it's nothing important,
tell him to be home
when we're having a guest.
That's what we consider
basic etiquette.
All right.
Don't be so hard on your son
in front of our guest.
So, you're Jae In's friend?
Please enjoy your meal.
Yes, and please speak
casually with me.
Yes, Dad. You can relax.
Yes, but today,
she was invited by Director Kang,
so maybe next time.
Gyu Cheol, we aren't at work.
We're home.
Don't call me a director.
Do you know...
what younger people call
people like you these days?
A boomer.
Eun Ho, have some beef
boiled down in soy sauce.
Honey, have some of this.
- What?
- It's your favorite.
It's good for our body,
so you can have it first.
Why are you giving this to me?
It was for you.
- It was yours...
- That's hot!
- My gosh.
- Goodness.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
I must've been a bit nervous.
Please excuse me.
It's all right.
I'll go alone.
But...
Mommy, this is really delicious.
Eun Ho, are you eating that again?
You're such a big piggy.
Look at your tummy.
Look.
You should've put down your phone
before you sat at the table.
It's from work.
I'll take it outside.
He bears the brunt of leadership,
so, of course, he must
always carry his cell phone.
I get it.
You should eat.
What are you doing? Are you crazy?
Come out.
I wonder what you and Jae In did...
in this bed.
What did you two do?
That's enough. You need to get up.
I think this room suits me.
I want to live in this house.
- What?
- I want to live with you...
in this house.
People say what you want desperately
will eventually come true.
I'm desperate,
almost to the point of madness.
We'll talk later.
Let's go downstairs first.
Kiss me.
Se Ri.
If you love me, prove it...
right now.
Wait.
It could be better,
but you did a good job.
Yes!
Gosh, I was so scared
you'd make me do it again.
Do you want to eat dinner?
It's on me.
Next time.
You may leave first.
Okay. See you tomorrow,
Ms. Kim.
Is she having trouble finding it?
I'll go.
It's okay. I'm done.
I'll do it.
Is she close to Jae In?
It seemed so.
Then, why haven't I heard of her?
She returned to Korea recently
after living in America for a while.
Jae In asked to find her a job,
so I took her portfolio,
looked over it, and loved it.
That was why I hired her.
I didn't do it for her connection,
so don't worry.
No matter what it is, do a good job.
It's your first project
after returning to Korea,
so there will be high expectations
and many concerns at work.
Make sure you prove yourself.
I will.
Seung Woo must go out often
with his friends these days.
No.
Stop it.
Gyu Cheol.
He's still a young man
in his twenties.
Don't be so hard on him.
You're only making
Ja Young's life miserable.
Did you hear that?
She's not here.
- Mommy, I'll find Daddy.
- What?
Eun Ho, take your time.
You'll end up falling.
Daddy!
Eun Ho, is he in the room...
(Queen's House)
If you'll be like this,
let's just end it.
I don't need anything else.
Let's just end it.
Are you happy?
What?
These are the files
regarding the dual contract.
I never thought...
I'd do something this indecent.
You must be Catherine.
How do you know my English name?