(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children and adolescents were
filmed under production guidelines.)
He cried,
made a scene, and insisted...
he had to go to the kindergarten,
so what could I do?
You won't find anyone home
even if you come.
Jae In also went out
to an engagement...
after she dropped Eun Ho off.
You can all come tomorrow
for dinner.
The chairman wanted to eat together.
Ms. Noh, I must go to my gallery.
I can't stay on the phone for too long.
Goodbye.
She just won't hang up.
These rich people are the stingiest.
All they have is money,
yet they don't want to waste
even a penny.
"Ms. Noh, I must go to my gallery."
"I can't stay on the phone
for too long."
Mom, that was so weird.
Stop that. It doesn't suit you.
Right. Did you ask Jae In's mom...
about my potential husband?
I need to talk to her in person.
I can't ask her that over the phone.
Mom, my first condition is that
he must be handsome. Okay?
Don't forget that.
Good grief.
His looks won't go a long way.
Your first condition is money,
the second is money,
and the third is also money.
Money is the best.
Right? Money is the best.
- Mother.
- Be quiet.
I might really end up dead.
Please help me just this once.
Good grief. Shut that mouth.
My gosh.
Why aren't you going to the office?
How can your company do well...
if you're at home acting pathetic?
My business isn't the problem.
My life is at stake!
It's really the last time.
Please? Mother.
I'd rather invest my money
in a lost cause.
You're the eldest in the family,
yet you can't even compare to Gi Chan.
You might as well call him
your older brother.
Mom, he said he might really die.
Death doesn't come that easily.
How dare you threaten me?
Pay me back first before you die.
All right.
So, how's Seung Woo doing?
He's doing well.
Do you mean that?
Or are you saying that
in case I'll worry?
A good punishment will do
that reckless kid some good,
but I can't go around
spanking a grown man.
(Chairman Kang Gyu Cheol)
Try to get him interested in work.
You already know
why I made him work for you.
Do your best to guide him.
Yes, sir.
This reminds me
of our high school days.
Right?
I still remember when you two were
Kang Jae In A and Kang Jae In B.
Time flies.
You two still look the same.
No, you look even prettier.
You, too, Jae In.
I keep forgetting
that you changed your name.
I have to use it often
to make it stick,
but you live in America,
so I didn't get a chance.
You'll get to do it more often
from now on.
What?
Are you back for good?
Yes, I came back first.
I have to find a place to live,
and I have something to do, too.
My husband will also return
as soon as he sorts everything out.
Hey, that's wonderful.
Let's meet more often from now on.
Next time,
why don't we all meet as couples?
It'd be great
for our husbands to be friends.
I also want to know
what he looks like.
Did you want to know?
- Yes.
- Of course.
You went to America on a trip,
so we were really shocked
when we heard you were suddenly married.
Tell me about it.
If you had told us,
we would've come and celebrated.
That was awful.
I'm sorry.
Back then,
I wasn't in my right mind.
My man and I were
crazy about each other.
We were passionately in love.
Well, we still are.
Don't just show him off in words.
Do you have a picture?
Let us see how great he is.
Do you want to see him?
I want to,
but I don't have any pictures.
He doesn't like taking photos.
He says it feels awkward.
Gosh.
My husband is the same.
He dreads taking pictures.
He reluctantly takes one...
only when Eun Ho asks for a selfie.
Is Gi Man like that, too?
Well...
I don't know. There recently weren't
many occasions to take photos.
Jae In, do you still work?
You must hold a high position.
I took a year of maternity leave.
It'll end next month,
so I've been wondering
if I should quit.
Why? Because of Eun Ho?
He needs his mother at this age,
and I'm even more convinced
after recent events.
Did something happen to him?
What?
Well, yes. He was kidnapped.
Thankfully, he returned safely
without harm.
Really?
I'm glad he was fine.
I'm grateful for everything.
I never want to go through that
or even think about it again.
You're right.
You can always go back to work.
It's your family's company,
so you don't have to worry.
But I should start worrying.
What about you?
I've been looking for a job,
but it's not so easy.
I've been away from Korea for long,
so I don't have any connections.
I haven't heard back from anyone
even after sending out my portfolio.
But someone with your career
should be able to find something.
I'll ask around, too.
Really?
Then, I'd be so grateful.
It's my husband.
I see.
Hello?
Yes, I'm eating lunch
with my friends.
I wanted to eat with you,
but I was a bit too late.
Are you disappointed?
You should eat lunch, too.
You must be hungry.
They seem so loving.
She says
they're still hot about each other.
(Recent files)
Okay. I'll call you later.
(YL Trading Company: Delivery Contract)
(YL New Town Multi-Use Building
Written Agreement)
Mr. Kang, I need to see you.
Come in.
Mr. Kang. Why did you open
all these files in this folder?
I had to look
for Balsan New Town's contract.
Hey, we talked on the phone.
Don't you remember?
I'm asking because you opened
other files, not just that one.
I didn't know what was what,
so I looked through them.
Did he not notice the fake contract?
What did you see,
and what were they about?
Tell me what you saw.
Contracts and project proposals.
I don't really remember.
They were all the same.
These are highly classified,
so not even a single page can be leaked.
Can you take responsibility
for your words?
What?
Gi Chan, are you suspicious of me?
Do you think
I'm an industrial spy or something?
Hey, don't be so official.
You're scaring me.
And why would I do that?
It's practically my company,
so why would I?
Says who?
Who said this company was yours?
Shareholders are the owners
of an incorporated company.
I'm a shareholder, too.
What I meant wasn't exactly that,
but it was still true.
Seung Woo.
You should watch what you say
as a member of the owner's family.
Gosh.
People are always watching
and listening at work.
I was blatantly honest
because it was you.
Are you sure
you don't know anything about the files?
I swear that I do not know anything.
He asked to check the contract
for the overseas factory development.
Are there any revisions?
I don't see any marks.
It's been reviewed already,
but he wanted to check again
for technical terms.
Did he say anything else?
No.
What was that contract I saw
on Director Hwang's laptop?
The company name is the same,
but the content is different.
- Hey.
- Goodbye.
- Come into the bus.
- Over here.
Hop in carefully.
- You've never been to a kids' cafe?
- No.
Is it fun?
No, I don't like it.
Why not?
We're in that awkward age.
When I want to play with older kids,
they shoo me away
and say I'm too young,
and younger babies are too immature.
Right. I see.
Eun Ho.
Mommy!
Give me your backpack. Okay.
- Mommy.
- Yes?
I'm not a baby anymore.
Why do you drop me off
and pick me up?
Because I feel less scared
when you're with me.
Can I do this for a few more days?
Okay.
Okay, then.
This is a promise sticker.
I'll keep you safe, Mommy.
Thank you so much.
This is nice.
You have gastritis.
Stay away from strong-tasting food
and alcohol for a while.
If you don't feel better,
come again next week.
Okay.
Goodbye.
Come in.
Snack delivery.
I got your favorites,
macarons and coffee.
Give me just five minutes.
Yes, Doctor.
The macarons are delicious.
The coffee, too.
Where did you get them?
I stood in line at a famous bakery
and got these...
for Dr. Do Yu Gyeong.
I never thought about marrying,
but that almost changes...
whenever I see you two.
I'm jealous, Dr. Do.
Are you not dating?
These days, people need money...
to date and marry.
Do you invest in the stock market?
What about funds?
They're both huge these days.
I don't know much about it.
Right, you were a fund manager.
Can you tell me where to invest?
Ms. Kim,
if you want to invest in a fund,
you should find someone else.
We work together,
so it'll be okay if things go well,
but it'll be awkward
when it's bearish. Don't do it.
Yes, Doctor.
Don't you trust me?
She wanted to invest.
Why did you rain on my parade?
If it goes well, sure.
But what if it doesn't?
Who do you think she'll blame?
It's me, not you,
and I can't deal with that.
Why are you here?
If you want money, don't ask.
I said I didn't have any.
You've changed so much.
Back in the day,
you always agreed with everything I said.
It's been five minutes. Go.
If you're interested in funds, here.
It's not this number, so...
- Honey.
- Yes?
- I wanted to see you off.
- What?
Let's go.
- What? Okay.
- Goodbye.
They've been married for years,
but they're still so much in love.
They were
college sweethearts, right?
Apparently so.
I would die to meet
a romanticist like him.
My type is Dr. Kim Do Yun
in the surgery department.
Go.
Honey. Yu Gyeong.
You know men are
only made of pride, right?
But I'll throw away everything.
If you tell me to die,
I'll even pretend to die.
If you ask me to kneel,
I'll do that.
What are you doing?
Get up. What's with you?
I don't care
if it's only 100,000 dollars.
Can you find a way to borrow some?
You need to stop. I have no money.
Dr. Do.
Gosh, my stomach hurts.
I have to run to the restroom.
I'll go. I have to go. Bye.
She came for a checkup,
but she got lost.
Ma'am, she's the doctor
of family medicine.
- I see.
- You can go with her.
Let's go.
What?
He was a doctor here?
My goodness.
Yes, hello?
Yes, I've been doing my best
to find the money.
Please wait a little more...
Yes. All right. Goodbye.
Gosh.
(Director of Planning Hwang Gi Chan)
Come in.
I'm here, Gi Chan.
Why did you suddenly come
without calling me?
I was nearby, so I stopped by.
How's Eun Ho? Is he all right?
Say what you want to say.
What? Say what?
You came to say something,
didn't you?
Gosh, you still have
that prosecutor in you.
Gi Chan, if you have
any spare money...
Gi Man,
I already made myself clear...
and said I'd never make
any monetary transactions with you.
What are brothers for?
I just need it for a month.
Gi Chan, you know that
I set you up with Jae In, right?
If I had known
her family was so affluent,
I would've hit on her and...
I was just joking.
I don't think
I have to hear you out anymore.
You should go.
I'm busy.
Hello?
You caught the kidnappers?
Yes, all right.
What? They caught the kidnappers?
Yes.
I need to go and check.
Hey, you don't have to go.
You can't go and show your face.
There must be reporters
stationed there.
People will find out the grandson
of a huge corporation was kidnapped.
I'll go.
I saw their faces, too.
I'll figure out the situation
and call you, so get back to work.
You said you were busy.
What are brothers for?
Take advantage of me
in times like these.
(Changpyeong Police Station)
They were the kidnappers, right?
No. It wasn't them.
See? He says no.
Are you sure?
Well, they look similar,
but they aren't the ones.
I saw them right in front of me,
so I'd know when I saw them.
- I'm sure...
- I'm sure it's them.
Yes, I'm sure... What?
Hello, I appreciate your hard work.
I was asked to come as a witness.
They are...
the kidnappers. I'm sure.
What? No. You got them wrong.
It wasn't them.
I was the one who reported them,
so I'd know.
You're the man
who kicked me on that day,
thinking I was the kidnapper.
You probably
didn't get a good look at them.
Trust me. I know it.
Hey, he said it wasn't us.
Hey, be quiet.
I mean, mister. Tell him.
Are we the kidnappers?
He's never had ramyeon
or tteokbokki in his life.
He's never bought any clothes...
because someone brings them for him.
He's never been
to a kids' cafe, either.
I feel so bad for Eun Ho.
Goodness, that poor kid.
His situation must be awful
if he can't afford ramyeon or tteokbokki.
Bo Ram, you should
invite him home sometime.
I'll make something delicious.
There are people who stay away from
those on purpose for health reasons.
But she said
he gets clothes from charity, too.
I'm home.
Hey, you're late.
I had to go somewhere.
Have some fruit.
Okay. Let me get changed first.
- Okay.
- Roar.
Try this, too.
- Do Yun, I'm coming in.
- Okay.
- Here are yours.
- Hey.
Thanks.
Whose handkerchief is that?
It's obviously not yours.
Your girlfriend? Yes?
My gosh. No. Last time...
If I may answer your question,
no, I'm not dating.
Come on.
You need to start going on dates.
Don't you think
your standards are too high?
I'm tall,
so of course, my standards are high.
- What?
- See? Look.
- I'm standing much higher than you.
- Come on. You're so silly.
This is why
you can't find a girlfriend.
Stop worrying about me,
and find your own dates.
Bo Ram is all I need.
Mommy!
Uncle!
- What?
- Yes, what?
- There's my love.
- Go, now.
They caught the kidnappers?
Yes.
- Where are you going?
- The police station.
Even at the kindergarten,
only the director knew...
that Eun Ho was YL's grandson.
But that kidnapper knew that,
as well as my phone number and yours.
It means he lurked around us
and kept his eyes on us.
Or there may be an accomplice.
I need to know...
how he found out about Eun Ho
and how they kidnapped him.
The police will
investigate everything.
They'll call us
when they have the result, so let's wait.
If we keep going to the police station,
the media may find out.
I'll ask them to demand
the harshest punishment.
Of course, we will.
He messed with a child,
not an adult,
and of all children, my son.
I'll make sure he never spends
another day outside. Don't worry.
Where's Gi Man?
He's still asleep
after drinking too much last night.
All he ever does is drink
because he has no joy in life.
You should eat.
I have to go to work right away.
You don't have to come
to Gi Chan's place tonight.
Na Ra and I are going by ourselves,
and that's final.
People say a woman's life
depends on who she marries,
but it doesn't apply
just to women in this day and age.
A man must marry the right woman
to turn his life around.
Gi Man's life has been nothing but trouble
after he married you.
You two were married for ten years,
but you haven't had a kid, either.
Every stock item and fund
he invests in becomes nothing.
Look at Gi Chan.
He now has a healthy son,
and his business is thriving.
It's all because
Jae In is a lucky woman.
I feel so confident
whenever I think of Gi Chan,
but all of that goes away
whenever I see you two.
I lose all my spirit.
Have fun at Jae In's place tonight.
I'm leaving.
Look at that girl.
She won't even pretend
to listen to her mother-in-law.
Who cares if you're a doctor?
Good grief. You reek of alcohol.
Get up. You have to go to work.
Darn it.
Jeez.
Gosh.
What's this?
"Hwang Gi Man, it's not just you."
(Mr. Hong)
"I'll also pull out..."
"hearts, eyes, livers, and kidneys
from your family,"
"skin them,"
"and drain every drop of blood..."
My gosh. Give it back.
Why are you reading that?
Give it to me. Let me see it.
Gosh, my heart is racing so fast.
Who's the lunatic
that sent you that message?
Who was it?
Give me that.
Give it to me.
- No.
- Give it to me.
Hello?
I am Hwang Gi Man's mother.
- Give it to me. Stop that.
- Stop it.
Did you send that text message?
What now? You'll take our hearts?
You'll skin me? Hey.
Do you know who my second son is?
He used to be a prosecutor...
who took in criminals!
What? What now?
You're crazy.
Who are you calling a kidnapper?
What?
What is he saying?
You were Eun Ho's kidnapper?
Tell me the truth!
I'm sorry.
My goodness. My gosh. You're...
Hey, don't be so mean
to your friend.
I want to go to the restroom.
You need to go to the restroom?
Hey! Stop it!
Eun Ho.
Uncle Gi Man.
I was going to go...
to an amusement park with you,
but something suddenly came up,
so I have to go somewhere.
That's why my friends will go...
and play with you.
They'll buy you the toys
and snacks you want to eat.
What do you say?
Do you want to go with them?
Okay.
Eun Ho, can you promise
you won't tell anyone...
that we met today...
and went to an amusement park?
Not even to my mommy and daddy?
Why?
It's because...
I'll get in lots of trouble
if they find out...
I took you to an amusement park...
instead of letting you stay
at the kindergarten.
I made you play instead of study.
Do you want me to get in trouble?
Or do you want to go back...
to the kindergarten?
So, it's a promise. Okay?
Promise me.
- We promise with all our hearts
And make a copy. Swoosh.
They reported this to the police.
Call her right now
and tell her that.
Also, have the toy
delivered tonight.
Why did you report this
if you wanted to see him again?
What?
No, I didn't. I mean it.
Who is that? Is that the kidnapper?
Darn it.
- How dare you kidnap a child?
- Wait!
There must be a misunderstanding.
Those two over there.
Get him.
Get that guy.
- Those two are on the same side!
- Darn it.
Hit me now.
Hey, you!
Mom...
So, the two of them were
caught by the police,
and the boss or whatever
began to blackmail you?
Yes.
Does your wife know?
No.
Don't tell her.
If your father-in-law finds out,
Chairman Kang will
also find out right away.
She cannot find out.
Mom, can you let me borrow
some money?
I'm serious. They might kill me.
Don't go outside for a while.
Just stay cooped up inside.
We have to go
to Jae In's place for dinner.
Good grief.
Don't you have any shame?
How can you want to go there?
We got invited,
so it's our duty to be there.
If you knew what your duty was,
why did you kidnap your nephew?
You have zero shame.
My goodness. It's just my luck.
I can't believe I was happy...
after giving you birth.
It's not like
I can stash you back inside.
It would've been much better
if Gi Chan were the eldest.
I wouldn't have had so much stress.
Listen up.
Do not mention
what you did to Eun Ho...
until the day you die.
If you ruin this family,
you'll die in my hands
before the loan sharks get to you.
Remember that.
- Do you like it?
- Yes.
Let's eat dinner.
I made a reservation
at a classy Korean restaurant.
I'm sorry.
We found Eun Ho safely,
so my family and my in-laws are
meeting up to celebrate.
I didn't know this was a bribe.
I was happy, thinking it was a gift,
not something to entice me.
I know you're disappointed,
but I have no choice.
Finding Eun Ho is enough.
Why is that dinner so important?
Do you really want me to stay?
If you say so, I'll stay.
Forget it. Go.
I don't want you
to feel belittled by your in-laws.
But tomorrow,
I'll do everything as you say.
She's Assistant Manager Kim Do Hee,
Mr. Kang's direct superior.
It must be quite tough.
Seung Woo doesn't know much,
so it must be hard
to get him to do some work.
It's all right.
Mr. Kang may not be proficient yet,
but he's doing his best.
If he tries to slack off
or mess around,
don't mind me
and give him a good lesson.
Yes, sir.
I'll reprimand him properly...
to make sure
the business doesn't suffer.
That's an answer I like.
Thank you.
Then, keep up the good work.
- Yes, sir.
- Good.
We're done!
Let's give it to Grandma...
- when she leaves.
- Okay!
This is for you.
It's a present from me.
You're my present, Eun Ho.
I'll enjoy this. Thank you.
Hey, that must be Grandma.
Grandma!
You're the eldest in the family,
yet you can't even compare to Gi Chan.
You might as well call him
your older brother.
Death doesn't come that easily.
How dare you threaten me?
Pay me back first before you die.
My goodness. It's just my luck.
I can't believe I was happy...
after giving you birth.
It would've been much better
if Gi Chan were the eldest.
If you ruin this family,
you'll die in my hands
before the loan sharks get to you.
Remember that.
It must've been very stressful,
but you can relax now.
Goodness. Yes, of course.
I feel so relieved
to see Eun Ho here with us,
and I already feel full
without eating.
Why didn't Gi Man
and Yu Gyeong come?
I thought you'd all come together.
Mom told them not...
They were both too busy.
Yu Gyeong has to see
too many patients,
and my eldest son is
busy as a bee with his business.
Hey, Ja Young. Hey, Jae In.
- Aunt.
- Mi Ran.
You didn't even call.
When did you return?
Don't you see my suitcase?
Just now.
We can catch up a little later.
There's another guest.
Why isn't he coming?
Eun Ho! Your uncle is here!
Hwang Eun Ho!
Your uncle is here!
- Goodness.
- Your uncle is here.
Gi Chan! Hey, Jae In.
Goodness, Mom!
I'm here, your pathetic eldest son!
Goodness.
(Queen's House)
I came here today...
to tell everyone something.
I have...
My dear nephew.
Do you remember Se Ri,
my friend who lives in America?
You met her at our wedding.
Do you remember her?
Is it Gi Chan?
Ja Young, you may find this upsetting,
but YL Group must be carried on
by one of the Kangs.