(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children and adolescents were
filmed under production guidelines.)
We'll conduct an interim check
for the designs,
so let's take a look.
I got
Ms. Kang Se Ri's design last night.
I have mine.
(Saseon-dong Reconstruction
Interior Design)
What is this?
This is crazy.
How can the designs be
exactly the same?
This is plagiarism.
Designer Kang Jae In
copied my design!
I heard you were doing
an interim check for the contest,
so I thought I'd drop by.
What's going on?
These designs look almost identical.
Can anyone explain what's going on?
Designer Kang Jae In
stole my design.
She didn't steal the design.
I know it because I watched
her work from the start.
It's been that design all along.
How can you say it's been copied?
Designer Kang Jae In
should be the one to explain.
Tell us.
I believe it's Ms Kang Se Ri
who copied my design.
That's complete nonsense!
Why would I do that?
Director Kim Do Yun is right.
On what grounds are you accusing
Ms. Kang Se Ri of plagiarism?
Otherwise, no one is going
to believe what you're saying.
I saw Kang Se Ri
working on it myself,
right at home.
I'm the witness.
Did you really see it?
I did. With my own eyes.
There's something I want you to do
to re-establish the trust...
you almost tore apart.
Designer Kang Jae In is working
on the redevelopment design.
Hand that design over to me.
Can you do it?
I'll give it a shot.
I got your email.
Thank you for your help,
Director Do.
Are you working?
This is the design
Kang Jae In is working on.
Make it yours completely.
I told you I could beat Kang Jae In.
Don't you trust me?
It's not about trust.
There's no point wasting energy
on something like this.
Kang Jae In was
the youngest design team leader.
She even won a design competition.
She's proven herself.
Let's be real about it.
What matters is that we've already seen
through her next move.
You'd be a fool to go straight
at her without using this.
I'm not forcing you.
The choice is yours.
Now, let's all calm down.
Ms. Kang Se Ri sent her design...
yesterday, and I checked it.
I got Designer Kang Jae In's
design just now.
Like I just said,
how could Ms. Kang Se Ri send me...
the design
before Designer Kang Jae In did...
when it wasn't even hers?
I just remembered.
Recently, Designer Kang Jae In...
went through my desk
while I was out,
saying she needed
to grab a shared file.
I had my design book
in my desk drawer.
I'm pretty sure
she saw it then.
I came to get the redevelopment request
for Saseon-dong.
It should be on Ms. Kang's desk.
I have to go out for a meeting.
(Export Contract)
(Team Leader Kang Se Ri)
There's a witness.
Assistant Manager Kang Seung Woo
saw it that day.
I'm not sure
if she looked at the design,
but I did see her open the drawer.
Are you still going to
deny it to the end?
All right, all right.
Let's all calm down.
This is just an interim check, okay?
Which one of these
belongs to Designer Kang Jae In?
This one?
Stop with the plagiarism nonsense.
Do it right.
You're entering this contest...
as the Head of Investment
and Development at DH Holdings.
Make sure you're judged
fair and square on your skills.
I will let this one slide.
We still have to compete.
I will make sure of that.
No need for any more
interim checks I guess.
That's it for today's meeting.
Keep up the good work.
I handed over the design materials,
so they'll never suspect you.
It's a throwaway design anyway,
so don't worry about it.
Bye, then.
You gave them the design on purpose?
I did.
Hwang Gi Chan asked Mr. Do
to steal my design.
You gave them the design on purpose?
That's right.
That's a relief,
but won't it be tough...
to finish a new design on time?
I started brainstorming right
after I heard from Director Do.
No matter what Hwang Gi Chan
and Kang Se Ri try,
they can't copy
what's inside my head.
It's going to be fun
on the day of the competition.
I came by to see my son's face,
but he's not in his office.
I thought I'd ask my daughter-in-law
for a credit card to shop,
and she's not in her office either.
What's with all these
back-to-back meetings?
It's like they never end!
There's not a single thing to eat.
Absolutely nothing.
This place and I just don't vibe.
We're like oil and water.
- Goodness!
- My gosh!
My goodness gracious.
Falling for the same person twice...
must be fate, right?
Was it "des..."
Dest… destick?
Death. It's death.
You could die in an instant.
You keep bumping into things
and falling over.
That's an accident
waiting to happen.
Right.
I've got urgent business.
I'll get going now.
Wait.
Clothes really do make the man.
He looks even more amazing.
A man is all about
the face and body.
That's everything.
But why did he show up here?
By the way,
is Gi Chan's meeting over or what?
Should I go to the office?
(DH Holdings)
What?
Look who it is!
You flirted with Kim Do Yun
to sneak your way back in.
How dare you show your face here?
If you have any shame,
get out of the chairman's company!
I didn't sneak in
by seducing anyone.
I was scouted fair and square
as a designer of DH Holdings.
If anyone should leave,
it's you, lady.
What did you just say?
Don't you dare lay a finger on me.
You touching me
makes my skin crawl.
What did you just say?
I'm disgusting? Me?
Hey!
You little witch, get over here!
Oh Seong, why are you sitting there?
Oh.
Watch your mouth.
He's the CEO of DH Holdings
who is investing in YL Group.
The CEO?
If he's the CEO
of an investment firm,
that means they're the ones
putting money into...
Gi Chan's company, YL Group.
Meaning they've got more money
than his company...
That's why he's investing?
What brings you here?
Is there a problem?
He's young. Great.
He's hot. Super great.
He's rich too?
It doesn't get any better than that!
How did I get so lucky?
If you're here to fight,
just do it already. I'm busy.
I'd better get out of here
before that fox starts...
running her mouth to Oh Seong.
The building is so big,
I got lost on the way.
Well, then.
I'll be seeing you.
Right.
Why are you looking at me like that?
She's just the lady
across the street. That's all.
I hope that's all she will ever be,
so don't ask.
You don't want to know.
Good afternoon.
Do I look good to you?
I am a complete mess
thanks to you-know-who.
I am sorry.
Look at him running away.
Where does she keep going,
always leaving her seat empty?
I only took this side gig
to mess with that clueless woman.
But this is boring.
Hello?
What do you want?
Why are you even calling me?
If you're hoping for
settlement money, forget it.
I'm not giving you a single cent.
What nonsense is this?
Settlement money?
What are you talking about?
You're not the only victim here.
I'm a victim too.
I am the one who's been
sacrificed for YL Group.
I was forced to break up
with the man I loved because of Dad,
and I had to marry someone
I didn't even want.
And even now,
I can't even call myself a mother...
to my own child.
I could only stand by and watch,
and I felt cursed.
Don't blame my brother, either.
If you had given birth to a son,
none of this would've happened.
Worried that the family line
would be discontinued,
Dad forced him to divorce you,
so he took in
Seung Woo to protect you.
You shouldn't resent him.
You should thank him instead.
Do you understand?
Wait.
From now on, using my son
as leverage won't work on me.
I'm done...
living like a shadow.
Don't mess with my son.
That's my warning.
Hello? Mi Ran!
Her son?
Mi Ran had a son?
Who's her son?
Why can't I remember anything?
Why do you think
I asked to see you?
Isn't it obvious?
You're just scared
I'll go to the cops...
and report you for assault.
I almost reported you for assault,
but I held back
because you had done...
some good to my family.
Is that all you've got to say?
Talk to Yu Gyeong for me.
Tell her getting a divorce from me
isn't the answer.
You've seen us
since we first started dating.
After all the years
we've spent together,
how can we just become strangers?
Besides, I was
so good to you, wasn't I?
You're my little brother's wife,
and yet I treated you with respect.
You reap what you sow, right?
Help me out here, okay?
"You reap what you sow."
Let me ask you something.
What kind of revenge should I get
against the so-called uncle...
who kidnapped his own nephew?
What kind of an uncle
would kidnap his own...
Jae In.
Just shut it.
Don't you dare call my name.
I was the one who blamed others
for my misfortune.
The one
who made my life miserable...
was me.
You're all ready to go?
I was a bit annoyed
when you ignored my messages.
But you didn't forget
about our date today.
Let's go. I'm starving.
Hello?
Yu Gyeong, have you been drinking?
I will head there now.
What?
Did he just run away
because he's too shy to hold my hand?
How adorable!
Yu Gyeong.
You're here.
Sit.
Right. Okay.
Didn't you drink too much?
Aren't you eating anything?
You'll wreck your stomach.
Can we get some fruit here?
Hurry up, please.
Seung Woo.
You know,
I really wanted to be happy.
I tried so hard...
to find happiness.
I tried, and tried again.
I thought I'd eventually get happy.
Maybe I was asking for too much.
An ordinary daughter,
wife,
mother,
friend.
That's what everyone becomes.
I guess just being ordinary...
was too much to ask for.
Yu Gyeong...
I don't know
what I have done so wrong.
I just wanted to live a happy life.
No matter how hard I try,
it just never works.
What was I supposed to do?
It's too much for me.
I'm exhausted.
Where did I put my phone?
(Genotyping Report)
(Kang Mi Ran and Kang Seung Woo are
99.99% related by blood.)
How could I have forgotten
such an important thing?
What's wrong with me these days?
Wait.
Is this the right way...
to the shop?
Why is Mi Ran's wallet here?
The co-op president?
You got the job?
Stop teasing me.
You're feigning ignorance
on purpose, right?
Ms. Mi Sook...
No, we're going casual now.
You made me the president, Mi Sook.
Mi Sook?
Who's Mi Sook?
Mi Sook.
It's your name.
Uncle Do Yun, Ms. Kang!
Yes?
What's prettier?
Right, tomorrow is
the pajama party, right?
Yes. We're going to dance
and have a fashion show too,
so I need to look the prettiest.
Bo Ram, you look
pretty in everything.
Uncle, no matter how pretty we are,
we always want to look even better.
Say what?
I say this one.
The color is going to
pop more in pictures.
I will pick this then.
You're going to look so pretty.
Do Yun, can I talk to you?
Sure.
Bo Ram, why don't you go try it on?
You'd better practice your walk
for the fashion show.
Okay.
- Do you want to go put it on?
- Yes.
Is there something on your mind?
I heard you were seeing someone.
No, I am not seeing anyone.
Why are you asking that?
You're my son,
so naturally, I got curious.
The other day, Oh Seong said...
you might have broken up
with your girlfriend.
No one in their right mind
would break up with my son.
It's been bothering me.
You really don't have a girlfriend?
Uncle Oh Seong is mistaken.
I don't have one.
You deserve to find
someone really good.
I hear people go to dating agencies
to meet people and to get married.
I don't want to go that far
to meet someone.
I prefer things to happen
organically.
Right. You have to find a good girl.
Hey, I want you to date
someone who has never been married.
What?
Someone who is single
and has never been married. A miss.
Hello.
Hey. What happened?
Hold on.
She's had quite a lot to drink.
I wasn't comfortable
just putting her in a taxi.
Right. Thank you.
Thanks for bringing her.
No worries.
She could really use
some extra support right now.
She's really struggling.
Do you want to stay
for a cup of tea?
Isn't she here?
Ms. Choi?
She's gone to bed early.
I think I'd better get going.
It'd be awkward if she saw me.
I just hope you will think...
that she's going through
a tough time emotionally.
As someone who's been
around her for a long time,
I know that she loved you
just as much as she loved Jae In.
We've all been fooled.
She pretended to love me.
She said she never loved me.
Her words may be harsh,
but to her, you were like her own.
I know it's tough,
but I hope you will try to understand.
Jae In worries about you a ton.
You know that, right?
I'll get going.
Please don't see me off.
I can't be bothered,
so no hair treatment for me today.
How refreshing!
Look how silky my hair is!
Goodness.
Come and eat.
What did you do with your hair?
Look.
I only shampooed,
but look at all this volume!
You should try it too.
Hurry up and come eat.
Coming.
Where's Gi Man?
He was completely drunk last night.
As if she's the only girl
in the world!
Why is he so crazy about her?
Have you gone to see her?
I went to her place,
but she wasn't home.
She didn't answer my call.
What a piece of work.
She is dead set on
getting that divorce.
I should never have
let them get married.
Gosh, it's giving me a migraine.
By the way,
that guy at your company, you know,
the head of the investment firm?
What's he like?
It's a foreign investment firm,
and the CEO is known
for being really difficult.
He's known for not investing
in just any company.
Gi Chan won him over.
Isn't he amazing?
Sounds like an amazing company.
They must have tons of money.
Of course.
Companies are practically
begging for their investment.
It was my husband
who made it through to them.
Mother, isn't he amazing?
He's an amazing guy indeed.
Of all people, Kang Jae In
had to get involved...
and make this a headache.
How do you know about this, Mother?
What?
If he finds out that I've fallen
for the investment firm CEO,
he will definitely flip out.
I went to see the chairman,
and I ran into that wench,
Kang Jae In.
She said she got "scarfed"
or something like that...
by that company,
so I thought I'd ask you.
Mom, "scarf" is something
you wear around your neck.
It's "scout." Got it?
Oh, please.
You know a tiny bit more than I do.
Scout is what I meant.
You don't need to worry about that.
I will take care of it. Don't worry.
All right.
Eat up.
This'll help with your hangover.
I'm really sorry.
I went overboard drinking last night.
Do you remember?
Seung Woo brought you home.
I do. Faintly.
Is something wrong again?
Did Gi Man cause trouble again?
No, it's not that.
No, I was upset about bottling
everything up all this time.
I thought I'd just have one drink,
and it got out of hand.
Yu Gyeong,
do you still resent Jae In?
I'm too small-hearted to let it go.
I don't know when it started,
but I started resenting Jae In.
That's why I wanted to beat her.
You had better grades,
and you got into a better college.
You proved yourself
as a capable doctor.
When they realize Jae In is
the heiress of YL Group,
everyone starts acting differently.
I couldn't stand watching you
lower yourself in front of them.
I thought if I could beat Jae In,
you could finally hold
your head up high.
So I pushed myself like crazy,
working harder than ever
at everything.
Even when I came in first,
I could never catch up to Jae In.
I thought it would be different
if she became family.
But even after
she became part of the family,
everything remained the same.
I don't resent her now.
I guess I was too insecure
and desperate for approval.
When I saw how Jae In
dealt with him...
over Eun Ho's kidnapping,
I realized just how
misguided I'd been.
Yu Gyeong, you are uniquely you.
Don't compare yourself to others.
To me, you are the greatest
and the prettiest girl in the world.
At least to me, you are.
I don't resent Jae In anymore, Dad.
I won't resent myself either.
It must've been tough on you.
Thanks, Dad.
I keep forgetting things.
I have a hard time
remembering where I put things.
It looks like simple memory lapses,
but I feel like we should
do some tests just to be sure.
I will say three words.
When I ask later,
give me the words in the same order.
Airplane, pencil, and pine tree.
What year is it now?
This year?
It's 2024.
No, it's 2025.
What season is it now?
Winter.
No, it's spring.
I'm feeling a bit cold
because I dressed lightly.
What were the three words
I said to you earlier?
They were...
Airplane...
Hello?
What?
Say it again.
Is Hwang Gi Man
Noh Sook Ja's eldest?
He is. But who are you?
Hwang Gi Man is with me.
If you want to save him,
prepare one million dollars in cash.
As if...
Who wouldn't know
this is a phishing scam?
Get it together, you punks.
You should work hard
to earn your money.
How dare you try to scam me?
Do you know who I am?
I am Noh Sook Ja.
How dare they try to scam me?
What?
They still haven't come
to their senses.
- Hello?
- Mother!
It's me, Gi Man!
Mom.
Mother, save your eldest.
These guys are...
going to kill me if you don't pay.
Save me, Mother!
Gi Man, where are you now?
Prepare one million dollars
in three hours.
I will call back.
Hello? Gi Man!
Hello?
(Chairman Hwang Gi Chan)
Yes?
Mother, calm down
and speak slowly.
What do I do?
Oh, my son.
Finally, you're here.
I told you to hurry home.
What took you so long?
Did you get another call from them?
Are you sure it's Gi Man?
It was Gi Man. It was his voice.
Mom, they use AI voice cloning
to clone people's voices and faces.
I gave birth to him,
so I know my baby's voice.
It was Gi Man.
With a terrified voice,
he said, "Mother!"
It was Gi Man.
His phone is turned off.
What do I do?
Goodness, I got something.
Let me see.
Mother, save me!
Gi Chan!
Save me!
Mother!
Gi Chan!
(Queen's House)
Do you want to have dinner with me?
I have an appointment.
There's something
I need to tell you.
Is it about my biological mom?
Yes.
Wasn't the Eun Ho
hit-and-run case...
closed after the culprit died?
Hong Man Su was behind it,
using that offender
to do his bidding.
Who on earth gave that order?
I am Hwang Gi Man,
the elder brother of Hwang Gi Chan,
YL Group's chairman.
He may have been dipping
into the company's funds.
Are you out of your mind?
The Saseon-dong Reconstruction...
Interior Design contest starts now.
Please cast your vote
for the design you like best.