(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children and adolescents were
filmed under production guidelines.)
(Episode 65)
Hello.
- Hey, Jae In.
- Hey.
Seung Woo.
Why are you here?
I'm here to drop off lunch boxes.
Se Ri asked me to make some.
Why did you make her do this?
Don't you know she's unwell?
I volunteered to do it.
Don't be so harsh.
Did I interrupt your meeting?
No.
Are you not going to say hello
to Director Kim Do Yun, Jae In?
Director Kim?
Nice to meet you.
I didn't recognize you at first.
We've met at the hospital, right?
You were there when I woke up.
Yes, I'm that person.
Do you work here?
Yes.
My name is Kim Do Yun.
I'm with DH Holdings.
Oh, my. What am I thinking?
I hope you like it.
It has to be good if you made it.
You're a licensed cook in Korean,
Western, and Japanese cuisine.
I am?
I thought something seemed familiar
when I cooked.
I didn't know.
There must be many more things
I have to learn.
I'm getting curious.
Is your brother-in-law
not in this meeting?
He has no business here.
I should drop off his lunch box.
Please enjoy your lunch.
Enjoy it, Seung Woo. You too, Se Ri.
Enough is enough.
Don't you know
that Jae In has amnesia?
Aren't you the one
who took things far...
and even held Jae In's funeral
in an attempt to hide her?
You were so devoted to her,
but she doesn't know you anymore.
I don't know what the intention
behind that question is,
but that was the best choice
back then.
I had a feeling
someone was after her life.
What are you talking about?
Are you saying
someone tried to kill her? Who?
I could be mistaken.
Let's eat.
Jae In!
I'm so happy for you.
I hope you're well.
I am.
I'm sorry to ask,
but I don't recall anything.
May I ask who you are?
My name is Jung Oh Seong.
We can say hello again
once you get your memories back.
Okay. I'm sorry.
Please excuse me.
(Chairman Hwang Gi Chan)
Come in.
Honey.
Hey. What brings you here
without a call?
I brought you lunch.
It feels odd to see you...
in my dad's office.
Why? Does it seem weird?
No, it was something
I couldn't imagine,
but it suits you so well.
This place reminds me of Dad.
I didn't get to stay
by his deathbed.
I feel like such an awful daughter.
Father would understand.
Right. On my way here,
I ran into that man...
named Director Kim Do Yun.
Where at?
On my way here.
He was the one who visited me
at the hospital, right?
He must be quite close to you...
if he visited me there.
Yes, well, he's the director
of DH Holdings,
an investment firm
that works with us.
My gosh, Secretary Yoon.
It's been so long.
Hello, ma'am.
It's been eight years, right?
You've become
even more composed in that while.
Thank you.
I'll return later, Mr. Chairman.
No, I was about to leave.
You should get back to work, honey.
Don't skip your meal.
I'll be home right after work.
I'll see you there.
- Please excuse me.
- Right.
Goodbye.
It looks like Jae In
really doesn't remember anything.
My heart dropped
when she looked at me...
like I was a stranger.
It's such a sad thing
for her not to remember...
her acquaintances.
Anyway, can you leave her
at that place?
We already know
what those people are like.
Wouldn't it be dangerous?
She should be fine
for the time being.
Mr. Kang moved in with her.
He did?
That kiddo must be
more loyal than he looks.
My doctor friend
at the hospital said...
her memories seem to be stuck
in her happiest period.
In other words,
these recent days were
the toughest for her.
I can understand.
She wouldn't have returned
to the past if it weren't tough.
But shouldn't someone
help her get her memories back?
We can't let her go on like this.
She'll live in pain again
once her memories return.
I don't know what to do.
I get what you mean,
but doesn't she
at least deserve a choice?
Looking the other way knowingly...
may be another form
of violence and negligence.
I'll think about
what would be best for her.
I have a meeting outside.
We meet again.
Please excuse me.
Have some coffee.
Where did you get it?
I got it at the new coffee shop
on the first floor.
We should give business
to each other.
- And for you.
- Thank you.
Do Yun told me what happened.
How's Jae In?
Did she get her memories back?
Not yet.
She'll get them back soon.
I just know it.
Of course. It will happen.
She's acting like
she owns the place.
I'm going to make tea.
Do you want a cup, too?
You never did anything
around the house.
What's going on?
I guess you can try
to make me a good cup of tea.
What are you waiting for?
I thought you were making tea.
Do you want tea?
Actually, I was going to make some.
Would you like a cup, too?
Have you become deaf already?
I want some tea,
so make me some!
Would you like a cup of tea, too?
Darn it.
Is she doing this on purpose?
How many times
does she have to repeat that?
I've been developing eye bags
from sleeping on the floor,
and she's now teasing me
with her well-rested face.
Gosh. Life must be good for you.
Darn it.
Darn it. Why do I
have to run out of my room?
I'm home.
Hey. You're home early.
I am. Where's Ji Ho?
He's playing in his room.
Goodness, are you all right?
Yes, I think the cut is pretty deep,
but I have to prepare dinner.
What do I do?
Can you do it instead of me?
What are friends for?
You should make use of her.
Me? But I'm a guest here.
Darn it.
Friends should
help each other in times of need.
Jae In's friend,
our family motto is,
"We never take a free lunch."
Why do I have to treat her
with respect?
Anyway, you should go upstairs,
put a bandage on it, and rest.
Okay. Thank you, Mother.
She's allergic to shrimps,
so just keep that in mind
when you cook.
Thanks.
Goodness.
Look at her.
She used to be such a friendly girl.
Honestly, she was the best daughter-in-law
I could ever ask for.
If Gi Chan hadn't fallen
for your temptation,
he wouldn't have made a mess
out of our family,
and they would've lived a good life.
Mother, I'm now
your daughter-in-law.
How can you say that to my face?
Don't you think you're too harsh?
What I said wasn't wrong.
You're only mad
because that was the truth.
What about her mother,
Choi Ja Young?
Do you want to continue to live
feeling belittled as her in-law?
She never treated you like a human.
Shut your mouth.
Her family is still far better off
than your no-name family.
I know you're dying to become her.
You were named Kang Jae In,
but you were a lowly nobody.
So you became jealous of her...
because she was an upper-class girl
and the daughter of YL Group.
Is that all you have to say?
Am I wrong?
Make dinner.
"We never take a free lunch."
Got it?
Mommy! I made
something awesome with blocks.
Let me show you. Come with me.
I'm busy.
But I want to show it to you.
All right. We have to eat dinner,
so let's take a quick look.
Okay!
My mom doesn't have an appetite.
She'll eat later.
Then, let's eat.
- Okay.
- Ji Ho.
This is too salty. It's so bad.
I hurt my hand,
so Se Ri did her best on my behalf.
Please enjoy it
even if it's not as good.
- Mother.
- What's wrong, Mom?
It's...
Did you put shrimp in this?
Did you, Se Ri?
Do you feel better, Mother?
I'm so relieved we had first aid.
You should go to the bedroom
and get some rest there.
No.
Jae In must be alarmed.
You can take her
and help her calm down.
She's right. Let's do as she says...
and go upstairs.
She's worried about you.
Then, please excuse me.
You should get some rest, Mother.
What?
Right. Mom. I have to take a shower.
I hope she'll be okay.
Does she need to see a doctor?
She'll be fine.
Anyway, did you know
she was allergic to shrimp?
She told me,
so I told Se Ri not to use shrimps.
I guess she forgot.
It's all my fault.
I should've paid more attention.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
It's all right.
How can you be so evil
and try to kill me?
It's a misunderstanding.
A misunderstanding, my foot.
You can't kill a person
and say it's a misunderstanding.
It really wasn't me.
I only made a little comparison
between you and Jae In.
Did that make you that mad?
You should've considered
fixing your behavior...
instead of trying to kill me!
How many times do I have to say it?
It wasn't me!
What?
Who's your daughter-in-law now?
It's me! Get yourself together!
What is wrong with you?
How dare you yell at me?
Once again, I...
Shut your mouth! Shut it!
Are you actually allergic to shrimp?
- What?
- You look too fine.
Did you put up an act...
to kick me out?
I can't believe this. I look fine?
My insides feel the worst,
and you call this fine?
If you dare to pull a trick
with the food we eat again,
not only will you get
kicked out of this place,
but you'll have to face my rage.
I won't let you get away with it,
so you better watch it!
I'm so strong that I was once told
to become a shot put athlete,
so brace yourself!
Hey! I haven't turned off
the fuse box!
- It burns!
- Hey!
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
What? Probably not.
You must be electrocuted.
That could've been bad.
- Goodness.
- Gosh.
- Darn it.
- Are you okay?
Don't men usually hold the woman
in their arms in this situation?
You'll catch a cold
if you don't dry your hair,
so dry your hair.
Will you do it for me?
That's always been a dream.
Why should I dry your hair?
Weren't you told as a kid...
always to do your own job?
Good luck.
Thanks, I guess.
The person you have reached
is unavailable. Please leave...
I'm in the study. I need to see you.
(I'm in the study.
I need to see you.)
Let go of me!
I can't put up with this anymore.
Wake Jae In up.
Wake her up and tell her everything!
Be quiet!
Are you going to wake
my entire family?
How long do I have to be patient?
I'm seeing my husband
in bed with another woman.
Do you expect me
to put up with that?
She has amnesia.
Are you going to use her amnesia...
as an excuse
to have an affair with her?
Have you forgotten?
This happened to her because of you.
Are you kidding me?
So what?
Do you expect the same
to happen to me? Are you crazy?
I'm just stating the fact.
You came when I was about
to pull my arm out without waking her.
I didn't do anything
to make you mad.
We're only sharing a room.
Nothing happened.
Anyway.
I heard Jae In told you
my mom was allergic to shrimp.
What's going on?
Did you
do that to her intentionally?
It wasn't me. It wasn't.
Why won't anyone believe me?
I've been fooled by you enough times
to stop believing your words.
Be honest.
You can't handle this
if she finds out the truth later.
She's scarier than you think.
I didn't do it. I promise.
If I really did that,
I would even kill myself
if you told me to.
Apologize to her
and say it was a mistake.
Why should I apologize
for something I didn't do?
Jae In did that
even when something wasn't her fault.
That's the etiquette
you show your elders.
I don't want to make comparisons,
but Jae In knew when to back down.
You should learn that from her.
She'll notice if I'm away
for too long, so I have to go.
If you have anything to say,
do it at work tomorrow.
Also, do not barge into that room.
This is a warning.
What are you doing here?
I was thinking about my dad.
He'd go to his study...
and read the newspaper
the first thing in the morning.
I'd always come over
and ask him to eat breakfast.
Do you remember that?
Of course, I do.
And I did that today, unknowingly.
I finished serving breakfast
and automatically came here.
I can't believe
Dad isn't here anymore.
Father will be heartbroken...
to see you sad.
Let's keep smiling...
to let him rest in peace
on the other side.
My son, you've been
looking thinner lately.
Is something bothering you?
In that case, let me know.
You know
I'm always on your side, right?
You need to stop.
No one is looking.
You're going to leave
without giving me a hug?
I'm leaving.
I love you, my son.
- Bye, Jae In.
- Bye.
Goodbye.
Have a great day.
Hello.
May I ask you
to fill out this survey?
Hello.
We've been developing
a new line of windows.
We're conducting a survey...
to reflect what our customers want.
Could you spare some time?
- Sure.
- Thank you.
This is a list of agencies...
that'll take up the project for
the Korean-style apartment complex.
Director Kang and I agreed
to pick one from the list.
I'm not here to get your opinion,
but there are procedures to take,
so I'm here to let you know.
You can't do this
without my permission as the chairman!
ES Agency's parent company...
may have been a subcontractor,
H and K Company,
but the agency itself was
proven to be free of trouble...
as a newly established business.
Chris, the CEO of ES Agency.
Naturally, I thought
he must be a non-Korean.
But I found something interesting
during my research.
His Korean name was Jung Hyeon Su.
Manager Jung of your competitor
framed Ms. Kang Jae In...
for leaking the contest design
and disappeared.
How did he become
the CEO of ES Agency,
a business affiliated with YL Group?
If you do not agree
to change the agency,
I plan to open a fact-checking committee
regarding this matter.
So?
Should I blow this up, too?
Let me know
when you decide on the agency.
I'll do that.
Come to my office. Now.
Mother was nearby,
so she came to see you.
Why did you want to see me?
I'll talk to you later.
Gi Chan, on my way here,
I ran into that doctor...
No, was he a director now?
Anyway, I ran into that punk,
Kim Do Yun, again.
Is everything okay?
Why would that punk
be a problem for me?
Na Ra told me
that his younger sister was...
the employee
who was killed by Jae In's mother.
Are you sure you can
let him lurk around at work?
It doesn't feel right.
Kicking out just her brother
isn't the end of it.
His uncle is around, too.
What? His uncle? Who's his uncle?
Patrick Jung of DH Holdings.
CEO Jung Oh Seong.
What? What did you say?
Oh Seong is... No.
That punk is the CEO's nephew?
My gosh.
This world can't be that tiny.
How did things
become this complicated?
Let's see.
Kim Do Yun and Oh Seong are
a nephew and his uncle.
Oh Seung's older sister is
the owner of the chicken place.
So, her daughter...
got framed
for having an affair with Gi Chan...
and was killed by Jae In's mother.
It's so complicated,
and it doesn't feel right.
Wait a minute.
My son isn't involved in this.
He never had an affair
with her daughter.
It's not like he killed her.
Yes, everything is good...
as long as Oh Seong
and I are into each other.
Who cares about others?
All right.
I'm home.
What's all that?
I've been bedridden for too long,
so I didn't have
anything decent to wear.
I went shopping.
People might hear that and think...
you're still the daughter
of a rich and affluent family.
I don't mean to brag,
but people do call my family
rich and affluent, Mother.
You're now married,
so you've become one of the Hwangs.
So, the money
you're splurging now is...
all hard-earned by my son.
You went shopping and returned
with your hands full of bags,
so I thought I could do this.
You can't think like that
just because I spend his money.
He lets me do that
as a good son to his mother.
You need to remain humble,
stay home, and assist him.
You can't want to live your life...
just as you have as a single woman.
Do you understand?
All right. I'll be careful, Mother.
(Investment and Development Team)
I sprained my ankle
after a meeting out of the office.
Did you see a doctor?
I'm fine.
I'll put some ice on it at home.
You can't drive in that state.
Come with me. I'll give you a ride.
Show me your foot.
It's all right.
Keep it there for a while.
I also got pain relief patches.
Are you sure
you don't need to see a doctor?
You're still the same.
You're still caring.
You'd run over to the pharmacy...
whenever I coughed a little.
I tried to bury those memories,
but they surged back to me.
You're right.
I also had forgotten...
I was like that.
Hold it.
It hadn't been long
since you started your investment firm.
What did you do before then?
I was out in the sea.
I worked as a navigator
and lived all around the world.
You must've been
with a lot of women abroad.
I'd be lying if I said I didn't.
You even married another guy,
so it would've been unfair
if I remained single.
Start driving.
But I couldn't find anyone.
I was pushed
out into the sea because of you,
but I never found anyone
who was like the wind,
someone who could push me back here.
I never found anyone like that.
I'll start driving now.
- You must've forgotten.
- Goodness.
That woman is
so harsh on her daughter-in-law.
How can there be
such an evil mother-in-law?
What do you mean?
You know where to look.
Does this feel unfair?
Do you feel wronged?
- Do you want to remain here?
- I'm home.
- Then, kill me.
- Hey.
Did you do this, Mother?
(Queen's House)
I feel bad for saying this,
but you should find
a place to move out to.
Are you telling me to leave?
This is way over the line.
You're living off me.
It's not me doing that.
Isn't she the woman
who sued you for sexual assault?
I want to tell you
that Mr. Kim Do Yun is innocent.
- I want to return to work.
- Return to work?
Catherine's identity
has been exposed?
Don't trust Hwang Gi Chan.
There's just too much
that you need to know.
Is Kim Do Yun going to expose
the truth to Jae In?