(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children and adolescents were
filmed under production guidelines.)
(Episode 17)
Hey, how old are you?
I'm six years old.
He's six? That means
it's been at least seven years.
No way. It began before the wedding?
This wasn't a simple affair.
He had kept two families.
This is why people say
you can never trust anyone.
My name is Hwang Ji Ho.
Hey, what did you just say?
My name isn't Hey. I'm Hwang Ji Ho.
Hwang Ji Ho.
My gosh.
You must be in shock.
It hasn't been long
since Ji Ho came back from the US.
I wanted to schedule something
more formal to introduce him,
but Ji Ho kept pestering me
and said...
he wanted to meet his grandma.
You can't deceive me.
Hey, I've been through
all kinds of highs and lows.
I know what you're up to.
Did you think...
I'd welcome you with open arms...
if you came with a son?
Not even in your dreams.
Mother...
Shut your mouth.
Why are you calling me your mother?
I never had a daughter-in-law
like you, so get lost.
Ji Ho is Gi Chan's son.
I don't know about me,
but please accept Ji Ho.
The only grandson...
I acknowledge is Hwang Eun Ho.
I don't need you to bring me a kid
he had out of wedlock.
And I don't even know
if he really is Gi Chan's son.
Get him out of this house now.
You can conduct a paternity test.
Stop babbling
and leave while I'm still nice.
Do you want to get humiliated
before your son?
I'm a woman of my word.
I'm at Changpyeong-dong. What is it?
It must be fatigue.
You should stay in bed.
Bye.
Was that your mother?
Yes, the trip to the burial ground
must've been tough for her.
Shouldn't she see a doctor?
I'll go. You can get some rest.
Your mother is returning tomorrow,
so you should be there for her.
She'll only feel offended
if she sees me,
so I'll leave
without saying goodbye.
Will you go to work tomorrow?
I should.
I have to catch up on lots of work.
Why do you ask?
I wanted to go
and pick up Dad's things.
I should clean out his office.
The person you have reached
is unavailable. Please...
The dead Kim Do Hee...
was my niece.
Why did it have to be him?
This is such an evil twist of fate.
Aunt Mi Ran, Seung Woo
still won't pick up his phone?
He won't.
And he hasn't been home, either.
How can you eat in this situation?
Mi Ran, you've never had any food
at a detention center, right?
You can't even imagine
a huge feast like this in there.
I wanted to eat everything I could
before I went back.
Aren't you worried about Seung Woo?
We can't reach him,
and we have no idea where he is
after he left the funeral hall.
And he never came home, either.
Why should I be worried?
He's not my child.
Ja Young!
It's obvious.
He must be wasting his life away
at a hotel,
drinking and splurging.
I covered for him until this day.
But now,
I have no reason to do that.
You were the one
who spoiled him all you wanted.
You ruined him.
That's just how he was born.
Many people grew up decently
even if they were spoiled.
See?
He wasn't even
at his father's burial...
just because I said something.
How can he be so ungrateful?
Mom, that's enough.
Is that all you have to say to me?
I did as you asked at the funeral,
but this is my house.
I'm going to say
whatever I want under my roof.
It doesn't matter
if you don't accept him as your son.
It still doesn't change that
he's the eldest son of the Kangs.
I'll look after him from now on,
so do not meddle with him.
Why would you do that?
Because I'm one of the Kangs,
and he's my nephew.
Other than your aunt,
you're the only Kang left.
Remember that.
How can you smile...
before Dad's funeral portrait?
I know you hate and resent him,
but how can you do that to the deceased?
He loved you.
If he loved me,
how could he have a kid
out of wedlock?
As a woman, don't you understand
how humiliating it is?
I'm not saying
what he did was right.
But he had
a sense of guilt about you,
and he truly loved you.
Everyone suggested
that he divorce you...
because of the damage
you brought on YL Group,
but he said no. Did you know that?
He isn't allowed to demand a divorce
as he's the one liable.
You would've been liable
for the divorce.
What you did was
more than enough to do that.
What did I do?
Don't you know?
I don't.
You killed someone!
I would do that again...
if I had to do it for you.
Stop saying you did it for me.
You aren't doing anything for me.
If anything, you're cornering me.
I'm humiliated to death...
to have you as my mother.
Even my own child...
doesn't understand
how I really feel.
Fine. I live my life alone anyway.
I won't go down like this.
My son.
Wake up, Seung Woo.
It's time to wake up.
Seung Woo.
Don't go, Mom.
Mom, I had a nightmare.
Can you hold my hand? Mom...
Who's my son?
I never gave birth
to a son like you.
Stop calling me your mother!
I do not want to hear this!
You were the one
who tortured me for life.
Do you get it?
Daddy!
Hey, Ji Ho.
Daddy, Mommy said...
we'll stay in Korea
and live with you from now on.
I see.
Please keep an eye on Ji Ho.
Ji Ho, I need to talk to Mommy.
Ji Ho, you haven't had dinner, right?
You can eat dinner with Grandma.
Okay.
That girl...
Why did you suddenly drop this bomb
without talking to me?
Are you calling Ji Ho a bomb?
I'm asking for your intention.
What do you think it is?
I kept telling you about it
again and again.
Didn't you hear me?
- I asked you to give me time...
- Time is always your excuse!
You changed your mind again
after Jae In got pregnant.
Would I ever have my time
if I sat around doing nothing?
I'm trying to save myself.
I need to live
to help Ji Ho survive.
Don't you feel bad for him?
Don't you pity him? He's your son.
I don't want Ji Ho to live
in the shadow anymore.
Ji Ho isn't the bomb. It's you.
Yu Gyeong knows everything
about you and me.
The truth will
come out soon, anyway.
Mother, I'll see you next time.
You don't have to see us off.
Goodbye, Grandma.
Let's go.
Goodness.
I have a headache.
Do you want some painkillers?
I guess he is Gi Chan's son.
He ate only the kind of food
Gi Chan also liked.
Right? He's Hwang Gi Chan Jr.
Jae In would faint
if she found out, right?
Keep your mouth shut.
Don't even say a word.
Mom, I think
I need to get a job done.
Do you need to get a job?
No, I don't mean an actual job.
I want to get something done
to look more luxurious.
In return,
I won't say a word to her.
Fine. Don't you dare say a word.
I'll make you look like
how you were before surgery.
Don't say something that scary.
Thank you, Mom.
I'm going to rest in my room.
Who did
all my troublesome kids take after?
Gosh, not only do I have
a huge headache, I feel stifled.
I can't sit around like this.
I should talk to a shaman.
Why did you go to the funeral hall?
Do you think they'll care?
You already know what they're like.
I know. But it felt so unfair,
so I had to go.
Not only did she kill Do Hee,
but they used the press
to make us seem like the murderers.
I couldn't take it.
It'll only hurt us
if we get emotional.
I must've gone crazy
because all my spite blew up.
I won't do that anymore.
I'll stay level-headed.
And let me know if you need help.
You must want
to take this to the end...
if you got a job at YL Group.
It'll be better to have a partner.
Let me know anytime
if you need my help.
Anyway, when will you tell her that
you quit your job at the hospital?
I'll do it later.
I think Yun Hee noticed already.
Your schedule was all over the place
because of surgery and whatnot...
when you worked there.
She seemed to think
something was weird...
now that you came home regularly...
Yun Hee, you should knock.
You can't just
barge into a grown man's room.
Did you quit your job
at the hospital?
See? I told you she noticed.
I overheard you two.
I'm working at a different clinic.
- Which one?
- I can never have enough time...
while working at a big hospital.
I'd have more time and energy...
to spend time with Bo Ram
if I had regular hours,
and I wanted to relax a little.
I received an offer,
so I decided to take it.
All right. I'm glad you did that.
It would've been better
if you opened your own clinic.
Can you help him out?
- He...
- I don't want that.
If I want to open a clinic,
I want to do it on my own.
If I wanted to ask him for money,
I would've done so long ago.
I'm like a bank teller...
who's always open
to Yun Hee and you.
Let me know
whenever you change your mind.
Okay.
Hey.
Let's just forget
about what happened to Do Hee.
What do you mean, forget it?
Yun Hee.
What I mean is this.
The chairman of YL died,
and his wife will be tried.
The law will be the judge,
so let's give it our faith.
You can stop minding this
and focus on your job.
I'll stop crying, too.
Do Hee is still here with me.
I'll keep her here...
and pull her out
whenever I miss her,
so don't worry about me, either.
Do you understand what I mean?
I do. I'll do as you say.
Good.
From now on,
let's think of Do Hee...
and Bo Ram,
and live bravely with a big smile.
- Okay.
- Okay?
Where's Eun Ho?
He went to the kindergarten.
Did your aunt go to work?
Yes.
They're waiting outside.
I'm not going to flee.
I'll go.
Your father came to see me
a few days before he died.
He asked me about that punk.
He didn't elaborate,
but he must've found out something
and became suspicious.
He didn't say anything to me.
He would've told you
only after he was sure.
That's his biggest strength
and weakness.
At times, prudence can be poisonous.
He approached you
because of our wealth and influence.
These people are
very lowly and despicable.
Don't you get it?
You also sound very lowly...
as someone who likes
to place people in tiers.
You should go.
They're waiting outside.
I'm going to work.
Make sure you eat lunch.
I'm not a kid.
I'll manage, so don't worry.
And call me if you need a hand.
You don't have to mind my business.
Focus on yours.
Hello?
It's me, Kang Mi Ran.
I'm listening.
Tell me why you're calling.
If you're free, I'd like to see you.
I want to talk to you in person.
I have no time...
or reason to see you.
Goodbye.
(Chairman Kang Gyu Cheol)
Don't worry about your business.
Gi Chan will do a great job
as a leader.
And don't worry
about Seung Woo, either.
I will...
take good care of him.
Are you all right?
Please take a seat here.
Why is that man here?
Thank you.
Hey.
My dad passed away.
And yes. Thank you.
My brother told me...
that you provided first aid
when my dad collapsed.
He was YL's chairman.
You knew that, right?
I found out at the hospital
when those reporters swarmed in.
I didn't want you to feel uncomfortable,
so I stayed quiet.
May the deceased rest in peace.
Hang in there.
You always appear before me
whenever times are tough.
It's as if you're my guardian angel.
Thank you so much.
People can only survive...
when a heart attack is treated
within 3 to 4 minutes.
So, I didn't do much.
You still look pale.
I'm fine.
I'm in the early stages
of pregnancy.
You can't leave like this.
Come to the clinic for a moment.
My wife will be here soon.
I don't think
she'll come around quickly.
Do you know him?
He's the guy who helped
when Eun Ho got kidnapped.
I see.
I thought it was something else.
- Something else?
- It takes a woman...
to understand another woman.
He seemed a bit too close to her
to call him...
just a guy who once helped her.
But if you also know him,
I guess it's not like that.
It's rooibos tea.
It's good for anemia.
And these are iron supplements.
Make sure you take them every day.
And...
And this.
Why are you giving me this?
If your father had been alive,
he would've given you this
to celebrate with you.
It suddenly came to me.
Celebrate?
You said you were pregnant.
I must've said something wrong.
Here.
No, you didn't.
I remembered how my dad sent me...
a basket of flowers
when I was pregnant with Eun Ho.
If I had known
he'd pass away so soon,
I would've visited him more often.
I'm sure...
your father already knows
how you feel.
It's getting cold.
Right.
So? Do you like it?
Yes, it's wonderful.
It tastes very rich.
Feel free to drink it every day
instead of water.
Hey.
Hello.
I thought you were coming to see me.
Why are you here?
I was on my way.
Honey, you remember him, right?
- He's the one who saved Eun Ho...
- Stop it.
It happened a while ago.
Stop bringing it up.
Didn't you refuse
to take compensation?
Did you ask my wife
to get you a job here?
Even jokes may sound serious
if you take it too far.
I'm sorry, Dr. Kim.
Honey, that's not the case.
What's that?
I got it as a present.
He congratulated me
for my pregnancy...
I don't think it's an occasion
for a stranger to celebrate.
Excuse us.
Let's go.
Honey. Hey.
I haven't even started yet,
but he's already suspicious
of his wife?
How interesting.
Can we walk slowly?
And you let go of my hand.
I feel dizzy.
Honey, the employees are watching.
What's going on between you and him?
Last time, you two supposedly
ran into each other by chance,
and now, he got a job
here at the in-house clinic.
How am I supposed to take this?
What are you getting at?
I don't understand...
how you can flirt with another man
after your father passed away.
I got dizzy because of anemia
on my way to your office.
Dr. Kim was there,
so I went to his office
to get iron supplements.
Things have been hectic lately,
so I had forgotten to take
iron supplements...
as recommended by my doctor.
Even so, who does he think he is
to give you flowers?
His intentions don't seem straight.
What intention?
Don't say such nonsense
that he likes me as a woman.
How is that nonsense?
Even married women are still women.
I'm pregnant!
Stop it.
I don't want our child to hear this.
Go home.
I'll talk to you there.
I have to go to a meeting.
An affair?
Who's having an affair?
You brat.
You already know everything.
How dare you lie to my face?
That's what the deity says.
Why are you asking me?
You already know.
But you probably didn't know this.
It's not just one of them.
They're both having an affair.
This couple is having lots of fun.
They're only married on paper.
Their hearts are elsewhere.
Wait, are you saying...
my daughter-in-law is
also having an affair?
Is she no longer supernatural?
What is this nonsense?
Shut your mouth!
That was my deity speaking.
(D...)
(Death)
What does this mean?
It's the character that means death.
Your second son killed someone.
What? That is utter nonsense.
No, that's not true.
You should at least ask him.
The victim is
related to his in-laws,
so you'll have to sever ties...
with your daughter-in-law
before he gets caught.
Get them divorced.
That's the only way
your son will live.
Why would
my perfectly healthy son die?
You keep saying the weirdest things.
Look. Look at this. Death.
What goes around
always comes around.
If he killed someone,
he must die, too.
You must do as I say
if you want him to live.
You said my daughter-in-law was
the biggest luck for our family...
and told us to make sure
we keep her around.
Why are you
suddenly telling me this?
You need to blame your son.
Don't get mad at me
for telling you how he can live.
Well, ma'am.
My daughter-in-law is
pregnant with their second child.
How can I make them divorce?
Can we use talismans
or hold a ritual?
Please hold a ritual
and stop everything from happening.
- I can pay you as much as...
- Do you want...
your son to die?
I would've told you to hold a ritual
if it could work.
You don't even know if the child is
really this family's blood.
Who's more important?
Your son or the kid?
My deity is telling me...
that your son also has
another child out of wedlock.
Well, I wouldn't know.
That kid is something.
He's a very smart one
who'll become a great man.
In ancient days,
he would've made you
the grand queen dowager.
Make sure you treat him well.
Hey, it's me.
Why didn't you come
to the chairman's funeral?
I thought you'd be here.
Something urgent came up,
so I couldn't be there.
- Did the burial end well?
- Yes.
Dad, you're not feeling unwell,
are you?
I'm fine.
I'm busy right now,
so let's talk later. Bye.
I felt too ashamed...
to say goodbye to him one last time.
This is a surprise.
I didn't see you at the funeral,
so I called to check in.
Are you doing all right?
Why do you ask?
Do you not want me to do well?
Why wouldn't I want you to be well?
You probably want to take
whatever inheritance I leave behind.
Father, that thought
never crossed my mind.
You better not.
I don't have anything
to leave behind,
but even if I do,
I won't leave it for you.
If you're the head of your family,
act like one.
Get yourself together
and live a better life.
If you have nothing more to say,
I'm hanging up.
Man, come on.
Why is everyone hating on me?
What did I do so wrong?
Do you all think I'm a joke?
Ms. Choi did the killing,
but I still couldn't say
Gi Chan was completely innocent.
But how is the blame on Gi Chan?
It's probably just wrong.
And they're both having affairs?
Something doesn't seem right.
Who do you think you are?
Who do you think you are, Yu Gyeong?
He's doing that again.
Good grief. If he got drunk,
he should just go to sleep.
Be quiet.
That's enough.
Get inside and go to sleep.
What's enough?
Eun Ho is in this house,
and so is Jae In.
Stop acting like a fool
and go inside.
Hey, did you
just call your husband a fool?
Did you call me a fool?
Will you be really late?
I have a lot of work to catch up on.
I'll call you when I leave.
Okay.
Who do you think you are
to order me around?
Darn it.
You should be grateful
that I still keep you around,
even though you can't have a child.
Why are you harassing me?
You need to stop!
What do you think you're doing?
Are you okay, Yu Gyeong?
Gi Man, have you gone crazy?
How can you use violence
on your wife?
Who did?
Me? I did that?
Yes, you did that.
This is
unbelievably nasty and vulgar.
Goodness. My gosh.
My goodness. What's going on?
Jae In, how can you say
such a brutal thing?
He never acts like this.
You.
Pull yourself together, you punk.
No, let go of me.
Goodness, Jae In. Calm down.
You don't have to raise your voice.
It's not a big deal.
It's a mistake. Yes.
People make mistakes...
every now and then in life, right?
A mistake or an accident,
he still can't resort to violence.
It is a big deal. This is a crime.
Goodness, a crime?
You're making me scared.
I'm sure it is so if you say so.
Yes, you're right. I think so.
But still, we're family.
Aren't we? Just let it go.
Her mother is in prison,
and her father is dead.
So, why is she acting so haughty?
Let's have a seat, Yu Gyeong.
Right here. Be careful.
I'll report him first.
Report him?
We need to make sure
this never happens again.
I can't just let it go
just because he's family.
It'll happen again.
Goodness, no. What do I do?
- No. Give me that.
- What are you doing, Mother?
- Give it back.
- Darn it.
My gosh! My goodness!
Goodness, Jae In.
I mean, it's not like
he always beats her up.
This was his first time.
If he did this all the time,
why would Yu Gyeong stay...
as someone who had
a good career as a doctor?
Isn't that so?
Just let it go. Okay?
Hey, Jae In. You know me, right?
I'll reprimand him
and teach him a lesson...
so that he never does this again.
Please don't do this
and let it go for my sake.
- Mother.
- You should go inside and rest.
- Goodness.
- Jeez.
Yu Gyeong, my...
Can you... Can you save my baby?
Can you save my baby?
Jae In!
Wake up, Jae In!
(Queen's House)
Jae In. Jae In!
And you already know
who'll treasure you...
the most, right?
My gosh. That hurts.
No way.
Aren't you Na Ra's mom?
It's you, right?
I need to know what's on your mind
to figure out everything.
Which one of them will it be?
Or do you want to live
with both of them?
What is it?
Did you kill someone?
Did you or didn't you?