(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children and adolescents were
filmed under production guidelines.)
Who's here at this hour?
Se Ri, I prepared a surprise
just for you...
to celebrate your discharge.
Do you want a hint?
He was very close to you
a long time ago,
and he called home a few days ago.
He asked for you,
so I invited him here today.
Who is it?
I don't know. We only had
a brief conversation over the phone.
You can ask him when he gets here.
Excuse me.
Hello.
I'm Ji Seong Jun,
Se Ri's ex-husband.
Oh, my. Se Ri.
Have you been married before?
Mr. Do, about the wedding photo
you found at Se Ri's aunt's place.
Are you yet to find
the man in that photo?
I've been looking everywhere.
We must find him.
She claimed it was Photoshopped,
so nothing will seem convincing
unless the man himself shows up.
I know that, too.
I will find him.
Ex-husband?
Whose ex-husband is he?
Didn't you hear him?
He said he was Se Ri's ex-husband.
Who's my ex-husband?
Are you in your right mind, Jae In?
My husband isn't this man!
Why are you yelling at her,
Ms. Kang?
Do you know me?
I don't know who you are.
What is this nonsense?
You weren't my husband.
You sent that
Photoshopped picture, didn't you?
I know you sent that to get money!
Get out of here now. Get out!
You're still the same.
Wait, this is too complicated.
So, you've been married before?
- My gosh.
- Mom.
- Mother!
- I'm home.
Na Ra, take her to her room.
Okay, Gi Chan. Mom, come.
My name is Hwang Gi Chan.
I'm Ji Seong Jun.
This isn't even Ms. Kang's place.
I don't think
you two should quarrel here.
You should talk later.
I must've made a mistake, honey.
He said you two were close,
so I invited him
without asking more.
I should've asked
for more information.
I'm sorry, Se Ri.
No, I'm sorry.
I should've told you the truth.
Please excuse my discourtesy.
This isn't your place,
so I'll go.
Stay there, Ms. Kang.
You said you didn't know him.
Se Ri.
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
She seems furious.
What am I going to do?
Don't mind her.
I have to do something,
so I'll eat dinner later.
Gi Chan and Se Ri,
this isn't the end of the surprise.
From this moment on,
nothing in your life will go
the way you expect it to.
Did Gi Chan want to meet him?
I saw Mr. Ji Seong Jun
going to the chairman's office.
Are you the man...
in Ms. Kang Se Ri's wedding photo?
So, you saw it.
This is a photo we took
at our wedding.
Honey, no. Don't believe him.
This was Photoshopped.
I've never been married to him.
You already did your research
and found out!
Jae In is behind everything!
Was that why you turned me
into a dead man?
Do you know who I am?
I don't know you!
Do I have to prove myself
by sharing where your moles are?
You're crazy.
Please excuse me
if you have no other questions.
Let me leave you with this.
You should be careful of her.
She's not afraid to do anything
when there's something she wants.
Shut your mouth!
Honey.
Shut that mouth.
Those wedding photos were all real.
Who are you?
How much of this is real,
and how much is a lie?
Honey, I'm so sorry for what I did.
This was long before I met you.
Our relationship
only lasted briefly.
I never loved him.
You're the only one for me.
I mean it.
Do you expect me to believe you?
Where do you get
that kind of confidence?
You dated me
while you lived with Jae In,
and I never raised a question
about that.
What?
I put up with it
for such a long time.
And in that while,
Ji Ho grew up without a dad.
Don't you feel bad for us?
I wasn't even two-timing you
like you did to me.
Can't you understand
that I have some history?
I'm not saying what I did was right.
But this was long before I met you.
So, do you expect me to forget this
just because it was in the past?
You should've told me before.
You should've given me a choice!
I was afraid you'd leave me.
I didn't want
to be abandoned by you.
Stop shedding
those fake tears and leave.
Yes, it's my fault that
I failed to make you trust me...
as a woman and a wife.
But I'm still in love with you,
and my feelings are still the same.
Honey, I got enough money
from H and K's slush fund...
to bribe the Chinese investor.
I'll do whatever it takes
to get them to invest.
Please give me a chance.
Make sure you schedule a meeting
with the investment company.
You may leave.
Hong Man Su, that cursed punk.
You must've wanted
to forget this past.
Thank you for your help.
Don't mention it.
It was nice to get my revenge
against Se Ri in this way.
She left me without telling me why.
Come to think of it now,
she didn't rush to marry me
out of love.
It must've been my background.
She mistook me and thought
I was made of money.
But I was way too short
of her expectations,
so she probably got disappointed
and left.
(Se Ri)
We could've talked in the office.
What do you have to say to me
all the way out here?
Shoot.
You called Ji Seong Jun there
on purpose, didn't you?
Yes.
How much information does she have?
You aren't hesitating
to answer my question.
It looks like
we're finally on the same page.
You were the YouTuber, right?
I don't know.
Do you have proof?
Wait, that thief
who robbed my aunt's place...
What took you so long?
How slow.
Then, you can't deny
that you were the YouTuber.
The photos and diploma that
the YouTuber exposed were...
all from my aunt's place.
This means you stole them!
Do I have to clarify...
your wrong guesses
and tell you everything?
If you want to know,
make a move and find out.
Do you really want
to take this all the way?
You can't win against me.
Wake up, Se Ri.
This time, I won.
I won't let you
keep doing this to me.
I'll tell Gi Chan...
that your memories are still intact!
You already did.
But did he believe you?
I'll torture you
in the worst way possible,
and this isn't even the beginning.
You better not mess with me.
I already told many people
all about you.
If I disappear or get hurt,
you'll face even worse things.
If you wish to live
for at least another day,
you should be careful.
Get it, Se Ri?
You've changed a lot.
That's not going to work,
so don't bother.
And don't even try to tell Gi Chan
that I have my memories.
Isn't it unfair?
He should suffer
as much as you did...
to make this fair.
Who knows?
It may make
your love even more passionate.
Stop this funny business.
Don't be deluded into thinking
only you know how to make recordings.
You better be careful.
Goodbye.
- I'm back.
- I'm glad you're here.
Can we talk?
I can't live with this kind of anger
and feeling this wronged.
Kick out that girl, Se Ri.
No, you can kick out both of them.
I commend her for getting the idea
to make me the gallery director,
but she already lost her baby,
so it'd be better
if you got to live in peace.
You can always find a new wife.
You're the chairman of YL Group.
Women would line up to be with you.
I can't do that now.
Why not?
She's Ji Ho's mom.
And she plays a role
in my company in America.
What about Jae In?
The same goes for her.
What's going on?
Have you fallen for her again?
No, there's a reason.
I have to go.
What?
(This folder is empty.)
They aren't here.
The files are all gone.
What are you doing over there?
Hey, Jae In. I'm leaving.
You can use my laptop.
Wait, were you going to use
Gi Chan's laptop?
You don't have
any designing programs, do you?
What?
No, I don't.
Right? I thought so.
I have the programs on mine,
so use that one.
Come with me. I'll give it to you.
Okay. Thanks.
Yes, thank you.
You should eat dinner.
Be careful, Jae In.
And let me know
whenever you need help.
I have to go out for dinner.
Bye.
- I'm home.
- You're back.
- What about your uncle?
- He's meeting someone for dinner.
Is he seeing someone?
I don't know. Why do you ask?
He's been paying more attention
to the way he dresses...
and coming home late,
so I had a feeling.
Maybe he's dating someone...
at work.
I wouldn't know. Should I find out?
No, don't.
Don't tell him that I asked.
I don't want him
to feel conscious of me...
and stop him from dating someone.
You should get changed.
Let's eat dinner.
Okay.
- Hello.
- Come on in.
I didn't expect to meet you
at such a fancy restaurant.
One moment.
What are you waiting for?
Have a seat.
I wanted
to treat you two to dinner...
and let you meet each other.
You didn't need to do that.
I already know she's your aunt.
She's not my aunt.
Seung Woo.
She gave birth to me.
It seemed like
you two were close in the past,
so I thought it'd be nice...
if you two became good friends
before you got older.
That's why I did this.
Was this too much?
I'm sorry.
I didn't know about this, either.
He asked me out for dinner.
It's okay.
So, you had a son.
It must be shocking.
I honestly didn't like
Mr. Jung's first impression,
so at first,
I never thought of doing this.
But after a few encounters with him,
I realized he had
an uncanny way of growing on you.
I was grateful for his advice, too.
Seung Woo.
- Let's eat.
- Okay.
Chairman Hwang got men
to go out and look for me...
because I didn't tell him
that your ex-husband was alive.
What now?
My life is in danger because of you!
Don't show up near your office
and keep a low profile for a while.
I'll call you when things die down.
He's just angry right now.
Don't you know that
he believes everything I say?
Give it time.
Jae In is the problem.
You're back.
Yes. Hey.
I sent you an e-mail
with the files...
I put together for the reporters.
Kang Seung Woo is her son?
Did she have him with Goo Jin Sang?
No, that's impossible.
Uncle Oh Seong, are you listening?
What? I'm sorry.
Hey, did you know...
who Kang Seung Woo was?
He's Jae In's younger brother
from another mother.
Why do you suddenly ask?
No, never mind.
Where were we?
Hello?
I was going to stop by
at the hospital later...
What did you say?
He regained his consciousness?
Really?
Goodness.
Yes, I'll run over there now.
Goodness, all deities.
Thank you very much. Goodness.
Gi Man woke up?
Yes, apparently so. The hospital.
We have to go to the hospital first.
Wait, I need my bag.
You should come with us, Se Ri.
No, it's all right.
You should go as a family.
Gi Chan, congratulations
on your brother waking up.
I'll get to work first.
Gi Man. My son.
It's me, Mom.
Do you recognize me?
It's okay.
Just lie there and stop moving.
I'm just glad you woke up.
How did you end up
rolling down the stairs?
You should've been careful.
How did you lose your footing?
Gi Man.
I'm glad you woke up.
I'm busy with a customer.
I'll reach out later.
I called her,
but she's texting me instead.
Is your crush not working out?
It's the same for me.
Does it show?
You seemed anxious.
I thought you were slow,
but you weren't that slow.
Don't be anxious,
and think in the long term.
You don't know if she'll accept you
in a year or two.
You need to give time
to let it sit with her.
You're capable
of saying these things?
Gosh. What do you take me for?
I fall in love easily,
but when I'm in love,
I always give it my all.
You won't find anyone else...
who can give you advice
for your crush's crush.
So? Don't you think that's charming?
I'm also giving you time
to let my feelings sit with you.
You know that, right?
If that's all, let's call it a day.
One moment.
There's something important.
This is a file on Designer L.
I knew you'd notice right away.
These are Designer L's background
and portfolio.
Everyone in the industry knows
who Designer L is these days.
You're right. This is
the hottest designer globally...
in the world of interior design.
According to rumors,
Taeseung Group is now
in contact to recruit the designer.
Wait, Taeseung Group?
That's one of our competitors.
I've looked into it, too.
Many other domestic companies,
other than Taeseung,
are also trying to recruit
the designer,
as well as our global competitors.
I believe YL Group also needs
a new kind of talent...
who'll bring change and innovation.
What do you think, Mr. Chairman?
Why don't we go ahead
and give it a try, too?
Then, why don't you take the job?
Me?
You're already aware that
our faith in you has dwindled...
quite a lot, right?
Covering up your scandals...
doesn't bring back the authority
you lost as the chairman.
So, you're asking me...
to recruit Designer L?
We'll be able to trust
and follow a chairman...
who contributes greatly
to the business.
Let me know if you can't do it.
I'll do it myself.
No, I'll do it.
I'll recruit Designer L.
(Chairman Hwang Gi Chan)
Director Kang Mi Ran is...
trying to make me fail
and push me out of my position.
I don't care what you do,
but find out where Designer L is.
I must find...
and successfully recruit
that designer to YL Group.
Yes, sir.
But Mr. Chairman.
You should see this first.
There are a few articles.
(The Truth Behind
YL Group's Luxury Apartment...)
(That Causes Disharmony?)
"The Truth Behind
YL Group's Luxury Apartment..."
"That Causes Disharmony?"
It claims that
the residential complex...
made in collaboration with Louis B
was an attempt by you,
the constructor,
and the person in charge at Louis B...
to take kickbacks
by inflating the prices.
Contact the constructor
and Louis B immediately.
Tell them I want to meet today,
as soon as possible.
Yes, sir.
These blew up so quickly...
as soon as we sent the file
to the reporters.
I get that he collaborated
with a luxury brand like Louis B,
but he shouldn't have
inflated the numbers this much.
He claimed to have used
high-end luxury materials,
but Louis B only took part
in the smallest aspect of the design.
He only used the brand
to inflate the prices.
People are showing
a huge reaction to this.
YL Group will have to
make a decision, right?
They won't be able
to condone this anymore.
Yes, I'll meet you
at the usual place. Goodbye.
(Chairman Hwang Gi Chan)
Honey, is everything okay?
I have to leave now.
I saw the articles and got worried.
And the staff are
all gossiping in the lounge.
So what?
Are you here to rub it in my face?
It's not easy to make
a rational decision...
when you face danger.
I wanted to give you some advice.
You don't have to be the one
to take responsibility for this.
I don't need your advice.
You may leave.
Why did you get so much food?
It's not much.
I just got some fruit and groceries.
Have you been well, Mom?
Yes. Where are you coming from?
I was at work.
You seemed to be concerned,
so let me tell you this.
Gi Man woke up.
Really?
Why did he roll down the stairs?
I don't know. I don't know anything.
- I don't know anything.
- Mom.
What's wrong, Mom?
She went out alone a few days ago,
and something
must've put her in shock.
Mom.
Mom? Don't be scared.
You're safe here.
I heard you had a tough day.
How did you know?
My aunt told me.
It must've been disappointing.
I also got mad and snapped at her.
At your aunt?
Yes.
I told her it didn't have
to be Designer L...
because our designers were good.
If she wanted to recruit Designer L,
she should've told you beforehand...
because, after all,
you're the chairman.
I mean, we aren't strangers.
She's my aunt.
I lost my cool and had a go at her,
saying she was too harsh.
Stay strong, honey.
You'll be able to find Designer L.
I have faith in you.
Jae In may end up
taking my position again.
No, this life is mine.
It's me.
Don't you need money
to keep a low profile?
I need some men.
There's a job to do.
Jae In.
You left first,
but you got here just now.
There was a lot of traffic.
It was rush hour.
Die, Hwang Gi Chan!
Jae In!
(Queen's House)
Call an ambulance now.
And get that punk!
Jae In.
Your brother doesn't seem well.
Let go of me!
What do you think you're doing?
I'm going to hurt your head
just as Gi Man hurt his.
Don't you know who I am?
What do you think will happen
if I tell the chairman...
about your attitude?
So, what I'm trying to ask is this.
Who's Kang Seung Woo's father?
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)