(Episode 10)
- Mom. - You got home early.
Do Yun, can you give this a taste?
I keep putting in more salt, but it still tastes bland.
It's a bit salty.
- It is? - Yes.
I didn't think so.
Why didn't you spit it out?
What now? These are all too salty.
I'll throw everything out.
Just leave them. I'll eat everything.
Stop talking nonsense. It's all right.
What did the police say?
Were they unable to catch the culprit yet?
No.
We put up signs and gave out flyers, so let's give it some time.
We might find a witness.
What's this?
Was this delivered here?
Yes, it was left in front of the door.
Isn't it yours?
(May the deceased rest in peace.)
(I hope this helps with the investigation.)
Something came up, so I have to go out for a minute.
- Be careful out there. - Okay.
I should clean this up.
What's with you two?
Who do you think you took after...
and were born with those pretty faces?
- Who? - Your DNA is...
all right in here.
I've never been happier, Mom.
I'm having fun raising Bo Ram,
and I'm content with my job.
I'll also continue to study...
and earn my master's degree and even Ph. D.
Different flowers bloom...
in spring, summer, fall, and winter.
Just like that, people all have different primes.
I know I'll see my glory days, too.
Just wait and see.
Yun Hee!
Hey, Yun Hee.
Goodness, Oh Seong.
Yes, Yun Hee. It's me, Oh Seong.
I'm sorry I came late.
I came as soon as I heard the news,
but it wasn't easy to travel from the middle of the ocean.
We said goodbye to Do Hee.
I should've been here.
She passed away on her birthday...
before she had a chance to eat her birthday meal or cake.
Bo Ram waited for her the whole day,
but they didn't get to meet.
Oh Seong.
Do Hee must be in a good place now, right?
She was a good girl.
Of course. Your husband must've come to meet her.
She passed away before she saw her glory days.
That really bothers me.
It keeps bothering me.
And your brother-in-law is too harsh.
He made me raise two kids all alone,
so why did he take one from me so soon?
That awful man.
Are you all right, Yun Hee?
I have a lot to do, so I need to pull myself together.
Goodness.
I must have an upset stomach.
I feel really stifled right here.
I should take some digestive medicine.
Hey, take a seat, Yun Hee.
What's up?
You need to cry.
- What? - You probably didn't get to cry,
trying to look after Do Yun and Bo Ram.
Back when our parents passed away when we were still young,
you didn't get a chance to cry, trying to look after me.
It was the same when your husband passed away.
I used to rely on you,
but it's the other way around now.
You can lean on me.
What are you waiting for? Just cry your heart out.
Do Hee...
My girl...
My girl, don't go.
My Do Hee...
You're under arrest...
for a fatal hit-and-run accident, subject to aggravated punishment,
resulting in Kim Do Hee's death.
Take him away.
What are you doing right now?
Gi Chan.
We'll talk at the police station.
I didn't kill her!
Do something, Gi Chan!
I didn't do it!
I didn't...
(Chairman Kang Gyu Cheol)
Gyu Cheol, this is bad.
Seung Woo got arrested.
What are you talking about?
I have no idea, either.
Detectives just came and took him away.
Summon Director Hwang immediately.
Seung Woo caused a hit-and-run accident?
I'm not sure.
We'll know for sure after the investigation ends.
Make sure you keep the employees quiet.
Look into this and find out what's going on.
Yes, sir.
Shouldn't we share this with Mother?
Call her, but don't tell her anything.
Tell her to come home immediately.
What is it? Why did you suddenly need me here?
Don't be alarmed at what I'm about to say.
It's Seung Woo.
He's at the police station right now.
Seung Woo is there?
Why?
So you called the chauffeur service and went home?
- Is that so? - Yes.
I'm telling you.
And exactly what time was it?
Don't you know what it's like?
How would I know the time after I get hammered?
Why did you recently get a new car?
I told you. My mom gave it to me as a present.
You're driving me crazy!
How many times do you have to ask the same question?
What did you do with the previous car?
Do you have evidence...
that I caused the hit-and-run accident?
Stop blaming the innocent.
Do you know who my father is?
He's the chairman of YL Group!
Please check the license plate number.
(59 M 2840)
It could've been the chauffeur service driver.
The driver was driving another car at this hour.
We already confirmed that.
We also found out that your car had already been demolished.
Did you know...
you could face worse punishment for destroying evidence?
Mr. Kang Seung Woo.
It's not too late to tell the truth.
You knew about it, didn't you?
You knew you were the driver who hit and killed...
Ms. Kim Do Hee, didn't you?
Yu Gyeong.
You didn't have to come.
We could've just met there.
You were on my way there, and I had to do something, too.
I never got to thank the doctor...
who helped Eun Ho.
- Do you want to give him a present? - Yes.
I'll come out quickly after I drop this off.
Hello, I...
I'm sorry. Next time.
Did you catch them?
Later.
Is something urgent going on?
Catch who?
It's his privacy. Let's go.
Okay.
(Celebrating your grand opening, YL Group Director Hwang Gi Chan)
Hey, Aunt Mi Ran.
I'm visiting my in-laws for an occasion.
Gi Chan? I haven't talked to him.
What is it?
I have to go right now.
Yu Gyeong, please tell Mother that I apologized.
What's going on?
I'll tell you later. Please do that.
Mom, don't you think this is too much?
You said I was the owner.
You can be the main cook and the owner.
They're both leaders, after all.
The main chef, the owner.
It'd look really cool if you came out...
with a customer's order in that outfit.
But still, Mom!
Sto!
I'm not your mother here. Call me the chairwoman.
Mom, it's stop, not sto.
It's the opposite of go, stop.
Stop.
Great job, Mom.
You have a killer pronunciation.
Don't use the word killer.
You'll be the daughter-in-law of an affluent family soon.
Speak with more class.
Okay. Mom.
It was very good!
See? That was wonderful. And you have a good pronunciation.
I'm here.
- Congrats on your grand opening. - Thanks.
You got something that didn't suit your size.
Why did you bring that tiny plant to celebrate?
It's from Jae In.
I'll celebrate with cash.
So, that was from Jae In?
I knew it looked expensive, although it was tiny.
Why isn't she coming in?
She left.
She left?
Something came up at home,
so she told me to tell you she was sorry.
She left without seeing her mother-in-law?
So, Ms. Choi probably won't come, either.
I don't think she can.
My dad isn't feeling well, either, so he'll drop by next time.
I only have two daughters-in-law,
yet they neither care about anything I do.
Darn it.
I paid to get dressed up for no reason.
Then, please take good care of this.
Where's Seung Woo?
The questioning is over, so he'll come out soon.
A hit-and-run accident? Says who?
Who dared to frame him for this accident?
The victim is someone you know.
You also know Ms. Kim Do Hee, who's in my department, right?
She recently passed away in a hit-and-run accident,
and the police said Seung Woo was the driver.
Mom.
Seung Woo!
Mom, please help me.
It wasn't me. I mean it.
You believe me, right?
Yes.
May I have a word with you?
Don't worry.
I'll do whatever it takes to help you.
I have no idea.
I was so drunk that I couldn't remember anything.
What if I really killed her?
Let's go.
Mom...
Excuse me. I heard you caught the driver. Who was it?
Seung Woo!
Was it you? Was it?
- Were you the driver? - Goodness.
Look at me!
You need to look at me!
Will you let go of me?
Bring Do Hee back! Bring her back!
Hey! Bring Do Hee back!
First of all, may the deceased rest in peace.
I'm sorry for your loss.
But those who are alive must go on.
You should remain level-headed in times like these.
What do you mean by that?
It's too harsh to make him an ex-convict after one mistake.
He's still young.
I'll compensate you as much as you want.
Think of it as a present from the deceased...
Present?
My younger sister died, and did you just call it a present?
How...
can you say something like that?
Finding fault and blaming him won't bring back the dead.
I'm telling you to take whatever you can get from this.
That would be best for each other.
For whom is this good?
A mistake?
How is that a mistake?
This was murder.
Your son didn't make a mistake. He murdered her!
She wouldn't have died if he had called 911...
as soon as he caused the accident! Do you understand?
I'll have him tried under the law.
I will not settle...
or show him mercy.
Again, let me tell you that your son...
didn't make a mistake.
He's a murderer.
Taken into custody?
The police were worried he might try to destroy evidence.
I know the prosecutor in charge, so I'll come home after a meeting.
All right.
Was it really Seung Woo?
Where's Mom?
She ran to the police station as soon as she heard it.
What are we going to do?
I'm worried about Seung Woo,
but if the press finds out, it'll impact our business, too.
- Mom. - Ja Young.
I need to get some rest first.
What happened?
Why was Kang Seung Woo arrested for what Jae In's mom did?
I was kind enough to send the evidence from my dash cam.
It's because the vehicle was registered under his name.
I thought they'd backtrack from the dash cam video,
but it looks like they finished investigating...
based only by the things in the video.
Did you erase all our voices when you sent the video?
Don't worry about that.
I edited that out.
Anyway, what's your plan now?
Will you let Jae In's mom go on?
You've already seen how frightening she can be.
I'll keep an eye on her for now.
What if she ends up killing you?
That won't happen.
Even if it does, I won't let it.
What's wrong? Are you in pain?
It's a stomach ulcer. I'm just stressed out.
I'll be fine.
They both fell asleep.
You can drink slowly.
Your mom may act like she's fine,
but you know she isn't, right?
The dishes she made...
a few days ago were everything Do Hee liked.
I feel bad for Bo Ram.
She needs her mom at this age.
She cried this evening, asking when her mommy would come.
I heard you told her she traveled somewhere far away.
Yes.
I couldn't make myself tell her.
You're right. She's too young to understand death.
It'll only hurt her.
Actually,
the police called and said they caught the hit-and-run driver.
They caught the driver? Why didn't you...
call me?
Hey, did you see the driver? Was it a man or a woman?
I just saw his back. He's a man.
I should've been there to beat him into a pulp.
He was Do Hee's colleague at work,
and they worked in the same department.
So, he's in the police station?
I won't let him live.
Mom will collapse if you act like this, too.
Calm down.
Darn it.
How can he be like this?
How can he do this to his work colleague?
Good grief.
Anyway, shouldn't you tell her?
I'll do it when the investigation ends.
She would go over every day if she found out,
and it would torture her.
I want this to be...
as painless as possible for her.
Good grief.
No, go away.
Go away.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Do not blame me.
It's all your fault.
You brought this upon yourself.
Let me live.
Let me live. Stop it.
Spare my life.
What?
Honey, wake up.
Honey!
Are you all right?
What about Seung Woo?
Is he home?
I must be out of my mind.
Seung Woo...
will be okay, right?
I need some hot tea.
Honey, should I come with you?
No, I need some time alone.
You should go to sleep.
Why haven't I thought of that?
Gyu Cheol.
Your son turned into a murderer.
I never imagined things would unfold like this.
This is hardly painful...
compared to how much you tortured me for life.
I have no idea.
What if I really killed her?
Seung Woo, you don't have to blame me.
You should've never been born anyway.
If you want to blame anyone, blame your birth mother.
Blame your father, who made me raise you.
It's all your sin and your karma.
Everything worked out nicely.
I finally got my revenge on you like this.
I'm back.
I heard you met with the prosecutor in charge.
How did it go?
It wasn't helpful.
Are you glad?
What do you mean?
You know who the victim is.
She disappeared from this world...
just as you threatened her.
You talk as if I have...
that girl's blood on my hands.
Did you think I convinced Seung Woo to do this?
Hardly.
I already know...
he's not that bold.
If you know that,
do whatever it takes to have Seung Woo released.
That's how you can repay us.
And remember one more thing.
It's a shame...
that Seung Woo got caught up in this unfortunate incident,
but this is when we say what goes around comes around.
She was punished by fate.
You should be careful, too.
You may be able to deceive people,
but you can't do that to fate.
Honey.
Was it really Seung Woo?
Did he do this?
Yes.
Thanks for your hard work on Seung Woo's case today.
You should go upstairs and get some rest.
Okay. Goodnight.
How can I spend a good night...
while Seung Woo is behind bars?
I'll take sleeping pills and nap briefly.
I'll give her the pills and be upstairs.
You should go first.
Okay.
I keep thinking about it,
but I still can't believe Seung Woo did this.
I berated him a few times,
so he began to call the chauffeur service every time he got drunk.
I even saw him doing it a few times.
It's all my fault.
As your dad said,
I spoiled him too much.
It wasn't your fault, Mom.
Jae In, you are...
my only hope and light from now on.
You're the only one for me.
You need to live a good life on behalf of Seung Woo.
You can leave him to me.
Only focus on seeing and thinking about good things.
That's the kind of world you need to live in.
Okay?
Mom.
Don't worry about me. Okay?
Jae In is...
my one and only child.
Everything I do, I do for her.
You should be careful, too.
What if she ends up killing you?
You were still up?
Honey.
Thank you.
My mom must be very grateful to you, too.
She said she'd leave Seung Woo to you.
If he did something wrong, he should be punished.
I don't want to go that far yet,
but please make sure...
there are no more doubts.
I'll do as you say.
Thank you, honey.
You've never been fearful or frightened of anything.
And you've never lost or been robbed of anything in life,
but you'll experience it very soon.
I'll let you have a taste of everything.
You asked them to conduct a thorough investigation?
Mother seemed to be quite worried.
I saw her taking sleeping pills last night,
so I felt heavy.
He's quite worried about you.
Thank you.
I couldn't sit around and watch this as your son-in-law,
so I protested firmly against my prosecutor friend...
to figure out the whole truth.
Above all, I trust Seung Woo.
All right. I'm glad you did that, Gi Chan.
Seung Woo's future is at stake,
so he can't be framed unjustly.
Hello.
We came even though it was a discourtesy to be here this early.
We were given the order to investigate thoroughly...
so that people wouldn't say it was done half-heartedly.
I understand that you're here to do good work.
But you should be investigating out there.
Why are you here at my place?
Well, we've been checking...
the whereabouts of the car on that day.
I saw CCTVs installed...
in front of your place and the parking lot.
Do you have the footage?
You may hand them over.
They're deleted automatically once every week,
so we don't have the videos from that day.
No, we do have it.
I believe our security team keeps a backup of the footage.
Jae In, no.
That's not the case.
Hello? Is this the security team?
What happened to the CCTV footage I wanted you to find?
Bring them over now.
Mother, they have the footage.
Aren't you glad?
Everything was fabricated.
The video was faked!
Honey, this isn't true.
I didn't do it.
Ja Young.
Did you really do this?
It wasn't me, Mi Ran!
Didn't you hear me?
This was faked.
Gi Chan tampered with this.
I know it!
Mother.
Did you kill her intentionally, knowing it was Ms. Kim?
What is he talking about?
Did you do this intentionally?
Mother had been suspicious...
that Ms. Kim and I were in an affair.
I clearly told her it wasn't the case,
and Seung Woo also tried to talk her out of this idea.
But even after that, she kept tailing Ms. Kim...
and threatened to kill her.
Ms. Kim became frightened and told me all about it.
Mom, you didn't do that, did you?
Jae In, listen up.
He's slandering me.
He got caught cheating on you with that woman.
I said I'd make him divorce you,
so he began to frame me as his way of protesting.
You need to stop, Mother!
I knew you never approved of me,
but did you have to take things this far?
Did you really do this?
Was it you?
If nothing else,
Seung Woo is...
your son.
Why did you do this?
It's your fault.
It's all your fault.
Honey...
How is he my son?
I never gave birth to him, so how is he my son?
Why is he my son?
How do you call him my son?
He's your son, but not mine!
He's not mine!
- Ma'am. - He's not my son!
You're under arrest for a fatal hit-and-run accident...
resulting in Kim Do Hee's death.
Come with us.
Mom.
(Queen's House)
The hit-and-run driver wasn't Kang Seung Woo,
but his mother?
I did it for you.
You're the only one in my life.
Remember this.
Seung Woo isn't your brother.
- What do you mean, no? - Do not let him have the company.
You're the rightful owner of YL, no matter what anyone says.
I got the gift. Thank you.
Is that doctor acquainted with Jae In?
He's the older brother of the woman her mom killed...
in that accident.