[English subtitles are available]
[Mr. Sarunsathorn Tanawarchrawat]
[Mr. Raveewit Jirapongkanon]
[Mr. Tanawat Sukfuengfoo]
[Mr. Pahun Jiyacharoen]
[Mr. Alongkorn Chaovanaprecha]
[Mr. Songsit Roongnophakunsri]
[Miss Nawaporn Chansuk]
[Mr. Kiatkamon Lata]
[Mr. Ratchapong Anomakiti]
[Miss Prissana Klampinij]
[Mr. Thanayoug Wongtrakul]
[Mr. Suthipong Teerasakul]
[Mr. Nirun Rattanapan]
[Mrs. Aunthisorn Chaovanaprecha]
[Mr. Rungradit Rungamonwanit]
[Chains of Heart]
[Mr. Tee, the guy with the big bike?]
[He threatened me.]
[He told me to go back.]
[Since you are already here,]
I want to do something thrilling.
[We will be together again on the 7th day of the 7th month, by Din & Ken]
Where is Ken?
Didn't he go with you guys?
Gun?
Ken?
Who are you looking for?
What do you want?
Where is Ken?
Who's Ken?
There's no one here.
Leave.
Ken.
He's the son of a Hong Kong restaurant owner.
You worked with him.
Ken?
Why would he be here?
He's not here.
Leave!
Can I come and have a look?
Suit yourself.
Ken?
See?
But, he really came to see you.
If he came, you would've seen him.
Ken?
I told you he wasn't here.
Just leave!
Fine!
Ken!
Don't worry about me.
Go after Gun.
I'll be right back.
Fin!
Hey!
What is this about?
You are rude when you speak to me,
my dear brother Fin!
Nok?
Come here and help me out!
Get over here!
I'm coming!
Why did you kick me?
Because you were rude to me, Brother!
I'm here!
Come here, brat!
Nok!
Next time, be nice to me, Brother!
Stop resisting!
Hey!
Did you die that easily?
Go away.
Hey!
Who is that?
Who are you?
It's none of your business.
Stay out of this!
Why did you have to kill Fin?
He botched the job.
Stay out of this!
Understood?
I got to go, Brother.
Hey!
Don't move!
I'm at the edge of the forest.
Yes, Mr. Lue.
I'll take care of it.
He wants to see you.
What is this about?
He told me he used to visit you very often.
But, he never brought me here
when he was in the area.
He said it was far and dangerous.
It's true.
What's true?
Nothing here is dangerous.
There is nothing but the forest.
Everything is calm...
and refreshing.
Where are you guys going next?
Are you going to sightsee around the area?
Um...
Din asked me to go on a trip.
Take this and keep it with you.
Raging Bull, what's your 20?
Standing by.
Ken.
I will drop you off later.
No, I want to go with you
No!
The forest is dangerous, Ken.
Wait here.
If nothing happens, I'll be back before sunrise.
Why do you have to leave me for this stupid job?
I'll be back soon.
Who on earth is this?
The Chinese guy who bought Seng's timber factory last year.
What does he want from us?
I don't know.
How could you let him see your face?
Does he remember you?
Don't worry.
He doesn't remember my face.
How you can be sure?
You need to hurry up and find out
why he is messing with Ken.
And don't let anyone else see your face!
Fool!
[Two years ago]
Din?
How many of them are there?
Are there any of us?
Hum?
Answer me, Brother!
Hey.
How are you, boss?
Hello, Chief.
Thank you.
Without you, I'd be in trouble.
My customers abroad place many orders.
They have already paid,
I can't cancel the orders.
This is Din.
He is the right-hand man I mentioned.
Oh.
He has a strong opinion of his own.
He likes to defend the nature.
Good.
Me too.
Kid.
Have we met before?
Boss.
He is the son of the massage parlour owner.
Oh?
Meaw's son?
Oh.
We're not strangers. We can talk this out.
Hey! Let him go.
I must apologize for my staff.
I know your parents very well.
We've loved and helped each other for ages.
I'll be sure to pay you.
Let's help each other.
Let your boss know.
Here.
Hey.
If it is not enough, you can tell me.
I am just and I have enough money
to pay you for the work.
Here.
Hey!
Din!
Idiot!
But he neglected his duty and caused damage to the nation!
You cannot support their illicit activities.
You have to arrest them!
Who the hell are you?
Huh?
How dare you lecture me?
I was here before you even got here!
The Chief was kind enough to pay you.
How hard is it to accept the money?
Camera?
Din!
Don't shoot!
Hey!
Why?
[That drawing is beautiful.]
Before they could be together,
they had to overcome many obstacles.
[Welcome to Din's world.]
Din!
Hey!
Where are you?
Din!
Over here!
Hey!
Where are you going?
The forest is that way.
Why are you going that way?
Go this way!
Go!
Cursed Din!
Quick!
Ken!
Din?
Din!
-Din! -Cursed Din!
Hey!
Who are you?
Din's friend.
Din's friend?
Who?
Din's friend is here!
I will take you to Din.
Who are you?
Nok!
Go!
How could I miss?
Quick!
Din!
Go! Keep going!
Go, Din! Go!
Why did you stop?
Where is my stuff?
Talk!
What are you doing?
Stop!
Please!
Where is my stuff? Tell me!
Din!
Mr. Lue.
Are you okay?
Din...
Calm down.
It's me.
That was it.
By the time I got you out of Fin's house,
it was already dark.
You were unconscious.
If I took you back to the hotel, it could take a few hours...
I thought
it'd be best to first get some rest at a place nearby.
You helped me again, Mr. Lue.
Don't mention it.
Can you explain everything to me?
Why?
Why were you attacked?
Why did Fin attack you?
And...
You are the one who told me that
the person who killed Fin
was the same person who hit us with a car.
Yes.
I remember him.
So who was it?
Why did he have to kill Fin?
Perhaps...
he wanted to keep his mouth shut
to cover something up?
The truth is,
your past is tied to this place.
I feel sorry
for your former lover.
Yes.
Din must be very happy
that you came to bid him farewell.
But I think,
he might also be sad.
He is more worried about you
because your is at risk.
It doesn't matter what I do or where I am.
Some people are trying to hurt me
and Fin from Jo Chua restaurant.
Some wanted Fin dead.
Who are they?
Do you know?
Or...
Do you suspect anyone?
I don't understand.
Why are they hunting you down?
Mr. Lue, you know how dangerous this is.
You don't need to know more than you do now.
Stay away from me.
Thanks for everything you've done for me.
Good morning, Mr. Lue.
You're awake.
Do you like painting?
Yes.
Do you want to try?
I don't know how.
This is your breakfast.
I bought it.
The food here looks delicious.
But I'm not sure
whether you can eat it or not.
Yes, I can.
I like all of them.
Really?
That's great.
So...
Shall we eat?
Take a seat.
Mr. Lue.
Yes.
It's me.
Where is your ride?
This is it.
This is my ride.
Where are you going, Ken?
It's still early morning.
I was taking a walk.
Great.
Let's take a ride together.
But first, put on the helmet.
Erm...
Is it too tight?
A little bit.
Better?
Yes.
Let's go.
I'll open the door for you.
Shall we go now?
Let's accept the monk's blessing.
AmitÄbha.
Have you given alms before?
Never.
Wait.
Be careful, it's hot.
Wow.
This shop is beautiful, Ken!
Let have a look inside.
I did some research.
It turns out that this restaurant is the most famous in the area.
It has beautiful views
and delicious food.
Yes.
Wow, it's here.
Wow.
This smells delicious.
Do you like kanom jeen saunam?
Yes.
I have tried it before.
Why?
Is it weird?
Not at all.
Maybe
it was your beloved's favorite dish?
I envy him.
Why?
Well...
For having someone like you as his lover.
You are loyal to him.
You don't fall for anyone else.
Thank you, Mr. Lue.
Despite everything,
he's the only one I have.
Oh.
Your friend is probably worried about you.
They might be searching for you.
Mr. Lue.
Yes?
Can I borrow your phone?
Sure.
Thank you.
Hello.
Hello
That's not very nice of you!
You spent the night with another guy!
That was too much!
Hey!
Ken.
What are you doing?
It's a long story. I'll fill you in later.
I'm calling to you
so you don't have to be worried.
But where are you now?
We'll go and fetch you.
It's okay, I will be back soon.
Mr. Lue will give me a lift.
Mr. Lue?
This is not cool at all.
You could get yourself in trouble!
Huh?
It's too much!
Hold on.
Ken.
Nok's underling that got caught
is now dead.
What?
Yes.
I think you are in danger.
Are you okay?
It's nothing.
My friends are worried about me.
Excuse me.
Have you been here before?
Yes,
but it was a long time ago.
The monk is here.
Greetings.
I'm Ken.
You?
Yes.
Is Din with you?
He didn't come.
I'm here with my friend.
Hello, Mr. Lue.
Stop!
Whatever reason we have
to be separated from each other,
we will meet again on this bridge
on the seventh day of the seventh month.
Din has probably been reincarnated.
Maybe he's having fun somewhere.
That's right.
He could be move on without us.
We're still alive. We should move on.
I heard that a foreign boy is wooing you.
Well?
Is it true?
Is he cute?
I will take Ken back.
Thank you.
Here,
the wall iris.
It represents your strong and unwavering love.
Okay?