I love you, Eul.
Stop it, Jun-young.
The entire nation knows
that you're a good actor.
So stop it already.
Think about what you did to her.
How can you even look at her in the eye
and say that you like her?
I love you,
Eul.
Jik kept telling me to be careful.
He said you and I live
in different worlds now.
He told me not to get confused
by every little thing you do.
He told me not to get shaken or hurt.
He kept warning me.
I guess I'm the crazy one here!
I'm the crazy one!
My gosh, I should've listened to Jik.
I never
used you or toyed with you.
Focus only on me.
Listen only to me.
I love you,
Eul.
Don't go.
Don't go, Eul.
We were just coworkers who got along well.
But then things just happened.
We're too busy to see each other nowadays.
My gosh, don't say that.
Stars always say that.
At your birthday party,
I heard Jun-young gave you
a bouquet of 1,000 roses
and sang you a song.
Everyone's talking about it.
JUN-YOUNG CONFESSED HIS LOVE FOR HER
ON HER BIRTHDAY
Well, that was...
He's a busy man. I didn't think he'd come.
He just suddenly showed up.
I was very surprised.
But after his concert,
Jun-young just disappeared
hand-in-hand with the producer
of his documentary
after proposing to her.
Did that shock you?
No, not at all.
I guess not.
It was a show to shield you
from prying reporters.
You knew about it in advance, right?
Yes.
She must be friends with a warlock.
I'm amazed. Your acting was excellent.
If so...
Eul.
Did you also know in advance
that Jun-young used you
to cover up their scandal?
Well, first of all,
he's a warm-hearted guy.
He's also considerate
-Of course I did.
-and sincere.
He told me at the concert hall.
He told me what he'd do
and asked me to react appropriately.
So you're saying
you put on an act, as well?
Yes.
What do you think?
Wasn't I pretty impressive?
Maybe I should try a career as an actress.
I'm really out of words.
Why are you telling me this now?
We were so worried about you
because we had no clue.
-Sorry.
-Saying sorry won't cut it this time.
Because of you,
your poor brother skipped school.
He couldn't sleep or eat.
Not to mention Hyeon-u who...
Forget it. You're such a brat.
I'll kill you.
You deserve to die.
I'm tired.
Will you please stop?
Would you like to say anything
to our viewers?
Hello, everyone.
I sincerely apologize for confusing you
and not telling the truth.
To protect me,
Jun-young acted a bit drastically,
risking his own reputation.
I hope you don't blame him too much.
Again, I would like to apologize
to his fans and mine.
Yu-na is amazing.
Playing the lead in a miniseries
really helped improve her acting skills.
I'll sue anyone who says
her acting is horrible.
Sir, you're deceiving the whole nation.
We aren't swindlers, you know.
There's no just reason for this.
What are people saying?
"A top celebrity couple is born."
"This is the class of a Hallyu star."
"He cares so much for his woman."
"Jun-young's so chivalrous."
"Where can I find a man like him?
I'm a woman similar to Yu-na."
That's right.
A star like Yu-na
matches Jun-young's level.
Not a common girl like that--
I see why you'd want this.
But what does Yu-na get out
of taking part in this con?
Even if she's your cousin's daughter--
She was offered four commercials
since the scandal.
After her movie failed,
people complained
that a supporting actress
had stolen the lead role.
But no one's saying that
after the scandal broke.
This is what you call a win-win situation.
Still, this is wrong.
What does that make Ms. No?
"I feel bad for the producer. Was she used
as a shield for the two stars?
She's a professional at this. If you
need to avoid a scandal, hire Ms. No.
Call the hotline at 1288-1288.
Call us now."
See? It worked out for her, as well.
If Jun-young's fans saw her anywhere,
she would've gotten killed by them.
But they don't even call her
a gold digger anymore.
I still think this is wrong.
The person Jun-young
actually likes is Ms. No...
But why is Jun-young so quiet?
Right? With his temper,
he would have come and yelled
and grabbed him by the collar by now.
But he's not even showing up.
It's making me nervous.
You're right.
Don't you think that's odd?
He hasn't called once.
This isn't like him.
Maybe
-he didn't read the news yet.
-That's not possible.
The scandal's the only thing on TV,
the papers, and the internet.
Maybe
there's a blackout at his house.
He'd still have access to the internet.
What's going on?
Talking about it just made me feel worse.
Why did you two have to bring that up?
I guess you feel
a little bit guilty after all.
Maybe...
Maybe what?
"Mr. Namgung, you jerk,
you must be really crazy for money!"
He could have thought that,
and maybe died from getting too angry.
Your dad grabbed me by the collar
last time, and now you're doing the same?
Does my collar belong
to you two? You jerk.
Hey, this is...
Hello, Grandpa.
Thanks for the food.
You're the best, Grandpa.
-Really?
-This is good.
There's cheese in it.
Hey, Grandpa.
Why didn't you tell us
about your rich friend?
What are you talking about?
I don't have a rich friend.
Thanks, Grandpa.
I love you, man.
Your friend is awesome.
Don't lie.
Your friend bought burgers
for the whole school,
even for all the teachers.
What are you talking about?
You must be mistaken.
Hey, Grandpa, the dean wants to see you.
See you later.
Thank you so much.
-Could you sign this for me?
-Sure.
"To the student dean."
Oh, you're the dean.
-Can I also take a photo?
-Sure.
Here's my favorite student,
No Jik.
My goodness. How could you?
Why didn't you tell us
you were friends with a star?
Could you say hello?
Hi. Study hard, okay?
It's been a while, Jik.
All the students, teachers,
and staff add up to about 930 people.
The burger set costs 6,100 won, right?
You've grown a lot since we last met.
-I wouldn't recognize--
-That's
a total of 5,673,000 won.
Give me your account number.
I heard you're really smart.
You want to go to medical school?
I can't pay all of it back right now.
I'll make a transfer every month.
Give me your account number.
Come on, give it to me.
Jik.
I
like your sister.
I like her so much that I'm going crazy.
I can't eat.
I can't sleep or breathe.
I'm barely living.
So I need your help.
Tell her not to run away.
Tell her to look at me.
Tell her to trust me.
I heard she only listens to you.
I'll send 5,673,000 won
to your agency as soon as I get the money.
Jik.
I never
used you or toyed with you.
Focus only on me.
Listen only to me.
I love you,
Eul.
I love you, Eul.
No...
CHOI JI-TAE
Sir.
I picked up the car you parked outside
Mr. Sin Jun-young's house.
Thank you.
For just one minute,
may I speak freely as a friend, sir?
Sure.
Stop this, Ji-tae.
You went too far already.
Apologize to Jeong-eun,
and give up on Ms. No.
Do as I say.
If she finds out who you are...
If Jeong-eun finds out who she is...
If your parents find out
who she is, then--
-Your minute's up.
-Ji-tae.
Your time's up, Mr. Kang.
Sir.
Yes, sir.
Ms. Kim, did you get what I asked for?
Who is it?
Na-ri said you hadn't eaten anything.
It already cooled down.
Eat up.
Here.
Go on.
She has hands, too.
It's not like she's critically ill.
You don't have to feed her like that.
If you don't want abalone porridge, I also
brought your favorite green bean porridge.
Do you want that instead?
I'm fine, so can you please--
If you're fine, eat.
Do you know how you look?
You look like you could die
a minute from now.
Open up.
Gosh.
This abalone porridge is horrible.
Don't eat it. It'll ruin your appetite.
This is my friend's place, not mine.
I can prepare my own food,
so please leave.
Eul.
That's right. Don't eat porridge.
You need to eat rice.
We Koreans need to eat rice.
You're really weird.
I heard you rejected her.
Why are you still hanging around?
You don't want her
but you don't want others to have her?
Does Ms. Kim Yu-na know you're here?
How would she?
I don't even have her number.
Gosh, that tasted really disgusting.
By the way,
let me
comment on how you said
I have no right to love Eul.
Do we need a permit to be in love?
I can love whoever I want.
Why else would we have free will?
Why are you smiling?
You're right.
A man loving a woman
isn't about having rights.
If you love someone,
you can just love that person.
I was confused,
but you straightened things out for me.
Thank you.
Who are you?
You're hiding an expensive watch
underneath a cheap jacket.
Who are you and why are you
hanging around Eul
in such a mismatched style?
That watch has such
a delicate mechanism that
no fakes have been made.
Who are you?
You're not a thief or a robber, are you?
Why do you care who I am?
We're just two undeserving men
who happen to like the same woman.
That's the unfortunate tragedy.
12 MISSED CALLS
HA-RU
Why didn't you pick up, Ji-tae?
Mom just collapsed.
Mom.
-Ji-tae.
-Why are you here?
She wanted to go to the sauna,
so I went with her.
She suddenly complained of chest pain
and passed out.
What did you do?
-What?
-What did you do that made her pass out?
What do you mean?
How could she have done something?
Mom's still alive because Jeong-eun
brought her here right away.
Where were you while all this happened?
I called you over ten times.
Sorry, Ji-tae.
I should have taken
extra good care of her.
I'm really sorry.
Why should you apologize?
Dad's on a business trip,
and Ji-tae didn't even pick up.
I would have died of fear
if I didn't have you to rely on.
Don't worry, Ha-ru.
Your mom will be fine.
The doctor said
it could be a side effect
of the kidney transplant.
We'll find out for sure
when the test results are out.
She'll be fine.
Don't worry too much.
Jeong-eun's talking to you.
Why won't you answer?
You didn't even thank our mom's lifesaver.
Ha-ru.
Where are your manners?
I'm going to tell Dad about you.
You shouldn't say things like that.
He didn't answer his phone
because he was at work.
It's hard to answer a call
when you're working.
Where is she?
Finish your meal and come out.
I'll wait out here.
Eat up.
Excuse me.
Can I have another bowl of rice?
Isn't that Sin Jun-young?
I don't think so.
What would he be doing here? It's not him.
-I think it's him.
-It can't be. Let's go.
You have an upset stomach.
The tip of your hand is cold
and it's lumpy here.
I know a doctor who can help you out.
Shall we go?
Ma'am, give us the check, please.
KOREAN FOOD RESTAURANT
Let go.
-Do I seem easy to you?
-No.
-Am I a pushover?
Then why are you doing this to me?
What did I do?
I'm just upset because you seem sick.
I feel worse because it's my fault,
so I want to help and make you feel okay.
That's all.
You just shed the title of a being
a gold digger thanks to Yu-na.
If people notice us fighting in the open,
it'll look really bad.
You won't die,
so just come with me quietly.
Just let go of my hand.
Mind your business
whether I'm sick or not.
-Say something that makes more sense.
-What?
I have no intention of letting go.
Shall we stand here all day?
You lunatic.
You got that right. Now come with me.
Do you want to avoid me that badly?
Yes.
My fans wish for a chance
to look at me for a minute.
They'd want to kill you
if they heard that.
Drop me off at the hospital and get lost.
Okay.
I'm good at getting lost.
I'll disappear from your sight right away
without leaving a trace.
But just not right now.
-What?
-I'll go after a minimum of three months
and a maximum of four months.
I'm going to cling onto Hyeon-u again.
I'll make a scene until he accepts me.
I'll visit him, call him,
-cry, beg--
-Do what you want.
I like him, not you.
-As if I care.
-Hey.
I don't care who you like.
Pride and jealousy?
I have no time for that.
Why is the hospital so far away?
Is it even in Seoul?
IHWASOO YUKGAEJANG
Where's the hospital?
SIN JUN-YOUNG'S FANS ARE NOT WELCOME
If my mom tries to chase you out,
say you're my anti-fan.
Your mom?
Yes. My mom.
She's an expert when it comes to
folk remedies for an upset stomach.
-This time, it's on me.
-Don't say that.
JUN-YOUNG AND YU-NA
HAVE BEEN DATING FOR A YEAR
We'll pay now.
Okay.
Did you enjoy your meal?
Yes, we did.
Welcome to--
Goodbye.
Thanks. Goodbye.
WE'RE CLOSED FOR PERSONAL REASONS
Let go. I won't run away.
Your mom's watching.
I'm sorry for introducing myself so late.
My name is No Eul.
Aren't you
-the gold digger?
-Oh, that.
I'm not a gold digger.
I'm just a victim who was used
to stop Sin Jun-young's scandal.
She has an upset stomach because of me.
Please help her, Mom.
No, you don't have to.
I'll just go and buy some medicine.
Sorry for intruding.
Goodbye.
You really don't have to worry.
I'm really not a gold digger,
and your son and I
are not dating.
That's not true.
There's something between you two.
Whether it's indigestion or not,
you're the first girl that Jun-young
ever brought over.
She's the girl I like, Mom.
I told you over the phone last time.
His manager told me that
Jun-young's not exactly
in his right mind these days.
He got hit on the head
with a wooden stick while shooting,
so his brain--
Anyway, I'm just trying to tell you that
he makes poor judgments--
I don't know why
I can't stop thinking of her.
She's been on my mind
for the last nine years.
And I realized that
I'm madly in love with her
only about two weeks ago.
Hey, Sin Jun-young.
This is strange.
Everyone on TV says
you're seeing someone else.
That's the only thing
people are talking about.
But here you are saying that
you like the gold digger,
I mean, gold miner...
No, this girl with the eyes
of a scared rabbit.
No.
That's what he says. It's not mutual.
-No Eul.
-What's going on?
She doesn't like you, but you like her?
Yeong-ok!
I think something is wrong with his head.
Yong-deuk.
Take the sign off and accept customers.
I can't believe we closed the shop
for two clowns.
What nonsense is this?
I'm good at
knowing where I stand.
Whatever your son says,
I'll do my best to avoid him.
You don't have anything to worry about.
Nothing will happen.
Hey.
If you don't believe me,
-I'll write it down and sign it.
-Why would you do that?
You're making me angry.
If that's not enough,
-I can just disappear.
-Eul.
I'll disappear to a place
where Jun-young can't find me.
Wait.
Don't poke too hard
just because you hate me.
Aren't you going to do it?
I didn't do it yet.
I see.
Please don't hate me too much.
I don't hate you.
Why not?
I'd want to kill me if I were you.
I don't. You know where you stand.
What's seven times eight?
-What?
-The times table.
What's seven times eight?
-It's 56.
-You're sane.
Your head's fine.
When Guk-yeong
fell madly in love with a gold digger,
he said three times three was eight.
What's eight times seven, then?
-It's 56.
-Good.
You're fine.
Why would someone who's sane
fall for someone
who wears cheap sneakers like that?
Girls who wear sparkly high heels
must be around you all the time.
I know, right?
Why did I forego girls
who wear expensive heels
and fall for a girl who wears cheap shoes?
The apple really doesn't fall far
from the tree.
Your father
ignored all the smart
and pretty college girls
and fell for your mother
who thought that Gandhi
was a Korean monk.
When you grow older
and learn how the world works,
you'll see that high heels
are better than sneakers.
You'll forget all about when you fell for
cheap sneakers.
Just like that.
Just like Choi Hyeon-jun.
With all his connections,
he could've easily tracked down your mom.
But all these years, he never did.
Welcome back.
Why don't you get changed?
He might find out
that you've fallen for a lowly girl.
Do you like her that much?
Enough to exchange your expensive suit
for a cheap jacket to match her level?
I want to spend time with my family today.
I'll have Mr. Kang drive you home.
-Goodbye.
-What?
Ji-tae.
Fortunately,
it wasn't what we feared.
Everything seems normal.
You can leave tomorrow--
No.
I fear for my health and my life.
Pardon?
I received my husband's kidney
and it extended my life,
but you can't say I'm cured.
A transplanted kidney
lasts about 10 to 15 years.
That's only statistics.
A kidney can fail at any time.
So you could say I'm terminally ill.
Ma'am.
"Our staff will do their best,
but the family members,
especially you, Mr. Choi,
must do your best as her husband
to help her relax and not get any stress.
You need to give her
extra attention and consideration.
We cannot guarantee the results
if she ends up getting another surgery."
Could you say that to my husband?
Honey.
Are the results back?
How is she?
I'm sorry to have to say this.
There are some causes for concern.
Is her body rejecting the kidney?
Her condition
is not that serious yet, but--
What, then?
What can we do?
What must I do?
You and I will become family
in a month's time.
I told your mother at the sauna that
I would like to become
her daughter-in-law soon.
Your parents' wedding anniversary
is next month.
I suggested we get married then.
Your mother looked overjoyed.
You should have
been there to see her face.
Stop!
How...
You can't pour fish sauce like it's water!
It's salty. It's so salty.
Well, then...
What are you doing, you fool?
You said it's salty.
My goodness.
Isn't Eul pretty
just like how you once were?
But I'm not going to let her
become like you.
I won't let her live the life you did.
I won't let her get discouraged
thinking about our difference
in status or background.
The cabbage tastes terrible.
Did they deceive me again?
I won't let her run off like you did.
What's wrong with the cabbage you sold me?
You said they were the best,
but they're so dry.
Didn't I say I wouldn't buy from you
if you lied again?
How dare they lie about this!
Whatever you say, I won't let her go.
I won't give up on her even if I die.
I'm going to do
whatever I want from now on.
Why are they so quiet?
Did Yeong-ok kill him or something?
Did you hear everything?
You could hear from here, right?
Not everything,
but I heard most of it.
Jun-young may look like a top star,
but his mom never cooked him
a warm meal whenever he came by.
He's a poor guy.
All he gets is an earful
of curses from her.
But...
Why aren't they getting along well?
Don't even go there.
She expected him to become a prosecutor,
but he quit school to become a celebrity.
His mom lost her mind...
Get the details from Jun-young.
What does your father do?
My mom's a single mother.
She had me when she was 22.
My father...
wasn't in the picture from the start.
When I was in high school,
she worked at a bar to pay for a tutor.
Then she got caught
trying to bribe my teacher.
I couldn't stand going to school
after that.
As if peeling fruits at a hostess bar
was something to show off about...
At a picnic in middle school,
she gave the teachers
boxes full of apples cut into
all sorts of shapes.
That wounded her adolescent son
more than anything.
She also stole something
when I was in second grade.
It's because I said
I wanted to eat tangsuyuk.
We couldn't even afford to buy rice.
Do you still think
I'm out of your league?
Thanks for helping me relieve
my upset stomach.
Bye.
Go home.
You just got back from a business trip.
What if you collapse, too?
I'll stay here.
I will stay
beside your mother.
Ha-ru will be afraid all alone.
Go home.
Dad.
Hyeon-u, do you want some noodles?
DAD
Hello?
I'm sorry, Ji-tae.
About what?
About everything.
I'll be good to you.
I promise.
You're doing fine as it is.
Please tell Jeong-eun that I thank her.
I owe her a lot.
Okay.
I'll tell her.
Good. Sleep well.
You too.
EMPTY
I only ordered two acorn jelly noodles.
I know. The rest of this is on the house.
-Why?
-I heard you went from
a national gold digger to Ms. Shield.
Your parents didn't raise you
so you could take bullets for someone.
-That's--
-I'm sure you must have
fallen for him at one point.
Instead, those two stars just used you.
Now eat up.
When you feel empty after being dumped,
it's best to fill your belly.
Since you set it all out for me,
-I might as well eat.
-Go on.
Tell me.
Were you dumped only
by Hyeon-u and Jun-young recently?
Was there anyone else?
You see, when it rains, it pours.
I know.
You should lower your standards.
Who are you meeting today?
-Hyeon-u.
-Who?
The Hyeon-u I know?
Yes.
Hey.
Most people only get crappy cars
after a luxury car drives away.
But for you, a luxury car drove away,
yet a Sedan still comes for you.
You ordered two noodles, right?
Yes.
MS. NO
Your call cannot be connected.
Please leave...
Where were you all day?
I brought gobchang, your favorite.
Guk-yeong, kneel.
-Just me?
-I'm too old to kneel.
The idea for the Jun-young and Yu-na fraud
came out of your head.
-Sir.
-I'm sorry, Jun-young.
I should've run it by you first,
but just know that
I made a hard decision
that would help you in the long run.
If I did it with
the tiniest bit of selfishness,
you can scald Guk-yeong's fingers.
Sir, why mine? I didn't do anything.
You did well.
Did he just say I did well?
Yes.
Why?
I think he's gone crazy.
My goodness.
Look at the state of the noodles.
What a waste.
Where's Hyeon-u? It's been over an hour.
He said he'd come.
-But he hasn't.
-I think this means he won't come.
Oh, my. I think you
just got rejected again.
Wait here.
I was going to ask him to hold me back.
What?
I don't care now. It's all his fault.
What do you mean?
Right.
No one would be in their right mind
in this situation.
8 MISSED CALLS
MS. NO
Hello?
No Eul?
I didn't hear that. What did you say?
No, don't say it.
I'll come right over. Say it to my face.
You were sorely mistaken.
If you thought
I would get discouraged,
give up, or step aside
over something like this,
then you were wrong.
Come at me with all you have.
I will never lose hope,
be sad,
or succumb.
I guess we really do look great together.
Why don't we date for real?
Maybe the person who was really used
in this situation was Ms. Kim Yu-na.
Come on, people might notice.
Notice what? The fact
that you actually like me, too?
Why are you mentioning her again?
Because I feel bad.
She was carrying Hyeon-jun's child.
Hyeon-gil!
The Minister of Culture and Sports
is giving you an award today.
Will Sin Jun-young be there?
Are you his fan, too?
I heard Congressman Choi Hyeon-jun
is coming too. Isn't that right?
It's the anniversary
of your father's death, idiot.
Just make some time
to say your prayers, okay?