(Queen In Hyun's Man)
- Oh!
- Isn't that him?
It is him!
- That's him!
- Oh!
- He's appeared again!
- It's him!
- Ugh!
- Don't you fear the gods?
My goodness!
My Lord!
Where have you been, My Lord?
Something came up.
Draw me a bath.
My Lord! There's a warrant out
for your arrest, sir!
Are you aware of that?
Isn't that blood?
Yes. I asked him if he
wanted me to call a doctor
but he refused.
What should we do?
It's Yoon Wol, My Lord.
I'm coming in.
You're ever-changing.
You barged in here even though
I hadn't answered you yet.
Weren't you struck by an arrow, My Lord?
How could you send the doctor away?
I'm mostly better now.
What do you mean, you've gotten better?
It's barely been a couple days now!
How could you possibly be better already?
First, we need to get you treated--
That world is beyond your
level of comprehension.
I am not severely wounded, so worry not.
For what reason did you return, My Lord?
I came to deeply regret not taking
your advice more to heart.
I do believe that the talisman has become
angry due to my misuse of it
so I have to make everything right now.
Please leave.
Open the gates!
We know that Kim Boong Do
is hiding out here!
Weren't you planning
to leave this place anyway?
So for what reason
did you return to the past?
You say that you'll testify, prove your
innocence, and maintain your honor
but what good is your honor?
Please, leave this place.
I may leave when the time comes,
but I must do what I must.
Can you not feel the
tension in the city?
The capital is overflowing with rumors of
the king planning to behead the queen!
Even the queen will face that sort
of fate, so surely you, My Lord...
The citizens are filled with rage.
You cannot escape this situation!
Please, leave!
Didn't you get angry last time
when I said I'd be leaving?
I was jealous.
I...
had harbored foolish
feelings in my heart.
I told you that I wished for nothing
but your happiness, My Lord.
But the truth was that I'd hoped that
you'd always remain by my side, it seems.
The officials are here, My Lord!
What are we to do?
Open the gates for them before
all of you are taken away as well.
Yes, My Lord.
My Lord!
The situation looks quite grim,
Your Highness.
There is nothing we can do now.
You must place the blame
for everything on that man.
You must tell them that young man
came to you multiple times
and dared to try and harass you
but that you firmly sent him away.
That'd be for the best.
I cannot say such a thing.
When you all left me
and were in hiding...
he was the only one who risked
his life to save me.
Saying that he tried to harass me
would be dishonorable.
Your Highness.
I cannot say the words that
you people wish to hear me utter
so do not foster any false hopes.
If the king refuses to believe me
and decides to punish me
I'd rather accept that punishment.
How could you say such a thing?
- Your Highness.
- What is it?
They say that Sir Kim of Hongmoongwan
is currently meeting with the king.
I, Kim Boong Do, have heard of your
summons just now, and have come.
Just now, eh?
My deepest apologies, Your Highness.
I was struck by arrows and
escaped, but fell unconscious
and I just awoke today.
You fell unconscious after
being struck by the arrows?
So where have you been
all this time, then?
My deepest apologies, Your Highness.
I do remember
getting struck by the arrows
but I'd already been in the captivity of
people unbeknownst to me when I'd awoke.
I risked my life to escape, and
just barely managed to get home.
So you were kidnapped, eh?
But after getting to the city
I heard people saying that I disappeared
by using some ungodly talisman.
Furthermore, I heard rumors accusing me
of doing all sorts of ludicrous things
and was quite shocked.
I swear to you, Your Highness,
that all of that was a machination
by those who had kidnapped me.
It is true that I have
a talisman with me
but it is a generic one written by
a monk to help me rest at ease.
How could something like that
possess any sort of ungodly power?
Such claims are no better
than the old wives' tales
exchanged by those who
frequent the temple.
And regarding that one
rumor circling the city
which is too loathsome
for me to even say aloud...
I believe that the only ones who'd
believe such a ludicrous rumor
are those who harbor ill will
toward the royal family.
How could such a thing ever be true?
How do you explain the
testimonies of those who claimed
to have seen you in the Queen's
chambers while she was exiled, then?
And what say you regarding the fact that
you'd also mysteriously disappeared
from your hut on Jeju
Island at that time, as well?
And furthermore, when you said that you'd
gone to your hometown, but hadn't
it was around the same time that
people claimed to have seen
someone just like you in the
Queen's private quarters!
What say you regarding that?
Is this not your attempt to confuse me
with your cunning words, once more?
That is all a part of the
traitors' plot, Your Highness!
The traitors' plot?
Are you implying that Min Am, who
is currently jailed, planned all this
and is framing you for all of this?
"A dead Zhuge scares away
a living Zhongda," eh?
But that is the truth, Your Highness.
If what you are saying is true
Min Am, who has been cut off
from the rest of the world
must immediately be sentenced to death
by dismemberment for treason!
What are all of your thoughts
regarding this matter?
I cannot trust either Min Am
or Kim Boong Do
so whose words should I trust?
Do none of you have an opinion
regarding this matter?
Shall I decide what to do, then?
Drag Min Am out from
the cells, immediately!
I'm sure that a royal decree pardoning
you will be passed in a few days.
You must have suffered quite a bit
up until now, sire.
It's not completely over yet, so we
can't rest at ease just yet.
It might as well be over, though, sir.
I'm sure the only thing that the
king is deliberating upon now
is how the queen will be executed,
based on his character.
What else will be left for
him to do after that, then?
He'll have to release her
political opponents, of course.
It's been a mere month since
she reclaimed her position.
Just a month.
Given that, this will
surely go down in history.
Come out.
What's going on?
The king has ordered you
to come to the palace.
The king wants him?
Why, all of a sudden?
The king says he wants to cross-examine
both you and Sir Kim Boong Do.
Kim Boong Do?
So that man has been captured, then?
Where?
He came to see the king
of his own accord.
I direct this question to Min Am.
Kim Boong Do stated that the incident
in which he was struck by arrows
as well as the scandalous rumors
about him and his talisman
were all a part of your plan.
Is that true?
Those are nothing but lies,
Your Highness!
In my current state,
I am completely immobilized.
So how could I have planned
all of those things?
Is that right?
I also heard while I was in jail
that he'd disappeared into thin air!
Kim Boong Do claims his disappearance
was due to your men kidnapping him.
Kidnapping?
Of course not!
I heard that he disappeared before
countless citizens' eyes!
So how could I have possibly
gotten him kidnapped?
This has nothing to do with me
in the slightest, Your Highness!
I also do believe that the
kidnapping claim is far-fetched.
It seems like nothing but a weak,
baseless excuse to me.
Your Highness!
How could you believe that a mere
talisman could hold magical powers
and yet call a kidnapping
"far-fetched?"
If you were to acknowledge
the veracity of this rumor
this land will be plagued with
superstitious rumors--
There is no need to draw this out!
Prove your innocence through your death!
Ever since five years ago,
up until what happened today
you conspired with others around you
and insulted me and expressed
contempt toward me, to no end
and tried to put me under your thumbs!
And I've become quite
disillusioned toward both of you.
Therefore, I have no intention of
siding with either one of you.
I did treasure you once, but
I won't forgive you for this incident
even if you pay the ultimate
price with your life.
And even if you are innocent
you must take responsibility
no matter what
for causing chaos among the citizens
and dishonoring the royal family's name!
Shoot arrows at Kim Boong Do!
- Your Highness!
- Your Highness.
Since we only have testimonies
and no decisive evidence
this is the only way to know the truth.
Your Highness, please calm yourself
and give this more thought.
After you've heard the opinions
of your cabinet, you can--
Your opinions be damned!
Do you think I'm unaware
of the fact that you will try
to talk me into sparing him
with your damned opinions?
I'll squander my entire life, listening
to all the opinions you all have!
What are you doing?
I told you to raise your bow!
I will promise you this
in front of everyone who is here.
If you are still struck by the arrow
and die by it while holding onto this
I will believe that everything
was a part of Min Am's plot
and I will punish him accordingly.
However, if you do disappear
you will have saved your own life
but prove that all the rumors are true
so you will never be able to
set foot in Joseon ever again.
And everyone with ties to you
will pay the price in your stead!
Give Kim Boong Do the talisman
and shoot arrows at him!
What are you doing?
Raise your bows!
What a peculiar feeling this is.
I never thought things
would end up in this way.
This surely isn't the best-
case scenario I had in mind
but I do think that this isn't
the absolute worst-case scenario.
There's no other way I'd be able to
put an end to the feud between us.
You bastard...
did you, by any chance...
Did you truly think that I would've
handed over the real talisman?
Let us die together.
The road to the afterlife won't
be lonely for either one of us
and I don't think it'll be half-bad.
Shoot him!
Raise your bows!
Yes!
Well, that can't be helped.
It's fine.
Yes, yes, yes.
See you next time, yes.
Damn it, this pisses me the hell off!
Hey, Han Dong Min's people even
canceled a photoshoot with us!
Aren't they going too far, here?
Why do they keep targeting us with work?
(Queen In Hyun's Man)
Was I...
was I deceived by that
man's schemes once more?
Bring him to my royal doctor!
What are you all doing?
- Hurry!
- Yes, sir!
Hey, I said let's go eat before we go.
You don't want to?
Can you stop the car for a second?
Why?
I don't feel too good.
What's the matter?
Do you have indigestion?
You didn't even eat anything
this morning, though.
Want me to go and buy some medicine?
- Soo Kyung.
- Yeah?
Can you look up something for me again?
- Look up something?
- I can't bear to look myself.
Sure, but look up what?
The 20th year of Sukjong's
reign in Joseon, June 5th.
This is what you want me to read for you?
"Sir Kim Boong Do, who'd concealed
himself, appeared once more--"
Huh? Kim Boong Do?
Hey, he has the same name
as that other guy!
"Sir Kim Boong Do appeared
and claimed his innocence"
"and claimed that everything was
a part of Min Am's plan."
"At this, the king claimed that Sir Kim
was trying to dishonor his court"
"and told him to be shot by arrows
to prove his innocence."
"The king called his soldiers and had
him shot by arrows in front of everyone."
"He died on the spot due to having been
struck by three arrows."
When I'd examined him, he'd
already breathed his last breath
and I couldn't save him,
Your Highness.
Thanks to you, I sentenced
my closest friend to death
and was filled with doubt once more!
Do you really think that
I will spare you after this?
- Your Highness!
You cannot do this, Your Highness!
This man must be sentenced to death!
All of you, go back to my audience hall!
- Your Highness!
"The king was filled with sorrow
and sentenced Min Am to death."
"And all those involved with him
were ordered to leave the country."
Want me to keep reading?
Hey!
Yes, Section Chief?
Oh my.
Oh, really?
Oh, I didn't know that
the time had been changed.
Oh, yes.
We'll be right there.
Yes.
Damn it, when did they
change the time?
Man, I don't think
we'll have any time to eat.
What should we do?
Want to stop by a pharmacy?
Are you really indigested?
Hey, Hee Jin!
What's wrong?
Hey! Oh my gosh!
Hey!
Whoa!
- Careful.
- Ow!
- Watch your step.
This way!
Which part hurts the most?
My leg.
- Your leg?
- Ow!
Wait, no.
My hip.
Excuse me,
where were you hurt?
What part of your body hurts?
Please tell us what
part of your body hurts.
Can you hear me?
Um, please say something.
The doctor will only be able to
diagnose you if you say something.
Why are you crying?
Where does it hurt?
Ms. Choi Hee Jin.
Ms. Choi Hee Jin?
Hey, what's wrong?
Why are you crying?
Take a good look at her to
figure out why she's in pain!
What will we do now that the last
of this family's bloodline is gone?
And what are we going to do
about the family's servants?
Aren't there other issues, as well?
Well, I'm sure that this home
will slowly fall into disrepair, too.
Your Highness.
I worry for your health.
(Queen In Hyun's Man)
Hey.
Han Dong Min!
What?
Ms. Hee Jin got into an accident.
Shouldn't you go visit her?
An accident?
Both her and Ms. Soo Kyung
have been hospitalized.
Well, how badly hurt is she?
Ms. Soo Kyung needs to keep a cast on
and needs to stay there for a month.
And Ms. Hee Jin...
doesn't seem to be too badly hurt.
But still, she's been hospitalized.
I did feel bad enough as it is, since
we canceled the photoshoot on them.
But she got into an accident
pretty much right after I called her.
I feel so bad.
Why should you feel bad about anything?
You're being so ridiculous.
Are you out of your mind?
Aren't you the crazy one, here?
You're really not going to go, even
though she got into an accident?
I'll go by myself if I have to.
If you're not going to go.
They said they're in suite 1003.
That's that way.
Oh, there's Ms. Soo Kyung.
Just look at her.
We're here, Ms. Soo Kyung.
Are you badly hurt?
Well, you know, I just--
No, no, no, no,
prop your leg back up.
Oh man.
Did you sprain it, or break it?
- It's broken, but it'll heal soon.
- Oh.
Hey.
Why are you crying?
Are you in that much pain?
Here, be careful.
Here you are.
Hey!
When did you come in here?
Oh, Hee Jin is sleeping.
Just leave her alone.
Huh?
Um, sure.
Where is she hurt, exactly?
Just here and there and everywhere.
She's fine. I'm the one
who almost died, here.
Man, I'm relieved that
you weren't more severely hurt!
Here, hurry and lie down!
Sure, sure.
- Here, here.
- Oh, yes.
Man, I'm so tired.
Why are we so busy?
Oh, damn it!
What's your problem?
Was I being too harsh to her?
Wait, no! Isn't it only natural
that I got mad?
What is it now?
Man, this is eating away at me inside.
Why is she crying like an idiot?
Ugh.
Yes, I'm getting discharged today.
Yes.
I'll call you as soon as I get home.
All right.
I'm telling you,
they're one and the same!
The actress Choi Hee Jin
was his guardian!
They do look alike...
but no way.
Hey, I was the nurse who
was in charge of him.
And I'm telling you,
he looks just like that guy!
Why doesn't she know, then?
It seemed that Choi Hee Jin
didn't know anything about this at all.
There are so many
strange things about all this.
What are you talking about?
Oh my.
I heard you two talking
about Choi Hee Jin.
So I was wondering what
you two were talking about.
Well...
What is it?
Well, that is...
The patient who was in the ICU
disappeared this morning.
And?
You know the patient who you
claimed to be the guardian for?
That man.
He looks way too similar
to him, you see.
What?
They said that he looked
just like Kim Boong Do.
And he'd been struck with arrows,
just as he'd been before
when he was admitted to the ER.
And it's not like there are many
patients who come in with arrow wounds!
Isn't it weird?
Where is that man?
They said he disappeared again.
He was on the brink of death,
and they barely saved him
but he disappeared this morning!
As if into thin air!
They said they had no idea how a person
in the ICU could walk out and leave.
They said that it was so strange!
I'll take responsibility for everything.
I can do it.
I'll definitely resolve all this
and come back.
(One Month Later)
Please come out.
The prisoners Min Am,
Moon Dae Soon, and Moon Dae Wol.
You are charged for treason and
trying to wreak havoc within the nation
as well as daring to disobey the king and
showing contempt toward the royal family.
And thus, you are
sentenced to be beheaded!
(One Month Prior)
Your Highness.
You scoundrel!
Do you have a death wish?
Did I not tell you that
you may not enter?
Yes, Your Highness.
But this arrow with a missive attached
was stuck in the front of your chambers!
What did you say?
Your Highness.
You scoundrel!
My deepest apologies, Your Highness,
for returning so late.
I did have my suspicions.
So it was true that you used magic?
Yes, it is true.
And it is also true that this
talisman saved my life.
It's also true that I was able to escape
the place where I was exiled...
and visited the Queen by using this.
You cur!
How dare you!
It is true that I used to visit her.
But the reason I visited her
was for your sake, Your Highness.
What did you say?
On that night...
the one who shot the arrow toward you
with a missive detailing the
assassination attempt against you was me.
Let's just say that you're
telling the truth now.
But do you truly believe
that I can forgive you
for showing contempt
toward the royal family?
Even if the talk regarding
the queen were all mere rumors
or the ministers had set up
a trap for you and deceived you
or the country fell into turmoil
the charges against you are
more than punishable by death!
I am fully aware that my sins
cannot ever be forgiven.
But I was fully aware
of what you wished for
and believed that everything I did was
for the sake of carrying out your will.
Therefore, I felt no remorse
toward my actions.
Isn't this what you wanted?
To reinstate the queen to her position
and punish Minister Min for his crimes?
But now, you are doubting
the queen due to false rumors.
I believed that I had to stop things
from dissolving into chaos at all costs
when we'd worked so hard to
restore order.
This is why I returned.
Really, now?
Yes, it is true that everything
that happened that night
were things that I'd
wish would happen.
And that is why I do not wish
to make all of this public
and allow those people to
regain political power once more.
However!
I must punish you
in one way or another.
How could I possibly trust someone who
deceived the royals and used magic?
That's right.
Please...
kill me, Your Highness.
What did you just say?
The situation became like this because
I evaded the death meant for me.
I feel that I must die as I was fated to
in order to restore peace and balance.
So please, kill me.
There is no other way to quell the
rumors spread by the citizens nowadays.
I must die and prove that the rumors
about the talisman are a lie.
This is the only way.
Do you truly mean that?
Yes, I do.
But in exchange, please execute
Minister Min after executing me.
That man knows about this
talisman's existence.
And we cannot be sure of what he'll do
next to arouse suspicion even after I die
as long as he remains alive.
Your Highness!
Let's go.
Are you asking me to kill you
with my own hands?
Are you using magic again?
How could you just forfeit your life
and make a request like that?
The reason I'm asking you to kill me
is so that I can live, Your Highness.
I will live.
I truly do wish to live.
So, please...
help me die with honor,
Your Highness.
If you do, I will never appear
in Joseon ever again.
My Lord!
You came here without
being seen by anyone?
But of course, sire!
But, what happened?
There is an arrest warrant out for you!
What will you do now, sire?
Remember this spot well.
If I am struck by arrows at the
palace tomorrow, and die
you must take my corpse
and bring it here as soon as possible.
What?
Your corpse?
There is a great chance that I may die,
but I do have a sliver of a chance.
So you must bring me here,
no matter what.
You must not delay.
Was I...
was I deceived by that man's
schemes once more?
What are you all doing?
Bring him to my doctor!
- Go!
- Yes, sir!
Is he dead?
He is still breathing, but he
has no chance of surviving.
Then, there would be no problem
with saying that he is dead now.
Declare that he is dead.
Pardon?
That's a royal decree!
(Emergency Clinic)
My Lord!
Oh... My Lord!
- Huh?
- Look over there!
Excuse me!
Wake up, sir!
Ow, that hurts!
Take a good look at her
and find out where she's hurting!
Hey, where does it hurt?
(Here lies Kim Boong Do of
the Cheongpoong Kim Clan)
(Level Five Scholar)
I'm here, sire.
Has everything been taken care of?
For the most part.
I cannot read,
so I didn't know what it said.
So I asked them to write it down for me.
Please read it over
to see if there are any errors.
Mak Dong said that
they'd stay in Hanyang
so I sent them over to Sir Park's home.
And the rest of them are
going to the elder's home.
Oh, and Yoon Wol
returned to the gisaeng house.
The gisaeng house?
That was the best option for her.
You weren't around,
so it'd be a bit strange
for her to follow the other
servants to another family's home.
Regarding Yoon Wol--
I'm sorry, but I told her everything.
I mean, I felt that it'd be too unfair
to keep this a secret from her, too!
So I told her that you're
actually alive!
But that she'd never be able
to see you again.
And what did she say to that?
So just know that.
You may never be able to see him again,
but at least he's still alive.
Isn't that right?
You're right.
At least he's alive.
Everything has been taken care of now.
Now that I've ensured that all of
you will be living comfortably
all I can do now is trust
my maternal uncle.
Shouldn't you be going now, as well?
Let us go.
Let us part ways here.
Just how long are you planning
to cry, when you are a man?
Will I truly never be able to
see you again, My Lord?
I am someone who has already died.
It is only right that I
disappear from this land.
My Lord!
Go on, then.
Go!
Hyah!
My Lord!
Let's go!
Hyah!
You should take your leave now, as well.
You've worked quite hard up until now.
Hyah!
My Lord!
Have you truly gone, My Lord?
If I keep meeting you, I might end up
being the one who defies death.
I may be a bit late, but...
I've come back.
Are you crying?
Why?
Who knows?
I have no idea why, but...
now that I no longer
have a place to return to...
I truly feel like I've
become orphaned.
You upset me so much that I was planning
to slap you or something when I saw you.
But I can't even say anything to you
now, since you're crying.
You really are a player.
A born player.
Why would you feel lonely?
You have me, after all.
Me! You have me!
The most beautiful woman on earth.
It's all over now, right?
Yes, it is.
It really is over, right?
Probably.
There are many terms that
I do not quite understand
and there are also many words
I've just heard for the first time.
But one term hasn't changed
throughout the years.
What?
I love you.