-=1 year later=-
I am still preparing.
You will also clear the
trash on that day, right?
Yes, yes. Call me then.
8 o'clock. Yes.
There's nothing worth taking. Not even one...
Hello?
Hey! You can't throw that tea set away.
I already threw it away.
I knew you would, that's why I called.
Don't throw it away, seriously.
Hey. I haven't seen you use it even once to drink tea.
You don't even use it...
I will use it.
I was saving it to use when we move to a
better house.
Just leave it.
Okay, I get it...
You better leave it.
I will really get angry if it's gone.
Just concentrate on your poster shoot.
I'm taking care of everything else.
Hello?
This is really...
I should be there.
Are you moving?
Yes.  It's the first time that I bought
a house, so I'm moving.
Wow, that must feel great.
You've earned quite a bit of money,
haven't you.
In the past year, I have
seen you in several commercials.
The appearance fees were pretty
minimal, so I didn't earn much.
President, you have a call.
Please wait a moment.
Director?
Miss Hui Jin, have you been well?
Yes. How about you, Director?
I've been busy. I called because
I have a favor to ask of you.
What is it?
My colleague from the educational department,
he's been pestering me to contact you
about a role.
Could you record a narration?
Narration?
He said it must be done
by you, Hui Jin.
He said that if it isn't Hui Jin,
the production won't be possible.
How can that be?
What kind of production would be impossible without me.
Thank you so much for agreeing to do this.
The director asked me as a favor,
so of course I have to do it.
But why does it have to be me?
This is the program "Untold Stories of History."
A documentary program that rediscovers
figures who were hidden in history.
I have seen it a few times.
But the name for the special this
time is "Queen In Hyeon's Man."
Queen In Hyeon's Man?
But what does Queen In Hyeon's Man mean?
Do you know about the unofficial historical
rumor that Queen In Hyeon had a lover?
Really? The drama I acted in didn't
mention anything about that.
It was probably left out because it was
such a minor episode.
There was only a very short record of
it in the Chronicles.
But last month, some very interesting
evidence was discovered.
I wanted to do a good job
with it this time. So I am
counting on you.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Aren't we late?
I already called to say that we'll be
30 minutes late.
Queen In Hyeon's Man...
If you look at the Chronicles of
1694, Suk Jong's 20th year, the 5th month,
there is an interesting passage.
It's about the Officer of Special Advisers Administrator
at that time, Gim Bung Do of the West Faction.
There was a rumor that he frequently visited Queen
In Hyeon's private residence while she was exiled.
This rumor circulated among the people.
Gim Bung Do?
This is my first time hearing this.
It wasn't in the script.
Gim Bung Do...
So tiring. I'm going to die.
You're back.
Hey, what was that earlier? What is this
documentary narration? Did you meet
the director?
I am looking at the notes now.
Why did you agree?
It's just wasting time.
I think it'll be interesting.
The title is "Queen In Hyeon's Man".
Not Lady Jang's man. Isn't it unique?
Queen In Hyeon's Man?
Isn't Queen In Hyeon's man Suk Jong?
No. Listen.
At that time, the Second Minister of the Board
of Personnel had a son, called Gim Bung Do.
This man is Queen In Hyeon's man.
The rumor was that when Queen In Hyeon
was deposed and living outside of the palace,
she and this man were lovers.
This rumor reached Suk Jong's ears.
Really?
It's true.
So, when Suk Jong brought Gim Bung Do
in for interrogation,
he died.
But it was discovered that
that wasn't the truth.
He was wronged.
The conclusion was that he died an undeserved
death because of baseless rumors. That was
the end of the story in the Chronicles.
I see.
But this documentary is about what
happened after that.
It gets interesting from here onwards.
It was clearly recorded in the Chronicles
that this man had died.
But now it has been discovered that there
were records of him alive after that.
Not long ago.
The descendants of Nam Gu Man, a prime
minister at that time,
revealed a memorandum last month
that was written by the Minister.
In the memorandum, there was a record
of Nam Gu Man's sighting of the still-living
Gim Bung Do.
What are you saying?
Nam Gu Man went on an inspection of the
border region and happened to see him.
The Gim Bung Do who was thought to be dead.
That was one year after Gim Bung Do was
recorded as dead in the Chronicles.
It seems that everybody is tired. Take a rest first.
-=The year 1695, the 5th month,
Pyeongan Province, Euiju=-
The food isn't good here.
-=The year 1695, the 5th month,
Pyeongan Province, Euiju=-
The food isn't good here.
It doesn't matter. Let's go somewhere nearby.
-=Prime Minister Nam Gu Man=-
Yes.
Please go inside.
No need. It's refreshing here.
Is there something I can use to wash my hands?
I'll bring it for you.
Where is it?
Aigoo, are you all right?
(Aigoo - oh dear, oh my god)
Wait.
Wait a minute.
You look like someone I know.
Hey, that--
Did something happen?
What is going on? I saw a dead man.
What?
Chase the man who ran away just now.
Find out who he is.
Yes.
A man who is tall and has short hair.
Ah, he's in this room.
But it seemed like he's about to leave.
Look here, do you realize that the person
you just bumped into was the Prime Minister?
His Excellency wants to see you.
You have to come with us.
Catch him! Catch him!
When I said he had to leave with us,
he ran away without saying anything.
Only this was left in the room.
This is not a book that can be read by commoners.
This handwriting is clearly Administrator Gim's.
What on earth is going on?
Where should we go?
Where do you want to go?
This way?
Okay, let's go and see.
The people are living safely. The military
personnel discipline is also very strict.
Is there anything else?
There was a strange incident.
A strange incident?
In Euiju, I happened to see a person who
looked exactly like Administrator Gim.
Not only did his appearance and figure look
the same, his handwriting and writing style
were also very similar.
So much so that I had the illusion that
the Administrator was still alive.
I wanted to detain him in order to question
him properly, but he disappeared.
Did the Administrator look like he had
been suffering?
What? Your Majesty.
I owe Bung Do a debt.
Your Majesty. Do Seung Ji has arrived.
Let him in.
Refrain from saying that you've seen someone
who looks like him. He's already a dead man.
Yes. Certainly.
I have no way of knowing what happened
between the King and Gim Bung Do.
But I am certain that he's alive,
and in order not to be caught,
he is traveling around the border regions.
Because I know that the Administrator's sacrifice
was necessary for the stability of the Royal Court,
my heart hurts to think of his difficult life.
However, to us,
his existence must forever remain a secret.
Aren't you going to sleep? Is it that interesting?
I feel sorry for this person.
What?
Gim Bung Do. Suk Jong didn't kill him
but chased him to the borders.
It wasn't an affair, but instead a one sided love.
I mean, a man from a prominent family,
who received the top score in the civil
examination at the age of 19,
and was highly respected by Suk Jong,
how did he end up in love with the Queen?
His life was totally ruined because of a woman.
Thank you.
I think I've seen him somewhere before.
Where? Looks like he's not from here.
I've definitely seen him somewhere.
Wait a minute.
Aren't you the person from before?
The person who came from Hanyang last year,
looking for the great master of Hyeonam Temple?
What brings you here? Seeing as you're
being hunted.
I had thought that the Eight Provinces
of Joseon were fairly large,
but they aren't.
Having traveled for a year, I've passed
by the same places many times.
Until when are you going to keep running away?
Aren't you tired?
I am tired. But although it's laughable,
this has become the reason I'm living for.
Being hunted is not a bad thing.
If I didn't even have the goal of running away,
I don't know how would I have lived each day.
If you have committed a crime,
wouldn't it be better to pay the price of the crime?
I want to do that too.
But to be caught and to pay the price would
be an even greater crime.
What do you mean?
I think I have stayed here too long.
I don't want to bring trouble to the temple.
Over there!
Don't say that you know me.
We have orders to arrest this man on charges
of murder. Come without making a fuss.
- Tie him up.
- Yes.
Start.
Last month, a memorandum by Prime Minister
Nam Gu Man was revealed.
His memorandum included a detailed report
of his unexpected meeting with Gim Bung Do
and his conversation with King Suk Jong.
A letter written by Gim Bung Do, which
was revealed along with the memorandum,
is also drawing attention.
The letter was written one month after
it was recorded in the Chronicles that
he died in the 6th month of the year 1694.
In it, his deep affection towards a nameless person
and the sadness of their parting is evident.
Considering the circumstances at the time,
scholars speculate that the letter was intended
for Queen In Hyeon.
Start.
This is a letter that's written both
to you and to me at the same time.
I might forget that I had ever written this letter...
Or even this letter itself might disappear.
For me or for you, this letter is written for
whoever may live holding on to the memories.
If I have a final wish, it is to remember you.
In a life without aims, to not even have those
memories
would be hell.
And you... Even if you should happen to read this letter
someday far in the future,
I pray that you will not be able to realize whom it is for.
Start.
A man who wanted his love to forget him.
It was probably because she was beyond his reach.
As for the man, was he able to
keep his memories?
It seems that he at least did not forget.
The woman is mentioned a few times in other
documents that were found with the letter.
Okay!
The first part is done. You've all worked hard.
Aigoo, I think I need a drink. As I get older,
it seems like having a drink does me good.
You've worked hard.
Miss Hui Jin.
You came already.
What's up?
For you.
You're doing all sorts of things nowadays.
Even a documentary.
It's because Director Yang asked for a favor.
I thought I saw reports that you were
filming overseas. When did you come back?
Did you miss me?
You must have missed me to search for news about me.
I don't want to say this because you'll
just act superior,
but news about you is all over the internet.
It's impossible not to see it.
It's not acting superior. I am superior.
Only you call it acting.
Why are you here?
You're not dating anyone recently, right?
I'm so lonely I could die.
Shall we start dating again?
Do you want to work till you die?
What is the use of earning so much money?
I'm lonely and you're lonely too.
I heard you are dating someone in a girl group.
And she's younger than you by 10 years.
It's been in the news.
She's too immature. She's always chattering
and giggling.
No matter how much I look and think about it,
there is no other woman like Choe Hui Jin.
Do I look that easy?
How about a drink tonight?
Don't keep asking me. There, how about
that person over there?
I think the two of you are perfect for each other.
Na Jeong?
Hey, Na Jeong!
What are you doing?
Do you want to date me?
She said we are perfect for each other.
What do you think?
I'm not very happy about it,
but if you are willing...
I'll do you a favor and date you.
Because I'm too lonely now, I can't afford to be picky.
You're crazy.
You see. She won't do. She's impossible.
When will you grow up?
I don't want to grow up.
What are you doing here again?
Miss Hui Jin.
Hi.
Hurry up, you're out of time.
Button your shirt properly.
I'll call you tomorrow.
I'm very busy.
Wait for me. Are you ready? I'm ready.
Bye!
See you.
Excuse me, Miss Hui Jin.
What is Miss Su Gyeong up to recently?
What are you talking about?
Is she seeing anyone?
Why are you asking?
Because I'm lonely these days.
There isn't anyone, right?
Even though she hasn't said anything,
it seems like there is someone.
Ah, is that so? I see.
You've got to be kidding me.
If he can't sleep at night then he should
just take a sleeping pill.
Why come after me? How can those two be
so alike?
- We're too soft-natured.
- My thoughts are exactly.
Do they think we're toys for them to pass
the time with? Seriously.
That's what I'm saying.
Really...
This old ajussi is setting his sights pretty high. Aigoo.
(Ajussi - older man)
So what did you say?
I said that you're seemed to have a boyfriend.
When did I have a boyfriend?
I had to do that so that he would give up.
Otherwise he'd keep bothering you.
Well...
What? Did I say something wrong?
No. You did well.
This girl is no help to my life.
We're going to be late, please go faster.
That's why I said not to film the documentary!
It's only a few lines of narration,
so why are they going to the extent
of filming it outdoors?
Just 5 minutes would be enough.
Just because you agreed to do it, they're
trying to milk you for everything they can,
is that it?
Miss Hui Jin, start from here.
The battle between the South and West Factions.
The conflicting fates of Queen In Hyeon
and Jang Ok Jeong.
Announce it like this while walking straight ahead.
And then stop right at the marker for the 5th level
officials and stand there while continuing the commentary.
Okay.
Good.
It's been so long since I've been here.
Pardon?
I came here almost everyday when I was filming
the drama, but now it's been a year since I came.
I guess that's right.
Wait here for a moment.
Yes.
What are you looking at?
I haven't been here for quite a while.
What? You must be joking.
As though you could have been to the palace
before. Who would believe such nonsense.
- Okay, shall we get started?
- Yes.
Cue.
The battle between the South and West Factions.
The conflicting fates of Queen In Hyeon
and Jang Ok Jeong.
This story has been dramatized countless times
on television. It is the familiar tale of a time
when political power changed hands.
In the year 1694, a battle in political affairs
led to much bloodshed.
In the midst of that affair, there was
a man who left an interesting record.
Caught up in allegations of a love affair with
Queen In Hyeon,
this man proved his innocence through
his death in front of King Suk Jong.
He was 27 years of age at the time.
An Office of Special Advisers Administrator
from the West Faction called Gim Bung Do.
He is today's lead character, Queen In Hyeon's Man.
Was he really in love with the Queen?
Or was he falsely accused as written in the Chronicles?
The son of a prominent family, at the
age of 19 he was a top student in the
civil examination.
He was once highly respected by King Suk Jong.
However, it was recorded that he died because
of his love for the Queen.
In this documentary, we will reveal
the story of his short life.
Cut. What's the matter?
Why...
Is there a problem?
Let's go. They said the interrogation will
be tomorrow.
Miss Hui Jin. Miss Hui Jin, are you okay?
It seems like something went into my eyes.
I apologize.
Sorry, I'll do it again.
Oh, I thought...
Okay, let's start again then.
-=Royal Investigation Bureau=-
The interrogation will begin early in the morning.
Who will be questioning me?
Because the charges are so heinous,
head investigator Yun Seong Mun said
he will interrogate you personally.
Yun Seong Mun.
We drew it according to the information
you gave us. However, it did not seem
like the same man.
My asking you to grant my death,
Your Majesty, is so that I can live.
I will live on. I really want to live.
That's why I'm begging Your Majesty
to let me die with honor.
In the future, I will not
appear in this world again.
I will not appear in this world again.
Hello?
Hey, I heard you cried during filming.
Who said that?
That PD called and asked if you were sick.
I'm not sick.
But why did you cry? I heard that you
cried very sadly.
I don't know why, either.
What do you mean, you don't know?
I don't know. Tears started falling suddenly
and couldn't stop, so I was confused too.
I suddenly felt really sad, without any reason.
What is this? Did you drink?
What is so sad?
I'm not in a good mood.
Why?
=I said I don't know. I'm just not feeling good.=
Is there any beer at home?
I think I need to have a drink.
Come back quickly.
Okay, I'll be back very soon.
In the old days, usually the wife would tie this for
her husband when he was leaving for work.
So, he would stand like this, and every morning
his wife would tie it for him.
As it was being tied, their eyes would meet
and a feeling would grow.
Then. This.
This is called the purpose of a tie.
The purpose of the tie.
Why is it raining so frequently?
What's wrong? What is this? What is this?
What is this, seriously.
Why am I like this?
Player? What player?
Who is the player?
You're a player over there too, right?
Good. Mr Player calls The Most Beautiful Woman in the World.
I will come back after settling everything.
Miss Hui Jin.
Why are you here this late at night?
Why do you look so drenched?
Footage...
What did you say?
Please let me have a look at the footage, the one called Queen In Hyeon's man.
This would be a better place if you're watching it alone.
Here.
Did something happen?
Because it's not edited yet, it's still a little bit messy.
First, if you want to stop, do this.
If you want to fast forward, do this.
If you have any questions, just ask.
The battle between the South and West Factions.
The conflicting fates of Queen In Hyeon and Jang Ok Jeong.
This story has been dramatized countless times on television.
It is the familiar tale of a time
when political power changed hands.
In the year 1694, a battle in political affairs led to much bloodshed.
In the midst of that affair, there was a man who left an interesting record.
Caught up in allegations of a love affair with Queen In Hyeon,
this man proved his innocence through his death in front of Suk Jong.
He was 27 years of age at the time. An Office of Special Advisers Administrator from the West Faction called Gim Bung Do.
He is today's lead character, Queen In Hyeon's Man.
A letter written by Gim Bung Do, which was revealed along with the memorandum,
is also drawing attention.
he died in the 6th month of the year 1694.
The letter was written one month after
it was recorded in the Chronicles.
In it, his deep affection towards a nameless person and the sadness of their parting is evident.
Considering the circumstances at the time,
scholars speculate that the letter was intended
for Queen In Hyeon.
This is a letter that's written both to you and to me at the same time.
I might forget that I had written this letter...
Or even this letter itself might disappear.
For me or for you,
this letter is written for whoever may live holding on to the memories.
When I first happened to come into
possession of this talisman,
I was very curious about
its cause and effect.
At first, I thought that the
realization of my dream
was the effect.
Shortly after, I thought
meeting you was its effect.
Then afterwards, I thought
that beginning a new life
in another world was the effect.
But it's only now
that I came to realize its effects.
If the cause was me surviving,
then me losing everything
was the effect.
My future. My honour. My values.
My people. And you, too.
I do not know what will happen now.
Will we forget each other,
or will we live unable to forget, forever in agony?
If I have a final wish...it is to remember you.
In a life without aims, to not even have those memories would be hell.
And you... as for you...
Even if you should happen to read this letter someday far in the future,
I pray that you will not be able to realize whom it is for.
A man who wanted his love to forget him.
It was probably because she was beyond his reach.
As for the man, was he able to
keep his memories?
It seems that he at least did not forget.
The woman is mentioned a few times in other
documents that were found with the letter.
I'm sorry. Just a moment.
Why didn't you answer the phone after calling me?
I had to search for you for so long.
Didn't you call me?
1 hour ago.
Hello?
Hello.
Are you listening?
Hello?
Answer me please, the world's most beautiful woman.
Are you going to carry on staring like that?
If you called a person who's eating and sleeping well,
shouldn't you take responsibility?
Close the door.
Come... over here.
You're real.
You're still alive.
How have you been for the past year?
I travelled around and left a lover in every province.
And realised that the year passed by quite quickly.
You really know how to lie.
The evidence is all here.
What's that?
What exactly happened?
The talisman.
The talisman was burnt.
Then how did you come here?
I came back because you called me.
Me?
You.
The use of the tie,
I missed its purpose when you taught me.
I almost used it for other purposes.
You missed the purpose of the tie?
So much that I could die from missing it.
Do you mean this?
Our fateful meeting occured through a gap of time.
And this fateful meeting was already ended a year ago.
Our reunion now is not because of that talisman.
But because of the link in our memories.
Our second meeting is destined by fate.
Now, I am his life-saver.
His price to pay is that he must remain by my side for a lifetime.
How does my letter exist until now?
How did this happen?
The Prime Minister and his descendants prossessions were discovered not long ago.
How can personal items be
exhibited so openly?
Looks like I have to destroy it.
It's in the museum.
That will never be destroyed,
unless the museum is also destroyed.
That's unreasonable.
I find it's really ridiculous now.
Claiming that you are her boyfriend
out of nowhere.
I have never heard Hui Jin
mention anything about you even once.
Starting now, tell the truth.
You hear me?
What school do you attend?
Where do you study, the school you attend.
Sungkyunkwan.
Sungkyunkwan University?
Where do you live?
Bukchon.
Bukchon?
The houses there are extremely expensive.
By chance, is it a tile-roofed house?
Why are you laughing?
My parents have passed away.
I am living by myself.
I am depending on the inheritance that
my parents left me.
Oh my god. Perfect conditions.
Perfect man.
My father was a politician.
Politician?