～
good morning. Ah Yukiya Good morning.
thank you. That's amazing.
Did you know that a new bakery has been opened in front of the station?
It's been featured in a lot of places though.
Wow. (Entrance chime)
Yes.
sorry. This is an authentic coffee sekke.
i am coming.
He seems busy lately, but are you sleeping properly?
Yes, right... There's no breaks.
Don't overdo it.
thank you.
Well, I have to work hard until the press conference on the 1st.
A day...
I know. There's no way I'll forget it.
What's the best present? Is it decided?
Hmm, yes.
But what about it? Huh?
No, from the brand that we made rings together
New designs have been released. Yeah.
It's a different atmosphere
I was thinking it would be nice if I could change it to suit my clothes.
ring? It's totally fine.
Well, I didn't think this guy's lifespan was one year though.
No, no, I wasn't saying that.
Use both!
10 more days? I'm looking forward to it.
From Ise Masayuki
Here is an explanation of the new business.
Um, the press conference is finally coming 10 days later.
We, the Ise Group, will celebrate its 150th anniversary next year.
We are the first private company to launch Japan's space travel service.
This project is definitely
It will attract attention from all over the world.
Four!
(applause)
Well, then on this project
We will explain the business contents of each company.
Good luck.
Ugh ugh ugh.
Wow, what! Was you there too?
ah. I brought it to you today because I had a little load.
Hey, don't drop it?
That's heavier than your life.
That's wrong.
(laughter)
Ah, dad.
"They are my family."
{Chairman of the Ise Group, one of Japan's leading companies
Ise Seiichiro is my father
《At the core of the Ise Group
Ise Masayuki, the president of Ise Bussan, is his older brother...
"He serves as president of iSE InterFashion Co., Ltd.
Ise Satoshi is a cousin
{And I'll protect the Ise group.
I work for them
"That's because it's a pretext..."
Seiichiro: Let him clean up the butt.
(Satoshi) He is destined to live behind the scenes for the rest of his life.
(Masayuki) I think the sweeping suits me
Oh, it's rare.
mother….
what happened? I mean to go home.
Don't take your computer out of the house until the press conference is over.
My brother. Ah, that's right.
Well then. Wait a minute.
Hmm...
He probably called out because he had something to do.
Just now, he's a former employee of iSE InterFashion.
An anonymous account posted a complaint.
Huh? Huh? It's not.
Delete it quickly.
Even when it comes to big things, I don't know, pay thief.
yes.
"I am due to the power harassment of Ise Satoshi, president of iSE InterFashion.
I've become depressed.
The company's response after that was the worst, and instead of guaranteed, I was fired.
Please help.
Please contact me if anyone is in the same situation as me."
(knock)
Thank you for your hard work, why not give tea?
Hanaho. Good luck.
Sorry, did you get in the way? Ah, no, sorry always.
It's fine, it's just boring.
Have you been busy lately?
Masayuki is exhausted every day, even though there will be a press conference soon.
That's right. I've been hit hard again recently.
What a sorry thing.
Ah, no, sorry, I said something unnecessary.
Is Hanaho okay?
Huh?
I thought something had been said again. Ah...
That's amazing, Yukiya-kun.
Well... But there's nothing I can do about it.
I can't... it's my fault.
That's not the case.
Please stop thinking like that.
Yukiya is kind.
If the press conference is over successfully
I think Masayuki will listen to his story seriously too.
Thank you very much.
Don't hold Yukiya too much into it.
It's not good to think about doing something on your own.
Tell me anything.
Yeah.
Are you okay? Are you not injured?
sorry! No, not at all.
Clothes...
It's fine, it'll come off if you wash it.
I didn't cry, great.
Sorry, thank you very much.
home.
Sorry to my brother?
sorry.
Yes, I'm glad I wasn't injured.
So, excuse me.
bye bye. bye bye.
(Kuna) Well, mom. (Kotoko) Yes.
I learned a new song. What! Let me listen and let me listen!
"Sparkling glittering"
(Two people) "I want you to have a sparkly glittering or something."
"Blink and look at everyone."
"Sparkling, you're not..."
Sorry.
Uuuuh, it's like Yukiya.
If you put it on overnight it will fall off.
thank you. Yes.
It's a bit... difficult to do.
Because I'm doing this now.
sorry. That's fine.
no…. yeah?
Please leave this like this until tomorrow.
Take a leisurely bath.
I'm sleeping first, good night.
good night.
～
Welcome to visit.
Boy Good morning. good morning.
thank you.
(knock)
please.
a….
Thank you for your hard work. thank you.
What about Hanaho today?
I went for a consultation. Ah...
So, um... It's just one more week.
Don't think you're going to stop it.
I've endured it for this day. It's the perfect time.
Fuyu-san.
The sweeping process has accumulated enough information to rot.
I'll definitely make it a success.
Is it really reborn?
Are you okay.
No matter what, you'll succeed.
Yuki-nii! Oh.
(Everyone) Yuki-nii! long time no see.
long time no see! What were you doing today?
Today we all jumped rope together. You jumped 20 times isn't it?
That's amazing. That's amazing. You Sakura
I've now been able to say 8th. Oh that much?
Hey, let's play quickly. Play! I'll play, okay?
Look at the train! Okay, let's play together.
Hey, let's draw!
It's tasty.
Are there any things you don't like? Yes... I guess it's in this one.
that…. yes.
Sorry all of a sudden, can you take a photo?
picture? Yes of course.
thank you.
It's kind of good, it reminds me of it.
I got rice!
Look, there's Kato's pork soup too. It's hot, take care.
How many do you eat? Me, eat both
Hey, hey.
Refill.
A secondhand? Was it tasty? It was delicious. Okay.
I also have a secondhand. Maybe I can go for about 100 more drinks...
Can you get 100 drinks? I have 1,000 drinks.
Today's fried chicken is super tasty.
delicious? Chikuzenni is the best...
If anyone else wants it, tell me. So I want it.
I went.
Yeah. I've been left to the point recently.
If it calms down next week
I feel like I can go again though.
what happened?
Ugh, I think Yukiya is amazing.
I can't do it. Huh?
No, that's it.
I feel like I want to prioritize my own life.
I just want to do it myself too.
Hmm.
Before I knew it, I wanted to be happy one day
Have you ever talked to me?
Yeah.
I don't know what happened to Erika in the past.
If you don't want to talk, you don't have to talk.
But it's the same for me too, right?
I want to be happy one day.
After finishing everything, we'll have two of us...
I agree.
Yeah.
That's right, it's my life.
I hope I'm happy.
of course.
thank you.
Yukiya is really kind.
I think so. That's right.
If that's the case, it's mother's blood.
(Hanaho) You'll come in the bath. Yeah.
That Masayuki.
Huh?
I'm today, that... on the scheduled date
If you like, I hope you get up.
please.
There are a few things being said, and I'm at my limit.
You know what I'm in now?
What...
I'm tired.
I'm doing everything about the space business.
You should know, though? That's what the president's wife does.
Ah...
If you can't rest at home, where should you go.
It's almost here, Mom.
(Masayuki) There's only 6 days left until the press conference.
Apparently they've also received requests for interviews from the New York Times and Reuters.
Ah.
If this business succeeds
The Ise Zaibatsu is one of the world's top class.
I guess so.
(Coughing voice)
Are you okay? It's nothing big.
I guess it's better to have surgery after all.
What will you do in the meantime?
That's what I did... Don't worry.
My regret is that there is no heir.
I asked.
It's okay. I don't want to worry about my dad.
～
(English)
Everyone, what are your plans for the future?
There's a French restaurant I want to take with me.
Are you going? please….
Everyone, are you going?
Which clothes are you using for the next poster?
It will be here. Ah?
No, I can move this one, I can't see it!
Yes, I'm sorry. I can't use it.
～
Acquisition? Yeah.
There's a big company called the Ise Group.
He ended up protecting his mother's factory.
Hmm, you're so kind.
Yukiya... Yeah?
Instead
My mother has to leave this factory.
why? Isn't this your mother's factory?
Hmm...
It might be a bit difficult for Yukiya though.
There's no choice.
To protect this factory with everyone who worked here.
So what will happen to your mother?
That's right, what should I do?
It's okay, it'll be fine.
If Yukiya looks like that
Even my mother would almost cry.
It's okay, isn't it.
Ah, no, I'll go... Mom!
dangerous! Because it's dangerous! Mom! Mom!
Go back! Go back! Mom!
It's dangerous, it's dangerous... Mom!
It's no good! Mom!
Don't go, it's no good... Mom!
Mom! It's no good!
Mom Mom... That's no good...
He is the child of the former president of Matsushima Electric.
I had to take him in because I had no relatives.
Wait, what about mom?
Give me back my mom.
Take care! Who are you talking to? ?
Your mother is
He was using his master for money.
For years, many years!
Who are you thinking about without knowing your position? ?
It's your mother who's the wrong person!
A terrible woman.
Are you going to do anything for money?
It's an accident that you were born into this world.
accident!
Hey, accident, accident...
Damn it! You
"This is evidence of the numerous fraudulent transactions that the Ise Group has been carrying out so far.
I have endured this for a long time.
Although it is called a sweeping
I've worked for them
"Tomorrow will finish everything"
Then there were two of us...
(The sound of the cup cracking)
(Vibrator sound)
hello.
Hanaho! Excuse me.
Why, why, how come this...
Brother. Brother, where is it?
Erika.
Erika... Yukiya.
Um, me...
I'm pregnant.
A child with Masayuki.
I know that it's a bad thing.
But I'm sorry.
This was the only way to make me happy.
I... I'm a really terrible person.
I couldn't contain my feelings, so I also did Yukiya's.
I've also hurt my sister.
But that's why I never thought I would do something like this.
I want to point it out.
sorry.
Sorry, what have you been saying for a while now?
picture?
I have no idea at all though.
yes? It's still the words though.
I only ask for one thing.
Separate from me.
Please divorce me.
What does that mean?
If you don't break up, I'll tell your dad.
What you're plotting.
(footsteps)
Everything was erased.
There's no way you could destroy the Ise family, right?
My Ise family.
Shut up and disappear.
For my happy life.
Dad.
～
"I will never forgive you.
No matter how many years I'll take, I'll get revenge.