You kid
You are so outrageous.
Is this how you treat your family business?
ah
I built the Duck Herding Industry with my own hard work.
Isn't it possible that today it will be destroyed in your hands?
Dad, you don't seem to understand whether it is me who is not serious about the company or you who are not serious about the company.
The City of Time project was originally built by me.
Now you have to give it to me
Isn't it normal that I can't do it well?
OK
You are right if you don't work hard, right?
You know how much I've spent on you?
You, you go to the crew right now and apologize to Director Liang
I dont go
Dad, you always say it's for my own good and for the good of the family.
For the good of the entire company
But when have you ever considered how my brother and I really feel?
I didn’t want to go abroad before.
You have to force me to go
Now I don't want to come back but you force me to come back
I don't care anyway
I must return the title of producer of City of Time to my brother.
hey
Hey, nephew, look, I have completed the transfer procedures for Uncle Xue.
Isn't it said that it's very difficult to get into Cixin Hospital?
And the attending doctor was changed to the famous Dr. Zhang.
What's so strange about this?
My dad is just lucky.
Maybe the hospital took into consideration that my father is a scientific research elite.
I gave you special treatment.
How can it be as simple as you say?
But it's a good thing that Uncle Xue can find Doctor Zhang.
Let's go talk to Dr. Zhang.
The situation is probably like this
We can only do our best
But anyway
Keeping the patient in a good mood will be of great help to the treatment
I hope you can cooperate more in your daily life.
Dr. Zhang, thank you for your concern.
We will pay more attention in the future.
There's nothing else.
Remember to spend more time with him
eat medicine on time
Thank you, Dr. Zhang
We're leaving first.
You're welcome, Dr. Xie
Hey Town
Do you know who is responsible for Uncle Xu's good fortune this time?
Didn't you just say you didn't know?
How come this is in your hand, Sister Rui?
I just saw this on Dr. Zhang's desk.
I secretly took a photo of it
Look at Ji Xiaorui
Assistant Director of City of Time
Isn't your mother the director of Time City?
Well, it seems your mother is not as cold as she seems.
If it's really him
I feel better about Liang Wan.
Xiaorui, turn right at the next intersection
I want to go somewhere first
Aren't you going home?
Not going back yet
I want to see someone good.
Dad, if the doctor gives you an injection
If you're scared, just hold my hand.
The disease will be cured after the injection
Qiao Rui, let's go back.
Director Liang, the person you said you wanted to see is Professor Xu Zhengyao?
Why don't you go down and take a look?
forget it
Some things are over.
It seems like what can happen
Let's go, yeah
What happened to my daughter?
No dad
ah
Your mother arranged this transfer for you.
I think he still thinks about us.
Our family will be reunited soon.
Dad, are you very happy now?
Your mother
He has his own ideas
After all, he has been gone from our lives for so many years.
You can't force anything.
This is how I love you, Mom.
That's the way you love me, haha.
Oh, by the way, Xiao Chen
The mining site we visited last time
It has been proven that it is indeed a group of dinosaur fossils.
My colleagues who work with me have already rushed over.
I want to go see it, too.
Ah, Dad, how can it be such a coincidence?
It happens to be a rare fossil group.
Those uncles are all paleontologists
The slightest movement makes me excited.
Hahahaha, this news report has already confirmed it, take a look
Dad, how can this be possible?
Your current physical condition does not allow you to travel back and forth
You must be well taken care of in the hospital.
I won't agree
My daughter, although none of you told me
But I know my own physical condition very well.
My father started to learn about paleontology when he was 18 years old and chose his major in college.
It's been almost 30 years
This is my life's work
I look upon him
Much more important than looking at my life
No one should go and see me one last time to say goodbye
I really can't reconcile myself.
I can die at dusk if I hear the truth in the morning.
I hope you can support Dad's last wish.
If you don't agree
Dad will also contact your brothers and sisters in school
Let them take me there.
I think this scene needs some rethinking.
Do you think there is something wrong with my performance?
Anyway, it's not the same as the archaeologist I imagined.
What's wrong?
Xiaojunjun
Ko Toshun
Xiaojunjun, what's wrong with you?
ah
Don't worry, it's okay.
I probably had a stomachache during the day.
I've been giving him injections all night.
Let him drink plenty of water after returning home in the next two days
Don't eat meat. Don't give him any dairy products in the last two days.
There shouldn't be any problem.
Thanks
Xiao Juanjuan is so good
Sister will take you home now
Hey, what happened to him?
are you sick
This kitten's mother just fell ill and passed away
Since his mother passed away
He became unhappy and refused to eat or drink.
Director Liang
You go
Meet Daddy
Although
I don't know why you broke up.
But I know that daddy has never forgotten you
Dad has stomach cancer.
There aren't many days left.
I beg you
Just go meet him.
mom
Your father's situation
Isn't that good?
I think
I'm just like that kitten
Nothing can be done
Xu Zhen
I understand your feelings.
Your father is sick.
The pain he endured
It should hurt more than all of you.
You are an adult
If you can't change him
Then you just have to accept him.
If you act sad
I'm sure your father will be even sadder.
So in the days to come
Spend time with him
Let him spend the rest of his days
Can be better
Your dad is a paleontologist, right?
he
Do you want to go to this place?
yes
but
The road is bumpy
His current physical condition is like this
So I'm worried
You don't have to worry about this
Leave the problems on the road to me.
I play a paleontologist.
It just so happens that your father is also a paleontologist
He wants to go to the painter's site
I also want to go to the painter's site
If you can go to the painter's mining site
It is a learning and improvement for me.
And with an expert like your dad by your side
What a rare opportunity!
How could I not catch it?
Did you fix the model for me that day?
oh
I'm just helping out.
I don't want others to think that my handling is stupid.
Thanks
Hey boss
You called me early in the morning
I am your agent
Not your assistant
I really don't understand why you would sacrifice an agent to help your assistant.
Xu Zhen's father is the country's top paleontologist
Where's your dad?
I need to get in touch with the best experts in the country
Come find the feeling of a banquet
Can you give it to me
Hahahaha
There have been some delays today.
The trailer must be completed within this week
Well, you can discuss it with the coordinator.
Ask him to send another notice.
Good leadership
Why
Mr. Lin, um, Mr. Lin, Mr. Lin
Wanting, I know everything that happened yesterday.
I'm so sorry.
Xiao Xiu is a very careless child.
I didn't expect to cause so much trouble to the crew.
I'll take him to apologize to you and the crew.
Hey, you don't have to do this.
Sit down and talk first. Okay, let's talk slowly.
Why
Wanting, Xiaoqiu, this kid just graduated and has no work experience.
There are many things that I can't handle well.
It's also my fault that I didn't set high standards for him.
How about this? I'll send another experienced person to the crew as executive producer.
What happened today?
Just for my sake
Don't bother with Xiaoxiu.
Sister
Understand
Good Chairman
I'll arrange it right away
Is it true that I can't ask any questions?
Can't ask
I won't ask about emotional issues.
I just want to ask him what hobbies or characteristics he has. Is that not okay?
Can not be done
Well, I'll go there with you later.
No, no, absolutely not.
You are a gossip reporter. Who knows what gossip you can dig out when your professional traits kick in?
This time, Mr. Gu is willing to take the initiative to take my father to investigate the scene.
We must not let him down.
You are not allowed to ask any personal questions when he comes, okay?
Yeah, ok, ok, ok
Revolutionary sentiment is above all else.
Do not worry
Just based on our friendship
I will never betray your boss Gu
Even though I secretly took photos
Before posting, I must give him a pair of 2.8-meter-long legs.
Even if you wear it as a 2.8 meter long leg, it won't work
Oh well, they are here.
Hey hey hey
I just take pictures
No taking photos!
hurry up
Can't shoot this, can't shoot this
Go back
Bye bye
Dad, they are here.
This is my father. This is Uncle Gu Chijun. Hello.
Let's get in the car, okay?
Hey Xu Zhan um hey
Who was that person just now?
It's a friend of mine.
Jinxiu did something wrong.
As a brother, you should help him more.
Dad, I will.
I will find an experienced producer team to do this.
besides
Last time my name was Liu Weicheng
Find that Li Qianer
So far, I haven't seen anyone.
It's my words that don't work
Is there some engine in here?
Li Qianer may feel malicious slander
I don't have the face to see you
But don't worry
I'll go find someone else to look for him.
A series of things happened
There is nothing that reassures me.
I don't know what you're doing
In addition to wanting to inherit dry raising
How to kick me out of the position of chairman?
In addition to this
You didn't think about anything, Dad.
Over the years
I have always regarded running a business well as the most important thing in life.
There was no slackness for a single second.
There is no selfishness
But I didn't know until today
No matter how hard I try
No matter how hard I work
I can't get any praise from you
In your eyes
Only blame and grievance
But have you ever thought about
You're doing this to my son.
Is it really fair?
right
It's really unfair
You've worked so hard over the years.
I never let you rest.
Well, start from today
Find a place to take a vacation.
I will find someone to take over your job.
As we said,
Execute it
Editor-in-Chief Liu
Didn't you already promise me?
Said he wanted to report about me and Gaia
Why do you suddenly regret it?
Everything I posted on Weibo and forums was deleted inexplicably.
I also looked for a lot of other media
They won't help me
If you reject me again, I will be helpless. Can you please understand me?
This is a big company helping
You really can't afford to offend a small newspaper.
Otherwise
Please contact other media.
I can't help you with my arrogance
Editor-in-Chief Liu
Hello, Miss Li Qian
I know a newspaper that can see the story you want.
I will send the contact information of the homepage to your mobile phone
If you are interested
You can contact him.
Who are you?
I want to thank you for fulfilling my father's wish today.
Mr. Gu, you are actually a very good person sometimes.
What do you mean by sometimes?
It should be every time
It seems that your understanding of me is still at a very superficial level.
What are you laughing at?
Oh, although you don't work seriously,
But since you have decided to be my assistant
I want to assign you some independent work.
What content
I won't hide it from you.
Please help me think of a solution.
How can I get my love?
Zhang Shiyu is already old and still single
I'm sure there's no good way.
So I think women should understand women better
Please help me think of a solution.
But I don't have any experience.
This work
Only success is allowed, no failure is allowed
If you fail
I think it will be hard for you to see your mother again
ah
Mr. Lin
Still can't find it. The people sent out have searched all the restaurants and bars that Xiaoxiu likes to go to.
There's no news from him.
The cards in his hand were not touched.
Yes, Mr. Lee
Xiao Xiu didn't take anything with him when he went out.
This child has never suffered any hardship since childhood.
I've been out for so long now.
I'm really worried
Director Liang
On the day of the promo shoot, my phone rang.
I'm really sorry
Dad's transfer to another hospital has been arranged.
Thank you
He's in much better spirits now.
He read in the newspaper that a group of Beresheetian fossils had been discovered somewhere.
We also went there together.
Don't take it to heart
I should do this.
ah
I picked up a wolf-finned fish fossil at the site yesterday.
For you
I remember you used to like this kind of painter
I mentioned you when I was chatting with my dad the other day
He said you have your own considerations.
Respecting a person's ideas is the best way to love him
So I won't force you to do anything anymore.
only
Me and Dad
I really miss you very much
I go first
Hey, I heard that Mr. Xiaolin has been away from home for two days.
The chairman took many photos and went to look for him but no one knew where he was.
I heard that he had a big fight with the chairman.
What kind of missing game are you going to play now?
When the filming of this drama really starts, we still don’t know how to shoot it.
Oh, I say, you acted really well in that scene just now.
I feel like you have changed completely since you came back from the fossil site.
How did it change? It's like a living fossil all over my body.
I mean
There was really some Professor Xu's position yesterday.
Um
Hey, has the director called the customer list?
I heard that Xiaolin has picked the
It's so difficult to shoot a trailer
What if it is time to start the machine?
can not imagine
Hey Xu Zhen
Hey Xu Zhen, where are you going? Xu Zhen
Xiaojuan, how do you know I'm here?
Have you forgotten that when we were little, you would run here every time you were unhappy and you haven't been sick until now.
Xiaoxiu, why are you hiding here again?
The adults are looking for you.
My dad must send me to study abroad
I do not want to go
He sent me away right after my mom died.
Why are you doing this?
Don't they want me anymore?
I don't have any relatives in this world.
Don't cry, little bear.
Do you still remember the four-leaf clover amber I gave you?
Xiaoxiu four-leaf clover amber symbolizes happiness
Look at him when you are lonely
It won't be sad anymore.
I remember you told me when I was little
Four-leaf clover represents happiness
Amber represents eternity.
Just hold this necklace in your hand
You can hold happiness forever
But now
I already know everything about you and Uncle Lin.
I know you are not an irresponsible person.
You did that on the set that day
You must have your own reasons.
The City of Time is all my brother's hard work
It's really unfair for my dad to do that.
So I'm going to give this project back to him.
So that's why you're screwing everything up on purpose?
But if you do this, it will only make the relationship between your father and your brother more strained.
Your father only blames your brother for everything.
If you really want your dad to listen to you
If you want your brother to come back
You should do things like an adult.
Make others respect your ideas
You have to become a great person first.
People will actually listen to what you have to say.
Thus
Wouldn't there be no more conflicts among the family?
Do you really think so, town?
Of course
Oh, go home quickly.
Uncle Lin has been waiting for you.
I think you are right.
I was so naive to do that.
The City of Time is the hard work of all of us
So I should perform better.
Only in this way can my brother and I
Dad saw my efforts
Thank you, Xiaozhen, hahaha
You changed your boss.
No, I'm working.
That
It's the Story Army
There's a new person to blow kisses to. No wonder you wouldn't even let me see him yesterday.
Hey, what are you talking about? Don't talk nonsense.
Help your boss expand his network
It is also part of my job to connect every link of the film.
I said, Senior
We are sisters.
If Gu Chijun blows a kiss, you must tell me immediately
We must not let other magazines get ahead of us.
But the small town
You're really lucky to have this job.
There are so many big stars around me
You're not interested in anyone.
I remember when we were little, we all posted and collected posters on the wall.
You are the only one who posted Li Siguang.
Hey, why haven't you eaten yet? If you don't cook, what will we eat?
Hey, come here quickly.
I have a question for you guys.
You say
How to confess to someone without being rejected?
Yeah, we're in love.
No, I'm asking for someone else.
If you continue to be single, I will use WeChat to find a partner for you.
You two are outstanding representatives of early love who have been dating since the second grade of elementary school.
I have failed many times along the way.
The experience value is definitely high
Tell me how to express your feelings to impress others.
Mm-m-m
I think first
The momentum should be big
Looks like a thief
Secondly, the difficulty level is high
Looks like a rich guy
the most important is
Good looks
For me, this is the most important
Everything else is secondary
Well, go away. Can you please confess?
No, no.
It's others who confessed to me.
Can you say something serious?
Haha, this is very particular.
First of all, it depends on who you are confessing to.
Male Female
female
Old, young, ugly, pretty, what's the star sign, what's the blood type, what's the personality
Different methods for different objects
Only by knowing yourself and your enemy and tailoring your strategy can you win every battle
Wait, isn't it the most important thing to impress people with your sincerity?
You should also find a way to let others see your sincerity, okay?
Who doesn't have a sincere heart even if they put aside their stomach?
The most important thing is to know what this person likes.
If you are a very realistic person
Then throw money at it
Tell him I have money and a future with him
If it's a dream
Then give him the stars, the moon and all kinds of Korean dramas
How to be romantic?
Find a beautiful place to talk to Beibeishi seriously
Suta
If it's a literary card
Then you have to be talented
How to catch fish depends on acquired knowledge
If it's a face control
Then dress yourself up to look more handsome.
Buy some high-end perfume
Make him think you have good taste
ah
Minor repair
Hey, brother is back.
You're back
I've seen the meal.
Um
Just got trained
Hey, do you know
Dad has been worried to death these past two days.
Don't do this again in the future.
I know I'll never do that again.
I've made you suffer these past two days.
What are you saying?
Okay, it's getting late, let's go back to our room and get some rest.
I can't rest yet.
I have to think about work later.
Work
Did I hear that correctly?
Yeah, I've figured it out.
All the empires of the company now are built by you bit by bit
That’s why I didn’t work so hard before
Our previous projects received a variety of problems
This is really wrong, so from now on I must turn over a new leaf and work hard.
This is the greatest comfort to my brother.
What are you doing?
Look, everyone else is working so hard.
Shouldn't I try harder?
Do good deeds
Dad will be very happy to know this news
Um
That's right, bro.
I have something to ask of you because I will have to trouble you with many things I don't understand in the future.
You have troubled me so little.
When did you become so polite to me?
Oh, it's troublesome.
It's still necessary to be polite.
I feel like you've become a different person.
When did you focus on work?
Is there? No?
Am I still the same?
20 years of dedicated work has never changed
wrong
I guess you are probably in love.
Um, where is it?
Um
normal friend
Ordinary friend aunt
You can't hide it from me
Go back to bed early, eh?
Xiaoxiu
Fang Yi
Where did this person go?
Be careful, I went out early in the morning.
Did you go to work?
His car is still parked at the door.
I do not know
I saw him rushing out in the morning
I can't even call you
This is really strange.
Now I go to work early in the morning
Hello, I have a lot of things to repair.
Stanislav Konway also has some jibs and stuff
What weekends off?
It's okay, you guys can attack me, I'll pay you whatever money you have.
Is this the takeaway you ordered? Just put it on that table.
Good morning. Have you had breakfast yet?
I have already eaten
You must not be full. Come on, have breakfast.
Thank you Mr. Xiaolin for breakfast. Thank you, thank you.
Get breakfast early
Thank you
Those who haven't had breakfast yet can take it here.
That's enough, Mr. Kobayashi.
My name is Wang. I am the on-site producer sent by General Manager Lin.
Then he asked me to go to the scene to help you. If you need anything, he will call you Hello Wang Zhipian
Hello, hello, have you had breakfast?
Ah, take one of this.
I'm telling you, our group's breakfast is really bad. From now on, I'll take care of breakfast whenever I'm here.
Mr. Xiaolin, this will cause our crew to overspend. It's okay.
As long as everyone is happy eating
I'm responsible for the overspending.
One more thing
Why hasn't Xu Zhen come yet?
There is no story-telling show today. What?
No, wasn't there a play about Story-kun yesterday?
Oh, don't you know?
Gu Shijun said he was not feeling well today and had to temporarily change his schedule with Qingziqin.
Physical discomfort
Hey, can the time of this announcement be changed at will?
You really don't take me, the producer, seriously.
No, this happened last night.
Then we couldn't contact you at all.
I see
Then I'll go first