[English subtitles are available]
[My Heart]
[Episode 1]
My name is Lu Qingqing.
I'm a strange girl
who is out of tune with the Qiyuan continent.
People here are honored by their magic power,
but I have no magic power even after so many years of practice.
I heard that there is a place called No Magic Valley,
and all of the people there have no magic powers.
I always thought that
I should have lived in No Magic Valley,
so that
I wouldn't be confined in the yard
and not be allowed to go out.
[Lu Mansion  Lu Qingqing  Magic Level ?]
Dapang,
do you want to test your magic power?
My lady!
Today Crown Prince will perform his capping ceremony,
so there will be many people on the street.
If the Master knows it,
we'll be punished again!
Take it easy, Baihe.
[Baihe  Magic Level 1]
I'll be right back after watching the scene of bustle.
My lady!
You can't go out!
My lady! My lady!
[Lord Jin]
My lady! Stop!
Stop! My lady!
[Xiaowu  Magic Level 4]
Stop. Stop. Stop.
My head!
Lord Nangong, I think we hit a rabbit.
Poor little thing,
are you okay?
His magic power field is so strong.
I feel so
[Lord Jin  Nangong Yixin  Magic Level 7]
warm and happy to be held by him.
I want to know whether I can get some magic power
if I bite him.
Gosh!
I should run! Run!
Let me out!
[Taowu]
Are you talking to me?
How can I read these two characters?
The seal should have been broken!
Who?
Who are you?
[Taowu  fierce monster of Qiyuan]
Me?
A fierce monster!
Wait!
Now, the capping ceremony begins.
The Commander of the magic power army,
Grand Preceptor Lu, please crown Crown Prince.
[The Commander  Lu Hongzhu  Magic Level 6]
Since the death of Emperor Nangong,
we haven't seen a grand scene like this in over a decade.
You're right.
You're flying too high. Slow down.
Get off me right now.
No.
I can't get off now.
I have no magic power, so I will die.
You doesn't have any magic power?
As a citizen of Qiyuan continent,
don't you have any magic power?
Then how did you break my seal?
Ugly kitty,
I just touched it, and you went out of it.
You are the ugly kitty!
I'm a spirit monster!
Ugly kitty,
slow down!
Damn.
I haven't flown in a long time,
so my flying skills are not very good.
I can't control the direction very well.
[Crown Prince  Nangong Mingyang  Magic Level 6]
Congratulations, Your Highness.
I do want to see the ceremony,
but not from the rooftop!
Guard royalty!
Qingqing?
How could you...
Dad!
Is she Lady Qingqing who has never
been seen in public?
Your Highness,
she is my daughter, Lu Qingqing.
She is so bad-mannered
and has bothered your ceremony.
Please forgive her.
Is he the Crown Prince?
He is so brave and handsome as the rumors say.
Kneel down, quickly!
Guard royalty!
Taowu?
Lu Hongzhu,
you have confined me for a long time.
I'll kill you!
Guard Crown Prince and the Empress!
Don't hurt my dad!
Is he your dad?
Then go to hell with your dad!
Lord Jin?
His field is so strong.
Why do I feel a little dizzy?
My heart beats so quickly.
Is she that red-eared rabbit?
It's you?
Lord Lu,
is she your daughter?
I think she was scared by the little monster.
Brother!
I knew you'd be here today.
Does she have magic power?
Don't kill him!
Taowu has an unruly character.
He is so hard to be tamed.
It took a while to trap him.
How did he come here today?
We don't know what happened,
but we'll definitely find out the reason.
Taowu likes freedom,
which is the same as me.
Since you guys can't keep him well,
what about giving him to me?
You are highly skilled,
so it'd be nice if you can keep him.
you keep him.
Thanks to the help of Lord Jin.
You are definitely the most skilled person
on the Qiyuan continent.
It has been more than a year
since Yixin visited No Magic Valley.
Why didn't you tell me you were back?
I was supposed to pick you up.
You are so busy with political affairs.
I couldn't
bother you with such a trivial thing.
Brother,
can you stay longer
this time since you came back?
I won't stay long.
I'll go back in a few days.
I can enjoy far more freedom in No Magic Valley.
What a shame!
He is so cubbish!
Yeah.
Are you talking about me?
I didn't call to account in court.
But I need a reasonable excuse
for Taowu's interruption of the capping ceremony.
Tell me,
how can I deal with it?
Your Highness,
it was because of my incompetence
that caused my daughter to make such a big mistake.
It's my fault,
so please punish me for my crime.
But I think that this girl
has nothing to do with Taowu.
Everyone had seen what happened.
Taowu wanted to kill you, Lord Lu.
Now that the issue has been solved,
we might as well let it go.
Yes.
I met him
only by chance.
Lu Qingqing,
you are not allowed to speak here.
Lord Jin,
thank you for your kindness.
But I think this thing
about Taowu needs further investigation.
It's a major event,
so we can't jump to hasty conclusions.
Mother,
even though Lu Qingqing had bothered the ceremony,
she also saved my brother with her life
when he was in danger.
Merits offset faults.
Crown Prince is kindhearted.
Then I'll assign the survey tasks about Taowu to Lord Lu.
For your convenience,
I'll give you the authority
to command the second army.
Subject to the will.
Your Highness,
[General  Murong Tuo  Magic Level 5]
this...
Crown Prince
and the Empress,
since the issue has been solved,
I'll take my leave now.
Dad,
listen to me,
it's not what you thought...
Don't talk more.
I'll punish you after going back home.
I really didn't mean to do that, dad!
Shut up!
Your Highness.
Lord Lu?
Why are you still here?
Are you waiting for me?
I'm really appreciate that
you saved me and my daughter today.
As it happens,
I have several jars of wine at home.
If you don't mind,
why not come to my place and have a drink?
Sure!
I have long heard that
your wine is extraordinary.
What about noon tomorrow?
No problem.
OK.
I'll leave then.
I'll have a good preparation
and wait for your visit.
He has helped me so many times
and I'll see him again tomorrow.
I think we are destined.
You made a mess, but got the second army.
You're so lucky,
Mr. Lu.
[Lu Mansion]
There appeared an auspicious sign at the capping ceremony!
Today is a good day!
Could it be that the magic power stone appeared again?
It would be great if that happened!
After the magic power stone returns to its place,
Crown Prince
can ascend the throne justifiably.
Since twenty years ago
magic girl took the magic power stone
to visit No Magic Valley and disappeared,
Lord Lu has been searching for years without a result.
The magic power stone is the most precious treasure of our country.
It should be found as soon as possible.
Twenty years have passed.
Will the stone finally appear?
Magic girl,
I know you must be alive,
but where are you?
How beautiful!
The world outside Lu Mansion is wonderful.
Follow me.
Miss Lu is an interesting girl.
I heard she hasn't had magic power for twenty years.
Lord Lu is afraid that his daughter might get bullied,
so he seldom allows her to go out.
Twenty years?
No magic power?
She doesn't look like it.
I heard her mother was from No Magic Valley.
So I think
that's why Lord Lu
always thinks about that place.
Doesn't Lord Lu look down upon
getting married to people in No Magic Valley?
Maybe he loved her so deeply
and couldn't control himself.
Nobody knows yet
who Qingqing's mother is.
Do you know what a mess you have made?
It was an accident!
I just wanted to see
the capping ceremony of Crown Prince
and collect together a jollification.
Jollification?
That's the imperial palace!
How could you just go there randomly?
I was wrong today.
But I want to know
how my sister can go everywhere she wants
while I can only stay in this yard?
Qingqing,
I know you grew up in this little yard
and feel so bored,
but I couldn't find a more appropriate way.
You're not like your sister,
she boasted strong magic power since her childhood.
You doesn't have any magic power,
so the world outside is too dangerous for you.
You're not gonna be able to
handle any danger outside.
I know you are caring about me, dad.
But I need freedom, too.
I want to see the world.
In Qiyuan continent,
a person without magic power can never be free.
Well,
if I have magic power,
can I go out then?
Qingqing,
today in court,
did you stun Taowu
with your magic power?
Me?
Wasn't it Lord Jin?
Or maybe I also have magic power?
I might see it wrong.
Dad, take it easy.
I will practice my magic power harder.
So please don't punish me today, okay?
Okay.
Since you want to practice magic power,
transcribe Magic Inspiration Scriptures a hundred times.
You can't go out of this room until you finish.
Dad!
Don't want to?
Sure!
You are negligent in caring for Lady Qingqing,
so I will punish you all.
Dad,
I will do it. I will do it.
[Lord Jin Mansion]
[No Magic Valley  Sikong Ying]
Sikong.
Today's ceremony was much more exciting than the Cuju competition.
It's too bad you missed it.
What happened?
The second daughter of Lu Hongzhu rode Taowu
and dropped into court from the rooftop
and almost ruined the ceremony.
Wait.
His second daughter rode Taowu into court?
Are you kidding me?
Taowu is the most fierce monster
in the Qiyuan continent.
How could he listen to a girl's order?
I don't know.
But that girl looks simple and honest,
you will believe my words when you see her.
By the way,
Lu Hongzhu invited me to drink at his home tomorrow.
Why did he suddenly ask you out for a drink?
Could Lu Hongzhu
have any intrigues again?
[Fengling Hall]
Lord Jin went to No Magic Valley for so many days.
Is there anything unusual
about his sudden return?
Your Grace,
he went to the palace after entering the city,
nothing was unususal.
I don't think he had anything to do with today.
Qingqing suddenly appeared in court today
and seemed to use magic power.
Then there appeared an auspicious sign,
which was a sign of the magic power stone.
I think the magic girl is coming back.
Qi Yi,
go and ask the secret agents in the valley about
whether they have seen some strange scenes.
If so, tell me right away.
Yes, your Grace.
My lady, drink some tea please.
I'm so tired.
I've only I've only copied it six times,
and there are still 94 times left.
That's so hard for me.
Dad is usually very easy-going.
I don't know what's wrong with him today!
Baihe?
My lady,
I won't help you this time.
Baihe,
I know that
you love me the best in this mension.
My lady,
if you could listen to the Mater's words
and stay at home,
everyone in this mension would love you.
But I like the world
outside very much.
They're totally different!
The world outside is wonderful.
My lady,
I think you should copy the Magic Inspiration Scriptures
a few times more.
Maybe you could be inspired one day,
and awaken your magic power.
Speaking of which,
I really felt
a little magic power today.
Before Dad reminded me, I didn't notice
that I really made the ugly kitty fainted.
And I even saved Lord Jin!
The ugly kitty?
A friend I made today!
It's ugly but cute!
Do you get the hysteria due to your desire for magic?
I'd be a rabbit if I lied to you!
Then show me. Change into a rabbit.
No way...
My lady,
you've had no magic for so many years.
It's impossible that you gain it all of a sudden.
See? Master loves you so much.
He sends you all the delicious food and interesting toys.
Lady Yunxi also loves you
that she never lets you suffer.
Just stay in the mansion.
I believe I can do it!
Let me think!
Did I use magic power back then?
Why did I suddenly get the power?
Lady Qingqing doesn't have any magic power,
[Lu Mansion  Lu Yunxi  Magic Level 3]
[Zhenzhu  Magic Level 2]
and she even runs out of the side yard
to make trouble again and again.
Enough, Zhenzhu. Stop it.
No matter what,
Qingqing is still a lady in our Lu Family,
and she's my sister.
I should dote on
and take care of her.
You're the most excellent one, my lady.
Why do they show more love
to Lady Qingqing, that dub?
All the good things are given to her first.
Zhenzhu, I'll repeat it again.
You should respect Qingqing.
No matter what,
she's my younger sister. Understand?
[Lu Mansion]
What?
Lord Jin is coming?
Why are you so looking forward to his arrival?
I thought you were bragging yesterday
when you said
he saved you.
I didn't brag!
He saved my life.
Or, in other words,
we saved each other.
But I heard
he has a bad reputation.
Reputation?
What reputation?
Why is his reputation bad?
It's said that he drinks, plays,
and fiddles around every day,
never caring about the image of Qiyuan Continent.
He's totally different from the diligent Crown Prince.
But his magic power is so strong though he loafs around every day.
That sounds more amazing!
My lady,
your mindset is still that unusual.
If Lord Jin can teach me a little,
will I stand a chance to awaken my magic power?
Maybe...
But there are so many girls courting him,
and he just ignores them.
He won't teach you.
No! My lady!
No way!
Baihe,
I'm not going to leave the mansion!
He himself is coming here!
I can't miss such a great opportunity!
Right?
My lady,
please don't!
Baihe, I promise,
this time no one will discover it!
It's definitely the last time!
[Lingqing Court]
Why did I get lost again?
Why am I in the kitchen?
Master ordered the rabbit meat today.
I was just worrying that No Magic Valley didn't supply rabbits,
and I couldn't make that dish.
And then you came here!
Gosh! I'd better run!
Close!
I'm done!
Little rabbit,
I got you!
Since you came to us today,
it's just your fate!
No!
Stop it!
Don't let it escape! Let's chase it!
It's Lord Jin!
Where is it?
Let's go that way!
Okay.
Your Highness!
Rise.
What are you doing here?
Your Highness,
a rabbit, the ingredient in the kitchen just ran away.
We're trying to catch it!
I saw it running that way!
Go!
Yes, Your Highness!
Jeez!
Luckily, Lord Jin covers me up!
The lady in the Lu's Mansion
welcomes the guest in such a special way!
Little rabbit,
I remember you.
You ran into my carriage yesterday, didn't you?
Lu Qingqing!
I'm done!
I almost forget that I not only ran into him,
but also bit him!
No!
I can't change back no matter what!
You don't change back, huh?
No! I won't!
You bit me yesterday!
I'm holding a grudge!
I, Nangong Yixin, am not a forgiving man.
How about this?
Today, let me bite you, too.
Then we're even.
Too embarrassing!
R-run...
From yesterday till now,
you've really impressed me, little rabbit.
Take advantage of me and then run away!
Lu Qingqing!
Your Highness, you condescended to visit my mansion.
My humble house is honored by your presence.
Mr. Lu,
your mansion
is so splendid
that a few glances
just make me kind of dizzy.
But this wine is mellow with a sweet aftertaste.
It's worth tasting.
It's my honor
that you love my wine.
I'll let the servant
send some of it to your mansion.
Thank you.
We're all human.
But why is Lord Jin's magic power so strong,
while I was born to be a dud?
He must have some special cultivating ways!
Now,
you've taken over General Han's military power.
Then you'll surely be busy from now on.
So it's improper for me to visit you frequently.
Yes, Your Highness.
Why can't I hear what they're saying?
The Crown Prince just came to power after the capping ceremony.
He's occupied with political affairs.
I'm just doing my best
to help him manage them.
After he gets the magic power stone,
and officially ascends the throne,
I'll return all these rights to him, of course.
Mr. Lu,
I don't care who has
the military power.
What I'm caring about is...
whether your daughter is engaged or not.
I mean
that Lady Qingqing who came out of nowhere yesterday.
Qingqing is still young.
I haven't thought about arranging her marriage yet.
I see!
Yesterday she rode Taowu
and fell into the capping ceremony.
I just wondered if someone
was trying to make a match for the Crown Prince.
The Crown Prince is so excellent
that my daughter is not good enough for him.
Yunxi,
serve Lord Jin with more wine.
She's been admiring you, Your Highness.
It's her honor
to meet you here today.
I've heard Lady Yunxi is so elegant and decent
as a model for the women in Qiyuan Continent.
Today we meet here,
and you live up to your reputation.
Thank you, Your Highness.
I'm flattered.
Mr. Lu,
your daughters
are all extraordinary.
Right,
where's Lady Qingqing?
I'm here!
Qingqing acted recklessly
and she's in her room to reflect on her mistake.
Qingqing?
Qingqing!
Are you all right?
Why are you not in your room
but here?
Reflect on her mistake in her room
for acting recklessly?
Go back now!
Now that she's come here,
why not let her drink with us?
Lord Jin asked me to stay!
You're more and more unruly.
Dad,
Lord Jin is our distinguished guest.
Qingqing should come out to greet him.
I'll send her back later. Is that okay?
Sit next to your sister!
I want to sit here!
So I can add wine for Lord Jin.
Please.
With a closer look,
Lord Jin really seems outstanding.
Qingqing,
you're so gorgeous.
You make the whole world pale in comparison.
I'm falling for you.
You're my dream lover.
Lady Qingqing,
aren't you too close to me?
Qingqing.
Come on, stand up.
You're usually so agile.
But why didn't you dodge just now?
I'm okay, Yunxi.
Luckily, this wine didn't splash on Lord Jin.
He's our distinguished guest!
There are so many people fawning on me.
But you're the most honest one I've ever seen.
Qingqing!
Look at yourself!
Go back now!
Dad!
Go!
Do as Dad says. Go back to your room.
Okay.
Wait.
You're so attentive today.
You're up to something, right?
Do you know what I came here for?
I've met numerous people.
No one knows better than me.
What's this?
The thing that you crave for.
Does he give me a secret rune of magic
to help me improve my magic power?
Thank you, Your Highness!
Enough, Qingqing.
Return to your room.
Yes, Dad.
Your Highness!
Thank you!
Baihe!
Have you seen it?
The secret rune Lord Jin gave me really works!
My lady!
Yes!
You have magic power now!
But are you sure it's due to this rune?
I'm absolutely sure!
Brilliant, my lady!
It means Master
doesn't need to keep you in the mansion from now on!
We can go out!
Yes, Baihe.
From now on, we can
walk through this yard gate aboveboard
to see the world outside together!
Yes! Bravo!
It's so lively in your mansion.
This visit is worthwhile.
You're joking.
I'll subject Qingqing to discipline later.
It's rare for you to visit my house.
And the udumbara in my garden
just happens to bloom.
Why not let Yunxi walk you there to have a look?
I just planned to ask!
On our way, I just found
your garden so exquisite.
It's worth roaming!
Yunxi,
take Lord Jin to walk around the garden.
Let the maids leave.
Don't spoil Lord Jin's fun.
Yes, my lord.
Dad...
Yes, Dad.
This way please, Your Highness.
Okay.
[Lingqing Court]
My lady,
Lord Jin has given some rewards.
Master asked maids in every yard to take them.
Did he?
Then why didn't he mention it just now?
Baihe, you go to take.
Lord Jin's rewards
must be something good!
Take more of them back!
Yes, my lady.
I'll be back soon.
Where are you going?
Why are we taking this road?
Just go ahead.
What are you going to do?
Go!
What...
Why did it suddenly disappear?
Why am I unable to use magic now?
Is my magic power getting weaker?
I see!
It's definitely because one piece of rune is not enough!
I should have asked him for more!
Baihe has gone for a while. Why hasn't she come back yet?
Baihe!
You knocked me over on purpose,
and even stained my dress!
They all saw it!
I didn't!
You're framing me!
You dare not admit what you did.
You're as unruly as your lady.
Let me teach you a harsh lesson.
Go!
Wash that dress for me.
You! You've gone too far!
You framed me on purpose,
and now you ask me to wash the dress with this hot water!
Do you want to kill me?
The floor is so dirty.
This dress was rewarded by Lady Yunxi!
Only hot water can make it clean!
Take her there!
No!
Let me go!
What on earth do you want?
Free her!
Lady Qingqing.
Help!
My lady!
You can vent your anger on me.
Why are you bullying Baihe?
My lady,
I dare not to do so.
You're our lady even if you have no magic power at all.
Baihe stained my clothes,
so I just asked her to wash it.
I have no magic power, so what?
Is it right to bully others just because
you have magic power?
If that's why you cultivate magic power,
then I just don't want it.
Did all of you see it?
Aren't they my sister's earrings?
How can you, a servant,
get her stuff?
Did you steal them?
My lady!
Please spare my life, my lady.
I know I was wrong!
It's Zhenzhu!
You!
Zhenzhu used them to bribe us,
and asked us to play tricks on Baihe with her.
Zhenzhu,
what else do you want to say?
What happened to me in the banquet
was also done by you, right?
I didn't retaliate before.
But if you go too far in the future,
I'll tell it to my dad and sister!
They'll surely investigate into it.
Let's see if you'll still be that arrogant.
Let's go, Baihe.
I... You...