(Good Partner)
(Divorce)
(In session)
(Plaintiff)
(Cha Eun Kyung)
(Han Yu Ri)
(Good Partner)
(All people, locations, organizations,)
(incidents, and backstories in this drama are fictitious.)
(Staff ensured child actors' safety in the filming of this drama.)
Once again, we are joined by Attorney Cha Eun Kyung...
who will provide us with enlightening solutions...
to the family matters of our listeners.
Hello, I'm Attorney Cha Eun Kyung, your representative.
Ms. Cha,
in TV dramas,
we see many affairs caught first...
not by the spouses, but by those around them.
Is that often the case in real-life situations?
(6 months ago)
(Letter of Appointment, Kim Ji Sang)
We appreciate you coming on board...
despite your busy schedule.
We'll look forward to the married couple's devotion...
to our law firm.
You're too kind. I'm the one who's grateful.
Medical disputes we take on at Daejeong...
will be of even better quality.
(Episode 3)
Jae Hui, is there anything you need?
I only wanted some water.
Jae Hui.
- Isn't it delicious? - Hey, Jae Hui.
- Hi. - Hi, Jae Hui.
- It's been so long. - Gosh.
- Goodness. - You're a big girl now.
Jae Hui, we're celebrating a big day for your dad,
so I hope you won't mind the loud chatter.
It's fine by me.
I'll head upstairs.
- Sure. - Good night.
- Good night. - How sweet of her.
- Isn't she a sweetheart? - She's adorable.
As the newly appointed...
in-house medical expert of Law Firm Daejeong,
Director Kim should say a few words.
Right. Well,
I'm busy up to my neck...
with the hospital and raising Jae Hui,
so I'm worried about the added responsibility.
I'll do my best though.
- Gosh. - Nice!
Congratulations. Let's raise our glasses, then.
- Congratulations. - Congratulations.
How did he get to join us as an in-house medical expert?
Did you propose it?
Mr. Oh voiced his concern over the quality of our medical cases.
I suggested bringing my husband on board first...
- and told him about it. - I see.
That means...
Director Kim now has two offices.
One at the law firm...
and one at the hospital.
Working in close proximity will allow me...
to see her at least once more.
- No way! - My gosh.
Can you be more of a love whisperer?
You're being weird.
I see everyone's glasses are empty.
Would you all like another drink?
- Sure. - Of course I'd like another.
We're out of booze though.
- Is it empty? - It is.
Ma'am, could you check the fridge for me?
- Have a drink. - Gosh, thanks.
There isn't any, but I'll go out to get some.
Gosh, no. I'll go instead.
By yourself?
I doubt you know where the store is.
I'll get the drinks for us.
Sure, you should go instead.
- I'll be back in no time. - Right.
Ms. Cha, allow me to pour you a glass.
It'll be a lot to carry by himself,
- so I'll help. - What?
- I bet it was quite the hassle. - Gosh, no.
You should try this.
Those still here should raise our glasses.
- Sounds good. - Sure thing.
Yes, it happens on many occasions.
Even though the spouses who are being cheated on...
find something to be odd,
a defense mechanism kicks in...
which tells them that it can't be true.
That's why those around them figure it out first.
How do you feel about the car now that it's been a few days?
I like how quiet it is.
I definitely prefer sedans to sports cars.
Of course. You're sensitive to sound.
Right.
Anyway, I need to study up on all these features.
I like how wide the display is.
Right.
Hold on. Is this a featured option?
- What's this? - Leave it!
Sender, Director Choi. "Where are you?"
"Where are you?" is the key phrase...
that leads to spouses discovering the affair.
"Where are you?" might seem harmless and meaningless,
but it's an intimate phrase only said between those...
who share their everyday lives.
Who's that?
A director at my hospital, of course.
I should be back by now after lunch.
I see.
(Director Choi)
Sa Ra, why does it take you long...
to get back to the office after dropping by the courthouse?
I'm sorry.
There's always heavy traffic on the way back,
so I just take the liberty to grab my lunch...
since I'm stuck between lunch hour anyway.
You're dismissed.
What if you have no definitive proof...
of your spouse's affair?
Should you feign ignorance?
Yes. While you gather the necessary evidence,
you must play dumb.
- Until you have absolute proof, - Hello.
be patient.
Director Kim isn't here at the moment.
I'm here with documents needed for his contract.
Could you pass these along?
But he'll be here in about ten minutes.
Is he on his lunch break?
Wait. Didn't you know?
He's only been seeing patients in the afternoon lately.
Gosh, of course. It slipped my mind.
(Hanareum Family Medical Clinic)
(Kim Ji Sang, Kim Jin Heon)
(Jung Hye Won, Han Sang Tae, Kim Gyu Bi)
Wasn't there a Director Choi?
We don't have a director by that surname.
Why do you ask?
What? It's nothing.
You see cracks here and there in your everyday lives.
Yes?
Do you have Jae Hui's phone?
Yes, she left it in my car...
after the trip to the museum yesterday.
You should've given it back to her already.
That's rich coming from someone...
who didn't even see her all throughout this weekend.
I left it at the law firm this morning.
Maybe you can take it to her.
Fine.
(Kim Ji Sang)
(To Kim Ji Sang, Photo)
But then,
you're hit with a moment...
when those cracks come together like pieces of a puzzle.
Gosh, I just got goosebumps.
Can you inform our listeners...
of what to do should that happen to them?
Stay rational.
And don't do anything emotional which you'll regret.
(Consultant, Internist Kim Ji Sang)
Yes?
Did you bring Jae Hui's phone to her?
No, I'm too busy with consultations today.
You said you'd get it to her.
I'm busy.
For instance, grabbing the cheating couple by the hair,
destroying valuables around the house,
or anything similar that could be used against you.
I see. Listeners,
if you find yourself in a similar situation,
please make sure to act rationally.
Do you have any last words?
An extramarital affair?
It can happen to anyone.
Please stay calm,
and escape from the tunnel of agony.
(Case 03: From Family to Non-family)
Ms. Cha,
you were aware of it all?
What are you playing at by coming to my house at this hour?
Well...
I thought you'd be clueless.
That's what you thought? Me?
Are you not...
going to divorce him?
I'm not.
I won't divorce him, so save the drama.
How can you let them get away with it?
If it were me, I'd immediately file for divorce...
and tell everyone at the office as well as the press.
What do I get out of it?
Can it be solved with a divorce,
a division of assets, and an alimony of 20,000 dollars?
Adultery isn't punishable by law anymore,
so that's the only legal action you can take.
I'm truly surprised...
by your one-dimensional way of thinking.
She's a secretary...
who I've been satisfied with for ten years,
and he's been caring for my child for 13 years.
Should I instantly remove them all from my life...
and accept 20,000 dollars in alimony...
which is less than what I make a month?
If that's all you can do right now,
that's the least you should do.
Lawyers your age let the law sway your decisions.
To be a true lawyer or attorney,
one must use the law to their advantage instead.
But you were betrayed by the two people closest to you.
How can you not do anything?
An extramarital affair.
Is it an unlawful act?
It's not, so what about it?
Are you saying you're all right with this?
Things are running smoothly at home and at work.
I need them.
I'm not talking about your family or your job.
What about your own life?
My family and my job...
are my life.
Are you really leaving?
I already told you.
This isn't to celebrate our wedding anniversary.
I'm seeing her to negotiate our divorce.
How can I believe that...
when marital spats never last long?
A marital spat?
How is it one when we're done as a married couple?
You won't eat with her, will you?
Didn't you cook doenjang stew with snails...
so that I wouldn't have dinner with her?
Busted.
I'll call you.
Is it our 14th wedding anniversary?
I guess I should've been more attentive about these things.
Why haven't you given me an answer?
- What answer? - I texted you.
How will you proceed with our divorce?
I came today since I knew you'd drag it out...
if I didn't ask face to face.
Right, the divorce.
What's your reason for wanting one?
Telling you will only lead to a quarrel.
Let's stop going around in circles and end the marriage amicably.
You're claiming spousal negligence...
on my part.
Negligence would be a waste of an expression.
I was in this marriage alone.
I don't want to keep talking about this, so just agree to it.
I'll be more attentive to Jae Hui.
No couples will stay married if they divorce for such a thing.
That's my reason for wanting a divorce.
What's been agonizing for me...
is only a simple matter for you that you can brush off.
How's that a reason for a divorce?
Should we go down this route...
when the entire nation will know about our divorce?
So that's what it is.
Even in this situation, you worry more about saving face.
A divorce?
What big difference would that make?
Forget it. We're back to square one again.
Sit.
I'm not one of your subordinates.
You listen up.
There's only one thing I want to talk about.
Which is?
The divorce, division of our assets, and custody of Jae Hui.
You're the best at discussing them.
Get back to me with an offer.
What can I do to change your mind?
Should I quit my job and be a stay-at-home mom?
Don't be melodramatic.
I never wanted that from you.
Then, tell me.
I'll do whatever you want.
You seem to have the wrong idea about this.
I no longer see you...
as my wife, the woman I love,
or Jae Hui's mom.
Call me when you're ready.
(1st Wedding Anniversary)
I'll make a lot more money and buy you the watch...
I couldn't buy when we got married.
Spending time with you like this is the best gift.
Ta-da.
You check the watch often.
Every time you check, you'll think of me.
(Law Firm Daejeong)
You all did great work this month.
- Great work, everyone. - Great work, everyone.
Keep up the good work next month as well.
- Sure. - Got it.
- Great work, everyone. - Great work, everyone!
- Great work. - Great work, everyone.
All right. Ms. Han, this is for you.
Will Ms. Han be interviewing our new clients as well?
I've been worried with all the new clients...
that have been coming our way,
so welcome.
What Ms. Cha has been doing alone will be divided among you three.
- Do you have the list? - Of course.
I sorted everything out neatly while also adding comments.
That reminds me.
Here you go, Ms. Han.
Thank you.
(List of clients to consult, March, 2024)
Ms. Han, come to me with questions...
if you have any regarding your interviews.
There isn't anything different with them being new clients,
so address them with confidence.
Yes. Thanks for that.
Ms. Han.
I bet you didn't know we receive 300 dollars per hour.
- What? Really? - Yes.
Me? I get 300 dollars?
It's what you're worth as an attorney of a major law firm,
not what your time is actually worth.
Ms. Cha, we're already aware of that...
without you striking us with the facts.
I'm also well aware...
that the partners' time is worth 500 dollars per hour.
Wait. What does PB stand for?
That's something I wrote down.
It means "pain in the butt."
Mr. Jun.
Isn't there a better way of addressing them,
like "people who need special attention and care"?
I'll keep that in mind next time.
Mr. Jun, what do you categorize as "pain in the butt"?
What do I categorize as "pain in the butt"?
What does pain in the butt mean?
All right. Here we go.
Let's start with A.
(Those who are lonely)
They aren't interested in a divorce,
but they come to us out of loneliness.
And B.
There are people who accuse us of robbing them dry...
with our high retainer fees.
And C is this. The nitpickers.
They nitpick at everything we say...
but don't fully understand our words.
Lastly, we have D. The indecisive.
It's hard to deal with those who are indecisive.
Anyway, knowing this will help you immensely down the road.
Also, it's company policy to limit our consultations...
to five sessions.
Please comply with that.
I see.
I didn't know there was a limit to our sessions.
But isn't it up to the clients...
to decide on the number of sessions they need?
This is a law firm.
This isn't a consultation center where you pay by the hour.
The reason people get more than five consultations...
is usually because it's hard for them to decide to get divorced.
There is also the goal of leaving...
the decision to get divorced with our clients,
though we legally represent them as lawyers.
Why do you think we hand over the list of clients...
who are here for the fifth time to the newcomers?
To wrap things up neatly?
We're asking you to send them away in a kind manner.
Clients like that are highly likely...
to change their minds repeatedly even after they decide to sue.
Those kinds of cases are hard for large law firms to handle.
I guess deciding to get married...
is hard for everyone.
But...
I can't understand the limit of five consultations.
Ms. Han.
There's no need for you to understand.
You just have to follow the rules.
Could you help clean up?
- Yes. - Yes. Bye.
Yes?
Ms. Cha. Someone is here for their fifth consultation.
Ms. Han is going to meet with them.
Please escort them to her.
Yes, ma'am.
Is there anything else you need?
No.
I was just looking at you because you looked pretty.
I see. Thank you.
Are you going on a date?
Yes, I have a date in the evening.
With my boyfriend.
You have a boyfriend?
I didn't know.
I see.
I'll introduce him to you when I get a chance.
Okay. You can go now.
I no longer see you as my wife, the woman I love,
or Jae Hui's mom.
Weren't we going to have a consultation with Attorney Cha?
Since you've already had four consultations with Attorney Cha,
it's better to get another attorney's opinion.
- Is that so? - Of course.
Attorneys have different opinions, so it'll be more helpful.
Hello.
Hello, Attorney Han.
This is my fifth time here.
Today is the last time, right?
Yes, it's a firm policy.
I'm paying for the consultations, so why can't I get more?
I agree. Come in.
A recording?
Yes. If you don't get a recording,
nobody will believe that your father verbally abuses you...
every time he gets drunk.
He's gentle when he's not drinking, right?
Gosh.
How can married couples secretly record each other?
That's a bad thing.
I've come all the way here,
but I still don't know whether divorce is the right thing.
If he doesn't drink, he's not bad for a man of his generation...
He is quite nice to me.
He doesn't plan to quit drinking. That's the problem.
Please stop it, Mom.
You're taking medication because you can't sleep...
from too much stress. Why are you still hesitating?
He's your dad.
He needs to walk you down the aisle when you get married.
Stop saying it's because of me! It's just an excuse!
If I get married, will you get a divorce?
There. Please calm down.
Ma'am. What exactly are you afraid of?
Your husband or divorce?
My daughter is getting married soon.
If her wedding is called off because of my divorce,
I won't be able to stand it.
Also, I don't have so many years to live anyway.
I don't know if it's worth it to be labeled as a divorced woman.
Your daughter already said she was okay with it.
And what do you mean? "Labeled as a divorced woman?"
Nobody thinks like that these days.
People will accuse me of throwing away my family...
without knowing what's actually going on.
I feel so frustrated.
So you're saying...
that you'll live in pain for the next 30 years...
for people who don't even know what's going on, right?
I think he has a lot of money because the few houses he owns...
all rose in value,
but he won't tell me.
When I ask him about it,
he yells at me saying, "Why do you need to know that?"
"Don't even think about claiming any of it."
Gosh.
There is only fear left in your marriage. You should end it.
I can live without him.
But without me,
he won't even be able to make rice.
Gosh.
He won't starve to death.
I'm sure he won't.
He'll die from disease after eating too much cup ramyeon.
With division of assets,
you can get half of everything.
And because the person who keeps swearing at you...
and being condescending to you will be gone,
you'll feel much more relaxed.
Will I...
really feel like that?
Mom. Dad's not even human.
So please just live your life.
How long are you going to live bound to Dad?
I'll help you work up the courage.
Here.
If you sign here, it's all over.
We'll take care of things from here.
Just follow my lead.
I told you to get rid of the person who came for the fifth time,
and you still took on their case?
Yes.
The mother couldn't decide so her daughter...
Call her Ms. Park Jin Sook, not mother.
It's not as if you're her daughter.
It's good that you noticed...
the daughter would pay for the legal fees.
Where the money will come from is key.
It wasn't about the money.
Her daughter was the key to her heart.
She felt guilty about giving up on her family,
even after so much sacrifice.
Her daughter was the only person who could free her of that feeling.
I'll tell Mr. Oh...
that you got your first case.
You've earned your meal.
It's true that deciding to get divorced is up to the person,
but I realized someone needed to help them make that decision.
Help them, my foot.
She went ahead with the lawsuit because she wouldn't have...
anyone to whine to after her last consultation...
at our firm today.
This is why a company's system is important.
Would anyone in the world actually decide...
to get a divorce because of a company policy?
Yes, Ms. Park Jin Sook.
I bet she will drop the case down the line.
If I support her well, I'm sure she will stay strong.
She can't go back to that miserable life.
Did you say "Just trust me" again?
Just follow my lead.
Are you some justice warrior?
Ms. Han. Please be honest.
You wanted to punish him.
He should be punished.
More than punishing him,
whether she can live on her own is more important.
Not everyone can get divorced.
Are you saying there's a qualification for divorce?
Of course, there is.
People like Ms. Park...
won't be able to live alone even if she gets millions...
in the divorce because she's too weak.
Then how about you?
You're qualified to get divorced.
All of a sudden?
Is it also because of society's judgment for you too?
Trash should go in the trash.
Your life is precious. You should live each day well.
Even when throwing out the trash,
you have to put food waste in the food waste bin...
and usable items...
in the recycling bin after cleaning it well.
It's not that simple.
You've done recycling on your own before, right?
Yes, I live on my own.
Is that so?
- Hello, Ms. Cha. - Hi.
- Did you eat? - Did you eat?
What did you eat? Are you going to court today?
(Mom)
Yu Ri. Someone at my church said they would introduce you...
to a good guy. I'm going to set up a date.
Now that you've gotten a job, you should start dating.
Gosh.
Did you have a nice lunch?
- Yes. - Hello.
Ms. Han. Have you had coffee?
Yes, I have.
- Let's have one more. - What?
- Out of the office. - Why?
To digest our lunch and whatnot.
So did you take on the case? What did Ms. Cha say?
She said, "Why did you do that?"
She's so mean.
Ms. Han. I'm so curious. Can I ask you something?
Why do you hate doing as you're told at work?
- Me? - Yes.
Do you have unresolved feelings...
of disobedience from your childhood?
No, not at all.
I'm just...
living each moment by my conscience as a lawyer.
Conscience?
I respect you. You make life very hard on yourself.
Cha Eun Kyung is the one who makes life hard on herself.
Why can't she just tell me that I did a good job?
How is she any different from Ms. Park Jin Sook?
Why? Is Ms. Cha not going to get a divorce?
She's not.
A divorce attorney will stay with her cheating husband...
because of society's judgments. Can you believe that?
Gosh. Isn't she ashamed?
Ms. Cha isn't the type...
to avoid getting a divorce because of society's judgments.
Could it be because of her kid?
Did you also know that it was Ms. Cha?
Me? I had no idea.
I was leading the witness,
and you caught the bait.
I didn't know that happened to Ms. Cha.
If I had a wife like Ms. Cha,
I would treat her like a queen.
Mr. Jun...
You'll keep this a secret, right?
Look. I'm an attorney too, you know.
Isn't confidentiality a legal duty?
- You will, right? - I will.
Gosh.
You must sleep well even after drinking two coffees.
I fall asleep as soon as I lie down.
Wait. How did you know this was my second coffee?
Leading the witness.
Look at that.
I had a quick blind date during my lunchtime.
You caught me. That's embarrassing.
Why didn't you do it in the evening?
I need to leave work...
right on time in the evening and have chicken and beer with you.
Mr. Jun. Do you really like me?
I really like you.
Love your colleagues, love your country, right?
Let's work together for a long time.
Stop being clingy.
Why? Let's work together for a long time. Don't leave, okay?
(Attorney at law, Han Yu Ri)
No, it's okay.
Do whatever makes you feel comfortable.
Ms. Han.
Without me,
he won't have anyone to take care of him when he's old.
I don't know whether it's okay for me to leave him like this.
Did you get married to take care of him when he's old?
Didn't you get married to be happy?
My daughter is on my side,
so he'll be totally alone.
He caused that to happen.
But still.
I'm worried...
who'll take care of him when he's old and sick.
It's not just you...
that has responsibility and duty.
Do you think the defendant will take care of you when you're sick?
Gosh.
He made you sick.
If only I didn't tell him that I met with you...
A part of me feels it's right to stop things now.
If you feel that nervous,
give my phone number to her husband.
Tell him to talk to you through me.
And just block his phone number.
Do it right now.
Is that really okay?
Of course.
(Husband)
I'm not going home.
From now on, contact me through my lawyer.
Gosh.
He'll go crazy if he can't get in touch with me.
It's okay.
I told you to trust me and to follow my lead.
Here are the records of Ms. Park Jin Sook's previous consultations...
that you asked for.
- Thank you. - Of course.
Who is this?
Yes? Hello?
Hey.
Are you happy to make a living by telling lies, you punk?
Who are you?
That...
You basically wrote a novel on that petition or whatever.
Look here. It's not a novel.
Those are the grudges in Ms. Park's heart.
Did you see me swear at my wife?
Do you have evidence?
All of my friends...
beat their wives once in a while.
They don't even feel bad.
I even say sorry and buy her gifts!
Gosh. Do you want an appreciation plaque?
I'm going to sue you for false accusations!
How dare a woman...
leave her house without making food for her husband?
There's nobody in this world who wants to cook...
for someone like you. You should've treated her better.
Tell Park Jin Sook to go back home right now.
I won't let her do this.
Ms. Park...
will never go back to your house.
I'm going to make sure of that.
Hey!
If you don't stop this right away, I'm going to kill you!
You're going to kill me?
I'm going to kill you!
You...
(Conference Room)
Mr. Jung.
Are you not leaving yet?
I have a lot of work left.
I heard you got a new case.
Good job. That's not easy.
Right...
Ms. Cha told me I shouldn't have taken the case.
Thank you.
Why can't people decide to get divorced...
even in the most ridiculous situations?
Are people that cowardly?
It might not be about being cowardly. They might be scared.
No matter how strong people are,
they fear being alone.
Gosh. You're so reliable.
You can do it.
Yes. Thank you.
- Work hard. - Yes. Get home safely.
- Here you go. - Thank you.
Yes. Yesterday...
Yes. Please wrap it up like that.
Yes.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Yes. - Are you done with your radio show?
Yes. Why?
Buy me a drink.
I can't believe Jung Woo Jin asked me for a drink.
Gosh.
Back in the day, you'd bring me here...
and buy me a drink after scolding me, right?
Did you even listen to me when I was scolding you?
You were the type to say yes but not actually listen to me.
It was totally the opposite.
I acted as if I wasn't listening,
but I etched each of your words into my heart.
Back then, I was just being a bit proud.
Now, you always nag at me.
And you tell me I have a bad personality.
I'm just telling you to be gentle with the newbies.
What if they leave?
You'll be the one that Mr. Oh gets mad at.
Do you think I care about what others think of me?
You do.
Did you know Han Yu Ri accepted her first case?
Right.
I thought she'd leave soon.
She reminds me of someone's beginning of her attorney career.
Me?
What are you talking about? We're totally different.
Why did Director Kim suddenly quit giving advice?
Is he not on good terms with you?
What are you talking about? He's just busy.
You barely express your feelings...
at home or work, no?
What's the point?
It only burdens each other.
You should express yourself in at least one place.
Living like that makes your life lonely.
You never got married before.
Married couples understand each other...
more than colleagues and friends.
So sometimes you need a spouse for that function...
more than your emotions.
Because it's a long-term relationship.
But in the end, you're having a hard time.
Why am I having a hard time?
That's out of the blue.
Eun Kyung.
You know I want to be helpful, right?
What are you saying? Mind your own business.
Darn. What on earth?
Does she...
live here?
So she does live here.
Dang it.
- Seriously. - Yu Ri.
You scared me.
- Mom. - What?
You should've called.
I made some greens.
I barely eat at home.
You will if you have side dishes.
Your dad always told me...
to feed you well.
That was my highest priority.
- Mom. - Yes?
He brainwashed you.
Why is your highest priority feeding me?
You need to see it straight now.
See what straight? He was right.
My goodness.
Yet, he backstabbed you. Don't you hate him?
I thought he only had a hard time making ends meet for his family.
Now I'm glad he backstabbed me at least.
Do people go crazy when they get married?
What's wrong with me?
Come on.
- We met again. - Hi.
Yes, we met again.
Ms. Han.
Hello. Mom?
We met the other day.
The last time I talked to her,
I realized you two work for the same company.
- We're meant to be. - I know.
Meant to be, my foot.
You're not with your boyfriend today?
He was tall and handsome.
You both looked like you could live without the law.
They're not afraid of the law.
I think he's working overtime today.
I see.
I'm going to try your recipe today...
and make beef brisket doenjang stew.
- Okay. - I loved...
your doenjang stew with snails.
I'm glad.
What?
- Go ahead. - Thank you.
Get off your phone and come and eat.
- Mom. - Yes?
Will you please stop acting friendly to everyone?
What do you mean everyone?
She's your colleague and your neighbor.
Have you forgotten your neighbor turned out...
to have an affair with Dad?
It looks perfect.
You don't...
pity Dad, do you?
You should pity yourself, not Dad.
You're the victim.
Victim and perpetrator.
Does everything look like a case to you?
Regardless, you're a victim, and he's a perpetrator.
Oh, this is good.
Anyway, why didn't you...
divorce Dad...
when you realized he was cheating on you?
Just because.
Because of me?
I hesitated because...
I'd disturb your studying.
And I tried to understand your dad.
- Mom. Look. - Eat.
You got the cause and effect relationship wrong.
I'm not the victim of Dad's affair,
but you because you decided to get a divorce?
How can you come up with that thought?
Seriously, Mom. It's so frustrating.
My goodness.
Why does everyone hesitate to get a divorce?
You're frustrating me more.
Wait until you have a child.
Did you study that hard...
just to promote a divorce?
Are you saying a divorce is bad?
That it's social evils out of the blue?
Fine. Continue to live in the Joseon Dynasty.
I can't live in the Joseon Dynasty.
I'm a divorcee from the modern time.
And why do you keep ignoring my texts when you're a modern girl?
Because they're not worth my attention.
Do you want me to set the date?
Do you want me to change the password?
You got a job. Come on.
Okay! I get it!
Okay? You just said okay.
Seriously.
Try the rolled omelet.
Mom. One second.
Yes, Ms. Park Jin Sook. What brings you to call me?
Ms. Han.
Are you sure...
about continuing this?
- What? - I mean,
he said he'd never drink again.
He's begging me to drop the case.
Do you trust him?
No, he was different this time.
He used to curse at me when he was drunk...
then begged for my forgiveness when he was sober.
But this time, he's begging me even though he's drunk.
- What did he say... - What the?
this time?
He asked me to come and cook for him.
He promised to quit drinking.
So I was wondering if I should make him hangover soup.
So you want to go back...
just to cook for him?
Don't ever trust him.
He's only eaten my food until now.
I'm sick of it.
Don't make any decisions for now. I'll see you tomorrow.
Seriously.
What is wrong with everyone?
Come and eat.
Ms. Park Jin Sook.
(Emergency Center)
I told you...
he might die!
Mom!
It's not her fault.
She didn't force you to sue him.
I'm so sick of it.
Unfortunate women like me can never get divorced.
I knew this would happen.
That's why I told you I wanted to drop the suit!
Why are you being so unreasonable?
Ms. Han tried to help us.
Be quiet!
I can't stand you.
Get lost.
Leave!
Let go of me! I'm sick of this.
I'm sick and tired.
Are you back from the hospital?
How should I...
handle the case now?
Let it sit for now.
If he dies, you'll have to handle the succession of property.
If he lives,
drop the case if the client wants.
Have you been through this too?
Of course.
Lots of people...
take their lives when they're served papers.
But that's not on the attorney.
Is it not?
If they commit suicide after getting served,
is it on the prosecutor?
If they commit suicide after being urged to pay taxes,
is that on the tax collector?
It's not.
You had a hesitant client,
and with a misguided sense of duty and poor sense of justice,
you made her sign the divorce papers.
You shouldn't have done that.
Do you also think I goaded her to get divorced?
I didn't say that.
What are you saying I should've done?
Please tell my mom to get divorced.
I never say that.
A divorce attorney doesn't decide who gets divorced.
Separate your personalities.
Han Yu Ri the attorney and Han Yu Ri the person.
Han Yu Ri the attorney can't blurt out...
what Han Yu Ri the person thinks.
Separate my personalities...
Instead of starting with you,
you should've started with...
the client's urge and wish to punish her husband.
Ms. Han?
Yes?
That was me trying to console you.
(Attorney at law, Cha Eun Kyung)
(Attorney at law, Han Yu Ri)
(Attorney at law, Jun Eun Ho)
How will he react...
when he gets the written complaint?
We'll have to see when he gets it.
How will he react if I move out?
What do you think?
He'll feel and realize you're actually breaking up.
Can she go back for the stuff she left behind?
Some will be cooperative.
It depends on the person.
That's enough for now.
What if the mother-in-law finds out? Will she call?
What happens to the rented water purifier...
when we divide our assets?
Do I have to pay it off?
The mother-in-law might or might not call.
And the person who paid the rental feel keeps paying it.
- Then... - Stop.
What if...
you get divorced now? How much can you get?
How much can I get?
Zero.
I don't think there are any assets to split.
I told you...
my husband inherited three million dollars.
Listen carefully.
You said he received the inheritance a month ago.
And you've been married for two years.
What if the court says you've been married...
for too short a time so you don't get a cut?
What? Then he doesn't get a divorce.
Then you shouldn't get divorced.
Then what must I do...
if I want to get at least half?
In that case...
I'll see you in 20 years.
What? In 20 years?
What kind of rule is that?
If you have any more questions,
- call this number again. - Okay.
I have another consultation right after this.
I need you to leave. I'm sorry.
Did you have lunch?
I know a nice tteokbokki place nearby.
If you'd like that.
- What? - If you have more questions,
- give me a call. - Okay.
- Twenty years? - Bye. Get back safely.
(Attorney at law, Han Yu Ri)
Let's get an ice cream.
What?
An ice cream?
"What if?" "What then?"
I hated those phrases in Korean and English classes.
- What did you do? - The obvious.
Eye for an eye, tooth for a tooth, what if for a what if.
I asked them questions in the same manner. That's best.
I'm envious of you.
Why is it so hard for me?
That's because you're sympathetic.
You keep thinking about the other person.
It's tough, isn't it?
When he called to say he was going to die,
did I have to take action?
That's on the person who threatened you with suicide.
Why should you take action?
What if...
He won't die, will he?
Don't mind it too much.
People like that tend to do things for show.
You seemed like an actual senior then.
That's a lot of strength.
(Park Jin Sook, client)
Open wide.
- Come on. - No.
- Open up. - I won't eat!
You must eat to go home.
Why should I even be here?
Why do you think you're here?
Darn it.
Just eat, you nuisance.
Whose fault could it be? It's yours!
- Why you... - Oh, gosh.
What are you doing?
Oh, hello, Ms. Han.
Goodness.
It's nothing. He's just being silly.
I just realized...
I was worried for no reason.
- Darn it. - Say you're sorry.
- That hurt! - You troublemaker.
Ms. Han. Come with me.
(General Ward A)
The lawsuit.
I bet she will drop the case down the line.
I'll drop it.
It's my rotten luck.
Someone like me can never get divorced.
Why would you say that?
A divorce...
is something for the rich and smart.
I really hope...
this incident changes your husband.
Goodness.
Ms. Cha.
Here.
Why are you here?
You've been through a lot, Ms. Park.
What brought you all the way here?
Ms. Park...
will drop the lawsuit.
Don't hope this incident will change your husband.
After time, his old ways will set in.
What is she doing?
The darn fool.
Come back when you're determined and convinced.
Regardless of how many consultations you had,
we'll take on your case for you, okay?
Thank you, Ms. Cha.
You even gave me a refund.
How about you attend couple therapy?
We'll put you in touch with an alcoholism specialist.
Pay for five sessions at once, and you even get a discount.
I see.
- Thank you. - Sure.
Then...
Goodbye.
Bye.
Will you just eat?
Goodness.
(Seoun University Hospital)
You told me to let her go.
Why did you come to win her back?
Despite a massive incident like an attempted suicide,
after a while, he'll go back to his old ways.
That's when she'll make up her mind and finally decide to leave him.
There comes a moment...
where you just accept everything.
And care only of the future.
Your husband is having an affair.
I know.
Are you not going to divorce him?
What do I get out of it?
Things are running smoothly at home and at work.
I need them.
He made you sick.
If only I didn't tell him that I met with you...
And I tried to understand your dad.
Ms. Cha.
What does it mean...
to be married?
- Why you... - It's my rotten luck.
Someone like me can never get divorced.
How can you feed someone who tormented you?
My daughter is getting married soon.
I hesitated because...
If her wedding is called off because of my divorce,
I won't be able to stand it.
I'd disturb your studying.
How can you put up with it for your children?
Strangers who have become family?
(Law Firm Daejeong)
(Attorney at law, Han Yu Ri)
Hey.
What is it now?
I apologize, Ms. Cha.
I can no longer work on the divorce team.
What are you on about?
Is it because of the attempted suicide?
I don't want to...
work at the expense of separating...
Han Yu Ri the attorney and Han Yu Ri the person.
Don't cling to what I said.
I think...
I see the assailant and victim...
way too clearly to be able to work on divorce cases.
Are you angry you couldn't get Ms. Park divorced,
or was your ego bruised...
because your case went how I said it would?
It's neither.
I made the call because I don't see...
my future.
Fine, then go. You never listen.
Leave.
- And Ms. Cha. - What else is there?
Your husband goes to Ms. Choi's place for dinner.
It could be that they live together.
How do you know that?
Ms. Choi lives in my building.
(Jung-gu Chungam-ro 214, One Space Studio Apartment)
Ms. Cha.
The affair with Ms. Choi.
I wasn't being nosy.
I just wanted to be on your side.
You can go.
(Jung-gu Chungam-ro 214, One Space Studio Apartment)
You're helpless.
Let me.
- I can manage. - I'll do it.
- You're hurt? - I got you.
You scared me.
Let me do the carrying.
- I'll help. - Carry this, then.
Just this?
Were you going to carry that?
- You're all grown up. - Goodness.
- It's fine. - No, let me.
- Come along. - My gosh. Let's go.
- What is it? - Nothing.
There comes a moment where you just accept everything.
And care only of the future.
Ms. Cha?
Your misguided sense of duty and poor sense of justice.
I like it.
- What? - You want to punish them, right?
I'll let you do that.
Did you actually drop by the studio apartment?
I didn't accept your resignation.
I want you to take my case.
(Good Partner)
How long have you known?
Affair partners always ask that.
They must really want to know.
There's a rumor that Sa Ra had an affair with a married man.
What will Mom and Dad do?
About the divorce.
I'll reveal how selfish you were...
and what kind of mom you were.
Will you be okay with that?
Ms. Cha!
What I read in the tabloids. Is it true?