(Good Partner)
(Divorce)
(In session)
(Plaintiff)
(Cha Eun Kyung)
(Han Yu Ri)
(Good Partner)
(All people, locations, organizations,)
(incidents, and backstories in this drama are fictitious.)
(Staff ensured child actors' safety in the filming of this drama.)
Why are we even here?
Mom, I'm not going in.
(May you rest in peace)
How did this happen?
A month ago, he was diagnosed with late-stage pancreatic cancer.
Then you should've called.
We're not exactly on speaking terms.
We're not,
but...
He's Yu Ri's dad.
You should've let her say goodbye one last time.
She can bid farewell today.
- What? - Hey!
Bid farewell and get going.
Don't talk that way to my daughter!
Who are you to come here and cause a scene?
Mom, it's fine.
Don't bother with her. Let's go.
Say goodbye to your father.
You were punished for betraying us.
That day,
both women in my dad's life...
cried...
for different reasons.
Ms. Han?
And right here...
It's another tale of two women.
(Case 02: Two Women)
Ms. Cha!
Why is it that I'm always caught in these situations?
Why?
I see you're still at the office.
I came by for the sentencing statement.
Ms. Cha, what brings you by at this hour?
I came to pick up some documents,
and I saw that the light was on in your office.
Things have been hectic with my case,
so I took the time to finally give myself a tour of the building.
I see.
(Relaxing Room)
Ms. Cha.
I'll be heading off from here.
Sure. I'll grab a cab further down the road.
Got it. Get home safely, then.
You too.
(Episode 2)
- Hello? - This is T Hotel.
(Hanareum Family Medical Clinic)
Nurse Oh, can you help her?
Sure, Doctor.
- Have a good day. - Thank you.
Thanks.
This is T Hotel.
You may check in after 3pm on Friday.
(Attorney at law, Cha Eun Kyung)
Come in.
Ms. Cha.
Kim Min Jeong and Kim Jun Hui who booked a consultation...
have arrived at the lobby.
Is that so?
Should I escort them to the VIP conference room?
The family has a lot of assets, I believe?
The plaintiff Kim Min Jeong is filing for divorce...
from a defendant worth six million dollars.
He's the son of Assemblyman Park Hyeok Se.
The same Park Hyeok Se...
who made the headlines regarding his succession of assets?
That's right.
I should aim to win a high percentage of them.
Escort them to the VIP conference room and...
Have Ms. Han join me.
Don't you usually take on VIP cases alone?
We have two plaintiffs.
Have Ms. Han join me.
Sure.
(Law Firm Daejeong)
I didn't doubt him at first.
It's snowing.
It's snow which you love.
Why don't we buy more of this...
to take with us when we go camping with Jun Hui?
I love that idea.
Ma'am, can we get five portions of tteokbokki to go?
- Sure. - Thanks.
I can't imagine how it would've been...
if you hadn't introduced Jun Hui's family to us.
The kids are fond of each other too.
Who knew I'd get to have a relationship...
with my wife's friend from middle school?
I'm the one who's grateful.
Most husbands would hate the idea of going on trips...
with their wife's male friend and his family.
Why? I absolutely love it.
Jun Hui thinks of me like a big brother.
Gosh, it's cold. It's cold, isn't it?
Your seat belt.
That's when I saw that minx's handprint.
We sleep in different rooms due to my snoring.
But it's cold.
That should've been a red flag.
That punk was looking at my wife with love in his eyes but...
Min Seok?
- Oh, hey. - I didn't question it at all.
Mi Jin and I were talking about what food to pack...
for our camping trip this weekend.
I must've fallen asleep.
I see.
Guys, it's late. You should both go to bed.
I'll see you soon.
Sure thing.
Like clueless fools, we...
We went camping together every weekend.
- There he is. - They're pure evil.
Here's your grilled meat.
Here you go, guys.
- Right? - Here you go.
Pass them along.
We have tangerines.
- Pass it along. - Pass it along.
Mom, can't I have soda before having the tangerine?
I'm afraid you can't.
- Just this once. - You can't.
I already said no to soda. Have water instead.
- Do you want some soda? - Yes.
Let's have it just for today.
- I'll get you some. - No.
But we're out camping.
When else would you have soda if not on a day like this?
I'll allow it today...
- since we're out camping. - Sure.
Isn't your dad the best?
- It's soda, your favorite. - Nice.
The moms should head to the caravan with the kids.
The dads will clean up the rest.
Min Seok, I'm afraid I have some bad news.
The heating system in our unit is out of order.
Really?
But it'll be cold in the night.
Let's all sleep in ours.
Are you sure?
But we'll be putting you out.
Why would you say that when we're practically family?
Kids, I have some good news for you.
We'll all be sleeping together today!
- Come on. Let's go. - Let's go.
Go on. Head on inside.
Let's hurry inside.
I must've had too much water.
It was as if I were awake in my own nightmare.
I should've killed them both in that very moment.
I had no idea...
that the handprint I had seen was actually hers.
We began to talk and the pieces of the puzzle...
finally came together.
I contemplated whether I had to tell him.
The pain was insufferable,
and I didn't know...
if I should inflict that on my friend as well.
But not telling him...
was even worse.
I see.
Did your wife admit to the affair?
At first, she said it was nonsense.
But she admitted it after seeing the camera footage we had.
We have a recording of her saying so.
I see.
Ms. Kim, do you have additional evidence?
Yes, photos of their trips together I found on his phone...
and the texts they exchanged.
I have screenshots of them all.
Everything will go well...
since you managed to collect the necessary evidence.
Ms. Kim, your husband comes from money.
You should aim for a big payout.
Am I entitled to that...
when he received most of it from his father?
His father's reputation as an assemblyman is at stake,
so I'll request mediation.
Ms. Kim will be a plaintiff in one case,
and Mr. Kim will be a plaintiff in the other.
There will be two separate cases.
Let's fight this.
Sure.
All right.
Here's our tteokbokki.
Try it.
All you're getting me are gimbap and tteokbokki?
Seriously?
This is a place for hipsters, and it's not easy to get seats.
On top of that, it wasn't easy getting this window seat.
Unbelievable.
Try this as well. It's so good.
Maybe it's because I'm having something tasty,
but I feel better.
It's good, right? What did I tell you?
To be honest, I went on a job search site yesterday.
A job search site? Are you kidding me?
Have you forgotten that we're a top law firm?
It's hard to get a job here,
so why would you resign so easily?
Mr. Jun, do you like being a divorce attorney?
You've been here for three months, so tell me how it is.
Hold on. How did you know that?
You know I've only been here for three months.
I thought you had been here for at least a few years...
judging by how you played the seniority card.
It's only by three months, but I'm still your senior.
I honestly thought that divorce cases would be fun.
I love TV drama series. Especially soap operas.
You became a divorce lawyer...
because of your love for soap operas?
That's right. It's fun.
Why make it harder for yourself...
by opting to research materials and case studies...
for mergers and acquisitions as well as criminal cases?
The thought of it gives me a headache.
I find that to be more fun.
She has one heck of an ego.
Fine, smarty-pants.
Yu Ri,
you seem to be talking casually to me.
Is it because we graduated in the same year?
Since that's the case, I'm sure I can speak casually.
That's a bit too soon,
but if speaking casually to me will help you be more relaxed...
at the office, I'll gladly allow it.
Just don't resign.
I bet you don't know how many new lawyers we hired...
over the past three months.
Why is he being like a lost puppy?
The clients must not have been happy about having...
to switch lawyers frequently.
You have no idea. That's why Ms. Cha was up to her neck in work.
She met clients in one place, listened to others complain,
and handled all the cases outside the city.
I developed nothing but respect for her.
Ms. Cha's daughter...
must only see her mom's face on TV.
Darn it. He's having an affair because his wife is busy with work.
Ms. Han, don't be like that...
and hang tight for one month.
The firm pays for lunch,
so coffee will always be on me.
It's fine. Why would you buy me coffee?
I want to, that's all.
Seriously.
- Are you interested in me? - What?
Loving your peers is the same as loving your country.
And together...
Didn't you know?
Dig in.
Give it a month, okay?
Ms. Han, are you working late tonight?
Yes, I still have a few things to go over.
We'll head home, then.
Sure thing. Good night.
Shall we?
See you tomorrow.
- Enjoy your evening. - See you tomorrow.
Let's get a few more drinks.
- Sure. They'll be on me. - Let's head inside.
Hi, do you have an empty table?
What?
You normally have the basic gimbap because you're short on time,
so I'm surprised you ordered tteokbokki too.
And the spicier one, might I add.
Spill.
It's nothing. I like the food, that's all.
Don't tell me it's what I'm thinking.
- Not yet. - Not yet?
(Attorney at law, Han Yu Ri)
I thought she was working overtime,
but she was writing her resignation.
Her too?
She thinks divorce lawyers...
just listen to clients whine and complain.
She won't last long.
How about giving her a 20-percent raise?
I'm not sure...
money will have a hold on her.
I noticed...
she wasn't too happy about her first win.
Is that why?
If she insists on leaving, soothe her.
Forget it. Why would I do that?
I shouldn't give her a chance to talk.
Eun Kyung.
Who would give you such advice if I'm gone?
Don't be so cold to the staff.
Don't make enemies.
What's going on? Are you going somewhere?
Where would I go?
(In session)
(2024-682, Plaintiff Kim, Defendants Park, Choi)
(Plaintiff)
Plaintiffs Kim Min Jeong and Kim Jun Hui are friends.
Out of consideration for their spouses,
after their separate marriages,
instead of meeting alone, the families went camping together.
Then their respective spouses had an affair,
and now they're suing for divorce and alimony.
Also...
the families spent weekends together as if they were one big family,
so please take into consideration that the plaintiffs'...
psychological duress would be as great as if their spouses...
had committed a crime you'd consider much worse.
(Plaintiff)
(Defendant)
Play the video.
What did you tell your wife?
That I'd go to exercise.
That's boring. Come up with better lies.
- She might suspect you. - This is a workout.
(Mich Hotel)
That's true.
Didn't we come here once before?
That motel behind an apartment complex.
This is a new place.
We've been to so many I got confused.
Let's go.
Defending counsel.
Do you admit to the affair?
It's true that...
my clients were filmed entering a motel,
but they are just good friends and there was no sexual intercourse.
As you know, we don't have to prove...
they had intercourse to say it was an affair.
The fact that Defendants One and Two were lovers...
We're in love.
Look up, Mi Jin. We did nothing wrong.
Be seated.
Your Honor.
Please put the defendant's claim in the record.
He admitted to his wrongdoing.
Yes, fine. Record it.
Defendant Two.
Do you admit to the affair?
If you call it an affair, then that's what it must be,
but we loved with all our hearts and are not ashamed.
Very well.
If Defendant One Choi Mi Jin takes the same position,
instead of continuing in court,
how about we try to...
settle this out of court?
Yes, well, I'd like to end this amicably with an agreement.
My wife will get a divorce,
but not custody. I'll keep the kid.
We can discuss the custody of your child...
during the hearing of the case...
your wife submitted where you're Defendant One.
Mr. Kim Jun Hui is the plaintiff in this case,
and Mr. Park, you're Defendant Two, the affair partner.
Don't mention your child here.
Exactly.
Seung Woo.
I want to raise him.
Drop it.
You don't mean your child...
but Seung Woo,
the child of Kim Jun Hui and Choi Mi Jin?
Yes.
Your Honor, could you include this in the record too?
Defendant Two, please sit.
Defendant One,
do you take the same position?
Yes. I want to raise our kids with him.
(Defendant)
The next hearing will be a negotiation.
On that day,
Park Min Seok's wife and Choi Mi Jin's husband...
will attend as participants to voice their opinions.
Let's talk this out with all four present.
Let's sit and rest a bit.
- You did well. - Thank you.
- Sir? - Hello.
What do you want?
As you know, Mr. Park's father is a well-known assemblyman.
He wouldn't want his son in the press.
That's none of your business.
Wouldn't you prefer a settlement...
to a written judgment stating a divorce?
Bring us a good offer.
We'll be waiting.
Let's go.
- Why that... - It's okay.
What were you talking about?
The easiest route.
You'll see next time.
Why do you say there's not enough proof?
When that woman and I exchanged glances,
I swear she gave me the side-eye.
She's the affair partner. I know it.
Yes, but...
we can't replicate that side-eye for the court.
I asked you to try to record your husband...
confessing to having an affair.
- Did you give that a go? - I did.
But he denied having an affair.
What did you do?
You didn't ask the question I told you never to ask, did you?
I asked if he slept with her or not.
I was so angry I couldn't help it.
If anyone asked...
"Did you sleep with her or not," I doubt anyone would say yes.
If you keep this up,
you'll get fewer and fewer chances to collect proof.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello, Ms. Cha.
Did you do well?
Sure you did. See you.
Hello.
He left right on time.
(Attorney at law, Han Yu Ri)
Darn it.
"You'll see next time?"
She's horrible at communicating.
No wonder her husband's fooling around.
(True affair stories from a divorce lawyer)
So,
is it true that most affairs happen...
- close to home? - My gosh.
- Most affairs happen close to home. - Darn it.
Should I see her face after work too?
Work colleagues, neighbors, friends' spouses.
It's even common among relatives.
- Gosh. - Is it common for one to be...
unaware when the spouse is having an affair with someone close?
Yes. Your spouse's affair is always someone around you.
Some people took years to catch on...
when their spouse was cheating with their neighbor.
With their neighbor?
- I don't think your husband... - Don't you talk like...
- would do anything like that. - you're in the clear.
Right? Yes?
(Attorney at law, Han Yu Ri)
Should I tell her?
(Cha Eun Kyung)
Oh, thank you.
The weather's amazing.
Here we go.
I thought I'd go to hotel lounges to drink...
when I became an attorney.
Are you looking down on convenience store cup noodles?
Look at the cherry blossoms. Aren't they pretty?
The petals are flying everywhere.
Hotel lounges are for people who are used to going there.
Smarty-pants don't start going...
out of the blue because they became attorneys.
Darn you.
I used to study in libraries and drink vending-machine coffee.
Now I'm typing petitions...
and drinking convenience store beer.
Nothing has changed.
I get your sob story.
Why did you call me over here when I clocked off?
We had lunch together.
- A friend's friend... - Yes.
saw her friend's husband...
making out with someone else.
But she's so torn as to whether...
she should tell the wife.
What would you do?
Me? I'd tell right away.
Don't I look like the type?
Yes, you do.
You're going too far over the line just because we're closer.
Sorry.
But...
maybe it's best not to know.
How is it best not to know? It's best to know.
Isn't it a waste to spend time and energy...
on a traitor?
That's why you'd tell the wife?
You bet.
If I found out even later on that my wife cheated on me,
I'd end it right then.
Why stay together when half the world is made up of women?
Even if half the world is women,
you made the hard choice of settling with one.
And I got unlucky.
I can say I made the wrong choice and try again.
It must be nice to be so simple.
You called me over to discuss something so simple?
What should we have for lunch tomorrow?
(Seoul Family Court)
Why are you staring at me?
Ms. Cha.
(Letter of Resignation)
I can't let her talk.
- I... - If you want to talk,
how about you wait until this case is done?
Wouldn't it be too late then?
Why would it be late?
- It's better than being premature. - What?
What is she talking about?
You asked what I told the defending counsel...
after the previous hearing.
Was that an attempt to settle?
I mentioned the assemblyman father.
I should hope the attorney got the message.
It was my way of suggesting he spend a little more...
on the settlement to preserve his honor.
There could be a custody battle,
so I don't think they'll bargain with money.
Is there anything that money can't solve?
What money can't solve...
is human emotion.
She'll quit even if I give her a raise?
Okay. Point taken.
Are you Kim Min Jeong?
I'm Choi Mi Jin.
That's the plaintiff's side. You sit over here.
Right.
You would be confused.
It's not a family gathering. The defendants sit together.
Don't mind her.
Can we submit our offer first?
Let's hear what Kim Jun Hui is prepared to offer Choi Mi Jin.
Okay.
The couple's assets amount to about 500,000 dollars.
They were married for less than ten years,
and Ms. Choi had no income for the duration of the marriage.
The contribution of household labor is valued at 20 percent,
so we're willing to give her about 100,000 dollars.
The father will have custody...
and he wants 500 dollars in child support a month.
Ms. Choi, what do you say?
Well...
I didn't earn anything,
but I can't leave with just 100,000 dollars.
From what I heard,
other women got at least half.
You weren't married for that long,
and you lived in the house that Mr. Kim's parents got him...
when he married...
which went up in value. You didn't actually contribute,
so you don't get half.
Does this even make sense?
And I want custody of our child.
You had an affair with the dad of your son's best friend...
and you want custody?
Could you...
face Seung Woo after what you did?
I raised him.
He can't live without me.
You can't live without him.
(Defendant)
Excuse me.
Will you hear our offer?
- Let's do that. - Okay.
As mentioned in court during the previous hearing,
My client Mr. Park wants to raise...
all three children,
the children of both couples.
You lunatic.
You're saying that again?
Why would you raise my kid?
Will you hear me out first?
In return, Park Min Seok will give plaintiff Kim Min Jeong...
thirty percent of his assets,
which is about two million dollars,
and Kim Jun Hui won't have to give Choi Mi Jin anything.
That's the condition.
That means he doesn't need the 100,000 dollars...
Ms. Cha offered.
You psycho.
Are you saying you'll buy my kid?
I knew you were a nutcase,
but you're worse than I thought.
That's a no.
Speak up. Say no.
Let me think.
Did you stop to think about...
how confusing it would be for the kids who'll have to call...
a family friend "Mom" and "Dad?"
This is child abuse.
The court should not allow this.
Think realistically.
You can work your whole life and never make two million.
The international school you mentioned.
I'm thinking about it.
You made an unexpected counter offer,
and we need time to think about it.
Give us a few days, and we'll have a response.
- Yes, let's do that. - Sure.
Thanks.
We're colleagues on the same side.
How dare you glare at me in front of the mediators?
Ms. Cha. This isn't right.
What do you mean? Elaborate.
It won't be a normal environment for their kids to grow up together.
Their case might set a precedent...
as a special case regarding child abuse law.
I see. Go on.
Shouldn't that absurd settlement...
have been dismissed immediately at the mediation?
Are you a police officer?
A social worker?
You're an attorney for the plaintiff.
That's precisely why I'm bringing this up.
You heard when Mr. Kim Jun Hui said he couldn't accept the settlement.
What about Ms. Kim Min Jeong?
There's no way she would give up...
on her children for two million dollars.
Everything must seem simple to you. Good for you.
Pardon?
You think whatever you like and act as if that's the truth.
If Ms. Kim chooses the money,
does it mean she's abandoning her children?
Did it not cross your mind...
that she might choose the money for her children's sake?
Do you know the cost...
of the annual tuition for an international school?
It's higher than your annual salary.
No parent would choose...
money over their children.
We're their representatives.
Because we are their representatives,
we're obligated to inform them...
about the pain the children will feel...
and the implications of agreeing to the settlement.
Ms. Kim will know better than anyone...
about the pain her children will face, not you.
Cha Eun Kyung is getting weirder with each passing day.
Gosh. Seriously.
- Hello. - Hello.
Is she that blinded by the incentive?
(Law Firm Daejeong)
Hello.
If she's getting a huge incentive,
it means her clients are getting a big incentive too.
Isn't that a win-win situation?
No! It's not a win-win situation or anything like that.
They're trying to make her choose between her children and money.
Ms. Han. Don't get emotionally involved.
You're overstepping your boundaries.
If you keep this up, it will only burden you.
I'm serious.
- Ms. Han. - Yes?
Come here for a second.
- Hello. - Did you eat?
- Yes. - Hi.
- Did you eat? - Yes.
Well, I had a question.
Let's say you saw the spouse of your acquaintance...
having an affair.
Then would you tell your acquaintance...
about the affair or not?
Is this about a case?
No, I was just curious about your answer.
I would have told my acquaintance right away.
But I was wondering how you would handle it.
I've got this.
I would pretend to be clueless.
What?
Why should I get myself involved in someone else's business?
Well, I would wait and see until my acquaintance handles it...
on their own.
It's completely different from what I would do.
By the way,
Director Kim Ji Sang doesn't come to the firm every day, right?
No. He works at an internal medicine clinic in his neighborhood.
He comes to the firm from time to time as an advisor.
I see.
I never got to say hello.
I'll introduce him to you soon.
Okay.
If I have to give her...
some of my assets, then I'll do it.
He wants to cover up what he did with money.
So I don't want to be a part of that or feed his arrogance.
I'm glad to hear that.
Let's fight for custody until the end...
and ensure the ruling states that he committed adultery.
He must bear that label...
- for the rest of his life. - Right.
At best, the alimony will be 20,000 dollars.
If you accept the settlement they offered,
you'll have saved 100,000 dollars. Do you understand that?
Yes. I've made up my mind.
I think your wife might get custody of your child.
Pretending to be generous and agreeing to the settlement...
might be a more cost-effective way for you to save some money.
No.
Let's say you were in my shoes.
Your husband cheated on you.
But he tried to throw money at you to avoid getting the ruling.
Could you forgive him?
I'm not saying you should forgive her.
I'm advising you to face reality.
You may think like this because it's only 100,000 dollars.
But things must be different for two million dollars.
Ms. Kim?
Hey. Gosh.
Could I get one more drink?
Sure.
I'll just be a piece of trash.
Hey.
Will you take the money instead of your children?
It's 2 million dollars, not 200,000 dollars.
Park Min Seok will justify his adultery...
and think he's not guilty anymore by paying you that amount.
You can only say that because you have a good career.
My children go to English kindergarten...
and wear designer clothes. That's the only life they know of.
If they come with me, I can't give them the same life.
My parents run a restaurant in the countryside.
They have no time to help me with my children.
All of his assets belong to his father.
So if I were to take it to trial, I wouldn't get much anyway.
I have 2 children, not 1.
I can't raise them.
Handing over the custody rights...
doesn't mean you're giving up being their mother.
It can be the contrary.
Non-custodial parents miss their children even more,
so they become more loving and get along with their children.
You've made the right decision.
Even if you don't have a fancy career,
your children will want to live with their mother.
They wouldn't want to live with their father's lover.
The kids are very good friends.
They will think of it as going camping every day.
Won't they be happy together?
That's just absurd. Don't try to justify your decision.
Then that jerk won't lose anything.
Why do you think Park Min Seok offered that much money?
Mr. Kim. Just like you said, do you think he was being arrogant?
He had always been arrogant.
He's trying to use his money to walk all over us.
Perhaps, he understands...
the seriousness of his mistake.
He probably wants to forgive himself by paying a fortune.
You don't think Park Min Seok is losing anything?
Money.
He will lose two million dollars.
He will become a man who has his wife, his family,
and his money, two million dollars.
He will have lost the most from this lawsuit.
So don't think of it as losing to him.
You're winning it.
When her children grow up,
they might think their father took care of them until the end...
while they remember their mother as someone who left them.
Ms. Han.
Why are you judging her?
You've crossed the line.
Apologize to her.
I'm sorry.
I kept thinking about it from your children's point of view.
So I overstepped.
Whatever decision you make,
the decision you make is the best decision.
Don't feel guilty.
Only focus on how to make the best of...
both of your situations.
We will represent you in whatever direction you set.
(Seoul Family Court)
The defendants offered a settlement the last time we met.
Plaintiffs, what have you decided?
(Judge)
I will accept it.
Ms. Kim Min Jeong. What about you?
Yes. I'll accept it too.
Once the four of you sign it,
the case will be closed.
Plaintiff Kim Min Jeong and Defendant Park Min Seok...
will divorce.
Defendant Park Min Seok will be the custodial parent.
The defendant will give the plaintiff...
two million dollars as a division of assets.
Plaintiff Kim Jun Hui...
and Defendant Choi Mi Jin will divorce.
Defendant Choi Mi Jin will be the custodial parent.
The plaintiff will not pay her child support...
or divide his assets with the defendant.
(Plaintiff)
(Kim Jun Hui)
All right. All the proceedings have been finalized.
Thank you, everyone.
Wait.
Hold on.
Mi Jin.
Our son...
Raise him well.
If he asks...
why I'm not living with him anymore,
tell him I'm living near my office...
because I have to make a lot more money.
Don't tell him about your affair.
Okay?
Let him have some soda. Okay?
Okay. I'll do that.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
Right here,
I see another pair of women crying.
How will they live their lives after this point?
When...
did their once-happy lives veer onto...
this miserable path?
Mr. Kim was completely against it.
Why did he have a change of heart?
I sent him the household investigation report.
Did you check it?
Did my son...
really say these things...
to the household investigators?
Yes.
It seems he's already figured out what's going on.
Even before they asked him anything,
he said he would like to live with his mother.
He said his mother needed him.
I still think it's a crazy idea that all of their children...
will live together.
You're so naive. Why did you let yourself get fixated on that idea?
Do you really think they'll move in together?
That's what all cheating spouses say in court.
That they will have a life together.
Do they think saying that will make them look less evil?
They won't move in together. Just watch.
But still. Ms. Kim lost her children to him.
She didn't lose them. She let him hold onto them.
Ta-da.
This is my new house.
- Mom. - Yes?
With her visitation right, she'll get to see them often.
The kids will slowly start saying they want to live with their mom.
Can you call Dad?
Park Min Seok...
became the custodial parent to justify what he did.
He'll be busy pretty soon. He'll want to send the kids to her.
- Hey, my daughter. - Dad.
I didn't get to see the glow-in-the-dark stairs again.
Could I sleep over at Mom's house?
So we can see them before we come back?
Sure. Okay. I'm in the middle of an important meeting.
Spend a few more nights at your mom's house.
Okay. I love you, Dad.
I love you too.
He enjoys taking down people.
Once the referee leaves, his passion will subside.
The custody battle to change the custodial parent is tough.
Just because the kids want to live with their mom,
they can't change the custodial parent immediately.
Come on.
What could the legal system do if the kids just moved in with her?
As you know, by law, she can't be forced to hand over the kids.
Right.
She will have her own property...
and get the kids back.
This is a complete victory for her.
Well, it was inevitable that the kids...
were bound to be hurt by this.
Our job is to maximize...
our clients' profits in the given situation.
Ms. Kim got her own house.
Ms. Han.
You'll get a new bag.
- Pardon? - Drive us to a shop.
What?
Am I going to buy a new bag?
We closed Ms. Kim's case with the two-million-dollar settlement.
Do you know how much we're getting for our incentive?
It will be a hard number to beat...
for the rest of your career as an attorney.
No. I'm happy with the bag I have now.
No. I'm not happy with it.
Let's see.
(1,500 dollars, 1,300 dollars)
She asked me to show you bags that can fit A4 computer paper.
Try this on.
I see. Thank you.
I'm double-booked.
(Wedding anniversary)
One, two, three.
- Happy wedding anniversary. - Happy wedding anniversary.
My gosh. I can't believe I'm celebrating...
a wedding anniversary. It's all thanks to you.
I wanted to come sooner.
No. I know you work at a law firm. It's not easy to get off work early.
I'll make partner soon. So be more patient.
- Things will get better. - Yes.
Of course, it will. Here's to my cool wife.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
I'll make a lot more money and buy you the watch...
I couldn't buy when we got married.
Gosh. I'm good.
Spending time with you like this is the best gift.
And...
Ta-da.
- Open it. - What is it?
What is it?
Do you like it?
You check the watch often.
Every time you check, you'll think of me.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Hello.
Is there anything you're looking for?
I'm here to pick up my order.
Are you Attorney Cha Eun Kyung?
- Yes, I am. - No way.
One second.
Is this right?
- Yes. - I'm a big fan of yours.
I love "All About Divorce."
I watched the recent episode too.
How can that jerk have an affair with his wife's friend?
I'm sorry, but can I have your autograph?
- Sure. - One moment, please.
(To Hye Rin)
(Have a happy family!)
(Cha Eun Kyung)
Thank you.
Ms. Cha.
- Are you done? - Yes.
Thank you.
Ms. Han.
I'm sorry, but were you with Ms. Cha?
- Yes. - Did she go home?
Yes, she went home. Why do you ask?
Nothing.
Is it common for one to be unaware...
when the spouse is having an affair with someone close?
Your spouse's affair is always someone around you.
(Attorney at law, Han Yu Ri)
The 16th floor CCTV footage?
We can only open it to partner lawyers.
This is Ms. Cha Eun Kyung's order.
Okay.
(Wedding Anniversary)
I'm home to get changed.
Are you coming to the hotel?
(I'm home to get changed. Are you coming to the hotel?)
Mom.
Are you still up?
When is Dad's conference going to end?
What's taking him so long?
I'll ask him.
Dad always says he'll be home soon.
I miss Dad.
Yes. Go to bed.
I'm going out for a second.
I'll see you at the hotel.
Last Monday...
Here.
(Monday, March 11, 2024)
So, Yu Ri wants japchae?
- A lot of mushrooms, please. - Get them.
You can add any mushroom.
Hello.
Oh, honey. That's Ms. Kim from my work.
- You know her, right? - Oh, hi.
She moved to our neighborhood recently.
- Hello. - Hello, ma'am.
We should meet more often.
Yes, you should come over.
Thank you.
- See you tomorrow. - Yes, see you at work.
Anything else? Did you say you were buying meat?
Yes.
- Sure. Let's go. - Yes.
I contemplated whether I had to tell him.
I didn't know if I should inflict that on my friend as well.
But not telling him...
was even worse.
Did you have to...
come all the way to my house at this hour?
Yes, I've always wanted to tell you this.
Sure. Go ahead. Say it now.
I have a place to go. Hurry.
Your husband.
Dr. Kim Ji Sang.
He's having an affair.
So?
What?
Your husband...
is having an affair.
I know.
What?
Then...
do you know with whom he's having an affair?
I know that too.
Choi Sa Ra.
There's no way a wife doesn't know her husband's having an affair.
They can tell with all their senses.
There are only people who failed to obtain the evidence.
(Good Partner)
You had a boyfriend?
I'll introduce him to you when I get a chance.
Are you not going to divorce him?
What do I get out of it?
How can you let them get away with it?
When he called to say he was going to die,
did I...
have to take action?
I can no longer work on the divorce team.