(Good Partner)
(Divorce)
(In session)
(Plaintiff)
(Cha Eun Kyung)
(Han Yu Ri)
(Good Partner)
(All people, locations, organizations,)
(incidents, and backstories in this drama are fictitious.)
(Staff ensured child actors' safety in the filming of this drama.)
Ms. Cha?
Your misguided sense of duty and poor sense of justice.
I like it.
What?
I want you to take my case.
(Plaintiff Cha Eun Kyung, Defendant Choi Sa Ra)
(Plaintiff Cha Eun Kyung, Defendant Kim Ji Sang)
(Plaintiff Evidence 3)
Were you...
preparing for this all along?
This is what I do for a living.
Wouldn't I have gathered evidence?
You said you wouldn't get divorced.
I gathered it to avoid a divorce.
Because as you know, the guilty can't sue for divorce.
I wanted to use the proof to stay married.
But...
you saw it for yourself.
I saw for myself...
and what I said to myself became meaningless in an instant.
It was hard, wasn't it?
I'm Cha Eun Kyung.
Skip the consolation.
Then what is it you want me to do?
Let's put on the most perfect divorce show the world has seen.
What?
A divorce show?
Court and media trials are all a show...
of fitting facts to the evidence.
Let's put one on.
(Case 04: Show)
(Episode 4)
I'm here to deliver court papers.
Who is Choi Sa Ra?
Hello.
That's me.
(Republic of Korea Electronic Litigation)
(Written Complaint)
(Plaintiff Cha Eun Kyung, Defendant Choi Sa Ra)
(Cause of Complaint)
(On jurisdiction)
(Plaintiff Evidence 3)
Ms. Cha's here.
Sa Ra, to my office. We need to talk.
Yes.
Leave it.
Sit.
So, what will you do?
- What? - The written complaint.
You read hundreds of responses.
How will you respond to this lawsuit?
Do I have to tell you that?
Tell me what outcome you expected...
or what your plan was.
I'm curious.
I don't have a plan.
- We just... - You just what?
Will you say...
it was love? No way.
I will resign.
I know so well how much you love this company.
You don't have to quit.
- I might as well... - Stay.
You're good at what you do.
Promotion season's coming up.
I thought you didn't approve of me.
Why?
Are you pleased you feel acknowledged?
Why...
Why did you call me by my name?
Everyone else called me "Ms. Choi."
Is that important right now?
How long have you known?
I knew you'd say that.
Affair partners always ask that.
They must really want to know.
I have no reason to listen to this.
- Excuse me. - Aren't you an affair partner?
You must know yourself...
that you were practically strangers.
You were less than strangers.
Do you take classes?
Where do you all learn the exact same dialog?
(Republic of Korea Electronic Litigation)
(Plaintiff Cha Eun Kyung, Defendant Kim Ji Sang)
(Purpose of Complaint)
(Relationship of the person in question)
(Defendant and partner's relationship)
(Plaintiff Evidence 7)
(Plaintiff Evidence 3)
- Yes. - What's this?
You both got it at the same time. You're a couple after all.
What did you do?
Shouldn't I ask you that?
How long have you known?
You want to know that too?
Is it something like that?
The despair and fury of two criminals...
who dreamed of committing a perfect crime.
Did you put a camera in my office?
Did you ask me to consult there to spy on me?
You have a creative mind.
I'm so sick of you.
Thanks for proving I made the right choice...
and that I should leave you.
Listen.
Don't call me.
Call my lawyer.
Your lawyer?
Did you tattle to Jung Woo Jin?
What?
Is this ready?
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
Ms. Han, you're here.
Hello. Why...
Is something wrong?
Sa Ra was served court papers.
Gosh...
Really?
As soon as she read the papers,
she was called to Ms. Cha's office.
She left all flushed and upset.
What could it be?
Maybe she was scolded.
You know how good Ms. Cha is at offending people.
Promise to keep this to yourself.
There's a rumor that Sa Ra had an affair with a married man.
Gosh, you need to be careful.
You know that can be defamation, right?
(Attorney at law, Cha Eun Kyung)
I gathered it to avoid a divorce.
Because as you know, the guilty can't sue for divorce.
I wanted to use the proof to stay married.
I saw for myself...
and what I said to myself became meaningless in an instant.
Ms. Cha.
Why...
did you choose me?
You didn't like how I handled court cases.
Why does everyone think I didn't like their work?
Because you always clashed?
You know I don't really need an attorney.
I know divorce better than anyone.
Then...
are you doing this to stop me from resigning?
But...
I need you.
What?
Why me?
Because we're different.
You have different views and interpretations.
And different solutions.
Let's say...
I need balance.
It's time to see our VIP client.
- Let's go. - Right now?
The CEO of a listed company.
We're fighting a demand of division of assets.
It's a case you must try.
She wants half the shares.
I worked like crazy to get the company listed.
The plaintiff currently resides abroad.
My wife and kids moved abroad ten years ago.
For ten years, I worked like mad and sent them money.
I even got them an apartment in Manhattan, New York.
The eldest is an adult and works now,
and the youngest comes of age soon.
She uses the kids as an excuse to ask for more money.
Out of the 23 years you were married,
you lived together for 13,
and you lived here alone for ten as the breadwinner?
Yes.
But we agreed to part ways five years ago.
You didn't put that in writing, did you?
Shoot. I should have.
There must've been a reason...
you decided to part ways.
What happened?
I never found proof,
but there was an affair of sorts.
You're wrong.
Are you delusional or something?
I wasn't going to say this,
but the Korean churchgoers say...
you walk with an arm linked with his.
I told you he's just a friend.
Do you have proof?
Shall I come over and find witnesses?
Let's break up.
- What? - I'm sick and tired of this.
I told you it's not what you think.
If you can't believe we, we must split.
Let's call it quits.
Do you mean that? You want a divorce?
I don't want to stay married to a man who doubts his wife.
The kids won't finish college for a few more years.
We'll sign the paperwork then,
but break up now.
Weren't you...
hoping I'd notice you were seeing other men?
And if I did have an affair,
that's on you.
For making me lonely.
She said that, but when your company got listed,
she changed her mind.
And pretended your marriage was fine and intact all this while.
The large sum would've given her ideas.
I don't have to give her half of what I own, do I?
The defendant will say you were married for 23 years...
and so she deserves to get half of the company.
We'll say the company was listed...
after the point in time when you agreed to part ways,
and so the shares...
should not be considered in the assets to be divided.
The result depends on proof.
Okay.
Was there any contact since then?
I did make a few trips.
To see the kids during their breaks.
I barely spoke to my wife.
Then there was COVID which put a stop to travel.
A trial depends solely on proof.
Your wife will provide immigration records and say,
"Look. He visited us in the US."
She'll use it to say you maintained an ordinary marriage.
A lawsuit is all about fitting facts to the evidence.
I wasn't there to see her.
What should I do?
It took a lot of work to set up my company.
If I give her half my shares, the whole thing will collapse.
My assets...
No, my company. Please save it.
What's the main argument?
The duration of marriage could be 18 years or 23 years,
and which it is decides...
whether the shares should be shared or not.
How do we prove which it is?
We'll get their phone records...
to confirm they didn't talk during those five years...
They could've talked often to discuss their kids.
Does that prove a broken marriage?
That's the case if they were in touch.
If there are zero records that they called each other,
can we use it as circumstantial evidence...
that they weren't in touch?
First,
we won't be able to obtain...
the call detail records from the phone company now.
Is that the only way you thought of to prove our argument?
Then...
Why do you think about...
asking Mr. Jang Hyun Sung's parent to be a witness?
Mr. Jang said he practically lived...
with his mother for the past five years.
Blood is thicker than water.
If we submit a statement from his mother as evidence,
do you think the judge will believe her?
Besides, how is living with his mother...
considered proof for the end of their marriage?
His wife is living abroad.
Off the top of my head,
I can't think of any other ways to prove their marriage ended.
Then I'll think about it a bit more.
Do you remember my special lecture at your school?
You must think outside the box...
while listening to the series of complaints from the client.
To have any chance of doing that, just let me go first.
You're not a student anymore. You're an attorney.
You can't be stuck at having the same, predictable ideas.
How will you handle my case if you can't do that?
See where your creativity takes you.
Understood?
Yes. I got it.
Okay.
It's not just a divorce lawsuit.
It's your case. Why do you want me to represent you?
I specialize in criminal cases.
My wife is Cha Eun Kyung.
Who's Cha Eun Kyung?
Is she famous for having gone through several divorces?
She's a divorce attorney.
It would be to our disadvantage...
if we were to hire an attorney who's acquainted with her.
That's why we're here.
This attorney from Daejeong... Is she that famous?
I've reviewed the written complaint.
(Evidence 5)
You guys had an affair right under her nose.
Their marital relationship had ended a long time ago.
They were no longer a married couple.
They were only married on paper. They were practically strangers.
By the time I started seeing him, their relationship...
had already ended.
If all she ever did was work, who took care of the child?
I raised our child all on my own.
She's closer to me than to her mother.
This isn't how a normal family functions.
She must've acted all bossy for having a well-paying job.
Seriously. This is the thing with women.
Whenever they start earning money, they act as if they own you.
But still. The evidence she has on you guys is pretty strong.
It's way too strong.
I never pegged you to be the bold type, though.
Since you guys lived together for 15 years,
you should divide your assets half and half...
and sign the paper. It will be simple then.
My top priority is gaining custody of my child.
Will it still be a simple process then?
You're a man. Why would you complicate it for custody?
Her mom should have custody.
Sir.
Could you help us settle this case?
Are you serious about wanting to raise Jae Hui?
Of course. She's my daughter.
(Plaintiff: Kim S. Hui, Defendant: Jang H. Sung)
Your Honor, the plaintiff and the defendant of this case...
aren't two spouses living in different countries.
Then what do you suggest?
They're two spouses who have been separated.
(Defendant, Plaintiff)
Yes. Go on.
(Defendant)
Some married couples agree to live in different countries...
due to different circumstances...
while maintaining their marital relationship.
But they are married couples...
who agree to live separately because their marriage has ended...
which makes them strangers, in fact.
So you're arguing that they had been separated financially. Correct?
Yes, Your Honor.
They stopped communicating with one another...
unless it was about their children.
Of course, they didn't have any sexual intercourse for years.
We were happy as a couple.
Everyone was so surprised how happy we were together...
even though we lived in different countries for so long.
Kim Se Hui!
Your Honor, she's lying!
She's doing this for money. She's putting on a show.
We lived as strangers since five years ago.
Sit down.
- Calm down. - What's he talking about?
Your Honor.
Three months ago, the defendant's company got listed.
The value of his shares went up tenfold.
The plaintiff is making a false statement,
so she can include his shares in the division of assets...
by extending the duration of their marriage.
That makes it clear what his intention is.
Your Honor.
He's the one lying for money, not me.
Now that he doesn't want to divide his assets,
he's arguing we were separated, we stopped making love, and so on.
He's lying.
You even cheated on me! Should I bring up everything?
Why do you keep putting on a show?
I should ask you to stop putting on a show.
How could you lie in court?
Do you have proof?
I don't see any need to respond to his accusation about the affair.
He has been sending such a large sum of money to my client...
which makes it hard to believe that they were separated.
You're right.
Looking the arrival and departure records,
you visited the US at least 2 or 3 times a year...
up until two years ago.
Yet, you argue you've practically been strangers for five years?
And you're separated?
You must prove that.
Yes. We'll prove it so by next the hearing.
Then we'll see you at the next hearing.
(Court of Korea)
Remember what the opposing counsel said in court earlier? Is it true?
Are you still sending her money?
Yes. Of course.
I send about 25,000 dollars a month for living expenses.
You send her that much money?
Stop sending her money.
Then how will she live?
She'll have to find ways on her own. She'll have to use her savings.
But isn't that irresponsible?
If she runs out of money, she might ask our children.
You said, "Of course" when we asked about the money.
Of course, you should send...
a generous sum of money to the wives of your children.
Of course, you should buy her an apartment in Manhattan.
Of course, you should send her...
tens of thousands of dollars even when you're broken up.
Do you really believe all this is your duty?
It's what I've been doing so far.
Fine.
Then isn't it also your duty...
to give her half of your shares for the company that got listed?
That's different.
My duty as the breadwinner...
has nothing to do...
with my company getting listed after our separation.
"Breadwinner." "Responsibility."
You chained yourself to these terms.
You let your wife take what you provide for her...
for granted for 20 years.
If you tell her now that you can't give half of your shares,
don't you think that would throw her off?
Well,
you have a point.
Fine. I probably wanted a sense of acknowledgment...
as a competent provider.
But what's so bad about it?
I never thought things would get out of hand like this.
You must now accept that she's not your family.
No. Accept that you are no longer...
the provider.
Ms. Park. Do we have another case that overlaps...
with Jang Hyun Sung's hearing in court?
It's okay if it's not my case.
I see. Then tell them I have to lead the trial in Daegu.
Request the panel of judges...
for Jang Hyun Sung's case to postpone the next hearing.
Why did you postpone the hearing?
His youngest child will be an adult soon.
Didn't you calculate when that would be?
In about three weeks.
That's why we postponed it after his child's birthday.
You should have checked the birthday and caught it on your own.
Is it because the judges are...
reluctant to recognize a statement from a minor?
Did you just figure that out?
His eldest child is in the US, so getting in touch will be hard.
So contact his youngest child.
Okay. I got it.
Ms. Cha.
Well,
like you said, I bought a car.
You don't have to give me a lift starting today.
Okay.
Yes, hello. I'm sorry.
You said the shuttle bus didn't run today.
Well, my next appointment is coming up soon.
Yes. Actually,
hold on.
Yes. I'll give you a call.
Ms. Han.
I'm so sorry. But could I ask you for a favor?
Don't tell me...
Jae Hui had a field trip today,
so I was supposed to pick her up myself. But I forgot.
Could you give her a ride to her academy just this once?
Me?
I have no one else to ask.
Well,
don't you think her father should do that?
Ms. Han.
You didn't forget that you're handling my case, right?
We're in the middle of a lawsuit. Should I call him to say...
I can't pick her up? Why give him any ammunition?
Could you postpone your next appointment?
I must attend the meeting with the VIP client.
You don't have any appointments this afternoon. Help me out.
Gosh.
Just this once. I'll text you the address.
You can go home after that. Thank you.
Ms. Cha!
You came five minutes late, so my schedule got iffy.
I wanted to take a break.
What? The time... Where's...
Get a grip, and just focus on driving.
Besides, it's a bit odd to see that an attorney isn't punctual.
What? What did you say?
You don't even have a decent wristwatch.
Forget it. Please drive safely.
Buy one. Buy a watch as well.
Time is everything to an attorney.
You must constantly be checking the time.
Daejeong is 1 of Korea's top 3 law firms.
Our fee is at least triple the industry standard...
as are our salaries.
Due to that, our efficiency should also be tripled.
So to perform efficiently,
you will need your own car and comfortable shoes.
You're Little Cha Eun Kyung.
I'm Little Kim Ji Sang.
I'm nothing like my mom.
You're just like your mother.
Aunt Sa Ra used to pick me up when I had field trips.
Is she busy?
Yes. Aunt Sa Ra is very busy.
So what are my parents going to do?
What? What do you mean?
Their divorce?
What divorce?
- Who told you that? - How could I not know that?
When dads suddenly go on a business trip abroad...
and don't come home...
or when moms go to Hawaii to live for a month,
those parents end up getting a divorce.
I don't know anything.
I think you should ask your mother yourself.
As if. You know everything.
I really don't.
Seeing how you came to pick me up, there's no way you know nothing.
You...
take after your mother a lot.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
All right. We're having beer with pork skin today.
Hold on. Here you go. Try that piece.
- It's really tasty. - Gosh.
So you picked her up at school? That's crazy.
You know what? I can pick her up ten times if I have to.
You know what?
You'll now be an attorney-encer.
- What's that? - You really don't get it?
It's a compound word of an attorney and influencer.
Ms. Cha is more of a superstar than an attorney.
But you're driving her daughter around now.
So you're bound to be famous just like Ms. Cha.
Is that so?
Gosh. It seems you've got a bright career ahead of you.
Don't you think I should have my chance first?
An attorney-encer, my foot.
I'm not her babysitter.
Should I report her...
- to the Ministry of Labor? - Hey, no.
If you don't want to do it, I'll do it.
I don't mind picking Ms. Cha's daughter up.
I can do it 10 or 20 times...
as long as I can be famous.
What's the point of gaining fame?
Isn't it obvious? I'll open up my own law office.
I'll get to start and finish work whenever I want.
To do that, I must be a free agent.
My seniors who opened their own law offices...
didn't seem "free" at all.
You're right.
Attorneys with their own offices seem to be busier. Right?
Should I just quit my job...
and marry a competent woman instead?
If you're interested in marriage, try harder with your blind dates.
Don't have one of those "quick" dates during lunch.
Hey.
You know what? I have a long list of blind dates coming up soon.
At this rate, I'm not sure...
if you'll keep having the pleasure of having lunch with me.
How many date requests are you getting?
Let me check, ma'am. Looking at the date requests so far,
I have about three dates a week.
Then you're practically a blind date machine.
Isn't that a waste of time?
You should just pick one already.
You see, I don't have that luxury.
Listen. People can be so weird.
When I told them I worked for a huge law firm in Korea,
they thought that I would only say the cool stuff and live in luxury...
like the attorneys in dramas.
But in reality, I'm just a pathetic office worker.
See? You're already miserable all on your own.
It would just get worse when you get married.
That's why I won't get married.
Humans are selfish beings who are incapable of sharing anything.
I do agree with that.
That's why we must meet someone whom we love...
beyond the innate nature of selfishness...
we have as humans.
If I were to meet a woman like that,
I'd want to marry her in a heartbeat.
Okay.
All right. So is there anything troubling you these days?
Order anything you want here...
other than the beef sirloin.
Have a lot of this.
The bus will arrive shortly.
Seriously.
I'm going to report her to the Ministry of Labor.
No matter how long I think about it, reporting her is the right thing.
What's the point of going on dates all the time?
I don't like any of them.
- I am... - Do they expect me to own a house?
- I rarely get to save up money. - an attorney.
- I'm not a babysitter. Seriously. - Gosh.
If I owned an apartment with the view of the Han River,
why would I work at the law firm?
I would've quit my job and opened up my own office a long time ago.
I would've accepted only the cases I wanted.
- You know what? Jae Hui... - Yes.
will be just like her mother when she grows up.
It was uncanny how much she took after her mother.
Gosh, that girl...
Oh, my head.
What...
(Motel Eunyu)
Motel...
Eunyu?
(Motel Eunyu)
(Plaintiff Evidence 7)
What am I doing here?
Oh, no.
Okay.
Round Three is on me.
Let's go for PB.
What's that?
Pork hangover soup and beer.
Get up. Let's go.
- Watch out. - Oh, no.
Oh, no.
My goodness.
Ms. Han.
Hello.
Your outfit is the same as yesterday's.
I thought you went home after dropping Jae Hui.
- Hello. - Hello.
No.
I'm wearing different pants.
Oh, right. Did you hand in the evidence? Motel Eunyu?
What about Motel Eunyu?
The picture you said you'd hand in by Monday.
Did you submit it?
Oh, yes, I did.
Okay.
Gosh.
(Attorney at law, Han Yu Ri)
Well...
Wait.
Send me your account number.
Insurance number?
- What? - What?
No.
Send me your account number.
What for?
You paid for everything last night. I'll pay half.
It's fine. Don't worry about it.
Don't refuse. It's not fine for me.
- And... - Yes?
Let's go for lunch separately.
Sure. Okay.
I have a blind date anyway.
Oh, I see.
- A blind date? - I mean...
- Go on your way. - Coffee...
- Bye. - Yes, bye.
Gosh.
- A blind date? - Why did I...
- Seriously? - ask for his account number?
- Have I lost it? - What am I going to do?
Have I gone mad?
This is insane.
Where is Ms. Cha?
Ms. Cha!
"Attorney C who is increasing her price..."
"through various activities."
"Due to an affair between her husband and secretary,"
"the country's top three law firm D..."
"is in an uproar."
"What is a divorce attorney's divorce going to be like?"
Ms. Cha!
This tabloid.
Is this true?
It's partially true, sir.
- What's going on? - Is it true?
I'll handle it. Go back to your office.
Why would you? It's my business.
I ordered the divorce team to increase the profit,
and are you providing it from within?
Is that it, Ms. Cha? Answer me!
Mr. Oh.
Everyone is watching. Don't be like this.
This tabloid hasn't been confirmed if it's true.
Even if it is true, it's her personal life.
You should leave.
This could lead to defamation.
Defamation?
What about my firm's reputation? And my reputation!
I'll handle it. You should leave.
(Attorney at law, Cha Eun Kyung)
(Attorney at law, Han Yu Ri)
Seriously.
You're the biggest problem.
You should've checked first.
How can you humiliate the partner attorney...
in front of everyone over the tabloid?
How can I stay still when my firm is mentioned?
I will make sure it won't damage the firm's reputation.
You do not have to worry.
You acting like this...
will damage the firm's reputation even more.
My goodness.
Eun Kyung.
- How can you do that? - Do what?
You let me hear about your divorce through the tabloid...
when we saw each other every day for over a decade?
You should've told me at least.
I'll take this chance...
to make Law Firm Daejeong...
a byword for a divorce.
Then Mr. Oh won't complain.
What are you going to do?
I am the channel and media myself.
Through the channel Cha Eun Kyung,
I'm going to let the whole nation watch everything about a divorce.
We should think about the direction of your lawsuit.
An attorney?
Did you go straight to Jung Woo Jin?
- Jung Woo Jin. - Yes?
I'll take care of it.
Yes?
Gosh.
If you want it all, come and get it.
Although, it'll be brief.
I bet you read the tabloids.
Up until this moment,
I thought they were only meant for celebrities,
but I must've been wrong.
They were surprisingly accurate.
Am I to blame for everything?
Yes, you're the only one to blame.
Don't be gossiped about by the entire nation,
and quietly settle.
Me? Why should I do that?
I don't even want to see your face, so get yourself an attorney.
I already have.
He wanted to meet you right away,
but I came to you first...
out of courtesy since we were once family.
How about a piece of advice?
Being represented by the same attorney...
won't seem ideal in the eyes of a judge.
Having the same attorney...
makes you look like a set of cockroaches.
Don't you think you'll be hurt by this?
You're even threatening me now. That's not bad.
You've changed a lot, Ji Sang.
I'll go back to my life...
after a moment of shame in the spotlight.
But you're a public figure.
I'll reveal how selfish you were...
and what kind of mom you were.
Will you be okay with that?
Bring it. Do your worst.
Are you going to continue with this lawsuit?
What about Jae Hui?
And you call yourself her mother?
Do you even have the right to be one?
You dare to say I'm not qualified?
You should've thought about Jae Hui first...
before things ended up this way.
Look here, Mr. Kim.
Listen to me loud and clear.
You are not to mention my daughter to my face ever again.
Also, I won't settle.
I wouldn't have sued you if that had been what I wanted.
Properly fight your battle with the right weapons. Got it?
I'll make you regret this.
Where's Attorney Cha Eun Kyung?
I have something to say to her.
- What could this be about? - Where's Attorney Cha?
She's not in her office at the moment.
Also, you can't come to see her without a prior appointment.
I came to see her in person because I can't seem to book one.
Ma'am, please calm down and book an appointment and...
Where the heck is she?
What is this about?
You changed the next court date.
Let's not drag this out and settle.
I'll concede and...
We won't settle.
Why should we settle?
I don't have to hear your offer to know...
that you'll only ask for 30 percent of the shares...
as if you're doing him a favor.
I don't need half of it.
That's me being generous.
I'm afraid we have very different ideas.
Our goal is...
not to give you 1 percent, let alone 30.
And he still thinks he has the right to call himself their father?
Being the breadwinner of the family doesn't make him one.
His children will receive their inheritance.
You say him earning money...
doesn't automatically make him their father,
but you're asking for more in the divorce.
I suggest you think about...
how contradicting that is.
I'll see you in court.
She came to the firm without her attorney?
She's not your average housewife, I give you that.
Let's give her what she wants and end this.
I'm exhausted...
by her doubting my role as their father.
You're willing to settle?
You want to pay her that large sum of money?
The mother knew you'd cave...
if she questioned your role as their father,
and you'll gladly give in to her demand.
Sure. We'll do just that.
- Sorry? - I love wrapping up...
my cases early.
Then, I'll call her to say that you'll settle.
You're hesitant to give me an answer...
despite sounding so determined earlier.
What do you think I should do?
You're not paying for her living expenses anymore,
so block any texts or calls you might receive from her.
She'll be swamped with paying the living expenses...
including the utility bills.
It's now her turn to give you an answer.
She must struggle with money first...
to realize that what she took for granted...
was the result of one's hard work and concerns.
I want to teach her a lesson too,
but I don't want her to mooch off our children.
Would you rather be dragged along by a woman...
who makes threats with your children?
Are you going to continue with this lawsuit?
What about Jae Hui?
And you call yourself her mother?
Do you even have the right to be one?
Don't lose focus.
The suffering might be unbearable for now,
but don't give up.
You should stand strong, win the battle,
and protect your assets.
You're almost there.
It's our youngest's birthday tomorrow,
and I'm ashamed to let her see...
that her parents are fighting over money...
on her big day.
Her birthday.
Your youngest daughter's birthday is a big day for us as well.
It's only a day away, so be patient with us.
Why is her birthday important to you?
Your daughters are the witnesses of your marriage,
so just be patient.
We'll do our best to make you feel like you won.
Ms. Han?
Ms. Han, your driving...
Ms. Cha, Jae Hui...
is like a younger version of you.
Is she?
Yet, you drove her home with this level of driving.
That's the thanks I get?
I drove her home safely at a slow speed.
Kim Ji Sang asked for us to settle.
- What was his offer? - I didn't let him talk...
because it wasn't worth my time.
He'll call once again after hiring an attorney.
He will.
Goodness.
As if it isn't Attorney Cha Eun Kyung.
So here's where we meet.
Can I help you?
I'm representing Kim Ji Sang and Choi Sa Ra.
I see.
I hear you're a public figure.
Being gossiped about wouldn't benefit you at all.
Everyone knows everyone in this particular case,
so let's settle without taking this to court.
I have no intention of doing so.
I'm her attorney.
From now on, please contact me if you have anything to discuss.
(Attorney at law, Han Yu Ri, Law Firm Daejeong)
Goodness, Ms. Han.
You look like someone who just graduated high school.
Well, I have to be in court, so...
Also, you look like a headmaster...
who is close to his retirement.
(Defendant)
We'd like to submit a written statement.
Sure. Pull it up on the screen.
"Hello,"
- "I'm..." - I'm...
- "the second daughter..." - the second daughter...
of the plaintiff and defendant, Jang A Reum.
Like you said, I contacted and met with...
Mr. Jang's second daughter who's currently in Korea.
Our parents...
did their best for us...
in their own unique ways.
In the year I was born,
my dad founded Areum Company that was named after me,
worked hard to grow it for 20 years,
and managed to have it listed on the stock market.
Our mom cared for us on foreign land...
so that we could receive our education.
Five years ago,
our parents said this to us in person.
They will continue to be our parents,
but not as a married couple.
They had agreed to live separate lives.
I was shocked to hear it...
at such a young age,
but this was common...
- among families in the US. - "Among families in the US."
"That is how I was able to accept it."
That's insane!
I doubt you'll rule based on the words of a teenager.
She's still a minor.
She wrote that statement...
after she had legally become an adult.
It's our youngest's birthday tomorrow.
Your youngest daughter's birthday is a big day for us as well.
Are you sure it was after her birthday?
Yes, she's legally an adult,
and I received a statement that favors our client.
Also, we submitted into evidence...
how the plaintiff changed the beneficiary...
of all her insurance claims to her mother five years ago.
When the defendant visited his family in the US,
he didn't stay at the plaintiff's Manhattan residence...
but at a hotel the entire time.
We also submit that into evidence.
Here's our last piece of evidence.
Please play the recording.
(Plaintiff)
I told you not to call me anymore.
Let's live our lives separately.
I called for the first time in three years.
But despite everything,
shouldn't we at least discuss our children's career paths?
I don't care if it was 3 years or 5. Don't call me again.
(In session)
(2024-527, Plaintiff Kim, Defendant Jang)
I thank you both.
She must've been ashamed to face the children...
because she gave up on the shares which allowed us to settle easily.
Your company went public...
after you and your wife were already separated.
Also, you've been providing her...
with enough money to spend on living expenses...
which made it hard...
to acknowledge her rights to the company's shares.
However, my guess is that the plaintiff...
wanted it to be over since she's practically broke.
Traveling to Korea for the trial and hiring an attorney...
all cost money, you see.
The children spent most of their time with their mom,
so I believed they'd take her side.
My youngest daughter is all grown up now.
She maintained an objective view.
She's no longer a minor.
So do not be fazed...
even if people try to threaten you...
by using your children against you.
Right.
You don't have any underage children among you...
which makes you as good as strangers.
I know the battle was tough.
The waiting was hard to bear,
and I almost gave up.
I appreciate you helping me stay strong.
This is an expensive meal.
I'll enjoy it. Thank you.
There's no need to thank me...
since we're paying for this with what we earned.
Jae Hui asked if you two...
were getting divorced.
And?
I feigned ignorance.
But I think it's time...
you told her.
I should soon.
Rumors about us are already circulating.
Kim Ji Sang and Choi Sa Ra's attorney...
keep contacting me suggesting that we settle.
Didn't this recent case teach you anything?
I don't intend to settle.
I won't give him anything.
If Ji Sang agrees to give up everything...
like Kim Se Hui did,
I'll reconsider the offer.
But the two instances aren't the same.
In Mr. Jang's case, he had already divided his assets...
by buying her the Manhattan house.
And for years, their marriage hadn't existed.
But in your case,
you were married for nearly 15 years.
You'll be forced to give him half of your assets.
No.
He won't get a penny.
Did you forget what you taught me?
I believe you're caught up in only getting your revenge.
Spouses who were cheated on all say the same thing.
They want the cheating spouse...
to end up with nothing.
That's the result of watching too much TV.
But if your spouse cheats on you,
even I'd want to get revenge in that form.
Revenge?
We're attorneys.
Let them get revenge on their own time.
In the eyes of the law,
even the unfaithful spouse is entitled to their joint assets.
Be clear with that.
You're right. I'm getting my revenge.
I'll have him get nothing in this divorce no matter what.
Are you kidding me?
Cha Eun Kyung, don't tell me you...
Why do these things keep happening to me?
Why?
(The defendant's marriage to the plaintiff...)
(was already wrecked due to Cha's extramarital affair...)
(Her office husband...)
Seriously?
(Good Partner)
How could nothing have happened...
between two colleagues of the opposite sex...
while working together for over a decade?
What are you two doing?
- You and Attorney Jung Woo Jin. - Han Yu Ri, you...
You're saying there wasn't an affair.
Of course it'll hurt Ms. Cha more since she's a public figure.
Keep coming after me, and I'll fight to the end.
I would like you to strongly consider a settlement.
It seems as though I hired the wrong attorney.