Good Partner
Daejeong
In session | Plaintiff
Good Partner
This drama is fiction.
Characters, places, agencies, events, organizations, and the setting have no connection to real life.
Child actors were filmed under safe conditions.
Episode 11
I'll be in middle school soon.
You don't have to drop me off.
Are you pushing me away just because you grew up a bit?
You're still a baby in my eyes.
I couldn't do it all this time.
Whether you're in middle school or high school, let me do it.
Okay?
Fine.
Attorney Cha Eun Gyeong
Dear Attorney Cha Eun Gyeong, the most awesome dolsing* in the world,
(*Korean for divorced solo)
please live happily ever after.
Call for me whenever you need after-service.
I'll come running.
Legal Representative Attorney Han Yu Ri.
After-service?
Seriously, Han Yu Ri.
- Yes?
- Attorney Cha!
CEO was looking for you earlier.
He says to come to his office when you're in.
- Yes.
- Okay.
Yes?
Can't believe...
you're late, Attorney Cha.
Take a seat.
Yes.
It's been noisy with your personal matters, Attorney Cha.
And it's all over now.
I wanted to hear your plan. That's why I called you in.
I had said I'd promote Daejeong's Divorce Team through my divorce.
But I'm sorry I ended up settling and couldn't keep the promise.
I'm not trying to get an apology from you.
I'm saying let's review if you must be in the Divorce Team
and if there's a need to keep the Divorce Team
as a separate team in a world where young people don't even get married anymore.
Are you saying we should get rid of the Divorce Team now?
You took the initiative and created the Divorce Team.
But I'm not sure if there's a need for a big firm to keep a divorce team.
What kind of role do you wish me to take on in the future?
You've been working here for 17 years now.
Haven't you thought that growing in a firm has its limits?
Isn't it about time you consider other options?
Opening up my office...
Or are you talking about my resignation?
I haven't thought about that...
I thought I had shown you sufficient performance in the firm.
Why don't you take a few days off?
You've gone through a lot.
There are many mediations scheduled next week—
Even without you,
things will run smoothly as if you were never here.
So, don't worry, Attorney Cha.
Case 11: Vacancy
Hello?
Oh, yes, Jae Hui's mother, is this a good time to talk?
Yes, Teacher.
Oh, yes. It's just that...
- Jae Hui got into an argument with her friends today.
- Pardon?
Jae Hui is a bit more sensitive than usual these days.
Is she like that at home, too?
Well, she's been the same all along at home.
She was in a good mood this morning, too.
I'm a little cautious to say this,
but children often feel the other parent's absence after a divorce.
I also think becoming aware of others' opinions is a factor.
So I think you'll have to pay more attention to Jae Hui, ma'am.
Yes, thank you, Teacher.
Attorney Han, Mr. Lee Seung Jun is here.
Hi.
Mr. Lee Seung Joon?
Yes.
Please have a seat here.
You two can sit as well.
Why did three young men come to the Divorce Team's office?
Did you get a plaint?
You can give me that.
One moment. I'll take a look.
Plaint
2. Immoral Act Between Kim Ha Yoon and Defendant
An adulterer?
You got sued for damages for being an adulterer.
I'm not an adulterer, Attorney.
- Seung Jun isn't.
- Seung Jun really isn't.
Ha Yoon is-— I mean...
I really didn't even imagine that woman would be married.
She even had a son who was in elementary school.
How did you meet her?
It's called Hug Hug.
Hug Hug? What is that?
It's a dating app.
Seung Jun never even had a blind date, so we installed it for him.
But it's really nothing shady, Attorney.
Young people these days use this app.
You've been working here for 17 years now.
Haven't you thought that growing in a firm has its limits?
Isn't it about time you consider other options?
Vacation
Yes?
Attorney Cha, are you busy?
Oh, I'm going on a trip with Jae Hui.
I don't think I took care of her during my case.
I see.
That's a great idea.
Don't worry about the office, Attorney Cha.
Please pay a lot of attention to Jae Hui.
Okay.
Attorney Jeong, here's the list of this week's new cases.
Yes. Thank you.
Attorney Jeong, did you hear?
Attorney Cha submitted a vacation request just now.
A vacation request?
I worked here for over ten years.
I think it's my first time seeing Attorney Cha going on a vacation.
Yes.
Seonbae, are you going somewhere?
I was just about to tell you, Attorney Jeong.
I'm going on a vacation.
Why so suddenly?
Nothing's going on, right?
Did you meet the CEO by chance?
Nothing's going on.
Why won't you ever tell me anything?
Let's be honest here. Okay?
We're on the same team.
There's really nothing going on.
Let me have a break, too.
For next week's mediation, you just need to go and sign
since the settlement proposal was submitted.
For the case with a motion to transfer,
I explained to the client that the estimated date is out.
I switched next week's consultation to an over-the-phone consultation.
- Okay. The written document for submission—
- Seonbae.
Don't worry about it and have a good time.
I got everything from Senior Manager Ahn.
Thanks.
Please take good care of the Divorce Team while I'm gone.
Han Yu Ri, too.
It's all done, right?
How can I prove this?
Yes?
Attorney Cha, do you have a minute?
What is it now? What's not working out?
Sit down.
This is a division of property schedule. Please take a look.
As you can see,
- the defendant has quite a lot of assets.
- Yes.
But I think they'll get too much if things go like this.
- Is that all?
- Yes.
But the situation is not in our favor.
Yes?
Hey, Attorney Han.
Attorney Jeong, do you have a minute?
Yes, I'm free.
I'm a bit confused because the plaintiff's claim and the
defendant's statement are too different.
Could you please take a look at the complaint?
Sure. Shall we take a look?
Thank you.
Let's see...
The plaintiff says the defendant intentionally approached his wife and seduced her.
But Mr. Lee Seung Jun claims to the contrary he was the one who was seduced.
Adultery cases are always like that.
They say the other person seduced them first.
But why do you think the client's story is a claim, not a fact?
There's a part that's pretty tough to believe.
Kim Ha Yun's husband's name is Hun, and her son's is Min.
But if you look at the evidence here...
Over here.
Lee Seung Jun clearly talks as if he knows about Kim Ha Yun's husband and son.
But when I asked Mr. Lee Seung Jun, he said...
"I also want to be by Kim Ha Yun's side just like Hun and Min."
Complaint: Plaintiff: Kim Hun
Hun is the husband...
and Min is the son's name.
And you didn't know she was married?
I know it's really hard for you to believe,
but they're the names of the moss she grows.
Moss?
Marimo. Moss.
They're mosses called Marimo. Aren't they cute?
Their names are Kim Hun and Kim Min.
The mosses' names sound like people's names.
Because they're my pet mosses.
They're family.
Claims like this are so absurd, Attorney Jeong.
I guess I should request the mosses as witnesses.
- It's too weird.
- Yes, that's exactly what I mean.
What I mean is the evidence that proves
Mr. Lee dated the woman with the knowledge that she was married.
It's too perfect.
That's weird.
It looks like the plaintiff planted an item in advance for use as evidence.
Sorry?
Her husband, the plaintiff...
planted an item in advance...
Huh?
Could it be that...
a married couple schemed together to bring about an adultery litigation?
It's your job to destroy that "Could it be," Attorney Han.
But did you know this?
An attorney's "Could it be" can be quite dangerous.
Give it some thought.
Could it be...
Was he really fooled...
or is he denying it after committing adultery?
Even if I want to believe him, a moss is out of the question.
It's called Hug Hug. It's a dating app.
Young people these days use this app.
Yes, the dating app.
Dating app, Hug Hug.
Jae Hui?
I bought this. Do you want to see?
Ta-da. It's a set.
Let's wear this and go on a trip.
- So suddenly?
- I took a leave.
You'll come with me, right?
Pretty, aren't they?
Yes?
- What are you up to? Working late again?
- Hey, Attorney Jeon.
Whoa, it's already 10 p.m.
- What are you doing?
- Huh?
Oh, this is called Hug Hug.
It's a popular dating app, apparently.
It's nothing, really.
You can go on home first today, Attorney Jeon.
- Okay. I'll get going, then.
- Okay.
It's done, right?
We got everything. Done!
Done.
What about this, though?
The backseat. I'll load them up.
Mom, will they all fit?
Yes, I'll carry the big one!
It's my first time going on a trip with you alone.
I'm cutting school on top of that!
Can't be.
It's really my first time.
Let's go on trips often from now on.
I won't excuse myself saying I'm busy anymore.
It wasn't an excuse. You've really been busy.
There. It's 25 cases for each of you.
Attorney Cha already organized them for you and
notified the clients in advance so nothing major would happen.
But they might still call you or require additional explanation.
So, she asked each of you to take care of them.
Wait, I already have more than fifty cases.
This is really too inhumane.
Attorney Jeon.
You know Attorney Cha and Attorney Jeong always keep more than seventy cases, right?
Fighting!
Fighting.
Take care!
That's because they're partner attorneys.
Gosh, this is nuts.
It just means Attorney Cha has that big a presence here.
Because absences make you realize the person's significance.
My goodness.
Where's Han Yu Ri, who said Attorney Cha is terrible and that she doesn't like her
on her first day of work?
I've fallen for Attorney Cha.
I admit. I like her so much.
For Han Yu Ri to say she fell for Attorney Cha...
As I expected, Attorney Cha is really competent.
I want to learn from her.
By the way, Attorney Jeon,
do you think you can help me out?
I can't! I already have enough on my plate—
What is it? Let me hear it.
Look at the camera?
Well, I think you can just relax.
Look this way just once.
Attorney Jeon, can you take a seat here?
- Here?
- Yes. Relax.
Relax?
Try holding this.
Try smiling, too.
Are you taking a profile picture for our homepage?
You look too stern and too much like an attorney.
An idol. Try to look like an idol.
An idol? I'm not good at that. Be cute and stuff?
What? Whoa!
What's this? Why are you so good?
Please register here.
- With this?
- Yes.
- Geez, this one is really weird.
- No, it's fine.
- For your hobby, choose tennis,
- Tennis.
- and cooking...
- Cooking.
Choose twenties for your age.
- Twenties?
- Yes.
There. Press it as you scroll.
Wh-Whoa, what was that?
What was that? Wasn't it Kim Ha Yun just now?
Scroll a bit slower.
You never get the same person again after you pass once.
- Slowly.
- I got it. All right.
Next.
Scroll to next...
Jae Hui.
Are you okay, Jae Hui?
Do we have digestive meds?
Why? Do you have a stomach ache?
Yes.
Maybe because I ate the bread too fast.
What should we do? I didn't bring the medicine.
It's fine. I'll just wait it out.
You didn't know I get indigestion easily.
I'm sorry, Jae Hui.
I'll hurry up and find a pharmacy nearby.
It's okay. I'll feel better soon.
All right. I brought us some cold coffee.
Thank you.
Did you get anything?
No, not yet.
I found her.
- This really works, huh?
- Whoa!
I got you, Kim Ha Yun.
This is daebak.
I found Ms. Kim Ha Yun in the app.
She lied about her age, too.
Everything you said was true, Mr. Lee.
- See?
- Do people lie to their own attorneys?
Yes, there are more than you expect.
I'm not 100% certain yet, but I'm skeptical about something.
Until it's confirmed, make sure not to say sorry to the plaintiff—
I mean, make sure not to say sorry to Ms. Kim Ha Yun's husband.
If you apologize, you're admitting you committed adultery.
Would her husband really reach out to me?
Be sure to remember what I said.
Yes, I understand.
What?
You said you'd help.
I can't really do anything about this.
Gosh, no, no, no.
We're not the attorneys in a drama.
- Why go that far, Attorney Han?
- I'm really sorry.
But it's so unfair for Mr. Lee Seung Jun.
He's in his early twenties, his prime.
But he's stuck and about to be labeled an adulterer.
This is for justice. Okay?
Just this once.
No, I can't. What if something happens to me? Will you take responsibility?
Yes, of course. I'll take responsibility.
No, I can't. This isn't it.
Excuse me. Are you from Hug Hug?
- Attorney?
- Yes, nice to meet you.
- Hello.
- Should we play a game first?
Yes.
Marigold Tennis Club
- Can we take a break?
- Sure. Are you okay?
You're good at tennis.
No, not at all.
Whoa, excuse me. I'm sorry.
I have low blood pressure.
This goes... Let me see.
Unfold it and...
Like this. Oh, I see...
- Are you done?
- Yes, I got it.
I get it now. I looked at the directions.
Mom, hold on.
- Huh?
- I think this goes inside the black one, not that one.
It says to use the black one here!
Look here. It's got the slit.
Oh, okay.
Right?
- Gosh. What's wrong with this thing?
- Come on.
- Aigoo.
- My goodness!
- Come on.
- I'm sorry.
It's my first time doing this.
No new notifications
- It's not done yet?
- Huh?
It's done. It's all done.
There.
Let's see how Mom's ramen tastes.
Gosh, it looks good!
There.
I'll give you some soup, too.
That's hot.
Looks good.
Go ahead. It's hot.
- Why aren't you eating?
- You added scallions.
I hate scallions.
Scallions...
Dad, you're still not done?
Hold on a second. I'll be done soon.
Boss, hurry it up.
I want the usual, please.
Chopped scallions and an egg?
Please skip the scallions!
Should I make a new one without scallions?
No, it's fine. I'll just eat it.
Add eggs instead of scallions next time.
Eggs. I'll add eggs.
I will make sure to add eggs next time.
Please try some of this.
Aren't you Attorney Cha Eun Gyeong from "All About Divorce"?
Yes, how do you do?
Yes, my mom is Attorney Cha Eun Gyeong.
Whoa, Attorney Cha!
Dad was too busy to come with you, huh?
Yes...
Honey, what are you doing?
What?
O-Oh, hello. Honey, one moment.
Honey, you really didn't know?
Cha Eun Gyeong's husband cheated on her with her secretary.
- Really?
- Yes! That's why they divorced.
Jae Hui, should we clean up now?
- You're full now, right?
- Yes.
Let's clean up and take a walk with me.
You can give me that.
We have three schedule changes on Thursday alone.
Let's set a new date. Okay? Set a new date.
Ms. Kim Eun Suk keeps calling. What should I do?
Attorney Cha said she explained.
She's impossible.
What should we do? I-In that case...
- Senior Manager!
- Yes.
Yes. Is there a problem?
I think we need to contact Attorney Cha at least once.
No, we can't do that. What should we do?
Should we contact her? What do we do?
- Oh, Attorney Jeong!
- Yes.
Boy, it's crazy here.
A client said she'll only speak to Attorney Cha.
I think we'll have to contact her.
No, please don't do that.
Gosh, it's her first vacation in ages.
I'll explain it to her, so please send me the file.
Yes! Thank you, Attorney Jeong.
- One chocolate flavor, please.
- One? You're not eating, Mom?
- Gosh, I can't eat ice—
- You should just eat one.
Should I? One more chocolate flavor, please!
- Please enjoy.
- Thank you.
- Welcome.
- Hello.
Jae Hui go slowly.
Mom, look all the way over there. Whoa, look at that!
Jae Hui, aren't you scared?
Nope.
Just kidding. I'm a little scared.
Look here.
Let me see. We look totally different.
- I think we look alike.
- What do you mean? I'm way prettier!
- Eun Chae, look there!
- Dad!
He's taking pictures.
One, two, three!
- One more time.
- One more time?
All right. One, two, three!
Okay! Eun Chae, hold tight. It's dangerous!
- I'm okay!
- Aigoo, it's fine.
Plaintiff Kim Hun, the Husband
Moss' (Marimo) name, Kim Min (Son)
Yeoncheon, Gyeonggi-do &lt;-&gt; Gangnam, Seoul
Three to four hours roundtrip
- Look here, Attorney Jeon.
- Okay.
Kim Ha Yun lives in Yeoncheon, Gyeonggi-do.
Marigold Tennis Court is in Gangnam, Seoul.
Exactly. It takes three to four hours roundtrip.
Who travels such distances to exercise?
As you said earlier, their goal isn't to exercise.
Also, at the tennis court earlier...
Are you from Hug Hug?
- Attorney?
- Yes, nice to meet you.
Someone was taking pictures of you and Kim Ha Yun.
It must be her husband, Kim Hun, the plaintiff.
This couple knows too well about the evidence needed for an adultery suit.
Let's meet tomorrow if you have time.
It has expired.
Gosh, it expired.
What should I do? I left my card at home.
Could you pay for mine first?
O-Oh, okay.
Could I get a membership, please?
For one or two people?
Two people.
Yes.
Straight and over.
A hotel's a bit...
They've done lawsuit fraud many times.
If I went to eat kimchi stew and saw the mosses,
I'd become an adulterer right away, too.
Aigoo, thank you for not telling me to go that far.
Hurry up and come.
How could that be? I don't get it.
I don't get it.
What do you want to eat?
Mr. Lee Seung Joon.
You're Mr. Lee Seung Jun, right?
Oh, yes.
Hey, you f***ing cheater.
Even if you didn't get a proper education at home,
shouldn't you have at least come and apologized first?
I-I'm-
I'm not 100% certain yet, but I'm skeptical about something.
Make sure not to say sorry to Ms. Kim Ha Yun's husband.
If you apologize, you're admitting you committed adultery.
It must've been tough.
What kind of nutcase is this?
Hey, you f***er.
Are you messing with me right now?
Hey, Seung Jun.
If things go to a verdict,
you're bound to become an adulterer.
I'm doing this out of pity for your life.
If you give me thirty million won right now,
I'll just agree to settle with you.
Th-thirty million...
You'll pay, right?
Okay.
Attorney Han, he said he'll cancel the suit if I pay him thirty million won.
I want to just pay him and end it.
You can't! Are you saying you'll admit being an adulterer?
That's absolutely not the case.
You have to fight to the end, then.
I'm doing my best as well.
If I don't give him the money right now,
he'll come to my school again.
If that happens, I'll be known as an adulterer, Attorney.
Don't lose heart, and hang in there for a bit longer.
I'll call you back.
Mom, look. Didn't I do a great job?
Didn't I do a pretty good job, too?
I get to try all sorts of things, thanks to you.
- I saw them do this.
- Mom, how did you know?
I also know a thing or two.
There you go! Jae Hui, try it.
- Is it good?
- It's delicious.
Are you sleeping, Jae Hui?
No new notifications.
♫  There's a small mirror in my heart  ♫
♫  No one will bother looking inside it  ♫
♫  I am looking  ♫
♫  ever so exhausted and tiny  ♫
Just put some cheese instead of scallions next time.
I hate scallions.
It's fine. I'll just eat it.
It's fine. I'll wait it out.
Good job.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
♫  'Cause you are beautiful  ♫
♫  A beautiful stranger  ♫
♫  Please hug my shrivelled heart ♫
I'm saying let's review if you must be on the Divorce Team...
Even without you, things will run smoothly as if you were never here.
So, don't worry, Attorney Cha.
♫  Please hug my shrivelled heart  ♫
♫  It will be very brief  ♫
♫  Eventually, it will pass again  ♫
♫  Always protecting me  ♫
♫  Even if someone tries to hurt you  ♫
♫  (Cause I am beautiful)  ♫
♫  (A beautiful stranger)  ♫
Jae Hui.
I thought I was needed both at home and at work.
But was it just a big misunderstanding?
Was I actually not doing well in either place?
♫  I hated you more than anyone  ♫
♫  In the end, loving you more  ♫
Could you confirm it for me?
What will happen to the case otherwise?
Of course. She requested a verification of facts.
How can I help— Oh, my!
Excuse me. How may I help you?
Who's Jeon Eun Ho?
- Sorry?
- Jeon Eun Ho.
I said, who's Jeon Eun Ho?
Hey, which one of you is Jeon Eun Ho?
Tell Attorney Jeon Eun Ho to come out!
Yes, I'm Jeon Eun Ho. What's the matter?
- Is it you?
- Yes.
- What are you doing right now?
- Let me go!
Has he gone mad?
What are you doing right now?
This is assault!
You'll wake up after a good beating.
What's the matter?
You're the higher-up here, huh?
I mean, this is a law firm, right?
That f***ing attorney slept with my wife!
What do you think about that?
- Who are you saying slept with whom?
- Come on!
- Calm down.
- How dare you!
Yes, sir. This is a law firm.
If you state false information in a public space like this,
it's defamation.
I'm calling the police.
Disgusting.
Hey...
You won't get away with this.
Also, the fake and real victims are revealed in the end.
How so?
The fake victim is in a rush
because he needs to take profit before his intent is found out,
so he can't wait around.
For example, he may threaten blackmail.
He'll do whatever it takes to produce fast results.
What the f*** are you looking at?
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
- Attorney Jeon, are you okay?
- Yes, I'm fine.
Attorneys Han Yu Ri and Jeon Eun Ho?
Come to my office.
So, Attorney Jeon is an adulterer.
No, I'm not. I'm definitely not. What are you talking about?
This married couple is a team of frauds.
This couple does this for a living.
Whoa, people like this really exist in this world, huh?
Attorney Han, you actually broke through the "Could it be" from back then.
But I didn't mean you should go this far.
I'm sorry.
As the saying goes, never say never.
They're really such terrible frauds.
All right. So, what's the plan now?
We need to close the argument now.
Ha Yun, I miss you. Shall we meet again?
Look at this.
Whoa, he doesn't even care the husband came to his work?
He totally fell for me.
I think he's actually more fired up.
Geez, seriously...
Throw!
Jae Hui.
All right. This one's a fastball. Catch it.
Son!
- All right. Catch!
- Yes.
Full power!
Your full power is nice.
I'll throw you in.
Fastball!
Jae Hui.
Jae Hui, please give me a hand here!
Could you help me with this?
The other side, please.
Nice! One more time.
Gosh, why is it so heavy?
One family bicycle, please.
You can take number three.
Let's go.
You'll be riding with your Mom and Dad, right? Three of you.
No, it'll be for two people.
I'm sorry. I thought it was for three people.
- Sure.
- You can take this one.
Let's go.
- Is it fun?
- Yes!
I'm fast, right?
I'll go faster.
Mom, in front of you!
Hey, Jae Hui. J-Jae Hui!
Wh-What do I do? Jae Hui, are you okay?
Look at me. Look at Mom.
Aigoo, wh-what's all this?
This tastes the best.
It seemed you're too busy to even eat out.
Do you usually eat here?
No, I usually eat out.
Aigoo, you even trimmed the cherry tomatoes. So much effort.
Hello, I'm Attorney Han Yu Ri, Mr. Lee Seung Jun's representative.
Attorney Jeon, what's the meaning of this?
It's a lunchbox this time, not kimchi stew?
You're really a fraud, huh?
I see...
- You're all in this together?
- Huh?
You and your husband are the only ones in this together.
Why live like that when you're still young?
If your husband is taking pictures right away on your first meeting,
it'd be impossible unless you're a band of frauds.
Well, i-it's possible.
Do you want me to sue you for fraud and interference with business, then?
You interfered with the business of Hug Hug by uploading false information
and your husband even grabbed me by the neck.
So he'll be investigated for assault as well.
F***.
Attorney, I'm sorry.
I'm under probation for another fraud right now.
I really can't get sued again.
You don't need to apologize to me.
You need to apologize to Mr. Lee Seung Jun.
Honey...
I mean, Mr. Lee Seung Jun...
I'm sorry.
Attorney, I'm sorry.
I'm under probation for another fraud right now.
I really can't get sued again.
You don't need to apologize to me.
You need to apologize to Mr. Lee Seung Jun.
Call Kim Hun and tell him to cancel the suit.
Oh, and also,
if he also submitted a complaint against our Attorney Jeon, take care of that, too.
Right now.
Honey, they found out. Cancel them right now.
Lee Seung Jun and Jeon Eun Ho were a team!
Thank you.
I'm not the one who did this.
This attorney here sacrificed himself.
Aigoo, you don't need to say that.
You need to treat me to something delicious.
Thank you so much, Attorneys.
Please take care.
Take care!
Railway Restaurant
-  Cheers!
-  Great work.
Attorney Jeon, I'm so sorry and
I'm tremendously thankful.
I'm sure you didn't want to do it.
I don't do things I don't want to do.
But I did it because it was with you, Han Yu Ri.
I'm really happy today.
Attorney Cha wasn't here, so I was really worried at first.
But I created a plan to prove my case and ran on my own feet to resolve the case
for the first time after becoming an attorney.
That's true.
It's the first time you did it entirely on your own, Attorney Han.
I can finally feel I really provided some real help in someone's life.
That's why I'm happy.
Seonbae, in what direction do you want our Divorce Team to go in the future?
A team that saves someone.
A divorce team that
opens up new lives, not putting an end to them.
It would've been great if Attorney Cha had been here.
I miss Attorney Cha.
- You get what I want to say, right?
- Hurry up and go. Yes.
Wait, is this my taxi?
Yes. Let's talk tomorrow.
Wait! I need to take Han Yu Ri home—
- Why are you sending only me home?
- Take care!
- Attorney Jeon, bye!
- Why are you sending me home?
If Attorney Cha Eun Gyeong had been here, you would've been scolded.
But I still want to compliment you.
Attorney Han Yu Ri, you did well on this case.
Thank you, Attorney Jeong.
Please get home safe now. I'll get going first.
Take care.
One second, Jae Hui.
There.
Nice and slowly. Aigoo.
- Be careful.
- Is the dad not here?
It's dangerous for you alone.
- Dad's not here!
- I'm the only guardian—
I'm sorry. I'll...
I'm texting Dad.
Jae Hui.
Why?
Can't I text Dad?
You can text him. Of course, you can.
Didn't both you and Dad want me to be a child?
That's why I'm being childish right now.
Why can't I do this?
I mean... D-Dad's far away right now.
So, if you suddenly tell him you're hurt, he'll be shocked.
Calm down just a bit, Jae Hui.
He'll come even if he's far away!
I'm hurt. He needs to come!
He needs to come running right now!
I'm by your side right now.
It's true I'm a bit inadequate,
but I'm doing my best right now, Jae Hui. Right?
I just...
miss Dad so much.
I hold it in again and again...
but I miss him even more.
I really hate Dad so much.
But I still miss him.
Mom...
is Dad really gone from our lives now?
I-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. It's my fault. My baby...
Emergency Room
♫  I'm also a little scared  ♫
♫  I'm afraid of everything hidden  ♫
♫  Like an old diary  ♫
♫  Although it is  precious  ♫
♫  Maybe I might miss it a little, indeed  ♫
♫  If we honestly faced each other  ♫
♫  how would it have been?  ♫
♫  If that's what happened  ♫
♫  would it have been okay? I think so.  ♫
She won't answer.
♫  I'm always falling down  ♫
Looks amazing...
♫   I feel like I'm losing my way  ♫
♫  I feel as though everything I had disappeared  ♫
♫  That's something which couldn't be helped  ♫
♫  You can't blame anyone  ♫
♫  Every time  ♫
♫  Always falling down  ♫
♫  The night has deepened  ♫
♫  When the dawn breaks  ♫
♫  can I say it  ♫
♫  In my cold heart  ♫
What are you doing here?
When I feel frustrated,
I come to the empty office after everyone's gone,
and I feel a bit relaxed.
How odd.
It's the same for me.
We have fewer places to go to while living only for work and home.
You and I both.
♫  That's something which couldn't be helped  ♫
♫  You can't blame anyone  ♫
Cha Eun Gyeong
♫  Every time  ♫
Cha Eun Gyeong's absence is huge.
♫  Always falling down  ♫
♫  Because I'm not ignoring a broken heart  ♫
Missed Call
Missed Call: Han Yu Ri
Han Yu Ri
♫  In the still darkness  ♫
♫    I don’t want to be lost  ♫
Hello?
Can I get after-service?
Attorney Cha, is something wrong?
Both at work and at home,
it seems no one needs me.
♫  I feel that everything I had has disappeared  ♫
♫  That's something which couldn't be helped  ♫
What should I do?
Please give me...
Daejeong Law Firm.
♫  Every time  ♫
♫  Always falling down  ♫
♫  Facing challenges I persisted  ♫
♫  Learning to navigate heavy days  ♫
♫  But, it's still hard ♫
♫  Because sometimes tears will flow  ♫
Good Partner
Just get a dismissal for the VIP's case.
I'll hold off on firing Cha Eun Gyeong temporarily.
The CEO gave it exclusively to Attorney Han Yu Ri.
I don't have the tenure to take on the VIP cases, but I'm on it...
Sometimes, unacceptable things happen.
I really need you, Attorney Cha.
Let's give our best and finish it well.
That's how we can protect my position, right?
♫  It's going to be the start for you  ♫