(Good Partner)
(Divorce)
(In session)
(Plaintiff)
(Cha Eun Kyung)
(Han Yu Ri)
(Good Partner)
(All people, locations, organizations,)
(incidents, and backstories in this drama are fictitious.)
(Staff ensured child actors' safety in the filming of this drama.)
(Seoul Family Court)
Defendant, I ask you this first.
Why must you be the one to raise your daughter?
To the family investigator,
you must discredit the mother as much as possible.
Be petty if you have to.
None of it can be proved, so say whatever you want.
I raised Jae Hui all by myself.
The mother was married to her job...
and only came home around 1 to 2 in the morning.
Look here, Mr. Kim.
She never once attended Jae Hui's graduation...
or entrance ceremonies.
What are you talking about?
I was at her kindergarten graduation...
and her elementary school entrance ceremony.
She's yet to graduate the latter.
How dare you lie?
Ms. Cha, I mean...
Plaintiff. I'd like to hear from the defendant first.
Right.
I learned how to raise a child and put it into practice.
Even when she recently had her first period,
I bought pads for her.
You know what that implies.
Is this true, Plaintiff?
Yes, that's true.
However, how is that important...
regarding this custody battle?
It's not even worth hearing about.
That's for me to determine, Plaintiff.
Defendant, is there more to add?
If I can say more,
I'd like to add that I made her birthday cakes myself...
because it was sad her mom never celebrated birthdays with her.
The loneliness one feels while raising a child alone?
You must experience it to know it yourself.
Plaintiff, please rebuttal.
For my child,
I took on the position as the breadwinner of the family.
For our child?
You did that to feed your career.
Are you saying it was all for our child?
Of course.
Of course it was for you and Jae Hui.
What an excuse.
Being acknowledged and moving up the ranks...
as well as poaching rich VIP clients.
You valued them over motherhood.
While you did, she waited for you and cried herself to sleep.
And 13 years passed.
Jae Hui cried herself to sleep again.
How can you call yourself her mom when she barely gets to see you?
You're even busier these days.
Just go about your work...
like always.
We're lovers.
But I never thought about remarrying.
I already failed once at marriage. Why would I want to marry again?
Stop it! I'm sick of it.
Know your place!
I'll protect you.
You must also...
be a working mom.
Yes, I am.
Promotions and snagging deals.
Is there a mother...
who devotes herself to work...
because it outvalues her child?
What motivated me...
was the fact that my success...
would provide my daughter with tools she'll need...
to easily navigate this world.
Like he said,
I admit I neglected my family...
while trying to move up at the office.
From here on out,
I will raise her with love...
and have her be a fine young lady.
I can't allow that.
All that's left for me in this marriage...
is Jae Hui.
She did everything she wanted to do...
that granted her wealth and a solid career.
I can't let her also have Jae Hui.
Eun Kyung.
I had court today.
- Are you done here? - Yes.
- Will you be heading to the office? - Yes.
I'll drive you.
Sure.
(Seoul Family Court)
I bet it was exhausting.
(Episode 8)
It'll all blow over.
For you and Director Kim...
I mean, Kim Ji Sang.
You can solely focus on Jae Hui now.
That, I should.
Thanks.
How he's trying...
to claim custody after what he did...
amazes me.
Can I put a positive spin on that?
We come across cases...
where both parents refuse to take custody.
Consider this as him saying he'll still be a father to her.
Is that it?
I thought that could cheer you up.
I have a favor to ask.
The family investigator is also a working mom,
so she seemed understanding of Eun Kyung's situation.
Your daughter will soon be attending middle school...
which means what she wants is crucial.
The family investigator will meet with Jae Hui.
In other words, this will be Jae Hui's choice.
What can I do, then?
I advise...
that you consider Choi Sa Ra as a card you can sacrifice.
A card I can sacrifice?
Financial support,
the fact that she's a girl,
and that she'll reach puberty soon.
Did you raise all those points?
It's better for adolescents...
to be raised by a parent of the same gender.
I spoke of that.
It's now up to Jae Hui.
The family investigator will be making home visits soon.
Kim Ji Sang decorated a room in the way Jae Hui likes it.
You should do that as well.
What does she like?
She's not childish enough to be swayed by that.
Ms. Cha, please.
I'm not saying you should shower her with gifts...
so that she will choose you.
What I mean is that you should express...
your love and interest for her.
I see.
That's a good idea.
How do you know about this when you don't have a child?
I may not be someone's mom, but I'm someone's daughter.
You came.
What's the case you want me to take?
Ms. Han, tell him.
Oh, right.
It's a custody battle.
According to the family investigator's report,
the child is greatly attached to the father.
We're most likely to win, right?
That's right.
It was an intense year-long case.
The son is a high schooler who is close to his father.
When the family investigator asked, he said he'd live with the dad.
There's a good chance the mother will finally give up,
so all you need to do is finish it up.
It just happened to overlap with another one.
Okay, I'll take care of it.
- Thanks. - Thank you, Mr. Jung.
(In session)
The investigation into the family...
revealed how much the son wishes to live with his father.
I suggest a settlement following a mediation.
(Plaintiff)
Your Honor,
I have evidence to submit.
Go ahead.
(DNA Test Report)
(Result)
(Park Seo Jin is not Park Ji Hwan's biological son.)
The custody battle has been going on for a year,
but now you're saying they're not biologically related?
I'm sorry.
Did the plaintiff...
deliberately withhold this fact?
Or did she just find out?
She was aware of it, but couldn't tell the father.
However, the biological father...
is now suing to claim his parental rights.
That is why the plaintiff wishes to end...
this custody dispute.
If the defendant isn't the biological father,
there will be no reason to continue this custody trial.
Defending counsel?
In the light of this new claim,
we'd like the time to reassess our strategy.
Sure. Go over this with your clients.
The next hearing will be a negotiation.
What?
She knowingly lied to him for 18 years.
They're not biologically related.
It hurts, but what can you do?
We'll drop the custody battle and sue her for emotional damage.
Thanks for this.
I'll talk to the father myself.
Since I took the case, I'll see it through.
Thanks for this, Woo Jin.
- I ask that you do a good job. - Sure.
Ms. Cha told me you were a respectable lawyer.
Right.
I'm afraid...
we came across an unexpected issue.
But she said my case was close to being over.
Did something happen?
This will probably shock you.
Is his mother still not backing off?
Unbelievable.
But I'm the one Seo Jin wants to live with.
You may tell me anything, Mr. Jung.
I've been through a lot this past year,
and nothing could shock me.
Seo Jin...
isn't your biological son.
What?
Seo Jin's mother...
submitted a DNA test report...
that shows you and your son...
aren't a biological match.
What the...
Is she actually going that far to win custody over our son?
Unbelievable.
She will stop at nothing.
I'm sure it was forged.
I confirmed its authenticity...
with your wife's attorney.
You are to run a test of your own...
if you don't believe her.
What are you saying?
How does this make sense?
Whose son is he if he isn't mine?
My Seo Jin...
has my personality...
and looks just like me!
The test must be wrong.
Whose son is he if he isn't mine?
Whose?
(Case 08: That's How Fatherhood Begins)
We'll get going first. See you tomorrow.
Be honest with me. Didn't you doze off?
Did you doze off as well?
I blacked out halfway through class.
(My everything)
- Are your classes over? - Yes.
What did the court say?
Did they tell Mom what I told the family investigator?
I bet it shocked her.
Don't worry too much.
No matter how this ends,
you'll still have two parents in your life.
No one can separate us.
Dad. When will you go home?
Can I come over to play a game?
Sure you can.
I'll come over now.
- What just happened? Get up. - Kick.
- Here goes! - A flying kick.
- A flying kick! - Uppercut!
A flying kick.
- No! - Yes.
- I won again. - I lost again.
It's not as fun now that I'm much better.
You should practice.
I let you win because you're my son.
Darn it.
It's time to go.
I wish the trial would end and I could live with you.
Do you think I'll let you play games all day if you live with me?
Brush your teeth before you go. You had some chocolate.
You said that for 18 years.
I will even if you don't tell me to.
Did you talk to the client?
He seemed to love the boy more than I thought.
This is a first for us.
Let's try and get the most alimony ever.
Yes, let's.
Money alone isn't enough to compensate,
but that's our job.
I'll expand the cause and demand of alimony...
and sue for child support that was paid so far.
We must also charge them...
for the expenses of the year-long custody battle.
We live in a world where parents abandon their kids.
He raised a child that wasn't his. He deserves compensation.
Yes.
You must consider giving up on Choi Sa Ra.
What do you mean "give up?"
What judge would give custody...
to a man who's living with his affair partner?
And what daughter would choose...
a dad who had an affair with a family friend?
Keep as much distance as you can with Choi Sa Ra.
About what we discussed last time.
You asked if we'd live together after I got a divorce.
I got my answer that day. You don't have to explain anymore.
After the divorce is finalized,
we can think about it then.
No. You and I have different circumstances.
It would be wrong not to be clear and allow a misunderstanding.
You just want to date me.
You don't want to marry me.
Did you come here to say that?
You made that very clear last time.
I talked to a family investigator...
and realized I have no energy to spend on anything else.
Jae Hui will come see me this week,
and even after the divorce, I'll still be Jae Hui's dad.
I don't want you to bring that up for a while.
What about our baby, then?
Are you saying Jae Hui needs her dad's care...
and our baby can be abandoned?
What do you mean "our baby?"
I'm pregnant.
What?
Eight weeks.
No way.
Is this for real?
- Are you ready? - Yes.
You'll be there for just a day, and you'll study?
There's homework, and I'm stuck. I'll ask Dad for his help.
I see. Is that it?
You don't like it?
Why would I dislike that?
I'm afraid you'll study all day when you barely have...
enough time to have fun with your dad.
The court will send someone to Dad's home?
Yes.
Relax and do your thing.
You can say anything you want.
- Dad's here. Bye. - Bye.
A trial to prove the child isn't his.
I think these cases are the hardest.
"Petition to deny paternity."
Doesn't the term make you feel sad?
Doesn't it, Mr. Jung?
It does. Denying paternity of a child.
It's heartbreaking.
Hello, Ms. Cha.
I attached the DNA test report Park Ji Hwan got and submitted...
a petition denying paternity.
Okay. Did we get the payment for the extra lawsuit?
Yes. I confirmed the wire transfer.
Good.
She's tough. She doesn't mind the sad lawsuit.
Be quiet.
Thanks a lot.
I hope Divorce Team Two will handle this well for me.
- Sure. - Okay.
- Give me another coin. - Instead of a coin...
You can jump in too!
Yes!
No way.
Neener.
One, two, three.
You have three-meter-long legs.
I got it.
We were here around this time last year.
It's been exactly a year.
Do you know I brought you here...
for the flower festival every year since you were one?
Yes.
Why did you bring me here?
Bringing you to the same place as you grew up...
made it feel like our memories grew as well.
Jae Hui, wave at Mom.
- Dad! - Jae Hui.
Hi, there.
Let's go.
What a good girl.
Miss Kim. Do you like the carousel when you're a grown girl?
Yes.
Do you really?
I prefer this to looking for something new to do.
Yes. You liked old things.
That's why you don't throw things out.
I never saw you...
get sick of something you liked.
Right.
How is your mom doing?
She always pretends to be strong and okay.
She's the same.
Jae Hui.
Even if you live with me,
you can see Mom as much as you want.
Don't worry too much about her.
After dropping Jae Hui off tomorrow, go to the OB-GYN with me.
- Rest in your room. - Okay.
I'll make you a strawberry juice.
Jae Hui.
This is the family investigator.
- Hello. - Hi.
Oh, this must be your room.
- Come in. - Well...
Can you let us two talk?
You can wait outside for a bit.
Oh, okay.
Thank you.
- Take a seat. - Thanks.
First, I think I should explain what I do.
The court wants to know what kind of relationship...
you have with your parents as your caregivers,
and who can provide you with...
the best living environment.
My duty is to check that.
You're basically here to ask who I prefer,
my mom or dad.
No, it's not like that.
Your mom and dad...
might not live together anymore,
but as your parents, for your sake...
I heard that so many times my ears might bleed.
Only when the adults are honest with me...
will I honestly say what I think.
Jae Hui, shall I read you a book?
It's okay.
Sleep well.
I took on the position as the breadwinner of the family.
You did that to feed your career.
While you did, she waited for you and cried herself to sleep.
And 13 years passed.
"This rose means so much..."
"because of the time you spent with it."
"But you can't forget."
"You're always responsible..."
"for what you tamed."
"You're responsible for your rose."
This is my favorite part.
"You're always responsible..."
"for what you tamed."
"You're responsible for your rose."
Hey, I feel the same.
Do you know you're Dad's rose?
Keep reading.
Kim Rose, read yourself to sleep.
I haven't read to you in bed in ten years.
Will you let me off?
No. I want you to read this book to me.
It's fun, and it helps me sleep.
Okay, then.
I'll keep reading to you in bed until you get a sibling.
"You're always responsible..."
"for what you tamed."
"You're responsible for your rose."
My Jae Hui.
This is how she waited...
every night.
You're always responsible for what you tamed.
You're responsible...
- for your rose. - For your rose.
- You're home. - Yes.
Oh, that...
It was really dirty.
I brought it out to wipe it down.
Get ready for school. I'll drop you off.
- Get changed. - Okay.
I told you not to come here. If someone sees...
I don't care if someone sees.
Was it nice to spend the night with Jae Hui again?
You must've had a lot to think about.
- You did great. - I can't go with you to the OB-GYN.
My dad wants you there.
What man goes to an OB-GYN while fighting for custody?
You're weighing me down now.
Why are you so inconsiderate?
You spent a whole 24 hours with Jae Hui.
Our baby's getting ready to enter the world,
and you won't even go to see it?
How is that the same?
How is it different?
All lives are equal. I'm saying the circumstances aren't.
I don't want to fight.
Okay.
Let's say I don't make such demands...
until the divorce is final.
What about after that? What happens then?
I told you. I'm not interested in marriage,
and I'll live with Jae Hui.
I made it clear.
Not being married to me doesn't mean you're not a dad.
I'm sorry.
I need time to think, but that time...
isn't right now.
If you don't get custody of Jae Hui,
can our baby...
live with its dad then?
That won't happen,
but if Jae Hui lives with her mom,
let's think about it then.
We informed the court that you deny paternity.
I think the family register will get sorted out.
We'll do our best so you get back...
the money you paid as child support so far.
Mr. Jun.
I want to drop the lawsuit.
I asked to see you to say that.
What? You can't do that.
If you don't set straight the records about your paternity,
you'll have to leave everything to him.
And even after you're divorced,
your ex-wife can demand you pay child support.
I think your emotions are preventing you...
from being rational.
I completely understand what you're saying.
I also know that you're just looking out for my best interest.
But she just happened to deceive me.
That's not my son's fault.
No one is saying that.
We're just urging you to protect yourself.
I'm doing this to protect myself too.
My dear son, Seo Jin...
Once it becomes official...
that he's not my son,
I won't be able to live like that. I'm sorry.
No, Mr. Park.
But I still don't think this is right.
You must think carefully about this.
You must maintain a rational mind about this.
You will have to pay child support...
when he's not your biological son.
No! He's my son.
I don't care about getting extorted out of some money for child support.
Thank you for meeting me like this.
Are you...
pregnant?
So you saw it.
Didn't you put it in there for me to find it?
Gosh. No, that wasn't my intention.
I care a lot about you too.
Why would you?
That's because...
we're close.
Don't you think you're being too cruel toward me?
I'm still in elementary school.
You're basically all grown up.
But it seems your parents treat you like a little kid.
You'll start middle school soon.
But if you ask me, I think you're all grown up now.
I helped my mom run her business when I was your age.
That baby...
Is that my dad's?
Yes. You have a sibling now.
You will be a good sibling to our baby, Sa Rang, right?
Sa Rang?
Does my mother know?
No.
If your mother finds out, she'll be deeply hurt.
The lawsuit will get dragged on.
There will be articles too, right?
Did you even apologize to my mother?
Jae Hui. I'm sorry.
It's all our fault as adults.
But you've sufficiently been loved by your father.
And your mother desperately needs you too.
Can't you tell the family investigator...
that you must absolutely live with your mother?
I'm really sorry to ask you of this.
Don't apologize to me. Did you apologize to my mother?
Jae Hui. Where are you?
I'm on my way home.
Jae Hui.
- Hello. - Hey.
What are you doing out here?
Did you come here alone?
I was just passing by.
Should I ask your mom to come down?
(In front of Daejeong Building)
I have no problem taking the bus on my own.
You don't have to wait with me.
Gosh, I know that you're a smart girl.
But I'll see you getting on the bus before I go.
Where are you going?
Home? Your academy?
I don't know where I should go.
You should go home.
Which one?
The one with my mom? Or the one with my dad?
When I was your age,
I had a complicated family matter too.
So I somewhat know what you must be going through.
So did the complicated matter...
get sorted out well?
Of course.
It was over in due time.
But of course, I think about it from time to time.
Hey.
Be safe.
Hello.
Gosh. Let me.
Okay.
I'm sorry...
for making you come over at this late hour.
I have no one to talk about this.
I see. I understand.
With whom could you possibly talk about what happened to you?
You can vent all you want on me.
Gosh.
Dad.
Hey.
Hello.
You must be Seo Jin.
Yes.
He didn't get back to me, so I stopped by.
My study room is in this neighborhood.
I always had pork cutlets for dinner my dad fried for me.
We also had late-night snacks before I went back home.
He said he was going to have a drink with you here tonight.
Gosh. You and your dad must be very close.
My dad has high blood pressure. He shouldn't drink this much.
Everything is okay with him, right?
Of course. Nothing is wrong.
Gosh. It's my son. When did you get here?
Dad. Wake up. We're almost home.
Gosh. My son is so reliable.
Don't go anywhere.
I won't.
What's gotten into you today? Your attorney is here too.
You have me for the night. Remember?
I'll sleep over.
Don't go anywhere.
Do you resemble your father a lot?
No. Not at all.
I see.
I'm the spitting image of my dad, aren't I?
Yes. You're the spitting image of him.
All right. Today, we're having...
S and B.
That's it. Well done.
Squid and beer.
Do you remember this was the very spot...
I told you about Kim Ji Sang's affair?
Right. You said it was...
about your friend of a friend or something.
You were such a bad liar.
Do you remember what you told me?
Me? What did I say?
If I found out even later on that my wife cheated on me,
I'd end it right then.
Why stay together when half the world is made up of women?
You said half the world was made up of women.
Gosh.
That was only a few months ago.
But I now have a different opinion about that.
What did Park Ji Hwan say?
He said he wanted to live as Seo Jin's dad...
as long as possible.
Do you still think divorce cases are fun?
Did you know that your behavior can be contagious?
You already infected me.
I'm too invested in this case now.
It was awful for you too, right?
That's why I couldn't go home right away.
I got you to drink with me here.
Before I started this job, I thought divorces happened...
because a spouse did wrong...
and the other spouse decided to end it.
I thought divorces weren't much different from breakups.
But...
it wasn't simply a breakup between a man and a woman.
Our textbook talks about the best interest of the child.
The principle says...
the child's happiness must be our top priority.
Gosh. When I met up with Mr. Park today,
I could understand what the textbook was saying.
Hang in there.
You too.
Cheers.
- Great meeting, everyone. - Great meeting.
What does Mr. Park want to do?
He wants to withdraw his intention for the lawsuit.
He raised his son with all of his heart.
I understand why he wants to remain as his legal father.
Once the two-year exclusion period ends,
he will never be able to file a lawsuit.
Shouldn't we try to urge him more strongly to pursue this?
I don't think there's any point trying to explain the legal risk.
Let's drop the lawsuit.
In terms of alimony and child support,
we should negotiate, so he doesn't face any loss.
I trust your judgment, so proceed accordingly.
- Okay. - Okay.
- We'll get going. - Good luck.
- Thanks. - Bye.
Bye.
(Mediation Room)
(Defendant)
I've had this job for ten years now.
But I've never had a case like this.
Could you say something to explain yourself, plaintiff?
I'm sorry.
Don't you think...
you should apologize to my client, not the mediator?
I'm sorry.
How could you do this?
Have you been seeing him the whole time we were married?
Were you telling me nothing but lies?
It was only that one time.
One time? Are you serious?
So it's okay to cheat on me just one time?
You even did the DNA test.
Why did you drag on this lawsuit for a year if you knew?
Were you using Seo Jin and me...
to cover up your mistake?
If I won, were you even going to let me raise Seo Jin?
How could you call yourself his mother after what you did?
It was really hard on me too...
when I had to keep lying to you.
Why do you insist on raising my son?
He's my son too.
Seo Jin wants to live with me!
Think about your son for once!
Gosh.
I couldn't keep lying to you.
When you asked me for a divorce,
I thought it was because I wasn't good enough.
I'm a lowly cook who fries pork cutlets.
I'll try to understand you and let's say I forgave you for it.
But how could you do this to Seo Jin?
The defendant must have been miserable...
to cope with the fact that he was deceived.
Despite that, he only thought about Seo Jin.
He decided not to take any legal measures...
as he was worried...
Seo Jin would be utterly shocked if he were to find out.
Honey.
Take this secret to the grave, please.
That's the only thing I want.
Just let me...
stay as my son's father.
(Mediation Committee)
We would like to ask for one thing.
We won't be able to take custody.
So let's not put...
any visitation restrictions for my client to see Seo Jin.
We can't allow that.
He's not the biological father.
Let's keep it at two visits per month.
Right, he's not.
But don't you remember he withdrew his demand for child support...
and decided not to file for a denial of paternity?
After all that, if you insist on visitation restrictions...
Eighteen years.
He raised Seo Jin with love for 18 years.
Let him see Seo Jin freely as much as he wants.
Let's settle on that.
(Plaintiff)
Thank you...
so much for helping me keep my son in my life.
Gosh, you don't need to thank us.
You're his father.
Even if we couldn't help you,
I'm sure Seo Jin would have come to see you often.
Right. His mother gave up on the division of assets.
So that's basically getting back...
the child support fee you paid.
That's the silver lining.
Right.
I will continue...
to live as Seo Jin's dad.
I'll do my best to make sure Seo Jin never finds out about this.
- I'll get going now. - Okay.
Hey, my son.
Yes. Where are you?
Yes. You're spending the night with me tonight, right?
Is there anything you want to eat?
Yes. See you later.
- Good work today. - Good job.
Good job today. Well done.
Not at all.
I'm going to head home first. For the family investigation.
Right. Sure. Bye.
Bye.
- Eun Kyung. - Yes?
It's all going to work out. Don't worry too much.
Thanks.
(Attorney at law, Jun Eun Ho)
- Mr. Jun. - Yes.
How did Park Ji Hwan's case go?
Well, it worked out.
But why am I so sad today?
You did a great job.
(Attorney at law, Jung Woo Jin)
Your room is very pretty.
Did your mom decorate it for you?
Yes.
Both my mom and dad are...
suddenly busy filling my room with my favorite items.
It feels like...
I'm getting my Christmas gifts for ten years at once.
You're humorous.
So?
Can you tell me what's on your mind today?
Can I get straight to the conclusion?
I wanted to ask if you needed a drink.
My work is done.
That was fast.
We didn't have to beat around the bush.
Really? That's better.
I'll get going.
- Yes. Thank you for your work. Bye. - Bye, Jae Hui.
- Thank you for the ride. - Sure.
By the way,
do you have something to celebrate?
In the middle of the custody lawsuit and the family investigation?
What would I have to celebrate?
Exactly.
But why do you look happy?
I'm not.
In the family investigation,
it said Jae Hui hadn't said...
what was on her mind.
Did she say she wanted to live with her mom? Is that it?
It's just my guess.
It seems Jae Hui has decided to live with me.
She said she was relieved.
Gosh.
To be honest, she asked me...
whether the lawsuit will be over if she tells the family investigator...
that she wants to live with her mom.
Did she?
Then I must be right.
For sure.
She's going to middle school soon.
Her opinion will be reflected.
You won't have to worry about her custody anymore.
You can be at ease for the last family investigation.
Thanks, Ms. Han.
What's this awkward silence?
Your advice to decorate her room with her favorites.
No, to express my interest in her.
That was very helpful.
After the last nurture environment investigation,
Jae Hui seemed somewhat relieved.
Can you tell me what you talked about?
In the first family investigation,
Jae Hui refused to talk.
She kept saying we have to be honest for her to be honest.
The grown-ups have to be honest with me first.
Until then, I don't plan to be honest.
When we hold family investigations,
children often say...
adults are lying.
Perhaps that's because...
they can't accept the fact their parents are breaking up?
No.
Children often say that when their parents force them...
to believe what they believe is not true.
What do you mean?
Jae Hui knows everything.
Oh, yes. Well...
- Her dad's affair... - No.
She learned that her dad was having an affair with Aunt Sa Ra...
before you did.
Ms. Cha.
Jae Hui was little Cha Eun Kyung.
You knew?
I thought you didn't know...
Did you think I wouldn't know? Me?
Look.
(She learned the defendant's affair with Choi Sa Ra...)
(before the plaintiff and was anxious.)
I'm no longer a kid.
But I guess Dad and Aunt Sa Ra...
didn't think I'd know.
Hi.
Where's Jae Hui?
She fell asleep while working on her homework.
- Jae Hui will wake up. - It's fine.
He lied to me in front of me.
I've never seen you getting sick of anything...
that you like.
Even if you live with me,
you can see Mom as much as you want.
So you don't need to worry about Mom so much.
Even though I gave him a chance, he lied to me until the end.
And...
this was really difficult for me to bring up.
What is it?
Tell me everything.
She will have a half-sibling.
When she went to her dad's house,
she must've seen the ultrasound picture.
- What? - Jae Hui...
told me to keep it a secret from you.
How could you hide this from me?
To be honest...
You should've told your mom.
Mom...
keeps lying to me to protect me.
I want to protect her heart.
I don't want to burden her.
Just as how all parents love their children in their own ways,
perhaps children are also...
struggling every moment to protect...
the way their parents love them...
and their sincerity.
Is that the way...
children love their parents?
Who is it?
I said, who is it?
Father.
(Good Partner)
I know she's our client,
but Jang Seon A is a nasty piece of work.
He tried to seduce me first.
An earnest apology. That's what I need to carry on.
I said I wanted even a forced apology from you...
instead of money.
You must pull yourself together especially in times like this.
I guess I don't deserve to be a mom.
How much am I supposed to do for her?