Good Partner
Daejeong
In session | Plaintiff
Good Partner
This drama is fiction.
Characters, places, agencies, events, organizations, and the setting have no connection to real life.
Child actors were filmed in a safe environment.
Attorney Cha Eun Gyeong is here with us again today,
and she'll resolve your family problems once and for all.
Hello, I'm Cha Eun Gyeong, your attorney.
Yes. Attorney Cha, you know how in the dramas,
there are cases where people around a person
find out about the spouse's affair before they do.
Does it also happen in real life?
Six months ago
Letter of Appointment
Thank you for taking the time out of your busy day to join our law firm.
We'll look forward to both of your performances going forward.
Don't mention it. I'll be in your care.
The quality of Daejeong's future medical cases will go up a notch now.
Episode 3
Do you need something, Jae Hui?
No, I just want some water.
Jae Hui!
- Aigoo, Jae Hui.
- Hello.
- Hey, Jae Hui, long time no see!
- Hi, Jae Hui.
- How are you?
- You grew so much
Jae Hui, it's a celebration for Dad today. You won't mind some noise, right?
Yes, I don't mind it.
I'll get going now.
- Yes, sure.
- What a sweetheart.
All right. Director Kim Ji Sang, who became Daejeong Law Firm's medical advisor,
should give us a word now.
Yes, well, I'm all over the place, working at the hospital and taking care of Jae Hui.
But I'm worried I took on another job. I'll try my best.
Congratulations. Let's have a toast.
Congrats.
So, how did you suddenly become our medical advisor?
Did you suggest it, Seonbae?
CEO was troubled by the quality of our medical cases,
so I proposed the idea to the CEO first and told him about it.
That makes the Director a man with two offices now, huh?
The advisory office at the law firm, and the doctor's office at the hospital.
Well, wouldn't we meet at least once more if we work in the same office?
Aren't you being too loving?
What a silly thing to say.
All of your glasses are empty, huh?
Shall we have one more round of drinks?
- Yes.
- Of course, I'll have one more.
But we don't have enough alcohol, huh?
- Why? There's no more?
- Yes, there's no more alcohol.
Ma'am, please take a look inside the fridge!
Thank you.
There's no more. I'll go out and buy some.
No, I can make the trip.
You will?
She probably doesn't know where to go. I'll be right back.
Yes, you should go instead, Honey.
- I'll be right back.
- Okay.
Attorney Cha, let me pour you a drink.
- I'll help him since it'll be too much to carry alone.
- Okay.
- It was a lot of work to prepare this, right?
- Not at all.
Should we have a toast with those who are here?
- I love it!
- Let's go.
Yes, there are way too many.
You deny it even if you notice something suspicious,
telling yourself it could never happen and being defensive.
So, you sometimes find out after the people around you do.
How's the car now that you've driven it a few days?
First of all, I like how there's no noise.
I think sedans are better for me than sports cars.
Yes, since you're sensitive to noise.
But I'll have to study it because it's got so many functions.
I like how the screen is wide.
What's this? It's got this function, too? Who's this?
- Leave it!
-  A message from Director Choi. "Where are you?"
The discovery of an affair usually starts with, "Where are you?"
"Where are you?" may not sound like much,
but it's a very intimate phrase used between people who share their daily lives together.
Who is it?
Oh, it's my hospital director
since I'm still not back even after lunchtime.
I see.
Director Choi
Sa Ra, why do you take so long at the court these days?
I'm sorry.
There's always traffic on the way back, and my lunch break overlaps.
So, I just ate lunch and came back in.
You can leave.
If you haven't secured certain evidence of your spouse's affair,
is it right to feign ignorance?
Yes, you can never let them know while you're collecting evidence.
You must hold back until you secure the perfect evidence.
Director Kim isn't here right now.
He asked me for documents regarding his contract.
Please give this to him for me.
He'll be here in about 10 minutes, though.
I guess he's at lunch?
Oh, didn't you know?
Director Kim only sees patients in the afternoon these days.
You're right. I forgot.
Kim Jin Cheol, Director Kim Ji Sang
Jeong Hye Won, Han Sang Tae, Kim Gyu Hui
By the way, didn't Director Choi work here?
None of our directors have a last name "Choi."
Why do you ask?
It's nothing.
You see loose links here and there in your daily life.
Yes.
Is Jae Hui's phone with you?
Yes, she left it in my car when we went to the museum yesterday.
You should've been more careful.
How can you say that when you couldn't even see Jae Hui's face over the entire weekend?
I left it in my office at the law firm this morning.
You can give it to her.
Okay.
Cafe Marrige
There's a moment...
when all those loose links get connected at once like a puzzle.
Whoa, that's scary.
Please tell our listeners what to do if that moment comes.
You must stay rational.
Don't get worked up and do anything you'd regret.
Director Kim Ji Sang
-  Hey.
- Did you take her phone to Jae Hui?
I can't because I've got consultations back to back.
You said you'd bring it to her earlier.
I'm busy.
For example, dragging the adulterers by their hair
or damaging your own home.
Things you'd get blamed for in reverse.
I see. Dear listeners, if you happen to experience this,
I hope you'll stay rational throughout.
Is there any last word of advice you have for us?
A spouse's adultery
can happen to anyone.
Please don't lose your composure,
and make it out of the tunnel of pain successfully.
Case 03: Strangers who became family.
Y-You knew all about it, Attorney Cha?
What are you doing now, coming to my house in the middle of the night?
I mean
I thought you didn't know—
You thought I wouldn't know?
No way. You're not going to get a divorce?
No, I won't.
I'm not going to do it, so you don't need to make a fuss over it, either.
How can you let those people get away with it?
If it were me, I would file the complaint right this moment
and let their workplace and the world know!
What will I get by doing that?
Getting a divorce and division of property,
does it get resolved if I get merely 20 million won in alimony?
Because that's all you can do
by legal means where adultery isn't a crime anymore.
Your one-dimensional thought process is truly amazing.
Drive out a secretary who's been taking care of my business for ten years
and a father who's been taking care of my child for 13 years.
Is it right to just go home with the 20 million won,
which isn't even close to what I make a month?
If that's all you can do right now,
you should at least do those things.
Attorneys your age are dragged around by the law.
You become a real attorney if you use the law instead of getting pushed around by it.
Still, two people closest to you betrayed you, Attorney Cha.
How can you just do nothing?
Right, adultery.
An illegal act.
It's not even a crime anymore. So, what about it?
Are you saying you're okay?
My work and home are busier than ever, and I need them.
Not your work or your home.
What about your life?
Work and home...
are my life.
You're really going to leave?
I told you all along.
I'm not going because it's our wedding anniversary.
I'm going to convince her to divorce me.
How can I believe that?
They say a married couple's fight is futile.
A married couple's fight?
We aren't a couple anymore, so what couple's fight?
You won't eat with Cha Eun Gyeong, right?
You called me over for soybean paste stew so that I wouldn't eat with her, didn't you?
You got me.
I'll call you.
Is it our 14th anniversary?
We really didn't get to celebrate our anniversaries all this time.
Why on earth won't you reply?
- Reply to what?
- I sent you the text.
How do you want to go about the divorce?
I came because you'd keep delaying it if I didn't talk to you in person.
I see.
Divorce?
What's the cause of divorce you're talking about?
Even if I tell you, we'll only argue.
Let's stop going around in circles and end it amicably.
You're saying I was negligent to my family, right?
Me?
Negligence doesn't even come close.
I was playing family all alone.
I don't want to talk anymore, so please just agree to settle.
I'll pay closer attention to Jae Hui.
If this were bad enough for a divorce, no families would be intact.
That's exactly the cause of divorce.
The difference where a situation
that's so hard I want to die is so trivial to you.
That's your cause of divorce?
If we get a divorce, the entire country will know.
Must you really take it that far?
That's the reason in the end, right?
Your reputation matters more to you even now, right?
If we get that divorce,
what difference will it make?
Forget it. Back to square one.
Sit.
I'm not your subordinate.
Listen up. There's only one discussion I want to have.
What is it?
File for divorce, division of property, and custody.
The stuff you know best about.
Break it down, and let me know.
What do I need to do to change your mind?
Do I just have to quit work and stay home?
Stop overreacting.
I never even wished stuff like that from you.
What is it, then?
I said I'll do as you say!
It seems you're mistaken about something.
You're no longer a wife, a woman,
or Jae Hui's mom to me.
Let me know when you're ready.
I'll make more money and buy you a watch I couldn't get you for the wedding.
Just spending time together like this is the best.
Ta-da.
You look at your watch a lot.
So, think of me once in a while when you do.
Daejeong Law Firm
Another great month where everyone worked hard.
Great work!
Please keep up the good work next month.
Yes! Thank you for your time!
- Thank you.
- Good work.
All right. Attorney Han, you can take these with you.
So, Attorney Han is taking new case consultations from now on, right?
I was worried because we were getting a lot more of them lately.
Welcome.
We're dividing up what Attorney Cha used to do alone among three people.
You've made the list, right?
Of course! I even placed comments on the list while organizing.
That's right. Here you go, Attorney Han.
Thank you.
Consultation List
Attorney Han, if you have any questions on consultations, you can ask anytime.
There's nothing particularly different for new case consultations.
So be confident. Okay?
Yes, thank you.
Attorney Han, we charge 300,000 won per hour for consultations. You didn't know, right?
- What? Really?
- Yeah.
I charge 300,000 won?
It'd be the value of the major law firm title you have,
not you as the individual, right?
We know very well, even if you don't remind us so harshly.
I also know our partner attorneys charge 500,000 won per hour.
By the way, what does "JS" stand for?
They're special markings I made.
It stands for jin-sang*.
(Blacklist of rude clients/customers in Korean)
Attorney Jeon, there are better phrases like "Subject to special management."
I'll try using that next time.
What's your standard for marking someone as JS?
My standard for JS, huh?
What does jinsang mean?
Okay. First off, here's number one.
Loneliness
People who come because they're lonely when they don't want a divorce.
And here's number two.
People who treat us like thieves, saying our fees are too expensive.
And here's number three. Nitpicks.
People who keep picking at your words,
but don't understand when you actually explain.
And lastly, we've got indecision.
People who are indecisive are very difficult.
Knowing these things will help you a lot later.
And also, it's our company policy not to give more than five consultations.
You must abide by that rule.
I didn't know there was a limitation policy.
But aren't the people free to decide how many consultations to receive?
This is a law firm, not a therapist's office, where you pay an hourly rate.
People get more than five consultations mostly because they can't decide to divorce.
It's to clarify that attorneys provide legal representation,
but they're the ones who must decide to get a divorce.
Why do newbies get the list of people who come in for their fifth consultation?
A neat disposal?
It means you should send them back nicely.
Those people are likely to take back
their decisions many times, even if we start the litigation.
So, it's not appropriate for large law firms to take their cases.
I think it's indeed difficult for everyone
to decide to get a divorce.
But I don't really understand the five-time limit.
Attorney Han, there's no need for you to understand.
You just have to obey. Okay?
- Please wrap things up here.
- Yes.
Have a good day!
Yes.
Attorney Cha, a fifth consultation client, is here.
Attorney Han will be doing the consultation.
Please take her.
Yes, I got it.
Attorney Cha, do you need anything else?
No, I looked because you look pretty today.
I see. Thank you.
I guess you've got a date?
Yes, I've got plans this evening...
with my boyfriend.
You had a boyfriend?
I didn't know.
You didn't know, huh?
I'll introduce him when I get a chance.
Okay. You can go now.
You're no longer a wife, a woman,
or Jae Hui's mom to me.
Aren't we talking to Attorney Cha Eun Gyeong?
Since you've met Attorney Cha Eun Gyeong four times,
it's good to get a second opinion from a different attorney this time.
- Is that so?
- Of course.
Since every attorney has a different opinion, it'll help you more.
How do you do?
Hello, Attorney.
Today is my fifth time.
So it's the last time, right?
Yes, that's true according to our company policy.
I'm paying my money for the consultation, so why won't you let me?
I know, right? Please come inside.
A recording?
Yes, if you don't record it,
no one will believe your father commits verbal abuse every time he drinks.
You said he's gentle as long as he's sober.
How can I record my own husband?
That's a bad thing to do.
I came all the way here,
but I'm still not sure if getting a divorce is the right thing to do.
As long he doesn't drink, for a man his age...
It's true Dad treats me pretty well.
The problem is he doesn't want to quit drinking!
Mom, please stop it now.
You even take medication because you can't sleep from the stress.
Why can't you muster up the courage?
It's your dad!
You need your dad to walk with you at the wedding!
Stop saying it's for my sake!
That's all an excuse.
So, will you divorce him after I get married?
Now, now. Please calm down.
Ma'am, the thing you fear...
Is it your husband or the divorce?
My daughter's getting married soon.
If her wedding is called off because of my divorce, I can't live.
Also, how many years do I have left to live at my age?
Why should I be labeled as a divorcee?
Your daughter already said she's fine.
And, a divorcee, you say?
There's no such thing these days.
People will say I abandoned my family
when they don't even know my situation.
That's so unfair.
So you're saying because of people who don't even know your story,
you're going to endure thirty more years from now, right?
I think he has quite a few assets because our few houses went up in value.
But he won't tell me.
When I ask him about it, he just gets furious and yells at me
not to have funny ideas.
You should end your marriage that's just full of fear.
I can live without that man,
but he can't even cook rice without me.
Aigoo! Gosh, he won't starve to death.
He won't starve to death, for sure.
He'll live on cup noodles, get sick, and kick the bucket.
If you divide the property, you can take half of what he has.
Also, there won't be anyone cursing or looking down on you all day.
So you'll be at peace.
Will it... really be that way?
Mom, Dad's not even human.
So, please live your life now.
How long will you let Dad walk all over you?
I'll help you take a step forward.
All right.
If you sign here, it's the end.
We'll take care of everything from that point on.
Just let me lead you.
I told you to wrap up the fifth consultation client, and you bothered to take her case?
Yes, Mother couldn't seem to decide, so her daughter and I...
It's Ms. Park Jin Suk, not "Mother."
You're not Ms. Park Jin Suk's daughter, are you?
But I'm glad you noticed her daughter will pay for her legal fees.
Knowing where the money will come from is key.
Her daughter was the key to her heart, not the money.
Feeling guilty thinking she's abandoning her family even after all that sacrifice...
Her child is the only one who will free her from that feeling.
I'll make sure to tell the CEO you signed the contract for your first case.
You've earned your keep.
It's true that deciding to divorce is up to you,
but I realized someone has to lead your heart along.
Lead, my foot.
She knew today was the last consultation,
making her sign the contract since she won't have anyone to complain to.
This is why a company's system is important.
Would anyone decide to divorce because of our company system?
Yes, Ms. Park Jin Suk.
I say she'll withdraw her compliant during the trial.
If I take care of her by her side, she'll be able to stay strong.
She can't go back to that hell again.
So, did you tell her to just trust you again?
I told her to let me lead her.
Are you the hero of justice?
Attorney Han, let's be honest here.
You just wanted to teach him a lesson.
He needs to be taught a lesson.
Rather than that, it's more important to know whether she can really live alone.
Divorce isn't for everyone.
Are you saying there's a qualification for divorce?
Of course, there is.
Someone like Ms. Park Jin Suk could never
live alone because she's too fragile, even if she gets a fortune in the division of property.
What about you, Attorney Cha?
You meet the qualifications for divorce.
So suddenly?
Is it also because of the social pressure for you?
Put the trash in the trash can.
You need to live every day of your precious life to its fullest.
Even if you throw trash away, food waste goes into the food waste bin.
Reusable items go in the recycle bin after a good wash.
It's not all that simple.
You've done recycling before, right?
Yes, I live alone.
Is that so? I see.
- Attorneys!
- Hey.
Did you eat?
We did.
What did you have?
Are you going to the court today?
Yu Ri, someone I know from church said they can introduce you to a good man.
I'll set up the date. Okay?
Since you got a job, you need to start seeing a man.
Gosh, seriously.
Did you have a good lunch?
- Yes.
- You're back.
Attorney Han, did you have coffee?
Yes, I did.
- Let's have one more.
- What?
- Outside.
- W-Why?
To get some exercise, too.
So, you took the case? What did Attorney Cha say?
She said, "Why bother?"
How annoying.
Attorney Han, can I ask you one question, purely out of curiosity?
Why don't you ever do what the company tells you?
- Me?
- Yes.
Do you have a rebellious spirit you couldn't resolve when you were young?
No! I don't have anything like that.
I'm just following my attorney's conscience every moment.
Conscience, huh? Respect.
You live a really tiresome life.
Cha Eun Gyeong is the one who lives a tiresome life.
Can't she just give a compliment for once?
Gosh, how's she any different from Park Jin Suk?
Why? Attorney Cha said she won't get a divorce?
She said she won't!
Does it make sense for a divorce attorney to live with a man
who cheated on her out of fear of the social stigma?
Isn't she embarrassed?
Attorney Cha isn't the type to be afraid of the social stigma of getting a divorce.
Well, couldn't it be because of her child?
You also knew that I was talking about Attorney Cha?
Me? I had no idea.
I just cast a leading question, and you took the bait, Han Yu Ri.
Wow, so that happened to Attorney Cha, huh?
If I had a wife like Attorney Cha,
I'd make her my queen and serve her.
Attorney Jeon, you'll keep the secret, right?
Excuse me. I'm also an attorney, okay?
Isn't confidentiality a legal duty?
- You mean it, right?
- Of course!
I guess you sleep fine even with two cups of coffee.
I pass out the moment my head—
Wait, how did you know this is my second cup of coffee?
- Leading question.
- Aigoo.
I just had a quick blind date during lunch.
I got caught. How embarrassing.
Why didn't you meet in the evening?
I have to get off work on time
and have chimaek* with you in the evening.
(Fried chicken and beer.)
Attorney Jeon, do you really like me?
I really like you.
Love your colleague, love your country. Right?
Let's be friends for a long time.
Stop being so clingy.
Why? Let's work together forever. Don't quit, okay?
N-No.
It's okay. You don't need to put them on.
Attorney Han,
I'm the only one who will wipe his butt when he gets old and sick.
So, I'm not sure if I can abandon him like this.
Did you marry him to wipe his butt when he gets old?
Didn't you marry him to be happy?
My daughter is also on my side.
He'll be completely alone.
He brought it upon himself.
Still, I just wonder who'd take care of him when he gets old.
You're not the only one with responsibility and duty.
Do you think the defendant will take care of you when you get sick?
My gosh...
He made you sick, in fact.
Only if I hadn't told him about meeting you.
I think it's kind of right to stop now while I can.
If you're that worried, give my number to your husband
and tell him to talk to me.
And you can just block your husband's number.
Please do it right now.
Can I really do that?
Of course.
Husband
I'm not going home.
You can talk to my attorney now if you want to contact me.
He'll go crazy if he can't even reach me.
It's fine.
I told you to trust me and let me lead you.
This is Park Jin Suk's past consultation notes you mentioned.
Thank you.
010-0825-5183
Who's this?
Yes? Hello?
Hey, are you happy to live like that, lying to people?
- What did you say?
-  What was that thing called?
You wrote a complete fiction in the thing called a complaint!
Excuse me, it's not fiction.
That's the sorrow in Park Jin Suk's heart.
Did you see me cursing at my wife?
Do you have proof?
And all my friends beat up their wives once in a while!
But they aren't even sorry.
- I even say I'm sorry, and I buy her presents—
-  Aigoo.
Do you want an award or something?
I'll sue you for false accusations!
How dare a woman run away from home without preparing her husband's dinner?
No one in this world will prepare dinner for someone like you.
You should've done better!
Tell Park Jin Suk to come home right now. I won't let her be!
Ms. Park Jin Suk will never go home again.
I'll make that happen.
Hey! If you don't quit this right now, I'll kill myself!
You said you'll kill who?
I said I'll kill myself!
Attorney Jeong!
Aren't you going home, Attorney Han?
I still have a lot of work to do.
I heard you took a new case.
Good job. It's not an easy thing to do.
Attorney Cha said I shouldn't have taken the case.
- Thank you.
- Gosh...
Why are people unable to decide to divorce in such ridiculous situations?
Do they lack courage that much?
They're probably afraid, not that they lack courage.
Because even the strongest person fears being alone.
Man, you're quite dependable.
Fighting.
Yes, fighting.
- Hang in there.
- Yes, please take care.
Yes. Thank you.
Oh, yes. About that, yesterday...
Yes, yes. Yes, please wrap it up that way.
Okay.
- Thank you.
- Yes.
-  Seonbae, are you done with the radio?
Yes. Why?
Please buy me a drink.
Jeong Wu Jin asked me to buy him a drink, huh?
You used to buy me a drink here after giving me a good scolding before. Right?
Did you even listen when I scolded you?
You used to say yes, yes,  but did not actually listen in the end.
You remember it completly opposite.
I pretended not to listen,
but I engraved everything you said in my heart.
I was just trying to put my tiny pride forward back then.
You're the one giving me an earful every day now,
saying I've got a bad temper.
I'm just telling you to be gentle to the kids.
If they quit again, you're the one who will be scolded by the CEO.
Am I someone who's afraid of others' opinions?
Yes, you're afraid.
Hey, you know Han Yu Ri accepted her first case, right?
Yeah, I know.
It looked like she was going to quit soon.
If I think about it, she's just like you-know-who when she was new.
Me?
What are you saying? We're totally different.
By the way, why did the Director suddenly quit being our advisor?
Are things not good between you two?
What are you saying? He's just busy.
Seonbae, you don't express your feelings at work or home, right?
What's the use in doing that?
We'd only burden each other.
You should do it somewhere, at the very least.
It's lonely to live like that.
Attorney Jeong, you've never been married.
You could say a married couple's relationship has more at stake
than coworkers' and friends'.
So, there's also a need to exist functionally rather than emotionally,
because it's a long-term relationship.
But you'll have a hard time as a result.
Why would I have a hard time?
Where did that come from suddenly?
Seonbae.
You know I want to help you, right?
What's gotten into you?
Mind your own business.
What's this?
Could it be she lives here?
One Space
She really lives in the same place.
Geez!
- Yu Ri- My goodness!
- O-Oh, my!
- M-Mom!
- Why?
Y-You didn't even call.
I brought some greens side dishes.
Gosh! I rarely eat at home.
You'll eat if there are side dishes.
That's how your Dad always was.
He said to make sure you're fed well
because that's the most important job for me.
Mom, that's gaslighting.
Why is your most important job feeding me?
Try to think critically now.
Think critically, my foot. He was right.
Don't you hate him for backstabbing you while saying those things?
I thought he only worked his butt off to feed his family,
but I'm glad now since he got to stab me in the back before he died.
Something happens to your brain when you get married, right?
What's wrong with my brain?
Just go.
Ma'am, we meet again.
Seriously. We meet again.
Attorney Han.
We met once last time.
I found out she works at your office while we were chatting last time.
What an interesting connection.
I know, right?
- Connection, my foot.
- Your boyfriend isn't here today.
He was so tall and handsome.
Both of you seem so kind that you don't need law.
They live recklessly even with the law.
I think he'll be working late tonight.
I'll make beef brisket soybean paste stew using the recipe you told me last time.
- Yes.
- The snail soybean paste stew was delicious.
Gosh, I'm glad.
Aigoo, go ahead.
Stop looking at your phone and come eat.
- Mom.
- Yeah?
Please don't go around making friends with just anybody.
What do you mean, anybody?
She's your coworker and neighbor.
Did you forget our neighbor was actually Dad's mistress?
Aigoo, the soup cooked so nicely.
No way.
You're not pitying Dad, are you?
You're the pitiful one, not Dad.
You're the victim.
Victim and offender...
Is everything a courtroom in your eyes?
Even outside of court, a victim is a victim, and an offender is an offender.
So delicious.
By the way,
why did you try not to divorce Dad when he cheated on you?
Just because.
Because of me?
I was hesitant that your studies would suffer because of me.
I also tried to understand your dad.
- Wait, Mom. Look at it this way, then.
- Try this.
The causality is wrong here.
You're saying I'd suffer because of your decision to divorce,
not because of Dad, who cheated on you?
How can you think that way?
Mom, it's so frustrating for me! Seriously.
Why can't people just get a divorce for crying out loud?
I'm more frustrated by you.
Try having your own kid later.
Did you study that hard to become an ambassador for divorce?
Are you saying divorce is bad and that it's a social evil with no end?
Sure! You can keep living in Joseon by yourself, then.
I can't live in Joseon.
I'm a divorcee. A modern divorcee.
Well, why do you keep ignoring my texts, Ms. Modern?
Because I've got my reasons.
I'm going to set it up, okay?
I'll change the passcode for the lock, okay?
You got a job now, so you should hurry.
All right! Fine! Fine!
"Fine"? You said that yourself, okay?
Client Park Jin Suk
Have some rolled omelet, too.
M-Mom, hold on.
Yes, Ms. Park Jin Suk. Did something happen?
Hi, Attorney Han.
Is it okay for me to continue doing this?
- What?
-  I mean...
he's begging me to drop the case, saying he'll never drink again.
Do you believe that?
N-No, no, no, it's a bit different this time.
He always cursed when he got drunk and begged when he got sober.
But he's begging while he's drunk this time.
-  What's he saying this time?
- Y-Yes?
He wants me to come make him food.
He said he'll really quit drinking.
So I wonder if I should go make him some soup, at least.
So, you're going to go back to cook food again?
Don't believe a word.
He's never eaten food other than what I made him.
Gosh, I'm sick of this.
Don't decide anything for now.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Why are you doing this to me?
Hurry up and eat.
Park Jin Suk!
Emergency Center
I told you he might kill himself!
Mom!
It's not the attorney's fault.
Did she force you to file the complaint?
I'm so sick of this.
An unlucky wench like me can't even get a divorce.
I knew this would happen.
That's why I said I'm not going to do it!
What kind of nonsense is this?
The attorney was trying to help us.
Shut it!
I don't want to see you.
Leave. Go away. Aigoo, get out of here!
Let go! Aigoo, I'm sick of this.
I'm sick of this.
How was the hospital visit?
What should I do with the case now?
Just leave it for now.
If he dies, Estate Law will take it over and process it.
If he doesn't die, you can withdraw it according to what she says.
Did something like this happen to you, too?
Of course.
As an attorney, you'll see a lot of people who kill themselves after receiving a complaint.
But it's not the attorney's fault.
Do you think so?
Is it the prosecutor's fault if you kill yourself after receiving an indictment?
Is it the tax official's fault if you die after receiving a tax collection notice?
It's not, is it?
Convincing a hesitant client to decide to divorce
with your shallow sense of duty and pathetic sense of justice?
You shouldn't have done that.
Do you also think I instigated her to get a divorce?
I didn't say you instigated her.
Then, what should I have done instead?
Please tell my mom to get a divorce.
I never say such things.
A divorce attorney doesn't decide if you should divorce or not.
Try to separate your personalities.
Attorney Han Yu Ri and the human, Han Yu Ri.
Attorney Han Yu Ri can't say what the human Han Yu Ri thought in her head.
S-Separate personalities...
It should've started with Ms. Park, and not you, wanting to teach her husband a lesson.
Attorney Han?
Yes.
I did my best to console you here. Okay?
If he receives the complaint, what do you think he'll do?
We'd only know after having sent it. Right?
Then, if I leave that house, what will he do?
Well, he'd think you're breaking up for real.
Then, what if I fail to bring all my belongings? Can I get them later?
Well, some people cooperate.
It'd depend on the person.
All right, now. That's enough—
In that case, if my in-laws find out, will they call me?
With the division of property, what happens to the water purifier that's not paid off yet?
Do I have to pay for it?
Well, they might call you or not.
And the one who was paying for the water purifier can continue paying.
- I-If-
- All right, now! What if...
you get a divorce right now, how much will you get?
How much can I get?
Zero.
There's no property to divide here, in my opinion.
I told you my husband inherited three billion won.
Please listen up now. You said he inherited it about a month ago, right?
And you've been married for two years.
If the court says they can't divide the inheritance because your marriage is too short?
- What?
- I won't divorce him, then!
Then, you shouldn't get a divorce.
Then, what do I need to do to get half of that?
For half...
I'll see you after twenty years.
What? T-Twenty years?
- Wait, how could that be?
- Wait.
- If you have more questions, you can call here.
- Okay.
I have another consultation right after, so you'll have to go now.
I'm so sorry.
Did you eat yet? There's a great tteokbokki place nearby.
Well, if you're fine...
Please call me if you've got a question.
- T-Twenty years...
- Yes. Please take care.
What?
Let's go get some ice cream.
Ice cream?
If, if, if!
I hated "if" phrases during English classes, either.
So what did you do?
What do you mean? Eye for an eye and a tooth for a tooth.
"If" for an "if" and asshole for an asshole.
It's easy.
I envy you.
Why isn't it so easy for me?
It's because you empathize so well, Attorney Han.
You keep thinking in the other person's shoes.
It's hard, isn't it?
When he called me and said he'd kill himself...
should I have done something to prevent it?
He's bad for calling and threatening suicide. What could you have done?
He wouldn't...
end up dying, right?
Don't worry too much about it.
People like him are likely just putting on a show.
You were like a seonbae just now.
That means a lot.
Client Park Jin Suk
Say ah... ah...
I'm not eating!
You need to eat to get discharged.
Why do I have to lie in a hospital bed?
What do you mean? Whose fault is this? Aigoo!
Just eat, you troublemaker.
Whose fault do you think? It's your fault! Geez!
What are you doing?
Aigoo, Attorney Han.
It's nothing.
He's just being difficult.
I can now see I was worried for nothing!
- Hurry up and apologize.
- That hurts!
Attorney Han.
I'll...
I say she'll withdraw her complaint before trial.
withdraw my case.
What a pathetic life I have.
As if I can get a divorce.
You shouldn't say that.
I think divorce is for people who are better than me.
I sincerely hope your husband will change from this.
Attorney Cha!
Here.
How did you come?
Ms. Park Jin Suk, you're going through some tough times.
Aigoo, how did you come all the way here?
Ms. Park Jin Suk decided to withdraw.
Don't hope your husband will change from this.
It'll probably happen again after some time passes.
Huh? What's this?
That shitty man.
Come back to us after you've made up your mind.
We'll do our best with your case
regardless of the number of consultations. All right?
Thank you so much, Attorney Cha.
You even gave me a full refund.
How about you get our couple's consultation?
I'll introduce you to alcoholism consultation, too.
You even get a discount if you pay for five consultations at once.
I see. Thank you.
Well, then. Please take care.
Yes.
I said to eat, for goodness' sake.
You told me to send her back, but why did you bother to make a sales pitch?
Despite a serious incident like attempted suicide,
the same situation will repeat itself.
At that point, she's bound to decide and divorce him.
There comes a moment...
where you just accept it.
A moment where you only look ahead.
I said your husband is having an affair.
-  I'm aware.
-  No way. You're not going to get a divorce?
What will I have left by doing that?
My work and home are busier than ever, and I need them.
He made you sick, in fact.
Only if hadn't told him about meeting you.
I also tried to understand your dad.
Attorney Cha!
What exactly is a husband and a wife?
What a pathetic life. As if I can get a divorce.
How can you feed your tormentor?
My daughter is getting married soon.
I was hesitant...
If her wedding is called off because of my divorce, I can't live.
that your studies would suffer because of me.
How can you endure it and live for your child's sake?
Strangers who became family.
Daejeong Law Firm
Huh?
What is it now?
I'm sorry, Attorney Cha.
I don't think I can work in the Divorce Team anymore.
What's this out of nowhere?
Is it because of the attempted suicide?
I don't want to live my life
while distinguishing Attorney Han Yu Ri from the human Han Yu Ri.
Are you going to pick at my words?
As for me... to deal with divorce cases,
I tend to distinguish the victim and the offender too clearly.
Are you angry you couldn't get Park Jin Suk to divorce, or
is your ego bruised because the case turned out the way I predicted it?
It's neither.
I made up my mind because I can't see my future.
Fine, leave. Do whatever you want to the end. Go, then.
Also, Attorney Cha...
What else?
Director Kim eats dinner at Chief Choi's house.
I think they might even be living together.
How do you know that, Attorney Han?
She lives in the same apartment building as me.
Attorney Cha, regarding Chief Choi,
I did it because I wanted to be on your side, not because I wanted to be nosy.
You can leave.
One Space Apartment ...
- No, I'll carry it.
- No, I can do it.
I'll do it for you.
- Did you get hurt?
- It was a prank.
You startled me, seriously.
Aigoo, I'll carry them for you.
- Do it together.
- Please carry this.
- This—
- Jae Hui, were you going to help, too?
You're all grown up, huh?
- I said we should do it together.
- Aigoo, I got it.
- All right!
- Gosh. Let's go.
What is it?
Nothing.
There comes a moment where you just accept it.
A moment where you only look ahead.
Daejeong Law Firm
Attorney Cha?
Your shallow sense of duty and pathetic sense of justice...
I love them.
Sorry?
You said you want to teach him a lesson, right?
I'll let you do that.
Could it be you really went to the apartment?
I didn't accept your resignation letter.
You take my case, Attorney Han.
♫  Facing challenges I persisted  ♫
♫  Learning to navigate heavy day  ♫
♫  But, it's still hard  ♫
♫  Because sometimes tears will flow  ♫
♫  my reflection in the mirror  ♫
♫  will also blur  ♫
♫  Keep holding on  ♫
♫  In the end there will be a bright day  ♫
♫  Remember this moment when your dream came  ♫
Good Partner
Since when did you know?
Adulterers always ask that. I guess they just have to know, huh?
There's a rumor that Sa Ra is the other woman.
So, what will Mom and Dad do? About the divorce.
If I reveal how selfish and what kind of a mom you were, will you be okay?
Attorney Cha! Is the rumor that's going around true?
♫  Feel free to pause—, please take a break  ♫