Good Partner
Daejeong
In session | Plaintiff
Good Partner
This drama is fiction.
Characters, places, agencies, events, organizations, and the setting have no connection to real life.
Child actors were filmed under safe conditions.
- Yes?
-  Hey.
Attorney Cha? I think you ought to come over to our house.
My instincts are telling me so.
It feels like Chun Hwan Seo will cause trouble.
Attorney Cha! What's going on?
Han Yu Ri.
Attorney Cha. Attorney Cha!
Attorney Han, you stay here.
Let me come with you.
How can I send you in alone?
He's the son of a well-known foundation.
He won't be able to act rashly.
But just in case, call the police if you don't hear from me in ten minutes. Okay?
- But still—
- If you tell the police I'm inside,
it might make the news and hurt the firm.
Say it's domestic violence and tell them to come.
It'll be okay. It'll be okay.
Mr. Chun Hwan Seo?
Honey! Honey!
You think I'm being funny? Huh?
I'll show you what happens if you look down on me.
Honey!
Mr. Chun Hwan Seo?
Mr. Chun Hwan Seo, are you here?
Ms. Yu Ji Yeong!
Oh, you're here.
Where's Ms. Yu Ji Yeong?
Ms. Yu Ji Yeong?
Ms. Yu Ji Yeong, can you hear me?
Ms. Yu Ji Yeong, wake up!
Ms. Yu Ji Yeong?
Please...
help me...
I beat her up enough to kill her, but she's still not dead?
F***!
Y-You really killed her.
You bitch! I didn't kill her!
She's the one who passed out and died.
How bothersome.
How much money do you need to get me on probation?
You need a life sentence, not a probation.
You just killed someone.
You killed her. She's dead!
If that's what my lawyer thinks,
she's no longer my lawyer.
You're a witness, and I don't have to let you live.
I'll make sure your daughter ends up the same way.
Attorney Han Yu Ri
The call is not going through. After the beep...
Call the police if you don't hear from me in ten minutes. Okay?
Say it's domestic violence and tell them to come.
(Number for police in Korea)
Shit...
F***...
Shit! Where is she?
Where the hell did she go?
Shit...
Shit.
Yes, Father.
There's a problem that needs to be taken care of.
Get your hands off me. I can walk on my own.
I promise to kill you one day, too. Okay?
Episode 13
If that's what my lawyer thinks,
she's no longer my lawyer.
You're a witness, and I don't have to let you live.
I see you're sitting in my office when I'm not even here.
I'll make sure your daughter ends up the same way.
Police
Attorney—
- Are you okay, Attorney Cha?
-  Are you okay, Attorney Han?
Yes.
Where are you?
I'm at the police station. What about you?
I'm home, of course.
As you said, I called the police after 10 minutes
and Chun Hwan Seo was arrested at the scene.
Good job.
Good job. You did really great. Good job.
Ms. Han Yu Ri?
Attorney Cha, I need to go for questioning.
I'll call you back.
Okay.
I'm Attorney Han Yu Ri
from Daejeong Law Firm.
How did you know to report the situation?
I'm Mr. Chun Hwan Seo's divorce attorney.
When I got there after receiving Mr. Chun Hwan Seo's call,
the door was left open.
And there were signs of physical struggle, so I reported it.
Did you go to Mr. Chun Hwan Seo's house alone?
If you tell the police I'm inside,
it might make the news and hurt the firm.
Say it's domestic violence and tell them to come.
Yes.
Please...
help me.
I'll make sure your daughter ends up the same way.
Case 13: To Make Up Your Mind
STOP School Violence­
I promise to kill you one day, too. Okay?
Attorney Han!
Are you all right?
I'm sorry about this being so late.
I thought I should inform you immediately.
Don't be sorry.
That's unnecessary.
So, Seonbae got home safely, right?
Yes, it seems so.
Well, I haven't heard from her exactly what happened.
But I think...
Mr. Chun Hwan Seo and Attorney Cha had some sort of...
- physical altercation. I think...
You must be really shaken up, too.
Let's go for now. I'll take you home.
Okay.
Thank you.
The company will handle the rest, so don't worry and get some rest.
I'll get in touch with you.
Okay, I understand.
- Go on in.
- Okay.
Yes, Director Chun.
Are you people aware my son has been arrested or not?
We've been informed.
I heard Attorney Han called the police. Did you know that, too?
Yes. Please calm down.
You think I can calm down right now?
What kind of an attorney reports their own client?
You still call yourselves lawyers?
We won't be able to proceed with Mr. Chun Hwan Seo's criminal case.
As if I'll let you?
I won't let this slide, you people!
Seonbae, are you hurt anywhere?
The company will take care of this,
so take the day off and get some rest.
I'll be in touch.
Yes, I understand.
I'm truly sorry, Director Chun.
Did you ask for me?
I heard you declined to take Mr. Chun Hwan Seo's criminal case.
This is a murder case.
It wouldn't be right to take this case, period.
You think the issue at hand is whether we take this criminal case or not?
A person died.
It hasn't even been 24 hours since Ms. Yu Ji Yeong died.
Ms. Yu Ji Yeong isn't the issue right now!
If the Chun Foundation rescinds all their medical and construction cases,
don't you know our company will falter?
I'll come up with a countermeasure.
Get out of here!
Dependable police, safe nation
If that's what my lawyer thinks,
she's no longer my lawyer.
You're a witness, and I don't have to let you live.
I'll make sure your daughter ends up the same way.
Attorney Han Yu Ri from Daejeong Law Firm?
Why was she at the murder scene?
Isn't she an accomplice?
Damn. I guess money can even buy you a lawyer while you murder someone.
Isn't that where Cha Eun Gyeong works?
Damn, what a bunch of scumbags.
His representative? She defended a murderer?
Why was she at the murder scene with him?
I bet they're all in on this together.
I heard the Chun Hospital's Foundation is large-scale.
Money is always the problem. Damn money.
That's what I'm saying.
Executive Director of Chun Medical Foundation, Arrested for Murder
Witness Is A Top Law Firm Attorney
On July 2nd, the eldest son of Director Chun Du Yeong,
Mr. Chun Hwan Seo, the Executive Director of the Chun Medical Foundation,
was arrested for assaulting and killing his wife, Ms. Yu.
Ms. Han of Daejeong Law Firm, who is Mr. Chun's legal representative in
his divorce case, was a witness to Ms. Yu's murder.
- Han Yu Ri?
- Attorney Han Yu Ri?
Executive Director of Chun Medical Foundation, Arrested for Murder
Witness Is  A Top Law Firm Attorney
It's the Chun Medical Foundation.
Everyone, would you believe it if I told you
the Chun Medical Foundation's son committed a murder?
Yes, I was also very shocked when I heard the news.
Our nation's largest hospital, Chun Hospital,
- belongs to this foundation.
- Right.
But there was one more person besides the victim at the scene
where the son of that foundation committed murder.
It was Attorney Han Yu Ri from one of the top three law firms in the nation,
Daejeong Law Firm.
A union between a major foundation and a law firm.
What could be the nature of their relationship?
Doesn't something smell fishy here?
I'm absolutely 100% certain that there's a connection between them.
Two hundred percent.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Hello!
Attorney Han! Are you okay? Are you hurt anywhere?
Y-Yeah. I'm really okay.
Why would you go there?
I told you to stop putting yourself in danger. Geez!
Attorney Han, why did you come in? I told you to take a break.
I need to catch up on some files.
And I just wanted to work.
Attorney Han—
Seonbae.
I told you to rest at home—
Why won't you two listen to me?
Are you okay, Attorney Cha?
You should be resting. Why did you come?
I mean, why are you named as the witness?
You only got there after the situation was over.
Why are you the witness?
Don't worry about me.
It's all going to be revealed eventually
and it's just an internet rumor.
How can we not worry? They're dissecting you inside out!
He's right. Reporters might swarm here,
so don't come to work until the situation blows over.
It's okay! I'm fine, Attorney Jeong.
Yeah, go home and get some rest, Attorney Han.
I'll take care of everything.
- I have to do it.
- Seonbae, don't get involved, either.
This isn't about individuals, Cha Eun Gyeong and Han Yu Ri.
The company will handle things,
so you two should stay out of this.
1st Hearing
Let us begin the hearing.
Prosecutor, please state the charges.
The defendant was the victim's spouse.
They fought frequently after the victim filed for divorce on June 4, 2024.
When the victim came home, the fighting began.
The furious defendant laid the victim on the floor,
sat on top of her, and punched the victim's face and head multiple times.
This assault caused subdural hemorrhaging on the victim's left side of the brain,
which lead to her death.
Do you acknofwledge the charges?
I-I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, Your Honor!
Yes, Your Honor. He accepts the charges regarding the assault.
However, we submitted the medical records
of receiving psychiatric therapy to prove the defendant's feeble-mindedness.
Please consider that this is the defendant's first offense. We ask for probation.
You murderer!
I had no idea my daughter Ji Yeong was telling the truth!
I thought my daughter would become a divorcee if I sided with her,
so I turned a blind eye and covered my ears!
Had I known she would be beaten to death after she left...
What's the big deal about being a divorcee?
I handed my daughter over to that murderer with my own hands!
My Ji Yeong died because of me.
I killed my daughter.
Ma'am, are you okay?
Please...
help me...
She would have lived if I had been a bit sooner.
Don't beat yourself up.
Did you see him?
Chun Hwan Seo's expression was that of relief, not anxiety.
I did.
I think he intended to kill Yu Ji Yeong from the start.
There's something wrong with this situation.
He should've been indicted for murder.
It was lacking evidence to indict him for pre-meditated murder.
What? Why would you report it when you weren't even a witness?
He was indicted for assault because it was determined
he had no intention to murder.
So, if I testify about my observations of Chun Hwan Seo's violent tendencies—
Wait, wait, Attorney Han. Think about this rationally.
You think that's going to work?
This isn't a drama. This is reality.
What if Chun Hwan Seo seeks revenge once he's released?
That will put you in danger, too.
- I...
- Please turn off the water!
If I can't divorce him this time,
I think it'll only end if I die, Official.
want to reveal the truth behind Ms. Yu Ji Yeong's death.
This is too unfair.
Attorney Han.
I wish Han Yu Ri would stay out of danger.
Okay?
My daughter ❤
The call is not going through. After the beep...
She should be at home. Why isn't she picking up...
I'll make sure your daughter ends up the same way.
The call is not going through.
My daughter ❤
Mom
The call is not going through. After the beep...
Hello?
Kim Jae Hui!
Where are you?
I told you I'm going to Coin Karaoke with my friends.
But why didn't you pick up your phone? I was... I was worried.
I couldn't hear it because of the loud music.
What's wrong?
Jae Hui, I'll...
I'll head over.
Send me the address right away. Okay?
Jae Hui did anyone follow you or anything today?
If a stranger tries to lure you, you must not follow them, okay?
Are you okay, Mom?
You're acting really strange right now, Mom.
Yeah. Everything's fine.
Fine, my foot.
Well, I...
I'm...
You were always right.
You know that, right?
Everything will be okay.
I'm standing in front of Deajeong Law Firm.
Recently, Chun Hwan Seo, the Executive Director of the Chun Medical Foundation,
murdered his wife and Attorney Han Yu Ri
from Daejeong Law Firm was revealed to be a witness at the scene.
The question is whether the two organizations are somehow connected.
Hello, everyone.
Continuing from our last episode, we will also talk about Daejeong Law Firm.
It's extremely shocking and suspicious that the establishment of the MOU
and taking on the divorce case for
Executive Director Chun Hwan Seo's occurred at the same time.
I have my suspicions that these events might've been planned from the start.
If I dare to make a guess,
I think the two organizations schemed a big picture
to mutually benefit each other.
Hey, did you see these comments?
Han Yu Ri is scary...
Geez, aren't they too harsh?
Han Yu Ri is a trashy lawyer.
- I know.
- It just became a fact.
What should we do?
Daejeong Law Firm is scummy.
Han Yu Ri and Cha Eun Gyeong are both trash.
Jeong Wu Jin is also trash.
Daejeong Law Firm, Chun Medical Foundation, MOU Crisis? Public Opinion Plummets.
Trashy law firm... trashy lawyers...
If that's what my lawyer thinks...
You're a witness, and I don't have to let you live.
I'll make sure your daughter ends up the same way.
Please...
help me...
Don't worry about me.
I'm fine, Attorney Jeong.
My Ji Yeong died because of me.
Please talk Han Yu Ri out of it.
Why? What is she saying?
She keeps saying she'll report Mr. Chun Hwan Seo's case.
But honestly, I'm worried.
She's already being badmouthed online when she's innocent.
If she steps forward a bit more...
Yu Ri will really be in danger.
You were always right.
Everything will be okay.
Attorney Jeong, you are officially registered as the CEO of our firm as of today.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
I'm sorry about all the commotion as soon as you became CEO.
CEO: Oh Dae Gyu succeeded by CEO: Jung Woo Jin
Yes?
"Trashy law firm, trashy lawyers."
Have you read the articles and comments?
It will all pass.
I'll prepare a rebuttal article.
Why on earth was a Daejeong lawyer at the scene of the murder? Why?
She recognized Mr. Chun Hwan Seo's violent tendencies
and went to separate Ms. Yu Ji Yeong from Mr. Chun Hwan Seo.
But the murder had already occurred.
Isn't that what Ms. Yu Ji Yeong's lawyer should've done?
We're the lawyers for Mr. Chun Hwan Seo!
Ms. Yu Ji Yeong didn't have a lawyer.
If we had respectfully redirected Director Chun's son's case
somewhere else from the start,
we wouldn't be having this discussion.
I agree.
A divorce case is outside the parameters of an MOU.
Accepting Chun Hwan Seo's case was the start of our troubles.
Because you had to accept that divorce case,
our construction and civil cases are suffering damages.
Are you...
now saying this is all my fault?
I signed...
the contract without confirming the other party.
It's my fault.
However, the important thing right now isn't pointing fingers. It's to find a solution.
And what's your solution?
From: CEO Attorney Jeong Wu Jin of Daejeong Law Firm
It's to terminate the MOU with the Chun Medical Foundation.
Absolutely not!
What a preposterous solution you brought to the table!
As of today, I'm officially registered as the CEO.
From now on, all the decision-making power lies with me.
Daejeong Law Firm
Statement ofVerified Facts
From: CEO Attorney Jeong Wu Jin of Daejeong Law Firm
These scumbags dare stab me in the back?
Railway Restaurant
The termination of the MOU was a huge loss.
Will you be okay?
A wrong process leads to a wrong result.
If that results in our loss, I'll just have to bear it.
It was huge income and a relationship that was necessary for the company's profit.
I might have turned a blind eye and covered my ears as well.
You did it to protect the Divorce Team and me.
I'm the one who turned a blind eye and covered my ears.
I'm regretting a lot.
I feel like this is all my fault.
2nd Hearing
I see the prosecution has changed the charges.
Please make your statement.
Yes, Your Honor.
We will change the defendant's charge from physical assault to murder.
Your Honor, this is absurd.
I had no idea Ji Yeong would die like that.
How could you accuse me of deliberately murdering her?
Defendant, please sit down.
Mr. Chun Hwan Seo, please sit for now.
I'd like to call on Attorney Cha Eun Gyeong of Daejeong Law Firm to testify.
The defendant's divorce attorney and the first witness at the murder scene.
I approve.
I'm Attorney Cha Eun Gyeong of Daejong Law Firm.
What brings you here?
Prosecutor.
Chun Hwan Seo must be indicted for murder, not physical assault.
Excuse me?
I'm...
a witness to the murder.
That woman...
How could that woman be a witness?
That woman appeared after Yu Ji Yeong died!
She doesn't know anything!
You... You're my lawyer!
Mr. Chun Hwan Seo, please calm down.
What's going on?
Why were you chosen as the witness, Attorney Cha?
I'm the one who made the report.
I'm the one who witnessed the murder.
What if the career you built at the company up until now all falls apart?
If the time has come for it to fall apart, then so be it.
I should've done this sooner.
The divorce lawyer of the
Chun Medical Foundation's son, Chun Hwan Seo, who beat his wife to death,
was later revealed to have been star Attorney Cha Eun Gyeong.
While Attorney Cha Eun Gyeong was selected as the witness for this trial,
the public is waiting to hear her testimony.
Damn these people and their comments.
"I knew it."
"Then Cha Eun Gyeong defended a murderer"?
"Whoa, what a scary woman."
There's another comment.
"Cha Eun Gyeong. She gave me the chills."
"What a complete psychopath."
"She's a trashy lawyer who goes around exposing her client's story"?
These damn airheads.
I ought to find them and report them so they come to their senses.
- Scroll down.
- Here?
- This one?
- This one.
Attorney Han, did you read the comments?
"National back-stabber."
People can be really cruel.
They're blind to Attorney Cha's dedication to Ms. Yu Ji Yeong
and are only obsessing over her legal representation in the divorce of a murderer.
Exactly, gosh.
The only person Attorney Cha betrayed was Mr. Chun Hwan Seo.
They have no idea.
Attorney Cha probably won't be okay at work, either, right?
Of course not. You think CEO Oh will let her be?
She's exposing the secrets of her client to the entire world.
Our existing clients will find it difficult to trust us.
And they probably won't seek our services in the future.
3rd Hearing
We will now proceed to question the witness.
Defendant
Witness, you can refuse to testify
Witness
the information you found out as an attorney or while under contract.
Will you give up this right to decline to testify and make a statement?
Yes, there's a great public need, as mentioned in the proviso clause
of criminal procedure law's article 149.
I'll give up my right not to testify and make a statement.
What is the relationship between the witness and the defendant?
I am the defendant's legal representative in a divorce
as well as the first person to witness the scene.
Please describe the situation when you first arrived at the scene.
When I arrived at the scene after receiving the defendant's call,
Ms. Yu Ji Yeong?
- the victim, Ms. Yu Ji Yeong...
- Please...
help me...
was painfully breathing her last breaths.
The moment I tried to call 119 (Korean 911 emergency),
the defendant grabbed my phone and flung it away.
At that moment,
I witnessed Ms. Yu Ji Yeong pass away.
So, there was enough time to attempt an intervention,
but the defendant stopped you.
Yes, she was definitely alive.
And as the defendant looked down at the victim,
I beat her up enough to kill her, but she's still not dead?
he said, "She's still not dead?"
No, that's a lie.
The defendant called me from the scene,
thinking the victim was dead.
There were instances,
I'm going to kill that bitch.
where the defendant told me he'd kill the victim.
So, I carried a voice pen to the scene.
Recording Log
I beat her up enough to kill her, but she's still not dead?
And the victim ultimately did not survive the night.
Yes.
During the divorce hearing,
If I can't divorce him this time,
I think it'll only end if I die, Official.
she said it would "only end if she dies."
That's how it turned out.
Hey! You're saying my son is a murderer?
How dare you lie in a court of law?
How could you stab my son in the back when you're his lawyer?
- That's enough.
- I'm far from done!
What? MOU termination?
Are you cutting ties so you can escape by yourself?
I won't let you or your father get away with this. Got that?
Just as Mr. Chun Hwan Seo's crime has nothing to do with you,
my actions have nothing to do with my father.
I'm the CEO of Daejeong now.
Please just refer to me.
Do you know how much I lost because of you people?
How each of us recovers our losses should be up to ourselves.
Thank you for everything.
Seonbae, let's go.
Let’s fix the outmoded law
Ease the proof of the reason for divorce
Everyone, the third hearing for Yu Ji Yeong's murder case is currently being held.
All of us might be the ones
Reason for divorce proved to be physical assault...
who caused Ms. Yoo Ji Yeong's death.
The families and society that consider divorce to be taboo,
Special procedures for domestic violence needed...
and the social pressure and difficulties of proving one's claims during a divorce trial.
Could those things have prevented Ms. Yu Ji Yeong from escaping domestic abuse?
We mustn't allow more instances like Yu Ji Yeong.
Attorney Han Yu Ri is protesting in front of the courthouse.
All of us might be the ones...
I warned her not to do something dangerous like this.
She's becoming popular on SNS right now as Attorney Picket.
And the difficulties of proving one's claims...
What do we do, Attorney Jeon?
...prevented Ms. Yu Ji Yeong from escaping domestic abuse?
Please give this a read.
What should I do...
Attorney Han Yu Ri!
Attorney Jeon— Wait, all of you—
Wait, you can't— How could you all be out here during work hours?
I'm really fine. I can easily do this alone.
- We'll do it with you.
- Yes.
♫  It's okay even if you're stopped, it's not the end  ♫
You told me to lay low, so why'd you bother?
Someone might pick a fight with you and
how could I leave you alone?
Thank you, Attorney Jeon.
Thank you.
Please take a look!
Please take a look here!
- One day, we might be in her place.
- Please take a look!
I'm saying this only now,
but how could two women decide to go to Chun Hwan Seo's house alone?
If you thought it could be dangerous, you should've notified the firm first.
I don't know.
At that moment, I was only able to think that I had to go.
How you try to solve things on your own all the time...
Please fix that.
Hey.
I thought I was loyal to my firm all those years, right?
But I was running for myself,
for my own sake, not the firm.
But why did I think I was sacrificing myself for my work and my home?
Seonbae, you know you're unlike yourself these days, right?
What am I usually like?
It came out just now. That's exactly it.
Th-That's who Cha Eun Gyeong is.
Though it's late, I approve of CEO Attorney Jeong Wu Jin.
To be honest, I approved you the moment I heard it.
Go and write the second season of Daejeong.
Not Oh Dae Gyu's Daejeong.
I'm talking about the new Daejeong led by Jeong Wu Jin.
Please take a look here!
Attorney Picket, Attorney Han Yu Ri.
She's seriously nuts.
- Gosh, she's unstoppable.
- Why is she doing this? So embarrassing.
I told you, right?
She's a lot like somebody I know.
Team 3 can wrap it up and send it over.
- Okay.
- That concludes this meeting.
- Thanks for your time!
-  Thanks for your time.
Thanks for your time.
Attorney Jeong.
Please take a look at the news.
Though late, it was recently revealed that while representing Chun Hwan Seo,
the Daejeong Law Firm resigned the moment they found out
about his violent nature.
In addition, Attorney Cha Eun Gyeong went to the prosecution in person
and made a report supporting  the late Ms. Yu Ji Yeong.
Experts' analysis say Attorney Cha Eun Gyeong's report had an influence on
turning the charge from assault to murder.
In fact, cases where the indictment is changed
during a trial are rare, so interest is increasing.
People are supporting Attorney Cha Eun Gyeong for her courageous actions.
There is a lot of controversy surrounding Attorney Cha Eun Gyeong.
Please say a word regarding this.
Attorney Cha Eun Gyeong put her career on the line
to provide the prosecution with the necessary information to change the indictment.
If it weren't for Attorney Cha's report,
the defendant would've received a lighter sentence
for physical assault instead of murder.
Attorney Cha is the most courageous person I know.
Also, attention is focused on whether the murder charge will be applied to Chun
and how the Supreme Court will come down with the final decision.
- Goodness gracious!
- I'm Reporter Park Yu Na reporting.
It's such a relief. What a relief.
It must've felt so unfair. Sorry for doubting you...
Get on your knees and apologize...
Attorney Cha, did you read the article?
I'm so glad.
Public opinion changed from criticism to positive.
It should've been like this from the start.
Thanks, Han Yu Ri.
I told you not to worry, but you just can't stay put.
I want to become a reliable partner you can depend on.
You're a good partner, Han Yu Ri.
Thank you.
By the way, you're such TV material.
You want to go on?
I'll introduce you.
No! I can't.
What do you mean? You were great!
- No?
- No.
There's only one day left until the judgment for Chun Hwan Seo's case.
Everyone did a good job in each of their positions.
Actually, Attorney Cha requested this gathering.
Is there something special you'd like to say?
From now on, the two of you will take cases on your own.
I wanted to tell you this.
- Sorry?
- Your prep files will still need reviewing,
but no more going to trials and forming litigation strategies together.
It's time to stand on your own, isn't it?
Then, we'll become true lawyers, right?
I'll do my best.
Sure.
Judgment
I sentence the defendant to
15 years in prison.
Hey, Judge.
Who f***ing bribed you, huh? Let go of me, you f***ers!
You accused an innocent person of being a murderer. You call yourselves human?
Let go! How much do you want?
I'll give you the money! Let's redo this.
How much were you paid?
All right! Look! I...
Your Honor! Your Honor...
Let me go! I'll give you money!
I'll get down on my knees! Please!
Let go of me! Let go!
- It's Cha Eun Gyeong!
- They're here!
Attorney Cha Eun Gyeong, you were Mr. Chun Hwan Seo's divorce attorney.
Why did you decline your right and give a disadvantageous statement regarding Chun?
I truly wanted to relieve the deceased from the injustice.
I believed there was a great public need.
I know very well how many victims still suffer from domestic violence.
Please say a word to those currently suffering from domestic violence.
Even as I speak,
someone out there is losing their will to live due to domestic violence.
Family should be a source of encouragement.
They shouldn't be a source of forceful oppression.
If your family tries to forcefully oppress you,
they're not your family.
Some criticize you for providing an unfavorable statement against your client.
What do you have to say about this?
It doesn't bother me at all.
I'm only deeply regretful I couldn't recognize the situation sooner
to prevent the defendant's actions to save the late Ms. Yu Ji Yeong.
The sentence seems harsher than a usual ruling. Is this true?
Yes. The law only punishes after the crime occurs.
It cannot function to prevent the crime from happening.
However, the court's decision like this one
will function to increase punishment and prevent crimes in our society.
I would like to express my respect and gratitude to the judicial branch.
A final word regarding this case, please.
All of our attorneys and employees at Daejeong Law Firm
did our best to relieve the injustice done to the late Ms. Yu Ji Yeong.
I express my condolences to the victim who died tragically.
How is she so cool?
Good work.
- Good job.
- Thank goodness.
- Good job, everyone.
- Great work.
- You did really well.
Attorney Han?
Yes?
You worked really hard.
I really thank you.
You really shouldered the hard work, Attorney Cha.
You were really courageous.
I'm thinking about doing one more courageous thing.
What is it? Just give me the word. I'll help—
I'm going to leave.
What do you mean leave?
To where?
I will go independent from this firm.
So, you should become independent from me.
♫  Which one is the right way?  ♫
♫  But there's nothing more I can do  ♫
♫  I ... Just live on like that  ♫
♫  I know very well each and every day can be a new day for me  ♫
♫  I'm doing a good job  ♫
♫  Today, I told myself again, even clumsy steps aren't too late  ♫
♫  That was a small consolation  ♫
♫  Keep holding on, in the end, there will be a bright day  ♫
♫  Remember this moment when your dream came  ♫
Good Partner
What is Attorney Cha Eun Gyeong's "Spring Back" like?
A place where I can swiftly recover spring for my clients.
If you put some money in the inmate account,
I'll sign your contract next time!
I refuse.
I couldn't close a contract and just wasted my time.
What if I can't even pay the rent at this rate?
Would you like to pay a visit here?
She's the most competent lawyer I know.
Just leave it to me.
♫  Because sometimes tears will flow  ♫