-Why are all the lights off?
-Jeong-hun?
Sang-hun?
Jeong-hun!
-Jeong-hun!
-What is going on?
Jeong-hun!
Jeong-hun, what's wrong?
Jeong-hun.
Jeong-hun!
-Sang-hun!
-Jeong-hun! Kim Jeong-hun!
Snap out of it!
Sang-hun.
Sang-hun?
Sang-hun!
Honey.
Something's wrong with Sang-hun.
-Sang-hun.
-Sang-hun!
Sang-hun!
Sang-hun.
Wake up, Sang-hun!
Die! Stop!
Die!
Stop!
CASE 3
THIS IS PENGSOO
ATTORNEY WOO YOUNG-WOO
Hello.
Look at you. You got your own nameplate.
"Attorney Woo Young-woo."
-You happy?
-Yes.
-Do you want me to take a picture?
Okay.
What are you doing? Why do you look mad?
Smile a little.
Let's just go back to looking mad.
Okay.
ATTORNEY JUNG MYEONG-SEOK
Hello.
Attorney Woo, please come
to my office right away.
Okay.
-Shall we take pictures some other time?
-Yes, some other time.
Yes, come in.
Attorney Woo. I put the case files
over there, so take a look.
Have you heard
of Sangjeong Pharmaceutical?
It's quite a famous
pharmaceutical company.
Yes.
EVIDENCE RECORD
The Chairman is a long-time
client of Hanbada.
But he's going through
a rough patch at the moment.
He has two sons,
but it seems as though the younger son
beat the older son to death.
And the Chairman
and his wife witnessed it themselves.
The cause of death is thoracic trauma.
He had 22 rib fractures
that caused internal bleeding
in his chest, leading to his death.
They say there's some sort
of faint mark on his neck,
but it doesn't seem
like it would've been life-threatening.
All this resulted
from the younger son's assault?
Yes. At least, that's what
the prosecutor seems to believe.
The fractures to the front of his ribs
may be attributed to CPR,
but for the remaining 11 fractures,
it's hard to explain with anything
other than assault.
The blood-alcohol level of the victim
at the time of his death
was at intoxication levels.
I don't think
he would've ended up like this
if he had been sober.
It's a pity what happened.
Is Kim Jeong-hun, the one who's been
charged with bodily injury
resulting in death, the younger son?
Yes.
I'll be handling this case,
but I'd like for you to join me.
The defendant has autism.
There should be a psychiatric evaluation
for Kim Jeong-hun on the next page.
SEOIN UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
AUTISM SPECTRUM DISORDER
ALSO REFERRED TO AS ASD
THIS DISORDER IS A COMPLEX
DEVELOPMENTAL DISORDER
Are you assigning me this case
because I'm autistic?
Wouldn't you know
the defendant better than I do?
And I'm sure the Chairman
would feel more reassured
if a lawyer with autism was on the case.
The official diagnosis for autism
is Autism Spectrum Disorder.
As you can tell from the word spectrum,
there's a wide variety of autistic people.
Like…
whales.
Even if they're all whales,
blue whales and right whales
have a totally different ecosystem
and social structure from humpback whales.
What's more is that--
Okay, enough about whales.
What is it that you're trying to say?
Right.
According to this evaluation,
Kim Jeong-hun is on
the severe end of the spectrum,
with a mental age of somewhere
between age six and ten.
I have never met someone like him.
Neither have I.
You're still better than me,
who didn't even know
the official term for autism.
Let's meet with them first.
Don't be so scared.
Hello.
I'm Jung Myeong-seok,
the attorney handling your case.
And this is…
I'm Attorney Woo Young-woo.
Whether it's read straight or flipped,
it's still Woo Young-woo.
Kayak, deed, rotator,
noon, racecar, Woo Young-woo.
Right.
Attorney Woo Young-woo
has autism spectrum disorder.
Like your younger son.
According to your younger son's statement,
the words "Die. Die. Stop." were repeated.
No matter how many times we ask
about what happened that night,
he only keeps saying,
"Die. Die. Stop."
How was the relationship
between your two sons?
It was good.
Jeong-hun was especially fond of Sang-hun.
Before Sang-hun got busy with med school,
he always hung out
and took care of Jeong-hun.
Sang-hun
was our son, but the kid was perfect.
He went to SNU med school
with a perfect score on the CSAT,
but he was also humble and warm
and was so good to his brother.
Does Mr. Jeong-hun normally
often say the words "die"?
No.
Jeong-hun saying something
like that is quite unusual.
He gets misunderstood by people
because of how big he is,
but he's a nice kid.
Sometimes,
he doesn't listen to me
and can be a little stubborn.
But he never threatens or attacks anyone.
So you have no idea in particular
as to why your younger son
beat up your older son?
No.
Looks like I don't know much
about what goes on in my sons' minds.
Would it be okay
if we meet with your younger son?
Meeting with him isn't an issue.
But I'm not sure if he'll talk.
He goes silent when he meets strangers.
They should still meet him at least once.
Jeong-hun is the defendant.
And we never know.
He might open up to Attorney Woo.
If only this elevator would hurry up,
we'd have ten more minutes
for our lunch break.
You're right.
-Do you know today's lunch menu?
-It's stir-fried pork.
Really?
It's here.
Have a nice lunch.
Excuse me, can you wait just a second?
-What is it?
-I'm sorry.
Hey.
I'm so hungry.
I'm starving.
Gosh, I'm hungry.
Closing the doors now.
If I knew you brought lunch from home,
I'd have come down first.
Next time, come down a bit later.
By "a bit later," how much later
do you exactly mean?
About ten minutes?
Okay.
While we work on the 17th floor
and eat lunch on the first basement level,
whales feed in the coastal waters of Ulsan
and sleep on the west coast of Japan.
For them, the coastal waters
of Ulsan are their kitchen
and the west coast
of Japan is their bedroom.
Migratory whales that move to the polar
regions every summer feed intermittently.
They only eat during the 3 to 4 months
that they stay in the polar regions.
-Jeez, Young-woo's doing that again.
-What?
Should I go stop her?
Since people only eat within eight hours
each day when intermittent fasting.
Just leave her be.
He doesn't seem to mind.
What?
The look on Jun-ho's face.
It doesn't seem like he minds.
Okay.
You promised. Be good, okay?
-Hello.
-You're here.
Kim Jeong-hun, come in.
Right.
Pengsoo!
Jeong-hun, I see you like Pengsoo.
Please take a seat.
Jeong-hun, sit down.
Sit down.
Take your headphones and sunglasses off.
I won't take my headphones
and sunglasses off.
Listen to me.
You promised, right?
Listen to me. I didn't promise, right?
It's fine. The headphones
and sunglasses look cool.
If it's okay with you two,
I think we should proceed like this.
Hi, Jeong-hun.
My name is Jung Myeong-seok,
and this here is…
Woo Young-woo.
Right, Young-woo and I
have a lot to ask you, Jeong-hun.
So, today--
Do you know what he's saying?
No, I do not.
Jeong-hun.
What's that?
Kim Jeong-hun, stop it!
Attorney Woo,
can you try asking him a question?
Mr. Kim Jeong-hun, do you recall the day
Mr. Kim Sang-hun died?
Why did you beat up Kim Sang-hun?
Easy.
Why?
-Why?
-Kim Jeong-hun. Stop it!
-Kim Jeong-hun.
-Why?
-Jeong-hun.
Mr. Jeong-hun, stop.
-Why?
-Kim Jeong-hun.
-Jeong-hun.
My goodness, Madame Attorney is home.
I have an inquiry for you, Dad.
Yes, please do inquire.
I have to communicate with a 21-year-old
autistic man, but it's difficult.
What should I do?
What is this about?
I can't tell you the details
because of attorney-client privilege.
I'm inquiring because I thought you'd know
since you live with an autistic person.
Then would you be so kind
as to trim spinach with me while I answer?
No, I don't want to.
Living with an autistic person
is indeed quite…
"Quite"?
Lonely.
For me,
it's you and me against the world.
But you, my daughter,
don't have any interest in me.
You still don't, but it was worse
when you were younger.
Why are you bringing up blind dates
and getting married when I have Young-woo?
What are you talking about, Mom?
You can't raise her.
You said you barely make it to the
bathroom because your back hurts.
Stop!
Mom!
You know what?
I bite the bullet every single day.
Why are you making it worse,
of all people?
Darn it!
Young-woo, what are you up to?
Young-woo. Daddy's in so much pain.
Blow on it for me.
Look, Daddy's crying.
Daddy's crying.
Is it that fun, Young-woo?
What are you trying to be
when you grow up?
Someone who puts LEGO pieces on the floor?
How should I put it?
It's like the feeling
of a father and daughter
living in this world,
hand in hand, is missing.
It felt like as long as you were fed,
you would've been okay with anyone
even if it wasn't your dad.
Do you still feel that way?
It's much better now!
I can have conversations with you.
You liked putting
LEGO pieces on the floor,
but you also really liked the law.
It was a relief.
Because that was something
we could do together.
Young-woo!
Here, have this.
If you keep crying,
I'll call the police officer.
And the police will scold you.
Young-woo.
OBUK CORNER STORE
Jeez, this little girl
has such a loud voice.
My eardrums were about to burst.
Young-woo, get up.
Ms. Woo Young-woo.
This action falls
under public disturbance.
If you don't stop crying,
I'll call the police for minor offense
and obstruction of business
of Obuk Corner Store.
Young-woo, get up.
Goodness.
Let's go home and read about
the Punishment of Minor Offenses Act.
The way you like law,
that person must like something, right?
You should dig into that.
"Dig into what he likes."
Isn't that too obvious
to call it your method?
Hey.
If you want good grades, study.
If you want to lose weight, exercise.
If you want to communicate,
make an effort.
Methods are always obvious.
What's hard is accomplishing them.
Right.
Now that I think about it,
living with you,
I really…
But…
it takes a really long time.
Conversations don't just happen right away
simply by making an effort.
Do we really have to do this?
I agree. Is this really effective?
Yes.
Hello.
Come in.
-Peng-ha!
Peng-ha!
Please, take a seat.
Here.
Sit down.
Let's soar through the sea
And go to the Billboard
It feels different
I feel good
With my little wings
Swim over the sky
I'm the very best
I'll be number one
South Pole Peng, Amazing Soo
-It can't get any better than this
-Than this!
I'm a penguin, an Emperor penguin,
The captain of all penguins
Marching toward the Billboard
Let's soar through the sea,
And go to the Billboard
It feels different
I feel good
With my little wings
Swim over the sky
I'm the very best
I'll be number one
Fantastic Pengsoo multiples
The more you divide
Thank you for sharing your love
Penguin's day
Happy birthday
There's no last place
We can all take up the challenge
Smiling dazzling eyes
Put your hands up, yes!
March, march, Captain Penguin
Confident legend of the South Pole
That's enough.
Yodel-oh-ee-dee, Yodel-oh-ee-dee
-Yodel-oh-ee-dee, Yodel-oh-ee-dee
Again! Sing again!
-Should we?
-Again!
No.
We can sing again
only if Mr. Kim Jeong-hun answers.
Again! Sing again!
Answer me first.
Why did you beat up your brother?
Why?
-Attorney Woo.
-Why?
-Mr. Kim Jeong-hun, answer me.
-Why did you beat up your brother?
-Why?
Die! Stop!
Stop! Die!
-Stop!
-Jeong-hun.
-Mr. Jeong-hun.
-Die! Stop!
Die!
Mr. Kim Jeong-hun.
Did your brother try to die?
What?
That "die" could be
an action, not what was said.
Not what his brother said but what he did.
His brother's actions?
When he died, Mr. Kim Sang-hun's blood
alcohol level was 0.321 percent.
He was unconscious.
And in his autopsy report,
there's a record of a mark on his neck.
It is written that it is unclear whether
or not he was strangled with a rope
because the mark is too faint.
Has your older son ever
attempted suicide when he was alive?
No.
Why would Sang-hun do such a thing?
Mr. Kim Jeong-hun.
Did your brother try to commit suicide?
Yes.
No.
Sang-hun isn't like that.
But you also just heard him say yes.
Jeong-hun.
Did your brother try to die?
Yes.
Jeong-hun, did your brother try to live?
Your brother never tried to die?
Yes.
Communicating with Jeong-hun at his level
is still not an easy task, even for me.
I appreciate your effort,
but this will be the last time
you meet with Jeong-hun.
-Let's go.
-Yes.
You're trying to find evidence that
Kim Sang-hun attempted suicide, right?
Yes. But I'm not sure if there would be
any useful evidence left
since the police would've
looked through everything already.
But in this situation,
the case itself is very simple and clear.
So the police wouldn't have felt
the need to work hard to obtain evidence.
I hope there's something left
among his things.
Jun-ho!
What?
Hi.
What are you doing here?
You live in this apartment?
No, I'm here for work.
What work?
-Do you still do volunteer work?
-Volunteer work?
Aren't you volunteering
for Nanuri right now?
What are you talking about?
No, this isn't like that.
-You should get going. I'm late.
-All right. It was nice seeing you.
Hang in there.
Is Nanuri a volunteer organization
for disabled people?
I'm sorry, Attorney Woo.
She's a friend from college,
and that was rude of her.
Well.
It's okay. I have autism,
so I guess it could be seen that way.
I apologize.
I kept this door closed
because seeing the room was upsetting.
His things should all still be there.
But I'm not sure
if you'll find anything helpful.
Okay.
Could we take a look by ourselves?
We'll let you know if we find anything.
If I were to try
hanging myself in this room…
This is about where Kim Sang-hun
was found lying.
Then this should be it.
You said Mr. Kim Jeong-hun is tall, right?
Yes, he seemed almost two meters.
So his eye level
would be around this high?
Yes.
Then…
He opened the door
and saw his brother hanging by the neck.
He must've tried to
stop him at first, right?
He's tall, so he could've
reached up and untied the knot.
Then Sang-hun would've fallen
to the floor with a thud.
Wait.
What's that?
Do you see that?
What?
I think I found it.
There are traces on it
as if it has been roughly torn off.
Could it be the rope
that Mr. Sang-hun used to hang himself?
And could Mr. Jeong-hun have torn it off?
We'll have to check and compare it
with the mark on Mr. Sang-hun's neck.
I think this is Mr. Sang-hun's diary.
It's from last year.
I sent the rope to National Forensic
Service to have it compared
to the mark on your son's neck.
I'll let you know
as soon as the results come in.
And also,
we went through your older son's diary.
And we've prepared some of the pages
because we thought you should see them.
According to the diary,
it seems like this incident happened
a few times last year, as well.
And your younger son witnessed it too.
What do you mean…
"this incident"?
I'm talking about suicide attempts.
You're making me repeat
the same thing over and over.
Sang-hun is not like that.
The only thing
I've been good at was studying.
I'm not even sure what that is now.
Is memorizing until I throw up studying?
I'm someone who is the worst
at what he does best.
Simply put, a loser.
The exams will probably continue.
And I will probably continue to fail.
I can't tell the difference
between life and death.
I can die.
If I die…
There isn't anything
people can't write in their diaries.
That's allowed
when you're having a hard time.
The important part is right here.
I do it as if it's become a habit.
I don't care if my brother sees me.
Die! Stop!
He can't seem to get a good night's sleep
ever since he saw me hang myself.
Die! Stop!
Does he have nightmares?
He watches me every night.
Die!
The idiot who doesn't even know
what dying is shakes in fear,
worried that I might die.
That…
is comforting to me.
Are you punishing us?
Did you call us here to let us know that
our child, who died a miserable death,
had suffered in life too?
Even on the day of the incident,
your younger son might've been
trying to stop the older one.
He might have beaten him up
because he got angry
after seeing his brother
attempting suicide continuously.
So what difference does that make?
The kid who was famous all over
the country for being good at studying
frequently attempted suicide
because of some mere academic stress.
If this gets out,
what becomes of our Sang-hun?
What would it be
besides disgracing a dead person?
Isn't getting a sentence reduction
for Mr. Jeong-hun, who is alive,
more important than the honor
of Mr. Sang-hun, who is dead?
He can't be seen as a person
who beat his own brother to death
without any particular reason.
There was a specific reason
that made his temper explode.
And now that the reason has been removed,
we'll have to show in the trial
that he won't commit violence anymore.
You be quiet!
What makes you so special
that you're calling my precious sons
by their names and judging them?
You're autistic yourself!
Honey, what's wrong with you?
Forget it.
Let's just call it quits.
I will give this case to an attorney
who won't insult my son.
The relationship between Sangjeong
and Hanbada is over.
Sir.
Ma'am.
-Hey.
-Yes.
I'm making ramyeon right now.
You want me to add one for you?
No, I'm good.
I'm not giving you a bite.
ATTORNEY WOO YOUNG-WOO
Attorney Woo, the mistake
my friend made last time…
What my friend did wrong
last time keeps bothering me.
I want to give you a proper apology.
You want to apologize to her. So what?
A male in his twenties,
who assaulted his brother to death,
has been charged
with bodily injury resulting in death.
The 21-year-old Mr. A,
who has autism spectrum disorder,
assaulted his intoxicated brother,
Mr. B, while their parents were out,
leaving him with a serious injury
of 22 rib fractures.
Mr. B was taken to the hospital
by his parents who had returned home
but in the end, passed away.
It was found out that Mr. B had achieved
a perfect score on the 2018 CSAT
and was a brilliant student
attending SNU medical school,
which only added
to the sorrow of the public.
ISN'T THE MED SCHOOL STUDENT DYING WHILE
THE AUTISTIC GUY LIVING A NATIONAL LOSS?
299 LIKES
I'M SURE HE'LL BE FOUND NOT GUILTY,
BY PLEADING INSANITY
HE KNOWS EVERYTHING EVEN IF HE HAS AUTISM.
SEND HIM TO PRISON.
I HAVE AN AUTISTIC NEIGHBOR
AND IT'S ACTUALLY SCARY
THIS IS WHY THEY SHOULD BE ISOLATED
LET'S NOT GO EASY ON HIM
JUST BECAUSE HE'S AUTISTIC
Hey.
Peng-ha!
I hear you got fired
even after you sang a song.
People often tell you
that you're rude, right?
that you pretend to be nice, right?
Attorney Jung.
I heard about what happened with
the Chairman of Sangjeong Pharmaceuticals.
You must be upset.
Well, I'm fine, but Attorney Woo worked
really hard on this, so it's too bad.
I see.
Attorney Woo, hang in there.
Where do you think you're going?
The fare…
What's the matter?
What seems to be the problem?
He just got into my taxi out of nowhere.
And kept saying "Hanbada."
So I brought him here, but he won't pay!
When I asked him
if he had money, he said "Yes."
I'll pay for his fare.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
Again. Sing.
Again.
Sing again.
Okay.
Call his mother and tell her
to come pick up her son.
And stay with him until she gets here.
Yes, all right.
Again. Sing again.
-Jeong-hun!
-Mom!
Goodness.
I was so worried!
Gosh.
Thank you, Attorney Woo.
I'm sorry Jeong-hun inconvenienced you.
It's fine.
Excuse me.
I've been doing some thinking.
Does it really have to be
revealed in court
that Sang-hun tried to make such a choice?
Jeong-hun can get
his sentence reduced anyway.
He has autism, so maybe
by pleading insanity.
I was hoping
you all would take this case back.
I don't think there will be anyone else
who would treat Jeong-hun
with such sincerity.
If you don't…
bring up that thing about Sang-hun,
I'll convince my husband.
Right.
Okay.
I will talk to
Attorney Jung Myeong-seok about it.
Attorney Woo.
I apologize for what my husband said.
I know
I shouldn't say this,
but we felt conflicted seeing you.
You and Jeong-hun both are autistic.
But you two are so different
that we couldn't help but compare.
We've heard that sometimes
people with autism are brilliant.
But seeing it in real life like this
made us feel strange.
You know, with autism,
most cases are like Jeong-hun.
And it just takes
too long for us to be hopeful
that he'll get better.
Hans Asperger, the first person
to do research on autism,
thought there was a positive side to it.
He said,
"Not everything that steps
out of line, and thus 'abnormal',
must necessarily be 'inferior'."
That with their new ways
of thinking and experiences,
people with autism
can later accomplish great things.
Hans Asperger was a Nazi collaborator.
His job was to separate children
who were worthy of living and who weren't.
To the Nazis, people who were
not worthy of living were those who were
physically disabled, terminally ill, or
mentally ill, including autistic people.
Jeong-hun, say goodbye.
Say, "I apologize for the trouble
I've caused. Thank you."
Peng-ba.
Even just 80 years ago,
autism was an illness
that was not worthy of living.
Even just 80 years ago,
Mr. Kim Jeong-hun and I
were people who weren't worthy of living.
Even now, hundreds of people
click the "like" button
on a comment that says,
"It is a national loss
if a medical student dies
and an autistic person lives."
Peng-ba!
That is the weight
of this disability that we bear.
WITNESS
I believe Mr. Kim Jeong-hun
had a meltdown.
Could you explain
what a meltdown is, please?
It is a phenomenon that occurs
to people with autism from time to time.
It is when they explode due to
not being able to withstand any longer
the stress they have been suppressing.
It's not something
that is done intentionally.
It just happens when they are overwhelmed
by the feeling of extreme helplessness.
There are a variety of types.
There are those that cut off
all communication and withdraw,
but also those where it can
manifest in very aggressive ways.
Like screaming, crying,
and even self-harm,
as well as displaying violent behavior.
So at the time of the incident,
the defendant's behavior
was a meltdown that he had
no choice or control over?
Thus, a symptom of autism
spectrum disorder?
Yes, I believe so.
That is all.
Witness, you are a psychiatrist
who is well-informed about autism?
Well, yes.
Right.
How many autistic patients
are in this courtroom?
What?
I'm asking because it seems to me that
there is one more besides the defendant.
What about the attorney
who questioned you just now?
Objection!
The prosecutor is insulting
the attorney with statements
that are both irrelevant
to the case and discriminatory.
Overruled.
Excuse me?
You're overruling my objection?
While the prosecutor's question
may be badgering the attorney,
I don't see it as being irrelevant
to the case nor as discriminatory.
Counselor, take a seat.
Prosecution, please continue.
So…
Is the attorney who questioned you
just now an autistic patient?
Just because one has autism does not mean
they all have to get treatment.
And I believe the phrase
"autistic patient" is inappropriate.
Even when she's doing that
in court?
Prosecutor, what do you think
you're doing?
What do you mean?
I'm asking whether or not the defendant's
attorney, Woo Young-woo, has autism.
I'm aware that Attorney Woo
has autism spectrum disorder.
However, I only know because I heard.
I did not diagnose her.
I'm not some sort of appraiser.
I can't say someone is this or that
the moment I see them.
Now, answer clearly.
Does Attorney Woo Young-woo
have autism or not?
She does.
-She does but--
-Do you think
that the defendant
is a mentally unfit person?
-Yes.
-Because he has autism?
Yes.
Then do you also think
the attorney is mentally unfit?
Objection!
We are on trial about the defendant,
but why do you
keep mentioning the attorney?
The attorney's medical history
is irrelevant to the defendant,
the incident, and the trial.
It is not irrelevant.
It is not irrelevant because the defense
is arguing for a reduced sentence
due to the defendant's autism.
If the autistic defendant
is mentally unfit,
can't the same be said for the attorney?
Does the prosecution
not know what mentally unfit is?
Having mental or physical disorders
does not mean they are all mentally unfit.
It is only when the disability affects
one's ability to discern things
and make decisions that they are
considered to be mentally unfit.
So the sentence of the autistic defendant
should be reduced
compared to other criminals,
but the arguments of the autistic attorney
should be recognized as equal
to other legal professionals?
Doesn't something feel off to you?
I'm pointing out the irony
of the attorney's argument.
Attorney Woo!
Your hand is still grabbing onto my butt.
Right.
Yes.
So that's why I fell on my back.
Your shoes…
Attorney Woo, your shoes.
Yes?
I was just hanging myself
and Jun-ho saved me.
Sorry, what?
Jun-ho first used his left hand
to hold up my butt.
And then used his right hand
to untie the knot around my neck.
Do you know what happened then?
My body was tipped backward
and I fell on my back.
What are you talking about?
According to the autopsy report,
Mr. Kim Sang-hun…
I mean,
the victim's ribs
had a total of 22 fractures.
Total of 5 on the front
of his right ribs, numbers 3 to 7,
and 6 on the front
of his left ribs, numbers 2 to 7.
And…
Wait…
May I point to your ribs?
What?
Sure.
And 11 on the back
of his right ribs, numbers 2 to 12.
And he doesn't have fractures
anywhere else. Isn't it strange?
The fractures
on the front of both his ribs
are highly likely from CPR.
The problem is the back of his right ribs.
The fracture is aligned straight
from number 2 to number 12.
Unless the defendant struck
the victim's back in a straight line,
it is hard to get this type of fracture.
However, if the defendant
tried to save the victim
with the same method
as Jun-ho, it is possible.
So, because the defendant
was holding onto the victim's butt,
he fell on the floor, back first.
So? What difference does that make?
That will make your younger son
not guilty of bodily injury
resulting in death.
Of course, he will be
found guilty of assault.
But he'll be able to get off from
the charge of killing your older son.
And the sentence will be much lighter too.
But…
for us to plead not guilty based on this,
we can't hide the fact
that your older son attempted suicide.
You need to decide, sir.
I've actually…
been thinking a lot about this problem.
When you reach my age,
children feel like
your report card for life.
As a father, I didn't want to admit
that Sang-hun was that unhappy.
But what is there that I wouldn't do
for Jeong-hun?
Proceed with what you just said.
Okay.
There's one thing I also want to say.
This was something I was going to
discuss with Attorney Jung alone.
But since we're all here,
I'll just say it.
All right. You two take a seat.
Okay.
From now on,
I want the trial to proceed
without Attorney Woo.
I know how hard you try, Attorney Woo.
However, you heard
what the prosecutor said during the trial.
Please think of
what is best for Jeong-hun.
But sir, you heard
what Attorney Woo told you just now.
We can take this in a different
direction than the last trial.
We'll not only emphasize
your younger son's mentally unfit state
but also plead not guilty based on
scientific evidence of the autopsy report.
I think…
the Chairman is right.
When I walk with Jun-ho,
people think he's doing
volunteer work for a disabled person.
When the taxi driver was holding on
to the defendant, I had money too.
But the driver didn't see me as someone
capable of resolving the situation.
I can tell how my autism
and the defendant's autism are similar
and how they're different.
But the prosecutor can't.
Which means…
neither can the judges.
I'm…
not an attorney
who is helpful to the defendant.
I'm…
not an attorney
who is helpful
to the defendant.
Please, convince the Chairman.
Of what?
Taking Attorney Woo Young-woo to court?
Yes. It's not like she's bad at her job
or that she made a mistake.
It's discrimination to not let her go
to trial because of the reason
that she won't be able
to effectively make her defense
due to her autism.
Weren't you the one who said,
"Did you not see
the second page of her resume?"
"You saw that but still accepted her?"
"How am I supposed to train someone who
can't even introduce herself properly?"
Didn't you say that?
What happened since then?
Back then,
she wasn't on my team.
Now, she is.
Well.
I do agree that
what the Chairman of Sangjeong asked is
unfair and discriminatory.
But I'm the CEO.
I have to do what the client wants.
So,
Attorney Jung, don't go to court either.
-What?
-You said she's on your team, right?
"If you don't go, I won't go."
You have to show them.
I can't be a fighter who fights until
the end for a rookie attorney's rights.
So you should show them.
That you two are one team.
Yes, all right.
Okay.
I will reassign the case to Attorney Jang.
Hand him the case files directly.
Why Jang Seung-jun, of all people?
You should at least
get that kind of penalty.
The Chairman might think
of this as very unpleasant.
Thinking you're protesting
because you're upset about what he said.
Okay, I understand.
Hey.
Myeong-seok?
What's up?
The CEO called you, right?
Yes, the CEO called me.
But what's up?
You should know if she called you.
Yes, I do know since she called me.
What are you getting at?
I just want to hear Myeong-seok
ask me for a favor himself.
Do me a favor.
What? I can't hear you.
Probably because I'm hanging upside down.
I can't hear you.
Do me a favor.
What did you say?
I can't hear you.
Gosh.
What?
Do me a favor, Seung-jun.
Can't you live without me, Myeong-seok?
How long do I have to keep
cleaning up after you, Myeong-seok?
Leave the case files over there.
I'll handle it for you.
I told you to put it over there.
Seriously.
What?
Myeong-seok.
Myeong-seok!
Darn it.
ATTORNEYS
Counselor, you may begin
questioning the witness.
Right.
DEFENDANT
What is your occupation, Witness?
I'm a medical examiner.
I do autopsy-related work
at the National Forensic Service.
What is the victim's cause of death?
He had internal bleeding
in his chest due to broken ribs.
Why would he have broken ribs?
The anterior fractures
seem to have been caused by CPR.
When the paramedics arrived,
the victim was already not breathing
and his heart had stopped,
so it is understood that the fractures
happened after his death.
The problem is
on the posterior side of the ribs.
There is a series of fractures
in the form of a slanted diagonal line.
Considering this location and the form,
it seems to be from a single,
continuous impact,
rather than separate, independent impacts.
You're saying it seems to be
from a single, continuous impact,
rather than separate, independent impacts?
That sounds quite complicated.
Can you simplify what you've just said?
It means that it's hard to say
that the ribs were broken one by one
because the fractures
are aligned in a straight line.
Instead, it would've been caused
by a single big impact.
A single big impact?
Could you give us an example?
At the time of the incident, the victim
seems to have fallen to the floor
after hanging
from the ceiling by his neck.
The rope that was found in his room
matches the scratches on his neck.
And on top of that, his blood
alcohol level was as high as 0.3 percent.
So there wouldn't have been
any reflexive behavior when he fell.
Then it's highly likely that
the fractures are from the fall.
Is there no possibility for the ribs
to have been broken
due to the defendant's assault?
Possibility? Yes, of course, there is.
However, it is a bit awkward.
I heard that the defendant
was extremely agitated
when he was attacking the victim.
In that state,
it would be difficult
to aim at the victim's ribs
in the shape of a neat line.
Thank you.
That is all.
Just a moment.
Let me ask a question first.
Defendant?
Mr. Kim Jeong-hun?
Yes!
You just heard
the medical examiner's testimony, right?
Did you drop your brother to the ground?
Yes.
Were you trying to save his life?
And it's not that
the rope broke on its own?
Yes.
Say it clearly.
Were you or were you not the one
to drop your brother?
Yes!
Mr. Kim Jeong-hun?
Were you trying
to save your brother or not?
Yes!
I asked these questions to check
if the defendant is capable
of understanding and answering questions
and testifying about what happened
at the time of the incident.
I think it is certain that the defendant
is mentally unfit as of right now.
The results will be good.
Is that so?
I was shocked that the prosecutor demanded
seven years of imprisonment
and claimed medical treatment and custody.
No matter what he demanded,
we proved our argument well.
And most of all, the judges
seemed to be understanding.
I think it's likely
that he'll be found not guilty
of bodily injury resulting in death.
And he'll get probation
for the assault too.
If not, we can always appeal,
so don't worry too much.
Okay.
Gosh.
It was no trouble at all.
It was an honor to be able to
finish your case myself.
You both worked so hard
to prepare for the trial.
I'm sorry.
Especially Attorney Woo,
you must be so disappointed.
It's fine.
-Thank you for your efforts.
-No problem, sir.
She's the--
Thank you, Seung-jun.
We'll get going now.
Attorney Woo, let's go.
Yes, you're welcome.
Excuse me.
Yes.
Could you wrap this up for me?
It's a gift.
-Sure.
-Thank you.
-Nice work.
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
AFFILIATION: HANBADA LAW FIRM
I HEREBY SUBMIT MY RESIGNATION DUE TO
PERSONAL REASONS, SO PLEASE PROCESS IT
RESIGNING PARTY: WOO YOUNG-WOO
ATTORNEY WOO YOUNG-WOO
Apparently, he got tricked by my uncles
and signed some weird memorandum.
Memorandum?
Yes, a memorandum that says he'll share
the land compensation with my uncles.
Your dad is getting land compensation?
-Ten billion won.
-That's great.
-Are you just going to watch the father
of your only friend become broke
after being fooled by his older brothers?
I'm not an attorney anymore.
-What? Why?
-I want to know the reason too.
Nakjo Village is a famous
date spot in Ganghwa-do.
-What?
-I'm rooting for you. You got this.
I want to be on the same
side as you, Attorney Woo.