Luang Wisut belongs with Lady Raya.
He's mine!
Thongkliao can give me what you can't.
I have a sense of shame,
so I wouldn't do it out in the open.
I hope Thongkliao is his last mistress.
I will turn love to disgust.
Let it be known.
I become vicious
when I meet the despicable.
I sympathized with Thongkliao
in the beginning.
But now,
I think what she's doing is not right,
especially to Lady Raya.
She's a good person.
Thongkliao shouldn't
have done this to her.
If Thongkliao
is going to steal the Lord
and hurt Lady Raya,
karma will get her.
Don't you worry about that.
Did Raya really send a letter to me?
Yes my Lord.
It looks like my son-in-law
is quite something.
Take this to Raya.
Yes my Lord.
Be careful. Don't let anyone see it.
And tell her, when I am free from duty
I'll visit her.
Yes my Lord.
Hurry up. She must be waiting.
Raya, I am going to the city to work.
When will you be back?
In a couple of days.
Lady Raya!
What's the matter Thong?
Why are you shouting?
Well…
I asked Thong to find me some herbs.
I've been feeling unwell lately.
Thong, go make the medicine for me.
Yes my Lady.
Are you… pregnant?
Well…
No, Luang Wisut.
I had my period this month.
It's alright. If it's meant to be,
a child will come.
Yes.
You should go now.
Please hurry back when you finish.
Alright.
What's the matter?
Raya.
Please take care of Thongkliao.
If she does something wrong,
teach her. So she won't do it again.
Alright.
Please hurry back Bun.
You've told me a hundred times.
It's because I'm worried about you.
And keep an eye on the Lord.
Don't let him flirt with any girls.
You sound like his wife.
I'm worried about Lady Raya.
Chuan, you know we are just servants.
We can't stop him.
Anyway, I'll try.
If he is involved with a girl,
I'll pretend to be interested in her.
Maybe she'll be interested in me.
Bun!
May goodness be with you.
Who is that?
It's Chuan,
Uncle Som and Aunt Mi's daughter.
The one said to be old enough
to take over Mi's cooking?
Yes my Lord.
Oh, she's all grown up, isn't she?
My dear Lord.
Please hurry back. I'll miss you.
I'll hurry back. I'll miss you too.
I'll take very good care of you,
Thongkliao.
Ouch!
My Lady, what's wrong?
I…
I'm afraid that when Luang Wisut
is back from the city,
he'll have another wife.
Really? A woman from the city?
No.
Then who is she?
Please tell me
who this shameless woman is.
I don't know how to say it.
But… you should know.
What should I know?
Well…
It looks like
Luang Wisut likes Im and Chuan.
I didn't want to alarm you,
but on the day they cleaned your room,
he gave them a lot of Sbai
and breast cloths.
Chuan and Im.
Also, before he left for the city,
he seemed upset to be away from them.
I don't want to say this.
But if you and I were not here,
by now, he would…
Chuan, Im, you're dead!
Thongkliao.
What are you doing?
I'm getting a knife
to stab those shameless women.
Don't do it.
Those two are stealing our husband.
Why are you stopping me?
I don't want this to be a big deal.
Think about it. If they died,
Luang Wisut would kill you too.
And after that, he'd have another wife.
He wouldn't mourn for you much.
Calm down Thongkliao.
Are you feeling better now?
Thank you for talking some sense into me.
Otherwise, I would have killed them.
Forget it.
If he has Im and Chuan as his other wives,
even if we hurt, we have to tolerate it.
I wouldn't mind if it was someone else.
But those two are like my sisters.
I can't accept
sharing a husband with them.
How would you stop him?
I can't stop him.
But I can stop those two.
Really?
Yes.
If you can really do that,
that would be good for me too.
I really mean it Thongkliao.
I can only let him have you
because you were here before me.
If it's someone else,
I would be suffering to death.
Those shameless women.
Despite having their own lovers,
they still try to seduce the Lord.
Don't worry my Lady. Apart from us two,
I won't let the Lord have any more wives.
Whoever thinks about stealing our husband
has to die.
It seems like Thongkliao
is easily provoked.
She totally believed you.
Foolish people always fall
into a smart person's trap,
especially a lustful woman
like Thongkliao.
Go to the kitchen tomorrow.
Let me know when they start fighting.
Yes my Lady.
I'll be in the kitchen
early in the morning.
This is for you.
Thank you very much.
Shameless women who like to be mistresses
are a good match for a wife like me.
Hurry up. It's late.
Lady Raya must be hungry.
Alright.
Here you go. Hurry up.
Hurry up.
Tuan,
Im and I will wash these cloths.
What cloths do you have to wash now?
The cloth that Lady Raya gave us.
After washing
I think I'll dry them with Ylang-Ylang
and jasmine, so they'll smell good.
You're obsessed.
A little bit Tuan.
Lady Raya's cloths are so good.
The Lady is so kind for thinking about us.
Of course, a high-class woman
is beautiful inside and out,
unlike someone who's over-ambitious.
Getting all puffed-up when they luck out.
Remember, these kind of people
will soon be in trouble.
Who are you talking about Thong?
No one. Whoever wants to take it
can take it.
Looks like she doesn't
want to die peacefully.
-What are those cloths?
-They're Sbai and breast cloths.
-Let me see them.
-Just normal Sbai and breast cloth.
Why do you want to see them?
If they're normal cloths,
what is there to hide? Give them to me.
I said give them to me.
My Lady. My Lady!
Are they fighting now?
Yes my Lady. I saw Thongkliao.
She looks very angry.
Let's go and watch.
-Let me see them.
-No. Let me go Thongkliao.
They're just normal cloths.
Why do you want to see them?
-It's my business. Give them to me.
-No.
-Give them to me.
-No, let me go.
Thongkliao, why do you want to see them?
Give them back to Chuan and Im.
They're just normal breast cloths
and Sbai.
If they're normal cloths,
what is there to hide?
The Lord gave them to you, right?
No. It's Lady Raya who did.
Don't lie to me. I know everything.
Don't ever think
you'll use cloth from the Lord.
Are you crazy?
They're trying to seduce him.
Who's doing that? You're crazy.
It's you.
-Ow!
-Chuan.
-Are you trying to seduce him?
Thongkliao.
Don't you think I won't fight back.
I also have functioning limbs!
Chuan, you're dead.
-Ouch!
-Stop!
Thong, I'm satisfied.
Shameless women fighting one another.
But they deserve even more than this.
Thongkliao, stop.
-Stop!
-Chuan!
Stop. Don't fight.
Stop.
My Lady.
My Lady,
please whip me.
It's my fault. I didn't mean it.
Please whip me instead.
Please don't do it to Chuan.
I'm the cause of it all.
Please whip me, my Lady.
It's my fault for crossing the line.
I do apologize.
It's alright.
It's worth getting hurt
if that makes you stop fighting.
My Lady, how are you? Does it hurt?
A little bit.
But I shouldn't have miscalculated.
What do you mean?
Think about it.
What would happen if I bled?
I should have waited longer
before barging in.
Do you mean this was all your plan?
Damn right. Getting myself hurt
for nothing would be foolish.
But that was worth it.
Thongkliao must be getting chewed out
by the other slaves now.
Soon she'll be an outcast
and no one will want her.
My Lady is so brilliant.
She's getting a taste of her own medicine.
How did Thongkliao turn into this?
Right? I'm really sorry for Lady Raya.
She got hurt accidentally
but she didn't complain at all.
That's what it's like
to be the first wife.
She's not a slave like Thongkliao.
And I told you
not to mess with Thongkliao.
-You didn't listen to me. Look at you now.
-Hey.
I've learned my lesson. From now on
I don't care anymore
if she lives or dies.
I will protect Lady Raya.
I won't let Thongkliao do anything to her.
Me too. The Lord deserves
a high-class woman like Lady Raya,
not a slave like Thongkliao.
If the Lord comes back
and sees Lady Raya's face like that,
I dread to think what will happen to us.
I've brought a good type of rice.
You can try planting it.
Tuan, get some water for the Lord.
Yes my Lady.
Raya.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Raya, let me see you.
What happened? Who did this to you?
Nothing.
Nothing? Then why is there
a handprint on your face?
Tell me.
Lady Raya, you should tell him.
My dear Thong, I'm fine.
Thong, what do you know? Tell me now.
It's Thongkliao, Chuan and Im.
Bring me those three slaves.
Yes my Lord.
My dear Lord, you're back.
I've missed you.
Why did you do that?
What did you do to Lady Raya
while I was away?
Luang Wisut, no one did anything to me.
Don't blame them.
I do.
If it's wrong, there's a consequence.
Otherwise, they will be spoiled.
How can you hit Lady Raya?
Bun, get me the stick.
My dear Lord.
I didn't mean it. It was an accident.
What accident?
I had a fight with Chuan and Im.
Lady Raya came to stop us
and she got hit accidentally.
And you, what did you fight over?
Why did you have to hit each other?
Tell me.
We had a little misunderstanding.
But anyway,
it was because
I love you with all my life.
I didn't mean to hurt Lady Raya.
My Lady, I apologize.
How about you Im?
I didn't mean to do it.
I apologize again, my Lady.
So, you are Chuan.
Yes my Lord.
How about you?
I didn't mean to do it either.
I apologize again, my Lady.
Raya,
none of them meant to do it.
What do you say?
I told you from the beginning
that I'm alright.
That's good then.
From now on,
you have to be careful.
Don't do this again.
Otherwise, don't say I didn't warn you.
Yes my Lord.
My dear Lord, are you tired?
Let me give you a massage.
Chuan, I remember your cooking.
From this trip to Phra Nakhon,
I've got vermicelli from Sampeng.
Can you make me crispy noodles?
Yes my Lord.
Wait.
Let me see your hand
if it's clean enough to cook for me.
I've seen it. It's clean.
You can go.
It's like I said.
These slaves are fast.
At first, Chuan acted innocent.
She was looking at the floor.
But when the Lord touched her hand
she got goosebumps.
Well, I think she is now
excited on the inside, waiting for him
to call her to serve him.
My Lady, you have to tame her.
You go and watch. Let me know
if there's something suspicious.
Yes my Lady.
Do your best,
so the Lord will be satisfied.
Alright, Mom.
Well, Mi.
Do you want the Lord
to take a liking to Chuan?
It's just for cooking Thong.
We are slaves.
We do whatever pleases our master.
That's good then.
I thought
you were telling her to be ambitious
and aim to be the Lord's wife
like Thongkliao.
Whoa Thong.
I wouldn't dare think about that.
That's good.
It's good that you don't think about that.
Chuan is my woman.
I've been thinking about telling the Lord
that I want Chuan to move in with me.
That's good.
You should tell him
that you want to live together.
I feel bad for Lady Raya.
It hurts. She's been suffering
because of Thongkliao.
Chuan, have you finished cooking?
So I can bring them the food.
It's almost ready.
What have you been doing?
You've been talking to me.
Crispy noodles are ready my Lord.
It looks delicious.
Let's try it. I'll feed you.
Chuan's cooking is really good.
She really did her best.
Where is she now?
Well…
She's working in the kitchen.
Mi, take this money.
Give it to her and tell her
it's a reward from me.
Thank you very much my Lord.
Tell her to cook for me again.
And cook for Lady Raya
to give alms to the monks too.
And you're old. You should rest.
Thank you for your kindness my Lord.
Im, you too.
You should work in the kitchen as well.
I want to try your cooking.
Yes my Lord.
The Lord really gave me this money?
It's true. Here it is. Take it.
Actually,
he's wanted you to work in the kitchen
for Mi for a long time.
But your mom didn't want to stop.
Well… I have to stop now.
Look. The Lord is so very kind.
Tomorrow, I'll cook for Lady Raya
to give alms to the monks.
I'll do my best.
Good.
Let me help too Chuan.
Alright.
My Lady,
we've prepared everything for the alms.
please allow me to give money
to make merit too.
Won't you keep it for yourself?
Living here,
I don't need the money for anything.
It's better to make merit for good karma.
It's good that you make merit.
You'll be comfortable in the next life.
For me, living under you and Lady Raya
is the best thing already.
You are grateful.
Let's go.
You're overreacting because your master
is kind to you. You don't know your place.
You're the one
who doesn't know your place.
-Damn you Chuan.
-Don't do it. I'm scared.
Let's go make merit.
If we're here for any longer,
Thongkliao will kill us.
What are you looking at?
You want to try me?
Long life, beauty, happiness and strength.
The Lord is interested in those two?
They are young fresh women.
How can you and I
compete with their youth?
It's probably not the two of us
because I'm confident
that I'm still young,
beautiful and fit.
What do we do now?
I've heard that Chinese merchants
are selling Chamob.
What is Chamob?
Female ghosts who died in the woods
and possess the area where they died.
They have strong vengeful spirits.
Women who own Chamob
will be blessed by charming spells.
All the men will fall head over heels.
If so, should we buy Chamob
from these Chinese merchants?
We shouldn't.
Even though it's a charm,
it's also a misfortune.
No good people would use those things.
It would be embarrassing.
Thongkliao,
I think we both have to give up
and let him have Im and Chuan
as mistresses.
I can't accept this by any means.
Bun, if you have a chance,
don't forget to tell the Lord about us,
and also Im and Ying.
Alright. Don't worry Chuan,
I'm planning to tell him.
Okay. I'll go now. See you in the evening.
Alright.
I'm going to work now.
My dear Lord.
Please hurry back. I'll miss you.
Why would you miss me?
I'll be back in the evening.
When you're out of my sight,
I miss you so much I could die.
You're always like this.
I'll hurry back then.
I don't want you to suffer.
I love you with all my life.
I'll hurry back.
You should go to work now.
-Alright.
-I'll walk you there.
Please hurry back.
My Lady, do you think
that the Lord still loves me?
I guess so.
It means my youth and beauty still work.
But to make sure,
I'll do everything to steer him away
from Chuan and Im.
My Lady, look at Thongkliao.
She can't ridicule me for long.
A slave like her will be in trouble.
Eh.
Hey.
Where is Thongkliao rushing to?
Huh?
Follow her and see Chuan.
Should I? She hates me.
We may fight again.
I'm afraid she'll put Lady Raya
in danger.
Then I'll go and see.
If Im goes, I'll go too.
I'll go too. Let's go.
What is Thongkliao waiting for?
It looks like she's waiting for someone.
Is she having an affair?
Tuan, what are you talking about?
Isn't it true? You do know
that she's fast about these things.
Now that the Lord is away,
she may be so starved
that she needs a fix from another man.
I don't believe it.
Thongkliao may be a vile person,
but she wouldn't be that promiscuous.
I don't believe it either.
Well, wait and see.
Look. I see who Thongkliao is waiting for.
It's just a Chinese merchant.
There's nothing.
But Thongkliao looks suspicious.
There's nothing. Let's go back.
Let's go.
Hey, do you sell Chamob?
Chamob?
Oh. Yes I do.
Well, you're lucky.
I've just got the Chamob
from a city that's famous
for charming spells.
Really?
Yes.
This thing doesn't come often.
It's rare to find a woman
dying unnaturally in the woods
whose spirit possesses a log
that we can use to make Chamob.
Then give me one.
It's expensive.
How much? I'll buy it anyway.
Here it is.
Oh, is this Chamob?
It gives you charms.
Hide it in your hair.
I guarantee your husband
will fall head over heels for you.
He'll never have mistresses.
Give it to me.
Money first.
You fell for it Thongkliao.
Hey.
Whoa. I was scared.
Wow, what a performance. That's yours.
Wow.
I'm so lucky today. I got a lot of money.
What did you give to that woman?
A real Chamob?
Whoa. What is Chamab? Samob? Chamob?
I've never heard of it.
I just heard about it
for the first time when you hired me.
But what is it?
It's just a wood carving
of a woman hugging a man.
But she totally believes it.
Maybe now she's sticking it on her hair
hoping her husband will love her.
Thong.
Do you want a Chamob
to use with your husband?
Go away! Go!
-Do you want some?
-Get going!
Did you see, Thong?
Foolish people always fall
into a smart person's trap.
Fool.
NEXT EPISODE
An insolent one like you
will face me, a servant.
Chuan!
If you would let me,
I will have only Chuan.
I will do everything
to get her out of this place.
It's like heaven's decrees
prevent you from marrying.
I'm worried.
Subtitle translation by: Panuway Baikeawon