What do you do when someone asks if you would like to do something together?
What?
I don't mind the intimacy, but he isn't quite the boyfriend candidate.
Then again, he's totally great as a male friend.
That being said, he's inviting me for drinks like it's a date.
Oh, that happens.
But even before that, when he asks for your LINE,
(T/N: Japanese messenger app)
it's a headache when you can't tell his true intentions.
Exactly.
"If possible" is such an annoying statement.
If they frankly said, "Please give it to me," it'd make it easier for us to decide, too.
Yeah, totally.
- I'm going to use the restroom.
- Sure.
"Do you want a cup of coffee?"
Excuse me.
Yes?
Um...
Does the lady who was drinking with me frequent this place often?
Are you talking about Minami?
No, the other lady.
Sone-chan?
Yes.
It was her first time here.
I see.
It's boats over horses for me lately.
They get me so pumped up.
Boats are much more exciting where I'm from.
You're from Saga, right?
I'm jealous! Now, I'm craving squid.
- How about coming with me next time?
- Of course!
Race 8 of Karatsu today is...
a close fight of 2-4-3.
What should I do? Spend money on it?
Want to have some hirezake after this?
(T/N: fish fins in hot sake)
Really? That'd be awesome! Let's go!
♫  Hey, ladies, where you at? So let's start it (let's start it)  ♫
♫  Just a night of lies can make you fall  ♫
­
♫  Can you feel your heart's exploding?  ♫
- Good morning!
- Morning!
Don't watch porn with the company's Wi-Fi. You'll get caught.
No, I wasn't doing that!
Oh, thanks for the drinks on Friday night.
It was nothing.
However, it was a terrifying experience.
Terrifying? What happened?
At the second bar, there were these lovely two women.
-  Good evening.
- But one of them was clearly dating the bartender.
So, I was complaining after leaving the bar...
My condolences.
When the other lady who left first appeared.
It was painfully obvious why you were buying us drinks.
That's because you were being a loser.
Leaving first only to come back and chat with us isn't normal.
Right?
But I bet someone like her doesn't have a boyfriend.
- She doesn't?
- No, I'm sure of it.
Morning.
So ironic.
Why don't women fall for nice guys?
I sense a story to be told.
Women are happier when they're loved, more so than when they're pouring out love.
I think I'm doomed.
What's going on? Is your relationship going south?
Last Friday, I went to a darts bar with Ryo-kun after you left.
What happened there?
Ryo-kun's friend was there, too.
A female friend.
Ryo-kun! I'll head home since I have to work tomorrow.
Huh?
What's going on?
Didn't I tell you about my rehearsals?
I'm a rookie actor.
Is that so...
A writer and an actor? He's quite busy.
Just like Tsutsui Yasutaka.
(T/N: Japanese author and actor)
Ryo-kun's overflowing with too much talent for a single lifetime.
You're so devoted, Meguro-chan.
When I saw Ryo-kun hugging that woman,
I tried to convince myself that he was only practicing with a fellow actress.
But jealousy still bubbled in me.
- So...
- So, what did you do?
I turned to Instagram.
Ryo-kun follows my account
and I posted that photo yesterday.
Is this about the ugly cocktail?
No, look carefully!
Ryo-kun checks my posts, and I wanted him to get jealous.
So I made sure the guy beside me was in the shot, too.
Do guys remove their arm hair these days?
What do I do, Sone-chan?
This is horrible, right?
Ryo-kun will be furious if he sees it, right?
I've made a blunder in my romance.
What do I do?
Hey.
Your phone's been buzzing. Aren't you taking a look?
It's probably just work. Don't mind it.
Is it another girl?
How can there be "another" girl if there isn't anyone else?
- Hey.
- Yeah?
- Are you jealous?
- No, I'm not.
- You are.
- Are you hiding something?
No, nothing!
What am I? A stalker?
It's been three days!
He hasn't replied for three days.
I've been texting him,
but I bet he's furious.
Peyang's Korean BBQ pork flavor's not bad.
Sone-chan, are you listening? It's been three days.
I'm sure this is a case where he doesn't even care.
That's definitely not true. Ryo-kun's a sensitive guy.
Being a bartender is tough. He has to face customer's all day!
I'm his source of comfort.
But my brief jealousy has hurt him.
I really have to reflect on my actions.
He's been leaving me on read, so I want to apologize in person.
Hey, Sone-chan, can't you visit Ryo-kun's bar with me tonight?
Sure, but I have to go home early to catch "Tokyo Swindlers."
What? You've been watching that?
Hey there! What were you two chatting about?
It's been three days without a reply from him!
- Hang on, what's this about?
- She's desperate.
Anyway, how are things with you and Nakazawa-san?
Ah, that Italian restaurant in Aoyama and low-rise mansion guy.
Oh, I lost interest in him.
What? But you were head over heels for him!
I contacted him frequently after that, but he ignored me.
Three days is nothing.
And two days ago, he texted me at 1am asking if we could meet up at his place.
That was when I lost interest for good.
Now, I have my eyes on a different guy.
Matsuda-chan, you're really the type to move on right away if a guy treats you poorly.
That's very true. I always put myself first.
If someone doesn't treat me right, I can't even spare a second for him.
I think he's someone unworthy of my time.
Matsuda-chan, do you listen to the Kano Sisters' "Fabulous World" podcast?
What's that?
Here is where you are.
Are you all attending Fujita-chan's wedding?
- If so, can you work reception?
- Got it.
Senior Mitsuki, are you organizing it?
Yes, but I won't be able to attend.
You aren't going?
Why must I spend time bearing witness to the happiness of others?
I'm busy pursuing my own happiness.
The ideal organizer plans everything perfectly, then misses the actual event.
Matsuda-chan, help me out for a second.
Okay!
The food was great.
Sone-chan, I want to marry someone I love and have a family with them after all.
I also want to raise kids and grow old with them.
That's happiness for me.
I get how you feel.
Honestly, when I heard about Fujita-chan's wedding, I felt really envious.
At 24, she found her lifelong partner.
Meanwhile, I'm already 28. What if things stay this way forever?
But you know what?
That's just a passing worry that we women in our thirties catch.
- Utsunomiya!
- Yes, sir!
Are you busy tomorrow night?
No.
In that case, we haven't had a welcome party for you yet.
I appreciate the thought, sir!
Is there anything you'd like to eat?
If it's expensive, anything works.
You're frank.
Yes, sir.
Come on, let's go.
How long must we wait here?
But a furious Ryo-kun is in there.
I've never seen Ryo-kun like that.
- I'm scared.
- Why the heck are we here in that case?
- I'm going in.
- What? Wait!
It's freezing.
Wait─
Welcome.
I guess I'll go home.
- What?
- See you.
Hey! Sone-chan!
- Ryo-kun.
- It's been a while, Minami.
What's wrong?
My texts...
Why haven't you been replying to them?
I know I wasn't being the nicest,
but I was really anxious because you wouldn't reply.
I was scared.
I thought you hated me.
I see...
I'm sorry that I frightened you.
Actually...
I've been trying out Mind Travel.
Mind... What?
With Mind Travel you project your thoughts into a completely different world.
By doing that, you can refresh your mind.
You'll be able to look at things from a different perspective.
If I don't do that, I won't be able to write a good novel.
Therefore, I projected my mind to Vietnam.
So that's what happened...
And you were mind traveling when I texted you?
That's right.
Texts and the like don't exist in that plane.
Sorry.
But I'm back now.
Feel free to text as much as you like.
I want to read all your messages.
Ryo-kun, you're indeed strange.
You don't like that?
I love it.
I knew it.
Ryo-kun, do you really like me?
Of course.
I'm always thinking about how hard you must be working.
Even when I was in Ho Chi Minh City, you were on my mind.
Let's have Banh Mi together next time.
Ryo-kun!
Hey, Ryo-kun.
Can I come here next Sunday?
Of course.
A younger colleague of mine is having a wedding that day.
A wedding? That's wonderful.
Really?
Do you also consider weddings wonderful?
Definitely, as long as your colleague is happy.
She's getting married at 24,
but I'm turning 28 this year.
That's why... Well, I wondered what you think about marriage.
It's something worth celebrating.
I also want to get married.
Why?
Huh?
Marriage is just a bond written on a piece of paper.
If I can be with you and we love each other, we don't need a piece of paper.
Wow, a typical scumbag's reply.
You think so, too? He's avoiding the issue, right?
He's blatantly doing it.
I guess we'll never be a couple.
Oh my, that's the first time you have adopted this attitude.
I mean, if he's utterly disinterested in marriage,
I'd have to wait forever for his proposal.
In that case, I'd rather prioritize myself like Matsuda-chan.
That's a great perspective.
Place yourself first! Right?
Wow, you should run for office! Vote for Meguro Yuriko!
You don't have to be in a rush to make decisions.
Take your time to decide whether to break up.
You like him, don't you?
Do you want to drop by the bar with me tonight?
- Again?
- Just for one drink! Please!
Ugh, but I want to know what happens to Harrison Yamanaka!
I just need you to probe about my future with Ryo-kun.
Thank you for the meal!
Motsuyaki is always delicious.
(T/N: Grilled offal skewers)
- Then I'll head home first.
- Sure.
- Thanks!
- Take care!
- Shall we go?
- Sure.
All right, boys.
- Do you want to go to Korido?
- You're pumping with energy.
Honestly, rookies should only answer with "yes" or "no."
In that case, it's a "no" for me.
Utsunomiya, you're coming, right?
- No.
- What?
I have plans tonight.
I don't want my girlfriend to worry either, so I'm going home.
- Wow, what a cool statement.
- Seriously?
- Thank you.
- Come on.
You'd miss the chance to meet a sleeveless babe.
I think it's much better to meet a girl who looks cute no matter what she wears.
Bye, I'm heading off.
- Take care.
- You, too.
Hey, was he trying to preach to me just now?
That's a win for Baba-kun this time.
Whatever, I'm going home.
- Take care!
- You, too.
Meguro-chan.
You're prepared for this, right?
What?
Talking about marriage is a heavy topic for any guy.
That's why Ryo-kun was avoiding the issue.
If he doesn't give you the answer you want, don't let it shake you.
Don't let your emotions take over.
That's what you need to be ready for. Can you do it?
Thank you, Sone-chan.
I've steeled myself.
Got it. I'll stay for just one drink.
Thank you.
All right.
You're doing great.
Okay, one, two.
Daddy, do your best at work!
Thank you, Anju. I'll do my best.
Okay! Daddy, I love you!
Anju!
I also love you the most in this world!
Hang on! Wait!
Wait! Stop!
I liked him!
I loved him!
I... really wanted to marry him!
It was worse than we thought.
I really considered marrying him,
but he betrayed me!
He's married and has a child!
I really loved him!
But...
Meguro-chan, I thought you'd move on quickly...
But you're bawling.
Sone-san!
What a coincidence.
I was also drinking nearby.
If possible, how about sharing a drink?
Oh, I'm Hiroto, Utsunomiya Hiroto.
- Last week, we were at the bar together─
- Dude!
You have horrible timing.
This isn't the time for drinks.
- Pardon?
- I have to get going.
- Apologies.
- I can't leave her alone.
- Yes, of course.
- I mean...
This is too entertaining!
E-Entertaining?
Hey!
Um...
If possible, can I have your number?
"If possible"?
Then no, it's not possible. See you!
♫  Hey, ladies, where you at? So let's start it (let's start it)  ♫
♫  Can you feel your heart's exploding?  ♫
♫  Let's get through the night  ♫
Does she despise me?
Are you waiting for Sone-chan?
No, not at all.
It's fine if I'm happy now.
I'll only say it once.
- Okay!
- 0-8-0.
- 0-8-0...
- 7-2...
See you!
So I have a chance.