I'm not afraid of you.
I'll teach you a lesson in the 20th year.
Tell me.
please
Wait for the
The
Looking for life
Killing him
In this era,
Am I wrong to perceive Moses's presence like a OLED tablet?
Those who were present a long time ago
Now,
Today,
You must listen carefully
Go ahead
Both a sound and high
Both eyes
Stand up
Francis
Come and hurry
You are always supported
things
давайте
The people of the country are all dead.
The North China Sea Temple Desها hotel
ienstabilized tens of thousands people.
The crime dissolved from the crime Dou family!
The crime...​
killed him...
The people of the country are all dead.
The women of the country the verdict would be completed soon.
greets the Chang
I'd rather be uniform, because then I'm not a demon.
What should I do?
Kill!
Kill! Kill!
Yes.
Kill him.
Can you go back to the right path?
Wang Lin has been in the palace for 20 years.
Now he is like Wei Wenjing and Wei Yishi.
He can't wake up.
He is a man of his own.
He is insolent and ungrateful.
He is greedy, despicable,
and despicable.
He is a man of his own.
He is evil.
Master, I want to ask you.
Is what I did evil?
Yes.
How should I let go of the evil?
I have never been more powerful
for the country.
I have never been more powerful for the country.
How should I let go of the evil?
Do you know what evil is?
I want to ask you.
Have you ever seen evil?
Have you ever felt what evil is?
Will you deserve none?
Man shall open the作.
Master, you know what evil is?
Which...
Of the divine.
Gelior
No
Ad if you dare dareretch to open it
below
This is Hell
It's like theカクリル牧彗星
New Taste
Teacher.
I've told you before,
men should show their loveиваем way.
good desires for the evil
confess it했어요
본色相本来就是空
若心中不邂念
怎麼会被眼前所见
谦动情绪
你们说他是rock
他是吗
还是我们的内心才是魔鬼
You are a ghost!
Stop talking nonsense!
I just want to ask you one thing!
Are you going to kill or not?
I just want to find the way out.
But the answer is not here!
Hurry! Take these two demons down!
Take these two demons down!
Prime Minister!
You...let me die!
Maybe it's fate.
I can't get the Immortal.
They are going to catch me.
You can revive me!
Do you think it's possible?
No!
What's wrong with you?
Madam!
You still have to go back with them!
No!
Madam!
I have been using you since I was a child.
I came to Mount Zu and saved them from the tower.
If you are telling the truth,
then everything is your conspiracy.
Yes.
You are all fake to me.
We were enemies.
I hate you guys!
You...
Don't ask!
I don't love you.
Cut me up!
rels!
Jiang Ming!
Jiang Ming and Yao Hu.
You two have no way back.
I'll ask you one more time.
Do you want to go back?
Do you admit your mistake?
Jiang Ming!
I can't go back.
I won't regret it.
I won't.
You!
I didn't have a life.
I was an orphan.
Thank you, master.
Thank you, father.
I'll repay you for your life.
I'll kill him now.
Master!
Ming!
Why didn't you hit me?
I'll kill you.
Everything is over.
Wu'er!
I was an orphan.
Although I had a master,
I still had a father and a wife.
But I was still an orphan.
I'm not good.
Let's go!
Brother Xiao, take care of master.
Master!
What happened?
What happened in the cellar?
The number of dead disciples in the prison
is not a problem.
You're the one who caused it.
I'm willing to do it.
You're willing?
Jiang Ming.
His ghost soul is a demon.
He killed all the disciples in the mountain.
He escaped from the place where he wanted to go.
He was told before he died.
How could it be like this?
Brother Xiao said that
a man should always think about his own life.
I'm willing to do it.
One year later
Between Mount
and Yisse,
Master Tai was a master at the Jinyin Decibel
Master Tai, the beloved son of General Jiang,
the beloved disciple of Jiang Ming,
has finally entered the Demon Realm.
Master Tai, you have hurt yourself.
You will never face the ancestors again.
Here, this drink.
Master Tai has given two of the last如果你.
I'm telling you, please go to the Rotor One through the rice cooker.
Thus the girl can now enter the water by itself
from the entrance to the pond.
and the master of the clan, Qi Yi.
Qi Yi,
all the things related to Jiang Ming's daughter's wish and the tower,
all the disciples of Shushan, will never be mentioned.
All the records related to Jiang Ming,
everything of them are all returned to them.
Jiang Ming's name seems to have never been mentioned.
From that day on,
the Shushan Sect was completely lost.
After many years, all the disciples of the clan have passed away.
The darkest history of Shushan
is now unknown.
Except for the mother and the brother of the sword,
the Shushan Sect has been destroyed.
Although all the records of Jiang Ming have been burned,
but the master set up a memorial in the palace
and has been sincerely giving it to him.
He hopes that he can help him to get to the top soon.
His memorial has not been able to be rewritten.
It's not easy to give him a memorial.
So Jiang Ming's soul has been left in the tower.
He can't leave.
Drink it, Jiang Ming.
Now you two are ghosts.
Do you know why we didn't let you in?
Are you scared?
Do you think we'll be scared?
Yes. It's not enough to lie to a child.
You're so mean.
If you were the girl you mentioned,
you would do everything.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Someone told me a story in the wilderness.
I know that it must be you.
The Shushan Sect must be your brother.
Who is that Shushan Sect?
You're so loud.
You can't be serious.
Forget it.
There's no secret.
There's no secret at all.
It's the queen.
It's Ling'er's mother.
You...
She and I are even cleaner than water.
Master, you told me before.
You gave me your lamp.
This is another story.
What?
You and another woman have another story?
No, you're a fake.
What do you know?
Then tell me.
I won't say.
You're a senior.
Since you have a relationship with the queen,
why did she take Ling'er away and make her 70 years old?
I know that I have a lot to do.
I must ask her what she's thinking.
I don't care what she thinks.
I must save Ling'er.
You can't do that.
Ling'er.
You're too much.
I'm more handsome than you.
You're useless.
You can't kiss me or bite me.
It's your responsibility.
Who told you to be my master?
I've prepared it.
I'll make you embarrassed.
You want to see me?
Yes.
Isn't this your sword?
Give it to me.
Take it.
Don't touch my mother.
Hey, you don't need it.
What do I use it for?
I'm a strong sword.
Take it.
Protect your self-respect.
Give me a strong one.
And these talismans.
You can use them in the tower.
And this bamboo.
It's not good for your hair.
You can use it to protect yourself.
And this carrot.
Hey, you're too much.
I can't take it.
You can keep it.
You're so stupid.
What's this wine?
It's called the Drinking God.
It's used to make wine.
Wine?
Yes.
I'm a strong man.
I can only use this kind of wine.
But you're too stingy.
You drink so much.
Why are you so stingy?
You hear me?
You're too stingy.
This is too powerful.
You've used wine many times.
You're too stingy.
You'll use this every time.
You'll be able to use all your spiritual power.
So remember.
Unless you die,
you can't use this.
So?
You're so smart.
I see.
And...
You're so handsome.
What's your skill?
This is the first Wanyue tree and the first cloud tree.
It's the perfect skill for the Qing and Huai.
This is the most important skill.
Awesome.
Is it useful when you're in the treasure?
And the last one.
You've learned it.
You'll be safe and sound.
Do you want to learn it?
Yes.
Tell me.
Don't be so stingy.
I won't learn it.
Take care.
Thank you, Shun Bu.
Thank you.
I'm not afraid of the earth.
I'll protect Ling Er and Sheng Liang.
Hey!
What's wrong?
You're making me nervous.
I'm afraid you'll be too fast.
I don't know who will kill you.
That old man.
He's a good man.
What's wrong?
Are you nervous?
It's not the first time.
What's so nervous?
What's the first time?
The second time.
So many times?
I'm counting them all.
You've met him since the first time we met.
You...
What's wrong?
You're a loyal friend to me.
No.
I like you after I've become a good friend.
I see.
What do you mean?
You like me?
I hate you too.
I don't care.
You promised me to be with me.
I see.
I'm done.
Let's go.
But we...
Close the door.
I have a way.
What are you doing?
You'll know later.
What's wrong?
I'm not afraid of you.
I'm afraid of you.
Step
You've learned to fly at a元house.
Miss Erni, where do you want to go?
I want to go to the Sea of Heaven.
Okay, let's go.
What's wrong?
Is that what we should do?
You already know what you know.
You don't need to know what you don't know.
Why do you keep asking?
What about Ling'er?
Do you want to know my answer?
Or you can't accept the fact?
People are so kind.
But we should be busy.
I don't think so.
She's the daughter of the Empress.
What about Ying'er?
Li Xiaoyao.
What?
Why do you still want to disperse Xiaoyao and Ling'er?
No.
I just want to be a good person.
Why do you want to do that?
Tell me.
Even if you want to escape, you can prove it.
Prove Xiaoyao's feelings for Ling'er?
Why do you want to be a good person?
Why do you want a girl who has been suffering for 70 years?
70 years is just a deadline.
It's Li Xiaoyao's deadline.
You want to let Ling'er go after Xiaoyao is dead?
That's good for both of them.
Ling'er, you don't care about her at all.
Why do you care?
She's suffering.
She's suffering because she's been abandoned by her beloved.
She's suffering because she's been left behind.
It's just a matter of time.
If Li Xiaoyao can see through this,
it's her fate.
Everyone has his own choice.
Do you want to let Xiaoyao be as good as you?
She's a smart girl. She has her own talent.
If she knows how to let go,
she'll have great benefits no matter she's a martial artist or a human.
Even so, why do you want her to be the same as Xiaoyao?
Jiang Yuxi will be the same as Zhang Zhizhi.
If she makes a few mistakes,
she'll be much bigger than him.
I don't understand.
It's your right.
Everyone has his own choice.
What do you mean?
The person who abandoned her beloved
made her suffer.
She got married to someone else
and even sacrificed herself.
This is your mistake.
You're still in charge of this at this moment.
You killed Wu Hou.
Why do you want this tragedy to happen?
So you still don't understand.
Yes, I don't understand.
Junior.
Look.
This is my heart.
Junior.
What is the matter?
You know you're in danger.
You're not saved.
This is the Taoism.
This is the wisdom.
You didn't see the wisdom in the water.
What you see is the surface of the water.
Look.
Look at you in the water.
You can't see yourself in the confusion.
You can't see the water.
You can't see the Taoism.
You know how to take it.
You can't let it go.
If this is the Taoism,
I'll use your Taoism to solve my problems.
Let it stop.
Just like what you did to me.
You dare not
or you can't?
When the ancient times began,
all the things in the world were divided into Yin and Yang.
So there are the heaven and earth,
and there are the curse and the evil.
Yin and Yang are united.
They are not lacking in anything.
They are not close to each other.
They are not united.
There is a legend.
Every person who comes out of this world
is actually just a half body.
One must find the other half.
The only other half.
This kind of life
can be called completely.
As long as you take the curse on the side,
find the other half's owner,
these two will be blessed by God.
They will love each other forever.
Today, I give this curse to someone.
No need. Thank you.
This is for you.
I'm willing to give it to you.
I'm on my way to Mount Zu to learn from you.
Does this have anything to do with it?
I'm going to join the Taoist sect.
I don't want to be a girl anymore.
Why?
Why not?
I heard that
you can join the Taoism and practice without hesitation.
This is the highest level of martial arts.
What is the highest level?
The world is the highest level.
There is no one to be the top.
The top is the highest level.
Aren't you the one who stands at the top?
Are you not your enemy?
You have teeth in your mouth,
but you have no teeth in your teeth.
People have their own limits.
In addition, you should only be the highest level of the Taoism.
Why don't you follow your heart?
The Taoism is to follow your heart.
To follow your heart is to follow your mind.
That's the real Taoism.
No one can know that.
Taoism is to follow your heart.
As long as you understand this,
you will not be the top.
Although I don't understand what you are saying,
I like your saying,
Taoism is to follow your heart.
We are destined to be together.
That's why I gave you the half of the Taoism.
You are the Taoism of the mountain.
That's your fate.
I hope you can use your own Taoism to get rid of the doubt.
You need to give it to someone.
Maybe you can solve a problem.
A hundred years of love.
You think you can solve it?
Taoism is to follow your heart.
As long as you understand this,
you will not be the top.
That's your fate.
No one can know that.
Taoism is to follow your heart.
That's your fate.
No one can know that.
Wow.
So awesome.
The way you are,
you are the most beautiful.
Although you are a little green,
but you are just a sword.
Not a sword.
A sword? What kind of sword?
When you are in Mount Shushan,
you will understand what is the real sword.
What about the introduction?
You will become a great weapon.
But you will be far from the Taoism
for your cleverness.
The world is small,
but the world is not.
You are so clever.
Give me a good gift.
What should I do?
I am afraid that I will be defeated.