I'm not afraid of you.
I'm not afraid...
of you.
Li Wei.
Goodbye.
Me?
You...
Master Li,
we've known that you would leave us for no reason.
Are you worried that my grandmother might kill me?
What?
You are unable to bear to let go of me?
Why do you want me to travel the land?
My wife...
I have've been here already for a certain period of time.
I should have come back to Chang'an to report my investigation to His Majesty.
What about you?
I want to go back to Suzhou to see my old aunt.
Okay, I'm fine. I'll take you back.
Really?
But I won't go into your house. I'm lazy to see that...
Whatever.
The world is full of lies.
Can you stop asking? You're making me angry.
Cousin, Master Li has resigned.
Goodbye, A-qi.
Cousin, goodbye!
Let's go.
What do you plan to do after I return to Suzhou?
I'll go back to Yuhang Town to fight against the enemy.
I'll go to Langji Tianya if I'm in a good mood.
I want to go too.
You don't want to?
Do you know how to be funny?
Actually...
I really don't know you.
What?
I think it's not a little.
It's a lot.
Don't push me.
I'm serious.
I've been thinking about you for a long time.
And I know that you've been with me.
Don't you feel sorry for me?
You're here again.
I hate men like you.
We've been together for a long time.
You shouldn't be so reckless.
What do you mean?
I'm a normal man.
You know what kind of person you like.
I know.
That's good.
Li Xiaoyao, I like you.
No.
I love you.
I'm not a chicken.
Do you think I can make you cry?
You taught me clearly.
I've seen it clearly.
Don't throw away those bad memories with me.
I know you're always so kind.
But I can let you have his existence.
Thank you.
Am I generous?
You're not like me.
You're kind.
Yes.
Situ Dan, do you think our new world is going smoothly?
We need your help.
We've found the right place to deal with the demons.
We've saved a lot of time.
We've got many treasures and pearls.
Do you think it's a coincidence?
I think we've made a good arrangement.
Who's so brilliant?
I don't know.
Young people, help me.
I'll go.
Thank you.
Do you have a friend who looks like a student?
He's almost as tall as you.
How do you know?
Go save him.
There were some men following him.
What?
They're old and don't know martial arts.
Where did they go?
Over there.
Cousin.
Which direction is back to Chang'an?
Over there.
Cousin, back to Chang'an.
But the boss told us that way.
That's the direction of the inn.
How can it be like this?
What's wrong?
I feel a little bored, so I'll feel as I was.
How is it so happy?
Is it a題?
It's also sounds like песile.
But when I suddenly heard the music,
I remember I acted in different ways
and got tired of me.
Since then,
how do you know that?
Like an kolk,
an old
romance.
There are many strange things on this road.
Maybe we have become the pawns of others.
No way.
Why did they do this?
For Ling'er.
What did you say?
They may be the people of the Banyu Sect.
They want Ling'er.
The Banyu Sect is the national religion of the South Zhao State.
Ling'er is the princess of the South Zhao State.
They don't treat Ling'er well.
No matter what,
let's go to see Ling'er first.
Hurry up.
Go.
Master. Master.
Princess, here.
Come on. Hurry up.
Hurry up.
Who are you?
I'm here to take her away.
No way.
Princess.
Master.
Ling'er is here.
It's safe for her.
Princess.
Wei.
Zhen.
Bing.
They are all dead.
Where is Ling'er?
Go find them.
Are you really grateful or being ridiculous?
No.
Is He being哭?
Is He rebelling?
Is he doing anything wrong or doing this dirty one?
Because his attack
No. I've never done this before.
How dare you say you didn't do it?
How can you explain everything you did in the camp that day?
Stop, sir!
Stop.
Father, what you did was a good thing.
You killed someone.
This is the father and mother of the two kings.
They don't care about the others.
Every time they go to war, they always have a good reputation.
This is the famous and famous high-ranking in the capital.
These people always escape to the battlefield.
They don't care about the others.
They deserve to die.
I've never done anything wrong like the answer I gave you.
You killed someone at the age of 15.
You didn't regret it.
You are not a person like that.
You killed ten people at a young age.
I'll let you pay for their lives.
These people are so cunning.
They are weak and they don't know how to attack.
This is not the reason why you killed them.
I didn't kill them.
The real people are not easy to deal with.
They don't know how to play the game.
I'm just a person who can do anything.
You are still so clever.
I didn't do anything wrong.
These people deserve to die.
I'll do it.
I killed you.
Father, you won't kill me.
Father, you really kill me.
Is the world a human being?
The world is a human being.
You really don't love me?
You should protect your child
as your father.
I'm so ashamed of you.
I have nothing to say.
Father, are you really not sad?
You killed my son.
I can't forget the pain
in my heart.
Until now, you still want to kill my son.
Are you not sad?
Father.
You still feel that you didn't do anything wrong?
It's true.
You can't keep it.
You want to kill me?
Come on.
Be cruel this time.
Don't be like the last time.
You hurt me.
I also hurt you.
I can't face
a person who is pure and loving.
I'm a devil.
What can I do?
I'll kill you.
You have made me a devil.
You can only enter the world
as a evil thing.
What's the point?
It's not the point.
I'm to take revenge on you.
This is just the grudge between you and me.
Don't be restrained.
I am willing to bear the responsibility of not taking responsibility
Are you willing to bear the responsibility?
Come on
This matter should have been solved long ago
Ok
I am willing to bear the responsibility of not taking responsibility
Are you willing to bear the responsibility?
Come on
This matter should have been solved long ago
Ok
I am willing to bear the responsibility of not taking responsibility
Are you willing to bear the responsibility of not taking responsibility?
Come on
This matter should have been solved long ago
Ok
I am willing to bear the responsibility of not taking responsibility
Are you willing to bear the responsibility of not taking responsibility?
Come on
This matter should have been solved long ago
Ok
I am willing to bear the responsibility of not taking responsibility
Come on
Father
Don't move
Or you will be broken into pieces
Father
I just want to see
whether someone like you
will cherish you
If you do
then in this world
there might really be a love
Do you know
If I am loved
I will learn to love others
Yes
Just like I am loved by others
Father
I hope someone loves me
Take care
Father
Master
Let's go
Don't come over here
Don't hurry up, Master Zhang
He is injured
He can't move
Otherwise...
What? I will break into pieces
Master Zhang, don't move
I am not hurt
I am just a woman
If I do this
I will be killed
Even if I die
I will not be punished
Where are you?
You are always a good person
No
I personally raised a demon
but I didn't want to
I let him do harm to the people
You?
Master Bai Yue
is called Shi Jie Ren
He is your son
Everything is because of me
Master Zhang
You have to stop
I will find a way to save you
No need
Listen to me
Master Zhang
You can do whatever you want
We will do our best to help you
You can't let the princess go back to Nanzhao
It's all my fault
No, it's all my fault
You can't let the princess go back
I know
Please apologize to the princess
I can't protect her anymore
She will understand
Master Zhang
Do you have any orders?
I...
Do you want to see Tang Yu?
Uncle
Master
My son
The biggest regret in my life
is that I never have any regrets
What's wrong with you?
Don't touch me
You are so selfish
You will be a great man in the future
Uncle
Remember
You should protect my son
Uncle
Master
Don't cry
My son
I am sorry to the country
I am punished
Master
Shizhang
Uncle
Don't worry
Do your best
In the universes, clap your hands
Ai Lian is from Anjia's family.
What a nail-shady she is!
She must be wearing a Husband's robe
where I haven't had any trouble with.
But our friends are from me.
From now on,
we'll end up seperately.
I will never forget the kindness that Father gave me.
We will never let him down.
The world is in heaven.
He will protect us.
We are in a different world.
I just went to Mount Shu.
I asked for the poison to cure the wound and let the princess out.
I will go with my daughter to save Qi and take her to Ping An.
We will meet at the mountain in the end.
Okay.
Okay. We will continue to succeed and not fail.
Mother, is there anything wrong?
Hello.
Uncle Baiyue.
Demon head, I want you to die in blood debt.
Uncle Baiyue, are you the big bad guy who killed the master?
I came here just to play a game with you.
Now is the second meeting.
It shows whether there is anything in the world.
Let us out.
Let us out or I will kill you.
Uncle Baiyue, why do you do this?
Uncle Baiyue.
Uncle Baiyue, why don't you answer my question?
Goodbye.
Uncle Baiyue. Uncle Baiyue.
Let us out.
Master, will they continue like this?
Love is good for the old.
As long as they love each other,
they will be safe and sound.
Just like they are in the bottomless cave.
Uncle Baiyue.
Master, I am not a demon.
I am a queen.
I am the daughter of the manzhao kingdom.
The manzhao kingdom is now in hot water and hot water.
As a queen, I have the right to take my responsibility.
I will use the power given to me by god to save my people.
I will do as they say.
Are you done?
Master.
I am not a demon.
I am a queen.
You don't have to say.
Show your true identity.
Immortal Tao Lao Lao.
Immortal Tao Wang Wang.
Immortal Tao Ne Xi.
Immortal Tao Gui Sheng.
Immortal Tao Gui Zhou.
Immortal Tao Chang Si Qi.
Chief Brother!
First of all, the Nan bateries mobilize directly
Now the second average morality
Up to ten millions to 더 than sixty million
allocates to Donder incinerator
Did Mrs. Song will there be an emergency?
The Demon King is coming!
The lock-and-lock tower is closed.
We can't go back to the mortal world.
We're selling vegetables!
Wait for me!
Look at the new vegetables!
Look at the vegetables!
Look at the flowers!
Wait for me!
It turns out that this is how the world works.
It's so good!
It seems that I was so childish before.
Because I can use this sword to train.
I can cut off the demon and remove the demon.
I can go to the deep of the justice.
I can go to the unknown to kill.
I can become the great hero who is respected by the people.
But this world...
It's not like this at all.
Even if you're so good at martial arts,
you can't do anything in the future.
I know.
Don't think about it.
There are some things that can't be solved.
But there is one thing.
I know that he is right.
And I must do it.
We'll go to Mount Shu to save Ling'er.
Girl.
Don't say anything gross.
I must say it.
I'm with you.
So you said it.
Is it a word of a gentleman?
It's hard to catch up.
I heard that the eye-catching man is ill.
He seems to be recuperating.
But...
Are you serious?
Even the emperor's will is correct.
But it's not that big.
I'm not.
Did the man just tell you that it's true?
No way.
He is with Aqi and is not drunk.
He is still fine.
So, Cousin is near here.
Let's go see him.
OK.
Yunyi.
Yue Ru.
Is it really you?
This is cousin's mother, my aunt.
This is Li Xiaoyang.
And this is cousin's good friend.
Hello.
Yue Ru.
You came to Chang'an.
You didn't come to the mansion to see.
We actually passed by here.
But we heard cousin's illness.
Is it true?
Yes.
Since the nth family came back from Jinyuan,
I've been getting strange disease.
I've been treating the doctor.
Even the imperial doctor came.
It's not possible.
Now his illness is getting worse.
I can't help it.
I'll go to the medicine temple to pray for him.
Yunyi, don't worry.
I have the Purple Gold Fox.
I can send the message to Yongcheng.
Really?
Since we found the doctor, it's useless.
We can't do anything.
That's great.
Yue Ru, we'll go back now.
Let's go.
Follow me.
Cousin.
Sit down.
Qing.
Why are you like this?
I'm fine.
You said you're fine.
You don't know how worried Yunyi is.
We heard a lot of people saying...
I just changed my mind.
I'm afraid that people will be mad at me.
Look.
I'm so confused.
I invited everyone here.
I'm a happy person.
You're kidding me.
I'd rather not come here.
But I want to know that Cousin is safe and sound.
Cousin, why are you getting more and more worried?
I'm really fine.
Husband.
The medicine is ready.
Hurry up.
You're married?
He's my wife.
Cai Yi.
Cousin, when did you get married?
I didn't mention it to you last time.
That's right.
I didn't even tell my master that I got married.
It's a big deal.
Please excuse me.
I got married a few days ago.
I didn't tell you.
Don't be so sad.
How did you know my cousin?
I should tell you.
You should ask the servants to make some good dishes.
I'll make a toast to my best friends.
Husband.
You should drink this medicine first.
By the way, where's Miss Ling'er?
Why didn't she come with you?
Chang'an has a lot of fun places.
I'll take you to have fun.
How are you?
After you left,
the people from Moon Sect came.
Master Shi.
He sacrificed himself to save us.
Such a good man.
Where's Miss Ling'er?
She was taken away by the chief of Mount Zu.
Why?
We don't know where Xiaoyao and I are going.
Don't worry.
Mount Zu is a famous place.
The chief is very famous.
I believe Miss Ling'er is safe.
I'm relieved.
Qi.
You're the one who's worried about Master.
It's great that you can stay here.
You're here and I'm coming.
Why are you still standing here?
Go cook.
Husband, it's almost cold.
Drink it first.
Get out.
What's wrong?
I'm worried about you.
I'm fine.
Did you hear that?
I know.
You're doing well.
Miss Tu Di.
I'm hungry.
Go cook.
I'll be back.
The doctor gets up early every morning.
I make medicine for Jingyuan.
She's the most likely to sleep at night.
Qi.
Jingyuan is so lucky.
She's called Saivong.
She's a good cook.
Who's Ma?
You.
That's right.
I'm much better than you.
Aunt Yun, how did you know him?
I didn't know.
I was lucky to go to the toilet.
Cai Yi is a poor child.
About a month ago,
his parents and he went to Chang'an.
But one day,
his parents suddenly got sick and died.
He was unwell.
He was buried on the street.
His parents died.
I was passing by.
I saw him poor.
So I took him back to the mansion.
I didn't expect this child to be so smart.
After he got married,
he made a few shots of the family's ancestral medicine for Jingyuan.
I didn't expect Jingyuan to eat it.
But he's so healthy.
I saw Cai Yi
sincere to Jingyuan.
He took her back to our family.
Even if he's happy for Jingyuan,
he's not like me.
I'm sorry.
But Jingyuan is not like you.
She's been making trouble for this.
She's like this.
She's always been a good help.
It's all my fault.
She's always angry.
During this time,
her illness
is not good.
Aunt Yun, don't do this.
Don't do this.
After so many years,
all the grudges and sorrows are false.
People's health is the most important thing.
I only hope
Jingyuan can be safe
and live a happy life.
Don't worry.
Since he's good to others,
he'll be good to others.
You said
Cai Yi came to our family.
Could it be
Jingyuan's kindness?
I'm sure it's Aunt Yun.
With her,
we can't use the golden gulud.
What? You want to leave?
We have to hurry.
Yue Ru,
I'm the only one
who can talk to you.
During this time,
you've been out there.
You've been suffering a lot.
Stay here for a few days.
Aunt Yun will cook you something delicious.
Okay.
But we still have to hurry.
Our family has raised more than ten horses.
You can rest here.
When you're well-groomed,
you can ride the horse.
I'll take care of it.
Then it's a deal.
But...
Can't you always
be my sacrifice?
I'll do it too.
And
Jingyuan is my good disciple.
He's my good friend.
Good.
Yue Ru,
you can sleep with me tonight.
We can talk.
Help.
Tang Yu Xiaobao, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Look.
The moonlight is so beautiful.
You're in a good mood.
You're making me mad.
Let's be quiet
so we can think of a way.
I...
I'm only thinking of one thing.
Forget it.
I'm not talking.
What's wrong?
Save your mouth for a while.
I'm thirsty.
I think you should cry.
Is it okay?
You can just
leave your eyes and mouth.
Then you can be free.
You want me to cry?
It's even harder
to leave here.
I'll tell you a story.
You might be crying.
No need, Tang Yu Xiaobao.
From the beginning...
Tang Yu Xiaobao.
From the beginning,
three people went on the road together.
They were going to a far, far away place.
They divided everything
into three small and medium-sized packages.
When the first person passed by,
he chose the biggest and heaviest package.
The other two people were smiling.
Silly.
But when I saw you on the road,
I was so tired.
Okay, stop talking about it, Tang Yu Xiaobao.
But it's weird.
The package of that silly man
was getting lighter and lighter.
And the package of the other two people
was getting heavier and heavier.
Do you know why?
Because
the package of the two people
were getting heavier and heavier.
And that silly man
must have been your good friend.
He was packing the things
and the food.
The more he ate, the lighter he was.
The less he was packing,
the more he was carrying the food.
The more he was carrying,
the less he was carrying.
The more he was carrying the food,
the less he was carrying the food.
How is it?
It's funny.
It's not.
It's okay. I'll talk about it again.
Chongqing.
Tang Yu Xiaobao.
I know you miss your master very much now.
Don't say you anymore.
Even I...
I really miss her.
I haven't known my tears for a long time.
My tears...
are very bitter.
Very bitter.
I'm so sorry.
Look, there's water.
Find Missbox.
Needed festival
I'm not afraid of you.
I really don't want to understand.
I finally understand.
I should let go.
Don't say anything.
I don't want to know.
I know that I still have
a beautiful dream.
Don't say anything.
I really don't want to know.