I'm not afraid of you.
I love you.
I want to meet you.
In my heart,
I can't compare with you.
We have been through the heavy world together.
We have seen the rich and beautiful world.
We have been together for a long time.
The world has changed because of us.
We have become more and more united.
I give it to you.
Let's go.
We have been through the ups and downs.
He didn't let go of my hand.
We have been holding each other.
We have walked every new and exciting path.
I started to believe that
we will be together.
The world is full of sea and sea.
It's not the same as before.
It's already in our hearts.
I'm leaving.
Why?
Go back to your place.
You can't go back.
Here.
It's your home.
Sorry.
No.
It's not me.
I belong to you.
Marry me.
But I've already engaged to someone else.
What will happen then?
Do you know that?
I want to be someone else's wife.
He is the national emperor of the Nanzhao State.
I don't care.
I know I love you.
You love me.
No.
I can't love you.
I don't care.
I can't love anyone else.
This is not what I promised.
You promised to give them happiness.
But what about you?
You don't want to give yourself happiness?
What's the promise?
Because he...
You want to betray your destiny.
You want to betray the person you love.
You want to betray your heart.
But this is a trap.
I don't care.
I don't want you to leave me.
I want to be someone else's wife.
I want to be someone else's love.
You are so beautiful.
We can finally be together.
I can just flash through air.
Fly in the dark with the power of all theadtion
Party
who are you
Old people's home.
What is this place?
I want to see my heart.
Everything will be fine tomorrow.
It's impossible.
It's my life's pursuit of true love.
If you want to pursue, you have to get it.
That's true love.
If you don't understand,
you will naturally think you haven't entered the Tao.
Tomorrow is your real time.
You will understand everything.
Old people's home.
Who is this old man's home?
What is going on tomorrow?
How is this the Tao of my life?
What's wrong with you?
I don't know. I don't know.
Ruozhuang. Ruozhuang.
I want to go back.
или
Jing'er.
I don't want anyone to leave me behind.
Will you take me to see her?
Did you hear me? She can't hide from me.
If I can't see her, I won't leave.
Sorry.
I won't leave you anymore.
I love you.
Let her go. I don't care, I don't care.
I'm not leaving.
We'll be together forever.
I won't let you suffer again.
Where are you going?
I'm going to find Brother Ruozhuo.
I'm going to...
You're muddleheaded.
You're not a Ruozhuo.
Sorry.
I'm Mo Yixi.
How could this happen?
How could I know?
You asked me, I didn't know.
Take me to see him, okay?
I'm sorry.
I'm Mo Yixi.
Why?
How could I know?
You asked me, I didn't know.
Take me to see him, okay?
I'll go by myself.
I'll take you there.
Why?
Is love a blessing?
Brother Ruozhuo.
Qu Zequan, Wang Zechi, Ma Zeying, Bi Zexin, Shao Ze De, Du Ze Huo.
Qu Ze...
Why?
Why did you come here?
I came here just to ask for a reason.
Get lost!
I can forgive you for everything.
I can forgive you for calling me a fool.
I can forgive you for being a fool and not saying goodbye.
I can forgive you for giving up on me and running back to Mount Shu.
But I can't forgive you for being a fool.
I just didn't give me a good reason at this moment.
Tell me, why?
I...
I just want to ask for a reason.
I want to be with you.
Because only then can I have the love of the world.
I can have the love of the seven emotions.
I want to have it on purpose.
Because only then can I let go.
If your feelings are not true,
then you never had it.
You have no ability.
You have no right to let go.
Do you love me?
I know you love me.
I can feel it.
Come with me.
We will be together forever.
Stop talking.
Come back to me.
Brother Ruo Zhe.
Don't tempt me again.
What is it?
Why did you get it?
Brother Yi Xi, I beg you.
Please help him.
He is choosing the coffin.
Put it down.
He will be here.
Anyway, he will come to me.
No.
How can we help him?
We can save him.
But he is the only one.
Why do I have to have it?
If I don't have the power to have it,
then I don't have to let go.
If I don't let go,
then I don't have the will to let go.
I have the power, the wealth, the power, the fame, the love.
I have all of these.
How wonderful it feels.
No.
I can't.
I don't want to go back.
I can't let go.
I can't go back.
I don't want to let go of all these.
I don't want to go back to the old me.
I don't want to be greedy.
Brother Zun Zun, don't.
We are the people of the world.
We are in the human world.
We have the seven emotions and six desires.
What is wrong?
Why do you have to get it?
Pours?
Who are you?
Robotjen
They are...
They are!
슬Eu
I've got it
That's the real essence of getting water up
Brother Ruozhou, you...
Jing'er, I love you.
Come on.
Can I?
Jing'er, close your eyes and feel everything around you.
Brother Ruozhou, I love you.
I feel that every kind of things in the Four Seasons are their breathing and their lives.
This is your grace.
Because you are the mother of the land, and you are the descendant of the female frog.
You already know that, right?
Brother Ruozhou, you are so kind.
I'm not afraid of you.
I'm the descendant of the female frog.
You already know that?
I already knew that when I first met you.
Am I very kind?
No.
You just don't have a real right to look at you.
My right?
You and I know that it's not a common right.
So your love for me is also a common love.
It's a great love, but not a small one.
Just like what you feel,
the plants and animals in the human world have their lives.
They all need love.
So your love for me is not to stay on the love of my children,
but to all the attention and love of all life.
Protecting them, giving them a good life, is your right.
It's hard to leave when the female frog knows it's bitter.
But as long as you see the things that are there,
the bitter and heavy life is worth it.
I understand.
Brother Ruozhou, I love you.
Just like all the things in my world.
Although I saw you,
I don't understand anything.
I don't want to understand.
I'm too much in love with people.
How can I do that?
They all found their way out.
I'm getting deeper and deeper.
I can't tell if I'm a weakling or a demon.
I'm still a woman.
I can't let go of my feelings for Qing'er.
But I always don't want to.
I still have to send Qing'er back to Nanzhao.
After we were separated,
Qing'er would never be pregnant as I already said.
Looks like they don't even need her anymore.
I had high fears...
since the time you went out with Qing'er.
They gave me hope and lead me back.
As long as we find the other half's owner,
they will be blessed and will cry for their lives.
Just like us.
Brother Yi Xi, I think you misunderstood.
No.
And this curse will indeed be with us.
Maybe I was burned at one moment.
But after this failure, I have already become another person.
Now, I am no longer pursuing these things.
There is more important thing waiting for me to do.
Qing Yuan, that mission is too heavy.
Let them leave together.
Let's go far away to find our place.
That is my mission.
My path.
I will do my best.
I will give this to you.
I wish you find someone you love.
At this moment, I am also a person of life.
I just want to continue this feeling.
I don't want to be able to do it.
Let's go with me.
I don't care if it's a hallucination or anything else.
I just don't want you to go back.
Why are you so stubborn?
I am not happy.
Don't you understand now?
You haven't woken up yet?
You are the one who doesn't understand.
You said it in a deep voice.
You know the real meaning of life.
You know the meaning of life.
Why are you back?
Why do you have to repeat the emperor's pregnancy?
Didn't you say that you have been in love with people?
You are lying.
That is my path.
You won't understand what I am saying now.
I just hope that you don't think about it.
You should know clearly that there is nothing between us.
We have never loved each other.
Remember, you are Mo Yixi.
You are Mo Yixi.
Yes, I know.
You don't have to say it again.
Okay.
I will tell you the identity of an outsider.
If...
If the emperor knows you are not loyal to him,
what will you do?
What will you do?
You will be dead.
If that is the case, I will face it.
I am destined to be able to go.
Go.
What?
The bad guys from Shoushan said that I have nothing to say.
But you are a young man.
What are you saying?
Don't you understand?
I am not going to face the emperor.
I am not going to be single and accept his love.
I just hope that you don't think about me with the idea of an outsider.
Yes, I am an outsider.
I really don't understand.
But...
In my world,
people should have love and hatred.
Qing, come with me.
He left.
What is the knife?
You are the knife.
Your Majesty, can you tell me a story?
Okay, tell me.
I took the knife from your hand to replace the knife.
We heard aorts stories about the young man.
I am not going to kill you.
I will think about it.
I will never stop.
You...
It must be a very beautiful story.
I've never felt that way before.
I know that...
I've always felt the best feeling in this world.
It's a pity that I can't bring this feeling to you.
I'm sorry.
Why should I say sorry?
I've given up on you in this world.
It's okay.
You'll come back eventually. You didn't give up.
I believe that you didn't abandon me at the last moment.
Don't you mind?
I mind.
I can't let you be happy in the future.
Do you know that I've been waiting for you?
Even if you refuse me now, I'll still wait for you.
The Queen of Nanzhao State only has you.
I used to think of you as a little person.
I won't forgive myself for being selfish.
I forgive you for coming back to me?
Actually, I've decided to shoulder my own fate.
I won't forget the day I promised you.
I'll do anything for the country and the country.
Even if you're not with me now, I'll still walk on.
You left me for a while.
I realized that if there's a common ideal and a common goal,
you can leave together.
It's a happy thing.
Qing, you're the one I'm destined to be.
But if I don't have the right, I won't force you.
How can you do that?
This is my best decision in my life.
Be my wife and the Queen.
Stay with me and bring happiness to the world.
Okay?
I object!
Get out!
How dare you!
You're confused, Brother Xi.
I object!
Stop!
You're my guest.
You're impolite.
Master Shi.
You may leave.
Chief, Qing and I will have a long life.
We'll have a long life.
We'll have to practice together.
I won't pursue this matter today.
I'll be the chief of the sect.
I'll take care of the wedding.
I'll leave you forever.
I'll be the Queen of the south.
Don't ask why.
Love is the blessing.
You'll become a despicable person.
You'll lose your life.
Love.
I'm the first time I drink with you.
It feels so good.
It's my first time.
I give it all to you.
We met in our dreams.
It's over in my dreams.
It's perfect.
I love you.
I like you.
Chief.
Chief, what's the matter?
Why do you call me Chief?
Don't you call me Brother Yi Xi?
I like you.
Chief.
Liya.
Chief, please respect me.
I'm fine.
I'm leaving.
Chief.
It's the Empress who asked me to come to see you.
Don't be late.
She asked me to remind you again.
You're not Ying Ruo Zhuo, not the Chief of Sword City.
You're Mo Yi Xi, the Chief of the City.
Liya.
It's okay.
I'm not worried.
How would the Saintess of the Sacred Realm know the love of the people?
Forget it.
You're right.
I've never tried it.
But I know what's going on.
You...
You know?
They're so hungry.
Eat something and wake up.
Everyoneون,
I'm here with you.
I enjoy coming on time.
com on time.
Yan knitting
Pe bullets
You're still dare to say that you know what happened
You are against the characteristics of female
I'm not Mo Yixing!
I'm Du Gujianxian!
I'm Ying Ruozhuo.
I'm Ying Ruozhuo!
I'm not Mo Yixing.
I'm the one you love!
I'm Wu!
Sir!
Wait!
I'm not Mo Yixing.
I'm not...
What is this place?
Sir!
Don't call me that!
Don't call me that.
I'm not Ying Ruozhuo.
Fine.
Don't do this.
Don't leave me.
Stay with me.
Don't do this.
Don't reject me.
Don't leave me.
I'm not Ying Ruozhuo.
I love you.
Don't leave me.
Fine?
Qing'er.
Yixi.
Don't make trouble.
Look carefully. I'm Yuanqing.
I'm the real her.
This is the real feeling.
No problem.
If yixi said no to my wind.
So I can see how feelings is.
But only what they can fill up the head again.
I certainly can think it's alright.
No business to look into.
I have plans and we can do whatever you want.
I...I...
How could I do this?
I...
I'm so bad at this.
I was trapped for 18 years by these unbearable reasons.
In addition to escaping, I couldn't find the way out.
I didn't expect that this secret that I buried in my heart
would still be in the past.
You wretch! You still keep talking!
That night,
she took my bones and gave birth to them.
Get out of here!
Anu is now so old.
She should know the truth.
Get out!
Say it again. I won't kill you!
I know that I owe you too much.
So you hit me with a few punches.
But I won't let her say it out loud.
I won't let her do it.
Enough! Stop arguing!
I beg you.
If you continue like this,
I'll make an excuse.
Please tell me the truth.
Do it.
Yes,
I'm your mother.
I was naive and though she'd come back,
I knew that he would accept a true person.
But then I realized that I had to accept the true person.
You grew up in the mansion.
This secret has reached the point where it cannot be solved.
If I continue to do it, it will only become a ugly thing.
I once thought that I don't want it.
But I can't do it.
Shi Sanwei has overcome all the pain for me.
He would rather talk behind my back and protect me all the time.
He would raise me up.
And I can only be a strict master in the growing of Anu.
Anu!