Here's the Americano you ordered.
Enjoy.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
HAN EUN-JI SENT YOU A VIDEO
HAN EUN-JI:
JUN-HUI, IS THIS YOU? OH MY GOD...
WHO ARE YOU TALKING TO?
ARE YOU IGNORING ME?
REPORTING ME WON'T GET RID OF THE VIDEOS
IT'S OVER FOR YOU, YOU SLUT
Sorry.
We've closed for the day.
I'll give you your order to go.
Sorry.
I think
you dropped these earlier.
They aren't mine.
I'll leave them here
since I found them here.
SOCIAL
SEX
SECRET
SEX LINE
S LINE
RED LINES THAT CONNECT SEXUAL PARTNERS
I'm late, aren't I?
Is something wrong?
Oh, I almost forgot.
Happy birthday.
It's before midnight, but still.
I was going to throw you an awesome party.
I want to...
ask you a favor.
What is it?
You can say no if you want.
I'm not sure
if this is okay.
I don't want to push you into anything.
I just...
If I were ever to be with someone,
I wanted it to be you.
I have a question.
What is it?
Do you like me?
Yes.
Oh, no.
I don't have... that.
You mean this?
It's amazing.
It is.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Are you hungry?
Should we get something to eat?
Sure.
Except the last bus home
is going to be here soon.
Well...
Wait here for a minute.
Okay.
I've always thought of myself
as a cursed child.
A kid who let her parents die.
I wanted to change.
But...
I couldn't.
I'm cursed.
Anyone close to me
will die.
UNKNOWN NUMBER
HAPPY SEVENTEENTH BIRTHDAY!
YOU ARE INVITED TO THE ROOM OF BOUNDARIES.
Detective...
I need your help.
Did you really not know
about Seon-a's S line?
If I had known,
I would have told you.
I always get
a birthday card
on my birthday.
There's no one to send me one.
I thought it was my mom at first,
but then I realized
someone was counting down the days
until my birthday.
Someday, I would be required
to do something.
And...
I think today is that day.
HAPPY SEVENTEENTH BIRTHDAY!
YOU ARE INVITED TO THE ROOM OF BOUNDARIES.
They lured you to the school,
gave me these glasses,
and Seon-a...
You're saying it's the same person?
A HAPPY AND WISE SCHOOL LIFE FOR EVERYONE
Will there be anyone at school
so late at night?
I ran a background check
on your homeroom teacher,
but nothing came up.
Lee Gyu-jin doesn't exist.
Going to the school premises
and looking for--
Detective, over there!
Hey, Sunglasses!
I almost died.
What happened? Who did this?
You told me to come to school.
But I can't remember after that...
Did something happen to you?
No time for that.
What?
We need to get out of here.
I came with Detective Han.
Detective.
Detective!
Come on.
What the hell?
Wait, didn't we just come downstairs?
Christ. Let's go.
What's happening?
Why are we still on the same floor?
Help us!
I think
we're trapped in here.
Trapped?
What do you mean?
NO ENTRY
The roof.
What?
There's nobody here.
Hello?
Anyone here?
The fact I met her
was a stroke of sheer luck.
I think
you dropped these earlier.
Did you give me these on purpose?
How do you feel right now?
What?
Do you still want to die?
Or...
Do you want to kill?
I don't understand.
The lines above people's heads.
You know what they mean, don't you?
Don't you want to get rid of them?
The red lines.
Others will be able to see
the world you see with these glasses.
It won't be long.
And no one will need glasses.
Aren't you excited to find out
what people will do
when that day comes?
For some,
it'll be a conspicuous weak point,
and others will try to use that.
Which is why
I came
to help you, Jun-hui.
After that,
I found a new purpose in life.
I am now ready
to sever my last sin from myself.
On the day the world turns red,
we will all
be born again!
Please...
I'm sorry.
Don't do this.
You know how much I love...
Gyeong-jin.
There's something I haven't told you.
I could see strange things
ever since I was little.
Are you calling this...
strange?
I think it's awesome.
Where did you get those?
- Take them off--
- No.
By the way...
I heard S lines will be visible
even without glasses if you die.
Is it true?
What?
That's what our homeroom teacher said.
Our homeroom teacher?
Lee Gyu-jin.
Father.
Don't you want to save Seon-a?
No!
Put the knife down.
I said, put it down!
Detective.
How was the world with the glasses on?
Wasn't it beautiful?
It won't be long
until the whole world is bathed in red.
Regular human beings cannot kill me.
Was it you
that pushed Seon-a off the roof?
If Seon-a weren't at the hospital,
would you have even cared
to give her a glance?
I gave you an opportunity.
Die!
No!
Where am I?
Your face...
Why have your eyes changed color?
Stop it!
Why are you doing this?
Haven't you always wondered
why you were able to see
the red lines from birth?
It was all for today, Hyeon-heup.
You're not cursed,
but a present and blessing.
That's a lie.
People killing each other,
having my friends and family die...
Knowing what I've been through,
how can you say
seeing S lines is a blessing?
People want to know.
Don't you get it, Hyeon-heup?
S lines.
Can't you feel the desire
of the people who are craving to see them?
I'm a mere mouthpiece for their longing.
Mom...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry...
I'm so late.
I had...
the glasses too.
- Hey, you're here.
- Hey.
Have you eaten?
What's wrong, honey?
Hyeon-heup...
it's not your fault.
You!
Your death
will bring to mankind
the blessed eyes of God.
You're too late.
I've already
proven the reason for your existence.
The two of us
have finished what we're here to do.
- What's going on?
- What's happening?
My glasses.
Hyeon-heup.
Are you all right?
Let's get out of here.
Detective.
Let's go and see Seon-a.
It's awesome.
Cool.
The sky's turned red.
Look above his head!
Get it off me!
- What the hell?
- Look!
Look, your head!
- Do I have them too?
- A lot.
- What?
- Look.
What is that?
What are they?
Someday,
everyone will see the world as you do.
A world where everyone can see S lines.
I finally got to be what I wanted.
A regular human being.
The world was in a state
of massive chaos for almost a year.
People tried to figure out
why S lines suddenly appeared,
but no one could find the answer.
GOOD LUCK ON THE NEXT CHAPTER OF YOUR LIFE
Seon-a eventually awoke from her coma.
In a world full of S lines,
she was reborn without one.
See you.
Seon-a and Detective Han
didn't ask each other any questions.
They were just relieved
at the fact that each other was alive.
I told you not to come.
What do you want for lunch?
Nothing.
It's embarrassing to eat with you.
What are you talking about?
Just look above your own head.
Didn't you see everyone?
They're all staring at you.
And as for me...
I was on my own again.
YOO JUN-SEON
Hyeon-heup.