ALL PLACES, INCIDENTS AND NAMES
IN THIS DRAMA ARE A WORK OF FICTION
Your skull's going to be quite sore today,
Hip Hop Girl.
Stop right there, you sinners!
You should go back.
-Sir.
-Don't you know your place?
You said you would do anything
that I ask you to do perfectly.
You don't know
what I'm going to ask you.
Know your place
and know who you are.
You must do your duty
before you ask for anything.
Don't you think?
I'll correct myself.
I apologize.
I'll go back to Yeongwol.
CHIEF PROSECUTOR
KANG SEOK TAE
Yes, Ms. Jeong.
What?
This just in.
In front of a food service company
that produced bad food,
the CEO is handing over a money envelope.
The chief of the hygiene department
takes the envelope
puts it in his inside pocket
with a smile on his face.
It's the same
with other employees of the department.
DON'T KEEP RECORDS OF PRO-JAPANESE
Furthermore, the food service company
hired gangsters and used force
on police officers
and a priest who helped them.
Collusion between the hygiene department
and the food service company
and loose administration.
Today, I saw the true picture
of Gudam District,
the district chosen as the most
well-governed and clean district.
I'm Reporter Oh Bo-yeong of UBS News.
Hwang Cheol-beom, what's your problem?
I told you many times to change your ways.
The priest already planned it
before he came.
It couldn't be talked over.
Do you still let the goofy thugs
take care of important deals?
It should've been either you or Mr. Kim
who handled the situation!
Fine! I made a mistake.
I made a huge mistake.
No.
I don't want your lame excuses anymore.
You made a mistake with Father Lee
and one mistake is enough.
You know what I mean?
-Oops, I'm sorry.
-It's all over.
-It's finished.
-Okay.
Are you okay?
You seemed to get beaten up badly.
Considering we had fewer people,
this isn't that bad.
Thanks for earlier.
Earlier?
It's the least I can do for you.
By the way, is your head okay?
I guess you didn't know
that my head is twice as thick
as others' heads.
I'm basically wearing
a thin bulletproof helmet.
I could feel that you were my senior
for the first time
since I started working here.
So you haven't felt that way until now.
How can I put it?
You looked spirited
and your eyes were sparkling.
My eyes are always shiny.
I think hanging out with Father Kim
has changed you.
What are you talking about?
You know what he's like.
How could you say that?
I'm a saint for putting up with him.
By the way,
isn't Father Kim like a detective?
He knows everything about our work.
You're right.
He does know more than he should.
Did you get hurt too, Father?
I didn't get hurt at all.
I came to see Detective Seo.
-Detective Seo, are you okay?
-Yes, I'm fine.
Father, your hand...
It's okay.
Are you okay?
Of course. This is nothing.
We're perpetrators.
-Victims.
-We're victims.
We were just walking by
and a man in dark clothes
suddenly showed up,
kicked him,
and hit his head.
What kind of a police office does that?
Look at what happened to my face.
Listen to me.
I didn't know it was a bribe
when I received it.
I thought it was a letter.
-How does that make sense to you?
-Why would I--
How is this a bribe?
Detective Gu, we just felt bad
that we troubled him to come.
He's right.
So, we just wanted to make sure
he can have some bibimbap.
-He's right.
-Silence!
Salute.
Why is it so unorderly here?
You can't just blindly bring
all of them here.
Well, they were all caught in the act,
so we had to arrest every one of them.
Nonsense.
Don't waste your time requesting warrants
and let them go on a warning--
Who said you could do that?
What do you mean by who said it?
I said it.
I'm the chief of this police station.
Wait. I think I'm hearing something
from up above.
I'm hearing something from up above.
Wait a second.
I hear something from up above.
God just told me you should shut up.
What?
Who do you think you are to shut me up?
It's not what I said.
It's what I heard from up above.
I'm only delivering the message.
You...
-Are you kidding me?
-Hey!
You. You thought it was a letter?
Are you dating each other?
Were you excited to receive
a heartfelt letter?
Is that why you smiled?
Do you want my heartful message too?
Father.
Why did you pick the metal one, of all?
We have plenty of plastic rulers here.
Metal ones make the best whip.
And you.
Does your bibimbap has
truffles and caviar in it?
You'll be hit by the edge.
Father.
I'll take care of him.
You deal with the man with bobbed hair.
Bobbed hair?
You punk.
I'm not just a man in dark clothes.
I'm called a priest.
-You're so dead--
-Shut up.
How can they be so shameless
when we have hard evidence here?
See?
Right, Chief Nam?
I'm about to have a stroke. Press here.
Yes, sir.
-Where are you going?
-To the district office.
That's where the fire is.
I'm going to go watch the fire.
Are you sure you're not going there
to make things worse?
"The Lord rained on Sodom and Gomorrah
sulfur and fire."
Genesis, chapter 19, verse 24.
Sulfur and fire?
Gosh. But I have a lot to do inside.
What does he mean by sulfur and fire?
-Avoiding us won't solve anything!
-It indeed won't!
-Let us in!
-You must let us in!
You can't just...
All the evidence they have
is just some cash
and the video clip of the scene.
That's true,
but you must not make any move now.
-Let's see how it goes and--
-No.
Even if we give more time to the press,
they will only exaggerate things.
I will take actions now.
No, don't. You must not.
They might have another card--
I'm putting my foot down on this case.
A transparent investigation.
A fair investigation.
I can promise you that.
Were you not aware
of the organized and chronic crime
that has been committed
by the hygiene department?
The result of the investigation will tell
whether it's an organized
and chronic crime or a one-time crime.
Please refrain from writing
any articles until then.
And I was unaware of this incident.
If it turns out to be
an organized and chronic crime,
what will you do?
I will disassemble the hygiene department
and make a more transparent
administrative system.
Goodness.
Is that it?
I mean, you're the director
of the district.
And yet are you putting all the blame
on the employees and the system?
GUDAM CATHEDRAL
Are you sure nothing is on you?
Father, with what right
are you asking that question?
Me?
With the right
of Gudam District's citizen.
Why? I can't?
Good.
What should I do to make you feel better?
That is
what you should decide.
But if I have to tell you something,
I believe what you need
to take responsibility for is
not your intention, but your action.
Well, if you think it's so unfair
that you take the responsibility,
then say it's on the employees.
Just because you managed to avoid
your responsibility today
doesn't mean you can do the same tomorrow.
I will correct myself.
It's happening.
-If it turns out
-It's happening.
to be organized and chronic crime,
I, Jeong Dong-ja,
will resign from the position
of the director of the district.
PRESS CONFERENCE:
HYGIENE DEPARTMENT'S BRIBERY
Is it
an unofficial announcement?
Ma'am, you should stop the conference--
This is an official announcement.
It's official.
There she goes.
She's shooting herself in the foot.
Make sure to keep your promise.
I'm telling you now.
Then be ready
to step down from your position.
PRESS CONFERENCE:
HYGIENE DEPARTMENT'S BRIBERY
This is the evidence of the crime
the hygiene department committed.
This is the copy of the secret ledger
that recorded all the bribes
that Wangmat Food gave
to the hygiene department
for the last three years.
For your information,
this is one-tenth of the original copy.
Why do you have that?
Is it certainly legitimate?
Do you think I, a priest,
would bring a fake document?
And I'm planning
on sending the original copy
to the Audit Committee
of Seoul City Hall myself.
And one more thing.
This is my present
for the reporters.
Okay.
This is why you shouldn't act imprudently.
Drinking during the daytime is...
Why is it still in the middle of the day?
So I didn't drink during the daytime then.
I drank in the morning.
I'm drunk.
Those damn thieves.
Where to?
It is said
that even a local priest lent a hand
with the disclosure of the corruption
of Gudam's hygiene department
and played a major role
in arresting the criminals.
-Where are you going?
-Wait.
As Gudam District and its director
was known for their integrity,
it is expected that this incident
will greatly shock the residents.
I'm Reporter Jin Jeong-nam of RBS News.
Thanks for the news.
Have a nice day, sir.
I checked on that person you asked about.
It means he's not just any person.
He could be a North Korean
under protection,
or he could've worked with us.
Or maybe someone
who can't reveal his identity.
This is exactly what I needed.
Chief Kang won't say no to this.
You scored big-time.
You're so good at driving others nuts.
I didn't drive her nuts.
It was the Lord's will
to enlighten her on her arrogance.
By the way, how did you get
the secret ledger
of Wangmat Food?
Then how about we work together?
There's something
you have to listen to.
Then where should we...
What about there?
You know, there is an old door
inside the warehouse.
We should hide the ledger there.
We need to find a door.
An old door.
That's it, Songsak. Bring it.
-You go.
-No, you go get it.
-Just go get it!
-Go!
-You go!
Come on. Just do it.
Yo-han and Songsak?
Goodness.
-I know you knew about it too.
-I did?
No, I didn't.
You seemed to notice it right away
when you saw Yo-han.
You pretended you needed to poop
to tip-off Hwang Cheol-beom.
No, I didn't. Why would I?
Goodness, this is upsetting.
I didn't let you go,
and you were all jittery.
If you really needed to poop,
you would have done it on the rooftop.
I'm very picky about
where I sleep and where I poop.
I don't poop anywhere.
This morning, you pretended
you had to poop so you could tip-off
Hwang Cheol-beom, right?
Goodness.
That's...
That's just an unfounded blame.
Gosh, I'm speechless.
If you didn't help Detective Seo today,
I would have killed you.
A moment of good deed saved your life.
Understand?
Why is poop always your excuse though?
But...
He doesn't let me explain.
This is just unfair.
That's not true.
I want you to find out
who took the ledger by the end of the day.
Yes, sir.
One after another, it's getting
worse and worse. This is great.
I have important information.
What? The priest is?
-Are you sure?
-Yes, sir.
It's from the NIS.
So you're saying he's someone
who has to keep his identity secret.
Yes, sir.
He might be an undercover trying
to pry into Gudam District's affairs.
Now it adds up.
I knew there must be something fishy
about that priest.
And about the Pope thing.
Unless some sort of power was involved,
you can't deliver your message
all the way to Vatican City.
That's what I'm talking about.
Prosecutor Park, you proved yourself.
Forget about all this
and come back to our office right now.
What are you waiting for? Hurry.
Why do you bug me so much?
There's something I must tell you.
I need to go out now. You have one minute.
About Father Kim Hae-il.
-What about him?
-He...
I mean...
about what he did today.
That thing about Wangmat Food
and the resignation
of the district director.
What about it?
I can solve it.
You can?
-How?
-Well...
"Wars and paintings must be seen
from a distance."
There's a saying.
So I saw it from a distance and...
You saw it from a distance and?
May I have a glass of water
before I tell you?
I'll give you one last chance.
Push it through as your plan.
Yes, sir.
I guess your time in Yeongwol did help.
You've become a lot more driven.
Thank you, sir.
-Let's talk later.
-Yes, sir.
Bye, sir.
This isn't what I imagined.
Darn it.
You can greet me later.
Bring me everything
on the Wangmat Food case.
-Okay.
Detective Seo. The warrant?
It's expected to be issued
by this evening, sir.
It was really cool
how you finished the district director.
All thanks to Yo-han and Songsak.
Wait a second.
Since when have the two of you
become so close?
Since we arrested those punks.
And of course, we should be close.
He's my teacher.
Teacher? Teacher of what?
Do you want to be a priest too?
Well, he's my teacher in many ways.
Goodness. What about me then?
Am I just a wooden stick to you?
I'll go send the secret ledger
to Seoul City Hall.
Do you want me to come?
-I'll go alone.
-Take care.
Bye.
What's with the chuckling?
What was that chuckling about?
I chuckled again today
I chuckled
It all started with rotten food.
That's right, ma'am.
One thing led to another,
and the district director is resigning.
Gosh, Father Kim Tsunami is
more persistent than he needs to be.
Whom I feel really bad for
is the girl in the hospital.
Those who play with food
have to be all murdered.
Why don't we just hire a killer
and murder all of them then?
I'm sorry. I was reminded of my daughter.
Bring the head and the employees
of the hygiene department,
the representatives of the sick girl,
the lawyer, and the CEO of Wangmat Food,
to Gudam Police Station.
And bring a reporter
who is good at storytelling too.
-Now.
-Yes, ma'am.
Father!
Where's the ledger?
Right, here.
I couldn't see it. Hand it over.
Wait, Father.
I'll go to the city hall.
You will?
I'll finish this.
I'm the one who took it and copied it.
Are you sure?
I think doing this
makes my heart pound like this.
I feel like I did something brave.
I know it's like that.
You feel scared but very proud.
-Good luck then.
-Yes, Father.
Brother Yo-han.
Why does it take so long
to issue the warrant?
I'm sure it'll be issued soon.
What do you want to eat?
Let's wait a bit.
I can't. I'm starving.
Let's have a big proper dinner.
It's on me.
Really?
Think about what you want to eat
until then.
"Restaurants nearby."
Let's see what's cheap and good.
I'll be right back.
Make sure to be quick.
If you come late, I won't buy dinner.
THE WARM-HEARTED AND TRUSTWORTHY POLICE IS
ALWAYS BY YOUR SIDE
What's with the reaction?
We were wondering
why you were so obsessed
with Wangmat Food.
We know it's about Eun-ji,
but we thought the investigation
on Father Lee had to be done first.
After all, bringing down the Goliath
was your master plan, Father.
The opponent needs to weaken down
for us to get the information we need.
I didn't know
you had such a great purpose.
You did a great job, Father.
It's not great.
You could have been in big trouble.
You should not beat up people too hard
or say curse words.
It will hurt you both physically
and mentally.
I heard you asked something to Father Han.
You asked him if I took a personality test
before I had become a priest.
Father.
Father?
I just said it as a joke.
You think it's funny?
Father.
Goodness.
By the way,
are we all settled
with Eun-ji's hospital bills now?
Yes. We can have it compensated
through trials.
Everything we have paid ourselves.
Thank you, dear my Lord.
Father Lee would have been
very happy to hear that.
Hang in there.
You'll be able to see your friends soon.
It doesn't hurt.
Take it easy, sir.
What did I tell you?
I told you
the district director and Mr. Hwang
would cause trouble someday.
I didn't expect this.
Why did she have to run
her mouth like that?
What if
someone from the opposite ruling party
gets elected after she resigns?
What will you do then?
Then there will be no more Savings Day.
Then we must make every effort
to keep her in her position.
Do we have to though?
-Pardon?
-It won't be bad
to have one of us take that position.
Right.
Let's ask Chief Kang as well.
How about
we keep this secret from Chief Kang?
As a matter of fact,
I think the same.
Why are you doing this?
I hate that look on your face.
But why...
Tell me who took Wangmat Food's ledger.
What?
I haven't been
this furious in a while.
Spill it out.
I don't know.
I asked the priest,
but he wouldn't tell me.
Move on to the next step.
I really don't know.
I gave you the information this morning.
I really don't know, sir!
I really don't!
Let me ask you again.
If you lie to me again,
you will become one with the scrap metal.
Like Transformers.
Now, who is it?
Who took the ledger?
I really don't know.
I really don't know! Help me!
It looks like he really doesn't know.
Let's go.
Well done.
Well done, Gu Dae-yeong.
I have no regrets.
Hwang Cheol-beom...
Give me the key, will you?
Be quiet.
Or order jjajangmyeon for me.
You know,
we're Hungry Gang
from South Chungcheong Province.
If the district director really resigns,
who's got our back?
We'll be doomed then.
She won't care about us
because she's leaving.
She will only take care of herself.
In the worst case,
let's disclose everything.
Let's tell the cops
that we just did what we were told to do.
SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT PROSECUTORS' OFFICE
Write the content, edit, and filter
just as I say.
Don't add anything unnecessary.
Just do as I say.
That damn reporter sounds all excited.
It looks like screenwriters are
not writing scenarios
but news articles these days.
Well, aren't we the same?
Why was the warrant denied?
I'm not sure, sir.
That's just how they noticed.
This is ridiculous.
JAIL
Release them.
You can all go home for now.
The hygiene department
and Mr. Ki should wait a bit.
-Why?
-Don't ask.
Hey, Hip Hop Girl.
Why are we releasing them?
Why is the warrant denied?
The prosecutor in charge is changed.
She's the prosecutor you know very well.
-Prosecutor Park Gyeong-seon?
-Yes.
I'll go home now.
But she just went to Yeongwol!
Why did she come back?
This is annoying.
Why are you so angry?
Of course, I am.
Every time I try to do something,
they play petty tricks.
Yes, Sister.
I'm not sure why the prosecutor
suddenly wants to meet me.
I think we should meet her
to see what she's up to.
I'm just nervous.
It shouldn't be anything bad, right?
Don't worry.
See you tomorrow at the police station.
What's wrong?
I guess Sister Park Gyeong-seon is
planning a counterattack.
Hello, Father.
I see that you've made a big mess.
You're not Kim Hae-il. You're Kim Tsunami.
You made it back.
You must have properly kneeled down.
Come on. Don't be so corny.
Who kneels down these days?
I know there will be very little chance,
but make sure to deal with the case
fair and square.
I swore in front of Lady Justice.
Fair and square. Equality and justice.
"Fair and square"? "Lady Justice"?
Are you sure it wasn't in front of a rock?
Why do you have so little faith in me?
Father, have faith.
-Faith.
- I do respect faith,
but what protects me is suspicions.
Now that I hear you attacking me
in a holy and gracious way,
I feel like I'm back for real.
Won't you say hi to me?
We haven't met in a while.
Hello, ma'am.
Mr. Lucky Man.
So your nose always looks like that.
I thought it got swollen
because you got punched on it then.
People from the hygiene department,
follow me.
I hate her.
I know you've been through a lot today,
so I'll make it quick.
-Give me the papers.
-Yes, ma'am.
Take the one with your name on it.
I'm sure you have a lot of complaints
toward the district office
and the director.
But public officers
shouldn't be emotional.
They've been paying your salary after all.
CCTV EVIDENCE
MASSAGE
ASSA KARAOKE
You wanted to just disclose everything
in the end, right?
"Whatever. Die you all!"
But you can't do that.
You must stay cool and responsible
until the end. Don't you think?
If you don't, you'll be charged
for what's written there.
Your wives, children, and parents
will find this pretty shocking.
If they find
you've been paying
for prostitution every month...
Now, we all agreed
that you take responsibility.
You guys are so cool.
If you're not insightful,
you should be informed at least.
And if you're not informed,
you should be intuitive at least.
And if you're not intuitive,
you should listen to other people!
I apologize, sir.
If you're so terribly sorry,
you should die.
You've been on a fast, so you're weak.
Save your energy.
We're dealing
with the district director's matter.
There will be good news soon.
She just announced that she would resign.
How could you smooth that over?
You'll see.
Even if she takes her words back,
there won't be big problems.
Just because of that one damn priest...
The priest! We must do something
about the priest!
We're not going to heaven anyway.
Let's just make him like Father Lee.
I think we should fix
our barn first.
We already lost our big cow.
Why would we fix the barn?
We need to fix it to bring another cow in.
Speaking of which, I'd like to suggest
that I become the leader
at least on the surface.
It's to make our bond stronger.
From now on, I want you to tell me
all the information you get
and the decisions you make.
Why all of a sudden?
And if we have to choose a leader,
why don't we vote...
Why?
Do you not like my idea?
Well, that's not what I mean.
I like the idea.
Well,
he is the one who knows
the best about us, after all.
Let's do it that way.
What?
Thank you.
Damn it.
Why did you have to make the rotten food?
Chairman Ki Hong-chan,
I want you to pay all the hospital bills
Eun-ji was charged until today
as well as the bills
she will be charged in the future.
But the trial hasn't even begun yet.
If you don't pay the hospital bills,
I will double your sentence for bribery.
Do you want me to triple it?
Fine. I'll pay.
And Sister, drop the suit,
write a memorandum, and get it notarized.
Promise that after you receive the payment
you won't bring up this anymore.
No, ma'am. I can't do that.
We will follow the procedure,
get the payment,
and have this company punished.
Sister.
They work with Lee and Park Law Firm.
Do you know it?
Of course. Even I know that.
If you want to follow the procedure,
it'll take at least two years
for you to be paid.
Who will pay
the hospital bills until then?
And even if you win the lawsuit,
you won't get all the money back.
Why? Because Lee and Park Law Firm
will do everything they can do
to cut down even a single penny.
You need to think carefully
what's best for Eun-ji.
What should we do?
I'll give you a couple minutes
so you two can discuss
and think carefully about it.
Hey, Mr. Yu.
You must be back from the Czech Republic.
I want you to look into a person
using your data.
Yes. His name is Kim Hae-il.
He's a priest in a catholic church.
Father.
Yes?
After everything we did today,
I hope it wasn't for nothing in the end.
Not this time. We have hard evidence.
But look at what's happening.
This is frustrating.
Why are you crying?
It's not because I'm sad.
I'm just so angry.
Those assholes.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I know this doesn't look nice.
It feels like I have a friend
who sincerely cares for me,
and it cheers me up.
You're embarrassing me.
I must have lost my mind.
Look at them.
Don't be so harsh on yourself.
Father, hold on a second.
Goodness.
Is she flirting with him?
If you're finished using it, give it back.
Let me wash it for you.
-Are you okay, sir?
-I'm okay.
Let me take you to the hospital.
I said I'm okay! Stop fussing about it!
I'm sorry, sir.
We found who took
the ledger.
What?
We had no clue because there were
no CCTVs in the factory,
but we found this from a dashcam of a car
that was in front of the factory.
Those scumbags.
Get them.
Yes, sir.
Kim Hae-il, that bastard.
Today,
let's not just use words.
Yes, sir.
Gosh, I feel so much better now.
I can feel my stomach is
now filled with happiness.
Songsak.
Let's have some fun.
Hello.
Let's see if you did the new homework.
Betty Botter bought some butter.
But she said the butters bitter.
Ready, go.
Betty Botter...
-Betty what?
-Betty...
You don't know how to apply, do you?
I taught you how to do it.
How could you not do it?
Try again.
Excuse me.
Hey, don't. Why?
Do you want to try what I do?
What are you doing?
Is this a battle?
Is it another tongue-twister?
Bring it on.
Let me show you my amazing pronunciation.
Then follow me. It's easy.
How much wood would a woodchuck chuck
if a woodchuck could chuck wood?
As much wood
as a woodchuck could chuck,
If a woodchuck could chuck wood.
What are you doing, Yo-han?
What?
Are you a rapper?
Try.
I'll finish it at one go,
so listen carefully.
How much wood would a woodchuck...
-Chuck...
-You failed.
How much wood would a woodchuck chuck...
-Yo-han.
-It's okay.
I was just warming up.
How much wood would a woodchuck chuck...
-a woodchuck... chuck...
-Wrong.
How much wood would a woodchuck chuck...
Swag.
How much wood would...
Woodchuck...
Chuck...
Wrong!
The word I hate the most
is "wrong".
Yo-han!
"Correct" is the word I like.
Let me kill you with my moist karate kick.
Hey, Mr. Kim.
Who?
Who do you want me to get?
I got them.
Then did you sign to settle?
Yes,
we need to save Eun-ji's life first.
The lawyer said that was a better option.
Then we can't punish them.
It will only reduce...
It will only reduce the sentence.
Then I made a mistake.
Father.
It's turned out
that District Director Jeong Dong-ja
announced her voluntary resignation
two days ago
as a result of a priest's sly mind game
in order to cover the church's faults.
I don't have good feelings about this.
Goodness.
Is that it?
A person talks to the district director
in a disrespectful manner.
It's Father Kim of Gudam Cathedral.
That really does sound awful.
Be quiet.
Why did they have to change
his voice like that?
Last month, Father Lee of Gudam Cathedral
committed suicide out of pressure
while being investigated
for sexual assault and embezzlement,
which was much criticized by the society.
And Father Kim attempted
to provoke the police
in order to change the public opinion.
Well, if you think it's so unfair
that you take the responsibility,
then say it's on the employees.
Okay! It's official!
Make sure to keep your promise.
Then be ready
to step down from your position.
The priest's impure mind game
got him the answer he wanted.
I, Jeong Dong-ja,
will resign from the position
THE PRIEST OF GUDAM CATHEDRAL CRITICIZED
of the director of the district.
Feeling humiliated, the district director
decided to take all the responsibility.
And what Father Kim did afterward
is even more shocking.
He threw the copies of unauthorized papers
in the air and made a scene.
A priest's duty is
to bring peace to our souls.
However, this priest harassed human souls
in order to take advantage for himself.
What should a true cleric be like?
It's a question worth thinking about
for all religions.
I'm Reporter Lee Mi-won of QNN News.
Father. Take a deep breath first.
This is malicious producing,
not malicious editing.
Hey, everyone knows such news is fake
these days.
HE IS NOT A PRIEST BUT A GANGSTER
HE CAN'T BE TREATED HUMANLY
SEOUL GUDAM POLICE STATION
Old Lady!
Could you show some respect?
You made the employees take all the blame,
used a sick girl to drop a suit,
and made a fool of me.
Well done.
Now are you going to start
increasing your property
and move on
to the Supreme Prosecutors' Office?
You're not just picking a fight.
You're slandering me.
Forget about everything else.
But how could you use the sick girl?
Whatever. You behave yourself.
What do you mean by,
"You behave yourself"?
You know, that Seo Seung something.
The detective who likes you.
That girl who smiles at you like this
and removes dust from your jacket.
That girl.
-What?
-You know, fooling around
with a young and pretty detective like her
might tarnish your image as a priest.
What kind of impure ideas
do you have in your mind?
How dare you say that to a priest?
Then how could you say all those things
about increasing property and stuff
to a prosecutor of Korea?
Fine.
Then I will use a different word.
Trash.
The worst kind of trash
that can't even be recycled.
You...
What did you just say?
Prosecutor Park. Father Kim.
You can't do this at the police station.
"Trash"?
That's the word I hate the most.
Well, you deserve it.
And...
It won't stop bleeding.
That's great. Let me hit you once more.
Sure. Go ahead.
I'd love to get settlement money
from a prosecutor.
-Take it easy, ma'am.
-Get off of me, Mr. Lucky Bag.
Detective Gu is older than you.
How could you talk so rudely?
-Did that offend you?
-Yes. What? No.
-He said he wasn't offended.
-I'm offended.
-How dare you assault a priest?
-Please stop.
I will go to a hospital and sue you.
Hospital?
Blood!
I will sue you back!
How can you sue me
when you're the one who hit me?
How could a prosecutor be so stupid?
What? You have never gotten
kicked by me, have you?
-Get off of me!
-Ma'am!
Oh, no. I'm sorry.
Ma'am, you have a very strong punch.
Even your punch is sly.
Sly?
I just have an extra-long middle finger.
Do you have problems with it?
Father, I'll go get some tissues.
Detective Gu.
Why do you live like this?
You don't have to hurt others
to live a decent life.
I didn't hurt anyone.
Me? What did I do?
Please care about other people, okay?
You're a prosecutor.
Other people?
Don't you know I've been having to
stay low and humiliate myself
because of you?
Forget it! You don't understand.
Are you saying it's because of me?
What does that mean?
Do you think I'm a sociopath
because I smile all the time?
Old Lady, you know
you could make a great sociopath.
There are so many sociopath tests
on the internet,
so try it.
You're unbelievable.
If you're a priest,
try to read humans' inner sides!
Gosh, I feel dizzy.
Detective Gu.
I failed to wrap up things.
And I even got beaten up.
This is embarrassing.
Half-point.
What are you saying?
You know, from judo.
No point, half-point, and full point.
You won half point this time.
You didn't expect to beat them at once.
Did you?
If you keep going,
there will be one day
you get a full point.
The man of full point, Lee Won-hee.
I mean, Kim Hae-il.
Gosh, you lunatic.
Why? I was just trying to be nice.
You're weird.
I should buy Yo-han and Songsak a drink.
They went through a lot because of me.
What about me?
If you want to pay, you can follow me.
I would like to try the holy drink
that a priest buys.
You love free stuff, don't you?
Me?
This is so offending.
Hello.
Where are you going? Where...
Why is he so fast?
Hey!
Father.
Come on here, all of you.
Step aside.
-You're slower than I thought.
-Can't you see this?
Do you know how heavy this is?
You are indeed slow.
Let's finish it today, Father.
We don't have to worry
about the priest anymore.
I heard he's nearly dead.
Father, your face...
I fought against Hwang Cheol-beom.
-If you look like this, he must be--
-He's dead.
Dead, my ass. He's totally fine.
He attacked him first from the back.
HERE COMES THE COUNTERATTACK
Let's check the situation
at Hwang Cheol-beom's vacation home.
Special investigation squad.
We're something like that.
How about we go undercover?
"It's something
you've never tasted before."
It's here. My gut is telling me.
Let's go. Let's go get them.