ALL PLACES, INCIDENTS AND NAMES
IN THIS DRAMA ARE A WORK OF FICTION
You, boy, are connected to my soul.
I love you, Hae-il.
Father Lee was secretly being investigated
for sexually assaulting a church member
and embezzling and misusing church funds.
this will come as a shock
to not only the religious community,
but also everyone else.
Don't you know what he was like?
That's total nonsense!
Check all the traffic
and security cameras.
I also want an autopsy done.
Did you think I'd get excited
and allow an autopsy
if you showed up here?
He asked me
to spare him some every weekend.
HE MEETS THE FALSE WITNESSES
And while I was praying,
he suddenly touched my thigh.
So step aside!
Do you think you can
knock me down with that?
HE TRIES HIS BEST TO NO AVAIL
Stop shooting. Stop it!
We're going to Paris, France, right?
Wait, why don't you go tell the pope
and see if that doesn't work?
Pope, pope, pope,
help me, pope!
Dear Holy Father.
VATICAN CITY
THE POPE FORMALLY REQUESTS
A REINVESTIGATION
He actually did as I said?
What?
You want me to cooperate with the priest?
Who is the detective in charge again?
It's Detective Gu Dae-yeong.
You aren't willing to reinvestigate.
No. What?
Weren't you supposed to appoint
the most competent detective?
Yes, that's Detective Gu.
Look at that face. What should I do?
I think I might end up killing him.
I'll help.
No, let them get going
and back them up from the station.
I should be on the field.
Quiet.
I'd like someone else to do it.
Anyone but this loser.
Loser?
You're being rude.
I'm the hidden ace
of the violent crime squad.
Don't speak to me like that.
Ace my ass.
You can sit here
and stuff your face with those snacks.
You're making me feel competitive.
What if I solve this case?
Solve it? I'll buy you lamb skewers.
That isn't enough.
Beef, special cuts.
It's a deal.
Okay.
Let the joint investigation
officially begin.
I read your records.
It turns out I am a year older than you.
So what?
So you should talk to me more politely.
What's my job called in English?
You are wrong. It's "Father."
-Do you know what "Father" means?
-Of course I do.
Now, should your father
talk to you politely?
-You are ridiculous.
-I'm glad that's settled.
-Where are we going?
-We will eat first.
Where are we going after the meal, man?
Sir?
The woman who claims to be a victim
of sexual harassment
and the general manager of the church.
You met them a few days ago.
I'll really press them this time.
Pressing them won't change the truth.
-Detective Gu.
-Yes?
Have you ever gotten stabbed
in your head with a beef rib?
Come on, don't be like that.
Every time you open your mouth,
you talk about maiming.
So remember,
no more throwing around
big words like "truth" or "fact."
Words like "truth" and "fact"
are the closest to a detective.
How could I avoid using them?
All right! All right!
Damn this lousy temper of yours.
Everything around you is a weapon!
Let me tell you once again.
If you rain on my parade
or try to mess things up,
I will send you on a field trip to hell.
Father.
I am the detective here.
I'm in charge of this case.
You are only an observer,
a person who observes. Okay?
You can observe all you want.
Just don't get in my hair, okay?
What does he think I am, chewing gum?
Why would I get in his hair?
I'm no chewing gum.
I can hear you.
There isn't even much hair to get into.
That balding, grumpy priest.
Who does he think he is?
Excuse me?
It was just a chewing sound. Nom nom, see?
Eat quietly. Have you no manners?
Don't chew so loudly.
It's a habit, okay?
Where did I put that rib?
All right!
Why are you so sensitive
about the chewing sound?
Please put this away, ma'am.
I guess they're busy.
The pope? For goodness' sake.
This is ridiculous.
Someone must have coached him
when he planned this out.
There is no other explanation
for how it suddenly blew up like this.
Which bastard is it?
Push it all the way
to the Blue House if you want to.
Wait, why don't you go tell the pope
and see if that doesn't work?
Come on. Go tell him.
Pope, pope, pope,
help me, pope!
If you find the person behind this scheme,
arrest that bastard as well.
Yes, sir.
Didn't the police get someone
who will disrupt the reinvestigation?
I don't trust them.
That priest...
He's bound to cause headaches.
You can tell, right?
See if you can come up
with a way to get rid of that priest.
-How much is the total?
-It's 26,000 won.
Thank you for the food.
-What?
-We are paying separately.
Put it on expenses.
I can only do that with my meal.
You take yours to the Catholic community.
How much should I charge?
-26,000 won.
-Okay.
You jerk!
-Did you charge the total to this card?
-Yes.
My card... Your Catholic, aren't you?
26,000 won...
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
Do you have any good ideas?
Anything that could stop him?
For goodness' sake.
He has the pope watching his back,
so I need a legitimate reason.
I have an idea.
What is it? Hurry up and tell me.
Let's disguise one of our guys as a monk.
-A Buddhist monk?
-Yes.
Then we can make him run into that priest,
pick a fight, and get a severe beating.
It will bring about
an inter-religious conflict
and that priest will be put
under the spotlight.
Then--
You actually want to do this?
-Yes.
-Make him go "Avalokiteshvara."
Then bump into the priest, is that it?
That's it!
He could shoot a dirty look, like this!
A dirty look. A dirty look? A dirty look!
No?
It's a good idea.
Would you get rid of those arm warmers?
This isn't the 80s!
Are you living in the 80s?
This is the Prosecutors' Office.
Ms. Park.
Yes?
Mr. Kim, the idol singer
from the Nonhyeon-dong meth case,
requests for an interview.
Really?
Tell him to drop by later today.
DAEBEOM TRADING
-Welcome, Boss.
What are you, flip phones?
I told you to keep the bow
within the 30-degree angle.
-I am sorry, sir.
Do you want the world to know
that you are a gangster?
The cleanup for the reconstruction site
will begin today.
Shouldn't you overlook the process?
-I can't go. Go instead.
-Yes, sir.
I told you the last time.
Did you forget again?
I am sorry.
Bye, sir.
DAEBEOM TRADING
Do the Peter Piper picked a peck thing.
Peter Piper picked--
Peter Piper picked
a peck of pickled peppers.
Peter Piper...
Peter Piper picked...
I give up. Come here.
-Is this where that woman lives?
-Right, dude. It's that way.
-"Dude"?
-It's that way.
Let me remind you just in case.
You can't lose your temper
and break things during the investigation.
-All right.
-Promise me.
I told you I won't do it!
Don't you trust me?
Quit it. That's too loud.
She is inside but refusing to come out.
Maybe she isn't home.
Don't you hear the sound
of pork belly sizzling?
Maybe the sound is echoing
from another house.
Why would the sound
of pork belly sizzling echo?
A hairpin? Seriously?
Like that's going to work.
Does he think he is in a movie?
What? Hey!
For goodness' sake.
Who the hell are you
to open the door of my house?
Well, it wasn't me...
We had no choice
since you refused to come out.
If I refuse to come out,
that means I'm not coming out.
-Who do you think you are?
-I am a detective!
I am a detective! A detective!
Gosh, those perilla leaves sting.
Are you a priest?
What,
are you upset about
my daughter's testimony?
Where is your daughter?
-Why do you ask?
-I have some questions for her.
She went on a trip to Europe.
-A trip to Europe?
-Yes.
-Where in Europe?
-Europe.
Where in Europe? I can't reach her.
I can't reach her either.
She will call me when she wants.
-When is she coming back?
-I don't know.
She's your daughter.
Isn't it absurd that you don't know that?
It isn't absurd at all!
Perhaps my daughter and I don't get along!
I have nothing to say, so leave.
-That's preposterous.
-Let's go.
-For goodness' sake!
Her eyes were shooting daggers.
-We came all the way here.
-She is on another level.
I don't care if she is on another level!
It's nonsense.
-She is different.
-If you come again,
I will call the police!
-Understood?
-Call the police! Go ahead and do it!
-Excuse me?
-Let's go!
She said she doesn't know!
Do you think she really doesn't know?
My gut feeling tells me that's the case.
Don't use your gut feeling.
I might end up beating you up.
Everyone in this neighborhood is a thug!
I am going crazy on the first day
of cooperative investigation.
-Hey!
-Ma'am!
Ma'am!
-He moved out?
-Yes.
It wasn't much of moving out
since he only had enough belongings
to fit in a bag.
Where did he say he was going?
He said he was going abroad.
-Where abroad?
-I don't know.
He said he won't be back for a while.
I wondered if he was running away.
Running away?
Was he in some kind of trouble?
Didn't you know about his gambling habits?
Until a few days ago,
creditors and gangsters came
to hound him.
I couldn't believe the church's decision
to let someone like him
do the bookkeeping.
How about his family?
His wife left with a child
a few years ago.
Who would stay with him?
Thank you.
Aren't you getting the picture now?
-What do you mean?
-Gamblers
do anything to have their debts cleared.
Don't disparage the gamblers.
There are many gamblers who are pure...
Well, yes, pure.
Pure?
Did you just say that gamblers are pure?
Do you want to go meet
the purest person in the neighborhood?
Who is that? Who is pure?
Gaozi said that human nature
can't be divided into good and evil
just like a body of water that hasn't been
decided whether to flow eastward or west.
Thus, human nature is
neither good nor evil.
That was Gaozi's belief.
Gosh, the lecture is difficult
from the first day.
Come to think of it, it's true.
You can't know whether you'll be
a good son or an utter bastard
from the moment you're born.
Isn't that right?
You are right, sir.
Have some noodles before you go.
I am not right, you punk.
Bastards are born bastards
like me.
By the way,
are you keeping an eye
on that insufferable priest?
Yes. Detective Gu is doing the task.
Even an idiot has his use.
-Mr. Hwang.
-What is it?
You should come on out.
What is it this time?
What a hassle.
Move. I just need a minute.
We don't care if you need a minute or 100.
Let's go. What would Mr. Hwang know?
I wouldn't use much of his time.
I am a busy man myself.
-My goodness.
-Come on.
What's going on?
Father, what brings you here
all the way to my company?
Detective Gu, you came as well.
Let me ask you something.
Here?
Why don't you come in
for a cup of Ethiopian Yirgacheffe?
I got it from a famous cafe in Gangneung.
You can enjoy Ethiopian Yirgacheffe
all you want.
-Where are the two of them?
-The two of them?
Who do you mean?
You have the best acting skills.
With you, it's not as obvious.
You could at least tell me
what this is about.
You gave me no context.
I am talking about the woman
and general manager of the church
who gave false testimony.
Oh, those two. What about them?
Are they having an affair?
Seriously,
why would you ask Mr. Hwang about them?
Keep your mouth shut, Detective Gu.
Don't tell me to keep my mouth shut.
You can't go around creating a ruckus
everywhere you go.
I can't help if you keep causing trouble.
That's it.
He is a fine example of those
who protect and serve.
I told you to keep your mouth shut.
My goodness.
I am a violent crime detective.
And I'm a busy priest.
Where are you keeping them?
Why are you asking me?
This is so frustrating.
Who could have bribed people into lying
and forced them into hiding?
Not the police or the Prosecutors' Office.
It's obviously the work of the thugs here.
I feel so victimized.
I am a businessman
who complies with the law and order.
What will you do if I find the two of them
and prove that
you forced them into hiding?
Let's have a bet.
What should the winner get?
Eels? Lobsters? A wrist?
I have a better idea.
Put your hands behind your back
and take a punch.
Father!
Watch what you say.
A youngster like you shouldn't interrupt
the adults' conversation.
Stay out of it.
Fine.
I will put my hands behind me
and take a mean punch from you.
If you lose,
you will put your hands behind you.
Sure.
I will put my feet shoulder-width apart
and put my hands behind me.
Gosh, where'd he get those balls from,
the Holy Spirit?
Get the two witnesses' departure records.
Both of them went away.
Do as I say.
Why are you so talkative today?
You are driving me crazy.
Why are you dragging Mr. Hwang into this?
You don't even have proof.
How much did you get
from Hwang Cheol-beom?
You are unbelievable.
Watch what you say.
Then why are you so determined
to protect him?
Protect him, my foot!
We don't have anything on him.
We should mind our manners
as we investigate.
If you mind your manners more,
you would be Hwang Cheol-beom's slave.
You need to stop attacking me.
For goodness' sake.
-Hey.
-What?
Get security camera footages from that day
in the vicinities
of Gudam Cathedral as well.
But there are so many...
Gosh!
For goodness' sake.
Stop being angry
and do it slowly and gently.
See? It works.
Go already.
This isn't right.
I only tried it because CEO Kim's son
made an offer.
Why is my crime the gravest?
Didn't you say you confessed
that you are the provider?
They said they will arrest
the CEO of my agency and my bandmates
if I don't confess.
Hey.
I see hundreds of suspects in a month
that change their stories like you.
Let's wrap this up cleanly, okay?
I am begging you.
My mother...
She is suffering so much.
Gosh.
You have incredible acting skills.
After you serve your sentence,
you should go into acting.
You will make it big, I'm sure.
I am not a meth provider!
Mr. Kim.
That's the thing with the law.
It's inorganic.
No matter how much you shout and cry,
you won't get a reaction.
That's the law.
Use this chance to learn about the world
and become an adult, okay?
Ms. Park. Mr. Kang wants to see you
in his office.
What did I tell you?
I told you that priest
is bound to cause headaches.
Can't we ignore his request
for the security camera footage?
Wake up. Did you forget?
He has the pope behind his back!
Contact this person and
take care of the security camera footage.
Who is this person?
Do you have to ask?
He is in charge of data at the center.
He works for the Prosecutor General.
What are you waiting for? Go get it done.
Yes, sir.
How many times do I have to tell you?
Going through security camera footage
is a lot of work.
We still need to do it.
Knowing where Father Lee went
will give us a lead.
We don't have enough manpower for that.
I will do it.
I will go to the situation room
and bring the footage.
I can do that, right?
You are a newbie with a lot of work.
I could go a few days without sleep.
You need to sleep.
Lack of sleep is the root of all diseases!
She said she will do it!
Why are you complaining
when it isn't your job anymore?
-Listen.
-Yes, sir.
I went over
the two witnesses' departure records.
They did leave the country.
Where did they go?
The woman went to Dubai.
-Dubai?
-Yes.
Dubai is in the Middle East.
I thought she went to Europe.
Europe...
-Well...
-She must have had a layover.
She must have had a layover in Dubai
before she arrived in the French Republic.
How about the general manager?
Well...
He went to France.
THE FRENCH REPUBLIC AND FRANCE ARE
THE SAME COUNTRY
One went to the French Republic
and the other went to France.
That's right.
Yes.
Fix it before you leave!
SEOUL GUDAM POLICE STATION
Hold on, Father.
Hold on.
Do you think the police station is
a middle school classroom?
Whenever you are angry,
you kick things and shout.
There is a limit to our patience.
Even when you are upset,
you should mind your manners.
How would you feel if we kick things
at the church?
You deserve it.
For goodness' sake.
Isn't it your duty
to forgive the world and people?
Why are you so out to get us all the time?
Half-baked forgiveness
is the root of evil and evil itself.
That's why I don't forgive easily.
"Your problem solver,
Gudam Police Station"? What a joke!
I should destroy it.
No. You can't destroy it.
Kick me instead.
Kick it. Go ahead and kick it.
It would be better to have you kick
an inanimate object.
For goodness' sake.
YOUR PROBLEM SOLVER, GUDAM POLICE STATION
Ma'am, I want stir-fried cartilage
and another bottle of soju, please.
-The one with a red cap.
-Sure.
Who told you to sit down?
I will treat you. Let's drink together.
Go away already.
Thank you.
Are you getting smart with me?
I just want to drink with you.
I am not getting smart with you.
I know you won't pour me a shot,
so I will drink on my own.
Let's forget about our differences.
Let's sit here as a man to a man
and become drinking buddies.
I don't trust my drinking buddies.
Fine. Keep pouring your own drink.
Please give me another bottle of soju.
He is the leader of Maegakkyo,
Ki Yong-mun.
Say hello.
I am eternally honored to meet you.
I am Ki Yong-mun.
I heard a lot about you.
You work hard
materially and spiritually for Gudam.
I try my best to offer help.
Mr. Hwang brought
Prophet Ki Yong-mun to Gudam.
Mr. Hwang picked up a competent man.
Thank you.
Starting next month,
he will manage the welfare facilities.
He will also start working on
setting up a foundation.
I would like to remind you
that you must do well
without creating any noises.
We hate noises.
I am sure you will do well.
I will do my best.
Woo-ta.
What is this?
To thank you for accepting me,
my followers and I prepared a small gift.
Woo-ta!
I have always
found toads to be cuter than frogs.
I am Detective Seo Seung-a
from Gudam Police Station.
I am here to retrieve the original copy
of the security camera footage.
Okay. Please wait.
Father.
May I give you a word of advice?
Sure. I won't listen anyway.
See? I can't hear.
I will compare it to a baseball match.
The score is nine to zero.
-Nine to zero.
Nine to zero.
Two outs, bottom of the ninth.
No runners on base.
The last batter is up.
The ball hits the ground
right in front of the pitcher.
At that moment...
At that moment,
changing the coach and players
and calling the owner of the club
won't change a thing.
Play a game you can win.
I don't know anything about baseball.
Do you have no grasp on reality
because you are a priest?
Are you doing this on purpose?
You stirred up troubles everywhere
including Vatican City.
Why on earth did you do that?
I thought I told you
to shut your mouth when I'm around.
Are you looking down on me
because I am drunk?
Are you doing this because of
your sense of justice as a priest?
These days, justice is like
the underwear
Superman wears outside his pants.
It's a joke.
Gu Dae-yeong. These days, even Superman
doesn't wear underwear outside his pants.
Watch the movie.
It doesn't matter how hard you work.
It doesn't matter
if you come back from the dead.
There are things
you can't penetrate or dig up.
Even if the pope's grandpa comes--
What? Are you going to punch me again?
Go ahead!
Just don't punch me in the nose.
You little...
You aren't normal, Father.
You are the only one
who doesn't know that.
Forget it.
Where are you going?
You said you will pay, right?
He had to remember that
despite being wasted.
Captain, I am at work and all is clear.
Detective Gu. I got a call.
The security camera footage
has been taken care of.
Already? Yes, sir. Salute!
But keep your eyes on
Detective Seo just in case.
Yes, sir. I will do that. Salute!
He is wasted.
Salute...
He always hangs up
in the middle of my sentence.
VIOLENT CRIME SQUAD 2
This is harder than I expected.
Don't work so hard.
Even if you sacrifice
your health for work,
no one will thank you.
Did you drink?
Yes, I did.
Then go to sleep.
I still have a few things to look over.
Stop dozing off
and take a 30-minute nap.
Here, have this.
Hey, don't you have a chicken sandwich?
I am sick and tired of triangular gimbap.
Chicken sandwiches get sold out
as soon as I display them.
Just say "Kop khun kap" and eat,
stop complaining.
Make sure you put one aside the next time.
It's my wish.
What happened to your lips?
Did Jang Ryong beat you up again?
Hey.
You should fight back.
Why do you always get beaten up?
I will punch him someday.
I will punch him many times.
Peter Piper picked...
Just you wait, Jang Ryong!
Hey, hey.
When you get beaten up and feel depressed,
go to your happy place.
Happy place?
Happy place, happy place...
Thailand...
Jang Ryong, that son of a bitch!
There are thoughts that make you happy.
For example, imagine
the smell of chicken in the elevator
that is getting delivered
to another house.
That's right. I love that smell.
I love the smell of instant jajangmyeon
in the internet cafe.
Gosh, my mouth is watering.
I have another one.
-Inside an apartment building, doors open,
-Yes?
smell of grilled pork belly
filling up the corridor.
That's right. The smell of pork belly.
Yo-han, did you hear that?
I'm so hungry, I can't hear a thing.
It's a customer, you pig.
How could you call me a pig?
It's no wonder Jang Ryong beats you up!
Jang Ryong. Jang Ryong...
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
I am telling you this
because you are a regular customer.
You are beautiful.
I have wanted to tell you
since last month.
-Hey, Mr. Part-timer.
-Yes?
It's rude to make a comment
about other people's looks.
And who are you to make a judgment
about my looks?
It wasn't a judgment.
It was a comment of sincere praise.
Let's say someone said to you,
"Gosh, you look like baozi."
Would you be happy?
What's baozi?
A type of Chinese dumpling.
KING-SIZED DUMPLINGS
I am not done yet.
It's buy one get one free
for king-sized dumplings, right?
Yes, it is.
Apparently, I look like
a Chinese dumpling.
Even if such thought occurs to you,
keep it to yourself. Understood?
Okay.
Why are you threatening him like that?
I am only admonishing him
because his comment was inappropriate.
I am not threatening him, okay?
Gosh, you reek of alcohol.
Even if he was in the wrong,
talking down to him and using harsh words
make you a bully. Isn't that right?
A bully?
As his elder...
In which year were you born?
I was born in 1993.
What? 1993?
Unbelievable.
Father. He was born in 1993.
Born in 1993?
What happened in the galaxy in 1993?
In 1993, Comet Shoemaker-Levy 9
was discovered.
It collided with Jupiter--
See? I am your elder.
Elder, my ass. Boomer is more like it.
Bye, Ms. Boomer. Bye.
Bye.
I can't believe he was born in 1993.
Gosh, what's with the floor...
For goodness' sake.
-Ouch.
-What are you, an acrobat?
Father.
Gosh.
Why did you drink like
there is no tomorrow?
Are you okay?
Who are you? What?
It's me.
Old lady.
Hold on.
You can't grope a priest like that.
Touching your body won't do me any good.
Why would I do that? For goodness' sake.
If you touch...
If you touch my body again...
I can't believe it.
Oh, hey.
What...
Are priests allowed to be this drunk?
I don't care. I don't care.
How much more corrupt do you need to be
to be satisfied, old lady?
The things that come out of his mouth...
Father.
It's impossible for me to be corrupt
since I have no power.
For someone smart,
you are incredibly dense.
It's not the powerful people
who become corrupt.
It's the corrupt people who rise to power.
Old lady, you fit the description
perfectly.
Perfectly.
I understood perfectly.
Go home, wash up, and sleep.
All right.
Thank you as always
for your service to the country.
Gosh, he always admonishes me
with his holiness.
For someone smart,
you are incredibly dense.
It's not the powerful people
who become corrupt.
It's the corrupt people who rise to power.
Old lady, you fit the description
perfectly.
Perfectly.
Yes, Ms. Park.
I am sorry for calling so late, Mr. Park.
What was the sentence for Mr. Kim,
the idol singer?
Let's see.
Four years and three months.
He won't be out of prison
until the FIFA 2022 World Cup in Qatar.
Is there anything you want to say?
Let's cut the sentence in half
and let him watch the World Cup.
Fix the documents tomorrow.
Yes, Ms. Park.
Stop peeing, you punk!
It stinks.
It stinks so badly that I can't sleep.
Did you drink beer?
That happens when you drink beer.
There isn't much to life.
It's like that.
That's what it is.
Beep.
Beep!
My goodness.
Have some. It's really tasty.
Did you wake us up
so that we could eat this?
It's too early to sleep.
Have a late-night snack first.
It's really tasty.
Here. Have one each.
-We should thank the Lord for food...
-Sister.
Gosh, it's hot. My lips.
Blow on it and eat slowly.
Did something happen?
No, nothing happened. Why?
Would you like soju?
No. I will just eat this.
I feel like something is missing.
Soy sauce! I will bring soy sauce.
Please wait.
Soy sauce. Soy sauce.
Eat it with soy sauce.
I will mix the two.
Here.
My goodness. My goodness.
-Leave it, Father.
-I am sorry.
It's okay. Please just leave it.
I am sorry.
Go to bed.
We will eat before we go to bed.
-Will you do that?
-Yes.
Then I will retire to my room.
I feel the happiest
when people enjoy the dumplings I bought.
So please blow on it and eat slowly.
Father.
Blow on it, okay?
I will dip it in soy sauce for you.
It shouldn't be hot.
There you go.
It has cooled down.
Here.
I will retire to my room now.
-Good night.
-All right.
Gosh, this is the biggest crisis
I have ever met as a nun.
What is his problem today?
Seeing him smile like that
makes me feel so sad.
It makes you feel sad?
I feel terrified.
Instead of showing anger,
he is showing craziness now.
You will be late today as well, right?
You are always late.
What are you doing? We're moving out.
Move out.
You said there were no children.
There were no children. Let go.
Don't lie, you son of a bitch.
What did you say, you lunatic?
There were children inside.
I told you that everyone
except for Korean citizens
are enemies who can be eliminated.
Those children were innocent!
They are enemies!
Children aren't an exception.
-Get it?
-Those children were innocent.
Prepare to leave the organization
when you go back.
Understood?
Those children were innocent!
My goodness.
In the end,
I couldn't protect even you, Father Lee.
You were the person I wanted to protect
until the end of my time.
I don't know if I would be able
to protect anything
from now on.
Enjoy your meal!
Why aren't you eating?
I ate already.
Don't lie.
I can tell you drank yesterday.
Eat some food to cure your hangover.
It's okay.
Don't you like Russian food?
It's a taste of home.
I hear you haven't been able to keep
that nuisance of a priest in check.
You shouldn't work so sloppily.
You should be smart.
What will you do
if things get out of hand?
Things won't get out of hand.
You don't need to worry.
I have my trust in you, Detective Gu.
Look at my eyes.
Look at my eyes filled with trust.
If the current situation
gets wrapped up nicely,
I will lead you
to the land of milk and honey.
May I leave?
Finish the food before you go.
It's okay. You should go if you have work.
You may leave.
Isn't your late partner's
death anniversary around this time?
Gosh, look at your pupils.
Stop glaring, okay?
Don't forget the lesson you learned
from your late partner,
Detective Gu.
Please! Help!
Somebody help me!
Somebody!
Yeong-cheon.
Yeong-cheon, why...
Yeong-cheon. Yeong-cheon, wake up.
Somebody help!
Please! Help!
Hey.
Really? Okay.
What?
Watch the footage from here.
This footage was taken
near the entrance of the cathedral.
If you watch the footage from 11:20 p.m.,
which is the estimated time
of Father Lee Yeong-jun's departure...
It jumps to two minutes later.
Yes. It looks like a freeze-frame
since there are no cars on the road,
but two minutes of the footage is missing.
There could've been an error.
It happens sometimes.
This isn't a videotape from the 80s.
Why would there be an error?
That's not all.
The security cameras that are installed
down the road are missing
a minute of footage each.
Is this the original copy?
That's what they said
at the situation room.
What did they say about the missing time?
They said the errors are frequent
because the equipment is old.
They said they are planning an upgrade
or whatever.
Digital devices aren't problem-free.
Even cellphones lag sometimes.
Again? How could you destroy
the police property?
Are you joking?
How could you edit an evidential material
as if it's a movie?
Who are you accusing of editing?
It's the fault of the device, not us.
Look here.
No security cameras
work so poorly these days, okay?
Why are you causing a stir again?
You even destroyed police property.
Pay for what you broke.
I'm sending an invoice for that
to the cathedral.
What a lunatic!
I will really send an invoice this time!
THE WARM-HEARTED AND TRUSTWORTHY POLICE
IS ALWAYS BY YOUR SIDE
YOUR PROBLEM SOLVER, GUDAM POLICE STATION
Where will we take the group photo now?
Well...
Isn't that man a priest?
He can't be.
No priests are like him.
Good work.
The original footage
has been destroyed, right?
Okay. I will report to Mr. Kang.
Okay.
What is it?
Ms. Park.
Do you still think
the scheme with a monk is
a bad idea?
You are quite tenacious, Mr. Park.
Why can't you be this tenacious
about work?
How could you think
that kind of a scheme would work?
This is
the Special Team Prosecutor's Office.
What?
Okay.
Ms. Park. Mr. Kim, the idol singer,
tried to hang himself
in the detention center.
He has been moved to the hospital,
but he is in critical condition.
Ms. Park!
Exactly what have you done
to make Mr. Kim hang himself
in the detention center?
You said you were confident.
How could you mess up
the situation so badly?
The reporters will swarm
to this place and the hospital!
I will take care of the reporters.
Forget it. Go home
before the reporters come.
Understood?
Yes, Prosecutor General.
I am sorry.
Please don't worry.
Well, that's... Yes.
Okay.
A lot of police officers suffer
from work-related traumatic events.
As the National Police Agency implemented
a new kind of treatment program,
my hospital became responsible
for Gudam Police Station's therapy.
Give her a round of applause!
If you are suffering mentally,
book a therapy any time.
Please don't hesitate to do so.
Isn't she really pretty?
Whatever.
The contents of therapy
will remain confidential.
Thank you.
There are no secrets
in this tiny neighborhood.
The words are bound to get out.
Don't worry.
I won't.
DON'T BUY FROM TOUTING STORES
What are you looking for?
You.
Sit down.
You don't need to greet me so warmly.
You haven't changed at all.
Hey, Hae-il.
I never expected to see Won Do-u,
the genius hacker who hacked NIS,
at a place like this.
It's all in the past.
What brings you here?
What do you think, you punk?
I am here to ask you a favor.
I guess you didn't know.
I don't work as a hacker any more.
I can't help you.
-Really?
-Yes.
The statute of limitations hasn't expired,
so I will report your past crime
-and receive a reward.
-What?
How many charges would there be?
Finance, press,
national security, and porn.
That porn wasn't my doing.
You didn't mind before.
Why are you doing this now?
Now, do you want to listen to me?
What's the job?
It's simple.
The whereabouts of two people.
It's simple indeed.
So how much can you pay me?
Priests don't have money. I am a priest.
What?
Go to this location
and secure the witnesses.
What will you do when you receive
the remaining payment?
Other than paying off your gambling debts.
I will leave this country
and lay low for a while.
How about you?
After I pay off my debt,
I will party.
I will party until I get sick and tired.
You make me laugh.
I see that you are in France indeed.
But
instead of the Seine,
I see Bukhan River.
Russian misters!
Gosh.
As I expected, there are tails.
Come here.
Stop right there.
You'll go to hell
for hitting women, brothers.
I don't care if you crush him or kill him.
Stop him.
THE INVESTIGATION FACES HARDSHIPS
Who were taken away?
What are you doing?
Grabbing the opportunity from God
is the only way
to live as a decent human being.
Yesterday, you were drunk.
Today, you are a seasoned priest.
THE CULT TARGETS CHILDREN
Starting a month later,
this lady will look after you.
A priest came! He deserted his God
and came to Prophet Ki!