[Governor's Secret Love]
[Episode 4]
(Where am I?)
(Was it)
(a nightmare?)
(No.)
(Murong Cang did kill Ankang.)
(The people around him
aren't to be messed with.)
(I must leave this place at once.)
(Maodan and the rest
are waiting for me.)
(These things)
(will be my wages for these days.)
(He should consider it as the alms.)
(No.)
(I better write a receipt for a loan.)
(Like a loan.)
(I think I've seen this paper before.)
(It's the letter Dullard gave me.)
(What a coincidence.)
(Maybe the papers in the palace
all look the same.)
[Receipt for a loan]
(Chief Eunuch instructed
to watch over her.)
(Why did you come out?)
She fainted.
It's going to be long sleep.
(Forget it.)
(It's better to run now.)
[Ancestral Hall]
Murong, you went to great lengths
to flush the mole out.
Why did you kill him?
[Memorial Tablet of Mother, Yun'niang]
(He crossed the line.)
(The situation was critical back then.)
(The murderer who harmed the Mu clan)
(had been on the prowl for me.)
(With the help of my father's friend,
Imperial Physician Yang,)
(I escaped castration)
(and hid in the palace as a eunuch.)
(I've been investigating the murder,)
(hoping to bring the culprit to justice)
(one day.)
I brought you this medication.
[Spy]
Have your men prepare this.
Thank you, Uncle Yang.
Your father, Imperial Physician Mu,
saved my life.
I see him as my family.
Before we get our revenge,
I won't let anyone kill you.
I will protect you
even at the cost of my life.
Uncle Yang.
I was desperate back then.
It was you who sent me to the palace
and helped me avoid castration.
It's all thanks to you
that I have reached this far.
Don't underestimate the culprit
behind this poisoning incident.
I know very well
who did this.
I need a reason to take them down.
Mu and Yun'niang.
Departed souls of the Mu clan,
[Memorial Tablet of Father Mu Yinyuan]
please bless Mu
to purge the evil,
clear the name of the Mu clan,
and restore peace to the Yin Dynasty.
(It seems)
(that I could get out of here today.)
Jixiang.
(Oh, no. Busted.)
(This is the only way to save myself.)
Jixiang.
That's a rare expression on your face.
This is Imperial Physician Yang.
He's not a bad person.
Besides, he's skilled.
I believe he could restore your sanity.
This girl
is hopeless.
I can't do anything about it.
Thank you so much,
Imperial Physician Yang.
I'll take my leave.
Please take care, Mr. Yang.
Since the physician said
you're hopeless,
keeping you here is no use.
You may leave.
Really?
I'm leaving, then.
Stop right there.
You understood
my words, though.
(He got me good.)
Godfather.
Ask me anything you want to know.
I'll tell you everything
as much as I know.
If it wasn't for you yesterday,
Ankang would've killed me.
How did you find that out?
Speaking of this,
I bet you know
I'm the well-known soothsayer
in Longevity Shrine.
I didn't know that,
nor had I heard it before.
Anyway,
when I touch someone
with my hand,
I could foresee their future.
Now tell me.
What did you see?
(Murong Cang is eccentric.)
(If I were to tell me
that his future is a mess,)
(he would probably think I lied.)
(I might lose my life.)
(I'd rather take my chances.)
I saw
that you'll fall deeply for me.
You love me
in spite of yourself.
Nonsense!
There's something else.
You wouldn't want to beat me
or scold me.
Lowly maid.
How dare you slander Chief Eunuch!
This is demeaning.
You deserve a thousand deaths.
Chief Eunuch, she...
You said
that I would fall for you,
then why did you insist
on returning to the shrine?
I...
By any chance,
does your lover stay there?
That's not true.
I'm waiting for someone.
Waiting for someone?
Hmm.
If that person
really cares for you
more than anything else,
you wouldn't have to wait.
Since you said
that I would fall for you.
Tonight,
you're going to serve in my room.
- What?
Don't make me wait.
Otherwise, I'll kill you
before I fall in love with you.
All right.
This is strange.
Chief Eunuch never allows anyone
to serve in his room.
Why did he let her in?
Did this girl bewitch him?
The two of them...
What has gotten into me?
Chief Eunuch is a eunuch like me.
Women can't bewitch him.
Never.
Since
you predicted
that I would fall in love with you,
you shouldn't go back
to Longevity Shrine.
I don't like disloyal servants.
(You actually believed in that?)
(Fake eunuch, it's not going to happen.)
Godfather, it's late now.
Please have a rest.
I should get going.
Continue.
Yes.
Previously,
you sang a nursery rhyme
in Longevity Shrine.
Sing that again.
Godfather, you're the most powerful man
below the emperor,
and an intrepid warrior.
You like nursery rhymes?
If you don't want to sing,
I'll snip your tongue
to keep you silent.
No.
I want to sing.
I'm going to sing now.
♪Winter breathes plum blossom scent♪
♪Virgin snow drapes a veil of frost♪
♪Lights peep through blooms and leaves♪
♪Like fireflies♪
♪That illuminate the night♪
♪Ushering you into the slumberland♪
Dullard, will you stay with me forever?
No one can always stay with you.
I want to go home.
You don't have a home.
This is your home.
From now on,
this is your home.
What did you say?
Nothing.
I said I'm tired.
Please take a rest.
I'm leaving.
Hold on.
What's the matter, Godfather?
I've thought
your prophecy through,
I find it rather amusing.
♪Strive to bloom in the empty city♪
From now on,
Chief Eunuch is your home.
Starting tonight,
you'll stay in my room.
(Get a grip, Yunjiao.)
(My dullard boy wouldn't say
such a nasty thing.)
♪My love returns deep down♪
♪If we meet on the day
when wind gusts up at the wrong time♪
♪Please grant me a good end♪
♪Even though our good times
might scatter at any time♪
♪Or we embraced
in fear of losing each other♪
♪If you are an untamed wind♪
♪Please carry me up into the sky♪
♪I shall leave a name on the cloud♪
♪Even though my youth fades eventually♪
♪The stranded boat
rises and falls with waves♪
♪Despite the parallel routes♪
♪We embrace
on the fleeting moonlit night♪
♪When the sun rises,
my love returns deep down♪
♪If we meet on the day
when wind gusts up at the wrong time♪
♪Please grant me a good end♪
♪Even though our good times
might scatter at any time♪
♪Or we embraced
in fear of losing each other♪
♪If you are an untamed wind♪
♪Please carry me up into the sky♪
♪I shall leave a name on the cloud♪
♪Even though my youth fades eventually♪
♪If we meet on the day
when wind gusts up at the wrong time♪