=Broken the Heart=
Do you think I can't recognize you
with a new face?
=Episode 1=
(Reborn)
(Imperial City, The South State)
(Yin Ruoshui,
Crown Princess of the South State)
(One day,)
I'll take the other half flute
back to repay you.
Let's take it as a token.
Your Highness.
(Yuwen Sheng,
Crown Prince of the South State)
Your Highness,
(Nangong Xi, Crown Concubine)
the front army led by my brother
took another city of the Yin State.
We should celebrate.
Why do you take me here?
Today
is the third anniversary
of this beauty from the Yin State
marrying me for peace.
It's the rule in the Palace,
so I have to come.
Fine.
Nothing can stop us having fun, anyway.
Stop.
Did I let you go?
Come up.
Hurry.
What's this?
A perfume bag.
Yin Ruoshui,
you really think I know nothing
about poison
and the mean tricks in your state?
Guards!
Tell me the truth,
otherwise,
I'll kill you all!
Your Highness, spare me!
Tell me!
Your Highness!
I'll tell you!
This is the poison that prevents
the Crown Princess from getting pregnant.
Yin Ruoshui,
do you wanna die?
I'd rather die than live here.
Why don't you just kill me?
I won't kill you,
and I've also prepared a surprise for you.
(The Yin State)
Brother!
Let go of me!
(Yin Yan)
Brother!
This is a gift for you
in celebration of our third anniversary.
You can wait.
Next will be your mother the Queen
and your father the Emperor.
Put her in the dungeon!
Yes!
No!
Brother!
I'm taking a nap.
You keep an eye on her.
Guards!
♪Before begonia is in blossom
the pears blossom like snow♪
♪Floating in the night sky
like an amber moon♪
♪The moon casts its light,
but love remains unsolved♪
♪Who is murmuring
with sorrow rising from my heart♪
♪Leaning against the window alone
and sighing about romance♪
♪In this hustling and bustling world,
memory is unstoppable♪
♪At two ends of the world♪
♪How can we meet♪
♪But the snow in Chang'an where you are♪
♪Won't fall in the south♪
♪An oil-paper umbrella appeared
in my dream♪
♪Leaving a lingering back♪
♪I expressed my sighs with a pen♪
♪Leaving my worries on the paper♪
♪And tears on my gown♪
♪But the snow in Chang'an where you live♪
♪Fell in the dim light♪
♪My thoughts of you
are engraved in the bluestone♪
♪But no one can feel it♪
♪If you are looking far at the other side♪
♪Can you feel my thought
caressing you like a breeze♪
♪Before begonia is in blossom,
the pears blossom like snow♪
♪Floating in the night sky
like an amber moon♪
♪The moon casts its light,
but love remains unsolved♪
♪Who is murmuring
with sorrow rising from heart♪
♪Leaning against the window alone
and sighing about romance♪
♪In this hustling and bustling world,
memory is unstoppable♪
♪At two ends of the world♪
♪How can we meet♪
♪But the snow in Chang'an where you are♪
♪Fell in the dim light♪
♪My thoughts of you
are engraved in the bluestone♪
♪But no one can feel it♪
♪If you are looking far at the other side♪
♪Can you feel my thought
caressing you like a breeze♪