In the end, the police were able
to rescue all the workers.
- But Mr. Phairot,
- Stop!
- the company's owner, managed to escape.
- Drop your weapon!
You have to help me.
If I get arrested,
you won't get away either.
Where are you now?
"The labor trafficking fugitive
has been killed by the police
for resisting arrest."
How did the police
get the lead on Phairot?
The news says
a good Samaritan tipped them off.
I was following that case too.
I got some information.
But it wasn't a big deal.
Exactly what
I'm looking for in a son-in-law.
Are you available? Would you take
my daughter under consideration?
Dad! Stop talking.
I think our effort was in vain this time.
Someone took our credit.
Next time, we must take it more seriously.
If you don't pay,
your garage may get shut down.
Think it through.
We must remove bad people's space.
What can we do?
We don't even know who the collector is.
Are you sure you really want to know?
Dad.
The collector…
is Chief Khachon.
Chief Khachon?
I'd sooner close this garage
than go against your grandfather.
- Huh? Grandfather?
- Huh?
PREVIOUSLY
Whoa. For real?
Doesn't sound like
someone of his statue, right?
The text is too small.
I can't read. I have to enlarge it.
Oi, read the room, Granny.
Come on now. I don't have to read
to guess the situation.
Chief Khachon has always been famous.
They say he's an honest civil servant.
Honest my butt.
Honest men won't collect protection fees
from their own son-in-law.
So, what do we do?
If the garage's closed,
people will lose their jobs.
If we expose Chief Khachon,
Kam will be heartbroken.
We don't do this job
to help only Ms. Kam and Ah.
We also do it to help other people
and, more importantly, this country.
So, no matter what,
we have to find evidence
to expose Chief Khachon.
Even if it means being hated by Ms. Kam?
On this specific issue, Granny,
I really can't be selfish.
That's my hero.
You mean that?
Guys.
Come on.
- Please be generous! Go!
You're really
Chief Khachon's granddaughter?
He asked to raise me,
but I chose to stay with my dad.
But still, I can't hurt my grandfather.
I really hate saying this.
I'm ashamed of myself.
But can you not expose my grandfather?
Don't worry, Kam. I'll do my best.
Thank you very much for understanding.
Then, I'm going to go see my dad.
He worries me.
He seems very stressed lately.
Want me to give you a lift?
It's okay. Seng's waiting to take me back.
Okay.
- I'm going to go.
- Sure.
Give Chief Khachon a big tribute.
Tell him it's from Peem, MP Pethai's son.
I'll cover Ah's garage's protection fees.
Do whatever it takes to get
Chief Khachon's endorsement.
But don't let Ah and Kam know
that I'm playing both ends.
Thank you, Kam.
You really are my goddess of luck.
Wow. Chief Khachon's salary
afforded him this huge mansion?
If it were enough,
he wouldn't be collecting protection fees.
You're right.
But be honest with me.
Are we sure we shouldn't be
in our superhero suits?
Oi, Thua,
heroism is in the heart.
Jeez.
It's in the heart or they didn't dry
in time after washing?
But since when did you become
a complainer like me?
You're aware of that.
Hey, hide quickly!
Easy. Be careful.
That's Chief Khachon.
What's in the sack his men are dragging?
- Bung. Start recording.
- Yes?
Sure.
All beings on earth
live according to their karma.
May you rest in peace.
Sir.
I took care of it.
But some people still resist.
Want me to deal with it?
Thanks a lot.
Ever since I got you as my secretary,
you've made my job a lot easier.
Without you,
I wouldn't have come this far, sir.
Let's go.
We have a meeting later, right?
Yes, sir. This way, sir.
Oh no.
Hey, don't tell me
Chief Khachon will kill Ah.
- Yeah.
- That's right.
Cruel to the point of planning murders
and burying bodies on his own property.
We can't let it go on.
We must deal with this quickly.
Then we should hurry.
We'll have Granny stop time.
- Yeah, come on. Grab me.
- Let's go.
- I'll stop time.
- Yes.
Let's go.
Here's the plan. Split up and search.
Got it.
I'll check this room, Granny.
Guys, this one's an office.
- Whoa, an office. Bung.
- Come on.
- Granny, read these.
- Yeah.
- Found it!
- You found evidence?
I found lots of cookies. Can I have one?
Typhoon, watch out.
Food in a room of someone like this
might be poisoned.
But there must be something in the safe.
I'll try opening it.
Ooh, there are toys.
This is… Granny?
- Huh?
- It's a picture of Chief Khachon with…
- Where?
- Ms. Kam's mom?
- Where? Let me see.
- They look alike.
You're right.
Which year is this from?
Granny!
- Gran… Gran…
- Granny!
We're in Chief Khachon's garden.
- Yeah.
- Or we didn't go back in time?
Hey, hold on a minute.
That's Chief Khachon's daughter.
Koy! Stop right now.
I won't let you imprison me anymore.
I'm going to live with Ah.
Move.
Sir, this guy climbed the wall to get in.
Sir.
Please let her go.
Don't imprison her. Don't hurt her.
I'll leave.
No.
Don't leave me. I'm coming with you.
Koy.
- You ungrateful child!
- Sir!
I won't hurt you.
But if you choose to go with Ah,
you and I will no longer be family!
That's too mean.
- Hey, I… I can't hold it.
- What's wrong, Granny?
- Granny!
Granny, you can't
time jump randomly like this.
Now we don't know where we are.
Jeez, the weather's unpredictable.
I can't help it.
- Where are we?
- So…
- this is…
- Buses?
- You're back, Ah?
- Where are we?
- Hide. Quick. Hide, Granny.
- Let's go.
If it wasn't Ah,
whose voice was that?
Hey, we're still in the past?
Koy?
Sorry.
I supervised the repair.
I want our garage's first bus
to be ready quickly.
Ice pop, your favorite flavor.
- Ah, I know I can't help around much,
- Hmm?
but please let me
take care of you with little things.
Just you choosing me
has given me the push to keep fighting.
Don't worry, Koy.
I won't be a nobody much longer.
I will be better.
For you.
I'm going to the market.
Do you want anything?
No. Do you want me to give you a lift?
It's okay. It's not far. See you at home.
Mm. All right.
Looks like
Ms. Koy's worried about something.
Should we follow her?
- Well?
- Let's do that.
- Let's go.
Hide.
You don't have to hide.
She saw us?
What do we do, Granny?
If we go out there,
will we change the past?
I just wanted to see how far
a stubborn child like you could go.
In the end,
you threw your life away
for this lousy bus garage.
So what?
You want me to come back?
If you ask me,
I might give you a chance.
I want to have a father.
But I want my baby
to have a father too.
Koy.
Can you accept us?
But if you can't,
will you please let us go?
I know you and your people
have been harassing Ah.
Fine.
I'll let you go.
Dad.
But from now on,
we're out of each other's lives!
Dad.
This is why Chief Khachon
hates Ah so much.
But no matter the reason,
whether it's personal or his selfishness,
what Chief Khachon does is unacceptable.
All the more reason to help Ah.
Then we should go back, Granny.
To look for evidence?
I have to go number two.
All right. Let me focus.
PRESENT DAY
Good thing I came back for that in time.
What are you guys doing?
I think we've looked
for evidence everywhere,
but we found nothing untoward.
The only place left is in there.
Oh. Have Granny go back in time
to watch him punch in the code.
No. She's already used
a lot of power today.
Look at her. She's already confused.
- Yeah.
- Mm, let's keep going.
So, Typhoon,
try using your power on the safe.
Good thing I have this on me.
I heard something.
- Come on.
- Give it a try.
Let's do it. All gone.
Come on.
Who are you guys?
Granny. Granny, stop time.
I'm not going to Ayutthaya.
Who are you guys?
How dare you break into my office?
I… No, we…
We're Kam's friends.
Kam?
That's right. Kam, Ah's daughter.
I hope you know her.
What do we do?
What if we got Ah and Kam in trouble?
Who are you to Kam?
Someone who can't stand
seeing her in trouble
because of the revenge
by her own grandfather
who's using his power
and position to commit crimes.
Nonsense. With a smart mouth like that,
you must be a bunch of frauds.
Let's talk at the police station.
Hey, wait. Stop.
No, you can't take us.
Because the evidence
that says you're a bad person
is in that safe.
Go on, Thua.
You're screwed.
This is not evidence.
Those are photos of Koy, my daughter.
Damn.
You're both good-looking.
- Granny.
- Hm?
Have you recovered? So we can escape.
How would that work?
Our faces are exposed.
They'll find us eventually.
There's nothing wrong with me.
Why? What happened earlier?
- It's bad this time.
- You're not fully recovered.
Eh?
But wait.
Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
I have a weird feeling that
we might misunderstand something.
Just seeing him keep old photos
turns you into a softy?
No. We looked for evidence
for a long time, right?
But we haven't found anything
that indicates he's a bad person. Right?
We're so screwed.
You guys really are Kam's friends.
And you used to be
a bus ticket taker at the garage.
I was, sir. That's right.
Then, let me ask you this.
When you talked
about Kam being in trouble,
my revenge,
and me abusing my power and position,
what were you referring to?
I saw with my own eyes that someone
tried to collect protection fees from Ah.
If you don't pay,
your garage may get shut down.
Think it through.
The collector…
is Chief Khachon.
I heard it myself that the collector
was you, Chief Khachon.
That's not true.
I serve the public with honesty.
The only thing I'm at fault
is I wronged Koy.
Everything else isn't worth mentioning.
- Eh?
What does that mean, old man?
You're really not lying to us?
But you have no reason to lie to us.
Because if you wanted us gone,
you could've put us in those sacks
and buried us in your backyard
like you did earlier.
Nonsense.
What I put in that sack and buried
was just a dead stray dog.
- Eh?
What about when you said,
"If they resisted,
then deal with it." What was that, sir?
I had my people put up
a food bank before I got permission.
If the people in the area resist,
then deal with it by packing up.
So, that means
we misunderstood everything?
All right.
Tell me everything you guys know.
I want to catch whoever
is throwing my name around.
Especially those who used my name
to hurt my granddaughter and son-in-law.
So, you're not mad at Ah anymore?
You know about me and Ah?
- Oh, well,
- Uh…
we saw the photos and the letter.
That's right.
I wrote a letter to apologize to Koy.
And I thought someday,
I'd get to apologize
to Ah and Kam in person.
I think that day has come.
Here's the thing, sir.
Someone claimed…
to work for you
collecting protection fees.
Who dared make such a claim?
And why haven't I been informed?
It might be someone closer to you
than you think, sir.
Thanks a lot.
I have an idea
who that person might be.
I'll look into this myself.
But you should clear this up
with Ah and Ms. Kam first.
As for catching the culprit,
why don't you let us help?
It's okay.
These things could be dangerous.
I don't want you guys to get in trouble.
It's no trouble.
I know someone
who can deal with this stuff.
Who?
Have you ever heard of this name?
The "Please be generous" gang.
Yes, sir.
I'll send the "Please be generous" heroes
to the scene right away.
Let's go, guys. Let's do this.
Mm-hm.
- Bung.
- Yes?
Stay close to me.
Don't overextend yourself.
Remember you have
another life to take care of.
Yes, Granny.
- Let's go.
Mr. Peem, I'm taking
the money to Chief Khachon.
Very good.
If he wants anything, just tell me.
We must have Chief Khachon on our side
because he'll be crucial
to my political base.
Yes.
Mom,
I'll show you
that I can do it and I can do it well.
Hey, what do you need?
Peem, it's me, Kam.
Sorry, Kam, I thought
you were one of my people.
It's okay.
I called you right away because I'm happy.
My grandfather just told me
that he wasn't the collector.
Someone's using his name,
and he's about to catch the culprit.
Huh?
I have to go. I'll call you back.
Damn it.
CHAIRMAN OF THE SPECIAL
MASS TRANSIT SYSTEM IMPROVEMENT COMMITTEE
Sir.
You're Chief Khachon's secretary.
He has me oversee everything.
Anyway, can you tell me now
who you're working for?
This is the money
requested by Chief Khachon.
In exchange for--
Hey! What are you doing?!
How did he get here?
Let's go and catch them.
You've been caught.
We've surrounded this place.
Who are these people?
- Hey!
- Stop time! Ow!
Granny, are you okay?
Mighty One, follow the secretary.
I'll follow the briber.
- You got it.
- Let's go.
Hey, that way!
Mr. Peem, are you okay?
None of your business!
Let's just go.
Hey.
- I got him, Granny.
- Hurry.
Sir.
You won a government scholarship
to study overseas.
Instead of repaying your country,
you use the opportunity
you're given to commit fraud
because you think I trust you.
You've never been poor.
You'd never understand!
I've never been poor,
but I've known poor people.
Poor people who work honest jobs,
who work hard until they're successful!
- What is this? Wait.
- Go!
- Sir.
- Go.
Go.
- We should go.
- Come on.
You're useless.
So, what happened, boss?
We read the whole thing wrong!
That secretary used Chief Khachon's name.
Chief Khachon isn't corrupted.
We're screwed.
Luckily, I stopped it in time.
Otherwise, those freaks
would've realized my mode of operation.
So, what do we do now, boss?
You lay low for now. Don't worry about me.
There are many more pawns I can move.
Go.
And Chief Khachon insists that
he was unaware and not involved
in his secretary Chanon's scheme
to collect protection fees on his behalf.
Chief Khachon also says he's ready
to cooperate with the authorities
to verify everything.
This is one more mission
the heroes of "Please be generous"
have accomplished to help the public.
It's a shame they didn't catch the briber.
That would've helped
further the investigation.
You already helped us a great deal, sir.
Please accept my sincere gratitude.
I'm the one who owes you my thanks
and apologies.
Sir.
Chanon, my secretary, is a capable man,
but he is corrupted.
He used my name to commit crimes.
I thank you for the fact that
no matter how hard life
has been for you,
you've never done anything untoward.
And you've raised Kam so well.
I apologize
for letting my ego blind me
and getting you all in trouble.
The joy of helping someone
is a hero's reward, right, guys?
Mm.
I feel that way too.
Yes.
And now, I've gained one more idol.
Boss?
How are you wiping these?
The chairs still aren't clean?
And have you mopped the floor?
Not yet, boss.
- You haven't mopped the floor?
- No.
You haven't, but the water's this dirty.
Get new water and mop the floor.
- Yes, boss. I'll do that right away.
- This guy.
- Boss!
- What?
Boss.
I bought you an ice pop.
Your favorite flavor.
Oh.
Thanks, Thua.
Wow.
I was craving this flavor.
This reminds me of Koy.
Kam's mother.
Her name was Koy. Hey, I'm not bragging.
My wife was a knockout.
Yes.
Wait.
Thua, how did you know
that I loved this flavor?
Ms. Kam told me once.
I see.
Brain freeze.
Please take care of her.
Take care?
- Take care in what way?
- My father-in-law.
I mean Chief Khachon. He told me
you and your relatives
broke into his house to help Kam.
Thank you all for worrying about Kam.
Please take care of her.
Even though Kam's fearlessly bold,
her heart is gentle.
That's why she's easily duped.
You got it, boss. Don't you worry.
I'll take great care of Ms. Kam.
I'm relieved she has good friends.
- Boss.
- Hm?
Chief Khachon also said that
you used to be a bus ticket taker
before you became successful
because of love.
Do you know that you're my idol?
- Really?
- Yes.
Thanks.
Then again, back in the day,
I was a reckless man.
But since I became a father,
I realized and understood Chief Khachon.
No one knows what awaits
in their future.
True, boss. True.
Success
doesn't come easily.
If it's up to me, I want my daughter
to marry someone rich and decent
so she doesn't struggle.
Like…
Mr. Peem. What do you think?
Right?
He's the best one out there.
What are you reading, Kam?
Peem.
How are you feeling? Still hurt somewhere?
I'm okay now.
Just seeing that you care
makes me feel better.
Oh, the photos
of my grandfather and my mom.
And his letter to her.
It's a shame.
If my mom were still alive,
she would've been so happy
to see those she loved reconcile.
She still is.
Your mom's always in your heart.
She must've sensed it.
Thank you very much, Peem.
You make me feel loved like--
Don't say,
"Like having my mom by my side."
No.
I feel like I can smile every day.
You've always been there for me
and fixed all my problems.
I'd love to make you smile
every day in an official capacity.
Huh?
Please be my girlfriend.
Isn't that too fast?
After I heard about Chief Khachon
and your family, I've realized that
I should tell you
how I feel before it's too late.
If I keep waiting,
we'll have less and less time together.
Or am I not good enough in your eyes?
Yes, I'll be your girlfriend.
I love you, Kam.
Kongfah's the one
my mom wired all her money to.
Your mom wired the money
because she loves dogs.
No. My mom was scammed.
NEXT EPISODE
"Please be generous" webpage
is investigating Kongfah.
There are complaints that
Kongfah doesn't really rescue dogs.
He scams people.
Kongfah's webpage info?
Or is this Please be generous's?
If you keep controlling me,
I'll kill myself!
- Mom! No, Mom!
- I'll kill myself!
Subtitle translation by: Chonnikarn Ounob