PREVIOUSLY
How could you do that?
Hey!
- If you know, you can't tell anyone!
- Why?
If the wrong people find out,
it could get messy.
Help me! Help!
If we find the kid,
we could get a million baht!
Title is with you?
Three million, in cash, unmarked bills,
in exchange for your son’s life.
Got it?
Those plainclothes cops
have been inside for a while, boss.
Looks like that kid’s dad
is pretty influential.
If I find out there are still cops,
what you’ll be getting back is a corpse!
Title! Don’t do anything to Title!
I’m giving you a chance.
Get all the cops out of here.
Title, hello? Hello?
Uh…
Torpob!
Go! Get everyone out of here.
Uh, please leave first.
I just eavesdropped.
I'll summarize what I heard.
Right now, at Torpob's house, there’s
a thief network reporting the situation.
Here’s the first thief, who reports
the situation to the second thief,
the one who kidnapped Title.
- Oh.
- Granny, I think
the thieves must be around here.
If you stop time, we can go find them.
If we find and follow them,
we might be able to find out
where Title is.
If that’s the case, I’ll stop time.
Wait a minute.
What about Typhoon and Bung?
I’ll stay here. You and Thua,
if you find out where the criminals are,
let me know right away.
I’ll call people and get the cops to help.
But this time, we can’t reveal ourselves.
Otherwise, we risk being mistaken
for the thieves.
So, I guess
I won’t be the hero of Ms. Kam, huh?
You’ll have plenty of time to be a hero.
I’m still here.
Me too!
I’ll also… Okay, we’ll trade roles.
Alright, let’s go.
- Ready?
- Ready!
Hey!
Let's go!
I'll stop time.
Granny and Thua are gone.
They took their phones with them.
In that case,
we’ll check out the area first.
- Yes.
- Let's go!
- Wait a second!
- What?
I’m hungry.
Hey!
Oh, look at that!
He's acting all sneaky and weird.
- Is that a thief? I think it is.
- Huh?
We should hurry and follow him.
Let's go!
Wow, Granny, it’s a good thing
we can stop time.
- Otherwise, we’d never catch up.
- Right.
Well, but…
He has a motorcycle.
If we let time run,
how are we going to catch up with him?
Wait a minute, Granny.
I think I recognize him.
Hey!
- It’s Neng!
- Huh? Do you know him?
Of course, Granny. Everyone knows him.
He’s from that gaming gang.
We can’t waste time.
Let’s hurry and save Title!
Let's go!
Oh, hey.
I’ve been around here for a while,
but I’ve never been inside this place.
This is Cherry's shop, Granny.
It’s a hangout for all the troubled kids.
Alright, here’s the plan.
Granny, stop time.
I’ll go inside and check it out, okay?
I’ll go with you.
I’ll never leave you behind.
Good. Let’s go, Granny.
There is only a small space here.
Where could they hide the kids?
- Hey!
- Did you find something?
This is the game I used to play
when I was a kid.
I can't believe kids
are still playing it today.
Thua, is this really the time for this?
He reads my mind. I’m sure this kid
is going to grow up to be a good person.
- Hey! Title!
- Huh?
Title?
Yeah, that’s him!
Wait. Don’t tell me
Title came here willingly?
What? I’m confused.
- Here’s the plan, Granny.
- Huh?
Let’s hide first,
let time resume,
and then we’ll see what happens next.
Alright, okay.
I’ll take a picture to keep as evidence.
- Come on!
- My phone!
I’ll silence my phone.
Hold on. Let me turn off the sound.
Over there!
Hey, send someone to pick up the money.
I told you I can pay off the debt.
As for the guy who brought the money,
you can keep him or do whatever
you want with him, it’s up to you.
That kid?
I’ll send him to the border today.
You want to make him a beggar
or sell his kidney, it’s up to you.
Either way, he’s not worth much to you.
Hey! What was that sound?
Okay, I’ll talk to you later.
Who’s there?
It's me.
Ah…
What the hell are you doing here, Jack?
I just spoke to the van drivers.
They'll pick up the kid tonight.
Alright, come talk to me about the kid.
Let’s go.
The phone breaks so easily nowadays.
A small drop and it's done for.
Look at this.
You can use mine.
Hey, the battery’s dead.
What should we do now?
Should we go back
and get help from the others?
We can’t do that, Granny.
What if Title gets moved in the meantime?
Right!
Here!
Hey, thanks! Just in time.
You’re here to help that kid, right?
Make sure you help him
and don’t pressure him
into running away from home again.
Wait. What’s going on here?
You’re the one who kidnapped Title,
and now you’re helping us?
I took him because I thought
his parents were abusing him.
I didn’t mean for him to be sold.
I didn’t think things would get this bad.
The batch of kids to be sent
to the border is a big one.
The people helping out,
make sure they do it right.
I have to go now. If Cherry finds out,
I’ll be in deep trouble.
Thank you. Thanks.
- Selling kids…
- A big batch!
Wait!
Typhoon, you need to act
super hungry, okay? Got it?
- Got it!
- That way, we can ask for food easily
and save up energy.
We’ll need strength to help everyone.
No problem.
I’m actually really hungry right now.
Let’s go.
I’m starving!
Do you have any food? I’m hungry!
Oh, sorry,
I’m sorry for making you hungry.
Let’s sit down first.
I’ll find something for you.
- Thank you.
- Sit, sit.
Here, eat this for now to hold you over.
Thank you.
You’re much kinder than Title said.
Really? So, what did Title say about me?
He said he didn’t get first place on
his exam, so he was too afraid to go home.
But Title still loves you.
I’m a bad person.
And Title still loves me?
Of course! Title said
he didn’t get first place,
so he didn’t want you to be disappointed.
Don’t worry.
There’s plenty of delicious food here.
How could he not come back?
I’d do anything to have Title back home.
If you’re still hungry, feel free to grab
something from the fridge. Help yourself.
Thank you so much.
- Hey!
- Hmm?
Hey!
But he must not tell the police?
Right now,
that’s a different matter, Ms. Kam.
The money Torpob is going to give is
with another group waiting to receive it.
As for Title, he’s with another group
waiting to be sold.
Let’s hurry, Kam.
We need to go save everyone!
What should we do? I have power now,
but if we go help others…
What if they recognize us?
What should we do?
Well, since we met,
no one has changed clothes, right?
So, I brought these for you all.
Whoa, winter jacket!
Socks.
And boots too!
They won’t recognize us.
Because we’re going as hero page
"Please be generous"!
What’s that?
- Let's go!
- Go where?
Just go. Let’s go first.
He's here!
Hey, has your guy shown up yet? They're
about to take the kid to the bus station.
Huh?
Hey! What should we do, Granny? Stop time?
We need to stop time.
No, we can’t. If we stop time,
the police won’t be able to get here.
What are you talking about?
So, it’s you, you traitor!
Jack!
Beat them up!
Hey, hey! Don’t hurt us!
What should we do, Granny?
They’ve caught us already.
Should we run?
We can’t, Granny.
If we run, they’ll take Title.
Wait a second.
How about this?
Granny, you go find a safe place first.
Or you can go find Phakbung.
Then I’ll follow them quietly
and send updates.
Alright, as soon as I leave,
I’ll snap my fingers
- to resume time.
- Yeah.
- Okay, Granny.
- Thua, you have to hide well.
Got it, Granny.
Okay!
Hey!
- Hey!
- Huh?
Where did they go?
Jack!
I’m not involved! You saw me.
I’ve been right here the whole time.
They’re gone.
They must’ve escaped already.
Who would want to get themselves
into trouble for someone else?
I think we should take the kid
and go, quickly.
Hey, everyone!
Hey, Granny, how did you get here?
Where's Thua?
Thua’s in danger. He's following Title.
- Huh?
- Right now,
even though we have to reveal our powers,
we must do it.
We have to help!
Who says we're going to reveal ourselves?
Huh?
Wait!
Here! Heroes need costumes,
like in the movies.
Hurry up!
Hey, hurry up!
Be quiet!
Faster!
Hurry up! Hey!
Where are the police?
Damn, they’re about to leave!
What should I do?
Go!
Hey!
Get in!
Stop!
Hey!
Where did you go earlier?
- You still owe me!
- Stop!
Hey, it's working!
What do you mean?
- Stop?
- Why…
Stop?
Hey, hold on tight!
Stop it!
What the heck are you doing?
Got it. Thank you so much.
The police said they've helped Torpob,
and the money is safe now.
But they still haven't caught the thieves
and haven’t found Title yet.
So, what Thua said is true.
We have to hurry and help him, Peem.
If you go through the alley ahead,
you’ll reach the bus station.
But you two shouldn't go there.
It's too dangerous right now.
No, I have to go.
Stay close to me.
Let's go. Lead us there.
We won’t let you harm Thua and Title!
Right, Bu--
What are you on, huh?
Fatty! Are you high on meth or laxatives?
- Hey!
- Stop!
Title!
Title! Kids!
Are you alright?
Title!
Title! Everyone, okay?
Where’s Title?
- Title, my son!
- Dad!
How are you, son?
Oh my.
Or you…
Or maybe…
This person is the one
who helped send the news,
which is why we were able
to save the kids in time.
So, who are you all?
You guys…
- Alright, done.
- How could you do that?
What’s wrong, son? What happened?
You guys are…
If you know, you can't tell anyone!
This has to stay a secret.
Why?
I just don't want to get into trouble.
If the wrong people find out,
it could get messy.
Why?
The ones who helped me, Dad.
REGULATIONS FOR VISITING DETAINEES
AT BANGSRI MUEANG POLICE STATION
BANGSRI MUEANG POLICE STATION
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
No one has testified about the gambling
or child trafficking gangs yet,
but we will continue the investigation.
Actually, we should thank those three
for being heroes.
Do you happen to know who they are?
Oh, I…
I’ve never met them before.
How did you know where Title was?
Uh, well…
Here’s the thing. It’s Jack. Yeah, Jack.
Jack was the one who helped Title as well.
Uh. So…
Is there a chance we could ask
the police to reduce his sentence?
I'm sorry, Dad,
for not getting first place
and for missing so many days of school.
It’s okay, son.
I’m the one who should apologize to you.
From now on,
I won’t pressure you anymore.
If you want anything, just tell me,
and I’ll get it for you.
All I want is for you to understand
and not scold me. That's enough.
Okay, son. Okay.
Hey, son!
It’s late now. Get some rest.
Yes.
Let's go to sleep.
Sleep well, my son.
Hey!
It's your gang!
Thank you for keeping the secret.
How did you guys get here?
Well,
we had Granny stop time,
and then we just walked right in.
We also came to check if you were safe.
I'm safe.
I promise I won't reveal the secret.
Everyone will get to be heroes
and continue helping society.
You both are so adorable, father and son.
We promise to use the money
to help everyone.
And we promise
we’ll be heroes and keep helping everyone.
- Come on. Let's high-five
- Combine our strength!
Hey!
- We’ll be going now.
- Yes.
Come on.
Let's go.
Hey.
Typhoon.
Let's go.
That was awesome! So cool!
Let's celebrate our success!
Yay!
Can I join the celebration?
- Ms. Kam!
Um…
Actually, I just remembered
that I haven't apologized to everyone
for being suspected,
and I haven't thanked you all
for coming to help.
Well, what do you mean?
Actually, the real hero is…
"Please be generous", not me.
Who says that?
If you hadn't sacrificed yourself,
no one would have found Title,
including that hero gang.
Actually, it's just you, Ms. Kam,
who saw me do something good.
I’m happy already.
Alright, let's eat!
- Let's celebrate!
- Yeah.
- Kam!
- Ms. Kam, please sit here.
- Plates, plates!
- I’ll handle it.
- Please, sit down.
- Come on in!
Sit down, please.
- Come on in.
- Go ahead.
Finally, the urgent mission
to find Title, who had gone missing,
has been completed,
thanks to these people's efforts.
PLEASE BE GENEROUS - THE PAGE CONTRIBUTES
TO GATHERING USEFUL INFO FOR SOCIETY
We're "Please be generous" team.
And I would like to announce
that I will be awarding a prize
to this team, just as I promised.
PLEASE BE GENEROUS
Granny, Bung, Typhoon! Look at this!
- We haven't finished yet, Thua.
- Hurry!
- What?
- What's wrong?
- Hurry up. Come quick!
- What?
- Hurry up!
PLEASE BE GENEROUS
7,300 LIKES, 12,000 FOLLOWERS
Finally, our page
is going to be recognized!
Why are you the admin
of the "Please be generous" page?
Well…
Why are you using the name
"Please be generous"? Who are you?
What is your connection
to the "Please be generous" team?
Did you create the page for personal gain?
Oh, hold on a second. Wait, wait!
Who should I answer first?
- Oh?
- Huh?
Let me hold this.
Whoa, there's a lot!
Alright.
I'm the admin
of the "Please be generous" page.
I have to tell you,
I can't reveal who the heroes are
because everyone's information
is confidential.
However, what’s not a secret is…
LAAB ITTHIRIT RESTAURANT
…me and everyone in "Please be generous"
agree that
we will help everyone who is in need.
For anyone who has a complaint,
please line up,
and we’ll help as much as we can.
I’ll make sure to sign for everyone.
Come on!
- Hey! What’s this?
- Wake up, Thua!
Stop dreaming about being the admin
of the page and telling others about it.
You have to keep it a secret
or we’ll all be in trouble.
I know,
but I’m sad! We’re famous
and rich, but we can’t tell anyone.
Hey! Here!
Look! The money's in the account.
We’ve got a million now!
You’re going to give me a lot, right?
Of course, I’ll give you a nice salary.
If you spend like this,
you’ll be poor again soon.
If you’re not careful,
you’ll be back to square one in a month.
But it's a million! What should I do?
You need to manage the accounts
and divide the money.
Some for emergencies,
some for the house,
some for the Laab restaurant,
some for our salaries,
and some for yourself.
Right! So smart.
It’s normal. Everyone can figure this out.
You’re an adult now.
Why didn’t I think of that?
Maybe you’re not smart.
What? Not smart? Come here!
See?
Thua!
Yes?
Kam is here, waiting outside.
- Huh? Ms. Kam came to see me?
- Yes.
Whoa, this is my golden year!
Ms. Kam came to see me!
Finally, the urgent mission to find Title,
who had gone missing, has been completed,
thanks to these people's efforts.
We're
"Please be generous" team.
Oh, Ms. Kam. What are you watching?
The "Please be generous" team.
They’re really amazing, right?
Yeah, they’re really cool.
I bet the real ones are even cooler.
- Do you know them?
- Yes, I do.
Uh, no, I don’t.
Well, I’ve contacted the admin
during the Title issue,
so we might be kind of close.
That’s good. So, do you feel like
this team looks familiar?
Familiar? How?
There’s one kid, two women.
One of the women is older,
close to Granny Cheuy’s age.
The kid is chubby, like Typhoon,
and the other woman
looks like Bung, right?
Hey, no way, Ms. Kam. These three
are always at the Laab restaurant.
And besides, they’re really weak.
How could they help anyone?
But they look so similar!
No, they don’t.
- Come on.
- Never mind.
Let’s talk about us.
I’ve got something important to discuss.
What’s our issue?
You can tell me, Ms. Kam.
Hello, Thua.
The important thing is
about Peem. He wants to talk to you.
Yes.
I’m sorry for the past.
If I’d known you were trying
to do good deeds for society,
I wouldn’t have interfered.
Alright. Here.
Please take this.
Just a little something from me.
Take it.
Peem has been stressed for days
after realizing he misunderstood you.
Don't blame someone for not knowing.
I won’t hold it against him.
Thank you.
- Thank you, Kam, for handling this.
- You're welcome.
Alright, we’re done here.
Let’s go, Peem.
Let's go, Kam.
Done?
Ugh, my heart hurts.
I really want to know who
the "Please be generous" team is,
the ones who came together
to create this page to help people.
They’re so cool, right, Peem?
The villagers are all so impressed,
they're liking the page a lot.
If it seems too good to be true,
don't trust it right away.
The fact that this team is staying
anonymous, not showing their faces,
there has to be something behind it.
If that's the case, that's too bad.
Hey, isn't he leaving yet?
Kam, your eyebrows are furrowed.
I’m not saying this to stress you out.
No one wants to see the person
they like feeling stressed.
Hmm? What do you mean by that?
I mean you, Kam.
You’re the one I like.
Oh, Thua!
Why are you standing in the doorway?
Well, I…
Uh, no. Ms. Kam, you left your wallet,
so I brought it back to you.
Thank you.
Hey, but if I leave now,
I'll definitely lose Kam.
I can’t let that happen.
Lose what?
- What?
- Ms. Kam.
I just contacted
the admin of "Please be generous".
I heard they’re currently looking
for a case
to win over…
Win over what?
They’re trying to defeat bad people.
They’re probably looking
for a new case to take on.
If anyone is in trouble,
or if you know anyone who is,
let me know.
- Really?
- Yes, really.
Well, if anything happens,
I’ll contact you right away.
Thank you so much!
No problem.
I’ll contact the admin shortly.
Who should I help?
It has to be something grand and cool,
something that will melt Ms. Kam’s heart.
I’m really in trouble right now.
Can you transfer me 200 baht?
Hmm?
Is this a scam?
I’m in a lot of trouble right now.
I don’t have money to divorce my wife.
Can I borrow 200,000?
Asking to borrow money again?
I’m a hero, not an ATM.
Hey, is this Naowjai
from the fried banana shop?
What’s going on?
Lately, the villagers
are really struggling.
They’re scared to walk past
the abandoned house at night.
They’ve been hearing
a female ghost wailing.
It’s giving everyone chills. Can you help?
What, you want me to fight a ghost?
Are you crazy?
It’s this house right here. It’s haunted.
Clear as day. The same house.
Even clearer now!
- Ghost, ghost, Granny! I saw a ghost!
- Ghost?
Where? Did you chase it away?
Don’t let it come in. Go away!
- Go away!
- Oh, Granny, stop, stop!
The ghost didn’t come.
It's at the abandoned house.
Oh.
If it were me,
I wouldn’t follow it either.
Hey, Thua, did you see a real ghost?
Kind of, but I don’t want to see one.
Even just hearing it gives me the chills.
And the villagers want us
to go fight the ghost?
- No way. Dream on.
- Wait a second.
It’s broad daylight.
How can a ghost appear?
- Oh.
- Jeez.
Granny, you don’t know anything!
When I went to the market,
they were all talking
about the haunted abandoned house.
They said it’s a pregnant ghost.
And in broad daylight,
it cries because it misses its baby.
But at night? It’s even worse!
Oh! You guys are so easily scared.
That’s why you believe
in all these ghost stories. Ridiculous.
Hmm, but why does it smell like this?
What?
Does the grape smell bad?
- Really?
- Where does it smell bad?
- Here, try it.
- Does it smell bad?
- How is it?
- Well, no, it actually tastes good.
- Yeah.
- Want another one?
Can you not make me
feel nauseous right now?
We can't let anyone know
about our situation yet.
Let's work together for now, okay?
Hey, Granny.
Bung.
You can tell me anything, you know.
I'm here for you, for everything.
I'm fine, Granny. I just don't like
this type of grape, that's all.
I used to not like weird foods
or strange smells, just like you.
When I was pregnant.
Bung,
I'm asking you seriously.
Are you pregnant?
Huh? Are you pregnant?
Huh? Pregnant?
I'm not!
But you look like
you've gained a lot of weight.
Hey, don't bully me.
I just gained weight, that's all.
I swear.
Hey!
It's time to deliver Laab to Tee.
I'll go deliver it myself. See you!
Hello, Ms. Kam.
Is there anything I can help with?
Oh no, what’s going on now?
So, what can I help with, Ms. Kam?
It's not just me who wants help.
The villagers are really struggling
and want the "Please be generous" team
to help out.
Just tell me, and I’ll pass it on
to the "Please be generous" admin.
You’re that close with them?
Can I get to know them too?
Hey, no, I can't.
If they find out, they won’t help.
It's a big secret.
Okay, fine. But this is kind of tricky.
I’m not sure they can help.
I don’t want to brag,
but there’s nothing
"Please be generous" can’t do.
They can help with anything.
Great! Could they help me get rid
of the ghost in that abandoned house?
What do you think, Thua? Can they help?
Of course, they can. No problem at all.
Thanks so much! That’s a huge relief.
Ms. Kam, there you are!
You should hurry home.
Ah is waiting for dinner.
Okay, I’m going now.
Thanks, Thua, take care!
Right. Yes.
Ms. Kam, how did you end up here?
If I didn’t have a motorcycle,
I wouldn’t dare come.
This place is haunted. Let’s go.
Take care, Thua!
Why would Ms. Kam ask me
to get rid of ghosts?
Why not tell the monk?
What am I supposed to do?
Oh!
What’s that sound?
This is the abandoned house.
…the haunted abandoned house.
They said it’s a pregnant ghost.
And in broad daylight, it cries
because it misses its baby.
Don’t tell me it’s true!
Sorry,
but don’t try to scare me.
I’m here to update you
about the "Please be generous" page.
- What’s that?
- Hey!
I heard a big project is coming up
to dismantle a human trafficking gang.
‪NEXT EPISODE
Bung, you're bleeding!
Bung!
She's safe now,
including the baby in the womb.
There’s a baby in there?
We can't let this go on.
It’s time to unleash our power.
Then, let’s go!
Subtitle translation by: Chonnikarn Ounob