You better shut up! Will you shut up?
Stop!
PREVIOUSLY
Typhoon!
At the shelter, they’ll help
take care of me and my mom,
and also find us a place to stay.
Typhoon, you finally
completed your mission, huh?
It’s really time for me to leave now.
Everyone. Let’s help Granny
search for her son, okay?
If only I’d been more decisive that day,
I could have stopped Arm
from going to work overseas.
There’s an update
on the human trafficking gang.
Let’s investigate it.
Either way, I’m not letting you out.
"If you go after me to Thua’s house,
I'll really run away from you for good."
I won’t give up! I’m going to separate
Kam from Thua, no matter what.
"My daughter is missing.
Her name is Phakbung."
Don’t reply to my mom’s messages,
or I'll run away from here,
and no one will ever find me again.
Don’t tell me
you’re here to convince me
to go back to Mom too.
I have no right to convince you.
because I don’t even know
what it feels like
to have time with a mom.
I'm not trying to be dramatic,
I’m just being honest.
I know how it feels to live
without a family.
Living without a family
is really lonely, Bung.
If you don’t go back,
your mom will probably feel lonely too.
It’s hard, though,
deciding between making her lonely
or breaking her heart.
What’s the right thing to do?
I can’t make that decision for you.
But if you decide to leave,
I’ll support you.
And if you don’t go back,
just remember.
This place can be your family too.
- Granny!
- What?
Hey, someone sent us a lead on our page
about the human trafficking gang.
We need to get to the warehouse!
- Let’s go, Phoon! Hurry up, Phoon!
- Thua!
- Huh?
- Phoon is staying with his mom now.
Oh, right!
So, it’s just me and you left, huh?
What about Bung? Let me call Bung first.
How’s it going?
She’s not answering. What should we do?
- Ms. Kam! Hold on. We’ve got Ms. Kam.
- Yeah.
Let me get the eggs off the stove.
Okay.
Okay, I’ll catch up in a bit.
Hey!
Seriously, Dad?
Today, you’re not running off anywhere.
I’m free,
and I want to spend time with you.
Did you ask me
if I want to spend time with you?
Kam.
If you’re running off to Thua’s place,
Seng and I are coming too.
Wherever or however
you want to save humanity,
I’m fine with it.
Well, I’m not fine with it!
This is the riverside warehouse
that the page follower reported.
Granny, they’re moving people right now!
That’s bad. You have to help them!
- But they have guns!
- Huh?
And I don’t have power like Phoon.
Can you really stop time?
I’m not sure about that. What do we do?
Or maybe it’s too risky.
Should we just leave it?
What about those people, though?
I’ll handle it!
- Hey, Phoon!
- Phoon!
How did you get here?
I called Kam, and she told me
everyone’s searching for Arm.
So, I asked Mom to let me come.
Don’t worry, Granny.
I’ll help you find Arm, no matter what.
Really, Phoon?
Thank you so much, dear.
Come here. Give me a hug! I missed you.
Wait, let’s get back to the mission.
I feel better now.
Come on. Let’s go!
Come on.
- Hey!
- Oh!
What is it, Phoon?
I didn’t mean to!
I just tried to grab the milk carton,
but my power acted on its own.
Right now, I don’t know what’s wrong.
I can’t control it.
Oh.
What a shame!
In that case, I'll stop time. Let’s go!
You said you were going to stop time,
so why are we here?
Yeah, wait.
Wait.
Look, we’ve gone back three hours!
Huh?
I don’t know!
I tried to stop time,
but it didn’t work.
Instead, it sent us back here!
Okay, Granny. Let’s think this through.
We need to get back to help them.
Oh.
We need to warp back. Go back now.
Go back?
- Warp back?
- Go back.
- Okay, I'll go back now!
- Hold her.
Hold her.
Hold.
- The same place!
- Huh?
We’re back to the present!
But they’re not here anymore.
- What the heck?
- You’re right, Thua.
Wait, let me try rewinding time again.
- Come on.
- Let’s do this, Granny.
- Hey, Granny!
- Granny!
What’s wrong?
I suddenly got this splitting headache.
Maybe you should rest for a bit.
Granny’s power is acting up.
Phoon’s power is also out of control.
Could it be that some higher force
is taking everyone’s powers away?
Huh?
Let’s rest for now.
If you’re calling just to say
there’s no progress,
I’m going to fire you.
Wait a moment! I’ve found your daughter.
What? Where?
I followed her to the bus community,
but then I lost track of her.
I’ll send you the location pin.
Alright, thank you very much!
Mom!
Excuse me. May I ask you something?
Stop for a moment, please.
Bung.
Bung, is that you? Why are you running?
Wait for me, Bung!
- Bung!
- Hey, the baby might slip out!
Your belly's big! Don't run!
Pregnant?
Bung is pregnant?
Everyone, this is bad!
- What’s wrong?
- Well…
My mom came here
and found out that I’m pregnant.
- Huh?
Are you sure that who you saw
was really Phakbung?
You said you only saw
the back of her, didn’t you?
She’s my daughter. Even if I only
saw her back, I’d recognize her.
Here’s all the information I have
on the human trafficking gang.
Thank you, Mr. Peem.
The information you provided
is very helpful to the police.
You're welcome, Officer. I’m determined
to do everything I can to help society.
Officer!
Please help my daughter!
She was kidnapped
by the human trafficking gang.
Here are pictures of our daughter.
My wife suspects
they’ve made her pregnant too.
Well, as soon as we found out,
we rushed home to find Title.
We really didn't know
the kid we helped
was the one everyone was looking for.
Phakbung is your daughter?
Do you know her?
Yes, I’ve met her before.
But she isn’t with
the human trafficking gang.
Is it going to dry out?
The powers are unstable, and now,
there's more trouble with Phakbung.
See, this is what they say.
Bad luck doesn’t come alone.
It brings its friends along.
So, what should we do? Can we help her?
Phakbung must be really upset.
She went to her room
and hasn’t come out since.
Should we go check on her, Granny?
Hmm, alright.
‪Let’s go.
Hello. Is anyone home?
Who are you looking for?
We’re looking for this girl.
Please open the door.
Phakbung, my daughter!
Phakbung!
The police are here.
Please open the door.
The clothes.
Gather the clothes, Phoon.
Alright, sure. Go ahead.
Feel free. Take your time.
Oh, who taught you
to hang the laundry like this, Phoon?
Thua hung them up.
Hurry up. Help out!
Oh no, it fell again.
Hurry!
Where is my daughter?
Um… Uh, well…
Search it, Officer.
Wait, calm down! What’s going on here?
Wait, Officer…
Well…
Thua.
Wait!
- Why can't we go upstairs?
- The room's a mess.
She must be upstairs!
Get out of the way. After you, Officer.
See? There’s nothing here.
I told you.
Wait a minute.
What about these clothes?
Who is the owner?
Hey!
These are Phakbung’s clothes!
And this is her bag.
These are definitely hers!
These are your child's, right?
- Yes, they are.
- Take him away.
Hey, calm down, Officer.
Wait! Let’s talk this over.
- Don’t resist, please.
- Whoa.
Where did you hide my daughter?
Tell me now!
Can we talk calmly, please?
Let’s talk at the station.
Where is my daughter?
- Calm down, Officer.
- Don’t resist, please.
Here, drink this, so you can calm down.
I know you’re worried,
but running away like this
isn’t the answer.
Please go back and meet your mom and dad.
No.
Why not? Don’t you trust your parents?
It’s because I know what they’re like,
that’s why I don’t want to see them.
Bung, listen to me.
Don’t be so pessimistic.
Oh, Bung, you’re here.
Bung, when did you come out?
Do you know we're in trouble now?
What happened?
It’s Peem.
He brought your mom to the house.
The police have already taken Thua.
Why did the police arrest him?
Because Bung’s parents think
he got Bung pregnant.
- Huh?
I didn’t kidnap anyone,
and I didn’t make Bung pregnant.
Please believe me.
But I remember
you were with Bung the whole time.
Well…
Okay, that part is true.
Then, confess.
How did you lure her?
And where is she now?
I don’t know
if I made the right choice or not
by running away from my parents.
If it were me,
I would go back and talk to my parents
and clear things up.
Whatever the outcome is,
I’ll deal with it later.
But they’ll be heartbroken, Thua.
See? Saying that means
you still care about your parents, huh?
Can you promise me something?
Please don’t tell anyone about this.
If my parents find out,
I want to be the one
to tell them everything.
But for now, I need some time to think.
Okay, I promise. I won’t say anything.
Listen, I really can’t say it.
Please understand.
Luring a minor is a criminal offense.
Even though you don't tell us,
you'll still end up in jail.
Hey! I’m telling you,
I didn’t lure anyone!
Please believe me.
I didn’t lure anyone. Please.
If you don't speak,
you’ll stay here for a while.
Take him to the cell.
Hey, what is this? Hey, Officer!
- You bastard! Give my child back!
- Ouch!
- Give my child back!
- Calm down.
Oh my, stop! Stop! Stop it!
Thua didn’t do anything wrong.
Officer, please let him go!
Thua didn’t lure anyone,
but he helped Phakbung.
She's pregnant. The baby doesn't have
a father, so she ran away from home.
Then she had an accident.
If Thua hadn’t helped her, we don’t know
what would have happened.
Bung is pregnant and without a father?
- Hey, dear!
- Oh my goodness!
Dear!
- Dear!
- Sit down at the table first.
Dear!
How is it?
If you’re worried like this,
why didn’t you go
with them from the start?
Did you hear everything, Ah?
Well…
I still can't bring myself
to face my parents.
Why?
Are your parents strict?
Or don’t they love you?
Seeing this reminds me
of when I was pregnant with Kam.
Uh, no.
I mean, her mom was pregnant.
I know. You don’t have to tell me.
It's a pity
that I didn’t make peace
with Chief Khachon back then.
He never had the chance to take care
of his only granddaughter
during such an important moment.
If I could turn back time,
I wouldn’t have made that mistake.
Well, back then, we didn’t know
if Chief Khachon would accept Kam.
I lost my chance,
but you still have time.
Kam.
How's Thua?
The police released Thua,
but your mom…
Huh? Mom?
What happened to my mom, Kam?
You can go home now, Thua.
MALE DETAINEE INTERROGATION ROOM
Alright.
I want to file a defamation complain.
Please take care of it, Officer.
It's part of the process.
If the suspect files a counterclaim,
it'll be a waste of time for the police.
Hey, but you’re not the police!
And you’re accusing me!
I won’t stand for it!
Why are you getting upset now, Thua?
Let’s go home.
He didn’t mean it.
Let’s just end it here.
I can’t, Granny. This is about my dignity!
Nonsense.
See? Clearly!
Officer, take care of this!
He’s accusing me again!
Hey! Where are you going?
Mr. Peem! I mean, Peem!
Officer, take care of this!
Yes, Ms. Kam?
Okay. I'll go now.
Uh…
Why did Bung come here, Kam?
I heard her mom’s not feeling well.
- This is bad.
- Why?
We haven’t told her
about the unstable powers yet.
What if she uses her healing power on
her mom? I wonder how that will turn out.
But from what I can tell,
my power and Granny's power
don’t seem too good either.
In that case, let’s split up
and look for her.
- Yeah.
- Let's go!
What happened?
- It’s nothing. Just a little bump.
- We'll go that way.
- Let’s go.
- Okay.
Mom.
I’m sorry.
Don’t, Bung. Trust me.
Why?
Bung.
Come out first. Trust me.
- Go.
- Let me go.
- I won’t let you go. Trust me.
- Bung.
- Sit down first.
- Sit down.
Sit down!
What’s going on here? Don’t you see
that my mom’s condition isn’t too good?
Bung, if you use your power,
your mom might get worse.
Everyone’s power is unstable right now.
Yesterday, I went to search for Arm.
Granny and I couldn’t control our powers.
Yes, I took everyone to the wrong place.
And he couldn’t control his power.
- Really, Granny?
- Yeah.
We wouldn’t lie
about something this important.
Here’s an idea. Just now, Thua got hurt.
Why not try using the power
and see what happens?
Let’s give it a try.
Come on.
- Come on.
- Good luck, Bung!
Ouch. Oh no.
- Hey, why did it turn out like that?
- Bung.
See? Do you believe us now?
Ouch!
From the information we've received,
we’ve been able to help
many victims of human trafficking.
We will continue to investigate
and target the masterminds behind it.
I heard this success was due to
your information, Mr. Peem. Is that true?
Yes. My team and I
are following this closely
and will keep working with the police
to dismantle this criminal organization.
Is it true that you're planning to run
for parliament
in the next election?
Wait a minute.
How did you hear about this?
- Is it true?
- Please answer.
Yes, it's true.
I ask for everyone’s support.
Okay, may I take a photo?
He's really handsome.
I almost had a famous son-in-law!
Hmm…
Hey, Kam.
Kam.
- What, Dad?
- Don’t you feel regretful about Peem?
No, Dad.
It wouldn't have worked out between us.
I'm more comfortable with Thua.
Hey!
Why are you bringing up Thua?
Don’t talk about him, please.
Fine, changing the topic.
Thanks, Dad.
- Thanks for what?
- For comforting Phakbung.
You knew?
How's she doing? Is she better?
Not yet, Dad. It’ll take time.
If I were pregnant without
a father like her, what would you do?
Oh!
My daughter,
always asking these questions.
Please answer, Dad.
Well, as parents,
when the child makes a mistake,
we still have to forgive them in the end.
So, if I were pregnant with Thua,
you'd be okay with it?
You're bringing up Thua again, huh?
- Bringing up him again? Shut your mouth!
- Just kidding, Dad.
- Don’t joke about it.
- Oh, just kidding.
- Next time, don’t mention him.
- Oh.
There’s no pregnancy. Nothing like that.
My head hurts.
The launch of your campaign
went really well.
The hashtag "Future MP Peem"
is trending too.
I must thank you, Nutty.
Without you, this wouldn’t have happened.
No, Peem, it's you who's amazing.
I only helped a little bit.
Is there anything you want?
I'll give you anything.
No need. I'm happy to help.
Thank you.
Mr. Peem, someone’s here to see you.
Peem, I need your help with something.
Thank you so much for agreeing to help me.
No problem. If there's any progress,
I'll update you right away.
Thank you.
Why are you wasting time
on something so small?
I sympathize. As a father, he probably
really wants to see his daughter.
Where did you take my daughter?
Isn’t this a bit much, Officer?
What’s the charge, Officer?
- Oh no.
- Officer!
You've been caught.
We've surrounded this place.
This cloth is the same as what
the "Please be generous" gang uses.
Does that mean those people
are the "Please be generous" heroes?
There is a kid, a pregnant woman,
and an elderly person.
Why didn’t I notice?
So, what do you want me to do next?
Keep an eye on them for now.
Got it.
I want to help my mom.
If something happens to her,
I’ll feel guilty for the rest of my life.
I understand.
But with our powers like this,
what can we do?
It’s not just your mom, Bung,
who needs help.
I’ve been getting a ton of inbox messages.
Hundreds!
Yeah, exactly.
So, how about we pick a case
and go after it?
Are you sure you want to go help?
What if it just makes things worse?
If you get caught, it’ll be a real mess.
I don’t want to just sit around.
The first thing we need to do
is figure out
why our powers are out of control.
How are we supposed to find that out?
Wherever we got our powers from,
that’s where we need to go.
I hope we’ll find the answer.
Let’s go. We need to hurry.
Let's go.
ROOM AVAILABLE, TEL: 099 2585192
Hey, have you guys noticed?
We haven’t heard anything about
the "Please be generous" gang lately.
Yeah, there’s a rumor they were taken out
by criminals. Is that true?
Are you crazy? What kind of criminal
could take them down?
They have superpowers!
But they’ve been quiet lately.
I sent them a message asking for help,
and no one replied.
Someone read my message,
but no one responded.
- Yeah.
- Same here!
Do you think
they’ve stopped helping people?
- Hmm.
- Huh?
Seems like those weird heroes
might be having some issues.
Then, let’s talk to them.
- Right.
- Excuse me.
I overheard you talking
about the "Please be generous" gang.
Is there something I can help with?
If there’s anything, let Peem know
if it’s about the community.
That’s right. I have a team
dedicated to solving social problems.
Yeah, he handles a lot of social issues.
- Really?
- Absolutely. Just tell me.
- That’s great! Please help…
- There's…
Me first. Someone keeps parking
in front of my house.
- We argue daily!
- I’ll handle it.
Please help!
Granny, do we really need all this stuff?
Of course! No one goes to pray
to sacred spirits empty-handed,
especially when asking for help.
If I were a spirit,
I wouldn’t want flowers.
I’d ask for snacks instead.
Don’t be silly, Typhoon!
Hey! Oh no!
- Thua.
- Huh, Granny?
I forgot the red soda!
Oh, Granny. What if the spirit’s
cutting back on sugar?
If we go back to buy it, we’ll be late!
Please, just one more thing.
It won’t be complete without it!
Don’t tell me we have to go back.
A man with a mustache buying hair clips?
Did you all see that?
He looks strange, doesn’t he, Thua?
Hey. When I bought flowers,
I noticed him earlier.
He acted the same way.
Is he following us?
- What does he want?
- Um…
Let’s find out!
- Gotcha!
One, two, three!
- Over here! Why do you follow women?
- What the heck!
Hey!
I almost lost the baby!
Is Thua still not here, Granny?
Right!
I think that guy’s following him,
so he's probably leading him away.
What should we do now?
Hello? Oh, Dr. Korn?
Is Mom’s condition critical?
Okay, I’ll head over right away.
- Go, go! Hurry to the hospital!
- Let's go.
- Hurry! Let's go.
- Alright.
Let's go!
I went to see Mr. Peem.
He promised to help find Bung.
You're here.
You tricked me!
Why did you lie,
saying Mom's condition was critical?
Don't you have anything better to do?
How did you know she’s my mom?
I saw the same last name.
And your mom’s missing child
isn’t exactly a secret.
Then tell me, why make me panic like that?
I’m sorry.
I was just really concerned about you.
I apologize for lying.
You still love and care about your mom.
Why don’t you go back to her?
You wouldn’t understand.
No, I don’t.
Why didn’t you do the right thing
when you had the chance?
And if something happens later,
you can’t fix it.
Are you prepared to carry
that guilt forever?
I…
Don’t do something you’ll regret later.
You don't know anything.
You can say whatever you want.
If I hadn’t run away from home,
they would have forced me to abort.
How do you know that?
Because I asked my mom.
I pretended it was for a friend,
but she couldn’t accept it.
What your mom said was just her thought.
She didn’t even know you were pregnant.
Stop talking. I’m leaving.
Doctor, please come to check
on the patient in room 3111.
Room 3111? That’s my mom’s room.
Hey!
Mom!
Bung, you should go out for now.
Do you think Thua will get caught, Granny?
Oh. I’m exhausted.
Bring me some water, please.
- Thua.
- So tired.
Why did you take so long?
I thought you got caught.
- Granny.
- Huh?
I won’t get caught easily,
but it took so long to shake him off.
He was really persistent.
Here, drink up first.
Who is he? Why is he following us?
I'm choking.
I don’t know, but it can’t be good.
Ugh.
Thua, Granny, Typhoon!
I thought I wouldn’t find anyone.
What’s up?
You didn’t check your phones, did you?
Huh?
Our page is getting flooded with insults.
I'M DISAPPOINTED - YOU ALL ARE CRUEL
LIARS - SCAMMER
They say we didn’t really
want to help people.
Well, our powers aren’t working right now.
What should we do?
Should we find a case
that’s easier to handle first?
No need. They’re upset
because someone else
is handling things for us.
So, they think we’re just sitting around.
Who did it for us?
Peem.
Does Peem know our secret now?
I’m going to expose all of them
and turn their supporters
into my base of power.
Someone from our page messaged
about finding an escaped illegal worker
from human traffickers.
- Arm!
- Really?
Without powers,
we can’t help Arm on our own.
We need to find a way
to get our powers back to normal.
Tell us where the person who ran off is.
Go ask him in hell.
Power of destruction!
Subtitle translation by: Chonnikarn Ounob