Madam is tired
Why don't you take a rest in bed?
Forget it.
There's no need to sleep too long before death.
You'll fall into a deep sleep after death.
Madam.
What are you doing here?
What's going on? What's going on?
Don't mention it.
After I showed the painting
to the master,
she wanted to
as a closed disciple.
He gave me such a big embroidery cloth.
and asked me to embroider a painting of mountains and rivers.
and asked me to finish it in 100 days.
I really...
Madam Sun appreciates you.
This is a good thing.
What's good about it?
I shouldn't have done this.
Don't worry.
No matter how much blood I bleed,
I'll help Her Ladyship
for Her Ladyship.
Forget it.
Your hands are stitched.
Stop embroidering.
It's... It's...
In fact,
I always
because the seat is too hard.
I got hurt because I kept changing my posture.
If I can sit
on the corner of the bed,
You won't get hurt.
You...
You can sit wherever you want.
I don't know
why you came together.
I was so surprised.
Why are you sleeping on the bed?
I helped Her Ladyship embroider till midnight last night.
I didn't sleep on the floor
so I didn't sleep on the floor.
So...
Have you forgotten the rules?
I'm going to
write a self-criticism for Her Ladyship.
Enough.
Don't you have
in the morning?
Go ahead.
I'll take my leave then.
You've been embroidering for the whole night.
It didn't move at all.
Chuntao.
Her Ladyship just got up.
Prepare some breakfast for her.
Okay.
Zi Mu.
After the court meeting,
after the court meeting.
Find a way
to send Her Ladyship there.
Master.
I dare not lie to you.
Prince Yu, you lied to me again.
You keep saying
to sit on the bed for embroidery.
But I didn't get any stitches.
and slept with me all night.
Zimu, I'll leave this to you.
I'm going to the court.
Father-in-law.
After eating
you and Mother-in-law made yesterday,
after you and Mother-in-law made.
She insisted on going back to her maiden home.
and have another meal.
How old are you?
Just go back if you want.
Zi Yu, back then,
your father-in-law
was a cook
in the barracks.
In terms of cooking skills,
the imperial chefs in the palace
are not as good as me.
I'm ashamed.
I should learn
from your father-in-law.
Don't mention it.
How about this?
You can go home with me.
Let Xinhuan
go home by herself.
I'll do as you say, Father-in-law.
Let's go.
Madam, calm down.
His lordship has a court meeting this morning.
If it's really for one night,
I wouldn't be in the mood.
But he can't lie to me.
I feel bad for his wound.
Yes.
But Rong Chuntao,
To be honest,
embroidery is originally a needlework.
It's not easy
who is willing to embroider for you
to embroider for you.
Madam.
The kitchen was on fire just now.
If you eat later,
the mansion won't be able to do it.
The kitchen.
Fire!
It's on fire.
I just ordered it.
Dad, mom.
Xin Huan is here.
Why are you dawdling?
How long have we been waiting for you?
Let's stop waiting.
Let's eat.
Eat. The dishes are getting cold.
Come, Zi Yu.
I haven't forgiven you
you lied to me last night.
I fell asleep last night.
Please forgive me.
Lower your voice.
I'll forgive you this time.
If you have
lie to me,
Then I...
Don't worry.
I will never lie to you again.
I forgive you
I forgive you.
Well, Your Ladyship,
this time?
can you
feed me so much?
I know.
What do you want to eat?
This one.
Is it good?
Yes.
One more
Be careful, madam.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Let me see.
Madam.
This...
You lied to me again.
No.
Madam.
You misunderstood me.
This...
Xin Huan.
You were fine just now.
What's going on?
Prince Yu.
Tell me the truth.
Did you lie to me?
Madam, I...
Xinhuan.
Madam.
Master.
Madam, let me explain.
Madam.
I know I was wrong.
I don't want to see you.
Madam.
I promise you.
I promise.
I don't want to hear any promise from you.
Everyone says I'm unruly and willful.
and made you suffer.
But every time
every time.
I fell into your trap.
You're the good guy.
I'll always be the one being scolded.
Madam.
I hate you.
I don't want to be with you.
I bought you some ointment.
I was chased three blocks.
I begged my grandparents
before they sold it to me.
I didn't tell you
about these things.
Because I want to
to feel at ease.
Because I'm afraid...
I'm afraid I'll fall for you.
I'm afraid that you...
just want to
with me.
Xin Huan.