Your Ladyship.
I know I was wrong.
You're not wrong.
I was wrong.
I shouldn't have believed that you really love me.
Madam, I'm wronged.
Kneel.
Okay.
Take yours out too.
Let's see
find someone to trap me.
I'm still angry.
Write 800 words of self-criticism now.
Don't sleep until you finish.
As long as you are not mad at me,
let alone 800 words,
Even if...
Go.
Yes, madam.
A new mission is about to begin.
The second round of hide-and-seek.
Go.
There's a thief picking flowers in the city.
Prince Yu knows the master of Pingyuan City.
If I leave without saying goodbye,
if I leave without saying goodbye.
Excuse me.
I can't tell who it is.
Not at all.
Who can tell who is wearing a mask?
Instead of being caught by Prince Yu,
it's better to
for him first.
Okay.
Got it.
Brothers and sisters,
Whether you can catch the flower thief
depends on you.
Catch the flower thief!
Catch the thief!
Prince Yu.
Where is he?
Madam.
This is your favorite cake in Pingyuan City.
And this.
You must like it.
Why do you still have money?
It's really gone now.
No. Look.
Prince Yu.
Are you a kangaroo?
Why do you have
so much money bags?
Madam.
I'm afraid of being robbed by robbers.
This is also for
for safety.
To be safe,
I don't believe you.
Stop!
You...
Take it off.
Madam, it's really gone.
Really.
Take it off.
Prince Yu.
Don't you hurt your foot?
I...
I'm weak.
I just wanted to wear it like this.
to look tall.
Your...
Son.
Madam, don't be angry.
Sit down.
Sit.
Look.
What?
I bought you new shoes.
Try them on.
Ma'am.
Get up and walk.
It looks nice.
She's indeed a perfect match for you.
You're so handsome.
I almost forgot the business.
Dear.
I like the shoes you gave me.
I don't know what to do.
It's all because you're beautiful.
You look good in anything.
Honey, you're exaggerating.
However,
I saw a wanted warrant
a wanted warrant for a flower thief.
I was thinking
if I get caught by him,
then...
Madam.
I won't let the plunders succeed.
You're right.
The best defense is to attack.
How about
we arrest him
tonight.
Your Ladyship is a loyal person.
I feel ashamed.
But...
Her Ladyship is fine.
Why don't you let the government do this?
I want to help the people.
This...
My dear.
As long as you are willing,
I won't frown
I will never frown.
But we need to plan
we need to make a plan.
No.
I have a plan.