(Assemble and upgrade.)
(The journey for the perfect 7)
PROJECT 7.
(The beginning of the Assembly)
(Self Assembly)
(Trainees assembled
their teams on their own...)
(and upgraded the teams.)
(The Title Song performance was
made by assembly and upgrade.)
(The second assembly)
(Position Matching)
(Vocal, dance, rap)
(By assembling and upgrading once again, )
(70 trainees survived.)
(And)
(World Assemblers participated...)
(in the third assembly, Rival Matching.)
(Two rival teams assembled by
World Assemblers' choice clashed.)
(Contrasting results)
(The fourth assembly, Original Matching)
(Performing new songs...)
(was the final test for the Final Match.)
(Selected by World Assemblers
in about 180 countries...)
(for 4 months' journey, )
(21 trainees survived.)
(Among them, the number
of people who can debut...)
(is only 7.)
(Surviving the Final Match, )
(who will be the last 7...)
(to run toward their goal of debuting?)
You can do it!
Nice!
Go for it!
("RUN" by PROJECT 7)
(100 trainees ran together for 1 goal)
("RUN")
(The first step towards their dream)
Hello. Thank you in advance.
("RUN", the first step towards their dream)
I wondered if I could have...
a dream of being an idol.
It started with that question,
and I challenged myself first.
There were so many awesome
people older than me in the waiting room,
so I was very intimidated.
At first, I thought it'd
be a good experience.
I decided to enjoy it and do my best.
I was so excited about
starting something new.
To those who thought I
won't be able to debut,
I wanted to show that I could.
This challenge started from that anger.
So I decided to prove myself...
and thought I could
debut if I prove myself.
That's how I engaged myself in this.
I began to dream of being an
idol when I was ten years old,
and I've run for it until
now without a break.
I had so many moments of trouble.
So many of them.
(The infinite unknown: Our
dream wasn't an easy one.)
I have been a trainee since I was little.
As I experienced a slump,
there were so many
moments I wanted to give up.
I wanted to become an idol,
so I came to Korea alone, and it was tough.
But I practiced hard.
I was most worried about
doing well in the show.
I participated in the
show risking many things.
I'm afraid I might not
show anything I have here.
Compared to what I thought,
I might not be good enough.
So I wanted to give up many times.
(We could get this far thanks to...)
("Up to you")
I realized that there are
people who came to see me.
It just feels like a dream.
I wonder if everything I'm
doing now is reality or not.
Every word of support...
really encourages me,
and I appreciate that.
I've found the reason
why I want to perform.
For those people, I've decided
to make it, no matter what.
I worked hard.
I worked hard with all my heart.
(I'm running, I'm almost there)
I'll give the last performance here soon.
Getting this far...
was very intense.
I didn't think I'd make
it to the Final Match.
I'm afraid it might be my last performance.
My dream of making a debut
became more desperate.
I could run this far since I
wanted to realize my dream.
I want to shine on the stage.
I want to be an idol and realize my dream.
- My dream... - My dream...
It's making my debut.
The dream of making my
debut was the beginning.
When I started to dream
it, I met PROJECT 7.
Since it's the last performance,
I want to give a performance
that I won't regret.
(I want the last performance
to be something I won't regret.)
(MC Lee Soo Hyuk)
In September 2024,
two hundred trainees,
for a dream of becoming an idol,
participated in PROJECT 7.
And here, now,
after going through five projects,
twenty-one trainees who were...
assembled and upgraded remain here.
Twenty-one trainees here...
are on the stage they've dreamed of...
through PROJECT 7.
And today, finally,
these trainees...
will complete the last
project for their dream,
their debut.
Who will be the trainees
selected by the World Assemblers...
and make their debut?
The top seven members who will debut...
as a global top-class idol group...
will only he decided...
by the hands of the World Assemblers.
PROJECT 7,
the final project will be broadcast live.
And the fates of the trainees...
depend on the last global voting.
The voting begins now.
Assemble your very own idols.
Let's assemble.
World Assemblers.
Soon, the real-time global
voting for the Final Match...
of PROJECT 7 begins.
(PROJECT 7's real-time
global voting for the Final Match)
The final result of the
Final Match is decided...
by summing up the 4th
global voting score for 4 weeks,
the real-time global voting
score during the live broadcast,
and the Director's benefit score.
The real-time global voting...
is available on PROJECT
7's official platform...
during the live broadcast,
and you can participate once.
Access the PROJECT 7 community...
and click on the voting link...
to participate in two kinds of voting.
The first one is the Individual Vote.
Among 21 trainees,
select 1 trainee you support,
(Vote 1 trainee you support. It
will be reflected in the ranking.)
Second, the Assembly
Vote for the final debut group.
(Select 7 trainees you want to
assemble your very own idols.)
Select seven trainees
you support for their debut...
and press the complete button
to complete your participation.
You need to participate in both
so that your votes are reflected.
So make sure you participate in both.
KANG HYUNWOO,
KIM SUNGMIN,
KIM SIHUN,
KIM JEONGMIN,
KIM HYUNWOO,
NAM JIWOON,
LYNNLYNN,
MAJINGXIANG,
PARK JUNSEO,
BINGHUA,
SAKURADA KENSHIN,
SEO KYOUNGBAE,
SONG SEUNGHO,
AHN JUNWON,
ANDY,
WOO HAJOON,
YOO YOUNGSEO,
YICHEN,
JANG YEOJUN,
JEON MINWOOK,
and JUNG SEYUN.
World Assemblers,
please vote for the trainees you support.
Let's assemble.
Five,
four,
three,
two,
one.
It starts now.
(Voting starts. It will end
during the live broadcast.)
Assemble your very own idols.
PROJECT 7 is broadcast live.
Hello, I'm MC Lee Soo Hyuk.
(MC Lee Soo Hyuk)
It's already been four months...
since I met the World Assemblers.
I remember that when I first met you...
I felt as nervous as the trainees.
And I still can't forget...
the trainees' eyes that had dreams...
when they first appeared on the stage.
Every Friday,
I was so happy to meet
the World Assemblers.
Until now, we've seen the Zero Setting,
the Title Song, the Position Matching,
the Rival Matching,
(KIM SIHUN)
and the Original Matching.
World Assemblers saw...
every moment...
the trainees grew, staying closest to them.
Now, we have...
only one left,
the last project to
assemble the debut team.
Among 200 trainees...
who participated in PROJECT 7,
only 21 trainees are waiting...
for the last votes by the World Assemblers.
Since all 21 trainees are qualified...
with talents to be an idol,
it's very difficult to predict
which one will debut.
Tonight,
by your votes, World Assemblers,
the debut team members will be selected.
Starting today,
according to the global voting score,
a total of 7 people in 1st to 7th place...
are not trainees anymore.
They will take the first step
as an idol through a debut.
Since the third Passing Ceremony to today,
the fourth global voting
has been on for a week.
The real-time voting score
during the live broadcast...
and...
the scores given by
the directors are added...
to decide the final
ranking of the trainees.
For the real-time voting, one
person can participate once.
It consists of the Individual
Vote and the Assembly Vote.
Also,
the votes cast during the live broadcast...
will be counted twice.
The real-time voting will
close after an hour from now.
Please remember that.
For the last week,
the fourth global voting was conducted.
From about 180 countries,
World Assemblers
participated in the voting.
For the trainees in PROJECT 7,
World Assemblers are sending
continuous support and attention.
I give my sincere gratitude for that.
World Assemblers,
which trainee's debut are you supporting?
(KIM SIHUN, let's make your debut!)
And,
(SEO KYOUNGBAE, please make your debut!)
would that trainee be able to realize...
his dream of making a debut tonight?
- Yes! - Yes!
Since the fate of 21
people is in your hands,
until the moment the debut team is created,
please stay with us to the end.
To witness the moment the debut
team is created from the closest,
here in Namdong Gymnasium,
five thousand World Assemblers joined us.
Thank you for coming
here in the cold weather.
Please send your support to the end.
(Incheon Namdong Gymnasium,
final special live broadcast)
(LYNNLYNN)
Now,
here's the last project...
trainees need to go
through for their debut.
I will now announce the
name of the last project.
The last project...
is the Final Match.
(Last project, Final Match)
Final Match is the final project
to be an important standard...
for selecting the final
members of the debut team.
World Assemblers,
according to your assembly,
each seven trainees built a team...
and three performances
in total were prepared.
As they are on the
threshold of their debut,
they prepared the
performances intenser than ever.
Please look forward to seeing it.
(You're the only one I
can see, JUNG SEYUN.)
(AHN JUNWON, I love you.)
This is the last time.
We only have the final
project performances left.
I feel very nervous as
much as trainees are tense.
And I see many people
excited and nervous...
for the trainees they support.
Until the trainees could come
up to the live broadcast stage,
these people guided them.
Without their help, the trainees...
wouldn't have been able to
prepare for perfect performances.
They are...
the directors of PROJECT 7.
(Ryan Sewon Jhun, Ha Sung Woon, )
(Lee Hae In, Bada, RyuD)
I've been to the Project Village
once to cheer trainees up,
and I saw them giving lessons so hard,
day and night with the trainees...
to show great performances.
That made me feel a lot of emotions.
Now I'll ask some questions to them.
Director Bada.
Hello, I'm Director Bada.
I heard PROJECT 7...
was in charge of increasing
your dopamine level.
Please say a word.
Yes.
I think not only I, but also
many World Assemblers...
had their dopamine and
endorphin increased watching it.
In fact, I felt happy...
not only on Friday but also at
every moment with the trainees.
And I hope today, the 21
trainees on the great stage...
do not get nervous and show
everything they want to show.
You can do it!
Now, based on his own experience,
he always gave sincere advice.
Here's Director Ha Sung Woon.
Hello, I'm Ha Sung Woon.
Since you've been through
the same moment like this,
you'd understand how the
trainees feel more than anyone.
- Yes. - Please say...
a word to cheer the trainees up.
First of all, you've worked so hard...
until you get to the Final Match.
Now, I actually think that
you can make a debut.
So, I hope you don't get nervous
and finish the performance well.
This is the beginning.
Today, I hope you run towards your dream.
You can do it!
(Ha Sung Woon)
Sometimes as a strict instructor,
and sometimes as a warm senior singer,
the directors guided them well,
so they could put on great performances.
And this was the trainees'
last class from them.
We have the video of their class.
The last class of PROJECT 7.
We will watch it...
now.
- Let's just begin. - Okay.
- All right. - Someone will light them up.
- When he places it down
like this, - One at a time.
- Bring it? - Someone has to make a path.
- Here. - I'll light and place them.
(Everyone seems busy with
something for some reason.)
How do I cut this?
Hey, can I do this instead?
- "A lot." - "A lot."
That's good. Let's go with that.
- Gosh, it could've pricked me.
- You're working so hard on it.
Gosh, I love throwing
surprise events like this.
(What is this event the
trainees have prepared?)
My gosh, I'm going in.
Are you okay?
(The kindness of teachers)
- Gosh, I'm not going in. - What? Go in.
- No. You go in first.
- Come on, go inside.
- I'm not going in. It's too much.
- Come in.
My gosh, what's all this?
- What is this? - Oh, my.
(Feeling awkward)
No way.
My gosh.
- What is this? - I can't do this.
- Oh, my. - We have to go like this.
- Goodness. - I can't believe this.
(They barely make it to the heart zone.)
Did you guys do this?
- No one's ever done this for me.
- Gosh, look at that.
Goodness, this is so sweet.
(An hour ago)
- Hey, that's way too dense.
- Aren't they too spread apart?
- Really? - No.
The candles on that
side are too spread out.
We might run out of them.
- So I widened the gaps. - Right.
- Let's go with this for now.
- Yes, let's do this.
- We'll widen them later.
- Let's move them later.
Okay. Let's stop there. We
have to spread them out again.
- Like this again? - Yes.
Or we could close this part in like this.
(It's not easy to make a
candlelit path for the surprise.)
- Let's spread them out a bit more.
- Hold on.
- The path should be longer. - Come here.
Okay. I realized something with this today.
I won't ever use candles
when I propose to a girl.
- Here? - Yes, there.
- Here? - Yes.
(Let's decorate the wall now.)
Is it not sticking well?
(The height only makes him laugh.)
- JIWOON. - Jump.
Or you hold onto it here.
There.
(Barely touching the paper)
- Anyone over 180cm? - Yes!
- Yes. - Can you come and help?
- Sure. - Yes.
- Can you come and help?
- Anyone over 180cm?
Do you need help?
YOUNGSEO, you said
your height was over 180cm.
I'm slightly under 180cm.
- Can you press on the tapes?
- Can you get the tapes?
- Great. - My gosh. You're so tall.
Nice.
What is a good message?
Something simple.
What a great sight.
- Did you finish? - It does look like...
we're doing our best.
- Whom is this present for?
- Ryan Sewon Jhun.
- Ryan Sewon Jhun? - Yes.
What should we do with this?
- What do you think we should do?
- It's so cute.
This is for Director Hae In.
- I should write that.
- It resembles her, right?
Director Bada...
I know her well.
She likes the right side of her face.
So...
I have to cover up her left side...
to show her right side with the bandanna.
I think that will make her happy.
(I did a good job, didn't I?)
(This guy is customizing the doll too.)
This is fun.
KYOUNGBAE. Are you good at sewing?
No.
(He's sewing for the
first time in his life.)
Okay. I did it right.
(His sewing skills are
improving little by little.)
Nice.
- Grab it like this.
- You can grab it like that.
(They work on the teddy bears
from the bottom of their heart.)
- Hey. - Isn't this cute?
What if they're so touched by our presents?
(Director Bada)
(They also signed the paper
with messages for directors.)
(Director Hae In)
Baby fairies, let's start.
- Start. - What? There's more.
- Let's go, cuties. - What's this?
- My gosh. - The babies.
(Dear Directors)
(They express their
gratitude all of a sudden.)
(Hello)
"Hello."
(Actually...)
(We...)
Let's make your singing sound sweeter.
(Singing more sweetly)
(You guys helped us a lot.)
(Feeling proud)
(So we're grateful.)
(We love you.)
Me too.
- Yes. - This is amazing.
We love you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Seriously.
- Thank you. I mean it.
- This could've been grander.
- It's not over yet. - What?
- What? - This one is for you, Director Ha.
- What's this? - No way.
- A doll. - And we all signed the paper.
- Really? This is amazing. - No way.
Director Hae In. I made this for you.
- Really? Thank you. - When you press this,
- you'll hear our recorded message. - Okay.
- Director Hae In is awesome!
- Director Ryan. Let's meet again.
Wait.
- Director RyuD. - Director RyuD.
(Each teddy bear has its unique message.)
Great!
- Really? - We personally...
- recorded messages in the dolls.
- Please accept our heart!
"Please accept our heart!"
So cute.
- We need luck. - We need luck.
- Thank you. - Luck named you!
What? You spoke without the honorifics.
Seriously.
Did you also decorate the paper?
- Yes. - Yes.
Did you also print it out?
- This is cute. - This is incredible.
- My gosh. Thank you.
- I'll hang it on the wall.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- I'll frame it and keep it. - Thank you.
- Totally. - Thank you.
They had fun with the event we prepared.
Seeing them being happy with
our presents brought joy to me too.
Our effort to prepare this
was completely worth it.
- Thank you. - Teaching you paid off.
- Thank you. Let's clean it up. - Nice.
- Hurry up.
- You guys should clean this up.
Actually,
we also prepared something for you guys.
- What? - We'll reveal it here?
- I'm going to cry. - No way.
- Really? - My gosh.
(They wrote letters for all 21 trainees.)
(They wrote down each word
from the bottom of their heart.)
(BINGHUA, NAM JIWOON, WOO HAJOON)
(You've been my number
one pick. I bet you didn't know.)
(I've become a fan of yours
through this show, HYUNWOO.)
(I'll always root for you.
(I know you'll do well.)
(You always work hard to reach your goal.)
We only had to write a
message to five directors.
But they wrote a message for 21 people.
- MINWOOK. - Really?
- Thank you. - HAJOON.
My goodness.
- Inside... - This is amazing.
- Oh, my. - Gosh.
- HYUNWOO. - Thank you.
- LYNNLYNN. - YEOJUN.
- Yes. Thank you. - Where's LYNNLYNN?
- Oh, my. - LYNNLYNN.
- Could we read it now? - LYNNLYNN.
- This is... - My gosh.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - My gosh.
- No way. There's a picture of me.
- This is unbelievable.
(Marines don't cry.)
You can't cry, come on.
Oh, my!
My goodness.
"I can feel sincerity
in everything you do."
"It made me think that you were
an amazing kid for your age."
"In due time,"
"everyone will see the time,
effort, and heart you put into this."
During my journey on PROJECT
7, there hasn't been a moment...
I wasn't giving my all.
I always gave my best to this.
She wrote that she could see it.
It felt like I earned her recognition.
"Hello, KYOUNGBAE."
"I was truly shocked when
you came to our booth."
"You reminded me of my young self."
She said I reminded
her of her younger self.
I'm feeling confident now.
Do you like yours?
"Dear SEYUN." And there's a heart too.
(Giggling)
"I bet it's been tough."
"But I trust that you're
learning a lot here."
"I truly hope you can shine for your team."
"Dear SEUNGHO who is
handsome and good at everything."
"Well done. I want to applaud
you for your hard work."
"I'll root for your dream."
"Keep running like this."
"Let's meet on stage someday. Good luck."
(Sniffling)
I keep hearing sniffling sounds.
(Where?)
"You have more days..."
I think SUNGMIN is crying way too much.
"Show us..."
"SUNGMIN, you were in my class."
"It must've been tough to be in my class."
Try it.
Yes. That's it. Did you see that?
"Thank you for always being so positive..."
"and trying your best
instead of giving up."
"All of your hard efforts will
come back and help you later."
"I'll always wish you luck."
Getting the letter in person...
made me more emotional.
You're crying way too much. Come on.
Why are you crying so much?
YOUNGSEO is crying too? My gosh.
It looks like the guys
in black are all crying.
(This guy in black is also crying.)
(Feeling proud)
I'm really grateful.
Right, me too.
Some of you will make a debut.
But some of you will not.
That could be...
because it's not your time yet.
If you keep working hard like this,
maybe, we'll be able to see each other...
at the top one day.
I've experienced that firsthand too.
I hope you'll keep trying.
Then we might be able to
see each other at the top.
Why do I feel like I'm going to cry?
- Hold on. - Don't cry.
I'm a feeling type. Okay.
(Feeling her emotions too)
First of all,
as the director of this show, PROJECT 7,
I had always given my best to you.
Personally, I wanted
to teach you guys a lot.
It was an honor that I could
be part of your journey...
to make a debut as a team.
And... Why do I feel like
I'm going to choke up?
Cry!
It was an honor.
(Are you crying?)
I'll help you all the
way to the last mission.
I know too well how you guys feel. So...
Don't cry.
My gosh.
I wasn't going to cry.
(Don't cry.)
Anyway,
I'll keep rooting for you guys to the end.
I would be thankful...
if you guys don't lose
the passion you have now.
- Okay. - Good luck.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
It felt like a goodbye.
It didn't feel like it
had been a long time.
But the show is already nearing its end.
I haven't shown the best
version of myself so far.
I'm grateful that they
didn't give up on me.
It really felt like the last mission.
I realized that I could give my all
because I met such good directors.
Attention, everyone.
(Showing their respect to
the directors one last time)
Bow to the directors.
- Thank you for everything.
- We love you. - We love you.
- We love you. - Thank you.
Thank you.
(As they hope to meet again...)
- Directors, let's meet again.
Wait for us.
(Run with us, Directors.)
During the trainees' journey on PROJECT 7,
the directors cherished
them wholeheartedly.
Director Ryan Sewon Jhun.
Yes.
It sometimes seemed you
didn't care about the cameras.
You truly cared for them
from the bottom of your heart.
- Yes. - After this,
you won't be able to
see them as often as now.
Would you like to say
something to the trainees?
So today is the final episode of the show.
I couldn't sleep well last
night. I was sad that it was over.
I am not a father yet.
But I treated and thought
of them as my own sons.
Actually, I had trouble
sleeping last night.
So that's where I am now. But I don't know.
I still consider myself a student of music.
I'm studying idol groups
and K-pop every day.
The thing is, I don't settle for less.
Well, some of the trainees
were eliminated, unfortunately.
I thought a lot about what kind
of helpful message I could give...
to you and the trainees
who will debut soon.
So I'd like to say this.
Don't settle for less.
Keep looking ahead and look up to the sky.
I hope you will become brave
kids who can keep charging forward.
And love yourselves.
Whatever happens today,
tomorrow might give you
something entirely different.
So I don't want you to
settle for less. That's my wish.
Here's my conclusion. Feel
the new vibe and the time.
As you feel the vibe, keep
challenging yourselves.
So you could become people
who can open up the next chapter.
Lastly,
thanks to the fans who
came here to see the trainees,
these trainees can perform.
So I just want to thank everyone.
Please love and support them,
so they could be a great team
together. And cheer for them too.
Thank you.
Thank you for your sincere advice.
Director RyuD.
Yes.
You taught them the fundamentals
of dance in an organized way.
Your affection for the
trainees must run deep.
Could you give them a
message as they wait to perform?
First of all, I mostly deal
with intense choreographies.
So the trainees who learned
from me must have had a hard time.
There were times I made them
practice 1 move over 50 times.
Because I wasn't a
talented dancer at first,
I wanted them to perform well...
even if they weren't the best dancers.
I really hope that my lessons come
in handy when they make a debut.
I also want to wish them
luck for tonight's performance.
I hope everyone walks away from
this with good, happy memories.
Thank you.
She cried quite a lot
during the last class.
Director Lee Hae In.
Could you also give a
message to the trainees?
I couldn't stop crying.
I became emotional just
by watching the video.
Firstly, due to the nature of the show,
we must often give them harsh feedback.
But they only got one
or half a day to practice...
before we evaluated them.
I would like to tell them that
what we see on this show...
doesn't reflect all the
potential they have.
And no one knows...
about their potential
better than themselves.
I want to tell them to trust...
the time and effort they put into this.
I hope they do their best
today as they have always done.
I'll root for them too. Good luck.
(YOO YOUNGSEO, the best vocalist)
(JEON MINWOOK, the shiniest star)
Before we begin the Final Match,
I will make an announcement...
everyone must be itching to find out.
Tonight,
a global top-class idol group...
will be formed.
The name of the group.
(The name of the debut
group will be revealed.)
I'm sure everyone here is curious...
about the name of the group...
that the top seven
trainees will perform under.
The name...
of PROJECT 7's final debut group...
will be...
revealed now.
(I can't wait!)
I can't wait.
The name of the final debut group...
will be revealed now.
We close our eyes for
countless moments in a day.
All the brief moments we close our eyes...
Even the moment we close our eyes...
CLOSE YOUR EYES.
All right.
The name...
of PROJECT 7's debut group is...
CLOSE YOUR EYES.
The group will captivate the audience...
not only through their performance...
but also with their music,
even with their eyes closed.
Every time the audience
closes and opens their eyes,
the group will transform...
into the idol group of their
dreams and continue improving.
I wonder...
which trainees...
will debut as members of CLOSE YOUR EYES.
Stay tuned to find out.
Moreover, CLOSE YOUR EYES...
will debut with the sponsorship...
of UNCORE, a joint label of YG PLUS, SLL,
and STUDIO SLAM.
They plan to perform actively...
on music shows and concert tours.
CLOSE YOUR EYES
will be a global idol group.
You can visit the social
media page of the group,
CLOSE YOUR EYES,
to find out about their future activities.
Please show them your
support and wish them luck.
All right. Let me ask another question.
Director Ryan.
Yes.
The name of the group has been revealed.
What do you think?
First of all, let me close my eyes.
I can see seven guys.
CLOSE YOUR EYES.
That has a nice feel
to it. What do you think?
They like it. And I like it too.
All right.
This will play a huge role
in selecting the trainees...
for the final debut group.
This last project will
be an important factor...
for the selection.
It's time for their Final Match.
The World Assemblers put
together 3 groups of 7 trainees.
"ACT UP."
"Antidote." "PSYCHO."
We will watch three
performances from the trainees.
Moreover, after the Third Passing Ceremony,
the voting clips for the
highlights of the songs aired.
The World Assemblers...
selected the members
to perform the highlights.
Which trainees got the honor...
of performing the
highlights at the Final Match?
(Which trainees won the
highlights of the songs?)
The selected trainees...
(Always PARK JUNSEO)
(Let's debut, WOO HAJOON.)
(KENSHIN)
You will find out through the video.
The first new song of the Final Match...
is "ACT UP." We will watch...
their training process
and their performance...
for the very first time.
(The performance of "ACT
UP" will be revealed soon.)
Let's watch it now.
- Nice to meet you. - Yes.
Nice to meet you.
Let's begin.
- Let's go. - Okay.
(They watch the choreography
video of "ACT UP" first.)
You can come closer to watch it.
(Director Bada created the choreography.)
(Impressed)
The choreography was really cool.
The choreography was totally my style.
It was really cool.
I love it. I love all of it.
I love the choreography.
Director Bada is indeed the best.
(Chuckling)
That's so cool.
(Unlike other trainees, ANDY
seems especially unhappy.)
I couldn't get the part I wanted.
When I was watching it,
I thought I wouldn't
stand out during my part.
Because he was able to push me out,
I ended up with a different part.
(It was Trainee AHN JUNWON's
turn to push out a trainee for his part.)
- He usually... - LYNNLYNN.
(He took the main vocalist's
role and pushed out LYNNLYNN.)
YICHEN is going to be the lead vocalist.
No!
Please.
(Trainee JUNG SEYUN was
inserted into Trainee ANDY's spot.)
(Then Trainee ANDY lost the
spot to Trainee PARK JUNSEO.)
(What? What's he doing?)
(That's just weird now.)
(JUNWON suddenly changed everything.)
(I was really angry.)
(Trainee AHN JUNWON brought
major changes to their positions.)
(Sighing)
Do you not like this part?
No.
I thought that some of my teammates...
wouldn't be happy with my decision.
I could clearly see that ANDY...
and YICHEN weren't happy with the changes.
I realized that...
I had a small part.
JUNWON pushed me down.
Other than that, I'm
just disappointed that...
this is our final performance.
It will be my last
performance on PROJECT 7.
So that's a bit disappointing.
My part is really minimal.
I'm done.
(Vocalizing)
(Giggling)
Since this is our final
performance, I want us...
to practice in a friendly
mood without any conflicts.
I hope we can get along
while preparing for it.
Okay. No problem.
Actually, I don't mind...
if I don't have a singing
part in this performance.
Completing the stage well is important.
It's okay even if I don't get a part.
(But there was a part that wasn't okay.)
Step over all the limits
(There's a pronunciation issue.)
Step over
Over. Gosh.
Step over all the limits,
Kill what's troublesome
- Yes. - Yes.
(The kick and bass become
louder, I flick my fingers on the stage)
(Another member with a pronunciation issue)
Lift the spirits higher
I have to pronounce one syllable at a time.
I think I should practice
how to pronounce more.
(There is another problem.)
(The high notes)
(Laughing)
(Goodness)
(We follow our own style)
(We jump up without fear again)
What's the tune?
The only person who could manage that...
was LYNNLYNN.
(Can sing high notes,
Can't sing high notes)
But for LYNNLYNN to do it,
the pronunciation issue made it difficult.
The note for the main vocalist...
was...
It kept staying on the second octave...
la and ti.
I think the note is very
high for the main vocalist.
How do I make this sound?
(He's in a panic because
of the high notes.)
(He's also in a panic
because of the high notes.)
(I'll gladly be the new wanna be)
(A fixed role is not for us)
Do you think you'll be
able to do it with practice?
- What? - Will practice make it possible?
Actually, I'm losing hope while practicing.
I was given an important, central,
and leading part. It's a
part with lots of high notes.
I'm a bit worried because of the burden...
that I want to create a good stage.
(They practice separately.)
(He practices the choreography separately.)
(They practice singing separately.)
We each were very
worried about our own parts.
I think that was why we couldn't
build the team chemistry...
and proceeded slowly.
(There's another problem waiting for them.)
- Everyone. - Focus.
There is...
one important thing left for you.
(There's an important announcement.)
It's...
(Announcement about the highlight part)
about the highlight part.
Goodness.
In the songs of the Final
Match, there are highlight parts...
that only one member in a team can take.
The highlight part.
All the trainees must
try out the highlight part.
Okay.
The trainees will all take turns...
to record a live performance
video of the highlight part for voting.
(Record a highlight part video for voting.)
The member who will take the
highlight part will be decided...
By the votes of the members?
The votes of the World Assemblers?
By the World Assemblers.
What?
I see.
I was curious about what
the highlight parts were,
and I thought, "Will I be able to get it?"
I'm really confident.
I'm the most confident
when it comes to this song.
This is the final stage.
I thought...
I should do my best
to get the highlight part.
The highlight part was cut out.
(They check the highlight
part for "ACT UP.")
- It's JUNWON's part. - That's me.
It could be playing from the previous part.
Is that so?
The highlight part could be my part...
or JUNSEO's chorus part.
I'd like the intro part...
and of course, I want the chorus part.
I think I'll get the chorus part.
At least one of the chorus parts.
There's a part that goes, "Act up."
I think I fit the part well...
considering the choreography
and performance as well.
I like it the most.
I think I'd feel very
bad if I lose the part.
- Can you all see it?
- It's the first verse's chorus.
Right.
(Highlight Part: Chorus 1)
- It's the first verse's chorus.
(He's about to lose the part he liked.)
I don't think I'm scared
about losing the part...
because I'm not good.
I'm confident, and I'd like to
get the part no matter what.
Act up
- Act up - Act up
- Everyone is singing the part.
- They're all on fire.
I'm confident in singing this.
JUNSEO might be better than me in dancing.
But considering everything,
I thought I had a chance to win the part.
In terms of the physical aspects,
I think I'd lose against
JUNSEO or MAJINGXIANG.
But in terms of the charm
or the unexpected charm,
I think I can do better
than the other members.
I'm trying to be careful...
because there are members without parts.
But honestly, it will be voted,
so I have to try.
The person who does it best
has to stand in that position.
I don't know who will take the part,
but I hope it will be
me. I want to keep it.
Act up
(One who tries to keep...)
(and one who tries to take)
I think I put in a lot of effort
in the highlight part challenge.
I'm the most desperate for it.
I'll practice hard,
and I hope I get the highlight part.
I should grab the chance...
to show more of myself.
This is the final chance.
That's why I want to
get the highlight part.
I want to sing the highlight part too.
We're going to act up
Act up
Please vote for me, World Assemblers.
Please vote for me.
The highlight part. Nice.
Hello. I'm Trainee
LYNNLYNN of Team "ACT UP."
MAJINGXIANG of Team "ACT UP."
I'll try out for the highlight part.
(Who will take the highlight part...)
(for "ACT UP?")
("ACT UP" by MAJINGXIANG,
PARK JUNSEO, YICHEN, ANDY, )
(JUNG SEYUN, AHN JUNWON, LYNNLYNN)
(You can listen to the original tracks...)
(of the Final Match on
the music streaming sites.)
(MAJINGXIANG)
(KIM SUNGMIN)
(KIM SIHUN)
The first new song...
of the Final Project was "ACT UP."
The seven trainees who prepared "ACT UP..."
performed first.
The stage expressed
the trainees' confidence,
composure, and style in their own way.
The person who took the highlight part...
was selected by the World Assemblers.
It was Trainee YICHEN.
(YICHEN took the
highlight part for "ACT UP.")
(YICHEN)
Director Bada, you were in charge
of the choreography of "ACT UP."
Yes.
Do you think the trainees
performed well on stage?
They did so well. Did you all see that?
- Yes! - Yes.
While making the choreography of this song,
I put a lot of thought
into it with the trainees...
as it was a very powerful
and charming song.
My team, BEBE also worked
hard in making the choreography.
I want to say I feel
proud of the trainees...
for performing so well on the stage.
I feel very proud as the choreographer.
Well done. It was so awesome.
(Let's debut, YICHEN.)
Director Ha Sung Woon.
Could you please say
a word about the stage?
First of all, I watched the
stage with my mouth open.
I think they did 100 times better...
than at the practice and the rehearsal.
When I put the concept and
visuals into consideration,
they pulled it off so well.
I think they were assembled very well.
I thought they could debut like that.
It was like watching a
stage on a music show.
It was amazing!
(MAJINGXIANG)
The trainees worked day and night...
to complete the "ACT UP" performance.
I hope they will get good results.
(Let's go, ANDY!)
(Well done, NAM JIWOON!)
PROJECT 7 is being broadcast live now.
The World Assemblers
who support the trainees...
are voting at the moment.
Now,
before revealing the second stage,
I think you'd be curious
about the rank of the trainee...
you're rooting for.
Based on the fourth global voting score,
there are two trainees who
are on the boundary of passing...
and being eliminated.
(YEOJUN)
(MAJINGXIANG)
You must be very curious...
about who the two trainees are.
The two trainees...
who are on the verge of being eliminated.
(The 2 elimination
candidates will be revealed.)
(JUNWON)
They will be revealed on the screen.
(KIM SUNGMIN, SONG SEUNGHO)
(JEON MINWOOK)
(KIM SUNGMIN)
No!
(KIM SUNGMIN, SONG SEUNGHO)
They are Trainee KIM SUNGMIN...
and Trainee SONG SEUNGHO.
The ranks of the
trainees won't be revealed.
(SEUNGHO)
(NAM JIWOON)
We still have more stages left.
It's getting harder to
predict the final result.
The result can be turned around any time...
until the voting is closed.
Please...
(KIM SUNGMIN, SONG SEUNGHO)
Please watch until the end.
Now,
we'll see the trainees...
of the second new song of the Final Match,
(The stage of "Antidote" will be revealed.)
"Antidote."
Who will be singing...
the highlight part of
"Antidote," the second stage?
And how amazing would their stage be?
The practicing process
of the seven trainees...
and the stage of the new song...
will be revealed...
now.
(Training room of Team "Antidote")
To me
I can't endure it
It only goes
Because baby, you are
Right.
The song is really nice.
It's nice. It's really nice. I
wanted to try this mood.
We were one
The choreography is so pretty.
- Is it difficult? - No.
It's not difficult. It's so pretty.
It's pretty.
(The draft of the
choreography of "Antidote")
It's so difficult.
(It's so difficult.)
It must be easier than theirs, right?
- What? - Than the other teams'.
- It's easier than the other teams'.
- That's a relief.
I was worried about SUNGMIN.
I watched the choreography of "Antidote."
It was very difficult.
One.
What was after this?
(Trainee KIM SUNGMIN is
slowly learning the choreography.)
I learned it from BINGHUA.
- I can dance now. - You can...
- show us from the front. - Okay.
Watch me and dance.
I'll watch SUNGMIN.
SUNGMIN dances well.
- How did he improve so much?
- Did I improve?
- It's better than I thought.
- You improved a lot.
I'm shocked. You're really good.
I can do it.
I'm not the KIM SUNGMIN from "RUN."
(Even in the vocal lesson)
- SUNGMIN improved a lot. - Thank you.
Good. Well done.
I think SUNGMIN improved a lot.
His dancing skills improved a lot too.
I was with SUNGMIN in P4.
He was bad at dancing at the time,
so I was very worried this time.
I can't memorize it.
But he did really well this time.
I think the phrase that says,
"Hard work never betrays you..."
isn't wrong.
(Director's interim evaluation)
There's only darkness
In a large room
You and I blazed up
Baby, I don't want to be
I don't want to be alone
Now run to you
Faster even if my breath runs out
Antidote
KYOUNGBAE.
- They're good. - Right.
There are many good vocalists
like YOUNGSEO and BINGHUA.
Yes.
YOUNGSEO was assembled well.
I think they were assembled well.
I think you fit this type of song well.
Even the previous song.
Right. You're a crucial member.
SUNGMIN.
- What happened? - You improved a lot.
You did that in one day?
I was shocked.
- You're amazing, SUNGMIN.
- You improved a lot.
Seriously.
What are you doing, SUNGMIN?
- You were slow. - I'm sorry.
No. You can practice.
You have to practice more.
Is this the best you can do?
If you do this part like this,
it'll all be ruined because of you.
You shouldn't prepare it like this.
I'm getting a reality hit.
(He kept practicing to
make a perfect stage.)
KYOUNGBAE. What's after this?
RyuD said he was shocked.
"You did this in one day?"
He said that.
I guess my efforts were shown.
Whenever I hear things like that,
I get to think I want to try
harder and show people more.
KYOUNGBAE looks cool.
Why is he cool...
- when he's the youngest? - KYOUNGBAE...
has a sexy charm that
can't exist at his age.
- Right.
- He doesn't seem like the youngest.
It's a sexy charm you
can't find from the youngest.
When he did this at the end.
- That's right. - It was sexy.
He's the youngest.
Personally,
when creating the choreography
for "ACT UP" and "Antidote,"
I felt happy as a choreographer.
It's not common for a choreographer...
to create a choreography
for such a good song.
I worked even harder this time.
So I personally want
you to feel that feeling too.
Your abilities and talent...
should become one so that it goes well.
So I want you to pour
out everything you got.
Right.
(They face the moment too.)
The highlight part.
I just hoped it wasn't my part.
Let it not be my part.
- Let it not be my part.
- I hope it's not my part.
I hope it's not my part.
It won't be.
If I lose the verse, I'd
have three lines only.
Isn't that my part?
No. It's a relief.
Is it this part?
- Okay. - It's verse two.
Hold on.
(The highlight part for
"Antidote" is the 2nd chorus.)
(Highlight part)
It has my part as well.
Right.
I thought, "Why did my
part have to be there too?"
But since it's my part,
I can practice SIHUN's part as well...
and take it.
It's a chance for me.
I lost the main vocalist's position.
This is driving me crazy.
It could be a chance for me since
I lost the main vocalist's position.
(Main vocalist: KIM SIHUN,
Lead vocalist 1: YOO YOUNGSEO)
The highlight part is a really good part.
I'm confident.
Teach me this part, BINGHUA.
Run to you
It was the chorus, so
I really wanted to do it.
I think I can now leave an impression...
on the World Assemblers...
that I can pull it off.
I want to take this part no matter what.
Since it's our last performance,
I want to look good...
to the people who are
supporting me, even just by little.
I think the highlight part is the part...
that draws all the attention.
I thought taking the highlight...
could affect our ranking as well.
I think I'm the one who
knows how high of a wall it is...
to be in seventh place.
As I'm really close to debuting,
I think the chance of me debuting...
will increase if I take the highlight.
Doing each project on PROJECT 7,
I loved the cheers I
received from the crowd...
on the stage.
So I've become more desperate to debut.
Each time I did a performance,
I grew greedier.
I didn't simply have
fun. I wanted to do better,
and I wanted to perform
better for the World Assemblers.
Actually, during Zero Setting,
I thought of just
giving it a try and leave.
And that was because I
hadn't trained myself at all.
But now, I can confidently say...
that I must debut.
I think I've become more
desperate to become an idol.
I want to shine on stage.
- I really want to debut.
(I really want to debut.)
(NAM JIWOON, let's debut.)
(My son whom I'm proud of,
NAM JIWOON, you're the best.)
- NAM JIWOON! - NAM JIWOON!
NAM JIWOON!
- NAM JIWOON! - Let's go!
(NAM JIWOON, let's debut.)
YOUNGSEO!
YOO YOUNGSEO!
(NAM JIWOON)
("Antidote" by YOO YOUNGSEO,
KIM SIHUN, NAM JIWOON, )
(SEO KYOUNGBAE, BINGHUA,
KIM SUNGMIN, WOO HAJOON)
(SEO KYOUNGBAE)
(You can listen to the original tracks...)
(of the Final Match on
the music streaming sites.)
Well done!
KYOUNGBAE!
KIM SIHUN!
(WOO HAJOON, you should debut.)
(Shoot a bullet to my heart.)
(SEO KYOUNGBAE)
(WOO HAJOON, you should debut.)
(YOO YOUNGSEO)
The second new track...
of the Final Match.
The seven trainees...
who prepared "Antidote"
have finished their performance.
We could feel how
desperate the trainees were,
and that must've overwhelmed
the World Assemblers.
(NAM JIWOON)
The trainee...
taking the highlight part of "Antidote,"
whom the World Assemblers
picked themselves.
It was Trainee YOO YOUNGSEO.
(The highlight part of
"Antidote," YOO YOUNSEO)
(YOO YOUNSEO)
(YOUNSEO)
Director Bada, you were in charge
of the choreography of "Antidote."
Yes.
How did you enjoy the performance?
First of all,
my hands are really sweaty.
I was also really nervous
while watching them.
While they practiced for "Antidote,"
I made them practice
expressing their emotions more.
Delivering your emotions
on stage takes a big part.
The trainees did really well on that part,
so I'm really proud of
them as the choreographer.
I want to tell them that they did well.
They were so cool.
(KIM SUNGMIN)
(NAM JIWOON, let's debut.)
All right, then. Director Lee Hae In.
Tell us how you enjoyed
their performance as well.
The choreography was really cool.
I didn't know they
could be this expressive.
Not just their dancing and singing skills,
but their expressions
on stage improved a lot...
thanks to the support from the
directors and the World Assemblers,
so I was really proud of them
while watching their performance.
YOUNGSEO and SIHUN,
who are more experienced,
led the performance well.
A trainee like SUNGMIN,
who was lacking at first,
could improve a lot. Seeing that...
surprised me a lot.
Everyone, you can do it.
(WOO HAJOON)
(WOO HAJOON, you should debut.)
(HAJOON)
All right.
The cheer for the trainees of PROJECT 7...
is getting heated.
If you want the trainee
you're rooting for to debut,
please vote for them now.
(KIM SUNGMIN, KENSHIN)
PROJECT 7.
The last project to determine...
the seven trainees who will debut.
Following "Act Up..."
and "Antidote,"
the third new song of the Final Match,
"PSYCHO" will be revealed.
(The "PSYCHO"
performance will be revealed.)
The seven trainees who
prepared for the performance...
will be revealed now.
(NAM JIWOON)
Among the trainees who prepared
for the "PSYCHO" performance,
the trainee who got the highlight part...
their practice,
and their performance, which
will be revealed for the first time.
They will be revealed now.
(Echoing throughout the Project Village)
(The humming of the trainees)
Even after arguing
- Shall we sit? - Yes.
(Team "PSYCHO" has energy
on another level from the start.)
Let's go!
Let's quickly decide
and pick our leader first.
- Okay. - Sounds good.
- I have a question. - Yes?
Do you want to be a leader?
- Honestly, I want to be one. - Okay.
- Give him a round of applause.
(Then we'll congratulate him.)
- Yes! - Gosh.
(He was chosen as the
leader in the shortest time.)
He's the representative psycho.
He's our representative.
- How can you put it that way?
- The representative psycho?
I'll put on a good performance
with great members like you.
You never know.
We might all make our debut.
- That'd be really nice.
- That's my lifetime wish.
I can sign a permanent deal too.
Me too.
(They were already in a festive
mood when their members were called.)
The member assembly for
Team "PSYCHO" is great.
We became a team with
the members we wanted.
I thought, "This assembly is crazy good."
I'm happy that I got to
perform with great members.
I felt that the practice would be fun.
Today, I hired a special instructor...
for the first part of the song.
It's Instructor KIM HYUNWOO...
who is sitting in front with bleached hair.
Please give him a round of applause.
This may look arrogant,
but this is the first move.
- Right. - Really?
- Make a bigger move like this.
- Like this?
Face front again and hit it.
(The students are following.)
Then you move like this.
(Making a big progress)
- Yes. - This is really fast.
HYUNWOO volunteered to
help with the dance moves.
I'm the afternoon instructor, Nutria.
- Move it like this. - Like this.
HYUNWOO is good at leading
the team with positive vibes.
I can't pull myself together.
I've always wanted to team up with SEUNGHO.
Finally, this is our last performance.
It's so nice that we
get to perform together.
(Oh, my. The beat is...)
The beat is...
SEUNGHO, which part?
- Right. - I think it was here.
I know that JEONGMIN is talented.
He's also good at sharing tips.
That's 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
(Showing great teamwork while practicing)
Psycho...
I think there is great energy...
because I'm so happy with my team.
The team consists of seven
people I wanted to pick...
if they gave me a chance to pick.
- I'll play the music. - Is it your turn?
(Sub-vocalist)
(All-rounder)
Run...
(This man froze as he sang.)
Turn this up, Psycho who looks like me
(Patting)
We're going right
(Going out of tune)
(Drinking water)
Oh, my. Why isn't this working?
(The all-rounder has a lot on his mind.)
(Even the main rapper...)
Make it like that
(Struggling as he faces the
rap part with a lot of Korean)
The lyrics are too hard for me.
KENSHIN and I wanted
to show that we were good.
He and I took the main
rapper and all-rounder parts.
Pulling it off...
is the most important
thing for our team right now.
Tonight...
This is making me go crazy.
I thought, "Was I too greedy about this?"
Did I lower the team's
overall performance?"
Nonetheless, I have to make it work.
How come I can't do this?
(Singing)
Try it three times.
(Learning how to sing like a cat)
You have to make the
sound come out from the side.
(Practicing as he gets singing tips)
(On the other hand, Trainee KENSHIN...)
SEUNGHO.
How do I pull this part off?
- What you want... - What you want...
What you want...
(Other trainees joining)
Do you think you got it?
What you want...
No, that's not it.
- Want... - Want...
Make the sound ring from the back.
There you go.
KENSHIN, you've improved
a lot compared to "Jealousy."
Thank you.
What you want...
KENSHIN practiced so hard.
We've been more like rivals...
fighting for 1st and 2nd places.
I think he can improve
a lot if we help him.
KENSHIN, let's practice together.
KENSHIN and I have to
practice hard to perform well.
You do it my way...
I can't wait to see their performance.
- These psychos. - Psychos?
The team assembly is amazing.
- They are all talented.
- It's a strong team.
It's impossible that
they cannot perform well.
(Flattered)
- Shall we start? - Yes.
Let's see it right away.
- Goodness. - Nice.
They are so talented.
- Of course. - What's going on?
Tonight, we are above our instinct
Run, now we're free
MINWOOK is a great singer.
Has MINWOOK always been a great singer?
Make you like that, hands over head
What you want, Yes, we get it
(Impressed)
(Amazed)
They are good!
They're talented.
The team assembly is too good.
- Yes, it's too good. - In just one day?
You all did better than I thought.
Maybe they have their know-how now.
They have great teamwork.
When MINWOOK and KENSHIN teamed up,
I was very worried.
"These two will team up as a duo?"
I was actually very worried. But
when I saw their performance...
These two were a great team
when they performed together.
They were just like one team.
You two did a great job as a
duo. The performance was great.
The assembly is excellent. I
can't wait to see the final one.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Team Psycho got great feedback.)
Well done.
(They did well for the interim check.)
We still have to go through one big stage.
Let's just face it.
The song's highlight.
- Let's take a guess.
- It's going to be fun.
Which part do you think it would be?
Make you lose your mind
- Maybe that one. - No, it's my part.
- This part.
- Maybe it's KENSHIN's solo dance.
I mean it.
- One, two, three. - One, two, three.
- This is it. - What?
- So this is the highlight.
- Yes, it's that part.
- You were right. - So it's that part.
(His prediction is correct.)
(Highlight)
(Screaming)
- Oh, no. - This is where I thought.
- I knew it was the highlight.
- It is cool, though.
(The highlight part)
This is it.
(Tormented)
This is where it can give chills.
I feel like this is where
it would excite the fans.
I think HYUNWOO will
do well with this part.
Luckily, the highlight
was where I could do well.
I think I can perform it well.
So I want to take this part.
I really want to take it.
- I wanted this part.
- You wanted this part?
I took the main rapper part
because I wanted this part.
- Really? - Because of this part?
Because of this part?
I wanted to do this
part. That's why I chose...
When I first saw the
"PSYCHO" performance...
(Who is it?)
(An all-rounder?)
(He was after the solo dance
part from the very beginning.)
I really want to take this part.
So I'm very anxious...
(Lying down)
SAKURADA KENSHIN.
You can do it.
Yes.
I've been memorizing the lyrics...
- Get... - Get...
(He has been doing his best
to pull off the main rapper part.)
I've been practicing the dance moves.
There's a chance that
someone else take the part.
I think you'll take the highlight.
I don't think so.
I think... Pork cutlet...
(Pork cutlet is confused.)
This part is really cool.
I really wanted to take this part.
Gosh, I'm in big trouble. I
have to practice really hard.
I could feel it...
when KENSHIN was upset.
I also wanted to do the highlight.
There would be competition within the team.
I realized, "This is a survival show."
If you want it
(Everyone's practicing his part...)
(after the highlight was revealed.)
(Thinking)
(As SEUNGHO resumes with his practice)
- With the new... - That's how you...
Here is my tip.
This is how you say it. "With the..."
But you accentuate the first word.
- Look. - The night full of...
- There you go. - With the new...
No, you sounded like...
We have to perform as a team.
If SEUNGHO can make his debut on this show,
he would be making his
debut with this performance.
Then he has to excel at this.
Can't you make it cooler?
- Like this. - JEONGMIN.
This is how you do it.
Do it the other way.
And you need to start with a ready pose.
You're just hitting it here.
- That's it. - I get it.
You got it now.
He and I are doing the final performance.
So I wanted to improve the
quality of his dance moves.
Just once...
(The reason why he takes great
care of Trainee SONG SEUNGHO)
JEONGMIN saved my life
as a trainee at the agency...
even when I was not talented at all.
I can tell you this for sure.
I helped him from scratch.
I'm sure SEUNGHO will agree.
We met when we were 17. Now we turned 18.
We're about to turn 19 soon.
We've been friends for two years.
I've been teaching him
the dance moves every time.
I've been helping him with
the basic dance moves also.
He was more like a savior.
We joined the show together,
but if I get to make a debut
alone with my ranking going up...
(Trainee SONG SEUNGHO made
it to the debut team by himself.)
Honestly, I feel insecure without him.
This is how I feel.
This is the Final Match.
This is the final stage for
both SEUNGHO and me.
As in, practicing together...
and living together as trainees.
Oh, no!
Hold on.
This will be aired for sure.
No! SEUNGHO shouldn't see this.
Here's why I cried during the interview.
I felt like...
it was our last time to
practice as trainees here.
Do you want me to share one more fun story?
I couldn't sleep well...
when I first joined the show.
You and your friends...
(They started together
at the same starting point.)
Your popularity went up so fast.
So I was really envious.
(He couldn't sleep
well as he felt anxious.)
I was waiting until I had more fans.
You have a lot of fans now.
So I'm happy!
I achieved a big goal after a long time.
When I first made it to the Top Seven,
the first thing that
worried me was my skills.
"If I really get to debut,"
"I don't think I can survive
with my skills. I'm in trouble."
- This is what I thought. - So...
This is how I really feel.
I feel like you'll really debut now.
I'm so grateful to this
show that I could help...
with your final performance.
I'm actually realizing my dream now.
I've always wanted to perform with you.
- We're finally performing together.
- In such a huge stadium.
We're putting on the biggest
performance together in the end.
We might not be able to
practice together anymore.
I wanted to do the last
performance well with JEONGMIN.
It would be nice if I
could make a debut here.
But I have to say goodbye to my team.
This situation has been
bugging me in my head.
We thought we would be
together. But one of us has to leave.
It would make me feel empty.
However, we got this chance
to perform our final performance.
I really want to make it exciting.
Since we're at it already,
I want to leave no regrets.
I'll do my best with what I can.
- Hold on. This isn't right.
- This is not the one.
We have to do this...
I wish we could do more
than just this performance.
I wish we could perform together...
for many other occasions.
But I know it's hard to do that.
He keeps smiling at me.
He smiled at me too.
Since the Final Match
could be the last performance,
I thought not only the
outcome but also the process...
should be beautiful when we look back.
If we feel happy at every moment together,
it will make the
competition better in the end.
That's great!
(The day of filming the song's highlight)
The last one.
Hello, I'm Trainee SONG
SEUNGHO of Team "PSYCHO."
I'll try the song's highlight.
(Who will take the song's highlight?)
JEON MINWOOK!
- KENSHIN, go for it! - JEON MINWOOK!
KIM JEONGMIN!
(KENSHIN, MINWOOK)
(I'm always on MINWOOK's side.)
("PSYCHO" by KIM JEONGMIN,
KIM HYUNWOO, JEON MINWOOK, )
(SAKURADA KENSHIN, JANG
YEOJUN, SONG SEUNGHO)
(You can listen to the original tracks...)
(of the Final Match on
the music streaming sites.)
- KIM HYUNWOO! - KIM JEONGMIN!
(JEONGMIN)
(SEUNGHO, cute pose)
(SAKURADA KENSHIN)
The last new song of the Final Match,
"PSYCHO" was prepared...
by seven trainees,
and they finished the performance.
I could feel the trainees' attitude...
that's intense and confident.
(YEOJUN did the greatest job.)
The World Assemblers selected...
the one who performed
the highlight of "PSYCHO."
It was KIM HYUNWOO.
(KIM HYUNWOO performed
the highlight of "PSYCHO.")
(KIM HYUNWOO, GOAT)
Director RyuD created the
choreography of "PSYCHO."
- Yes. - Director RyuD.
Do you think the trainees
completed the performance well?
First of all,
on Christmas Eve, we, all men, gathered...
and practiced all day long.
I was in charge of
upgrading the performance,
so my focus was on making an
awesome performance, no matter what.
For Team "PSYCHO," without a worry,
I could enjoy preparing
for the performance.
They're such nice people.
They have great teamwork,
and they gave a wonderful performance.
I'm so proud of them and
I feel thankful for them.
I loved it.
(KENSHIN, KIM HYUNWOO)
Director Ryan Sewon Jhun,
please tell us what you
think about the performance.
This is...
not a performance of music, I thought.
I thought it was a performance of art.
That's because...
if you look at it from the
beginning to the end of the music,
it has a complicated organization.
The song needs a lot of practice.
Of course, the other two
teams were also great.
I think this is a song that
requires a lot of practice.
But it was amazing.
Oh, my. They're awesome. You're the best.
You did a good job.
PROJECT 7 is broadcast live.
We have about 20 minutes left...
until the voting closes.
(The real-time global
voting will close soon.)
World Assemblers who haven't voted yet,
the voting will close after 20 minutes.
Please do not forget to vote.
If there's any World Assembler...
who hasn't participated
in real-time global voting,
you can cast your valuable vote...
for the trainees you support.
Please support the trainees' dream...
to the end.
(HAJOON)
(YEOJUN, you were the best.)
While World Assemblers...
cast the last vote,
we can watch a video.
The 21 trainees...
received special gifts.
Let's watch the video now.
(Project Village in snow)
(In Project Village, )
I'm having Christmas with PROJECT 7.
(Christmas has come.)
Let's write, "Realizing
the dream of debut."
- Debut. - Is it "b?"
(My wish is to debut and win
1st place on a music show.)
- Or... - Yes, a wish.
(Trainees wrote letters with their wishes.)
(I wish my parents and the people
I love stay healthy and happy.)
(My wish is to make a debut!)
I can't reach it.
It hurts.
You managed it.
(They're excited to decorate
the Christmas tree together.)
It's been a while since I decorated a tree.
I did it when I was very little.
How do you hang this?
(Putting on a ribbon)
A ribbon doesn't go with you.
(My wish)
(Hoping everyone's wishes come true)
- It's beautiful.
- I need to take a proof shot here.
(The tree 21 trainees decorated together)
(Under the tree, that night)
- What's that? - Oh, my.
We have gifts.
- I guess Santa Claus visited us.
- It was Santa!
- It was Santa! - Santa Claus?
What's inside?
Each has a name on it.
- That's amazing. - It's true.
- It's a real gift. - Really?
- What's in it? - It's heavy.
That's true.
- This is mine. - KENSHIN.
How come he has such a big one?
- It's also heavy. - Not every big gift...
is expensive, right?
Shake it.
I envy you. You got a big one.
- Thank you! - Thank you!
(What are the gifts arrived for trainees?)
I'm most curious about JUNWON's gift.
Let's open it first.
- We should open this last. - No.
- Stop it. - I can't see it.
- I can't see any. - LYNNLYNN.
I think it's NCT's album.
- An album. - It must be expensive.
I think, since it's in the box,
- it's a book. - A book?
- I like comics.
- Right, you read comics a lot.
What could be this?
What's inside?
I think it must be a
department store certificate.
- I think it's a candy. See?
- He's guessing.
It's a candy.
- I hear the sound of a can.
- Something like star candy.
I think it's something like cookies.
As I see SEYUN's gift is
the most nicely wrapped.
I'm curious.
- SEYUN's gift is wrapped nicely. - Right.
- Shoes? - Shoes.
- No. - What is it?
- Chocolate? - Shoes?
It's a snack.
(JUNG SEYUN's gift is a snack.)
- What is it? - There's a letter.
What is it?
Seriously.
Why? What is it?
(Trainee JUNG SEYUN suddenly sheds tears.)
- JUNG SEYUN. - What is it?
Is there a letter too?
Seriously.
- I feel like tearing up. - No.
Hello, SEYUN.
It's Mom. I guess you're surprised.
Did your mom send it?
His mom?
In 1, 2, 3.
(Meanwhile, Team "PSYCHO" also...)
It's a snack set.
It's snacks.
- It's a snack set. - It's snacks.
It's really snacks.
- It's really snacks.
- Is it a toy for a puppy?
- Wait, this is.. - What's that?
What's this?
(A dog toy in Trainee KIM HYUNWOO's gift)
It's what my dog plays with.
Is it sent by your parents?
Seriously, this is what they're doing?
It's a volleyball.
A volleyball?
(Christmas gifts from trainees' families)
My son, you must be having a hard time.
I worried about you a lot,
but I'm so relieved that
you seem to be doing great.
It's already been over three
years since you became a trainee.
You and I once had a conflict
and resented each other,
but I don't think it was a waste.
You shed sweat and tears in sadness.
I know that more than anyone in the world.
You...
As you're away from home,
it makes me only think of
how I made you feel sorry.
Dear my youngest boy SEYUN,
you've been through a lot.
I love you, my boy. You can do it, SEYUN!
I miss Mom so much.
This is my favorite snack.
I see.
Seeing it in the box, I
knew my mom sent it.
But I was so charged with emotion...
My baby SEUNGHO, it must be tough for you.
I thought you were still too young,
but seeing you on TV...
But seeing you on TV, I feel proud.
You're praiseworthy, and
I also feel sorry for you.
(I haven't done much for you, and
I thought you were still too young.)
(But seeing you on TV, I feel
proud. You're praiseworthy, )
(and I also feel sorry for you.)
I hope...
(I hope your effort leads to happiness.)
your effort leads...
I remembered that I
complained since I was tired...
and argued with my mom sometimes.
KENSHIN, you had a cute
smile since you were little.
You were a child everyone loved...
and you made everyone happy.
You went to Korea alone,
where a different language is used.
When I first saw you dancing...
as the center for the
title song of PROJECT 7,
I was so happy that I
shed a flood of tears.
(I was so happy that I
shed a flood of tears.)
I cheer for you with all my
heart. You can do it, KENSHIN.
From your mom and dad.
It doesn't match JUNSEO's concept at all.
- That's it. - What on earth...
What on earth is this?
(Trainee PARK JUNSEO's
gift is a teddy bear and a letter.)
Dear my boy.
Are you doing all right?
You must be tired physically and
mentally being in an audition show,
but you always have a bright look,
think positively, and do a good job.
I'm so proud of you, son.
I'm so thankful that you came to me.
Happy birthday, son.
And what I sent to you is a teddy bear...
to celebrate your birthday
on behalf of the family.
What's this?
This isn't even working.
Gosh, it surprised me.
(The teddy bear celebrates his
birthday on behalf of his family.)
She got a great gift for you.
- For me, - Happy birthday to you
it was encouraging.
Happy birthday, dear friend
(His mom's gift stopped his tears.)
(Next, Trainee YICHEN opens his present.)
I guess it's a video.
It's my grandmother.
Did my grandmother film it?
Hello, dear YICHEN. It's your grandmother.
- It's my grandmother. - How are you?
My grandmother...
is Ahn Myung Geun's granddaughter.
She's almost over 80 years old now.
I miss you so much,
and I'm so glad that I
can see you on the show.
I loved to see you sing and
dance since you were little.
I hope you take good care of your health.
I always cheer for you with a glad heart.
My grandmother filmed
the video like this for me.
I hope you stay healthy for a long time,
and I'll go home soon to see you.
- BINGHUA? - It's BINGHUA's turn.
- Let's go. - Wait a minute.
I need to get my heart ready.
You're right.
Did they send a video message?
Is it a video message?
I hope the path you walk
for your dream to shine.
BINGHUA, if you have a dream, run to it.
Have courage, find your dream,
and enjoy your performance.
We'll cheer for you forever. You can do it!
(Is he crying?)
(Is he not crying?)
Now, is he laughing or crying?
He scares me.
I mean,
I mean, I've never heard them saying...
something like this.
I guess filming the video
made them say that way.
(Everyone looks so nervous.)
In fact, it's kind of funny.
(Trainee BINGHUA's
family gave him a laugh.)
I'm going to be on the
final stage after the practice.
With the cheer from my parents,
I got more confident to
move on to the next level.
I think I can really work harder.
I'll do my best not to disappoint them...
and make them feel proud of me.
Dear my SUNGMIN.
I guess you must be tired
from practice these days.
There's nothing I can do for
you except for sending support.
Since you've been doing all right,
you'll bear a fruit as much as your effort.
Seeing my son putting
in effort and growing up,
I'm worried that it must be tiring,
but I also feel proud of you.
However, when we see you putting
effort with passion day and night...
for your dream to be an idol singer,
we always feel sorry that we
can't give you more things for you,
and we still feel sorry
now as your parents,
You only have a little time
left there. With your colleagues,
we hope you give a fun...
and nice performance.
I'll say one thing that made
me upset watching the show.
You never say "I love you" to your parents,
but you said it to YONGHYUN.
(YONGHYUN, I love you.)
(The expression of affection
made his parents get jealous.)
You made us upset.
Still, you're our favorite forever, JIWOON.
We love you so much.
Your mom and dad.
I never said I love you,
but I love you.
(Embarrassed)
If I have time after this performance,
I'll go home and hug you tight.
I love you, Mom.
It's almost been over ten years.
Look at that. His mom
put so much sincerity.
How come it's so long?
(Dear my MINWOOK)
Oh, my.
Wait, this won't be easy.
(His mom sent him a three-page letter.)
Dear MINWOOK my sweetie,
I guess it's my first time...
to send you a handwritten letter.
My precious son MINWOOK.
You were a bit picky and sensitive.
You were beautiful,
good-looking, cute, and smart...
since you were little.
And when you were a 12th
grader, you suddenly said...
you wanted to be a rapper,
and that surprised me a lot.
I thought you'd do what
you want without a regret,
and after three years,
after you serve in the army,
you'd find your career.
But you were so busy
and diligent practicing,
working part-time, and having auditions.
If I had supported you more back then,
the path you're walking on now...
(If I had supported you more back then)
must have been easier for you.
Because I...
Because I was ignorant,
(I was ignorant that you
went through more difficulties.)
you went through more difficulties.
I didn't know how to help you...
(I didn't know how to help you.)
except for watching and waiting.
MINWOOK.
You've been working hard every moment,
and you always made me proud.
I love you. Hang in there, my boy.
Everything will be all right.
Right.
It's been a while since I cried this much.
I want to stop my mom
from feeling sorry for me.
"I want to find..."
"success..."
"and make my mom
happy." I had that thought.
Despite the difficult times,
you've worked diligently until today.
All of us are proud of you, ANDY.
Do you remember when you
first went to Korea to practice?
To be honest, I cried secretly
every time I answered your call.
Adhere to the Korean rules.
Work and live upright.
Don't touch anything dangerous.
(Gosh, Dad.)
"When I saw you prepare for the show..."
"and practice without anyone's help,"
"I was half worried and half apologetic."
"You couldn't play with friends,
eat, or make good memories."
"Seeing you spend the teenage
years, the golden age that way..."
"made my heart ache so much."
"I saw you practice until
your hat was soaked..."
"and your toenails were broken..."
"before you fell asleep
in an exhausted state."
"My heart ached because
I couldn't do it for you."
"But I also learned a lot from you..."
"since you always enjoyed
yourself and stayed serious."
"HYUNWOO, you have to be
the star wherever you're at..."
"these days. I'm rooting for you."
"You must've struggled a
lot and had many worries."
"I'm proud of you for
persevering and coming this far."
"When I watch you sing and dance on TV,"
"I feel like I've taken the
most effective energy drink..."
"in that moment."
"I'll always stay reliable
and cheer you on."
"JEONGMIN, it's time for
you to look ahead and run."
"You're running diligently
even at this moment."
"YOUNGSEO, I'll always root for
you as you run toward your dream."
"My precious son, YOUNGSEO."
- "I love you." - "I love you, HYUNWOO."
- "I love you." - "I love you. Heart."
"I love you, my son."
"Your loving mom and dad."
"Your loving dad who
will always cheer you on."
I stayed manly and didn't shed tears.
I'll become successful and go home, Mom.
Just you watch.
Please root for me until the end.
I love you.
I love you, Mom.
I love you guys.
I love you so much.
(Their Christmas on PROJECT 7
was warm thanks to the families.)
It's okay.
Don't cry.
They're the trainees' first fans...
who'll remain their fans forever.
The parents' supportive words...
moved me as well.
(Always PARK JUNSEO)
Thanks to the parents...
who always remained supportive...
as dependable allies,
the trainees could endure
the exhausting practice...
and come this far.
I personally wondered what to do...
with the heavy atmosphere.
I thank Director Bada...
and LYNNLYNN's father.
Assemble and upgrade, PROJECT 7.
The real-time global voting will end soon.
If you haven't voted for the trainee...
you were rooting for,
please make sure to
cast your precious vote.
Let me make the announcement again.
Soon,
the real-time global voting will end.
After the voting comes to an
end, the votes will be counted.
Then...
the final rankings will be announced...
to determine the debut team of PROJECT 7.
Which seven trainees...
will enjoy the happiness of debuting?
Will the trainees you're rooting for...
be able to realize their
dreams of debuting?
With the trainees that were
chosen by the World Assemblers,
the world-class...
idol group will be born.
Please watch until the end.
(JANG YEOJUN, SONG SEUNGHO, JEON MINWOOK, )
(KYOUNGBAE, SUNGMIN)
(JEON MINWOOK, debut as the center member.)
The members of CLOSE YOUR EYES...
will be revealed soon.
Soon,
the final members who
debut through PROJECT 7...
and work as CLOSE YOUR EYES...
will be revealed.
So please stay with us until the end.
Now,
the real-time global voting...
will end.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
The voting is closed.
(Is there another present
that awaits the trainees?)
What's this?
(What's this room?)
(It contains the World Assemblers' love.)
(The room is full of
messages for the trainees.)
What?
My goodness.
There's me.
Where am I?
I'm right here.
(The World Assembler Room
is full of precious memories.)
(Our lovely and talented
MINWOOK, all of us know...)
(how hard you worked to prove your talent.)
(MINWOOK, you always did your best.)
(The world will give
you the fitting result.)
(MINWOOK, I've been very
sick since July of this year.)
(You gave me laughter and
strength to support someone!)
"MINWOOK, I've been very
sick since July of this year."
"There were many stressful moments..."
"and days I passed out,"
"so I was quite depressed."
"I was sick and stressed out,
but watching you perform..."
"made me forget about
my struggles and smile."
"You gave me laughter..."
"and strength to support someone!"
I hope that you won't be depressed.
I hope that you'll be healthy.
I'll do better...
and shine more on the stage.
I hope that you'll become happy...
through me.
(YEOJUN, hello! I'm proud
of you for improving yourself...)
(and growing through each competition.)
(Watching you grow a bit at
a time made me want to cry.)
(I hope your wish and my
wish will come true this winter!)
"The all-rounder, YEOJUN."
"It's nice that you always
work hard for your dream."
"It's my dream to become a trainee,"
"so you give me a lot of courage."
I haven't debuted yet,
but there's someone...
who's motivated by me
to work toward her dream.
I'm quite surprised.
Had the 16-year-old YEOJUN...
who first began to dream watched this,
he would've cried a lot.
I'd like to give one reply.
I hope that it won't be your
dream to become a trainee.
I'll diligently prepare
for the final on this show.
I hope we'll be able to
meet on the stage later.
I can feel so much love.
"I had a stressful year as a 12th grader."
"During the stressful time
of preparing for CSAT,"
"you were my best comedian..."
"Comedian?"
"Idol, vitamin,"
"and oxygen tank."
"Now, I'll support you always."
"So please continue to move forward."
(A heartwarming message
from a World Assembler...)
(who wants him to
continue marching forward)
Thanks to you, I could come here...
without giving up in the past four years.
I'm serious.
(To HYUNWOO)
"Whenever I struggle with the job hunt,"
"I get energized by
watching you work hard."
"Don't forget..."
"that you make more
people happy than you think."
One performance remains.
If I can give more
performances in the future,
I'll continue to give you strength.
It says, "Big Brother SEUNGHO."
"There must've been times you cried a lot."
"Thank you for persevering."
"There's a phrase I like very much."
"If you can't avoid it, enjoy it."
"I hope our words will comfort you."
I'll be a big brother and work hard.
"Big Brother JEONGMIN."
(His cheeks go red.)
"I love you so much. I'll
vote for you diligently."
"Please come to the graduation ceremony."
"I'll bring paper and a pen
and get your autograph."
"I'll get your photos too. I hope
that you'll always be happy."
"Stay healthy and don't
catch a cold. I love you."
My goodness.
I'll go to the graduation ceremony.
"HAJOON,"
"I hope that you'll
perform with confidence."
"I'll root for you in every moment."
"So let's debut."
I also want to be with
the World Assemblers...
in every moment.
"Big Brother AHN JUNWON."
It's nice that there's a fan
who calls me "Big brother."
"I know that you work hard."
"So I hope that you'll continue to smile."
"We'll follow you until then."
I hope the World Assemblers
who are walking with me...
will be full of happiness and good fortune.
"Thank you for showing your smile always."
"You shined the most when
you became the center member."
It's nice.
(KENSHIN looks for another
message by a World Assembler.)
"KENSHIN, don't forget Korean."
"KENSHIN,"
"I'll always root for you."
Thank you.
Please continue to root for me.
(My beloved ANDY, words can't express...)
(how special you are.)
(ANDY, hello. Don't regret it...)
(even if you don't get
the result you wanted.)
"No matter where you're at,"
"I can find you in 0.5 seconds..."
"because you shine..."
"more than anyone on the stage."
"It was really nice to meet
ANDY on PROJECT 7."
"Good luck!"
(Good luck!)
"SUNGMIN, hello. I'm your fan."
"Let me criticize you first."
"I was shocked when I watched
your 'Hype Boy' performance."
"But your 'Merry-Go-Round' performance..."
"moved me and made me feel proud."
"I want to see you grow even more."
"I'll root for you."
"I'm your fan."
I really like that part.
It's very precious that
there's a fan of mine.
This is incredible.
"YICHEN,"
"I love watching you
laugh, cry, and get angry."
I think this person liked it...
when I got angry as a P5 member.
"I'll root for you..."
"so that your dream will come
true and you'll continue to smile."
Thank you so much. With this energy,
I'll work hard on the final stage.
Thank you.
I'm so thankful that this person
loves even my angry side.
"I'm a World Assembler..."
"who has rooted for you
since your last challenge."
"Thank you for not giving up on
your dream of becoming an idol."
There are fans who waited
for me. Thank you so much.
"JUNSEO, you're very talented,"
"precious, valuable, and special."
"You're more perfect than you think."
I don't know if I'm that perfect.
I'm so thankful for the
fans' words of support.
I'll work hard.
Thank you.
"LYNNLYNN,"
"I was moved by your effort on PROJECT 7."
"I was so moved when you placed 35th..."
"in the Second Passing
Ceremony that I cried."
Thank you. Without you,
that wouldn't have happened.
I didn't know if I could
give the third performance.
I didn't know if I could perform "Trigger."
I can't believe I did so well.
Thank you for voting for me.
What's this?
Am I included too?
"You're much more charming than you think."
"People like you and
want to be with you..."
"more than you think,"
"but there will be moments of doubt."
"If you tell me then,"
"I'll tell you once more..."
"that you're very cool."
(Moved)
Thanks to people who continue
to support me without giving up,
I could reach the
finals with gritted teeth.
I'll put it up on the wall and
read it when things get hard.
Thank you so much for
writing this message...
with sincerity.
Thank you so much.
"I know that you had
difficult days in the past."
"I'll stay by your side always."
My fans are looking forward to seeing me.
So I must keep on running without stopping.
That was why I loved listening...
to "RUN" on PROJECT 7.
"RUN." That's how I feel.
I want to run to the World Assemblers.
I love you.
(I love you.)
"Hello, KYOUNGBAE."
"Words can't express the
difficult path you've taken."
"But I'm so proud of you."
"Whenever things get tough,"
"don't forget that we're
always rooting for you."
"KYOUNGBAE, let's debut!"
(Let's debut!)
I said that what I wanted to hear...
the most was, "KYOUNGBAE, let's debut."
Thank you so much...
for writing this heartfelt message.
I like all of them.
(I like all of them.)
"BINGHUA,"
"thank you for making my life happier."
"I'll always love you..."
"and support you..."
"even when there are difficulties."
I'll make sure to realize my
dream of becoming an idol.
I'll never give up.
I won't give up.
There it is!
"YOUNGSEO, you're the
kindest and gentlest person."
"Your voice is like..."
"the passing wind in the starry night sky."
"YOUNGSEO, don't forget
this even during the dark time."
"Light finds its way in the end."
(Light finds its way in the end.)
It's very...
Like this person said,
there were many difficult times...
that could be described as the dark age.
But whenever that happened...
There were fans who rooted for me.
Through PROJECT 7,
I could challenge myself.
I think I found my way and
am running toward my goal.
Thank you always.
(Thank you always.)
During the Heart Assembling Event,
there were so many fans.
(The trainees met the World Assemblers...)
(for the first time at the
Heart Assembling Event.)
It was my first time...
meeting people who rooted
for me and paid attention to me.
I felt both awkward and happy.
Many people...
who root for me and
truly wish for my success...
made me feel thankful.
I won't forget them until the day I die.
It's thanks to the World Assemblers...
that I can practice until late at night.
Words can't express it.
They're this much precious.
If I think about my fans
when I'm exhausted,
I can dance 100 more times.
That's how precious they are.
Instead of just receiving support,
I want to give them energy.
I want to be someone
who can give happiness...
to the World Assemblers.
I want to be remembered as a trainee...
who happily runs toward his dream.
A cool trainee.
What are we doing here today?
- Recording! - Recording!
We're here to record a fan song...
- for the World Assemblers. - A fan song.
- A fan song. - With love.
It's a fan song for the World Assemblers.
That was why I thought,
"I'll deliver my sincerity..."
"to my fans."
"I want to sing this song
in a precious and nice way."
I had that desire.
I sang the song while thinking...
about my fans and family.
What do you want to do?
What do you want to show?
The game of guessing the number.
- Hello. - Hello.
- I'm in your care. - Okay.
(They begin recording "Yesterday,
Today, and Tomorrow...")
(for the World Assemblers.)
(They want to repay for
the World Assemblers' love.)
I really thank the World Assemblers.
I want to show them my cool side.
There are many people who
believe in me and wait for me.
I felt emotional...
because I wanted to repay them.
I'm always thankful for my fans.
They give me strength and support.
I want them to be happy.
I'm so thankful.
Being able to perform before
people who root for me...
makes me the happiest in the world.
I'll continue to give them strength.
- World Assemblers. - World Assemblers.
- We love you. - We love you.
We love you.
("Yesterday, Today, and
Tomorrow" begins now.)
- All right. - Thank you.
("Yesterday, Today, and
Tomorrow" by PROJECT 7)
YICHEN!
Way to go!
(You can listen to the original tracks...)
(of the Final Match on
the music streaming sites.)
Let's go, MAJINGXIANG!
YICHEN.
(MAJINGXIANG)
(KIM SIHUN)
(Including small and cute
items that the trainees love)
(There's even a cozy
bed. Where is this place?)
(A pajama party on PROJECT 7)
- It's 9pm. - Let's get it.
- Let's go. - Let's go!
Let's have a pajama party.
Let's have fun. Let's go!
Clap!
No way.
You look like Principal Ench.
Right, I'm that man.
We have one dinosaur called Dooly.
This is really cute.
(And two cats)
We should put this down.
What?
(The MCs for the pajama
party Part 1 appear.)
- Assemble and upgrade, PROJECT 7.
- PROJECT 7.
(Assemble and upgrade, PROJECT 7.)
They sounded like him.
They sounded exactly like him.
- You sound just like him.
- You sound exactly like him.
Hello, I'm one of the MCs...
for 2024 PROJECT 7 Award Ceremony,
- AHN JUNWON. - I'm KIM SUNGMIN.
This is the one and only
award ceremony in the world.
The 2024 PROJECT 7 Award Ceremony...
will start now.
It's starting now.
(I really can't wait!)
You're good.
KENSHIN, which award would you like to win?
A cute award.
Cute Trainee Award?
What about you, BINGHUA?
What kind of award do you expect to win?
Tough Man Award.
Tough Man Award?
(BINGHUA wants to win Tough Man Award.)
No way.
Trainee BINGHUA, do you have a conscience?
We will announce the award winners.
First of all, YICHEN, please come up.
Me?
(YICHEN is the first
honorable award winner.)
Is this done 1 by 1?
I'm curious.
(What kind of award will YICHEN win?)
This award is given...
to a good son who listens to his mom.
(Good Son Who Listens to His Mom Award)
- Is he a good son? Why? - Good Son Award.
After his mom kicked
him out and scolded him,
- he became a good son. - Really?
That's why he got scolded.
(I'm happy even if I'm scolded.)
(What YICHEN's mother who's in China said)
(That's not what I taught you.)
She scolded him.
Since then, he has been
saying "Everyone, join me."
He changed completely including
his gentle way of talking and look.
As he acted as a good
son who listens to his mom,
this award is given to him.
- Do you obey your mom? - Of course.
- He's a good son. - Really?
He's a good son.
Congratulations.
- Congratulations, YICHEN.
- Congratulations.
- Congratulations. - It's an award.
I'm really obedient towards my mom.
The next award is called...
I Put It in My Assembly Basket Award.
What does "basket" mean?
It might be someone who
got many Assembly Votes.
Is it KENSHIN?
- Or SEUNGHO? - Is it one of us?
The award goes to WOO HAJOON.
Please come out.
- Congratulations. - It's HAJOON.
His "Time After Time" costume
looked like a shopping basket,
and so it became the talk of the town.
Compared to before, his
ranking increased by a lot.
This award is given to him as
we can't wait to see his next move.
Gosh.
That's the best award.
- Congratulations. - Nice.
The next award is given...
to someone who made many
people laugh on PROJECT 7.
Since When Were You So Funny Award.
KANG HYUNWOO Award?
It must be KANG HYUNWOO.
LYNNLYNN, please come out.
(It's LYNNLYNN, not KANG HYUNWOO.)
That's true. "Please."
Congratulations.
On PROJECT 7,
LYNNLYNN's Korean has
been improving every day.
Not only can he sing,
dance, and speak Korean,
but he also has a sense of humor in Korean.
We recognize him for
making many trainees laugh.
That's why this award is given to him.
LYNNLYNN has been
looking his best these days.
The next award is...
Sculpture Even When He's Crying Award.
Oh, my gosh.
Sculpture Award?
(During the last 4 months of PROJECT 7)
(the trainees cried a lot.)
- We should comfort him. - It's okay.
(Which of them cried the most beautifully?)
Congratulations, BINGHUA. Please come out.
The queen of tears.
- You're beautiful. - Congratulations.
He looks like a princess.
The queen of tears looks beautiful.
As the sensitive and sympathetic type,
he cried a lot throughout the show.
Among PROJECT 7 trainees,
he had the most crying scenes.
BINGHUA tugged at World
Assemblers' heartstrings.
People were impressed by...
how beautiful he looked
even when he was crying.
In hopes that he'll only
cry out of happiness,
this award is given to him.
Please don't cry anymore.
(He tries to hold back his tears.)
This award is called...
MAJUNG Award.
(Next award is MAJUNG Award.)
What? MAJUNG Award?
- MAJUNG Award. - It must be for you.
- The award... - Is it for me?
I will work harder until the final round.
I love you.
Congratulations, that was MAJINGXIANG.
The next award is called...
Eardrums Got Melted Award.
The main vocalist.
It's Most Frequent Leader Award.
KIM SIHUN kept being the leader.
I love you.
(I Love You Award)
Goodness.
Don't stop him. Just wait.
I'm about to attack him in five seconds.
Give it to me.
It's called Cuteness Overcomes All Award.
- Is he cute? - Congratulations.
Yes, he's cuter than you.
He's cute.
You Smile At Me Like This Award.
(He's also smiling.)
Successful Trainee From Gyeryong Award.
(The buttocks of KYOUNGBAE
who's opinionated)
His buttocks. Hold on.
Look at his buttocks.
I don't want to look at them.
The next award is called...
The Gap is Insanely Huge Award.
- The Gap is Insanely Huge Award.
- The Gap is Insanely Huge Award?
- Why? - KIM JEONGMIN.
What about me?
- HYUNWOO. - Is it me?
- It's either JEONGMIN or HYUNWOO.
- KIM HYUNWOO.
I think that it's HYUNWOO.
We need to be consistent.
It's KIM HYUNWOO who isn't consistent.
Congratulations, HYUNWOO.
(It's an athletic meet.)
KIM HYUNWOO is called
PROJECT 7's main dancer...
you can count on.
Unlike being innocent
and mischievous like usual,
he completely changes
and becomes charismatic...
when he's on stage.
With the shocking gap in personality,
he won the hearts of the World Assemblers.
That's why the award goes to him.
(He tries to look amazing...)
(but fails.)
(Trembling yellow socks)
What's that?
It's "Jealousy."
(He's back to being innocent KIM HYUNWOO.)
Congratulations.
This award is very "SHALALA."
Go up, SEUNGHO.
You can tell that it's "SHALALA" from afar.
(You can tell that it's
"SHALALA" from afar.)
We got the bow.
With his pretty looks,
SONG SEUNGHO makes
other trainees around him happy.
During Original Matching, he
showed off his lovely charms.
He was noticed by many World Assemblers.
As he made the stage shine like "SHALALA,"
the award goes to him.
- HO SEUNGSONG. - You're handsome.
HO SEUNGSONG.
For the next award,
only one person comes to mind.
I didn't expect such a name for an award.
It's called...
Happy Nutria Award.
(Happy Nutria Award)
- It's finally here. - What is it?
We don't know who it is yet.
We don't know yet.
KANG HYUNWOO, please come out.
- Yes. - Oh, yes.
He brought laughter and
energy to Project Village.
As he always had the look for Happy Nutria,
the award goes to him.
Postscript. Happy Nutria, Happy New Year.
Help him.
The name of this award is very sexy.
Puddle in the Collarbone Award.
- The buttocks? - What did you say?
Puddle in the Collarbone.
Right here.
(This is a puddle in the collarbone.)
Thank you.
- I can't see your collarbone.
- Congratulations.
Thank you.
The next award is...
Good Job on Korean Award.
KENSHIN.
- KENSHIN. - Me?
SAKURADA KENSHIN, please come out.
Thank you.
(As a beginner in Korean,
he could only say hello.)
Nice to meet you.
"I love you, girls."
"Girls, please love us."
As we're proud of him
for learning Korean...
that stole the hearts of many
girls, this award goes to him.
(Here is another heartbreaker.)
Becoming Girls Award.
I wasn't going to say it today.
Come on, girls.
(Feeling embarrassed by
JEONGMIN's acting cute)
The next award is...
Human Sleeping Pill Award.
It must be NAM JIWOON.
Why? Is it because he sleeps a lot?
No.
He talks slowly.
Yes.
(Passing out right away)
(Snoring)
- What? - This is NAM JIWOON.
This is NAM JIWOON.
- Have you started? - Yes.
Did I really fall asleep?
By making more trainees fall asleep,
I'll become more suitable for this award.
- He's slow. - Thank you.
- He's really slow. - He talks very slowly.
JIWOON.
Finally, we have only one award to give.
Cute Cutlet.
- Pork Cutlet. - Pork Cutlet.
This award is Popular Big Brother Award.
JEON MINWOOK.
Congratulations, MINWOOK.
One of the eldest trainees on PROJECT 7,
JEON MINWOOK always tries to help out...
his younger members and the team.
He's popular among all the trainees.
- Right. - That's corruption.
That's corruption.
That's why this award goes to him.
All right.
- I like MINWOOK. - Yes.
- I like him, too. - Me too.
- Thank you. - MINWOOK, you're so cute.
Is there any award for the MCs?
Hello.
I'm Special MC SEO KYOUNGBAE.
I'm JUNG SEYUN.
- You're amazing. - All right.
There's also an award for
MC JUNWON and SUNGMIN.
- What is it? - AHN JUNWON.
(He makes himself nervous.)
Skill Improvement is Breaking News Award.
(Skill Improvement is Breaking News Award)
Breaking news.
The main character of the event is here
There's something moving about it.
It's really moving.
That's amazing.
Amazing.
What kind of award...
will go to SUNGMIN?
He went out on his own.
Morning Sun in Cold Winter Award.
- What? - What did you say?
- Morning Sun... - It's called...
Morning Sun in Cold Winter Award.
Whatever the situation,
KIM SUNGMIN never lost his bright smile.
As his smile melted the cold dormitory,
this award goes to him.
(Sparkling)
KIM SUNGMIN, you look handsome.
I will keep trying to smile.
- Thank you. - Gosh.
That was nice and clean.
All right.
Unfortunately, this is the end...
of the 2024 PROJECT 7 Award Ceremony.
Good job, guys.
That's a bummer.
Next time,
I hope that all 21 of us will succeed...
and meet at a real award ceremony.
That's moving.
This was one-day MC AHN JUNWON.
And KIM SUNGMIN.
- Thank you.
- Give them a round of applause.
Well done.
(2024 PROJECT 7 Award Ceremony is over.)
(Next up is the pajama party Part 2!)
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
PROJECT 7 End of the Year Awards...
Keyword Talk, I'm your MC,
Cutie KIM JEONGMIN.
(Part 2 MC KIM JEONGMIN)
Cutie. What?
It can be said that all 21 trainees here...
dedicated their everything
on PROJECT 7 in 2024.
They worked very hard only for PROJECT 7.
- Right. - That's true.
Shall we reflect on the year 2024...
and recall the past
according to the keywords?
- Okay. - Okay.
Here we go.
The keyword is Friendship Among Men.
"Friendship Among Men?"
To narrow down 200 trainees to 21,
we said goodbye to many people.
It couldn't be helped
because it's a survival show,
but we can never get
used to saying goodbye.
It's so hard to get a
chance to perform with you.
- Seriously. - I know what you mean.
Is there any eliminated trainee
whom you miss the most?
There are so many.
I can think of so many people.
- There are many. - ABE YURA.
There's one person.
I really miss JEONG DEUNHAESOL.
During our practice for
"3D," he was very helpful.
He relied on him a lot.
So I miss him very much.
I really miss SVIAT.
SVIAT, are you doing well?
Don't eat too much snack. I love you.
I miss FONG ATILLA.
- ATILLA. - ATILLA.
My friend.
- You can do it, my friend. - My friend.
(You can do it, my friend.)
We've gotten very close on PROJECT 7.
- Yes. - Right.
Before PROJECT 7 is over,
is there any trainee that
you feel awkward with?
Yes, there is.
(Yes, there is.)
Why does he sound so positive about it?
Among the remaining trainees,
there's only one who's my age.
- Mr. KIM SUNGMIN. - Yes?
He calls him Mr. SUNGMIN.
Mr. KIM SUNGMIN?
Hold hands and talk
while looking at each other.
- Seriously? - Make...
three compliments about each other.
I didn't expect it to become a big deal.
- Say three of his strengths. - Okay.
Say each other's strengths.
This feels so awkward.
It's so awkward.
When I saw SUNGMIN for the first time...
- Look at him in the eye.
- Make eye contact.
- For the first time...
- Look at him in the eye.
Make eye contact.
(They can't hide feeling
awkward and embarrassed.)
At first...
Keep looking at him in the eye.
You have a nicely proportioned body.
You're very handsome.
It's good to see you work hard.
(Cringing)
What are you guys doing?
You won't be close friends.
- What are you doing? - The two of them...
(Stammering)
YEOJUN.
They might grow apart even more.
You reminded me of DOYOUNG
of NCT when I first saw you.
Don't say that.
I thought that you were handsome.
- What's wrong with you?
- They do look similar.
You're a good dancer.
I thought that I could practice with you...
if we got on the same team.
I imagined it several times.
I see.
- Thank you. - Thank you?
- Let's be friends. - I love you.
I love you too.
- You two should be friends.
- That was so awkward.
I shouldn't have said it. It's so awkward.
This is really awkward.
Tonight is our last
night in Project Village.
I'm sure that you spent...
an unforgettable year on PROJECT 7.
Tell us your new goals...
and resolutions in 2025.
I want to sing a lot, which is what I love.
I won Eardrums Got Melted Award.
Performing as much as possible...
to melt more people's
eardrums is my resolution.
I hope that next year,
all 100 trainees on the show...
will make their debut somewhere.
And we'll get to perform together.
- I agree. - Yes.
I hope that we'll be more amazing than now.
That sounds good.
All right.
Isn't this our first time...
that 21 of us gathered for a talk?
You're right.
We should have tangerines.
- Good job, JEONGMIN. - You worked hard.
- Well done. - Well done, JEONGMIN.
(It's already time to sleep
after a lot of laughing.)
- SUNGMIN, - Sleep well.
- SEUNGHO... - KYOUNGBAE.
SUNGMIN, on your right.
(They wrote in the practice
journal at the end of each day.)
We finally became successful.
(What will they write in their
last practice journal entry?)
Look at this.
Some days, I wrote
a lot. I wrote a lot too.
In September...
I was a leader in the center.
It was for "LALALALA."
I had a sense of responsibility then.
It probably wasn't obvious.
"HYUNWOO brought a lot of energy,"
"so I expected his energy
to continue on stage."
Yes.
"I don't think I'm fit for being a leader."
(Inside their practice journal, )
(there's a record of their
memories up to now.)
"If I can be in the next
project, I won't be the leader."
Weren't you being too honest?
This isn't a journal.
- It's an autobiography.
- It was difficult.
What's this?
(The trainees read their
journal and recall their past.)
Time passed by fast.
(The trainees read their
journal and recall their past.)
It's done.
My handwriting looks so good.
"Tonight is our last
night in Project Village."
"We had 6 projects
during the last 4 months."
"Both internally and
externally, my skills improved."
"I also matured a lot as a person."
"It seems like the second
turning point in my life."
"For me, 2024 was spent on PROJECT 7."
"Two hundred trainees..."
"and staff members, you worked very hard."
Thank you.
It was really moving.
(Snoring)
Now that I'm about to start...
- He's starting now. - He's starting now.
Here I go.
"I was busy today."
(Laughing)
"We had a talk that
we've been waiting for..."
"during the pajama party."
"The award ceremony made me realize..."
"that this is really the last time."
"The next time 21 of us gather again..."
"will be right before the performance."
"It makes me sad."
"I hope that everyone's
practice goes well until the 27th..."
"without getting injured."
"I also hope that the performance..."
"of the remaining three teams
will turn out to be their best."
"Good luck, everyone."
- You can do it. - Let's go.
We can do it.
"The practice journal that
started on September 6..."
"reached its end."
"Each of us had a different life..."
"before joining PROJECT
7 with one goal in mind."
"Only 21 out of 200 trainees remain now."
"I met many different friends,
sang and danced with them."
"It was very hard, but I was happy."
"I learned many things."
"I also met good
people in Project Village."
"I will never forget this place."
"Now, it's time for us to leave..."
"and show how amazing we
can be in the bigger world."
"I didn't vacate because I was nervous."
"The thought of vacating
after surviving until the end..."
"makes me feel proud of myself."
"I'd like to say to the 21
trainees that they worked hard."
"There were both sad and happy days."
"I want to thank myself
for overcoming them."
"Let's make our final
performance amazing..."
"and unforgettable."
"When there's a start,
there's always an end."
"After my experience here,"
"I think I can do well anything anywhere."
"I feel sad that this is our last day."
"We went through many difficult..."
"and joyful times, and I enjoyed them all."
"This experience has been very precious."
"I made many friends."
"I learned and grew a lot too."
"It will be the last day
and our last time together."
"I hope to achieve what I
want to do in the future."
"I can do it."
"It's a message..."
"to myself now and in the future."
"From the first step I
took in the hot summer,"
"difficult days started."
It looks so pretty.
(PROJECT 7 trainees took their
first step during the hot summer.)
"After a long journey, PROJECT 7 is..."
"coming to an end in the cold winter."
"Every day had been difficult."
(Days that weren't always easy)
"Trainees who overcame
the hardship together."
"I'd simply like to say this."
"Well done, everyone."
"December 21, 2024."
"KYOUNGBAE who loves everyone."
That was great.
- We wrote a letter to us. - That's insane.
I have affections for you too.
- I love you. - "Affections?"
(PROJECT 7 practice journal
is completed up to the last page.)
For the final performance, we
should take care of ourselves.
JIWOON, could you say something?
Here we go.
Sleep well.
Sleep well. Sweet dreams.
(It's really time to fall asleep.)
- Sweet dreams, everyone.
- I can't sleep right away.
My goodness.
Goodnight, everyone.
(Their last night, another
unforgettable memory)
This is live PROJECT 7.
The real-time global voting has ended.
What you've been waiting for the most.
The final ranking of the trainees...
will be announced soon.
(Final Top 7 will be announced.)
Tonight,
final seven trainees to make
their debut will be decided.
The score of the fourth global
voting that took place for a week,
the real-time global voting score,
and...
the directors' scores will be totaled...
to decide the final group to debut.
For the last time,
I will call out the names...
of the 21 trainees.
KANG HYUNWOO.
KIM SUNGMIN.
KIM SIHUN.
KIM JEONGMIN.
KIM HYUNWOO.
NAM JIWOON.
LYNNLYNN.
MAJINGXIANG.
PARK JUNSEO.
BINGHUA.
SAKURADA KENSHIN.
SEO KYOUNGBAE.
SONG SEUNGHO.
AHN JUNWON.
ANDY.
WOO HAJOON.
YOO YOUNGSEO.
YICHEN.
JANG YEOJUN.
JEON MINWOOK.
JUNG SEYUN.
Among them,
only seven of them will make
their debut dream come true.
Unfortunately,
the 14 trainees who won't get selected...
will stop their journey
towards their dream.
PROJECT 7's...
Top Seven.
I will announce them now.
(Stepping up from "Boys Planet")
The trainees to debut will be named...
in order from 6th to 1st place.
The member in seventh place,
the last one to join CLOSE YOUR EYES...
will be announced at the end.
(SONG SEUNGHO, JUNWON)
(MINWOOk, SONG SEUNGHO)
Who will be the last top seven...
and join CLOSE YOUR EYES,
the top boy group in the world?
Now,
I will announce the final ranking...
and names of the final trainees to debut...
selected by the World Assemblers.
When your name is called, please come out.
First, it's the trainee in sixth place...
who will join...
CLOSE YOUR EYES.
(Debut member, 6th place)
(6th place)
This trainee is...
one of those who almost didn't make...
the cut.
During today's Final Match,
his facial expression was perfect.
It completed the performance.
One word that describes...
this trainee would be "passion."
He persevered until the final with passion.
A trainee who will make his debut
as a member of CLOSE YOUR EYES.
(6th place)
The sixth-place winner who
must've been the most desperate.
His final score...
is 4,027,238 points.
(I came to see KIM HYUNWOO.)
JANG YEOJUN.
(Final Top 7, 6th place JANG YEOJUN)
It's JANG YEOJUN. Congratulations.
(6th place)
(JANG YEOJUN)
Congratulations, YEOJUN.
Trainee JANG YEOJUN, please step forward.
As his last attempt...
to become an idol singer,
JANG YEOJUN participated in PROJECT 7.
(YEOJUN)
Feeling more desperate
and passionate than anyone,
he successfully moved the
hearts of the World Assemblers.
He made his dream of debuting come true.
I congratulate you wholeheartedly.
JANG YEOJUN, your speech, please.
Hello, this is JANG YEOJUN.
(JANG YEOJUN)
(6th place, final score
of 4,027,238 points)
I ranked...
eighth during the interim check.
That's why...
I didn't prepare my speech...
as not to expect anything.
But...
PROJECT 7...
(JANG YEOJUN)
People at BEICOS and everyone else...
who helped me join PROJECT 7.
I'd like to thank all of you.
(JANG YEOJUN is debuting!)
Also...
In the audience, CHANYONG,
Mom, Dad, and Ha Ram.
I made my debut.
Also, outside of the show,
they geniunely helped me.
I'd like to thank...
those five directors.
All the staff members on PROJECT 7,
thank you very much.
And...
all the trainees...
whom I competed with,
thank you so much.
Thank you.
World...
World Assemblers.
I love you!
(JANG YEOJUN)
JANG YEOJUN.
His debut has been confirmed.
Please take the sixth-place seat.
Everyone knows how
desperate JANG YEOJUN was.
His parents in the
audience, World Assemblers,
and all the other trainees...
are congratulating YEOJUN's debut.
I hope you don't forget
the passion you've shown...
and become an idol...
who continues to strive until the end.
Next,
this is the trainee who will be
making his debut as the fifth place.
(The fifth member to debut)
This trainee...
(5th place)
is a trainee who looks the
happiest when he's on stage.
With his distinct facial features,
he is the visual center
member with a cute smile.
He's the visual center trainee.
Despite his young age,
this trainee always showed...
the best performance with a wide spectrum.
The trainee who will debut as a
member of CLOSE YOUR EYES.
The trainee in 5th place
who will take a spot in Top 7.
The final score of the
trainee in fifth place...
is 4,128,532 points.
It's Trainee SONG...
SEUNGHO.
(Final Top 7, 5th place SONG SEUNGHO)
Trainee SONG SEUNGHO, congratulations.
(SONG SEUNGHO)
On PROJECT 7, Trainee SONG SEUNGHO...
not only showed a great performance...
but legendary good looks
as well during every project,
capturing the hearts of
the World Assemblers.
He also showed great improvements...
with efforts that everyone approved of.
As a trainee with good
looks and great skills,
he made his dream of debuting come true.
Congratulations once again.
(SONG SEUNGHO)
Please give us your speech.
Hello, I'm SONG SEUNGHO.
(5th SONG SEUNGHO, )
(Final score: 4,128,532)
First of all,
to the trainees who performed with me...
in P5, Team "SHALALA,"
Team "LALALALA," Team "Merry-Go-Round,"
and Team "PSYCHO." Thank you so much.
Although we didn't get to debut together,
JEONGMIN and SEYUN.
Thank you so much for leading me so far.
I'll do well, so please root for me.
Also, our directors.
Director RyuD, Director
Bada, Director Hae In,
Director Ryan Sewon Jhun,
and Director Ha Sung Woon.
Thank you so much.
I'll work even harder and
show better performances.
World Assemblers, thank you!
SEUNGHO showed amazing growth on the show.
Is there anything that
changed while you were...
on PROJECT 7?
Actually, I hadn't performed much on stage.
No, I nearly had zero experience.
At first, I was really nervous.
But thanks to the cheers and support...
from the World Assemblers,
I got to enjoy performing on stage.
Trainee SONG SEUNGHO.
He took a spot in Top Seven.
Please take a seat...
in the fifth place.
With his outstanding stage manners...
and great looks,
Trainee SONG SEUNGHO stole
the hearts of many World Assemblers.
I really hope you'll be
able to become an idol...
who gets approved by the global fans...
by stealing more hearts
of the World Assemblers.
(SEUNGHO)
(SEUNGHO, YEOJUN)
Next.
I'll debut the next member
of CLOSE YOUR EYES.
The trainee in fourth
place will be revealed now.
(Debut member, 4th place)
This trainee proved that
he could pull off any part...
that was given to him.
Normally, he looks shy,
but he exudes great
power and energy on stage.
It's the trainee who wants to hear,
"Let's debut" from the World Assemblers.
Now.
The trainee in fourth place...
who will join CLOSE YOUR
EYES. I'll announce him now.
(4th place)
The trainee in fourth place to
enjoy the pleasure of debuting.
With a total score...
of 4,285,473...
It's Trainee SEO KYOUNGBAE.
(Final Top 7, 4th SEO KYOUNGBAE)
Congratulations on winning fourth place.
Please come forward.
(Let's debut, SEO KYOUNGBAE.)
Trainee SEO KYOUNGBAE
challenged himself to become an idol...
for the first time through PROJECT 7.
He started off in 19th
place on the 1st week,
but he showed incredible growth...
and earned popularity.
He kept rising as the leading
candidate to make his debut.
In the end, he realized
his dream of debuting.
Congratulations.
You're joining the debut
team in fourth place.
Please tell us how you feel.
Hello. I'm SEO KYOUNGBAE.
(4th place, SEO KYOUNGBAE)
(Final score: 4,285,473)
First of all,
(SEO KYOUNGBAE)
I'd like to thank...
the World Assemblers for supporting me...
to take this honor.
Thank you so much.
Also,
my family who supported me...
during my journey on PROJECT 7.
I made them go through so much.
(Let's debut, SEO KYOUNGBAE.)
Now that I'm debuting,
please forgive me.
All right.
Thank you so much for joining my journey...
on PROJECT 7.
I'll greet you again...
through a new chapter, CLOSE YOUR EYES.
Thank you!
(SEO KYOUNGBAE, let's debut.)
The youngest trainee on PROJECT
7, Trainee SEO KYOUNGBAE.
Is there anything you want
to say to the fellow trainees?
Guys.
Thank you so much for
being with me for five months.
I learned a lot from you.
I hope you know that this isn't the end.
I hope...
we can grab a meal later.
I love you.
Trainee SEO KYOUNGBAE,
congratulations once again.
You can take the fourth-place seat.
Actually, Trainee SEO
KYOUNGBAE cried by himself...
on the first night here...
as he wasn't familiar with
the place and was tired.
But he grew strong in no time...
and became someone who could console...
the World Assemblers,
and I'm proud of him for that.
I hope you'll become an idol who grows...
with the World Assemblers.
I'll sincerely root for you.
After working hard for three
months, this trainee got to debut...
in third place. I'll announce him now.
(Debut member, 3rd place)
This trainee is both talented and charming.
In every project, he
showed off his presence.
Even during difficult times, he
didn't show he was struggling.
He quietly held out...
and became even stronger.
(3rd place)
This trainee...
is getting lots of love from every trainee.
The trainee who will debut...
in third place, carrying
many people's wish.
(3rd place)
The trainee in third place...
received...
a total score...
of 5,053,962.
It's Trainee JEON MINWOOK.
Congratulations.
(Final Top 7, 3rd place JEON MINWOOK)
(JEON MINWOOK)
Trainee JEON MINWOOK,
congratulations once again.
Please come forward.
Trainee JEON MINWOOK kept first place...
for the 1st and 2nd Passing Ceremony.
He was chosen as the
trainee who'd certainly debut.
He continued to receive lots of
love from the World Assemblers.
And without any surprise,
he succeeded in debuting in third place.
Congratulations.
(MINWOOK)
Trainee JEON MINWOOK who won third place.
Please say a word.
Hello, I'm JEON MINWOOK.
(3rd place JEON MINWOOK)
(Final score: 5,053,962)
From the start of PROJECT 7...
and until now,
I could be in a high rank...
thanks to the World Assemblers...
who gave me lots of support
and love. Thank you so much.
Thank you.
(JEON MINWOOK)
(I'm always on your side, JEON MINWOOK.)
Also, the directors who helped
us regardless of the show.
Even after PROJECT 7 ended,
they helped us grow even more.
RyuD, Bada, SUNG WOON, and Ryan Sewon Jhun.
Director Hae In.
And MC Soo Hyuk. Thank you so much.
Is there anyone you're
most reminded of right now?
Right now... My mom.
Please say something to your mother.
(I'm always on your side, JEON MINWOOK.)
I don't think there hasn't been a moment...
when I thought I made you proud.
But I hope I made you proud tonight.
I love you, Mom.
(I'm always on your side, JEON MINWOOK.)
Trainee JEON MINWOOK.
Congratulations on your new beginning.
Please take the third-place seat.
In every project, Trainee JEON MINWOOK...
participated sincerely...
with responsibility for
his performance and team.
I hope you'll continue to
be sincere in everything...
and show great performances
to the World Assemblers.
I'll root for you.
(3rd place)
Assemble and upgrade,
PROJECT 7.
Now, only first-place winner...
and second-place winner
are left to be announced.
The honorable first-place candidates...
whom the World Assemblers chose themselves.
Who are the two candidates?
(The 1st-place candidates
to make their debut)
The trainee who will make his
debut as the first-place winner.
Who could it be?
(1st-place candidates)
I'll announce the 2
candidates for 1st place.
(1st-place candidates)
PROJECT 7.
The final candidates for first place.
(1st-place candidates)
The two candidates.
It's Trainee MAJINGXIANG...
and Trainee SAKURADA KENSHIN.
Trainee MAJINGXIANG and
Trainee SAKURADA KENSHIN...
are the final candidates
of 1st and 2nd place...
of PROJECT 7.
The two candidates, please come forward.
Trainee MAJINGXIANG is someone
who can reinterpret any song...
in his style...
with his deep voice.
And we can easily call
him the symbol of hard work.
He's more serious about
practicing than anyone.
Also, he expresses his love
for the World Assemblers...
whenever he has a chance.
He's a trainee who loves his fans the most.
Trainee SAKURADA KENSHIN...
overcame exhausting training...
on PROJECT 7 with his bright smile.
(Final Top 7, 1st-place
candidate SAKURADA KENSHIN)
He shocked the World
Assemblers with his loveliness...
as soon as he made his appearance.
He's a trainee in the top rank...
who maintained his
position in 1st and 2nd place.
Among the two candidates,
there's a final winner...
chosen by the World Assemblers.
(KENSHIN, MAJINGXIANG)
Before announcing...
the final winner...
Trainee MAJINGXIANG.
Yes.
How do you feel to be
a first-place candidate?
I never imagined myself...
being a first-place candidate...
in the Final Match.
The World Assemblers...
and those who continued to
support me and the directors.
And the production crew. Thank you so much.
I got to earn a chance
to win first place...
thanks to the support you always give me.
It's...
(I'm here to see MAJINGXIANG.)
I can't explain this feeling.
It's so...
Mom. Mom, I love you.
I must say...
(MAJINGXIANG, to the top)
I know I've made this promise,
and I'm going to keep it...
by meeting you,
World Assemblers, every single day.
I love you. I won't let you down.
Now the other first-place
candidate, SAKURADA KENSHIN.
Yes.
How do you feel to be
a first-place candidate?
First off, I'm so delighted
that I can make a debut.
And...
I'd like to give thanks...
to Director RyuD, Director
Bada, Director Lee Hae In,
Director Ha Sung Woon, Director Ryan Jhun,
and MC Lee Soo Hyuk. Thank you so much.
And...
I'd like to give thanks to my family.
Thank you.
And...
I'd like to give thanks...
to the other trainees
who have trained with me.
I'm looking forward to placing first.
All right, now.
Between MAJINGXIANG and SAKURADA KENSHIN,
who is the first-place winner?
I wonder...
who will be seated at the top
of the final seven trainees...
between MAJINGXIANG and SAKURADA KENSHIN?
The 1st-place winner of PROJECT 7.
(Who is the final 1st-place winner?)
(KENSHIN)
(MAJINGXIANG, to the top)
The winner has received...
a final score...
of 6,004,528.
(To be continued)
The first-place winner...
will be announced after commercials.
Assemble and upgrade,
PROJECT 7.
The glorious first-place
winner is left to be announced.
(I'm here to see MAJINGXIANG.)
(KENSHIN)
All right. Let me announce the winner.
The 1st-place winner of PROJECT 7.
(MAJINGXIANG, to the top)
The winner has received...
a final score...
of 6,004,528.
He has received a score of 6,004,528.
It's Trainee MAJINGXIANG. Congratulations.
(MAJINGXIANG is the
1st-place winner of the final top 7.)
MAJINGXIANG practiced day and night...
to improve more each time,
and like his signature greeting,
"To the top,"
(MAJINGXIANG, to the top)
he has reached the top at last.
Congratulations.
We'll look forward to
seeing your new charms...
which you will show as
part of CLOSE YOUR EYES.
(MAJINGXIANG, to the top)
Trainee MAJINGXIANG,
you've achieved your dream to
debut as the first-place winner.
Please say a word.
Okay.
I love you so much,
World Assemblers.
Mom, I love you too.
She's watching this right here today.
Mom.
I love you.
And...
I actually...
- Well... - You can feel free...
to speak to your mother in Chinese.
Sure.
Since a year ago,
I've wanted to make a debut.
But at that time,
I wasn't good enough...
to achieve my dream.
I was truly sorry for it.
So,
I'd like to say to my fans
and World Assemblers...
who have supported me
that I love them so much.
I always tell them that I'm sorry.
Whenever I check the Internet,
they always tell me not to get intimidated.
So I'm not going to cry today.
I'm going to make a happy smile today.
And my wish is for World Assemblers...
to be healthy and happy every day.
I'd also like to meet World
Assemblers every day.
To the top.
Please remember my name. I love you.
Now,
I'd like to say a word in Chinese.
I love you.
I'm not so good at speaking Japanese,
but I'll learn a lot from KENSHIN.
I'm sorry.
And I'd like to give
thanks to the directors...
for supporting and helping me...
whenever I was struggling.
I love you so much.
And the production crew.
The producers and scriptwriters...
always had meals with us every day.
We met and spent time together every day.
Actually, I was in bad condition yesterday.
I was very sick.
And the production crew...
looked after me as if I was their family.
Now that I did the best I
could and got to make a debut...
through PROJECT 7,
I'd like to send thanks and
love to the production crew.
(MAJINGXIANG,
congratulations on your debut.)
Congratulations once again.
And with a final score...
of 5,107,798,
Trainee SAKURADA KENSHIN...
placed second.
(SAKURADA KENSHIN is...)
(the 2nd-place winner of the final top 7.)
SAKURADA KENSHIN has the charm...
of making everyone smile...
with his positive energy
which no one can refuse.
Throughout the show,
he has been adored by everyone.
(KENSHIN, I love you forever.)
(KENSHIN)
I'll support him to be an idol singer...
who delivers happiness
through amazing performances.
Now, let's hear a word...
from the second-place
winner, SAKURADA KENSHIN.
Yes.
(2nd, SAKURADA KENSHIN)
Dear World Assemblers,
thank you so much for your votes.
There's a story...
I'd like to share with you.
I'm not so good at Korean yet,
so let me read this slowly.
Until two years ago...
when I was...
a freshman in high school,
I lived in Aomori...
located below Hokkaido of Japan.
At that time, I was
simply a high schooler...
who liked K-pop.
During my...
freshman...
During my freshman year,
something happened that changed me.
(KENSHIN)
In February of my
freshman year in high school,
my family...
suffered from a big fire accident.
A big fire accident.
Everything in our house
was burned to ashes.
The cause...
of the fire...
was the cables on the roof.
There was nothing...
our family could do to prevent it.
I couldn't take anything from the house.
Everything was burned to ashes.
Fortunately,
no one got hurt.
However...
But after that day,
I happened to lose my smile.
Just by seeing a flame, my body shook.
I felt lethargic...
and depressed.
But I didn't stop...
taking dance lessons...
because when I danced,
I could forget about the fire accident...
and enjoy that moment.
(KENSHIN)
(Please hug me.)
I realized...
how precious music was to me.
When I told my parents,
they suggested I take it more seriously.
So I dropped out of high school...
and joined a dance school in Tokyo alone.
After that, I happened...
to pass the audition...
and come to Korea alone.
My family...
must've worried...
a lot about me...
for chasing my dream alone.
But they trusted my smile...
and sent me here.
Throughout PROJECT 7,
I tried to smile as much as I could.
I wonder if I could deliver you...
how precious a smile is...
at least by a bit.
I hope your everyday life...
is full of what makes you smile.
I'll try my best...
to be an idol singer...
who always makes you smile.
I want to do that for you no matter what.
I'll keep doing my best.
(KENSHIN)
And...
I'd like to give thanks...
to the directors,
my family,
and the other trainees.
And...
I want to talk about my friend, ANDY.
During the Zero Setting,
I was on good terms with him at first.
I didn't know,
but ANDY...
I'll do the best I can. Thank you.
The two trainees achieved
their dream to make a debut.
Congratulations to you both.
Please sit down on the
1st and 2nd place seats.
And please don't forget
your resolution today...
and be amazing in your career...
so that you can live up
to the trust and choice...
that the World Assemblers have given you.
Please be seated, both of you.
(2nd place)
Congratulations.
(MAJINGXIANG)
All right, now.
It's time to announce...
the last member...
of CLOSE YOUR EYES.
(The last and 7th debuting member)
As the final 7th-place winner of PROJECT 7,
this trainee will join CLOSE YOUR EYES.
The name...
will be revealed shortly.
Assemble and upgrade,
PROJECT 7.
We only have the last
seventh-place winner...
left to announce.
A total of 15 trainees...
haven't been named yet.
Who will be...
the only trainee that will
join CLOSE YOUR EYES...
as the last member?
(Who is the last and 7th debuting member?)
(7th place)
After the four-month journey,
who will get to achieve
his dream to make a debut?
He has put everyone
in awe by showing off...
his beautiful dance moves
during the performance today.
In any situation,
this trainee never loses his bright smile.
He's charming like a human Retriever.
This trainee is known
for his splendid smile.
The last and 7th debuting
member of PROJECT 7.
The trainee...
in the last place of the top seven is...
He has received...
a final score of 3,656,653.
(7th place)
Congratulations.
It's Trainee KIM SUNGMIN.
(KIM SUNGMIN is...)
(the 7th-place winner of the final top 7.)
(SUNGMIN, let's debut!)
Trainee KIM SUNGMIN,
congratulations once
again. Please come forward.
Through PROJECT 7, he received...
dance and singing
lessons for the first time,
growing his dream to become an idol singer.
Each project,
(KIM SUNGMIN)
he constantly made hard efforts.
(SUNGMIN, let's debut.)
As a result, he managed to improve
more than all the other trainees...
and safely made it to the debuting group.
He started from zero...
and came all the way up to making a debut.
Congratulations.
Trainee KIM SUNGMIN, please say a word.
(7th, KIM SUNGMIN)
I was named as an
elimination candidate earlier,
so when I performed "Antidote,"
I was worried if I was
getting the choreography right.
I wasn't sure if I could
pull off the performance.
Thank you for giving me this seventh place.
For supporting me to place seventh,
I'd like to give thanks to
the World Assemblers...
and my beloved grandma,
aunt, uncle,
and sisters. I love you all.
My parents couldn't make
it here today due to work.
I'd like to say that I love them so much.
And the directors helped me a lot...
so I could improve. I love you so much!
Yesterday was my birthday.
For you,
I practiced with the other
trainees in the training room.
I wondered...
(KIMSUNGMIN is debuting.)
how excitingly I should spend my birthday.
The trainees, the scriptwriters,
and the producers...
said happy birthday to me
as soon as it turned midnight.
It was so touching.
I wanted a debut...
for my birthday present.
And I'm so happy...
that I did get a debut...
as my birthday present.
I love you all.
(KIM SUNGMIN, let's debut.)
Trainee KIM SUNGMIN,
congratulations on your debut.
Please sit down in the seventh-place seat.
The last trainee that the
World Assemblers assembled...
for CLOSE YOUR EYES...
was Trainee KIM SUNGMIN.
Congratulations.
The special real-time
broadcast of PROJECT 7.
As a result of the voting
done by the World Assemblers,
the final seven members of the
debuting group were selected.
The World Assemblers helped the trainees...
achieve their dreams to make a debut.
We send our sincere thanks...
to you all once again.
Assemble your very own idols.
PROJECT 7.
Here are the top 7 trainees of PROJECT 7...
and the members of CLOSE YOUR EYES...
selected by the World Assemblers.
CLOSE YOUR EYES will soon begin to race...
to become a top idol group.
Please keep supporting their activities.
Next week, on January 4...
at "Golden Disc Awards,"
you'll get to watch
their first performance.
Please give all your support.
We'd like to give our sincere
thanks to the World Assemblers...
for sending so much support
and love for almost four months.
(Please give a lot of support
and love to CLOSE YOUR EYES, )
(the world's top-class idol group.)
Of around 200 trainees
who tried out for PROJECT 7,
seven trainees achieved their
dream to make a debut today.
But the rest of the trainees,
around 190 of them,
will race more for their dream.
Dear World Assemblers,
please support their desperate journey...
for their incomplete dream until the end.
PROJECT 7 ends today,
but please give your
unchanging love and support...
to CLOSE YOUR EYES,
the seven members who achieved their dream.
(MAJINGXIANG)
(SEO KYOUNGBAE)
As...
another World Assembler
who supports the trainees...
and the host of PROJECT 7,
I happily enjoyed every moment with you.
Now,
let me express our gratitude
to you for the last time.
Dear World Assemblers,
thank you for loving the show.
(Dear World Assemblers, thank
you for watching PROJECT 7.)
All right, then.
With the lead of MAJINGXIANG,
the final 1st-place winner of PROJECT 7,
we'll say the last chant
to the World Assemblers.
- Trainee MAJINGXIANG. - Yes.
Please stand up and lead the chant.
Trainees of PROJECT 7,
chant to our dear World Assemblers.
- We'll do our best. - We'll do our best.