THE NINTH PLACE OF TRAINING, A QUIET BEACH
Did you bring us here to sell us off?
I wonder what we'll do today.
I feel so nervous. I mean, the beach?
Gosh, this is so fake. You made it look…
-So fake.
-…like we're on a vacation.
This is fake, isn't it?
If I knew, I would've brought my swimwear.
RIGHT THEN
-Hello.
-What are you, a tourist?
-What's going on?
-What?
DRESSED LIKE SOMEONE ON VACATION
-What is this?
-Why are you dressed up?
-I was told to wear a vacation outfit.
-Really?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
Hello, anchovies.
-Hello.
Judging by the coach's outfit,
can you guess what we'll do?
What could it be?
It's obviously a vacation outfit.
Vacation?
-Maybe we'll rest.
-It looks like a vacation outfit.
Your ninth mission is…
Today, you don't have a mission.
-What?
-For real?
You don't have a mission.
-What are you saying?
-Don't lie.
-Seriously?
-But there's the 12-hour timer.
-I know.
And there's even a massage bed.
Muscles damaged by exercise
recover and grow through rest.
Yes. That's right.
Rest is as important as exercise,
they say.
So we prepared this.
A self-sufficient vacation.
It's Anchovy Retreat.
"Retreat"?
You said it's a vacation.
Why is it a retreat?
You asked earlier why there was a timer.
You can enjoy your vacation
for 12 hours from now.
-What?
-For real? What's going on?
However,
you must earn the expenses yourselves.
Hold on.
Of course.
But how do we earn the expenses?
By doing the bodyweight exercises
you have done so far,
you can earn them.
We have to exercise after all.
Per push-up, sit-up, and squat,
you can earn 20 won.
If it's 20 won per one,
it's 200 won if you do 10.
Since the burpee test is more difficult,
it's 40 won per one.
With the money you earn by doing them,
you can have lunch and dinner.
What is this, Animal Crossing?
SELF-SUFFICIENT VACATION, ANCHOVY RETREAT
But it is a vacation.
The producers will count how many you do.
HOW TO WIN THE KEYCHAIN TODAY?
We'll give you guys lucky pouches.
The one with the most money at the end
wins the keychain.
So the one who exercises more,
earns more, and spends less
than the others wins the keychain.
To make it feel like a vacation,
we prepared outfits for you.
They may be in a floral pattern,
but they're prison uniforms.
The 12-hour vacation starts now.
FEELING AWKWARD TO JUST REST
ALL OF A SUDDEN
Gosh, this is pretty awkward.
I didn't expect this.
By the way, do you want
to have a big lunch or dinner?
No, I want a light one.
How about we have a light lunch
at a convenience store?
-Like cup noodles.
-Sounds good.
-Cup noodles.
-Right, I like that.
-So let's say we need 5,000 won each.
-Right.
It means we must do at least 250
to have lunch.
-For 5,000 won.
-Right.
-250 in total.
-Then first thing,
let's exercise to eat.
All right. Let's each do whatever we want.
DANIEL GETS STARTED FIRST
STARTING WITH BURPEES, THE HIGHEST VALUE
Forty won.
Two.
40 WON PER BURPEE
Three.
It's not going to work.
Burpees are too tiring.
Five.
-200 won?
-You earned 200 won?
-Pay him right away.
-What?
So you pay us right away like this?
-200 won?
-Seriously?
Oh, so you earn your money like this.
This isn't bad.
If you do some and rest and do some again,
it's doable.
TWINKLING EYES
You guys are all going to be rich today.
A SMILE SPREADS ACROSS HIS FACE?
I'll do 10 squats now.
You can do it whenever you want.
EVERYONE STARTS EARNING MONEY
BY DOING WHAT THEY'RE CONFIDENT IN
Five. I just earned 500 won.
I earned 500 won too.
How much did you earn, Jonathan?
-I earned 200 won.
-200 won?
600 won.
QUITE GOOD MONEY
Hey, how about we give it our all
-and earn like 10 million won?
-Hey.
Why buy a meal with it, then?
I'll just save it
and buy a house.
We'll finish it in no time.
I earned 500 won.
WITH A GOOD START, HE RESTS RIGHT AWAY
Seriously, this is not bad.
40 MINUTES INTO THE VACATION
Lying on the beach?
I haven't done this in ages.
LOOKING AROUND
I'm going to the restroom.
The restroom…
JONATHAN IS GOING TOWARD THE RESTROOM
How much is it?
It's 2,800 won.
2,800 WON OUT OF NOWHERE?
-Did you wait on purpose?
-Yes.
So they wouldn't see it?
That's right.
WHEN EVERYONE ELSE WAS RESTING
-600 won.
-Yes.
JONATHAN LOOKS SUSPICIOUS
Let's do this.
-They shouldn't be conscious of me.
-Right.
How much I earn, don't tell anyone but me.
To them,
I'm not doing anything, understand?
WHILE THE OTHERS WERE AWAY FOR A WHILE
HE EXERCISED HARD ALONE
Do you have a towel?
I don't want them to see me sweat.
You can't tell them how much I've earned.
If I fail to win the keychain today,
it's over for me,
so I had no choice.
I earn as much as I sweat.
I'll play fair and square
and win the keychain today.
Here,
I'll do 100.
PREPARING TO EARN
First,
to fool them…
1,000-WON BILLS IN HIS HANDS
GO INTO HIS UNDERWEAR
This money is my asset now.
I won't lose it unless someone touches it.
Depositing it in your underwear?
Yes, an underwear deposit.
-That's such a private place.
-Right.
Stop doing that.
GLANCING AROUND
TAKING SO LONG
TO SEE IF ANYONE'S WATCHING HIM
THEY HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT'S HAPPENING BEHIND THEM
HE'S EARNING MONEY FAIR AND SQUARE
DOING SQUATS LIKE A MEERKAT
By the way, what's Jonathan doing?
Sleeping? Maybe he's taking a nap?
Hey, he's doing something over there.
Let's go get him.
BUSTED
Let's get that punk.
He's doing something over there.
That sly punk.
You're doing exercises alone, you bastard.
THE MEERKAT GOT BUSTED
Hey, this punk's sweating!
He's sweating!
INCONCEALABLE EVIDENCE OF EXERCISE
-No. It's not like that.
-I can't believe you!
How much did you earn?
-Not much, seriously.
-How much?
-Show us. How much is it?
-Not much!
So how much?
-Hey, follow me.
-Okay, follow us.
-Come here.
-I had a stomachache, for real.
Hey, act friendly.
-I wanted to poop. I can't even poop here?
-All right, come here.
How much?
-How much?
-Tell us honestly.
After I went to the restroom,
I did exercises and earned 1,000 won.
THE AMOUNT IS OBVIOUSLY TOO SMALL
-Geez. Take off your shoes.
-Tell us where your money is.
-Take out the insoles.
-There's nothing there.
-Hey.
-I'm not lying!
Where's your money? Tell us now.
-Per 10 won, you get a punch.
-Tell us where your money is.
-I don't have any.
-A punch per 10 won.
-Tell us. Now.
-Seriously.
-He's hiding a lot here.
-Take off your underwear.
-Where did you hide it?
-No.
-Stay still.
-There's nothing there.
-Is it in here?
-Look, he's hiding a lot.
-Where is it?
-Where? Tell us now.
-I'm not hiding any.
Why put your hand in there?
Is it in there?
We're not taking it away.
Just be honest and put it all in here.
Where was it?
TAKING OUT 1,000 WON
Take it out now.
Don't make us put our hands in there.
Hey, why do you have so much?
+ 1,000 WON
You punk, how much do you have?
They're such bad people.
They ganged up on me in the alley
and tried to take my underwear off.
EMOTIONAL
This is
what I got after I played fair and square.
-Lift this a bit.
-Is there another pocket in there?
This punk has more!
IN THE END, HIS HAND GOES IN DEEP
Aren't you supposed to be the bank
that protects me?
Hey, there's money in here.
PROTECT YOUR MONEY YOURSELF
-Hey.
-Got more?
Do you have about 5,000 won?
I don't have any more.
-I think you have more.
-I don't, honestly.
Guys.
I'll tell you the total sum for now.
You have earned 11,640 won in total.
We can have a meal
if we put it all together.
Let's have a meeting
about lunch.
SO JONATHAN HAS A LOT OF MONEY?
So Jonathan, sit down.
Go ahead.
Let's say you have 7,000 won…
-Okay.
-…and I have 1,000 won.
-Then you have much more than us.
-Right.
So I'm suggesting you spend
your money for us to eat.
That we all eat together.
In return, to acknowledge your efforts,
we'll support you to make you
win the keychain at the end.
How will you do that?
In the end, the one with the most money
-wins the keychain today.
-Right.
So I'm saying we'll make sure
you win it today.
-I'm suggesting that we all eat equally.
-Right.
Like communism.
A DEAL THAT SOUNDS SO TEMPTING AND SWEET
BUT CAN HE REALLY TRUST THEM?
Then I need something that'll guarantee
I won't be betrayed.
Since I only have 1,000 won, I've already
lost the will to compete.
Each of you give me 500 won, then.
-As a deposit?
-Yes.
Put down a deposit.
-Why do I have to give it to you?
-What happens then?
-I have much more than you, right?
-Right.
If you don't keep your promise, I take it.
I was trying to make him spend his money
to eat without exercising.
No deposit, no deal.
There's no deal.
I'll humor them for now
and raise the deposit later.
What are they going to do
if I lay down the rules?
I mean, we can never trust each other now.
THE DEPOSIT IS ONLY 500 WON?
Hey, I'll pay the deposit.
-So when we eat, you have to pay for me.
-Okay.
-Give me 500 won. I'll give it to DinDin.
-Open it.
I realized how to make money.
"Seriously, I'm going to win
a second keychain," I thought.
Did it feel like easy money?
It did.
I'll collect the money and pay for them,
and I'll still have some left.
I thought Daniel should pay 2,000 won.
Four cup noodles.
Kimchi to share.
A big bottle of something to drink.
And dumplings to share
with your 2,000 won.
Okay, with my 2,000 won.
CURRENT AMOUNT: 11,640 WON
DANIEL, DINDIN, O3OHN, JONATHAN
Let's get busy.
Let's work and earn money.
I'm dying for a cup of sports drink.
I need sugar.
-Where's the convenience store?
-Go out, turn left, and go straight.
I really need some sugar.
HE ONLY HAS 2,300 WON
Let's see what they have.
Ice cream? Hold on.
But ice cream is expensive these days.
How much are they?
Let's see.
I don't think
I even have enough to buy a Goo Goo Cone.
I should go check how much it is.
Hello. Could you scan this
to see how much it is?
-That's 2,500 won.
-What…
It's 2,500 won.
-2,500 won?
-Yes.
TAKEN ABACK
Is there anything
that's "buy one, get one free"?
-Is it "buy two, get one free"?
-Yes.
HE DOESN'T EVEN HAVE ENOUGH
TO BUY THIS ONE GOO GOO CONE
Gosh, hold on.
I need to earn 5,000 won, then.
Just to have that ice cream.
I like Goo Goo Cone so much.
I like it better
than any other ice cream cone.
STARING AT HIS MONEY
Goo Goo Cone will definitely sell.
I thought I should buy and sell them
to the others.
It's 5,000 won for three.
If I sell it for 2,000 or 2,500 won,
it's a sweet deal.
Okay, let's do this.
WISHFUL THINKING, ON
So I did squats like crazy
in front of the store.
Six, seven.
Eight, nine.
PUZZLED
I named the operation "Goo Goo Coin."
I'll make money with this "coin"
and outdo Jonathan.
Three Goo Goo Cones.
HE FINALLY GETS THE SEED MONEY
It's so rewarding.
Even if I sell one for 2,000 won…
Since I bought them for 5,000 won…
EXCITED TO THINK THAT HE'LL EARN MONEY
Seriously…
-Yes.
-Three Goo Goo Cones.
I'll just eat one first.
EXCLAIMING
SWEET TASTE OF CAPITALISM
NOW LET'S MAKE A DEAL
Hey, he bought two ice cream cones.
-No, three!
-What?
O3ohn, how much is the ice cream?
Bro.
-What is this?
-How much is it?
-I'll sell it for 2,000 won.
-What?
I bought it for 2,200 won,
but I'll sell it for 2,000 won.
-That's too expensive.
-No.
-It's 2,200 won.
-No, hold on.
If we don't buy them, they'll melt anyway.
-Right. I won't buy it.
-No thanks.
WHAT?
-I won't buy it.
-Not eating.
-As you wish.
-I won't buy it.
It's 2,000 won.
I won't buy it.
Come on.
-Make it 500 won.
-What?
No, I bought them with my money.
So make it 500 won.
-Jonathan, it's 2,000 won.
-Yes?
Jonathan, if we don't buy them,
they'll melt anyway.
Okay.
Besides, I like World Cone better.
All right, let's let them melt.
And how much did you say
you bought them for?
2,200 won each?
-Yes.
-That's "buy two, get one free."
Do you take me for a fool?
Hold on, I'll go put them in the freezer.
Gosh, what a fool.
Darn it. I should've just bought
something cheap.
That was all for nothing.
No one's willing to buy it.
The strategy was wrong.
Gosh, this is so frustrating.
Darn it, I'm screwed.
A MENTAL STATE OF A PERSON
WITH A FAILED INVESTMENT
I'm so screwed.
STAGE 1: LETHARGIC
I have another plan.
I'll try again when they crave sugar.
STAGE 2: WISHFUL THINKING
Gosh, I should've
just bought something cheap.
Can I get a refund?
STAGE 3: REGRETTING
You egged me on.
STAGE 4: BLAMING OTHERS
Should I just steal it?
STAGE 5: CRIMINAL ACTIVITY
They'll want it when they crave sugar.
STAGE 6: MORE WISHFUL THINKING
I should do it when they're not doing it.
-Count it for me.
-Okay.
FORTUNATELY, BACK TO EXERCISING
I'll work hard
and save up.
I'll get back on my feet
and make a deal with something else.
It won't work like this.
HE HAS 100 WON, BUT HE'S DILIGENT
MEANWHILE, JONATHAN SEEMS TO BE RICH
-Fifteen?
-I have 15,000 won.
The taste of money!
If you have a lot of money?
You don't need a plan.
No plan.
Now, I need to earn 3,000 won
before lunchtime.
I'll buy lunch with the money.
-Oh, and put that money aside?
-Yes, I'll put it aside.
LUNCH WITH JUST 3,000 WON?
What we agreed on
are four cup noodles,
a big drink, and kimchi to share.
-And dumplings.
-Dumplings.
Okay, that's it.
-Yes.
-Okay.
HE'S RICH BUT BAD AT MATH
Okay.
Don't you want ice cream?
Will you sell it for 100 won?
Darn it. I won't sell it.
I'll just have it.
Wait a second.
-Aren't you going to have lunch?
-I am.
But you didn't pay much.
I paid 500 won.
Everyone else paid 2,000 won.
Hold on a minute.
Pay 1,000 won now.
I can't trust you.
Those who paid 2,000 won,
what do they get?
Cup noodles, kimchi,
-a big bottle of something to drink.
-Drink?
IS THAT SO?
-I get to eat the same with 1,500 won?
-Yes.
-Deal.
-Yeah.
It's a good deal for me, then.
Of course.
-Anyway, I got your back, man.
-Okay.
RIPPED OFF BUT STILL GOOD
SO EXCITED AFTER EXTORTING JUST 1,000 WON
Damn it. What a thug.
THE TWO ANCHOVIES START WORKING OUT
WHILE SOMEONE WATCHES THEM
FROM A DISTANCE
OBSERVE
LOOKING VERY SUSPICIOUS
Let's go.
DINDIN HEADS SOMEWHERE
HEADING TOWARD THE PLACE
THAT EVERYONE EXPECTS
What if someone steals my ice cream?
What a fool.
Someone's eating something in there.
SOMEONE'S RUNNING IN
-You came.
-Hey.
No, no. That's an e-cigarette. Gosh.
It's prejudice.
-You came.
-Hey.
Have an ice cream.
-Where's it? Okay.
-In the freezer.
Hey, you should share
something so delicious.
I'm keeping an eye out for him.
Damn it. I'm so worried.
Should I keep them in another bank?
Wow, this is so good.
I must come out of poverty first.
My Goo Goo Cones…
HAVING A BAD FEELING
I'll go check.
Hold on.
RUNNING BAREFOOT
AFTER HAVING A BAD FEELING
He's coming!
You're barefoot?
Yes. I was in a rush.
MISSED THE TWO THIEVES BY A WHISKER
Damn it!
Those crazy bastards.
Seriously.
GOO GOO COIN DELISTED
Damn it! Those crazy bastards.
Seriously.
Whose is this?
LET'S RUN WITH
THE THIEF'S BELONGINGS FOR NOW
Whatever. I'll just take it.
Crazy bastard.
How dare you eat my ice cream?
SO THRILLING
O3ohn's gone.
What?
ACTING INNOCENT TILL THE END
THE THIEVES CAUTIOUSLY COME OUT
Oh, shoot!
He ate it all, but he's busted.
That fool.
My God. I can't believe they ate them.
I was doomed.
I never thought those lunatics
would eat all of my ice cream.
I have to survive on my own.
I can't expect teamwork.
I'm so mad. There's no team today.
Give me back my deposit.
-What?
-Give me my deposit back.
Why?
-Someone ate my ice cream.
-Yeah?
There's no team today.
-Give me my 1,500 won back.
-Hold on.
I don't need kimchi or a drink.
-You don't need kimchi?
-No, give it back.
-Now.
-Give you your 1,500 won back?
I can't. I already received it.
Wait a minute, O3ohn.
Hold on. O3ohn, hold on.
DESPISING HUMAN BEINGS,
HE REFUSES TO HAVE A CONVERSATION
-Listen. Those two…
-Okay.
-Give it back!
-Give what back?
Give what back?
My money.
No, that's mine.
Give my money back!
-Your mouth smells sweet.
-What do you mean?
MURDEROUS LOOK
Give this back.
Anyway, I'll get my deposit back.
Okay. Give me my 1,000 won back.
I'll leave the alliance
and get 1,500 won back.
-Seriously?
-I'll do it on my own.
I told you, you already paid,
so you can't get it back now.
What kind of team retreat is this?
What's wrong?
-What's going on?
-You said you'd give it back.
-I'll give it to you.
-Yes, give it.
-He's such a fraud.
-Give it to me now.
Here.
I've given you 1,500 won.
-Okay.
-Let's go.
As we decided,
three cup noodles since he's left.
O3ohn's out?
-He wants to eat on his own.
-He's out.
-Really?
-Yes.
-I'll do it on my own.
-Let's go.
Let's go.
-Okay. Cup noodles, kimchi…
-Kimchi…
-…dumplings…
-…a drink.
-…a drink. Okay.
10 MINUTES AFTER THEY WENT
INTO THE CONVENIENCE STORE
Goodness, the prices are so…
Hold on a second.
Hold on.
Are you okay?
Why is everything so expensive?
In any case, you have to pay 15,800 won.
HOW JONATHAN WENT BANKRUPT
I didn't know it'd be like this.
It's my fault, because I thought
cup noodles would be 800 won each.
ACTUAL PRICE: 1,500 WON
And 2,000 won for soda.
ACTUAL PRICE: 3,800 WON
And 2,000 won dumplings.
ACTUAL PRICE: 4,900 WON
THE SUM GOES WAY BEYOND HIS EXPECTATIONS
It's 15,800 won.
But when I saw it was over 15,000 won,
I thought I've been living all wrong.
I realized I was still so clueless
about the ways of the world.
Now that I think about it,
it was an absurd deal.
-He suggested something so ridiculous.
-I know.
I mean, seriously,
what the heck?
-What was he talking about?
-I still don't understand.
I don't either, now that I think about it.
A DISASTER CAUSED BY A BAD DEAL
Something went very wrong.
-Oh, no.
-How much do you have left?
-Just 1,200 won?
-Yes.
YOUR MISFORTUNE IS MY HAPPINESS
Just start exercising now.
I have enough money
to have a meal, actually.
-I have more than him.
-Shut up, dude.
AGAIN, YOUR MISFORTUNE IS MY HAPPINESS
Listen, Jonathan.
Let me give you a piece of advice.
You listen to DinDin too much.
The way it looks,
you'll end up in last place.
It's so hard for me right now.
I'm so hurt.
He's so, so…
He's so mean.
He brought this upon himself.
He paid over 10,000 won alone.
Geez.
I'm better than him, then.
I lost 5,000 won.
He lost over 10,000 won.
So I'm better off.
Enjoy your lunch.
Enjoy.
Enjoy, everyone.
HAPPINESS FROM 2,000 WON
HAPPINESS FROM 1,500 WON
HAPPINESS FROM PAYING HIS OWN MEAL
DEPRESSION FROM PAYING 15,800 WON
Wow, it's so good.
It's so meaningful today.
I made so many good memories.
We talked a lot
and got to know each other better.
SILENT
Having such a feast with just 1,500 won.
Jonathan, smile a little, will you?
-It's delicious.
-I know.
Enjoy.
JONATHAN HAS LOST ALL LAUGHTER
-Eat up!
-Okay.
You punk.
All right. Tell me honestly.
How much do you have?
I have zero won.
I have 5,000 won, for real.
-I have zero, honestly.
-5,000 won.
I have 1,000 won.
How much do you have?
-I have 1,000 won.
-That's a lie.
I think he really only has 1,000 won.
Let's eat up,
-and let's not betray each other.
-Right.
Since this is a retreat, let's enjoy it.
Let's make a toast.
-All right, to Jonathan!
-To Jonathan!
Jonathan, I hope you win today.
REMINDING THEMSELVES AGAIN
OF THE MEANING OF THE RETREAT
Everyone,
while you're enjoying your lunch,
I'll just tell you the total sum.
-The total sum?
-Yes.
It's 12,300 won in total.
Someone has more than what they said.
SILENT
You guys have 12,300 won in total.
Seriously, every word you say…
God, I can't believe this.
I called a truce just now,
and you do this?
DinDin, tell us right now.
How much do you have?
-Seriously.
-I have 5,000 won.
-You have 5,000 won? I really have none.
-Yes.
There's no way.
What do you mean?
-What? I really have no money.
-He has none.
-How much do you have?
-I have 2,000 won.
Come on, stop lying.
THE RETREAT IS GOING SO WELL
Let's take a nap.
-I'll nap.
-After getting changed.
Okay, get some rest.
Anyway, how could you not know the prices?
Are you an idiot?
Let's just take a nap.
Let's nap.
PEACEFUL NAP TIME
FORGETTING REALITY,
HE'S HAVING TIME TO HEAL
LAUGHING
WEIRD NOISE COMING FROM SOMEWHERE
DANIEL IS EXERCISING ALONE
I'm so tired.
Okay.
Give me the money.
CRAZY ABOUT MONEY, HE GAVE UP ON THE NAP
HE GETS A SUDDEN SURGE OF DOPAMINE
You want the drama-show version?
The reality-show version.
The drama-show version.
He's good. That's so good.
DANIEL IS IN TOP FORM
But
how should I make them spend on dinner?
That's the problem.
-Spend what?
-Their money.
LOOKING FOR HIS NEXT DOPAMINE RUSH
Seriously.
Can I have one of the drinks?
Sangdon.
What happens if I have one of them?
All of your money will be confiscated.
LAUGHING
There's no drink left in here.
POURING WATER IN AN EMPTY CAN
Where's Jonathan?
JONATHAN'S STILL HEALING HIS WOUND
ON HIS WAY TO LET OUT HIS DOPAMINE
Jonathan.
I bought these two for 500 won.
-Really? Let me have a sip.
-Have one.
-Thanks.
-Sure.
Get some rest.
INTENTIONALLY TAKES A DRINK FIRST
GULP
Jonathan.
-Jonathan.
-Yes?
Is the drink good?
What? He must've conned him.
For God's sake…
HOW COULD YOU BE FOOLED AGAIN?
Jonathan.
I told you not to trust anyone.
HAVING A BLAST
You can just pay the price for it.
Taking all your money would be too harsh.
Shouldn't all his money be taken?
That's what you told me earlier, Producer.
But you virtually conned him, man.
-How much is it?
-1,400 won.
This is 1,400 won?
That drink is expensive.
I'm going to cry.
Stop saying such ridiculous things.
I won't pay. I can't.
Hold on, you won't pay?
I'm not going to pay it. Never.
Then, just 1,000 won.
Yes, pay 1,000 won.
-Take 1,000 won from him.
-Seriously, this is so…
HE GETS CONNED AND GETS 1,000 WON TAKEN
DESPISING HUMAN BEINGS TO THE MAX
I have 1,000 won left now.
I told you not to trust anyone.
Jonathan's so naive.
You grow as you get played.
In life, a bit of negativity
promotes growth.
He will grow.
Oh, go away!
O3OHN COMES OUT
All right.
-O3ohn.
-Where did you get that?
-Did you buy it?
-Yes.
-Where? How much is it?
-You're so thirsty.
It's 200 won.
-It's 200 won per can?
-I'll go buy it.
VICTIM 1 IS SILENT
THE PERPETRATOR IS EXCITED AGAIN
TO FOOL ANOTHER ONE
Give me the drink.
HIS DOPAMINE NEVER RUNS DRY
O3ohn.
-A new one? Did you go to the store?
-Yes.
-I bought it for 200 won from the staff.
-For real?
-Thank you.
-I got it for you.
You must have a lot of money.
WITHOUT ANY SUSPICION
Of course, I can do this much for you.
All right. O3ohn.
You drank it, right?
SMILING AWKWARDLY
THE HAPPY CON MAN
HOW COULD YOU BE FOOLED AGAIN?
Hey, it's 1,700 won.
For God's sake, what's wrong with you?
We'll take 1,000 won from you as well.
This is so annoying.
DinDin and Daniel are villains.
You see, after he ate my ice cream,
I started thinking of destroying him.
I'll steal his money or whatever it takes.
-Then, I'll handle Daniel.
-Yes.
Okay.
-You handle DinDin.
-Okay.
Let's shake hands.
-A pact?
-Okay.
-A pact without money, okay.
Just five more. One…
THE DESIRE FOR REVENGE GIVES HIM STRENGTH
My friend.
Why are you doing it here?
The sand's all over you.
To prepare against a con man,
I should work harder.
I mean, how else can I beat a con man?
All right, Daniel.
Well,
do you want to make bigger money?
How?
We're men, so something physical.
No, I don't like physical.
Get my question right.
I can't trust anything
that comes out of your head.
It's all trash.
All right. Or something from the staff.
-A question for both of us?
-Yes.
Okay, let's do it.
Then have DinDin join too.
Let's do it together.
Hey. How about we all bet our money
and the winner takes it all?
Okay.
-All right.
-Let's do it.
BETTING QUIZ GAME
1,000 WON PER ROUND
So, 1,000 won each?
-Put them in the center.
-Okay.
3000-WON PRIZE FOR GUESSING CORRECTLY
Why do you have so much?
-When did you save it?
-When?
I never saw you exercise.
When did you save this much?
Gosh, I can't believe you.
WHEN DID DINDIN SAVE UP SO MUCH MONEY?
30 MINUTES AGO
What's he doing? Is DinDin really asleep?
-Yes.
-I guess he was really tired.
WHERE'S DINDIN WHO WAS TAKING A NAP?
HE'S EXERCISING?
I believe there's a mission.
I'm sure of it.
I should have some money to compete.
EXERCISING TO MAKE MONEY FOR GAMES
I should wait for a chance
for me to join the competition.
I'll seize it and win.
I'll make a good investment and win.
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR THIS MOMENT
The first question.
The show you're on now,
Anchovy Physical Camp,
when will it be released?
-DinDin!
-Jonathan!
-DinDin was faster.
-At 8 a.m. on Friday.
Correct.
Damn it.
Where's your love for the show?
Do you guys want to keep going?
-We should.
-Of course!
Suddenly you have a chance to be rich.
-Only those who have the money join.
-I'll go all the way.
-I placed my ante.
-I'm in.
-Give me the money!
-This is a rare chance.
Who are the five main characters
in Romance of the Three Kingdoms?
-DinDin.
-Me!
Guan Yu, Zhang Fei,
Liu Bei, Cao Cao, Zhuge Liang.
Correct.
GO AGAIN
-Okay.
-Do you have money to bet?
I have 300 won left.
Then you want out, O3ohn?
What a fraud.
What the heck? You got some more.
The K League 1 standings of 2025.
-Say first, second, third places.
-DinDin!
DinDin!
Jeonbuk, Gimcheon,
and Daejeon.
Correct!
It seems like
your financial status has changed a lot.
I'm so screwed.
I lost everything.
A GAMBLER WHO LOST EVERYTHING
THE ONE WHO SUGGESTED THE GAME HAS LOST IT
Goodness, he has so much money.
I had such a good meal with 1,500 won
and earned good money now.
Goodness.
DIAL 1366 TO REPORT ILLEGAL GAMBLING
Hold on. I got three questions right,
-so I earned 9,000 won.
-Yes, 9,000 won.
It's amazing it went as planned.
To tell the truth, I didn't really
think about winning the keychain today.
But I got ambitious
and thought I should go for it.
Translated by Wayne Ryu