THIS PROGRAM IS ABOUT
PHYSICALLY WEAK CELEBRITIES
EXERCISING REPEATEDLY AND ENDLESSLY
IF YOU'RE WONDERING
WHY THEY'RE SO EXHAUSTED,
PLEASE TRY IT AT HOME
In movies,
right before they enter the afterlife…
You know how it all fades?
All right, last one.
-Darn it.
-You can do this.
Hey, get up! Get up!
They're not just anchovies.
They're patients.
Come on, how are we
supposed to do this with patients?
"EVERYONE HAS A PLAN UNTIL THEY GET
PUNCHED IN THE MOUTH." MIKE TYSON
ANCHOVY PHYSICAL CAMP
THE FIRST DAY OF ANCHOVY PHYSICAL CAMP
FIRST TRAINEE OF ANCHOVY PHYSICAL CAMP
FIRST ANCHOVY, CHOI DANIEL
What is this?
I don't think I'm an anchovy.
No one's ever called me
weak like an anchovy.
You see the thing is…
you may think
that it doesn't quite suit me,
but I'm on the intellectual side.
I'm an intellectual.
Wisdom. Yes, wise.
"Wise" would be better.
To take Romance of the Three Kingdoms
as an example,
I'm like Zhuge Liang.
-You know what I mean?
-Romance of the Three Kingdoms?
I'm wise like Zhuge Liang.
When I play a game,
I see right through
the nature of the game.
I grasp the key nature of the game
and what I need to do to win.
But that's not what this show is about.
I think you're mistaking this
for a mystery-solving show.
Maybe I am. Why did you cast me then?
Honestly, I don't really care
what others think of me.
I think of myself
as an intellectual person,
-a wise one.
-Okay.
Wisdom! Wise, wise!
I'm an intellectual!
I'm a very intellectual man.
SECOND TRAINEE OF ANCHOVY PHYSICAL CAMP
I feel so happy when I run.
Seriously, I love exercising.
I mean,
I can't ever be considered an anchovy.
I can never accept that I'm an anchovy.
Most people probably think
I'm weak like an anchovy,
but all of my friends will say
that I exercise hard.
I'm sure of it.
I'm serious. You know nothing about me.
My nickname is the Ichon-dong Hammer.
Comparing me to Jonathan, Daniel,
and O3ohn about exercise
is absolutely nonsensical.
See, this is why
Tyson said everyone has a plan
until they get punched in the mouth.
It goes like this and like that.
This is how you do it.
You just got knocked out.
SECOND ANCHOVY, DINDIN
THE THIRD TRAINEE OF ANCHOVY PHYSICAL CAMP
Hello.
Okay.
"Q. DO YOU KNOW THE TITLE OF THE SHOW?"
Well, there was one word in the title
that bothered me.
The word "anchovy" got on my nerves.
"ALL OF THE TRAINEES DENY IT"
Be careful, be careful, be careful.
How would you rename it if you could?
It'd be "Jonathan and the anchovies."
Something like that would make sense.
Seriously, I mean it.
THE STAFF / HAHAHA
THE THIRD ANCHOVY, JONATHAN
Why are they laughing?
What do you think today's mission will be?
I have no idea, but I was…
asked to take out insurance.
It occurred to me that the producer
may have some dangerous stuff planned out.
I was a bit scared, but that's no problem.
Whatever it is, I'll get it done.
AND…
THE LAST ANCHOVY ARRIVES
Someone arrived.
I smell an anchovy from the car.
He's looking in the mirror
before getting out.
-It's O3ohn.
-O3ohn, you have a mirror in your car?
-Hey, you look in the mirror?
-Why did you look in the mirror?
-I can see you couldn't sleep a wink.
-You look in the mirror?
You didn't get any sleep, did you?
I haven't had the chance
to say a word yet.
Hello.
We've wanted to cast you for a long time.
"THE LAST ANCHOVY, O3OHN"
Let's talk about
-when you turned down our first offer.
-Thank you.
To be honest, I hesitated because
it's called "Anchovy Physical Camp."
Because I'm not an anchovy.
Not anymore, anyway.
So have you been boxing
for two to three years?
-About two years and a half.
-I see.
We have high hopes for you.
WELCOME TO THE ANCHOVY PHYSICAL CAMP
I have no idea what we'll be doing.
What could it be?
DinDin, do you know
the purpose of this show?
Any assumptions?
Well, it'll probably be us completing
some mission as a team, don't you think?
Is today's mission related to basketball?
-I have no idea. We know nothing.
-They didn't tell you?
Have they told you anything?
-No, nothing.
-Me neither.
-Yo, yo, yo.
-I think we can count on Jonathan today.
-No, don't.
-Jonathan, you look like an athlete today.
Producer, looking at Jonathan now,
he's far from being an anchovy.
Exactly, that's what I mean.
Maybe his mentality's weak
like an anchovy.
-Oh, his mentality is?
-Yes, like an anchovy.
You must be in peak condition today.
-What could we be doing?
-I should save my energy for later.
Tell me about it.
What on earth could it be?
-Hey, look.
-What?
It looks like a massage bed.
That's a massage table.
Isn't it for manual therapy?
Isn't that for treatment or therapy?
-It's not for exercise.
-You're going to…
-That's…
-Here's what I think.
-There's a timer over there.
-Yes, the timer's the key.
That means this is a speed game.
There are three or four timers over there.
How about we pull the line a bit forward
to about here?
"THE ANCHOVIES ARE IN FEAR"
Yes, let's come a bit forward.
I'm feeling uneasy.
Anchovy Physical Camp trainees, welcome.
-Thank you.
-In any case, this is the beginning.
-Yes, whatever we're facing.
Welcome. Welcome, everyone.
You all represent anchovies.
Through this camp,
you'll be transformed from anchovies
into physically outstanding men.
Today's training is called…
Secluded Training.
-"Secluded…"
-What?
-Secluded Training.
-"Secluded"?
Beginning now,
for the next 12 hours,
you cannot leave this place
until you complete the mission.
What is this?
Why are you pressuring us with the door?
It feels like
everyone's going crazy in here.
You're still giving us food, right?
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Excuse me, there's no time!
To anchovy that presents
the best performance
will be awarded an anchovy keychain.
"WHOEVER COLLECTS 3 KEYCHAINS
WILL BE GIVEN A 2-MILLION-WON GIFT PRIZE"
And that bell over there is the GG Bell.
The moment you ring the bell,
the game ends.
-What?
-No, we don't need it.
We'll never ring it.
"A FEW HOURS LATER"
-No, no, no!
-No, don't do it!
-Don't do it.
-We just might succeed.
HOW WILL IT END FOR THEM?
Here's your mission for the day.
Within 12 hours…
This is important.
This is the most important part.
Push-ups are a man's basic exercise.
-Your mission is to do 2,000 push-ups.
-What?
-That's…
-What's that?
How can we possibly do 2,000 push-ups?
-The muscles will explode.
-Exactly.
-I doubt we can do 1,000.
-Is this a joke?
-We knew you'd all say that.
-All right.
Once you finish 200,
the reduction game will unlock.
Two hundred?
And you can use it
to reduce your push-up count.
-But…
-Okay.
If it's 200 push-ups,
we could just each do 50 right now.
-We could finish before it gets dark.
-In an hour and a half.
We invited an expert today
to make it accurate.
-What?
-Who?
Who?
Gosh.
-Hello.
He looks like a fitness trainer.
Hello.
-Hello.
-Nice to meet you.
I'm Park Solbin,
a physical therapist and fitness trainer.
Nice to meet you.
-That's why you brought this.
-Yes.
If the situation requires it,
I'll help you on that.
But it'd be like forced labor then,
wouldn't it?
If I complain about my arms in pain,
I'd get massaged and have to do it again.
-That's forced labor.
-Exactly.
I mean, in this day and age…
These are scary people.
I'll show you how to do a proper push-up.
Spread your hands shoulder-width apart,
and go down until your elbows reach
a 90-degree angle.
Then get back up.
Man, that's the standard way.
The 12 hours begins now.
-Okay!
-Let's go.
-All right, let's do this. We got this.
-Jonathan, let's go.
-Yeah.
-You can do this easily.
-That's right. Easy.
-Do it easy and slow. Don't rush.
-Right, easy and slow.
That's good.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
It's easy for him.
-Of course it's easy for him.
-Five.
-Six.
-Easy… Wait, he's shaking a bit.
Seven.
-He's shaking a bit.
-Eight.
You're doing well.
-Ten.
-Almost there.
Almost there.
You're almost there, Jonathan.
He's already lost his smile.
"HE HAS SUDDENLY GONE QUIET"
It's a piece of cake for him.
I told you, Jonathan lacks stamina.
-You're right.
-He only gets bursts of power.
Okay, you're done.
-Look at him sweating.
-Good job, good job.
-Why are you sweating so much?
-You're sweating buckets.
"SWEATING BUCKETS AFTER ONLY 25 PUSH-UPS"
-Are you okay?
-Good. You're all warmed up now.
-He's warmed up now.
Yes, I'm fine. I'm good.
All right. Let me go right away.
I think he'd probably be
-the best at this among us.
-Yes, since he boxes.
All right.
I'll start. Is this the right form?
-Start as you are.
-Okay.
One.
-Two. Three.
-He looks stable.
He does it so effortlessly.
-Man, you're a natural at this!
-You're looking stable and steady.
He's light as a feather!
Let's get it!
You're looking like Bruce Lee!
"HE UNLEASHES HIS POWER
DESPITE HIS WEAK LOOKS"
-Let's go!
-I guess you really do box.
Twenty-five. Okay.
"FINISHES 25 PUSH-UPS IN NO TIME"
-How was it? Was it easy?
-Yes, it was no sweat.
-Good job. Great job.
-We can definitely clear this.
I've got a feeling that we can do 2,000.
No doubt.
-You really are a pro.
-Let's get it done and go home.
I'll start now.
One. Two.
-Three. Four.
-You're good, you're good!
-Five. Six.
-He's very fast.
-He's fast. Good!
-Seven.
-He's very fast.
-He's fast.
Eight. Nine. Ten. Just three more.
Wait. I'm screwed.
I knew I was screwed while doing it.
-We're never gonna be able to clear this.
-No, never.
We're never making it to 2,000.
-Seriously?
-I think I could do 100.
But while going down,
I felt I couldn't do it.
-You felt it?
-These muscles told me.
-Did they scream at you?
-But we just started.
Daniel, let's give it a shot.
-Okay.
-We can do this.
-It's nothing. You got this.
-All right, let's go.
-Show us what you got!
-Let's go, let's go.
-Let's go.
-You're good.
-What?
-Three.
-You're doing good.
-Looking stable!
Wow, he's good.
-I know, right?
-Two.
-Three.
-See? We're not anchovies.
-Six. Seven.
-You can do more.
What's that sound?
Is it because you're so happy?
-That's good.
-Wait.
-Just five more.
-Five more?
"5 MORE, AND THEY'LL HAVE DONE
100 IN TOTAL!"
-Two. Three.
-Five.
"100 PUSH-UPS DONE IN 9 MINUTES"
Daniel.
You understand what I mean now, right?
-At 20, these guys told me.
-We can't do it.
-These guys up here, right?
-Yeah.
They go, "Wait a second."
How about we do another round of 25 each?
-We can all do it, right?
-Yes, of course.
-Let's do another round.
-They're talking,
but it's ignorable.
I'll tell them,
"Shut up! I'm not done yet!"
"Hey! I'm not done."
"SOOTHING AND COMFORTING HIS PECS"
-"Shut up! Read the room, man."
-We can do another round.
Let's get it!
One.
-Two. Three. Four.
-Let's speed it up.
-You're doing much better.
-This is good.
-Four. Five.
-Five.
No, not yet.
Don't talk to them just yet.
-Shut up! Just shut up!
-Come on.
-One. Two. Three.
-Okay.
-Four. Five.
-It's coming out.
One more? All right.
"JONATHAN AND DINDIN EACH FINISH 25"
It's still doable.
-Right. It's doable.
-It's not too bad yet.
One. Two.
-Three. Four.
-Wow, he's so good.
-Five. Six.
-He's so cool.
-He's very stable.
-Eight.
-He's a pro at this.
-He looks like a superstar.
He might as well be Cha Eunwoo right now.
"O3OHN IN REALITY,
BUT CHA EUNWOO IN THIS REALM?"
-Let's get it!
-All right.
You got this.
"JUST 25 TO GO UNTIL THE DEDUCTION GAME"
-Three.
-You can do this.
-Four. Five.
-We all did it.
-Let's go, let's go.
-Wait. Hold on.
-Just ten to go.
-Ten?
-Ten. Let's go.
-Let's go for ten.
-One.
-Just nine left now.
Two. Three.
-Now six.
-Four.
-Five.
-Five. Just five more.
-Hold on.
Just finish it
so we can find out the mission.
-All right!
We did 200.
"200 PUSH-UPS COMPLETED"
Good. Good job.
All right,
you have completed 200 push-ups.
Here's the first deduction game.
If you succeed,
200 push-ups will be deducted.
This game to test your grip strength…
is cracking an egg with one hand.
An egg?
Jonathan can do this
since his hands are big.
Cracking an egg's easy, isn't it?
It is, right?
Is it hard to crack a raw egg? Why?
Each person will be given 30 seconds.
Even if one person succeeds,
we'll count it as a success.
Wait, is it really that hard?
I think it'll be easy.
Is that really hard?
"YOU'LL SEE"
I don't understand.
You can't press on the egg
with your fingers,
since it'll crack easily.
You must crack it
-only with your palm like this.
-Okay.
"THE FIRST REDUCTION GAME:
CRACKING AN EGG WITH ONE HAND"
Grab it properly and get ready.
Is it that hard?
-All right.
-Ready.
Set, go!
-What?
-Are you serious?
-Seriously?
-Come on.
-Come on, man.
-Stop fooling around.
Come on, man.
Hey, why can't you do it?
-DinDin.
-Hey.
Come on, stop trying to be funny.
-DinDin.
-What's wrong with him?
Do it right and crack it!
DinDin, come on. Crack the egg.
-Hey, be serious.
-Is he pretending?
-Come on.
-His face is red.
-DinDin.
-It must be really hard.
Come on, the mission comes first.
But why?
Hey, people will
-call you out for this.
-The time's up.
"DINDIN FAILS"
Hey, seriously. We need to do this.
-Who's next?
-Let's go in order of height.
-I'll go.
Hey, be serious.
He was doing that for show.
You take it serious
and give it a real try.
-Ready, set…
-It's really intact.
Go!
Hey.
Hey!
-What's wrong with you?
-Seriously.
-What are you doing?
-I'm not kidding.
Come on, this…
-It's time to be serious.
-Don't try to be funny.
People will call you out.
Seriously.
-Why won't it crack?
-Are you serious?
It really won't crack!
-The time's up.
"O3OHN FAILS"
It's totally intact.
What is it like? Is it as hard as a rock?
-I'll tell you what it's like.
-Okay.
-It's like facing a freaking big wall.
-Right.
It just won't budge.
-Really?
-Yeah.
I mean, it's just an egg.
How is it like a wall?
All right. I'll try then.
-You try last, Jonathan.
-Yeah, since your hands are the biggest.
-What do you mean, it's impossible?
-Are you ready?
Set, go!
Hold on.
"WITH A GRUNT, HE SHARES THEIR EXPERIENCE"
I heard a bone cracking.
-I almost broke my hand.
-I heard it.
Come on, what are you doing?
-What are you doing?
-Are you serious?
I mean…
Why can't I do it?
I really can't do it. Look.
It's not time to be funny.
This is hilarious.
Hold on.
Look, his ears are so red.
"CHOI DANIEL FAILS"
-I told you.
-No way.
I get what you meant.
-Right?
-It's like a wall is in front of me.
-It's like, "Wait. What?"
-Seriously.
That's how it feels.
It's impossible.
But Jonathan is different.
-If Jonathan cracks it,
-Yes?
200 push-ups will be deducted immediately.
"THEIR DESTINY DEPENDS ON JONATHAN'S PALM"
Let's begin. Ready, set…
Go!
Jonathan.
What?
It really won't crack.
Come on, your hands are bigger than ours.
Just try to crush it.
My hand hurts.
IT CRACKED!
THEY SUCCEED IN CRACKING AN EGG
THE EGG CRACKER
-Let's go, Jonathan!
-Good job!
-Yeah!
-Jonathan!
That was incredible.
-That was amazing.
-You're awesome.
Your middle name should be "Strongman."
You're a freaking strongman.
That was amazing.
We'll deduct 200 push-ups.
"200 PUSH-UPS DEDUCTED"
-You did amazing.
-You freaking strongman.
-He killed it.
-His body looks different.
It really does. You suddenly look so cool.
WHILE THEY CONGRATULATE JONATHAN…
SERIOUS
-So he did this and then this?
-Yes, it looked odd.
The way I see it…
I don't see his thumb in the video.
Listen, everyone.
One of our cameramen just noticed
that Jonathan's grip looked strange
when he cracked the egg.
-No way.
-What about the grip?
Yes, what about it?
-It looks like
-What about it?
-Jonathan's thumb went inside.
-No way!
No way!
-No, no. Hey!
-But that's how…
-Hey! Hold on.
-I checked.
I checked it myself.
-Can I see? What do you mean?
-Yes, you can.
-Be my guest.
-Let's see.
Show them.
You see, what's important is…
We'll check the video,
but at international events,
once decisions are made,
-it's over.
-Since the decision's made.
That's right.
-The referee should've pointed it out.
-He's right.
But you already made the call.
-The result is already out.
-Right.
-Right, so this is…
-Are you going to call it a foul now?
-No, right?
-The staff should take note of that
-from now on, and…
-Exactly.
CHECKING THE VAR
REPLAY
HE PROPERLY GRIPS THE EGG AT FIRST
Jonathan, just use your finger.
It's impossible otherwise.
HMM…
SLIDING HIS THUMB INSIDE
THE TRUTH UNFOLDS
Okay, I'll be honest.
I also saw him slide his thumb inside.
-So I told Daniel
-What are you talking about?
-and O3ohn about it earlier.
-I never did such a thing.
-What's wrong with you?
-I never did that.
I told them about it.
"5 MINUTES AGO"
How did he crack it?
He put his thumb inside.
-Don't tell them.
-Should we lay low?
Yes, lay low.
-Don't tell them.
-Yeah.
"THEY WERE ALL ACCOMPLICES"
I didn't press the egg with it.
-If I'd done that, then…
-What matters is
that they already made the call.
-You did?
-Yes, the referee did.
-The call was made.
-All right. I'll repent then.
-Yes, you do that.
-That's right.
-What you did was wrong.
-He'll repent.
-Producer, he'll repent.
-It's all good then.
-Apologize to him properly.
-Apologize to him.
I apologize.
-He didn't know.
-I'm greatly sorry.
-But there are a lot of cameras here.
-Yes, apologize.
-You should do better.
-Jonathan.
-Please apologize to everyone properly.
-I really…
-Tell everyone that you're sorry.
-I'm sorry, everyone.
-We're sorry.
-I regret it.
Since countries have
their own cultures and ways…
Why don't we speed it up?
-Let's do another round then.
-Okay, let's do that.
-Should we do 25 each?
-Okay, sounds good.
-And then we'll do the mission.
-Sounds good.
We'll be done in no time.
One. Two.
Three. Four.
Goddammit.
"HE CURSES AFTER ONLY 4 PUSH-UPS"
It's tougher on the body after a break.
One.
-Two.
-Damn, hold on a second.
Three.
-You're doing good.
-I'll do three at a time.
What are you doing?
I'm not kidding. It's so tough.
Guys, you can't be like this!
O3ohn sure is a pro.
YOUNG BLOOD TO THE RESCUE
-He's our ace.
-Three. Four.
-Five.
-All of his abilities
-are in his physicality.
-Let's go, O3ohn.
-All his stats went to his physicals.
-Nine.
"DESPITE THE ODD COMPLIMENT,
HE REMAINS CALM"
That's it, that's it. Three more.
JONATHAN THE TIRELESS STRONGMAN
THANKS TO THE YOUNG ANCHOVIES,
THEY FINISH 200
-All right.
We did 400 in an hour.
We just need to do this five more times.
Just like last time,
you'll get 200 push-ups deducted
if you win.
-Right.
-In this game,
we'll test how strong your punches are.
-That's…
-Come on.
-This is for me. I'll go first.
-I'm the Ichon-dong Hammer.
-You go last.
-Oh, okay.
This is it. This is my chance.
The game is called
"Punch Out the Candles."
What?
"PUNCH OUT WHAT?"
"Punch Out the Candles."
I've tried it and it's impossible.
In this game,
you must blow out ten candles
using only your punches.
-What?
-It's impossible.
-Like this?
-You'll try it one by one in a relay.
If there's even one flame left
or if your fist touches any flames,
"THE SECOND REDUCTION GAME:
PUNCH OUT THE CANDLES (PRACTICE GAME)"
I can't do it.
It's impossible.
-Maybe he can.
-Why are you shadowboxing with flames?
-Watch me.
-Now he punches.
-I didn't actually punch.
-What was that?
Give it a go then.
What are you doing?
"BLOWS OUT OF HIS NOSE"
-What are you doing?
-Watch your nose.
-I can't do that?
-Of course not.
But blowing through my nose
is a habit of mine.
-I'll give it a try.
-Try it, Jonathan.
Did you get your wisdom tooth removed?
-What?
-What's this pose?
Did you get your wisdom tooth pulled out?
-What's with the pose?
-I have my ways.
Everyone has their own ways.
-Hey, we'll check the VAR.
-No, no.
-Let's have a cameraman on him
-Come on.
-To film only his face.
-I wasn't doing anything wrong.
All right, I'll do it seriously.
"SHOCKED"
Okay.
-You're good. What?
-How did you do that?
"WATCHING VERY CLOSELY"
Hey, save it for later.
You know how to do it.
-How do you do it?
-Do it later.
-How?
-Teach us.
-Do it as if you're really punching it.
Really?
As if you don't care if you get burned.
Punch it.
-You're so good.
-Great.
-Nice! Nice!
-Why are you so good?
"THE STAFF WHISPERING"
I think you're touching the flames.
What?
-Gosh, what is this again?
-Hold on.
What do you mean, he touched the flames?
-No way.
-I didn't even feel the flame.
If he did, he would've gotten burned.
-Didn't your hair get burned?
-It did not.
"HAIR BURN?"
-Hey! This is racism!
-That's racism!
Where do you mean I got burned?
-Where? Tell me.
-Hey, Jonathan.
Do you want me to tell you
which parts are burned?
-Then is this unburnt?
-Explain that!
"FORGIVE ME…"
-What are you talking about?
-That was harsh.
Hey, hold on.
This punk. He got wax here.
Hey, you said you didn't touch the flames.
-What's this?
-Someone must've put it here.
I saw something so white.
"THE SECOND DEDUCTION GAME:
PUNCH OUT THE CANDLES"
Let's go!
-Let's go!
-Just do it relaxed.
I'll give it a go.
You failed earlier.
-Okay!
-Two!
Three!
Calm down.
Just do what you can.
I don't think I can do it.
Yes, you can.
Please!
-You can do it.
-Please.
You little shit.
-Closer.
-You should get closer.
Nice!
-Okay.
-Good.
-Doing well.
-Take your time.
Now you have a bit more than half left.
-You little shit.
-Hit the middle.
-Okay!
-That's it!
Hey!
"YOU LITTLE SHIT"
You finish them all.
You little shit.
"CONFIDENCE MAX"
-It's okay.
-This isn't good. There are four left.
-You can do it, O3ohn, right?
-Yeah.
-You have to.
-I'll blow out at least one.
-Just two.
-You have to punch harder than usual.
-All right.
Here I go.
Hold on.
"TEAM KILL!"
That doesn't count.
"THAT DOESN'T COUNT! VS. IT DOES COUNT!"
-It was a timeout.
-You shouldn't have done that!
No, I stopped it.
Why would you stop him like that?
He was fooling around. He wasn't doing it.
I was about to punch, but because of him…
-Since I stopped him, can you…
-No, no.
He already punched.
"HOWEVER…!"
It's okay, we have Jonathan.
-Let's go.
-Let's go, Jonathan.
One.
"THEIR LAST HOPE, STRONGMAN JONATHAN"
-Let's go.
-Four left!
-Jonathan, let's go!
-It's okay if you fail.
Just be relaxed.
You can do this. Just crush them!
It all depends on me.
Here I go.
"HE BLOWS OUT 2"
-Yes, Jonathan!
-Hey, take your time.
-Nice. Let's go, you got this.
-Take your time.
You can do this.
It's easy for him.
-You got this.
-Jonathan, don't be nervous.
Blow them off at once.
"ONLY TWO MORE TO GO
UNTIL THE 200 PUSH-UP DEDUCTION"
Relax, relax.
Just as you've done.
"PLEASE!"
Is there any additional chance we can get?
"NOPE"
I couldn't control my power.
-I just had too much adrenaline in me.
-You failed to get the 200 deduction.
-But you see,
-Please, one more chance.
-this is a fun game.
-Cameras out.
Just one more chance!
We were almost there.
We were so close.
We need to do 200 more
to get another chance.
Darn it, we were almost there.
Well, I think DinDin is
monkeying around too much.
He really is.
I think he and the production staff
might be on the same side.
He just might be a mole.
DinDin is a mole.
I strongly suspect that he's their spy.
You look more like a spy than I do.
Right now, you look like
a North Korean soldier.
-How many have we done?
-How many in total?
You've done 400 push-ups.
THE ANCHOVIES ARE DISPIRITED
AFTER FAILING THE DEDUCTION GAME
It's tough, isn't it?
-Yes, it's gotten…
-It's too tough now.
I'm getting exhausted.
This is bad.
It's tougher than I thought.
Should we try another round now
Yes, let's do another round now.
Are you sure?
Oh, I think it's not that bad.
HIS FACE SAYS OTHERWISE
Now it's too much for him.
When he goes down,
it's already too much for him.
He's like a corpse now.
-Then it's just the three of us now.
-He was already gone.
So he came back from the dead.
AN ANCHOVY FROM THE AFTERLIFE
What do you mean, I was already gone?
-Okay, let's get it!
-Let's go.
Let's go. I'll go first.
-Okay.
-I'll go first. Let's go.
One.
Two. Three.
Goddammit.
Why did I agree to join this show?
Four.
REGRETTING MORE AND MORE
Here I go!
He sure is young.
THE YOUNG BLOOD PUSHES AHEAD
-Six.
-Four more. Show us what you got.
Seven.
He's shaking a lot.
-Last one!
-Let's go.
One last one.
-Okay! Nice!
-Okay, okay.
One. Two.
Four. Five.
Hold on.
He's exhausted too.
Two more.
Last one! Okay!
If Daniel does five,
we can have our mission.
"ONLY 5 MORE TO GO
UNTIL THE DEDUCTION GAME"
-Okay, okay.
-Are you sure?
-Can you do it for me?
-Yes.
"WHAT?"
I'm a knight in shining armor.
Let's get it!
-Let's go.
-Let's get it!
One. Two.
-Three. Four!
-Last one.
200 PUSH-UPS COMPLETED
THANKS TO THE KNIGHT
800 PUSH-UPS DONE IN JUST TWO HOURS
Okay!
We'll begin the next deduction game.
This time, 100 deductions are on the line.
-Just 100? Come on, why?
-Why? It was 200 before.
See? They're scared now.
-They're scared.
-Come on, let's go for 200.
But it's only been
a bit more than two hours.
Listen, guys.
I don't think we need to do it quickly.
-Right. We can…
-Let's take our time.
We can take it easy.
If you win,
you'll get 100 push-ups deducted.
This game will test
your physical strength.
-Egg again?
-It's called "One-on-four Arm Wrestling."
In this game, you'll go against
one of our staff one by one.
If any of you beats him, you win.
There must be someone strong
among the staff.
I'm sure of it.
You'll only be given one chance.
Are you guys all ready?
-Yes. We'll do it.
-Yes.
All right.
We'll present to you our player then.
Everyone else, step back.
THE STAFF'S PLAYER APPEARS
There's no one here.
What?
"THE STAFF'S PLAYER STANDS SHYLY"
"SOMEWHAT UNPLEASANT"
-This is bad.
-He has long arms.
Can I touch your arm?
May I?
Can I ask about your arm wrestling record?
Do you know your stats?
My arms aren't that strong.
-He's a strong man.
-His bones are…
-He would've been loved by noble ladies.
-He's got strong bones.
Noble ladies would've loved him.
It must be in his genes.
But…
He might not be an actual staff member.
"AN ABSURD WAY OF THINKING"
I really am a cameraman.
But the way he's holding the camera…
-Is that a fake camera?
-Maybe he was trained today.
They probably told him,
"Just hold the camera like this."
"THE THIRD REDUCTION GAME:
1-ON-4 ARM WRESTLING"
First, body weight is crucial here.
-Since you two are heavier, we two will…
-Right, us two.
We'll tire him out.
-Right.
-And then you two…
You go first, and then O3ohn.
And then Jonathan and me.
"THE CAMERAMAN GETS READY TOO"
Let's go.
"THE PLAYER ENTERS"
I think he got a tan in a rush
to look like a cameraman.
It's so red.
-It's like he got a partial tan.
-He's so red.
PLAYER 1: DINDIN
JUST HOLDING HANDS MAKES HIM FUSS
What was that?
Look, I think he's a professional.
-He's a professional.
-It hurts so much.
-I'm just holding on lightly.
-Sir.
"HOLDING TIGHT"
Come on. Hold on a second.
I can't hold his hand properly.
Ready, set, go!
Hold out!
You have to tire him out.
Out.
"DARN IT"
No, listen.
-He's laughing.
-No, listen. Daniel, just listen to me.
I can't hold his hand right.
-It's so thick.
-Yeah?
Now, next player, please.
-O3ohn.
-I'll do my best.
-Ready.
-Wait. Please go easy on me.
Wait. Please go easy on me.
Set, go!
-This is bad.
-All right.
"DYING MAKING A FUSS"
-You try it.
-He's that strong?
I'm not good at arm wrestling.
"PLAYER 3: CHOI DANIEL"
It hurts so much.
-Now.
-It's looking good.
-Ready.
-Good.
It's looking good.
-Ready.
-Good.
Set, go!
It's working!
Okay. Good! Oh, no. No!
"FIRST MATCH WORTH WATCHING"
-No! Let's go!
-Daniel!
-Let's go!
-Hold on!
-Just hold out.
-Hold out.
UNEXPECTEDLY NECK AND NECK
-Just tire him out.
-Ten more seconds.
BUT THE BALANCE STARTS COLLAPSING
BOUNCING BACK
-Great, Daniel!
-Good, he's shaking.
-Good.
-You're doing well!
-He's shaking.
-Good!
Push it. Good job.
Okay. Daniel, get out of there.
Go right away.
"DRAGGED OUT"
No, wait.
Let's go right away.
Let's go right now. Get back down!
Let's go right now.
"FORCEFULLY CONTINUING THE GAME"
Right away!
-Right away!
-We should do it right away.
"THE FINAL ROUND"
-Ready. Set, go!
-Hold out!
-Watch your wrist!
Curl your wrist.
-Gosh.
-Hold on.
WILL IT BE THE CAMERAMAN WHO'S TIRED OUT
OR JONATHAN WHO DID 150 PUSH-UPS?
THE BIG GUYS' BIG MATCH
What in the world? Why's he so strong?
-Why's he so strong?
-My God!
Jonathan, let's go!
You can do this, Jonathan.
Just hold out a little longer.
Jonathan, finish it! Now, now!
Come on, you got this!
What? He's using tricks.
100-DEDUCTION GAME FAILED
Translated by Wayne Ryu