After Mr. Oh left,
our team regained stability
as he had wished.
-Hello.
-You're here early.
Good morning.
What did the legal team say
about the Malaysian project complaint?
It's under review. They think it won't be
hard to deal with since our fault is low.
I scheduled a meeting tomorrow
at 3:00 p.m.
Okay, good job.
I wonder why Japan hasn't replied yet.
-Hey, Mr. Hwang.
-Yes?
-Complete this by noon.
-Yes, sir.
Many people,
were trying to keep me at ease.
However, the more they did so,
the more reasons there were
for me to leave.
However, I stayed for just one reason.
Geu-rae.
What did I tell you?
Stick it out.
And?
Make sure
you win.
Win.
Don't forget.
It's because of his advice.
Even if you think you won't make it,
you must fight until the end.
In the game of life,
one begins many things,
even though the end is certain.
That's...
That's why.
The day that I must leave this company
is steadily approaching.
Would you like a cup of coffee?
-Sure.
-Me too.
Okay, I'll go get some.
April is the cruelest month.
It breeds lilacs out of the dead land,
it mixes memory and desire
and it stirs dull roots with spring rain.
You feel me? Don't you feel it?
It sharpens your senses.
Does it or doesn't it, Geu-rae?
Don't you feel it in your bones?
If you feel itchy, go to the public bath.
It's disgusting.
What? The love?
Which teams are going
to the work transition meeting?
Weren't they us, Sales Team One, Resource
Team, Steel Team, and Textile Team?
We don't have to go, do we?
No, we don't.
Work transition meetings give me
a sense of déjà vu.
A sense of déjà vu?
You mean, Mr. Ma and Mr. Oh's conflict?
I'm leaving first. I have to finish
organizing our team's receipts.
-Okay, go ahead.
-Okay.
His contract is ending soon
and there's nothing much we can do.
Mr. Kim and Mr. Cheon say they are trying
to find a way to help.
But there's a limit to it.
And honestly, there's nothing much
they can really do about it.
But Ms. Sun is doing her best
to find a way to keep Geu-rae.
I'm willing to do anything
if it would help him to stay.
Did you get the lowest bidding forwarder
for the Myanmar project?
No, we didn't.
Since the Myanmar project is unique,
I proceeded with our previous forwarder.
Do you guys just proceed with the work
without even getting an approval?
Mr. Park. This is how...
This is how we worked under Mr. Oh.
This is how you worked?
And how did you work?
I see.
So, since you have your own way, you want
me to shut up and just go with it?
No, sir. What I mean is...
Let's just do it the way I want to, okay?
Do I have to explain myself and convince
you guys every time we do something?
-Can you get me a coffee?
-Okay.
I've been observing you guys
these past few days.
And I'm not sure whether you're working
or just arguing about everything,
or just acting like you're working.
You know? You guys are a mess.
Don't explain things to me.
Can you just submit a report?
Keep your calls to me short and sweet.
We already exchanged documents.
So why do keep repeating everything
over and over again, huh?
-I'm sorry.
Don't your mouths ache
after chattering all day?
-Hand me the coffee.
-Yes, sir.
I'm going to do my best to get a competent
and well-qualified new employee next time.
In fact, I'm going to get a newbie
with the best qualifications.
So until then, let's try to
hold down fort.
Go back to work.
I told you to put more water in.
I told you to put more water to the point
that you feel there's too much water.
I'm sorry. I'll bring you another cup.
Forget about it.
Hey.
Why didn't you take care
of the Chungsol payment?
They shipped their products out ages ago.
Do you want to get sued?
They haven't submitted their physical
and chemical report yet.
The product warranty is missing too.
If they said they would submit it,
believe them.
If I send their payment
and they receive it,
will they still take care of those
missing documents? What if they don't?
Then I would have to take responsibility.
Responsibility?
You sure like the word responsibility.
Your parents sure made
a fucked-up guy out of you.
You trust nobody. You're self-centered.
And you're just a chaotic mess.
Whenever it regards Chungsol,
why do you always go crazy?
My parents fucked me up?
-I always go crazy?
-Clear the payment.
Got it? Do it immediately.
I'm not going to fucking look at this.
NOTICE FOR COOPERATION
WITH INTERN SELECTION
Why don't they just take care of their
current employees first?
Steel Team will assist Resource Team's
urban energy business with Japan
by proceeding
with an additional new project
for the disposal of electronic products,
such as discarded refrigerators,
among other products.
I hope the transfer of all necessary
and related files is completed soon.
Mr. You and Ms. An will assist
as much as possible.
The Textile Team has agreed to take over
the asbestos fiber project.
If the Resource Team provides us with all
the files on the asbestos fiber project,
we'll try to develop and advance it
into a Malaysia export project
through triangular trading.
Jeez. What the heck?
Why does the Resource Team always have
to transfer their work to other teams?
When our business becomes profitable,
a task force sprouts up or we're told
to transfer our work to other teams.
-Hey, Mr. Jung.
-Yes.
What the heck were you doing?
What? I'm sorry.
Sales Team One
and Three are working on a high-speed
internet cable installation project.
But we received mineral resources
as payment from Ghana.
So we're asking the Resource Team
to take care of it.
So why do you receive payment
in the form of mineral resources?
Barter deals are a thing of the past.
Is that not so, Mr. Jung?
Well...
Yes.
But an inspection team formed
by several French companies is in Korea
to discuss the potential
of financing the development project
for Ghana's mineral resources.
And also it seems
a lot of international companies
are trying to win the energy development
projects in Ghana.
They appear to be...
They appear to be what?
What about it?
What?
We feel it's a good opportunity to link
our business with that activity, sir.
Yes, that's it.
Our team will try to find buyers
of manganese ore and bauxite ore.
Why should the Sales Team do that?
Our team is more than capable of doing it.
Is that not so, Mr. Jung?
What?
Then suit yourselves.
Please find us potential buyers
by tomorrow.
Ms. Sun...
That's fine.
I'm going to the next meeting.
Let's end it here.
The rest of you can wrap up
what we've just discussed.
April 21st: Second year since employment
Why couldn't I speak properly
and even stuttered in front of Mr. Ma?
-Is your meeting over?
-Yeah.
Goodness. My fate is sealed.
Ever since Mr. Jung spoke up
against Mr. Ma,
he seems to have a vendetta against us.
Heck, our office may be even moved
next to the toilet.
Zip it. Words can become reality.
The good days will come around,
sooner or later.
When is that day?
The day Mr. Ma retires from work?
Hey, Hyung-ki.
Aren't you supposed to be
in London by now?
I wish Mr. Ma was a temporary employee.
Hey, Young-yi.
Geu-rae's contract termination date
is quite near, isn't it?
Well, yes.
Jeez. When Geu-rae leaves,
someone else will have a hard time.
-And that's, Mr. Kim.
-You bet.
Whether it's an intern or a new employee,
he'll have to teach him the ropes.
And that's only after Geu-rae's
replacement is actually recruited.
Yeah.
When in the world has Sales Team Three
ever had new employees?
But Geu-rae probably won't get
a contract extension, right?
A contract extension means making him
a permanent employee, so why give it?
Ms. Sun and Sales Team Three seem
to be searching for ways to keep Geu-rae.
But really, their efforts are in vain.
They know it's impossible to keep him.
Whoever becomes my partner,
I thought I only need to do
my part properly.
But still I thought it would be good
to be partners with someone
I'm comfortable talking to.
I just wanted to tell you.
I didn't ask you to be my partner
due to the shady reasons that
you may have had in mind.
I'm sorry for turning you down.
Don't be sorry.
Apologize after you get accepted.
By the way, Young-yi.
I'm sorry.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
It's sad, isn't it? You only had three
other colleagues to begin with.
Is there really no way?
That's all I think about nowadays.
There's no way, isn't there?
Maybe you can make it
into a company-wide agenda.
A company-wide issue?
The more the better, you know.
What if many employees openly discuss
and dwell on the issue?
Then the company may have to reconsider.
I'm not saying that's a solution,
but it's a start.
Make it a company-wide issue?
Right, according to Mr. Ha,
the point is to get as many employees
as possible to understand
Geu-rae's situation.
That Geu-rae is an asset to the company.
That Geu-rae deserves a contract
extension.
-How?
-Yes. How?
We can't do a presentation
for him on his behalf.
And we can't put up posters,
like we did in college.
And we can't just go to our superiors
and implore them, like in a movie.
Why can't we? We just have to go.
We can talk, persuade, beg,
and cry out loud, can't we?
You know, this is like our last resort.
Why is it so easy
to make a fool out of someone,
but so difficult to get people
to see the value of someone?
Where are you going?
I have to try something.
I'm willing to even try the method that
made me look like an idiot in the past.
I'm leaving too.
I think I have an idea.
What?
Hello, Young-yi?
Yes, Ms. Sun. I have...
I have a favor to ask of you.
I am Seok-yul Han,
a newbie on Textile Team One.
Since I have been with the company
for two years, I guess I'm not a newbie
This is the same Seok-yul Han
who wrote that messy issue in the past.
First, I would like to extend
my rather late apology.
There's a reason I am apologizing first.
I hope that you won't close this message
upon seeing the name of the sender.
Today, I wish
to convey a very important message.
No, not convey, but sincerely ask.
about the the two-year
contract employee, Geu-rae Jang
My colleague who works
in Sales Team Three.
I sincerely hope that he's able
to become a permanent employee.
I believe that we shouldn't overlook
Geu-rae's excellent work performance
for the company.
Although I understand that,
internal rumors are difficult to resolve.
Ever since he joined us with news
that he had a supporter helping him,
interns were discontent with the notion
that he received special treatment.
That's not necessarily true.
We're not asking
for special treatment on his behalf.
We just want a fair evaluation
of his efforts.
Two years ago, we formed a team
and passed the final presentation.
Then he was placed in Sales Team Three.
He was the first among us newbies
to have done a presentation
for the company executives.
He is the Geu-rae Jang
who managed to make the abandoned
Jordan used car project into a success
as a result of this presentation.
He got in easy.
Yes, some employees have
negative views of Geu-rae Jang.
They say he got in through connections
and didn't go to college.
Therefore, when we all joined
the company as permanent employees,
he was only hired
as a two-year temporary employee.
He was also severely humiliated by other
interns during our internship days.
However,
he worked harder than anyone else,
always putting the company's
interests before his.
MYANMAR PROJECT
SALES TEAM THREE
Is that for Geu-rae?
Well,
yes.
I'm hoping that it might help him.
I'm trying to make a file
proving his performance in projects.
Yeah, such portfolios are necessary for
permanent employee transition evaluations.
Let me take a look once you're done.
All right. Thank you.
He comes to work with us
but leaves office much later than us.
He worked twice as hard as we did
to make up for his lack of qualifications.
When he lost charge
of his approved business project
because he's just a temporary employee,
he moved on without a single complaint.
Place a new person in charge.
You know, I...
I've never been more embarrassed
of my qualifications until today.
I feel that way too.
What is it with qualifications that make
one person so different from another?
Why should that person's effort
be treated so differently from others?
That is something
that needs to be reflected
in company regulations.
But transition to a permanent position
without review is improbable.
Yes, you're correct.
But I ask that he must be reviewed fairly
and not judged differently
due to Mr. Choi's incident
during his quantitative
and qualitative standard evaluation.
Please be fair to Geu-rae Jang.
In order to evaluate one's adaptability
to work, basic principles are required.
Although it was difficult
to estimate Geu-rae Jang's
basic principles in trading,
he has shown sufficient potential during
the last two years of his employment.
Geu-rae Jang should become
a permanent employee.
Long ago, he once told me,
"I will sell this fabric with you,
Seok-yul."
Please allow me to keep that promise.
Although I have had my share
of shameful moments in front of you,
I would like to keep that promise.
Please consider my request.
Yes, may I know if the payment was made
for the Malaysia contact lenses project?
Yes, we have completed
the proposal review.
Profits increased two-fold
due to inventory surplus.
Please reply immediately.
We ask each team send one employee
down to the lobby
for college graduate intern selections.
-Well, new interns again.
-Right.
It feels like Geu-rae
just started a few days ago though.
It's good to have newbies, isn't it?
Go and make sure that
they know who's in charge.
Go ahead.
Okay, I'll be on my way down.
See you later.
Hey guys, can i talk to you for a bit?
What?
Do you mean that there is a possibility?
Headquarters will send guidelines
to all subsidiaries soon.
Contract employees who exhibited
superior skill and experience
will be given a permanent position.
As it is an opinion that was developed
in an upper management meeting,
it is likely that our company
will follow it too.
The tides have changed.
Mr. Cheon and Mr. Kim,
your help is needed.
I will also try my best to help.
First, collect and organize all the files
that reflect Geu-rae's work performance.
And keep it in one file folder.
Yes. We will do that.
Okay.
Hey.
Let's try it, Geu-rae.
YOUNG-HO PARK
SALES TEAM THREE MANAGER
Can I...
Can I have a dream again?
-I'm back.
-Why are you late?
I'm sorry. I'm very sorry.
Delivery has been backed up.
You have no time to waste!
It seems this door has to be fixed,
so it shuts properly.
Gosh. This is too much.
-Welcome. Come in.
-Can I have one roll of  kimbab ?
Okay.
Can we get two bowls of ramen
and one roll of  kimbab  please?
Okay.
Hey, how is your intern doing?
Don't remind me.
The guy's a college graduate but doesn't
even know how to use a printer.
So he asked for your help?
No, he asked his mother how to use it
over the phone, standing there.
What the heck?
That's unbelievable.
Oh, man. That is so wrong.
I don't know how to not
do things on my own.
Since I don't know how,
you can teach me.
You could give me a chance.
Goodness.
Well, thank you. I'm starving, let's eat.
I'm sorry I missed your kid's first
birthday. I was on a business trip.
DONG-SIK KIM
Hey, Hurry. You said you need to
go back soon.
Yeah, probably.
MS. JI-YOUNG SUN
Yes. Hello, Ms. Sun.
Mr. Oh, long time no talk.
How have you been?
Don't worry about me. I'm doing okay.
I'll lay the foundation
for our fledgling company.
So if you get fired, come to us.
Just trust me.
I'll have the red carpet laid out for you.
So if you get sick and tired over there,
throw your resignation letter
at Mr. Ma and head over here.
Mr. Ma is not even my manager,
so why throw it at him?
Is that so?
About Geu-rae,
he passed the evaluation review
of Human Resources today.
His case now goes to the planning and
evaluation board's meeting.
He now just needs a majority vote
from participants.
I'm receiving word from various channels,
and it seems likely that Geu-rae
will be offered a permanent position.
Yes, well...
That's good news.
Thank you.
Please keep supporting him.
When will the results be out?
Tomorrow.
Okay.
Thank you.
All right. See you.
-No results yet?
-Yes, no results yet.
Things should work out
since Ms. Sun is in the meeting too.
You know, I overheard Mr. Ma
and Mr. Jung talking the other day,
and it seems they're optimistic since it's
a regulation from the headquarters.
Furthermore, Geu-rae's performance
is in good standing
and many superiors have given
their recommendations.
Good morning, everyone.
Why are you so busy all day long?
I just have a lot of stuff
to submit before 5:00 pm.
Let's have lunch together later.
I might have to take a rain check on that.
I have to eat lightly with my superiors
while continuously working.
Hey, Geu-rae.
Your team is proceeding with the Shenzhen
digital door lock export project, right?
-I heard they asked for more products.
-Yes.
Doesn't our team also need to obtain
a Chinese security related project?
Yes, we do.
We don't need your team's approval, right?
Well, I think you will need it.
I think we won't. Keep up the good work.
-See you later.
-Okay.
Hello, how do you do?
Geu-rae, regarding the discarded fridge
regeneration case files and materials,
I left them on your desk.
Since they're all sorted
by steel, copper, aluminum and plastic,
they should be easy to read.
Thank you very much.
Also, our task force team
business report from the last quarter.
May I take a look at it tonight?
Sure. Baek-ki said he needed it, so
I already gave it to him this morning.
Thank you.
Geu-rae, let's go
for a drink one of these days.
It would be my pleasure. Thank you.
Where are those Malaysia files?
Ms. Sun is coming.
What is this?
I received my company email
and just sent it as a commemoration.
I'm sorry. Really.
This is why I love being a trading man.
Congratulations.
Give me some respect!
Speak for yourself!
What?
Everyone is saying whatever they want.
Why can't you say anything?
You know, I would like to get to know
you better, Geu-rae.
Since you're already in our team,
just hang in there by all means.
Hang in there, and you'll be successful.
Hang in there,
then you'll somehow step closer
to a complete life.
We all have
an incomplete life so far.
Okay.
The contract for the Vietnam helmet
project has arrived.
In order to test this helmet,
you got harassed
by the chicken restaurant owner
for an entire month.
The point was to find a Korean product
that could compete against a Japan one.
And without actually trying it out, there
is no way to convince Vietnamese buyers.
The lightness, strength, ventilation
system and air resistance.
These guys nitpick on everything.
Okay, I got it.
You're the real export master.
We got the contract, thanks to you.
And it's our company's best performing
project yet.
The Vietnam helmet export project.
Mr. Chung-ki Moon has followed us.
What? What did you say?
The Mecca cellphone!
Make it a success this time too.
I can't do it.
Hey, are you disrespecting me
because I'm a salary-earning president?
You're the ones who called me in to do
the job. Then why don't you listen?
What? Are you flexing your power because
you and Sang-hyup Kim are co-owners?
Do you know I was leading a comfortable
life working at One Aluminum,
getting off from work at 6:00 p.m. daily?
It's good.
It's a good project item.
How is it?
It's pretty good, isn't it?
The business plan is appealing.
It's good.
Let's do business together
as a partnership.
Let's do it.
But let's make someone else the president.
It's not you nor me.
What?
Let's make
Mr. Boo-ryeon Kim the president.
Boo-ryeon Kim?
Really?
That cold calculating guy?
He's a fucking aggressive perfectionist!
If you agree, we're partners.
If you disagree, I'm out.
Getting off from work on time is
really important to office workers.
I know you've been working
so late every day.
And what's with the 50-50 nonsense?
I invested 51%
and Sang-hyup Kim invested 49%.
This company always has to be run
with this ownership share division.
Okay, so have 51% shares!
Do the Mecca phone project
while I'm asking nicely.
Damn that Chung-ki Moon!
Having loyalty even though I don't mind
if he has no loyalty or not!
Is this for real? Jeez.
Hey Mr. Kim.
Come quickly to the office
and talk to our president.
JUNE 13TH: DRINKING MILK DAY
The milk is almost ready.
It's time to drink it.
I'll be visiting MyungJin C&C.
Okay. Keep up the good work.
-Hello?
- Hello?
Hey, my youngest son!
Daddy, buy me some chicken!
Half seasoned spicy and half fried, right?
Hand me the phone.
Clean up here, okay?
Damn. Although you have changed companies,
but why do you come home late like before?
You said you would reflect
on your life at your new company.
You promised to make up for lost time
and talk more with the kids.
You also promised a trip to Jeju Island.
But we still haven't gone.
And what about the camping trip?
You also promised to fix the curtain rod.
But for the last four days, you have just
ran out the door every morning!
So, what time are you coming home?
I'll be pretty late since I have
three client companies to visit.
Okay, I'll have dinner on my own.
Okay, got it.
You said, Martin arrived from Sao Paulo.
What? I must have gotten it wrong.
Go to the airport and pick him up.
I was on a work trip near the airport
and could have picked him up after lunch.
But you said he already arrived
at our office.
I came as fast as possible
without eating lunch.
Did you? I didn't know.
You should have told me.
Still not leaving?
Seok-yul, you can't go on vacation.
We have an office security session.
What session? I already checked.
It just came up. Push your vacation back.
You did this on purpose, didn't you?
I explained myself clearly,
and Mr. Moon already approved it.
It's my father's 60th birthday,
and we'll have a family vacation.
How do I put off my father's birthday?
Who said you could go on vacation
at this time of year? You idiot.
Are you shouting at me right now?
If I tell you to put it off, put it off!
Mr. Moon is going on a business trip
in your behalf. So the date stands!
Hello.
Okay, yes.
Hey, I have some time. Let's have a drink.
Okay, got it.
Jun-sik Sung of Textile Team One
is having an extramarital affair
with Chungsol's Kyung-sun Lee.
This act has created major setbacks
with business proceedings,
so therefore please investigate.
Shit.
Yes, Mom.
I'm sorry that I can't be there.
It's just that I'm so busy at work.
Absolutely. I earn all the money in Seoul.
Yes.
I know Dad's hurt by this.
May I talk with him for a minute?
What?
He won't talk to me?
Come on.
Have a pleasant trip
in the tropical country.
I'll absolutely go next year. I promise.
Yes, I got it. Keep safe.
You miserable piece of shit.
Why didn't you just pocket
the leftover money?
Then it would have been easier for me
to tattle on you.
Some private life you have...
Excuse me, I'm sorry.
But is there a Jun-sik Sung here?
-That's him.
-There? In the white shirt?
Thank you.
Hello, are you Jun-sik Sung?
-Yes, that's me.
-You're him?
Yes.
That hurt!
Hey, are you Jun-sik Sung?
-Hey, who the fuck are you?
-Who are you?
You know Kyung-sun Lee, don't you?
What? Ms. Lee at Chungsol?
Yes. Ms. Lee at Chungsol Textiles.
She's a manager at one of our client
companies. What about her?
Who the hell are you?
Who am I? Me?
Who do you think I am?
Who?
You fucker...
What did you do with my wife?
What the hell are talking about?
I knew you would try
to weasel your way out.
So I took pictures!
Look here. This is you kissing, isn't it?
You still don't know?
You really don't know?
-I think it's me.
-Look closer! You think it's you?
Hey, you little jerk.
You fucking piece of shit.
You fucking wife thief! Lift your chin up!
I'm so sorry.
-Come here. Get your ass over here now!
-Hey, Mr. Moon.
-Seok-yul! Help!
-Trying to run away? Get over here!
Are you sorry or are you not?
-I'm so sorry, sir.
-Now, you're sorry?
Now, you're sorry?
Please calm down, sir.
You can't be doing this here.
How far did you go?
Did you have sex with her?
You piece of shit...
Zip it. I don't want to know.
-I'm sincerely sorry.
-Shut up and come here!
Come here!
Come here! To this table!
You fucking bastard! Get back here.
I said I'm sorry.
I'm going to leave after I kill you!
Get your ass back over here.
I am really sorry.
You fucking piece of shit!
Give me back everything
that my wife bought you.
-This watch...
-Return everything!
This watch.
And these shoes.
And wait a minute, these socks too!
-The necktie too.
-Not all that crap!
Are you fucking kidding me?
The car! The car keys!
-What? A car?
-Here you go.
-A car?
-Yes, car keys. But this is actually mine!
You son of a bitch!
No, here you go. I'm really sorry.
I really am...
BMW?
Hey, you bastard!
You can't be doing this here.
Hey mister,
has your wife ever had an affair?
-No.
-See? You don't get what I feel. Hey you!
Why do you live this way?
Shit.
You should have brought me some
wet tissues, you insensitive shit.
-Hey, Baek-ki.
-Yes?
Your performance for this quarter exceeded
expectations by 150%.
Thank you.
You're going to catch Mr. Kang soon.
-No way, sir.
-You should watch out, Mr. Kang.
Congratulations, Baek-ki.
Thank you.
By the way, this...
This is a printout of the e-mail
we need to send to Germany,
and you didn't revise
the word errors I had pointed out.
Mr. Kang.
The word sie you see here
is supposed to be written
with a capital S.
Because we need to use the honorific form
in this particular sentence.
We do?
Yes.
By the way, Mr. Kang.
There is something I forgot
to mention the other day.
You know, in German,
on how to pronounce the letter W.
You said to think of it as
taking a toothbrush and putting it too far
down your throat that you retch.
And then use the retch sound
to verbalize the letter W.
-Yes, I did.
-Right.
But actually,
it should sound like
you're popping out condensed air
from your mouth and not your nose.
Like this,  wa .
This is the correct way to pronounce it.
So...
Wasser.
Wagen.
Weis.
Wa...
Is that so?
The German language academy I went
to taught it the other way.
Which academy did you go to?
The Wahr German language academy.
Okay.
The tutor there is from my college.
I won't make it to lunch.
You don't have the stomach to taste it?
Well, you know.
Hey, you got over watching horror movies.
So let's continue your progress.
If you can't eat it, I'll take it.
Didn't you say you were too busy
for lunch?
I was so starving that I finished work
in a heartbeat.
Is Mr. Sung okay?
Crying shit, bloody nose, all beaten up,
and the humiliation. He's a disgrace!
Will he be able to continue working
at the company?
Since he's a psychopath, absolutely.
But I want to know...
When did you go watch movies together?
I like watching movies too.
You shouldn't discriminate colleagues.
Do you like horror movies?
What? Why watch horror movies when
there are so many other genres to watch?
I miss Geu-rae.
Since four became three,
symmetry has been destroyed! Get it?
It's crap.
If the subject is an item,
use the active form.
If the subject is a person,
use the passive form.
You know our Mr. Park?
He opened a new restaurant
and is searching for a manager.
Do you want the job?
No. Tell him thanks, but no thanks.
But do you have any other options?
I'm searching. And I have to attend
the Chinese language academy.
Is your Chinese any better?
Try speaking a few words to me.
Ni hao.
How can you talk to your mother like that?
You little brat.
Forget it.
I can't teach you
since you don't know anything.
Yes? Young-yi.
Hey, Young-yi.
Hey, you're here.
It's been three weeks.
Yes.
It feels like three years have passed
since we used to meet every day.
You didn't even have a farewell party.
And you left just like that.
I know you probably did it to detach
yourself quickly and move on.
But those you left behind felt guilty
over your departure.
No, that's not why I left quietly.
You know, after you left, Seok-yul
doesn't even come down to our floor
since you're not around.
The company hired new interns.
But none of them have that "it" factor
like you had.
What?
Hey, they're all here.
Hey Geu-rae. Long time no see.
-Hey, Geu-rae.
-Hey Seok-yul.
-I wish you work with us .
-Oh jeez.
-Come on. Hold up.
-Why? What?
What? Mine?
-Drink it if you get tipsy.
-Thanks.
-What about me?
-And me?
I'm jobless, you know.
It's great to see you all.
You know, I want to leave your heart,
mind, and soul,
but I keep lingering.
-Then you can leave forever today.
-Don't say that.
Geu-rae's heart isn't some place, where
you can just waltz in and out of.
What's wrong with you guys?
Hey, Geu-rae. I want to know
what rank am I in your heart?
Am I just an employee or manager?
-Come on. Stop the nonsense.
-Cut it out.
This isn't funny?
Hey.
Hasn't Mr. Oh called to hire you?
From Mr. Oh's point of view,
maybe he thinks it's too early to ask
since his new company is still unstable.
That makes sense.
Adventure and risk could be a burden.
Maybe that's what he thinks.
Why don't you try calling him first?
What?
Yes, try it and just say hello.
Geu-rae.
A place like a company
isn't a place you can just go in
and come out as you please, right?
Just like how my love
for you can't get in and out as I please.
-Hey, cut it out.
-Stop it, man.
Seok-yul. Just put this in your mouth.
-Another toast.
-Things never change, do they?
You're happily humming
because everyone is working
and you're not?
Mr. Oh.
How did you find my address?
You have settled down, haven't you?
What?
It's already been three weeks.
The milk is ready.
You already have shirts, a necktie
and a suit.
And a briefcase.
And formal shoes.
You can show up for work immediately.
Yes. Mr. Hong, come on.
You can't just say the subsidiary
materials are not transshipped yet.
They wouldn't complete the payment
because of a complaint.
You keep insisting you destroyed
the picture of the products,
but who would believe that?
That's what I mean.
This is Geun-young Kim,
an intern for Sales Team Three.
Hello?
Dong-sik.
Didn't you complete the payment
for the Philippines timber project?
Come on, be quick!
Why do they keep calling my team?
-Gosh.
-Got it, sir.
This is Dong-sik Kim of Sales Team Three.
Yes, sir.
The meeting with Dasun Chemical tomorrow?
Please wait.
Yes, right.
Right. I reserved the restaurant
Hwaryun at five o'clock.
I understand, sir. Bye.
Nowadays,
I feel like time goes by too slowly.
It used to go by so fast.
No fun.
Are you still trying to find fun at work?
I guess so.
Drink it.
What?
-We need to drink it.
-Whatever...
Why...
Why do I feel lonely?
It's weird. This picture was put face down
at One International, too.
-Hello, sir.
-Yes.
-I'm back.
-Hello.
-The document is ready, sir.
-Alright.
Did you send the invoice, packing list,
bill of lading for the Uzbekistan project?
I sent them two hours ago.
-By the way, sir.
-Yes?
I've wondered about this for a long time.
What's that?
I'm busy. Tell me.
Why do you keep putting
your family picture face down?
What?
Because my wife is noisy.
You haven't heard my wife nagging yet.
There's just no end to my wife's nagging.
When her nagging gets out of control,
I go numb and my soul is crushed.
I see.
Do you really understand how I feel?
How's it going with our job posting
for an experienced employee?
The number of hits is increasing,
but no one applied yet.
Well, you know...
A young internship program.
Shall we use that program?
Thanks to deregulation, small business
can have the benefit from the program.
Really? I'll look into it.
All right.
I didn't mean to throw the door open.
Is this my station?
Is this a registered trading firm
in the trading association?
What should I do first?
Hey, Mr. Kim!
No, Mr. President. Hello.
I already looked
around this whole building.
The rooftop just sucks. So disappointing.
Geu-rae! Delete the ad
on the online job site quickly.
No more fun working on the 15th floor.
I'll quit. Delete it, hurry!
Hey, what are you doing?
We follow the standard procedure, bastard!
We'll properly hire people.
What kind of standard procedure?
You said, be radical.
He also came through connections.
Come on. What's wrong?
Only Geu-rae can be radical?
But what about me?
-Accept me!
-No.
-Accept me please!
Where are you going, you punk?
Don't do that. Hey...
Come to me!
Wow!
I got a little nervous.
Get back to work!
What? Jin-sang Seo?
Jin-sang Seo stole the samples of
cellphone case from the factory in China.
What are you talking about?
The metal cellphone case
that we contracted with?
-Yes.
-Where is he? Can we find him?
-Do you know where did he go?
-Jeez, that honey swindler.
We're tracking him down now.
Our expat is looking into it
at the Chinese immigration office.
It won't be hard to locate him.
I see. Keep me updated.
I'm just at a loss.
Jin-sang Seo, that bastard.
He set the world on fire in the end.
Our contract could be cancelled.
-What now?
-How many projects for One International?
-Three, sir.
-What about us?
We have two contracts. One is in progress.
That's it.
It's only a matter of the buyer's trust
and HR controls for One International,
but it's life or death for us.
Jeez. Jin-sang Seo, that bastard.
-Hello.
-He flew to Jordan.
What? Jordan?
All right. We'll leave soon.
Can the Vietnam project be delayed?
If I don't show up tomorrow,
the contract could be broken.
Then Geu-rae should go.
Apply for the visa and buy the ticket.
-Yes, sir.
-Call Mr. Cho in Amman.
Yes, sir.
This is a flight ticket to Abu Dhabi.
And this is a flight ticket
from Abu Dhabi to Amman.
Please take your passport
and baggage tag. Enjoy your trip.
Yes, sir.
I just got the tickets.
You have to transfer at Abu Dhabi.
You should not get out there.
-I know, sir.
- When you arrive in Amman,
Mr. Cho will pick you up.
You know his number, right?
Yes, sir.
Okay, good.
Be careful with the food there.
-Mr. Oh.
-What?
-I'm not a kid.
-Well...
-All right.
-Bye.
Mr. Geu-rae Jang.
Yes, Mr. Cho.
You must be tired after a long flight.
I'm fine.
Where is Jin-sang Seo?
It's confirmed that he's in Amman.
We searched all the hotels
and guesthouses, but he's not there.
I have no idea where he is staying.
-Any acquaintances?
-He's got no acquaintances here.
Have you been to Jordan?
If you go to the backstreets in downtown,
there's a nice, small
yet inexpensive hotel.
It costs only 10,000 won a day.
Have you checked the hotels
in the old section of the city?
-Hotels in the old section?
-Yes.
I don't think there are any hotels
in that area.
I guess there are only a couple
of them, but they are...
-They are old.
-Yes, they're old.
-And cheap.
-Yes.
You can stay there
only with 10,000 won a day.
However,
I don't think Jin-sang Seo will stay
at such a place in Jordan.
He could be. Please look into it.
All right.
But where's Mr. Oh?
-Hello.
-Where are you now, sir?
-I'm checking the land now.
-Land?
Are you really going to do it?
You know why the Russian Mafia mobsters
have tattoos on their knees?
-What?
-It means they won't kneel down, ever.
What?
We never give up.
We need to whatever we can do.
Right. But do we really have to...
We should always have a plan B.
Whether or not our business succeeds
depends on this. Stay sharp!
I was told it wouldn't take long
to build one.
I need to hang up
because of the phone bill.
-Hello.
-I'll see you in Petra after three hours.
What? In Petra?
"Two roads diverged in a yellow wood.
I took the one less traveled by.
And that has made
all the difference."
Bravo.
Al-Khazneh.
The Treasury of the Pharaoh.
The gate of Petra.
Merchants had to pass by here.
The Persian Gulf in the East.
The Red Sea in the South.
And the Mediterranean Sea in the West.
This place was an ancient trade hub,
connecting all of them.
The Silk Road?
Come to think of it,
when I was 18 years old,
I dreamed of traveling around the world.
While I was watching  Indiana Jones
and  Last Crusades ,
I promised myself that I'll travel.
Indiana Jones?
Yes.
It totally slipped my mind.
Since I came to Jordan, I remembered it.
My dream.
Dream.
Petra...
As the trade route was shifted,
this city has been forgotten
for more than 1,000 years.
I see.
So I thought about it in my head,
that even if you forgot your dream,
your dream still remains there.
Even if you don't see the road,
the road still remains there.
Lu Xun once said,
"Hope
can't be said to exist,
nor can it be said not to exist.
It's just like
roads across the earth.
For actually there are no roads
to begin with,
but when many men pass one way,
a road is made."
I see.
By the way, Mr. Oh.
Yes?
Why did you want to meet me here?
I just told you.
What?
What? When?
-Just a while ago.
-What?
I just told you.
Well... What?
I should have brought Young-yi here.
If I had told her,
she would have understood it immediately.
I should have brought Young-yi.
By any chance,
does that mean I must catch Jin-sang Seo?
-Mr. Jang?
-Did you find him?
It's Cairo Hotel.
Let's meet in front of the hotel.
-Mr. Jang!
-Yes.
This way, please.
Did he already check out?
Mr. Seo.
Goodness!
Move away!
Move!
Mr. Jang!
Fuck!
Oh, damn!
Shit!
Oh, my goodness.
What the hell is wrong with him?
My neck.
I broke my ribs.
It hurts. He's going to kill me.
Where is it?
What are you talking about?
The samples that you stole
from the factory in China.
What? What did I steal?
Mr. Seo.
If you return them,
you won't face charges.
-What?
-If you don't,
you'll go through criminal
and civil trials.
You'll sell your house, and go to jail.
What are you trying to say?
Are you crazy? I just quit my job
and came traveling here. Is that wrong?
There's nothing in his room.
You bastard!
Let go of me. You're hurting me!
You guys will pay for this.
I'm going to contact the embassy.
This is a diplomatic issue.
Do you have any evidence? Evidence, okay?
-This won't work.
-What?
Where am I?
In the middle of Wadi Rum.
What? Wadi Rum?
Thanks.
Come back. It's cold.
Mr. Seo, let me tell you again.
If you return them,
you won't face charges.
I really don't know.
Why are you doing this to me?
Hey, Geu-rae.
Why are you threatening me?
Am I an employee of your company?
Am I a Korean citizen?
Seriously.
Hello, Mr. Oh.
We caught him, but he won't talk.
Since we don't have any evidence,
we can't help it.
-Wait, Mr. Jang.
-What?
Russia.
Mafia mobsters' knee tattoo?
You see? Come on.
-I got it, sir.
-If you find the evidence,
I'll turn myself in.
Russia's Vasily Corp. is looking for you.
Mr. Cho.
How many stakes does the Russian
Mafia have in Vasily Corp.?
What?
According to Mr. Oh, it's over 70%.
Do you think it's true?
You're right.
I heard the mafia has been financing
the company in recent years.
However, I didn't know it's that high.
It's like the company is virtually owned
by the mafia.
Owned by the mafia?
Mr. Seo.
Mr. Oh asked me to deliver you a message.
What message?
In Russia,
drums beat, but laws are silent.
Jeez, I don't get it. Why are you...
Let's wrap up.
I'm whipping! I'm riding!
Where drums beat, laws are silent.
Tell me where you hid them.
They're my friends so let me talk to them.
Mr. Jang!
Amman Airport...
They're in a locker at Amman Airport.
The locker number is 28. I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Please tell them to leave.
Mr. Jang.
You're indeed One International's
trading man.
How come he's One International's man?
Why is he One International's man?
It was just a figure of speech.
Mr. Jang made every effort
not to damage One International...
Why is it because of One International?
It's all for the sake of our company.
That's the same.
If One International gets damaged,
then your company will get damaged too.
-When your company gets damaged...
-Stop it!
Don't you know our company motto?
We may lose the work, but not our people.
I heard that's your own motto, sir.
Dong-sik, that punk.
Along the edge of the abyss
on the very brink of the precipice
I'm riding my horses, I'm whipping them!
You're a bad bastard.
I'm not.
-Hey, Geu-rae.
-Yes.
How come you didn't say anything when
they said One International man.
Sorry?
Any feelings left for One International?
No, sir.
Dude, you used to say you're satisfied
as long as you work as a regular employee.
Jeez, you said that.
Then a year later,
you become interested in higher salary
and more benefits, right?
That's right. Please increase my bonus.
What?
You really have no feelings left
for One International?
I don't know.
This punk.
-Convince me, sir.
-What?
Convince me, so that you can keep me.
What's your selling point, sir?
What's your selling point?
My efforts.
I haven't made any efforts so far,
so my efforts are freaking fresh and new.
What? How fresh and new?
I'll do my best.
I'll definitely do my best.
Just drive, punk!
I had a car accident before.
You shouldn't hit my head.
A road
is not just where we walk,
but also where we move forward.
A road where we cannot move forward
is not a real road.
A road is open to everyone.
What? Hazard pay?
But not everyone can take the road.
Are you in the army? What hazard pay?
You ordered me to catch him.
I risked my own life.
Jeez, you're so mean.
I'm on the road again.
Come on.
And
I'm not alone.
How can you leave us like this?
Oh no...
Honey...
EUN-JI KIM
Subtitle translation by You-jeong Kim