Mr. Oh.
Hello.
We're on the same team now.
Wow, Mr. Kim.
You always look like you're a good worker.
I'm Geu-rae Jang.
Oh, you are the new contract worker.
I heard somebody hooked you up with a job.
I heard you're only a high school
graduate. You're quite lucky.
How did he get in?
I heard he doesn't have any connections.
Where is my desk?
It's here, right?
Whose is this?
Let's work hard.
What are you saying?
Please send someone else.
If that's not possible, please forget
about giving us more people.
Listen Sang-sik.
-What's wrong with you?
-I'm asking you
to send me someone that'll be helpful
to Sales Team Three.
That is Mr. Park.
Where can you find someone like
Mr. Park these days?
When I was in resources,
he was an excellent worker.
You can't be 100 percent pleased
with everything.
You need to adjust to one another.
Just think about work. Just work.
Hey, Mr. Jung.
I heard you recommended Mr. Park.
Yes. His performance is excellent.
What are you saying?
We all know that you're just trying
to get rid of him.
-Get rid of him?
-I have ears, you know.
I hear things.
I know he gave you a hard time
when he worked with you.
He has potential, but just doesn't fit
the Resources Team, that's all.
If my leadership
was a bit more sophisticated,
I'm sure he would have done a better job.
It sounds to me that he's someone
you really wanted to get rid of.
Hey, high school graduate.
Yes.
Come here.
You're not even a high school graduate,
you only have a GED?
Wow, you really did well coming here,
didn't you?
That's amazing, right?
How did you pass the final presentation?
Mr. Kim, you didn't leak the topic
or something, did you?
I'm sure there's nothing you know
how to do, right?
You do have a pretty face.
I guess we can use your looks
for something.
Looks are important in sales.
Don't get too intimidated.
You have a girlfriend, right?
Let me see her picture.
-Let me see.
-Get to know each other later.
Let's organize the desks.
Mr. Oh.
There are subordinates here.
What's with the tone of your voice?
It makes me a bit uncomfortable.
How was it in the other department?
Well, of course, it's...
Mr. Jung,
how did you address Mr. Park there?
Okay.
I don't think I was out of place.
All right, then.
You didn't have to go and make a call.
Why are you just standing there?
I'm sorry.
Why did you just stand there like that?
What?
Then again, how could you stand up to him?
But why Mr. Park of all people?
Seriously.
It's not going to be a smooth ride.
Geu-rae, get the materials
for the meeting ready.
EPISODE 9
These are the materials.
Those are the materials
for the Middle East projects.
See if there's anything that might fit us.
Jeez. I just got here.
I was only here for three days.
I didn't even get used to the team yet.
Why are there so many?
When am I going to finish reading these?
This one is probably going to kill us.
This one will not profit enough compared
to the work we'll have to put into it.
Hey, high school graduate.
Did you pick this?
Sir, this one will not work.
You can't do projects in the Middle East
merely with just your will.
Then why don't you bring some items
that will be good to work on.
Sir, are you even paying attention
to what I'm saying?
Let me get adjusted first.
Even when a gambler joins the game
in the middle,
he takes time to see what the stakes are
and how the game is flowing.
Jeez.
You're very competent.
I'll be back tomorrow.
Call me if anything comes up.
Yes, sir.
This is Baek-ki Jang.
Has the interview date been set?
Yes.
It's on a weekday.
No, it's fine. I can take a day off.
Yes.
Hey. Who asked you for this?
Don't do things you weren't told to do.
OUT OF PAPER
Man.
Here you go.
Damn it.
Young-yi, what are you doing?
Did you not ask for it?
As you said,
I will withdraw from the project.
But while you are working on it,
I will do all of your chores for you.
Really?
Fine. Do it.
Clear this trash can
and wash it.
What? You don't want to do it?
No, sir. I'll do it.
While you're at it,
clear all of the trash cans.
Yes, sir.
Summarize it and bring it to me.
Okay.
Hey. What is she doing?
I ordered her to do it.
She really wanted to.
What's wrong with you?
Just because she wants to,
you can't have her do things like that.
Really.
Baek-ki!
Is this the way for you to be accepted
as a member of their team?
What are you doing with...
-Baek-ki.
-My goodness!
Seriously.
Damn it.
What is... Shit!
Please see me outside.
What was that?
Are they dating...
Are they going out?
Answer me Geu-rae.
I don't have a clue.
Fine.
You and I both don't deserve
to be treated like this.
If the company doesn't want me,
I don't think I should stay.
If it's the same for you, then just leave.
Baek-ki.
Don't even interfere
with my business like that.
I didn't mean this
when I said you should give in.
Is giving in to everything
what you've decided to do?
Yes.
-For me, that's my way...
-That's not a good way.
Then what else can I do?
What else? If you know, tell me.
Working hard doesn't work.
And it gets worse if I don't.
What am I supposed to do?
I didn't learn in school
how to have people
that have already pushed me away
to open up to me.
It's not taught in English
and Math subjects. That's why...
That's why I'm doing what I can.
I'm doing everything that I can think of.
This is the way I've found.
If you found your own way,
let's keep out of each other's business
and do what's best for ourselves.
I'm going to quit the company.
Hey, Seok-yul.
Sir, I just sent the documents
to Taejin Company.
Good job.
I can really count on you.
Do you want to have some coffee?
Sure.
Have the most expensive one.
-Two caramel macchiatos, please.
-Okay.
Sir, this card is not working.
What?
Could you try once more?
It's not working.
Here you go.
YOON-A: YURI IS BETTER AT ACTING THAN
WHEN I FIRST STARTED
-Sir, here's your coffee.
-Thank you.
Sir, your card.
Yes, my card. Thank you.
You exceeded your limit.
What?
That's right. How much was it?
It was nine thousand won.
Well...
I don't have any cash.
It's okay. It's on me.
Really?
You're a real man, Seok-yul.
Also, about the polyester project.
The Canadian buyer will call in a bit.
Organize the item list by then.
Wait, Canada?
They said that they would call
at 11:00 a.m. their time,
it's approximately midnight here.
-Midnight?
-Yes.
And tomorrow,
accompany the management
to the breakfast meeting.
Breakfast meeting?
Go to King's hotel by five-thirty.
Do you mean 5:30 a.m.?
Yes.
Right.
I have a business trip early tomorrow.
So I can't go.
Something's wrong.
Mr. Sung just can't do anything
without me.
Okay.
-File these.
-All right.
This is like
not getting paid
after doing a part-time job.
Like I got stabbed in the back.
Yes, Seok-yul?
Geu-rae, I'm in the break room
Can we talk for a moment?
Why?
Here.
What is it?
Listen to me.
Listen and let me know what you think.
You know that Mr. Sung
-is a very good person, right?
-I don't know.
What? Anyway,
something's not right.
-I think that...
-Do you think he's making you do his work?
Yes. Do you think so, too?
Do you think that Geu-rae?
Do you think so, too?
Hello?
It's me.
-Who is this?
-Don't you know your superior's voice?
Yes, Mr. Park.
Print me the EPC TF project
for the Steel Team.
-Yes, sir.
-Is Mr. Park here?
-No.
-Where's Geu-rae?
I'm not sure.
He was just here a moment ago.
There we go. It's good.
This is... Good!
Wow!
-You missed it!
-Yes!
Your phone's been ringing.
Are you going to be okay?
It's fine, you punk.
Overcome
the obstacle
in front of me first.
Yes! 10,000 won each.
-He got that?
-It's 10,000 won each.
-That was shady.
-It went like this.
Give me 10,000 won each.
Is that all you have? You, too?
Well...
Never mind, you punk.
-Thank you.
-Thank you, sir.
All right. Win big.
Are you going to the sauna now?
I have a coupon. Do you want it?
Hey.
I am a member at the Phillip Hotel.
I don't go to those regular saunas, okay?
Are you going to wear those to the hotel?
Are you crazy?
Hey.
What do you want me to do with that?
Put it down.
You should have brought a shoehorn.
You have no consideration.
I'm going to meet with a vendor,
so take this back, okay?
-What is that?
-This is...
It's nothing, sir.
Where's Mr. Park?
He went to meet with a vendor.
Which vendor? He just started here.
It's a vendor he knew from the other team.
Geu-rae, call him.
Okay.
How was in at the other department?
Mr. Jung,
how did you address Mr. Park there?
I don't think I was out of place.
Those are the materials
for the Middle East projects.
See if there's anything that might fit us.
He's still a salary man.
That good-for-nothing bastard
is too arrogant.
Where is he? Is he gone for the day?
No, sir. He went to Pohang to meet buyers.
Yes, this is the Steel Team
of One Enterprise.
Yes. Mr. Kang is on a business trip.
Okay.
Okay. I'll relay the message to him.
Give it to him.
Right, this is the EPC TF project.
The report that Mr. Kang made seems good.
So tell him to get
the approval from the steel team.
The Resource Team and our team need
to get it approved, too. It's urgent.
-It must be done, right away.
-Yes, sir.
I'll let him know as soon as he gets back.
-Where's Mr. Cha?
-He went to Myanmar on business.
This team needs
to recruit more people, too.
You're not physically here
but looking elsewhere,
are you?
Pardon?
See you later.
MYANMAR EPC TF PROJECT
Time really flies when you're having fun.
It's already time to go home.
Mr. Park, where did you go?
What?
Damn it. Hey you, contractor.
Didn't you tell him?
I told you that I went to meet a vendor.
-I did...
-Did you meet your vendor at the sauna?
The scent of the charcoal
in the sauna is still strong on you.
Our Sang-sik.
Your keen sense of smell
is still quite sharp.
Hey, Mr. Park.
Yes?
You should use formal titles
when you are at work.
Okay, I will.
You've become so bossy unlike before.
You weren't like that, you know?
You should stop going to the sauna
during work hours. It's not right.
All right.
I'm sorry.
I should work. This one. "Halal"?
Should we do this?
Well, is it feasible?
Well, it won't bring in much
in the beginning,
but it's great to understand
the environment of the Middle East.
It's not bad for Team Three
to do it as a case study.
Okay. Great.
But I can't do Middle East items
by myself.
-Mr. Kim.
-Yes?
Give me Geu-rae. All I need is him.
Mr. Park, Geu-rae is not...
I can't have him?
Why?
You're not capable?
I don't need that much support.
I'll just have him do things
that a high school graduate can do.
You're a high school graduate, right?
Wait.
-You didn't even graduate, did you?
-Hey, Mr. Park.
Sir, if you allow it,
I'll support Mr. Park.
Geu-rae.
Don't you know the order of rank?
Who's higher in rank? Mr. Oh or Mr. Park?
You should know better.
Hey, Dong-sik. Stay out of it.
Don't interfere.
What are you saying? What do you mean?
-What?
-Enough.
The order of rank
is really fucked up here.
A deputy is acting up to a manager?
Wow. The atmosphere here is nice.
Did you guys already get close?
-Hello, sir.
-Yes.
How's Team Three?
I'm really looking forward
to working with them
as a team.
Team Three's business is very important.
Work hard.
I took the extra mile to have you here.
-Yes, sir. I'll do that.
-Good.
Sir. where do you play golf these days?
My wrist got hurt a while back,
so I haven't been out recently.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Anyway, I'm expecting a lot from you.
Work hard.
Goodbye.
You really fucked me over this time.
He was a really good employee.
He specializes in the Middle East,
so he'll be of big help for our team.
I know.
He was the legend of the 120 million
dollar Jordan export project.
That was the best result
from the Steel Team.
And Mr. Park played a big part then.
Really?
He was a deputy manager then.
He was in charge of communicating
with the local vendors.
Everyone agreed that he played
the biggest part in winning the deal.
That's when it all started.
He became unstable since then.
Let's take him in.
Since he joined Sales Team Three,
he's one of us.
Even if we lose deals,
we don't lose people. That's our motto.
That's your personal motto.
What's with your nonsense?
Come tomorrow,
support him well with the halal project.
It won't be easy, but bear with it.
That's your specialty.
Perseverance.
-What?
-Sir, I don't like that either.
Geu-rae. What's wrong with you?
It's okay to get criticized
for not doing your work right.
But personal attack is something else.
If you don't like it, say something.
People will say you have no self-esteem.
Come tomorrow,
support him well with the halal project.
It won't be easy, but bear with it.
That's your specialty.
Perseverance.
Sir, I don't like that either.
Geu-rae. What's wrong with you?
It's okay to get criticized
for not doing your work right.
But personal attack is something else.
If you don't like it, say something.
People will say you have no self-esteem.
ATTACK TACTICS
Jumping into danger is not
the only way of showing courage.
You're not even a high school graduate.
You only have a GED?
Avoiding the area of danger
where you want to jump into
and silently going along is also courage.
Immediately reacting to a backflow
is foolish.
If I remain in the current as
the opponent tries to cause a backflow,
it will just create a backflow
to the opponent himself.
Sir, if you allow it,
I'll support Mr. Park.
So standing firm and keeping my flow,
is the best defense
and the strongest offense.
Hold on, please.
Excuse me.
-Hello.
That guy is quite impatient.
Baek-ki.
Yes?
-What?
-Well...
Baek-ki, you were an intern
for Resources Team Two, right?
Yes.
What was Mr. Park like?
Since you were on the same team...
Are you trying to make me talk
behind a senior's back?
No, I'm not.
If that's what it sounded like,
I apologize.
He's going to be a bit too much for you.
I can imagine how he is treating you.
Don't take everything so personally.
That will be easier for you.
Just ignore him.
This is the list
of the halal meat distributors.
What? Already?
You really are the competent,
underqualified newbie as they say.
How did you find it?
I found a team that had done halal
projects and got it from them.
I also contacted current Arab vendors
and inquired about halal business.
Pretty good.
You know
I said I'll only ask easy things from you.
But you still need
to know how to do basic things.
Basics. I'm talking about basics.
For example, you need to know trade terms.
Do you know what A/S is?
I'm not talking
about repairing refrigerators and stuff.
At sight.
It is a condition that it must be bought
or paid when the promissory note is given.
You are good.
Volume rate.
It's a type of discount
for large shipments.
It is a discounted rate given
as the freight volume increases.
Knocked down.
Exporting goods in pieces
to be assembled once received.
The taxes on the finished goods
are higher.
Therefore it saves on cost in countries
where labor cost is low.
W/M.
It gives the shipping company the right
to choose whether to use
weight or capacity
to calculate shipping cost.
If the buyer asks this,
how would you answer?
You don't understand?
English is part of the basics
in a trade company.
What are we going to do with him?
He's just not qualified.
Jeez.
Good job.
He's so childish.
Cocky bastard.
Yes, sir. I understand.
Mr. Jang, Mr. Kang can't come today.
Okay. I understand.
-Hello.
-Hey.
Mr. Kang is coming today, right?
When is he coming?
-He can't come today.
-What? He can't?
No. What should I do?
What's wrong?
They want each team
to send the revised budget
for the EPC TC project today
to the Finance Team for approval.
Steel Team needs to send it in too.
It's nothing much.
Do you think you can do it?
What?
Mr. Kang finished
the whole report before he left.
All you have to do is summarize it
and input the budget and timetable
and sort it into approximately five pages
to meet the approval standards.
I don't think Mr. Kang will approve.
Let me call him.
Would you like some coffee?
It's fine.
MYANMAR EPC TF PROJECT
I'll get it.
This is Baek-ki Jang of the Steel Team.
Baek-ki, it's me.
I just heard from Mr. Yoo
from Resources Team Two.
Do you think you can do it?
I understand.
Okay.
Just because you're quitting,
you won't do a mediocre job, right?
I'm counting on you.
MS. SUN-JU KIM
CONFIRM
REQUEST FOR APPROVAL
REQUEST FOR APPROVAL NOTES
REQUEST MADE FOR HAE-JUN KANG
WOULD YOU LIKE TO SEND THE REQUEST?
THE REQUEST HAS BEEN SENT
Sir.
This is the investigation
for the butchery process sorted by kind,
location and certification process
is done.
Leave it there.
Hey,
can you massage my shoulder a little?
It's really hurting. Just a little.
What's wrong with my shoulders?
It hurts.
You don't want to?
No, sir.
Yes, that feels good.
Did you learn how to massage or something?
You're so good.
You really have a knack for it.
Even if you leave here,
you'll have something to make a living of.
Mr. Oh, he's really good.
I think that's enough.
Geu-rae has a lot to do.
It's not going to take that long.
Okay. That's fine.
I'm feeling better now.
Geu-rae.
Did you learn
how to do a foot massage, too?
Can you massage my feet too?
Every time I move like this,
it hurts so much.
What are you doing?
Yes, that hurts.
Hold on. Stop.
Yes, sir. I'm good.
Yes. How's everything with you?
Right. I was transferred to another team.
Geu-rae. Let's talk for a moment.
Well, you know...
Is it because of your name?
What?
Well, because your name is Geu-rae,
and it means yes.
If you don't want to
and you don't think it's right,
just say so. It's okay.
I'm not just talking about Mr. Park.
Usually, when a newbie starts his new job,
he'd get frustrated or overdo it
after reality hits him.
But he'd find the right path eventually.
But you're not like that. You just do
everything told without complaining.
You seem like you're ready
to accept anything that is thrown at you.
You're like a long-term prisoner
that's just been released.
It's like you're doing everything you can
to adjust to society.
I'm sorry. I think I was out of line.
But Geu-rae, you're really like that.
I don't know much of your past, okay?
I know you are a high school graduate
with a GED
who has not done anything until now.
Tell me.
What kind of life have you live until now
to be so cooperative and self-sacrificial?
As for me,
I wish that
I'll be able to get to know you better
in the near future.
I'll get going first.
Go and get some sleep.
You stayed up all night
to prepare for the meeting.
You didn't sleep at all, did you?
It's okay, sir.
Accommodating the management
is actually the deputy manager's job.
Good job.
Mr. Sung must be tired, too.
Going on a business after an all-nighter.
-An all-nighter?
-He didn't even have to go.
Why would he volunteer for that?
He didn't have to go?
How much of the Canada polyester project
has been processed?
You don't know much about it, do you?
Well, I have...
Sir, I'm back.
Seok-yul, did it go well?
Good job.
Bring me the polyester project.
I need to take it up for review.
Yes, sir.
MR. JUN-SIK SUNG
Seok-yul.
You didn't send me the email
with the times for the polyester project.
If you did the work, you should have sent
me the file, too. Did you forget?
What's the matter with you?
Sir, here you are. I revised the list
as they requested, yesterday.
-Let's get going with it.
-Yes, sir.
You heard him, right? Let's get going.
-Excuse me, sir.
-Yes?
I have something to tell you.
I can't do it.
What?
You can't?
I'm too busy.
Can't you just do it yourself?
-What?
-It's your job.
The polyester export
and this morning's breakfast meeting...
Hey, Seok-yul.
I'm busy with the next quarter's report
that I need to give to the manager.
I can't do your job as well.
What? You can't do my job?
You just stepped out of line.
Are you trying to say
that I dumped my work on you?
-Yes, I do think that...
-Hey!
This is why newbies nowadays
are troublesome.
You can't even help your senior with that?
I'm teaching you the ropes,
not dumping my work on you.
You need to watch what you say!
Baek-ki.
There was a reply from the Finance Team
regarding the report you sent.
Got it. All right.
MS. SUN-JU KIM
DEFERRED
What? There's no reason
for it being deferred?
Mr. Kim, not again.
It's Mr. Kim's
unique way of communicating
when there is no reason written.
It means that you have
to find the reason yourself.
It either means that it's completely wrong
or that it's missing an important factor.
-Usually, that's what it means.
-Okay.
I don't think you did it all wrong.
Take a look and see what you've missed.
Yes, sir. Thank you.
It either means that it's completely wrong
or that it's missing an important factor.
Damn it!
Hey, you.
Here.
-Hey, Young-yi.
-Yes?
Wipe my desk, too.
Yes, sir.
-Young-yi.
-Yes?
Clean mine as well.
-Okay.
-Me, too.
Yes, sir.
Are the documents still not done?
It's almost time for the meeting.
It's done.
Darn it. Young-yi, clean this up.
Okay.
Hey. Are the documents okay?
-Yes. Fortunately.
-Okay, good.
You should have been careful.
Young-yi, clean it up.
Yes, sir.
Stay. I'll get it.
What's wrong with us?
We are a soccer ball
that everybody is kicking around,
an abused Cinderella, a vegetable,
and a pushover.
Jeez.
Hey, Young-yi.
Face it head on.
I told you to be aggressive.
There's a saying in go, "Learn
to compromise when you can't change"
Immediately reacting
to a backflow is foolish.
So, If I remain in the current as
the opponent tries to cause a backflow,
it will just create a backflow
to the opponent himself.
What is he talking about?
-Hello?
-Ji-hyun Lee from Search and Brain.
I called to confirm tomorrow's interview.
That's right. It's tomorrow.
Yes, it's possible.
No. I will take a day off.
Yes.
-Yes?
-Sit down.
I heard you got deferred.
-Yes.
-You didn't get the reason either?
Yes.
I just came from the Finance Team.
Is this it?
-Right. Yes.
-Let's see.
You can't write out
the schedule like this.
Make a form that is applicable
to the approval format.
You need to calculate man/month, yourself.
Look, you don't know how much manpower
you need if you don't enter it.
You have to calculate it.
This is new. What kind of format is this?
I've never seen it before.
What kind of format is this?
Didn't you receive the training regarding
the One International standard format?
Revise it and re-send it.
The Finance Team keeps nagging.
I think that the  hahoe  masked witch
is getting on them.
-Go ahead.
-Thank you.
-A good try.
Even Geu-rae doesn't do it like that.
Sir. I'm going home now.
-Okay. Go ahead.
-All right.
Geu-rae, go home.
Yes, sir.
Geu-rae.
Hi, Young-yi.
-Are you going home?
-Yes.
We really worked hard today, too.
Yes.
-I'll see you tomorrow.
-Yes.
Hey, contractor!
Going home?
-Yes.
-Wow. Things got easy.
Going home on time?
Goodbye, sir.
This kid.
Hey.
If she gets married,
she'll be the next Ms. Sun.
If she doesn't, she'll end up like
Ms. Kim, right?
See you tomorrow.
I'll see you tomorrow.
You seem like you're ready
to accept anything that is thrown at you.
You're like a long-term prisoner
that's just been released.
It's like you're doing everything you can
to adjust to society.
A long-term prisoner
that's just been released.
What's wrong with that?
I'm showing you everything.
Why do you need to know about my past?
Sir, where are you?
Could you wait for me a bit?
I need to show you something.
Okay.
This way, sir.
Great view.
-It's very high, isn't it?
-It's okay.
-This is it.
-Really?
I'm home.
You're early.
Wash up and eat. I boiled some mackerel.
I didn't do the seasoning right.
So it's a bit fishy near the tail.
-It's always fishy.
-That's why today,
let's decide on who will have the tail
before we go in.
Lose the stereotype of thinking
that moms are able
to eat fishy food and all.
Let's do rock, paper, scissors.
He's our team's deputy manager.
Hello.
My goodness.
Your senior came all the way here?
-How about dinner?
-No, I'm fine.
I'll be leaving right away.
Geu-rae wanted to show me something.
What?
Maybe he's hiding a girlfriend?
Maybe not?
You little brat! What have you been doing?
What are you doing
that a rumor like that is being spread?
Wait, ma'am. I was just joking.
-Joke?
-Yes, just a joke.
-I know.
-Yes. Pardon?
I was joking, too.
A joke should at least be like this.
Mr. Deputy's joke was not funny.
The punchline was just plain.
Let's go in, sir.
Mom, please give me dinner.
I'm sorry.
Please excuse me.
I'm not sure how that was.
Well. This was really good.
Thank goodness.
Well, this...
It's so fishy. It's not edible.
Really?
I guess I'll have it then.
Well, this. I should...
I thought our guest might have
some other taste in food.
Well, why didn't you...
Then, please enjoy your stay.
Yes, thank you.
What about the tail?
Should I have eaten the tail?
Even the tail...
That's my mom's humor.
She thinks that she's really funny,
but she's not.
-Humor?
-Yes. Don't worry about it.
Yes, right. It was humor.
That's right.
I'm really curious about something.
Why is your house so empty?
We threw everything out.
The long-term prisoner doesn't need
things he used in prison.
I'm sorry. I was really out of line.
I said I was sorry, okay?
I threw everything out.
But there's still a lot left.
You have a go table?
-I used to play go.
-Go?
Yes.
My uncle taught me when I was a kid.
-I guess he thought I had a talent for it.
-I see.
Soon enough, I jumped into
the real life of go.
That means a life committed only to go.
you only make friends
at the go institute.
It's a life where you play go
by looking
at the manual for more
than ten hours a day.
That was my life in my teens.
I wanted to become a pro go player.
Of course, I failed.
That's why I'm in front of you now.
I threw away almost everything I had.
But there's one thing
I couldn't throw out.
This is the manual of all the plays
I have done in my go life.
-May I see it?
-Sure.
Every night I would look at it
to see why I won or lost.
I wrote down the reasons
for me to accept the game.
Then my teacher would make notes
for me here.
I did this since I was 11-years-old.
When I look at that,
I can remember everything that happened.
That is amazing. Just amazing.
Wait, what's this?
This is the record of my game
since I started working.
-Game?
-Yes.
I considered my daily work like a game.
It's a game diary.
Why does this have more pages
than the other one?
The game of go
is a game played by two people.
But there is a game in which one master
plays several games
at the same time with several opponents.
Usually,
the master always wins.
I found that in society,
there's a game like that.
But in society the game
is a bit different.
Those that are not masters have
to play with many opponents.
One game with you.
One game with Mr. Oh.
Another game with another team.
And also a game with my rival.
And in time,
I might have to play
with the company itself.
In go,
there's a rule called handicap.
When a master plays with non-masters,
they start with four to eight steps ahead.
But in society,
the masters play handicap go
against the non-masters,
or the newbies that is.
The master plays with four to eight...
No. They actually play
with uncountable steps ahead
of the opponent.
But what's scarier
is that the non-masters have the same
rules that must be followed.
The same rules?
I must do more.
Especially for a guy like me,
if I do just as much as others,
I will not be able to adjust.
Being a newbie means
that although you don't have experience,
you still must do more and strive.
How did you come to our company?
I have a sponsor.
He is the president of a company
called Sungwon Inc.
So you came in through the director.
That's why Mr. Oh...
Get out.
Get out, you bastard!
You have a good sponsor.
The director probably
doesn't even remember me.
I've never met him personally
after I got hired.
Your sponsor should have helped you
a little earlier, right?
He did.
After I passed the GED,
he hired me right away.
Why did you quit?
At that time...
I didn't hide my past as a go player.
At first, they were curious
and were friendly with me.
Then they started to doubt me.
After that,
the doubt became the truth.
They thought that I was not flexible
because I was a go player.
They thought I was too serious, too.
I stayed for a year
and then enlisted in the army.
Is that why you kept your past from us?
Because we would think of you as a loser?
You're not a loser.
I'm not from a good school.
It was difficult to get a job for me, too.
But once I was accepted
and started working,
it didn't seem like I already succeeded,
I just felt like I opened a new door.
I think that it's not
a matter of success or failure.
I think we live our lives
by opening new doors until we die.
Then what about success?
I think it might be
what you think
of that moment of your life.
As you work, there are some projects
that don't come through,
but you still feel like yourself
and you feel a sense of achievement.
Do you think that's a failure?
There are times that even I lose
in a game, I feel good about it.
Is that it?
I'm not sure, but don't you think it is?
Come tomorrow. Let's get along better.
Thank you.
You know, I have a Twitter account.
I didn't have anything to post,
but I just have the account.
Do you want to get one too?
On the bulletin today, they said not
to be online friends with your seniors.
Then I'll get going.
How about Face... Never mind.
Goodbye.
Don't look back. Go inside.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Did you not learn anything from our team?
I think it's not the time to learn,
but to use my skills.
I've already mastered the basics
in school, during my internship,
and during my new employee training.
If the basics that you are talking about
was that important, why didn't you
tell me that from the start?
I gave you lots of opportunities
to find your own faults.
Teaching me the basics
is just your excuse.
It just seems like you don't like me,
that's all.
Just face it head on.
Senior or not, just go head on.
Hello?
Baek-ki.
Aren't you calling me because
of the report?
Yes.
Which part is it?
It's just all wrong.
You didn't input the man/month, right?
Yes.
How should I do it?
It's 18 million won for four months,
so divide the resume
to middle cost laborers into four.
We usually calculate
4.5 million won per person.
Calculate it by laborers.
You left out
the piping floor plan too, right?
Piping floor plan?
We had it done before,
but it didn't work for us.
There is a revised file
that the labor company sent us.
It's in the quarterly contract.
Ask Da-in to find it for you.
Okay.
Then I should input that into
the timetable and the budget, right?
That's right. As I told you before,
prepare it to meet the format,
make sure it's within the file frame,
add the notes,
show the percentage of the change
and resubmit it.
For timetable, meet the format.
Baek-ki.
Yes?
I'll see you tomorrow.
Okay.
GEU-RAE JANG
DONG-SIK KIM
FOLLOW
REQUEST TO FOLLOW
I'm not sure what it shows,
but the world is full of people
that want to show things.
DONG-SIK KIM
Why do people want to show themselves?
In go, the bigger picture
influences the individual moves.
It's the world that the go board has
formed, within the confines of the grid,
If the go board is not
confined by its grid,
and life is full of opportunities,
there won't be winners or losers.
Really? I love it!
This world decides
on a part that's called "me."
Just once.
To be condoned,
to be understood, people show themselves.
Man, do I have to do it again?
Why is my stock price
always declining? Damn it.
I can no longer
work with you, like this.
What did you say?
See? Mr. Park is still useful
to the company.
Fucking hell.
Keep an eye on your subordinates!
-Hey!
-That guy. Isn't he Mr. Shin
-from Samjung Trading Company?
-What is he saying?
Let's see if he's a lazy pig
or a lost dog.
You don't know shit.
Let's have a real dinner.
-Baek-ki, I'm begging you, please.
-Pull out.
Geu-rae, you son of a bitch.
Subtitle translation by Joo-hee Kim