I know you have trust issues.
I've already forgiven Val.
But it's not just about Val.
It's about me, too.
When you told me
that you love me,
I was left speechless.
You've known
from the start, right?
That I don't belong
in this world.
Jaja, I'm still a ghost.
That doesn't matter to me.
No conditions.
No expectations.
I love you no matter what.
There's no other princess
in my life...
...but you.
But I'm still leaving.
Everyone I love
ends up leaving me.
Jaja, it's not your fault...
...for loving someone.
We'll always be in your heart.
You're in my heart forever.
Until the end.
Excuse me?
Could you not throw
those flowers this way?
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Treb!
[SQUEALS] Treb!
Mmm!
Is that really you, Treb?!
Have you been reincarnated?
- Mmm!
- Were you kicked out of heaven?
How can I touch and smell you?
- Miss, wait--
- [SNIFFING]
You're getting too touchy.
You have abs?!
[GASPING IN WONDER]
Wow! Wow!
- Your abs are so hard!
- Yeah, I know. I know!
My abs are hard, yes.
But what the hell are you doing?
You just suddenly jumped me.
Why are you acting like that?
You weren't like that.
- So rude.
- Oh, so I'm the rude one?
You're the one poking
my bread-like abs,
and I'm the rude one?
- You owe me 10 pesos.
- What? Hey, wait! What?
- Why?
Miss, when you're at a bakery,
if you poke the bread,
it's as good as sold.
You poked me four times.
That's 2.50 pesos a piece.
Your total is 10 pesos.
Don't worry,
I won't charge you for the hug.
Pay up.
[CELLPHONE RINGS]
Hello?
[WHIMSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay, okay.
I'm on my way.
Okay.
You're using a cellphone?
Okay, okay, okay.
[WHIMSICAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Okay, how about this
so we can call it quits?
Give me a smile.
One smile,
and we'll call it quits.
Oh, he wants a smile now, huh?
Just a smile.
Come on.
Smile.
Like this, see?
Smile. Smile!
[WHIMSICAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Ma, she won't give me a smile.
What should I do?
She said you're lucky
you're cute.
[WHIMSICAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Treb?
Amador?
He's not Treb?
Huh?!
Why does he look like Treb?!
Lord, are you messing with me?
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
"Scare Jaja to Death"
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[BERT] Let's go!
[EMMA] Oh! Thank you, Bert!
That's a bit heavy.
- Sorry.
- No worries. I got it.
Wow, you're such a gentleman.
Oh, and thank you for taking me
to a coffee date.
That was sweet.
Yeah. Sweet,
but it was good.
- Hm?
- The coffee was good.
Ahh.
We can use that idea
for our new business.
[EMMA CHUCKLES]
Actually, yeah.
But thanks for waiting
while I got a perm.
That wasn't for business, right?
You took so long, though.
I was able to do some shopping,
as well as get a haircut.
Oh!
How do I look?
Does it suit me?
B-Beautiful.
[CHEERY MUSIC PLAYING]
You look beautiful.
- Me? I...
- You look--
- Aah! Aah! Aah!
- Ahh! Huh?!
- Hey!
- What?
- What's--
- Aah! Aah! Aah!
Hey, hey! Hold on!
Calm yourself.
Calm down. Calm down.
- What is it? What happened?
- It's Jaja.
- Jaja?
- Jaja!
- Jaja?!
What happened?! Where is she?!
- Aah! Aah! Aah!
- [JAJA] We have lemon! And...
There you go!
- Drink up!
- No, no!
No, Miss Ja-- Woah!
- Dino, take the bottle.
- Mm!
Girl?!
- That's enough.
- You'll be together forever?
Why don't you kiss?
- That's enough, Miss Ja.
- Together until the end...
- She came here like that.
- Really?!
- Girly pop!
- Come on!
Dino, Spencer,
we'll take care of this.
Sorry about her.
Thank you so much for helping.
Bye, you two!
Hey, let's drink more later!
Girly pop?!
Girly pop!
Ahh...
- Woah, woah, woah!
- Hey!
Girl, so is there
something going on?
What?! What are you
talking about?!
What's going on?
Are you possessed, girl?
Possession!
- Treb possessed someone!
- What?
What are you
talking about, girl?
Here.
[GASPING]
That... Is that Wilberto?!
Mm-hmm!
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
Close your eyes for a bit.
Just feel the moment, okay?
This is it.
This is really it.
This is the day
you will be with the person
who will annoy you
the most forever.
The person you want
to hit the most...
but you just can't do it
because he's the person
that you love the most.
And even if you are
grumpy with him every day,
he will still keep
hugging you every day.
Because you...
You are the one he loves.
In sickness and in health...
Cross your heart,
and even if you die...
You and him will still
be together in heaven.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
- Okay, okay!
- [MUSIC STOPS]
- I've got it.
- Y-Yes, sir.
Fix the groom's makeup
a bit, please.
- It needs a bit of work.
- Copy, sir.
Lower this a bit.
Okay, guys.
- Perfect weather.
- Mm-hmm!
Perfect venue.
What a perfect couple.
Let's do it!
[YUJIE] The ex of all exes?
- Yes!
- No way.
- The one that got away?
- Yes!
- Best cutie ever after?!
- Why is he dressed like this?
- Exactly.
This is probably AI.
- Hey! That's not AI.
- Look.
He's real.
And bestie, earlier,
we met at the cemetery.
- Oh?
- And you know what I did?
I touched his abs.
- Mm!
- Get a hold of yourself!
Do you really need
to talk about his abs?
Mm-hmm. Fact-checking, okay?
I was just
fact-checking, bestie.
Just to make sure.
Also, do you have
a long-lost cousin?
That Macmac Amador?
- Mm-hmm.
- "Ama..."
Ah, there you have it.
- "Ama-like..."
- Yeah. "Ama-what?"
"Ama-think" he's
your resurrected ex.
[EMMA]
Hey, stop that, will you?
What resurrection
are you talking about?
Treb's okay.
He's in heaven now.
He can't go back.
It's a one-way ticket.
You never know.
Maybe he had his face changed.
Ooh! You have a point!
Your face isn't like that
back in college.
- That's not--
- No, it's true.
But that's not it.
If he had facial surgery,
why does he look
exactly like Treb?
And of all people, why Treb?
[EMMA] Yeah, that's so weird.
Oh, wait a second.
- Maybe he inherited his face?
- Huh?!
When, where, and how?!
Actually, I don't know how
that would even happen.
Do you have an idea?
[BERT] Forget it for now.
She's drunk.
Mm...
Brace yourself, Macmac Amador.
I'll find out who you are. Hmph!
- Have some.
- Thanks.
- At least she's calm now.
- You want some?
- Here.
- Why this part?
Okay, show me
a bit more sweetness.
Cheek to cheek for this shot.
Okay, feel the moment, guys!
[GIGGLES]
- Beautiful shot.
- Hey.
I think I want to feel
the moment as well... with you.
- You want to feel it?
- I do.
[SENSUAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[CLEARS THROAT]
- Oh, um...
- You have a husband.
He might come after me, ma'am.
He's not important.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Well, here's my contact.
Oh?
[GIGGLES]
That's my business number.
If you need a photographer
for any events
like weddings, or funerals...
We'll be there.
Just give me a call.
- Okay. I'll call you.
- Yes, ma'am.
Okay, another shot!
Okay. Three, two, one... smile!
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
[CHEERFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
This shot is beautiful.
Son, why don't you
get a girlfriend?
Someone who'll
take care of your heart.
That way, you won't
always be busy with work.
Yeah. Why don't you do that?
Dadoods, my heart is fine.
Besides, it's you two
who should take care.
I saw you two eating
those pork rinds earlier.
Hey, hey, hey, hey...
Don't worry about
those pork rinds.
Your fans sent all of those.
Of course, we'll eat them.
- We can't just throw them away.
- [CHUCKLES]
Just stick to the
pork rinds, Uncle.
Of course. Why would I
go after your girls, boy?
I don't like girls
that are too young.
And I don't understand
how they speak nowadays.
They say things like
IDK, LOL, LBM...
Sounds like they have
stomach problems.
[CHUCKLING] LBM...
Kids nowadays
are something else.
You know, son,
During my and
your mom's time...
Mm?
We didn't have
prenup photo shoots.
There was only one photo shoot,
and it was on
the wedding day itself.
Ooh, your dad's being nostalgic.
- You're messing with me again.
- [CHUCKLING]
Don't worry, Dadoods.
When I find
my future girlfriend,
I'm going to take lots
of pictures of us. I promise.
Oh, Macoy!
You keep saying that,
but we haven't seen you do it.
You're just always flirting
and charming girls,
holding back your feelings,
or breadcrumbing... Hmph!
Bread cru--
What's breadcrumbing, Uncle?
I know what it is!
Back in our day, we didn't
have those things. Too bad.
I would've taken my shot.
If a girl looked at me,
I'll make her mine.
So you annoyed her
until she said yes?
- Exactly.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Don't teach my son
stuff like that.
You're better off taking
this seriously, like I did.
Oh, come on, brother-in law.
You're so old school.
He shouldn't waste
his good looks.
Didn't you say
he looks like you?
Hey, hey, hey,
you listen to me.
I don't want to hear that
you got a girl pregnant, hm?
Oh, come on, Dadoods.
Don't you trust me?
I trust you. But him? Nah.
And that's because you keep
teaching him stuff like that.
Learn to take things seriously.
Dadoods, we're going to
get there someday, okay?
Oh, yeah... What are you
looking for in a woman?
Is she even human?
[CHUCKLING]
It's simple, Uncle, Dadoods.
Of course, I want someone
who's true to herself.
- [DOOR SLAMS]
- Hey, girly pop!
Hey.
- Hey!
- What the--?!
Someone with principles.
What now? Are you sure
about this? Let's just go home.
We'll come back tomorrow.
Let's go.
Someone brave.
I told you not to come with me
if you're not sure.
But you're drunk!
We can't just let you
come here alone.
You might do something
inappropriate here.
And of course,
someone with a fighting spirit.
Hey, Ja!
They might think we're thieves.
Now I got it!
He's looking for
Gabriela Silang.
- [THUMPING]
- Hey! Watch it!
- What are you doing?
- Here we go.
- It's open. Come here.
- We could go to jail for this.
Girls like that are gone.
They don't exist anymore.
You know, son,
if that's your ideal woman,
you should start looking now.
It'll be a long time
before you find her.
[EMMA] Where is she going?
[JAJA HUMMING]
- Woah, woah, woah!
- Come here!
[MACMAC] You can't find love.
It comes to you. Just like what
happened to you and Momshie.
Hey, hey, hey,
it was different for us.
Your mother and I were
destined for each other.
We first met
on a sunny day.
And then, she looked at me.
When I looked at her,
it started raining!
And then, it was like everything
slowed down around us.
And then we stared
at each other for a long time.
That's when the rain stopped.
Amazing! [CHUCKLING]
[CHUCKLES]
- Sounds like climate change.
- [CHUCKLING]
Go on, laugh at my story.
If that happens to you, I'm
going to laugh at you so hard.
- It was sunny, then rainy...
- Cut it out.
It was sunny...
Hey, girl.
Can't we just go back next time
when you're sober?
Shhh!
I just want to show you because
he really, really, really,
really, really, really, really,
really looks like him.
Shhh! Don't be so loud.
- I just need five minutes.
- Five minutes for what?!
- [HUMMING AWAY]
- Jaja!
Hey, let her do what she wants.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay. [GIGGLING]
[WHIMSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Woah...
I'll soon find out who you are.
Hmm...
Marcus Amador...
[WHIMSICAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey!
Someone broke in, Dadoods!
- It's Jaja.
- Jaja!
- [SQUEAKS]
- Hey! What's going on?!
Call the police, Dadoods!
It's a thief!
- What's going on?!
- Trying to escape, huh?
I'm not a thief!
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
She's not a thief!
[SQUEALS] Is that you?
Is that really you, Treb?!
You?!
You...
Wha-- Miss, are you obsessed
with me or something?
- Hm?
- This is stalking!
Be thankful that I'm used
to being chased by girls.
Excuse me? Yuck!
- I wasn't stalking you.
- Then why are you here?
Ah, we're sorry.
My bestie really just
wants to talk to you.
Behave.
Dadoods, call the chairman.
Tell them we caught a thief.
Hey! You're the thief!
You stole his face!
- Huh? What?
- What?
What is she talking about?
We're really sorry.
She's just...
Our friend's just
going through something.
Ah... That's why
she smells like that.
No, no, no.
It's not what you think.
It's tequila, yeah?
Oh, it's not that one.
It's tequila.
Miss, just get your friend home.
Go now before
I call the chairman.
Go on! Call the chairman.
I'll have this place haunted
by my ghost friends!
- Ugh!
- She really has a screw loose.
Hey, my third eye's open.
I can see dead people!
- [CLEARS THROAT]
- Well, in that case...
Why don't you use your
first and second eyes
to see that the gate's closed
and knock before entering?
It was unlocked.
What was I supposed to do?
You should've locked it.
Oh, uh, um...
Hold on a second.
Excuse me.
Uh, can you really
see dead people?
Mm-hmm! Yesh, shir!
Anyway... Good night!
Bye-bye!
Uh, we're really
sorry about this.
- I'm filing a complaint.
- Uh, wait. Wait...
Here, this is our card.
You can come any time.
You'll get a free coffee.
And feels.
Fine, fine. Get out of here.
- We're really sorry.
- Jaja!
What is wrong with you?!
So, that's that.
A brave and spirited girl.
But she's crazy, Uncle.
You're right.
- My gosh!
- My head's aching!
- That was so embarrassing!
- Good morning!
- Here's our menu.
- What was that, girl?
- I'll get a white mocha.
- Okay.
You know, I shouldn't have
agreed to go with you.
We almost got arrested
because of your delusions.
I'm really sorry.
Relax, girl. Calm down.
- Okay. I'm trying, okay?
- Just relax.
I hope you're done
with that Gen Z Treb.
Girlie pop, yes, I promise.
Especially now that I've seen
how bad his attitude is.
You know, he and Treb
only look alike.
But not a single drop of blood
is the same between them.
[SMACKS TABLE]
"She's not Celine.
She will never be Celine!"
[SMACKS TABLE]
"Celine is dead!
And she won't be coming back!"
Hey! We're not in Barcelona!
We're in the Philippines!
Stop joking at a time like this.
- Come on, guys.
- So, what now?
Have you closed
the chapter of Treb's lookalike?
I've shut it closed.
- Really closed?
- Love it.
Yes! Because
I'm so tired of this!
- Feel good morning!
- So tired, so tired...
- Welcome to Kafeels!
- Hi, good morning.
So tired of this...
This way, sir.
Hey, this place looks new.
Are we welcome here?
- Don't worry about it. Come on.
- This way, sir.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah...
- Okay, that's enough.
I'm tired.
- Hi.
- [GASPS]
[GASPS]
- I'll handle this.
- [YELPS]
[CLEARS THROAT] Uh...
Hello! Welcome to Kafeels!
- Hi!
- Good morning. Hi.
Uh, sir, we're really sorry
about what happened last night.
Ah, don't worry. Forget about
it.
Oh, we can't do that.
Do want a coffee?
A caramel macchiato?
What about an espresso?
Maybe a pasta?
No thanks. We came
here for another reason.
- Oh.
- She's the reason.
Oh, did you mean me?
- Hello, sir.
- Uh, not you.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- [QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
Uh, the girl hiding at the back.
Ah...
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Hello, sir.
- Uh...
Dear, is it true that
you can see ghosts?
Oh, sorry, but our séance
services are closed today.
Just come back on Thursday.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Maybe you could
make an exception for us?
Pretty girls like you
can do that, right?
- Oh!
- Uh...
Besides, we couldn't find
any other scientists.
- Huh?
- Hmm?
- Uh--
- Oh!
I'm not a scientist.
It's "séance."
You know, talking to ghosts.
- Mm-hmm, exactly.
- That's what I said. Scientist.
- No...
- That's different.
We're really sorry, sir.
Just come back on
Thursday for our promo.
That's when we do
séance services.
If you want, we can give you
a big, big, big, big discount!
Can't you really make
an exception this once?
Even just a short one?
Yes. We came here just for that.
- Sorry, sir.
- We're really sorry.
If you want,
we can give you free coffee.
But if not...
- just come back on Thursday.
- We're not coffee people.
Oh! What about tea?
Or pasta?
- We also serve food here.
- No. It's all right.
- It's fine. Thank you.
- We're sorry.
Just come back
another time, sir.
Come back on Thursday, sir.
[SHOUTING] Wait, don't go!
I'll help you.
- Really?!
- Yes. Please have a seat.
- She's doing it?
- Please have a seat.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, miss.
Just relax there, okay?
- I'm just going to get ready.
- Oh, okay, okay.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- All right.
- Girly pop.
- I'm happy they agreed to this.
You're really doing this?
It's to repay their kindness,
girly pop.
We should thank them
for not having me arrested.
We're lucky they agreed
to have a séance
even though it's not Thursday.
Just wait for a bit, sir, okay?
They're just preparing.
- Yes, all right.
- Thank you again.
What was that?
- I know, right?
- [CHUCKLES]
I was creeped out.
But wait, I'll just go pee.
I see the restroom over there.
- Sure, sure.
- I really need to go.
My bladder's about to explode.
[CHUCKLES]
[TENSE MUSIC STING]
[SMOOCHES]
Oh, hello, sir.
Um... [CLICKS MOUTH]
Are you here for
a séance as well?
Oh, yes. I'm hoping
to talk to my wife.
- What about you?
- Oh...
So, we both lost our spouses.
[WOMAN SIGHS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Next time, okay?
My pictures are great
when you take them.
- Thank you, thank you.
- You inspire me.
Can we have another
photo session?
- I have another client soon.
- I'll just change outfits.
- She can go ahead.
- You should go with her.
-No.
-I have a client waiting for me.
We can eat first.
No, no, no.
Your ride is here.
Don't worry,
I booked this myself.
My next client is waiting.
- Are you sure?
- Mm-hmm.
- I can stay longer.
- [SULTRY MUSIC PLAYING]
- Let's just reschedule.
- I thought we had something.
Miss, there's nothing
between us, okay?
You thought wrong.
You can go now.
- Oh, come on.
- Bye.
Mister, thank you.
I'm telling the truth, okay?
- You have to believe me.
- Dadoods.
It's not my fault, okay?
- It just disappeared.
- Macoy!
- What happened?
- Well, son...
- Your mother's ring...
- ...was stolen!
- What?!
- Yeah!
[SIGHS]
The person who took it
was at Kafeels?
I don't really remember.
All I can remember is
that Badong and I
went to Kafeels
so I could talk to Yesha.
- But that didn't happen.
- I went to the restroom.
After using the restroom,
I saw him just staring ahead,
as if he had seen a ghost.
So, I told the owner
to call an ambulance.
But before it arrived,
he regained consciousness.
When I woke up,
the wedding ring was gone.
This is what I was afraid of.
This is why I can't leave
you two alone.
My sister told me
to look after you two.
- What does the ring look like?
- It's a small circle.
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
No. It's a simple ring.
Uh, it was inside a green pouch.
And it's made of real gold.
I worked hard for
a long time to get it.
And then, engraved on it
are the words "Y2K Forever."
[BADONG]
Yeah, but it's the wrong size.
It's tight. You need soap
to put the ring on.
Right. That's why my wife
couldn't take it off.
Boss, we can't lose
my mother's ring.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Where is this Kafeels?
Who's the owner?
- [EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [HUMMING]
Jonathan... Jonathan...
[HUMMING]
Girly pop, I know you.
You've done a lot more
embarrassing stuff
than just trespassing.
So, for sure,
there's something more
behind why you decided to
help that jerk's father, right?
I know he's not Treb, bestie.
Oh! In that case, why?
Because he looks
so much like him.
Oh, come on, girly pop.
So, what?
He triggered
my feelings for Treb.
You know, even though
I'm very annoyed with him,
I still want to see him.
Because he reminds me
of Wilberto.
You just want to see him?
No feelings?
Hmm? No way. I have
no feelings for him, bestie.
- Okay. You said so.
- [WOMAN] Um...
Excuse me. Hello.
I'm still here.
- Oh, sorry.
- Sorry, sorry.
- Just go, bestie.
- I'm sorry, okay?
Hmm.
Sorry about that. Uh...
Jonathan...
What's his last name?
- It's Cruz.
- Oh.
- [QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
- Oh, wow.
All she says is "Cruz."
[CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY]
Jonathan... Cruz?
Can't you give anything
more specific, miss,
so we can find him faster?
Santos.
His middle name is Santos.
Jonathan Santos Cruz...
Unique name.
Okay, miss.
Whatever I do,
you need to do it, too.
This will make it easier
for us to contact Jonathan.
Okay.
Copy what I'm doing.
And close your eyes, too.
Okay. So grumpy.
Jonathan Santos Cruz,
can you hear us?
- [WIND BLOWING]
- [EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh!
Miss, I can feel him.
Jonathan... There!
I can feel his presence.
He's this way.
[GASPS]
It feels like
he's behind me, miss!
There.
I think I can feel him
coming closer.
I can even smell him.
- [SNIFFING]
- [EERIE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Why does he smell so familiar?
[CONTINUES SNIFFING]
[SHRIEKS]
What are you doing here?
There really is something
wrong with you, huh?
Miss, don't get swindled
by this woman, okay?
She's a scammer!
- Hey! Wait...
- [CHAIR SCRAPING]
Who are you calling a scammer?
And swindling customers?
Sir, we're not scammers!
We're not tricking customers.
-We're running a legit business!
-I'm sorry, ma'am, sir.
I'm warning you.
- Miss, wait here.
- Miss, I suggest you leave.
- Show us proof!
- Exactly!
If you want, we'll even
show you our business permit!
- What's going on here?
- Girl...
They want to close down Kafeels.
What?!
[WHISPERING]
Sir, just take them away.
- No! Link arms!
- Link your arms!
- Give me your arms, girl.
- No, not like that!
- Hey, do it right!
- Get that person first.
- We stand united!
- Yeah, that one.
Ma'am, we're sorry.
Someone filed a complaint,
saying that you're
scamming your customers.
That's why the chairman
wants us to investigate.
The audacity...
Who filed the complaint?
We're not committing any crimes.
Hey. You were the one who
filed the complaint. Am I right?
Because you tricked my father.
Where's the ring?
What ring are you
talking about?
You're just pointing
fingers at us.
Dadoods was last here when
the ring disappeared, okay?
And you accuse us
of stealing it immediately?
- It could've been a customer!
- Yeah, right.
If I were you, hmm?
And you better listen.
Just give back my mother's ring.
Come on, give it back.
- The nerve of this guy.
- How dare he accuse us!
- Come on, give me the ring.
- [STAFF MURMURING]
Whatever happens,
we're innocent.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
Girl!
This is so frustrating!
[SNIFFLES]
Hmph! [SMACKS TRUCK]
Why is this happening?
Calm down, Ja.
Calm down. Calm down.
He isn't Treb. He isn't Treb.
He isn't Treb. He isn't Treb!
[SOBBING]
Is this my karma because
I entered their house?!
Are you mad because of that?!
I'm sorry, okay?!
I'm sorry!
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOBBING]
Look at this girl.
- I'm sorry, okay?! I'm sorry!
- She really has a screw loose.
She's really making a scene
in the middle of the street.
Well? [CHUCKLES]
- [SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
- [RAIN POURING]
You can't find love.
It comes to you.
Just like what happened
to you and Mom.
It was different for us.
At first, it was hot that day.
And then, she looked at me.
- [SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [RAIN POURING]
When I looked at her,
it started raining!
- [SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [RAIN POURING]
And then, it was like everything
slowed down around us.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
["IKAW LANG, SINTA"
BY MIGS AND DIXIE MARIE PLAYING]
And then, we stared at
each other for a long time.
["IKAW LANG, SINTA" CONTINUES]
I found the scammer.
Really?
Hey, hey, hey.
- Got you!
- [WOMAN WHIMPERS]
This is the ring.
- Where?
- Here.
- Hey, hey, hey!
- Oh my!
[WOMAN SCREAMS]
Why'd you put it on?
Hey, calm down!
I knew this would happen.
Two, one...
[GRUNTING]
["IKAW LANG, SINTA" CONTINUES]