You don't have to be afraid
to hope anymore.
He's given it to you, right?
Give him your feelings, too.
Go all out.
Emma's right.
You're the one I love,
not Treb.
It's you, Macmac.
- Who is he?
- The first ghost I helped.
We were always together,
so I fell for him.
I thought you were kin.
I was a rebound.
You see your ex in me.
- That's not true.
- How can I believe you
when you kept this detail
from me?
I guess we have to
slow things down.
We're just slowing down, okay?
We're not breaking up.
What happened to you?!
Get some sleep!
What if Macmac
decides to leave me?
Just give him space.
Why'd you let her
flirt with you?
No need to get jealous.
No need to get jealous
of Treb, too.
What do I have against a ghost,
who's probably an angel, too?
I'm sorry for not
telling you sooner.
This is what I was afraid of,
you doubting
my feelings for you, too.
Whenever I look in the mirror,
But when I see you,
I don't see Treb.
I see the man I love.
- [SOBBING]
- [SHUSHES]
I'm so scared right now, girl.
[GLUM MUSIC PLAYING]
I feel like it's going
to happen again.
[SOBBING]
I feel like he's going
to leave me, too.
[SOBBING]
And the catch is,
he has a point and I get it.
[SOBBING, SNIFFLING]
Girl...
- Stop this, okay?
- [SNIFFLES]
You always blame yourself
when people leave you.
What if...
What if he's right, bestie?
What if I agreed
to be Macmac's girlfriend
because he does look like Treb?
- Are you still confused?
- [JAJA SNIFFLES]
I'm second-guessing
everything now, bestie.
- [JAJA SNIFFLES, SOBS]
- [SIGHS]
[EMMA] Just remember
your guiding light.
["HALINA" BY CHRSTN PLAYING]
[EMMA] You've gone
through a lot, bestie.
But I know...
how true you are
to your feelings.
Just listen to your heart, okay?
It knows who you really love.
["HALINA" BY CHRSTN CONTINUES]
[SCREAMS]
[WATER SPLASHES]
[EMMA] Come on, bestie.
[JAJA] It's not my fault
I have feelings for a ghost.
[MAGICAL WHIRRING]
["HALINA" BY CHRSTN CONTINUES]
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
[EMMA]
They may look alike, but...
Macmac is his own man.
["HALINA" BY CHRSTN CONTINUES]
Did you get your answer?
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[EMMA] Come here.
[SOBS]
["HALINA" BY CHRSTN CONTINUES]
[SNIFFLES]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
"Don't Awaken the Dead"
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[KIKO CLEARS THROAT]
Son, this is empty.
Oh.
Dad, sorry.
[PILL BOTTLE RATTLING]
Here it is.
[MACMAC EXHALES SHARPLY]
- Uh...
- [WATER POURS]
Son, is there a problem?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MACMAC] It's Jaja.
She's just like me.
We're total fools for forever.
Hey, what's wrong with that?
You see...
there's this guy
she loved first.
And until now...
she still loves him in heaven,
just like you loving Mom.
[CLICKS TONGUE, SIGHS]
Kiko...
- What?
- Macmac...
Thanks to you two.
I'm ready to leave.
Hey, wait a minute.
We're not asking you to leave.
But if that's what you want,
it's fine by us.
I understand it now.
I always told you that
I have to look after you
because it was my sister's
last request before she passed.
- I loved her so much...
- [GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
and I didn't want
to fail her final wish.
But the truth is...
the real reason
I didn't want to leave...
is because I was scared
to be alone.
I couldn't accept
that my sister was gone.
But I can't keep living in fear.
I have to accept that
she's no longer here.
But accepting it doesn't mean
I don't love her anymore.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Badong...
I'm sure Yesha knows that
and she also knows that
you love her so much.
She asked me to make sure
you two are perfectly okay.
And that's what
I'm seeing right now.
I'm honestly the one who's not.
I'm sure that was exactly
what Jaja's ex wanted.
He wanted to make sure those
left behind would be alright.
So, what if you look
like her ex?
If you love her,
that's all that matters.
[UPLIFTING MUSIC PLAYING]
Don't let her go.
Anyway, Uncle,
feel free to visit anytime.
- Of course, I will.
- Oh, you...
If you want,
I'll visit every day.
- Take care, Uncle.
- Badong...
I'll walk you out now
before you change your mind.
[COMICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
- Are you two sure?
- Yup, we're perfectly okay.
- You might miss me.
- No, just a bit.
["SUGAL" BY RYAN CHONG PLAYING]
[KIKO] What do you look for
in a woman?
[MACMAC] I want someone
who's true to herself.
- [KIKO] Mm-hmm.
- [MACMAC] Has principles.
You'll shut down our cafe
- and ask me if I'm okay?
- I want to know if you're okay
since we'll meet again
at the community hall.
[MACMAC] Someone who's tough
and won't back down.
Hey, you thief!
You've already been caught,
but you still won't admit it!
[MACMAC] She's really tough.
She was even angrier
at the scammer than me.
The ring's really for her.
[KIKO] You went to the cafe
to find justice,
but instead, you found love.
["SUGAL" BY RYAN CHONG
CONTINUES]
[KIKO] Did it hit hard?
[MACMAC] For real, Dad.
I've never felt this way before.
["SUGAL" BY RYAN CHONG
CONTINUES]
A promise ring.
This is to remind you
not to worry...
because I'm here to stay.
I love Jaja.
I may look like you...
but I'll fight for her.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Your change, ma'am.
- It's short by 50 pesos.
- Oh.
We'll call out for you
once it's ready.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Thank you.
Ah, miss? Excuse me.
One milk coffee nut latte
for Miss Princess.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy!
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
Can you stay over there?
- I'll just talk to my baby.
- Okay, bye.
Thank you.
Bert?
Hey.
You okay?
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
How's Ja?
[SIGHS DEEPLY] Let's trust
that she'll get through it.
She's had love woes before.
She can be a love guru
if she wants to. [CHUCKLES]
Of course, I'm still
on Grandpa's side.
But I guess you're right.
I'm just making up
for the times I pushed her away
when she needed me the most.
Bert...
She never took that against you.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
Well, I guess Grandpa
would be proud
if I just support Jaja
with who she chooses.
- Hmm!
- [SWEET MUSIC PLAYING]
That's what I like
about you!
I'd die for you if you want to.
- Hey, not so soon.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Oh, why?
- I haven't opened my third eye.
I wouldn't be able to see you.
- Hmm! Stop it!
- [CHUCKLES]
Come here, cutie.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
You always mess with me.
- What's going on?
- [GASPS]
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
Uh... Hi!
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
Hi, guys. Um...
[COMICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
- Mm-hmm?
- What's going on?
Well, um...
- Hmm?
- Say it.
- What is it?
- Just tell us.
Come on.
- Alright, I'll say it.
- Mm-hmm.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Okay.
This is it.
- Don't be shocked, okay?
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay.
- And don't pass out.
Yujie, I know you so well.
I know you'd pass out.
- But control yourself, okay?
- Okay.
- Are you ready?
- Ready?
- Don't overreact, okay?
- Okay.
[COMICAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
We're a couple now!
And clean the bathroom,
will you?
Then, we'll clean up that area
afterwards.
Is that it? Is no one going
to scream or be shocked?
What?! You're a couple now?!
Okay, that's good.
- Give me a kiss.
- You're also a couple now?
You're all couples,
and I'm alone?
Alright. Go clean up.
Everyone, back to work.
- How about you?
- Let's go back to work.
At least, we're happy.
[LAUGHS]
- I don't care.
- You do, though.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
- Uh... [CLEARS THROAT]
- [QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
Uh... Jaja?
Ja...
Ah! Oh...
- Yujie.
- [IN SWEET VOICE] What?
Listen.
If you mistake me for Jaja
one more time,
I'll really make you mine.
I won't do it again.
I'll just go to the washroom.
[IN NORMAL VOICE] To clean.
Oh, okay, okay.
- I'll just clean up.
- Yeah, you need that.
Bert, Emma...
Where's Jaja?
Where's Ja?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
It's all clear to me now, Treb.
I love you.
Yeah. There are moments
when I think about you.
I'll never forget you.
Jaja.
Treb?
It's me.
Macmac?
I-I went to Kafeels.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
They said I'd find you here.
But I guess I'm too late.
You've already
made up your mind.
What?
I-it's fine.
[CLEARS THROAT] It's fine.
Uh...
I know we look alike.
So... bro?
Wilberto, if you can hear me,
I'm sorry that I'm the one here.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Do you remember
what I promised you?
I said I won't give up on you.
I'm here to stay.
However long I'd have to wait,
even if it takes years,
I'm going to wait...
until I replace Wilberto
in your heart.
[CHUCKLES]
You dummy.
- [LAUGHS]
- Jaja...
I'm trying to be serious
over here.
I just came here to say goodbye.
- What?
- Mm-hmm.
I can't change my past.
And most certainly,
I can't change your face.
Well, sure.
I tried to pretend
that you're him.
You may have the same face,
but I fell in love with Macmac.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CHUCKLES]
I even had this customized.
It's my surprise for you.
[CHUCKLES] Wow.
Turn around. I'll put it on you.
Don't take this off, okay?
I won't take it off
even while sleeping.
There we go.
Alright.
Alright then.
Let's see.
[JAJA] There.
It's a match, see?
With this, I promise
to never leave your side.
And if you take it off,
we're going fight every day.
- You promise?
- I promise.
And I promise to never
leave your side, too.
Aw...
You're so full of surprises.
You always surprise me, too.
You have your lights show,
and I have this.
Hmm...
Maybe that's why we're a match.
[SIGHS IN CONTENTMENT]
When I look at your face,
I see Macmac.
The man I love
with all my heart.
["IKAW LANG, SINTA"
BY MIGS, DIXIE MARIE PLAYING]
["IKAW LANG, SINTA" CONTINUES]
[BOTH GIGGLE]
So?
[JAJA GUSHES]
["IKAW LANG, SINTA" CONTINUES]
Bestie, are you sure about this?
You're not going
to miss them?
Keep in touch, okay?
Emma's still here to help you.
I got you, guys. [CHUCKLES]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
This is it, girlypop.
Mother dear said
just follow the steps
and then,
you'll be ghost-free in no time.
- Let's do this.
But, girl,
is this your final answer?
I only had my third eye
opened to see Val.
But I found someone else.
I found Treb.
And I guess I hesitated
to have it closed because...
I was hoping
to see him again.
But you found me instead.
Okay, alright!
Exactly!
I found the love of my life!
So...
It's time to move on.
Time to start a new chapter,
right?
- Yes.
- We'll miss you.
I'll miss you guys too.
Thanks for all the help!
Goodbye.
That's the best part.
I can still feel them
even if I can't see them.
Mm-hmm.
If you guys need anything,
drop by every Séance Thursday.
Your loved ones
don't have to pay a dime.
Okay?
Okay.
Ready?
- Mm-hmm.
- [EXHALES] Okay.
Everybody, follow my lead.
[EMMA, JAJA HUMMING LOUDLY]
[ALL HUMMING LOUDLY]
[LOUD HUMMING CONTINUES]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[EMMA CHANTING MELODICALLY]
From now on...
[LOUD HUMMING CONTINUES]
I am closing your third eye!
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LOUD HUMMING CONTINUES]
You will never spirits again!
[THUNDER CLAPS]
Oh my god!
Jaja?
- Aah!
- [SCREAMS]
- Oh...
- Girl, it's me.
- Oh, I thought...
- It's me!
Just kidding!
You look great, girl!
- That's Yujie!
- Right?
- You look great!
- How do you feel?
Do you still see them?
They're gone!
- Aw...
- No more ghosts!
- No more ghosting...
- Forever!
- No more ghosts!
- Yay!
Blow the candles.
- Congrats!
- Mm!
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
That's it? Just a hug?
I think you guys should kiss.
- Oh, really?
- Ah!
- Kiss!
- [CHANTING] Kiss! Kiss!
- What do you say?
- Kiss.
- Go on.
Alright, we'll kiss for you.
Only if you guys kiss too!
- Yes! [GUSHES]
- [CHEERS, CLAPS]
Really?
Give us a kiss!
[CHANTING]
- [EMMA] Us? Really?
- Yeah!
- Give us a kiss!
- Alright, we can do that!
As long these two kiss too.
- [GUSHES, EXCLAIMS]
- You two first.
- Go on.
- Game!
- Game?
- [DINO] Just this once.
Then it's your turn.
- Yeah!
- You go after us!
[CHANTING] Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
Let's count down!
- Three! Two! One!
- Go!
- Kiss!
[GUSHING, SHOUTING]
- Oh!
- [SHOUTING, CLAMORING]
- [YUJIE] They're done.
- Our turn!
Let's count down again!
- Let's start!
- Okay!
- Three! Two! One!
[GUSHING, SHOUTING]
- [YUJIE EXCLAIMS]
- [LAUGHS]
[CLAMORING]
- Your turn!
- No!
- You have to!
- Let's count down!
- Three!
- [MUFFLED EXCLAIM]
- Wait, pipe it down.
- Yeah--
[SHOUTS]
Wait a minute!
Your turn!
- It should be lit.
- Okay.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Okay, game.
- No countdown?
- [CHUCKLES]
- Okay.
- One, two, three, go!
- Three! Two! One!
- Oh!
- [EXCLAIMS]
["IKAW LANG, SINTA"
BY MIGS, DIXIE MARIE PLAYING]
["IKAW LANG, SINTA" CONTINUES]
- Director?
- [DIRECTOR] Hmm?
Can I laugh this off first?
- Don't laugh! [CHUCKLES]
- [LAUGH TRACK]
[LAUGH TRACK]
- Aah!
- [SLAP]
- [LAUGH TRACK]
- What was that?!
[LAUGHS] Sorry.
But you... [STAMMERS, LAUGHS]
- Go on.
- Hmph!
[SHOE THUDS]
That's another case.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [LAUGH TRACK]
- [GIGGLES]
Ja?
- [LAUGHS]
- Yes? Why?
- Ouch!
- [FYANG GIGGLES]
- [DIRECTOR] Cut!
- My nose! [GIGGLES]
[LAUGHS]
Uh, excuse me.
We need to roll.
[LAUGHS]
[CREW] Vivoree will look at you,
then she will-- [STAMMERS]
- [LAUGHS]
- Huh?
[CREW] Wait a minute.
[OBJECTS CLATTER]
- [CAT MEOWS]
- [CHUCKLES]
- We can take you on!
- Yeah!
- Please, don't!
- [LAUGH TRACK]
Oh, shoot. I need to pee.
Be right back.
- Ja!
- What?!
- [LAUGH TRACK]
- Why?
Okay, fine. Just let me know.
- Where you going?
- You go there.
- They saw you!
- [WHIMPERS]
- Are you a contractor?!
- Hey!
- Oh...
- Oh, sorry.
- [LAUGH TRACK]
[CREW] Oh, hey!
- [CHUCKLES]
- [SHOUTS]
We should've gone
straight to the hospital.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING SOUND]
- [LAUGHS]
- [FYANG] I forgot my line.
You forgot your line!
- Wilberto's still looking.
- Oh, right. Sorry.
Can I join in?
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]