You have to work for it.
That's love for you.
Guys, I won't leave
until I talk to Jaja.
It's closing time!
[SNORES]
- Wait!
- No!
I told you I won't give up.
Pani?
What's "pani?"
- It's--
- Just forget it.
So that's why.
She was ghosted by her ex.
I know.
- [LOUD CRASH]
- Ah! Treb?!
- "I'm here for you."
- That's not Treb.
Macmac is his own man.
They're very different.
Same face, but different hearts.
I'm not messing around!
My heart's been broken
many times!
I saw you posts with Val.
He took you for granted.
But me, I won't leave you.
I've heard that many times.
I'm different from them.
- You're proposing already?
- It's a promise ring.
Just wear it when you're ready.
Treb! Please manifest anything!
Should I give him a chance?
Ah!
- What happened?
- There's a cockroach!
- Right there!
- If you're messing with me,
- just return the ring.
- Then cut my finger off.
Gotcha! Are we together now?
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay...
Okay! W--
Wow.
That's your OOTD?
What's wrong with it?
Girl, you have to dress up!
It's your first time
to go out with your boyfriend
and that's what you're wearing?
Girl, I put effort on my outfit
the last time when we went out.
And then?
It got wrinkled
by all the rides we took.
This is fine.
So you really won't
put effort this time?
No.
[COMICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
You aren't sick, are you?
Spirit who possessed my bestie,
leave her body now!
Leave!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
What are you doing?!
Girl, this isn't like you!
I've known you since diapers,
so I can tell when
you're holding back.
I'm not.
Girl?
I said, I'm not.
Girlypop...
Okay.
You don't have to be afraid
of getting your hopes up.
He already gave you his heart.
So, reciprocate his feelings.
Go all-out.
Love with all your heart.
It's for real this time.
Don't hold back anymore, okay?
[SQUEALING]
OMG! That's my girlypop!
[MACMAC] Good morning!
Hello.
He was waiting inside,
so I let him in.
Ah...
Thank you, Bert.
- So...
- Hi.
Does your boyfriend look good?
[CHUCKLES]
Whatever.
You look good.
Bert, you can't
drive today, right?
Want to ride with us?
[MACMAC CLEARING THROAT]
Nah... Nah.
Our destination...
Yeah, our destination
is out of the way.
- So...
- Hmm.
- It's not ideal.
- Yes.
So you are a couple.
- Not yet.
But don't you worry.
I know Bert is doing his best
in courting me, right?
- Right.
- And I plan to say yes to him
on the day you celebrate
your monthsary so we'll have...
- Bestie anniversary!
[EXCLAIMS IN GLEE]
- Yes! Alright!
- These two...
You really are a pair
of weirdos, huh?
The guy who fell for a weirdo
is the weirder one.
Yeah, we're weird too.
But we have to go.
- Bye, guys!
- Bye!
- Bye, love birds! Enjoy!
- Take care!
Take your time.
[EMMA] Thank you.
- Let's go.
- Wait. Listen to this first.
- What's that?
- Here.
Give it a listen.
And then...
Choose a song.
Pick a theme song for us.
Ew! Cringe!
You know what?
The next time we go
to the cafe,
I'll treat you with
10 cups of coffee
to get rid of your hangover.
Well...
I'm just drunk in your love.
Boom! Bars!
- Ew! You're so corny!
- Come on! Let's go!
Ew!
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
"HEARTBREAK IN MANILA"
- Careful.
- What are you cooking?
We traveled so far and--
- Ow! My eyes!
- Relax! Don't get mad now.
What do I tell
our grandchildren?
How we fought
on our first date?
- No, thanks. Wait.
- Grandchildren?
- Getting ahead of yourself?
- Take a big step.
Well, I like getting ahead.
Careful. Keep your eyes closed.
Okay.
Okay, wait.
Watch your head.
- Oops.
- Hey.
- Careful.
- Tell that to yourself.
- Slowly now.
- What is this?
- I'm getting impatient.
- I'll count from three, okay?
Then open your eyes.
Three, two, one...
Go.
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
Can't afford movie tickets?
I can afford them!
I just wanted to do this.
- Wow.
- I can't do this in the cinema.
- Mm.
- Hey.
I'm not a pillow.
Pillow? Your bones are digging
into my skin.
Oh, is that so? No.
Stay there.
- Why?
- No return, no exchange.
[SNIFFS]
Okay. No return, no exchange.
Geez, you even prepared flowers.
Of course.
Hey, wait.
Let's take a picture.
Selfie!
Smile!
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
Your phone's too bright.
Can I see?
- Here.
- I look ugly there.
- But I look good in there!
- Another one.
- No!
- I'm the photographer here.
Three, two, one...
[BRIGHT MUSIC CONTINUES]
You're so annoying!
Want to watch a movie?
- Fine.
- Okay.
- Hurry up.
- Tell me if you feel cold.
- I've got blankets here.
- I do feel cold.
- Here. I came prepared.
- Wow, what a boy scout.
Okay!
It is cold!
- Oh my god.
- You feel cold?
Yeah. Good thing
I wore deodorant.
Deodorant?
Are you saying I stink?
No, it's just...
You like sniffing me out, right?
That's why I put on deodorant.
I heard your urge
to sniff someone
can turn into an addiction.
Pfft! Where did you hear that?
- I mean... [SNIFFS]
- Ew!
- [SNIFFS]
I'm just smelling you.
Smell me too.
- No, you stink.
- Come on!
- No, no. I don't want to.
- Do it.
Go on.
See?
- Smells good, right?
- Your armpits stink.
No. If you hate it,
I'll smell yours.
Ew!
[MACMAC SNICKERS]
Hey!
- Stop it.
- Alright. Let's just watch.
I also brought food
if you get hungry.
- Want this one?
- [EXHALES LOUDLY]
Give me some.
I'll dig in first.
You offered it to me.
I should go first.
What's that movie called?
[MACMAC] It's good.
See? I told you so.
- Mm!
- Mm-hmm!
[SPUTTERS]
- [COUGHING]
- Hey! You okay?
Stop eating like
you're dying of hunger!
Hey! Hey!
- [JAJA GRUNTING]
- [MACMAC SPUTTERING]
- Spit it out!
- [COUGHS]
- Hey! Come here. Drink water.
- [SPITS, COUGHS]
It's because you eat like a pig.
I know. [CLEARS THROAT] I know!
Have some water.
I'll call an ambulance.
Are you okay now?
Are you really?
Are you okay?
You sure? Hm?
We should've gone straight
to the hospital.
You might need to see a doctor.
What if you choke on something?
Well? Want me to call a doctor?
- [MACMAC CHUCKLES]
- What's funny?
Are you worried?
Of course!
Because... you love me?
Wow.
You could die...
and leave me.
Come here.
[MACMAC GRUNTS, COUGHS]
Just kidding! Just kidding.
You know...
Bad people
are hard to get rid of.
Huh?
This is not the time
to be making jokes!
You were about to cry.
No, I wasn't!
- Huh?
- I was trying to be cute.
Don't worry, I'm here.
Alive and kicking.
But I'm sleepy.
- I'm going to sleep.
- Go ahead.
Hey.
["HALINA" BY CHRSTN PLAYING]
["HALINA" CONTINUES]
[JAJA] Emma's right.
I love you, Macmac, not Treb.
["HALINA" CONTINUES]
[MACMAC] To make your
morning even better, lovebirds.
- Thanks, boss.
- That's sweeter than you both.
[JAJA] Good morning!
- Good morning!
- Macmac!
Good morning, Jaja.
You didn't tell me
you were coming.
- You should be resting.
- Relax. I'm fine.
I brought us breakfast.
- Starting early, huh?
- Hi, Miss Jaja.
You two are inseparable.
- Be careful, you two!
- I'll take that.
- It's fine.
- Let me.
- I got this.
- Let me take care of you.
What is this?
A chessboard?
A Ouija board!
Ouija board?
A lot of people
signed up for Seance Thursday.
Aren't you tired?
- From what?
- From doing all these seances.
At first, yeah.
Mm, but either way,
I still see them everywhere.
Even in the bathroom!
Good morning, Aiden!
I hope your girlfriend
comes next Seance Thursday.
Alright. Invite her, Ja.
- Thanks. Take care!
- Wait a minute.
- Even in the bathroom?
- Mm-hmm.
They could be perverts!
Aiden! Tell me where he is!
Where is he?
- [GIGGLING]
- I'm just making you laugh.
Your punches will go
right through them.
Besides, the spirits
I help are nice.
They only have
unfinished business
preventing them
from crossing over.
All they want is
to be with their families
and loved ones again.
Tsk.
You know, I'm happy
you help a lot of people.
But the question here is...
[CLEARS THROAT]
Hmm?
Who is making you happy?
[MOUTH CLICKS] Hmm...
- You!
- Yes! Correct! [CLAPS]
Excellent!
Heard that, Aidan?
Correct.
Right answer. [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
You're so silly!
- Should I stop?
- No!
Alright, come here.
Come here.
You won't feel tired
in my arms, Jaja.
Mm, I'm not tired of ghosts.
Because they have so much love
for the people they love.
It's quite amazing.
That love never goes away.
Even when the heart
stops beating,
love remains.
- Do you agree?
- Mm-hmm.
Because that's how
my dad is to my mom.
And hopefully...
- Hopefully...
- Hmm?
Us too.
- Mm...
- [MACMAC CHUCKLES]
[JAJA GIGGLES]
- [JAJA GUSHES]
- Good morning!
- Oh!
- Way to ruin it-- Good morning.
- Oh...
I didn't know we'd be
welcomed by so much sweetness.
- [YUJIE] Yes! Oh! Oh! Oh!
- Right.
Wow! Wow! Wow! Wow! Wow!
- Is that a dog?
- One, two, three! Wow!
I'm the only one
not doing the HH.
"HH"?
What's HH?
Wait here.
Well, Yujie.
HH.
- Hmm.
- Just close your eyes, okay?
Aww.
[MACMAC] Give me your hands.
I'll guide you.
Close your eyes, okay?
Trust me.
Close your eyes.
How long have you had
this monkey here?
[LAUGHTER]
It hasn't been long.
Holding Halaman (plant), HH.
- What?
- Mm.
- I'm right.
[JAJA] Plant.
- I've never seen it before.
- Do you think it's funny?
[MIMICS MONKEY SOUNDS]
[CHUCKLES]
Are you happy now?
- Oh.
- It suits you.
- [MIMICS MONKEY SOUNDS]
- [LAUGHTER]
- [YUJIE] Are you satisfied now?
- Not bad.
Hold a higher branch.
- [MIMICS MONKEY SOUNDS]
- There you go.
Ja, where's the sales report
for yesterday?
Oh, right! I'll email it to you.
See? So forgetful!
- [JAJA] I'll send it.
- Okay, I'll wait for it.
Girl, we'll just
set up seance downstairs.
- Okay.
Hey, Yujie, time to work!
Okay. I'll bring this with me.
Your pet looks expensive.
Where'd you get it?
Cartimar? [CHUCKLES]
This one, Jaja.
Where should I put--
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Who's that?
[LAPTOP SHUTS]
Is that...
Wilberto...
de Guzman?
I saw the tomb you visited.
I-Is he your ex?
The one you call "Pani"?
Why...
Why do we look alike?
I don't know.
[JAJA] Treb! [GUSHES]
Is that really you, Treb?!
Have you been reincarnated?
Call the chairman.
Tell them we caught a thief.
Hey! You're the thief!
You stole his face!
You can go now,
Grandpa Wilberto.
- Uh... Huh?
- Oh.
I mean, bro, you can go now.
Pani?
- Huh?
- One point for Grandpa.
What does "Pani" mean?
- Nothing.
- It's her ex.
I think I like you.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Do you like me
because I look like him?
Is that the only reason?
I don't know
- how to explain, Mac--
- Why?
Why? Are you still affected
by him?
He's a ghost.
He's your ghost?
The one that got away?
He was the first ghost
I helped.
Emma and I.
We helped him find his sister.
Since then,
we have been inspired
to help ghosts
and people
with unfinished business.
That's why we started Kafeels.
Since we were always together,
I fell in love with him.
But he already crossed
to the other side.
And then you saw me,
who looks exactly like your ex,
who's a ghost.
I thought you were related.
- What?
- I don't know why
you two look alike.
Your Uncle told me
that your Momshie
was a fan of heroes.
So I thought
that she probably saw
Wilberto's photo.
I don't know.
Maybe she saw it while she
was pregnant with you.
I was surprised
when I met you.
Rebound.
You used me as a rebound.
- No.
- That's why it was so fast.
I just matched your pace.
W-What?
That's because I'm sure
about you, Jaja.
You, on the other hand...
You went along with it
because you see
your ex in me.
That's not true.
You didn't even tell me
that you have a ghost ex.
It's not normal
to talk about your past
to your present.
Jaja, we look alike.
That's a different story.
How do you expect me
to believe you
when you were able to keep
this information from me?
Jaja, I'm not Wilberto.
And I will never...
be him.
I know.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I think we should...
slow down for a bit.
No.
Ja...
We'll just slow down.
We're not breaking up.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KEYPAD CLACKING]
[EERIE MUSIC STINGS]
[SCREAMS] Ah!
[WHIMSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Girl, what happened to you?
You're going to give me
a heart attack.
Why don't you sleep first?
What if Macmac
breaks up with me?
Girl, stop overthinking.
Just give him space.
What if that space gets bigger?
Girl, I thought you were
done with your clingy era.
I'm not being clingy.
I just don't like us fighting.
Look at me,
I can't even sleep.
[EMMA] Let it rest.
Then talk it out tomorrow.
Maybe you just have
to sleep it off today.
What if I wake up
and I'm single again?
[CLICKS TONGUE]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[JAJA] Emma's right.
You're the one I love.
Not Treb,
but you, Macmac.
Oh, hey! Where--
Hey! I said--
- Girl!
- [DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
I said talk it out tomorrow.
[TRAFFIC NOISES]
[MACMAC] Smile.
Wait.
- Here's my best angle.
- Miss, is the photoshoot here?
[MACMAC] Okay.
3, 2, 1...
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
Nice shot.
Just give me five seconds.
It's so hot.
Whoo! It is hot.
[MACMAC] How about this photo?
It's hot, right?
Is it just me, but...
I think it's getting hot
in here.
Look, you're sweating.
- Uh...
- [CHUCKLES]
It's hot, right?
Let's get back to it, ma'am.
Look at the camera,
and try to think
of a person or thing
you want to have.
I-It's you... Okay.
Okay, okay.
Wait.
[MACMAC] Okay, ma'am. Three...
- Do I look pretty?
- ...two, one--
- [WOMAN] Hey!
- Put your shirt back on.
You might get cold.
Wait. Excuse me, who are you?
I'm his girlfriend. Why?
- Take over for now.
- Okay, Mac. I got it.
- Let's go.
- [WOMAN] So unprofessional!
- Don't touch me!
- I paid you, guys!
You're stressing me out!
[WOMAN] It's not my angle! Here!
[MACMAC SIGHS]
What are you doing here?
Why do you let her
flirt with you?
And the way she looks at you...
You're not even stopping her
from touching you. Did you
forget you have a girlfriend?
You have it better.
You're jealous of a person.
Don't you think?
Come on, Macmac.
Let's fix this.
I can't sleep
because we're not okay.
Jaja, there's nothing
to be jealous about.
It's my client's birthday,
so she wanted a photo shoot.
That's all.
Fine.
You don't have to get
jealous of Treb either.
Jaja, how can I erase that
from my mind?
I'm jealous of a ghost.
How do I compete with someone
who's not even alive...
...maybe even an angel?
You're not a rebound, okay?
You're the one who's here.
["HINDI TAYO"
INSTRUMENTAL PLAYING]
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry,
I didn't tell you sooner.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
I'm sorry, I got scared.
["HINDI TAYO"
INSTRUMENTAL CONTINUES]
Because...
[SNIFFLES] Because what
if you leave me too,
just like they all did?
Because that's
what I'm afraid of.
["HINDI TAYO"
INSTRUMENTAL CONTINUES]
That you'll question
what I feel for you.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
You know, Jaja...
when I look in the mirror...
I always worry that
maybe you only loved me
because of someone else.
No.
Jaja, that'll haunt me
for the rest of my life.
But when I look at you,
I don't see Treb.
["HINDI TAYO"
INSTRUMENTAL CONTINUES]
I see the person I love.
- Are you sure?
- [JAJA SOBBING]
Jaja, we have the same face.
[SOBBING]
Go home.
Get some rest.
[JAJA SOBS]
["HINDI TAYO"
BY BRYAN CHONG PLAYING]
I love Jaja.
I'll fight for her.
I know how real
your feelings are.
So, just listen
to your heart.
Who do you
really love?
Looks like I'm late.
Seems like
you've already chosen.
Everything's clear
to me now, Treb.
I love you.
["HINDI TAYO" CONTINUES]