♪There's a voice that calls from deep within♪
♪Sing praises before the Hall of Villains♪
♪Take control if you wish to enter♪
♪Fear is just another form of pain♪
♪Life is but a fleeting dream♪
♪Anger arises when emotions are manipulated by external influence♪
♪Suffering is born from dwelling on misunderstandings♪
♪All good deeds share a common purpose♪
♪Boiling with fury, trembling in search of a worthy opponent♪
♪Add some extra fun♪
♪To satisfy my hunger for thrills♪
♪Lost in reverie, the world around me awakens♪
♪Filling in an interim role as a temp♪
♪A thousand compassionate hands extend with mercy♪
♪The world goes wild for me♪
♪Men are the sources of all evils♪
♪The thought lingers in my mind♪
♪I walk my own path freely♪
♪Since I've come this far♪
♪Even if I know I might regret it♪
♪I'd take action without any hesitance♪
[I Am Nobody: The showdown between Yin & Yang]
[Adapted from Under One Person, created by Mi Er]
[Episode Five]
[This is a work of fiction. Any resemblance to existing entities is purely coincidental.]
[All actions and abilities performed are fictional and should not be imitated.]
Qing,
I took the liberty of inviting you over
to ask you for some help.
Come on.
I'll take you a for visit.
OK.
Great.
Qing,
"Ten Qimen Practitioners and nine are crazy."
Is it true?
Yes.
The challenges of phantasmagoria are extraordinary.
Not everyone can handle it freely.
Then what happens if someone who isn't skilled enough
enters the phantasmagoria?
The phantasmagoria turns the heart
into presentation.
Beginners will experience
an indescribable pleasure.
All your wishes are coming true.
You are capable of anything.
You can't bear to give up that kind of pleasure.
But probably you are losing yourself
in reality.
Is there any way to control it?
Well, I am taking a further exploration
at the deep secret of the phantasmagoria.
But I don't have a suitable way or approach.
Qing,
if only
you came to this village earlier.
Okay, we're almost there.
What do you think
of the Furnace?
Pretty awesome.
So do you want to try
using this Furnace?
This is Ms. Zhao
and this is her son.
Chief Ma,
he is...
His name is Zhao Nian.
He used to be an office worker.
He practiced some Qimen Skills
he picked up from somewhere.
Then he's like this.
Another ordinary man
who wants to be an Outsider.
You can say that.
But unfortunately,
he took the wrong path.
His mother
came to Biyou Village
to wake him up
with the help of the Refining Furnace.
I didn't want to bother you.
But I'm not good at phantasmagoria.
Zhao Nian's vital signs
are increasingly unstable these days.
Therefore,
I have no choice but to ask for your help.
Mr. Zhuge,
Chief Ma said
you could save my son.
Please!
Please help us.
Please get up, Ms. Zhao.
Mr. Zhuge,
please!
Please!
Save him or not.
It's up to you.
Okay.
I've been wanting to try the Furnace for a long time.
What should I do?
Qing, I knew
you would help them.
In fact, I've done a lot of efforts
with the Refining Furnace
before you came.
I tried to rebuild the human meridian vessel
in the Refining Furnace.
It's useless.
There's no problem
with the running of their meridian vessel.
They are just lost
in their own consciousness.
But let's take another perspective.
The phantasmagoria is built from the meridian vessel.
With the help of the Furnace,
you can integrate your meridian vessel
with Zhao Nian's,
so that...
We can share the phantasmagoria.
Right.
That’s why I need your help, Qing.
Interesting.
I know what to do.
Tell me how to operate it.
The Refining Furnace will get everything ready for you.
All you need to do
is bring Zhao Nian out.
Qing,
you will enter not only his phantasmagoria
but also your own.
I don't know what is going to happen.
The more you say it,
the more interested I am.
Bring it on.
Stop wasting time.
A fairyland.
Amazing.
But the visual effect is too...
There are so many people.
Which one is Zhao Nian?
What a grand welcome ceremony!
Surrender!
Surrender?
I won't.
Does any of you
dare to be the enemy of me, the Number One Saint of the Three Realms.
You take away my magic weapon.
I'm going to kill your whole family.
I took your magic weapon.
Take it back
if you are capable.
Seven stars break the sky.
Whoever stands in my way,
no matter which God,
even heaven,
will be...
Sir!
Your highness,
may I know your name?
Nicholas
Zhao
Yunshang
Nian.
Who are you?
He even changed his surname!
Shut up!
My surname
has been here for thousands of years.
How can someone like you slander it?
Qing,
Why did you come out?
Mr. Zhuge,
how is my son?
I think
he is quite happy now.
We don't need to help him.
He's fine.
Stop kidding, Qing.
Even you can't do anything?
Mr. Zhuge,
just say a number
and I'll give the money to you.
That's not what I meant, Ms. Zhao.
How to say it?
It's not difficult
to take him back for his situation.
But he may go back again at any time
after he wakes up.
Chief Ma,
can you erase
part of his memory
when he wakes up?
I can't.
I was only asking.
Why are you so serious?
Never mind.
Let me try again.
I'll have to do it my way
if it doesn't work this time.
The phantasmagoria
is hidden in the weakest part of the deep consciousness.
He can be influenced greatly
by what I do.
Zhao Nian may be shattered by this.
Is it okay, Ms. Zhao?
Please.
Then I'll try again.
It's you again
I just cut you into ashes.
Are you
from the immortal Eastern Ghost Tribe
in the legend?
Your highness,
I'm not some ghost.
I'm here because of your mom.
She asked me to take you home for dinner.
My mother?
Do you think I'm stupid?
My mother is trapped
in the Deceased Emperor Tower
for protecting me,
the only blood of Taichu.
Tell me,
what are you here for?
I can't stand you anymore.
In short,
the happy life you are living
as an Immortal is fake.
In reality,
you are just an ordinary office worker.
Interesting.
I'm becoming interested
in your background.
Right.
I had some weird dreams before.
In my dreams,
I was ugly,
humble,
and weak.
In the dreams,
I didn't want to hurt anyone.
However,
everyone else wanted to hurt me.
Everyone else looked down on me.
You are wrong.
In fact, nobody looks down on you.
They don't look at you at all.
Everyone is busy.
Why will they look at you?
Rubbish.
I forgot to tell you
I am a sorcerer.
The phantasmagoria
is my home court.
You took my hit without vomiting blood.
The level of your martial arts
is at least the Advanced Stage of Crazy.
You are an advanced stage! Your whole family is an advanced stage!
I didn't want to do this.
But the only way
to stop you from wallowing here
is to defeat you completely
in your deep consciousness.
Now
are you going back with me?
Defeat me
completely?
You know nothing.
Built with three thousand Great Taoists,
The second of the three world-destroying demon swords,
Sky Cutting Sword!
Chief Ma,
is everything okay?
How so?
It's the first time it reacts like this.
Is it Zhuge Qing's Ji
that causes components overloading which triggers the vibrations?
Cut the sky?
Why do you always want
to cut the sky?
The voice
isn't from that man.
Tell me,
did the sky provoke you?
Why do you want to cut it?
Who are you?
Me?
I'm you in the real world.
Now way.
You are a monster.
Monster!
I can destroy heaven and earth.
I can break the void.
Why can't you kill me?
It's simple.
Because everything you are experiencing now
is all an illusion.
And the dreams
you don't want to remember
are real.
Who do you think you are?
Why should you define what is real?
Do you think you are God?
To be right,
even God
has no right of defining reality.
And I
just defined
that this world is just an illusion.
Illusion?
The air,
earth
and the knife in my hand,
I am feeling them.
Why should you
define what they are?
Feeling?
If feelings can be taken for real,
there won't be so many people in the world
practicing hard.
Are you seeing it?
Feelings are unreliable.
If feelings mean the reality
then your reality
can be twisted by a few pills.
You said this world is unreal.
Is the world in the dreams you talked about
is real?
Yes.
Because it's more reasonable.
It's unreasonable to be able to defeat countless masters with one blow
You have no strength.
You are yelled by your boss and don't dare to look up. That's more reasonable.
So it's more real there.
Tao is reality.
Reason is reality.
Evidence of that world being real
is in your memory.
Everything in this world
originates from there.
I don’t want that kind of reality.
I don't care
about reality
or illusion
as long as I am powerful.
Powerful?
Do you mean
this?
Chief Ma,
what's happening?
No.
The components are not acting right.
Qing,
you need to hurry up.
I don't know
how much longer the Furnace will hold.
Look,
I shattered your world with one kick.
Is it powerful?
I don't think.
Because I don't see any reason
from the kick.
And you can't imagine the hardship I went through
when I was practicing?
Reason...
So many reasons...
You are so annoying.
So what if it's unreasonable
when I can experience
the pleasure of being powerful?
The thing is that powerful people are reasonable.
No matter boxing,
mathematics,
or physics,
the people
become powerful
on the way of exploring truth.
This is by no means an easy way.
Think about it if you don't believe me.
In the dreams you don’t want to mention,
aren't you
walking on that way too?
What else can you do?
Do it again!
Which one is more real?
Which one is more powerful?
The God who wants to cut the sky
or the nerd that studied all night?
Yunshang Nian
is much better than the trashy Zhao Nian, right?
Shut up!
Oh no.
I have to stop the Furnace first.
Mom!
My son!
I'm a coward.
I'm useless.
So let’s talk about the most important thing
since you are awake completely.
Do you know
why you were trapped in that situation?
You rode with lax reins?
Do you know the concept of "monkey's heart, horse's will"?
This phrase is from a classic book in Han Dynasty.
Journey to the West also used this concept.
I don't have to explain
the meaning of it.
An ancient Practitioners once had an interpretation.
They compared the monkey
to Sun Wukong,
and the horse to the White Dragon Horse.
Follow the heart.
Defeat the evil.
The monkey's heart jumps around.
The horse runs everywhere.
If you can't keep your heart,
it's easy to lose yourself
and get into trouble.
This is the so-called "Ride with lax reins,
doomed to disaster."
This is how an ancient practitioner
understand Journey to the West.
Of course he could be wrong.
But one thing was right.
Even from a modern person's perspective,
we should stay true to our heart,
have a strong mind
and a strong body.
That's the real Practice.
You went crazy this time
because you were taken over
by your feelings.
I'll ask you another question.
What's the name of Sanzang's horse?
White Dragon Horse.
Another identity of the horse
is the Third Dragon Prince of the West Sea.
Here's a pretty simple riddle.
Interpret the Third Dragon Prince of the West Sea.
The West...
The Third Dragon Prince...
The third Qian of Yao...
Right.
That's the last thing I want to tell you.
I won't interfere you
no matter where you go or what you do.
But I hope you remember it.
I will.
I will remember it forever.
The third Qian:
A man should work hard during daytime.
Be vigilant even at night.
Then he's doing it right.
[The third Qian: A man should work hard during daytime. Be vigilant even at night. Then he's doing it right.]
Thank Chief Ma.
He saved you.
Thank you.
Don't thank me.
The Refining Furnace and Mr. Zhuge saved you.
It's not easy to be an Outsider.
Go back.
Remember
Biyou Village will always welcome you.
Zhuge Qing.
Who is that?
Qing?
He really entered my phantasmagoria.
But I didn't have any thoughts.
Wouldn't the phantasmagoria exist
if you don't think about it?
Who do you think you are?
The man you woke up
didn't hurt anyone.
He just wanted a place to be peaceful
where he can accept himself.
Why wouldn't you let him do it?
Meanwhile,
you keep talking about truth and reasons
but never
dare to admit what you want.
You don’t even dare to admit your own desires.
He hid in the phantasmagoria.
You are hiding in Biyou Village.
How are you smarter than him?
Shut up!
I just said the truth to you and you can't stand it.
Isn't it your own choice?
Do you really think that Ma Xianhong
called you here
just to save
an unimportant office worker.
You have already figured out
that Ma Xianhong was taking advantage of you.
But you still accepted it
because you wanted to see the Refining Furnace.
Do you know
what changes you will bring to the world?
Shut up!
You made a mistake
and it's irretrievable.
Zhuge Qing,
you lost.
You lost completely.
I told you to shut up!
Qing?
What's wrong, Qing?
I'm fine.
Maybe a little tired.
Chief Ma,
the Furnace...
Good it is ruined.
As long as you don't care.
I'll go back then.
How could I not care?
Qing,
do me a favor.
Stay for a while.
What are you doing with Chief Ma recently?
You are being mysterious.
He asked me
to do him a favor.
Have you finished?
I guess so.
What’s wrong with you?
I'm trapped.
And it has trapped me
for many, many years.
What is it?
An old rival.
I have been trapped
since I was little.
Where is he?
I'll help you deal with him.
It's wherever I am.
You can't help me.
Fu Rong,
I have to face it.
It's a battle of life and death.
You are the only one I can trust now.
Please guard me.
[Divine Forge]
[Three days ago]
Ma Xianhong,
what do you mean?
Don't you always wanted
to see Divine Forge?
I'm giving it to you now.
You are giving it to me?
It's just a book.
You did me such a great favor.
I'm just repaying you with this small thing.
I even feel sorry about that.
Zhuge Qing,
isn't this what you want?
[Divine Forge]
Zhuge Qing...
[A man who practices to improve his virtue progresses day by day.]
[Divine Forge]
Zhuge Qing...
What do you want?
What do you want from me?
I surrender.
I am not as good as Wang Ye.
I'm afraid of Wang Ye now.
What do you want from me?
It's you.
Yes.
It's me.
For real,
I can't let go
no matter how many times I lose to Wang Ye.
I can't surrender
if I can't beat you.
It seems you know very well.
But the thing is...
Can you beat me?
[Divine Forge]
A "Divine Forge"
makes you lose your mind.
And I
[Divine Forge]
can face it.
How can you beat me,
the man who masters Eight Supremes?
Don't pretend to be a victim.
You take me as your demon.
I take you as my shame.
[Divine Forge]
You should know
if you work with me,
sooner or later, the two of us
will be invincible,
not to mention that small Wang Ye.
[Divine Forge]
The more I look at you,
the more appreciative I am to Wang.
He's helping us
by not telling us the Qimen Manipulation.
Don't you understand?
Nonsense!
Who mastered all the skills of Four Pillars
of Heaven, Earth, Human and God
in less than seven years?
It's us.
He learned it half way
and still masters it.
Will we, who have great talent,
be hurt by it?
You are indeed awesome.
No.
Just like what you say about Wang.
The skill you crave for is indeed awesome.
The temptation is too big. I can't win.
Challenging you
is in fact a gambling.
I'm betting the final legacy
of Wuhou Sect on it,
Samadhi True Fire.
You want to use
the thing you can't even master
to fight with me.
Light it up.
Light it up to me if you can.
You piece of trash from Wuhou Sect.
I'll give you two options.
Either
I kill you here
or
you study Divine Forge with me.
I surrender.
I'm a piece of trash.
I choose the second option.
You should have been this smart earlier.
[Divine Forge]
How can it be?
That's impossible.
We didn't succeed when we did it together.
How can you do it alone?
So that's it.
Fortune and misfortune depend on each other.
The Eight Supremes are too terrifying.
So there isn't extra fear
for the Samadhi True Fire.
You have become a slave to Divine Forge.
And I
am liberated.
You lit the Samadhi True Fire only by chance.
Does it make you forget who you are?
Can you control it
with your ability?
Can you really control it?
Do you really think you can get rid of me?
Even if you can control it,
can you burn me
when I can roam around the phantasmagoria?
Come on!
Burn me
if you can.
Did you forget
what the Samadhi True Fire is for?
With spirit of the upper Elixir,
Qi of the middle Elixir,
Essence of the lower Elixir,
Light up the fire of life
with energy.
The fire does not burn wood,
The fire does not burn earth or stone,
The fire only burns the souls of everything in the world.
Samadhi True Fire,
Break!
Zhuge Qing!
Anyway, I've always wanted
to burn up this place.
Thank you
for guarding me.
You did it, Zhuge Qing.
I did it.
I asked Chen Duo
about
what happened
and how
Liao died?
[Five years ago]
Let's start
from the operation to exterminate Medicine Immortal Association
five years ago.
Are you okay?
The poison concentration here is too high.
The suit can't protect us
if we stay here any longer.
We need to get out of here immediately.
We won't find any more survivors.
Look around.
Even serpents and scorpions
can't survive in the environment
let alone people.
Send a request to the headquarter.
Let's get out of here.
Come here.
Take care of him.
Everyone, take your things
and leave here immediately.
Hurry!
We got a situation here.
Don’t' be afraid,
little girl.
Come with me.
♪Standing out, second to none♪
♪I was born fearless and different♪
♪I venture into the unknown, making the world my home♪
♪Concealing my identity, seeking a life in full bloom♪
♪Journeying through challenges, I carry the weight of responsibilities♪
♪Seeking the truth, no matter the snares♪
♪I'll face the adversity of this universe♪
♪I'll command the thunder and turn rain into flowers♪
♪I won't be in anyone's shadow♪
♪Because I'm the master of my own destiny♪
♪The light behind me shines forth♪
♪Illuminating the pitch-black darkness♪
♪I say to myself♪
♪If you don't follow your heart, how will your heart follow you?♪
♪I will not forget it♪
♪My strength lies in my resilient soul♪
♪I cross mountains to see the rivers♪
♪I endure the worst and learn to be adaptive♪
♪I persevere, spending ten years honing my skills♪
♪I hear from afar♪
♪My true calling♪
♪I see hope appears before dawn♪
♪In dreams, I listen to stories untold♪
♪I let go of my mortal burdens♪
♪And I strive to become a better version of myself♪
♪The path I desire is not a stroll♪
♪The person I aim to be, I'll claim my role♪
♪Too many pursuits♪
♪Blind you from what you want the most♪
♪I'm used to setbacks♪
♪Because I'm not afraid of making mistakes♪
♪Life is unpredictable♪
♪We're all just visitors♪
♪Despite the weight on my shoulder♪
♪I don't feel exhausted♪
♪Tearing off the talisman on me♪
♪I know I won't give up♪
♪The plum will bloom despite the snow♪
♪Butterflies fly in pairs♪
♪As I look back, tears blur my vision♪
♪Turning longing into a breeze, heading to the north♪
♪I cross mountains to see the rivers♪
♪I endure the worst and learn to be adaptive♪
♪I persevere, spending ten years honing my skills♪
♪I hear from afar♪
♪My true calling♪
♪I see hope appears before dawn♪
♪In dreams, I listen to stories untold♪
♪I let go of my mortal burdens♪
♪And I strive to become a better version of myself♪
♪A competitor?♪
♪I don't care who you are♪
♪Clenching my fist at all times♪
♪On the horizon♪
♪I shine like the eternal stars♪
♪I march forward♪
♪Despite the bruises and the wounds♪
♪I'll sing with all my might♪
♪When you're with me♪
♪A competitor?♪
♪I don't care who you are♪
♪Clenching my fist at all times♪
♪On the horizon♪
♪I shine like the eternal stars♪
♪I march forward♪
♪Despite the bruises and the wounds♪
♪I'll sing with all my might♪
♪When you're with me♪