From now on,
don't say anything.
Shut your mouth.
Don't worry.
Mr. Liao.
Someone said they could cure me.
Chen Duo.
Nonsense.
Forget it.
You heard me?
That's not important.
The important thing is
that you come back with me.
Yeah.
Mr. Liao.
That's not important.
The company
and the Bunker
are not important, either.
For me,
only you're important.
Chen Duo.
Don't push me.
♪There's a voice that calls from deep within♪
♪Sing praises before the hall of villains♪
♪Take control if you wish to enter♪
♪Fear is just another form of pain♪
♪Life is but a fleeting dream♪
♪Anger arises when emotions are manipulated by external influence♪
♪Suffering is born from dwelling on misunderstandings♪
♪All good deeds share a common purpose♪
♪Boiling with fury, trembling in search of a worthy opponent♪
♪Add some extra fun♪
♪To satisfy my hunger for thrill♪
♪Lost in reverie, the world around me awakens♪
♪Filling in an interim role as a temp♪
♪A thousand compassionate hands extend with mercy♪
♪The world goes wild for me♪
♪Men are the sources of all evils♪
♪The thought lingers in my mind♪
♪I walk my own path freely♪
♪Since I've come this far♪
♪Even if I know I might regret it♪
♪I'd take action without any hesitance♪
[I'm Nobody]
[Adapted from Tencent Comics, Under One Person]
[Episode 2]
[This is a work of fiction.]
[Any resemblance to existing entities is purely coincidental.]
[All actions and abilities performed are fictional and should not be imitated.]
I felt comfortable
when Feng Baobao
did that to me.
Who's that?
It's late.
[Zhuge Qing, Wuhou Qimen]
Funny.
You want me to come with you, right?
I'm coming.
What do you want?
Whipper.
No.
It's a double-headed snake.
There's one more.
You wanted to kill me.
Then don't blame me.
You're not human.
Good job.
Who made you?
Perfect.
So perfect.
The forging skill is exquisite.
It's much better than our Zhuge family.
However,
you are flawed.
You used acupoint striking.
But sometimes you struck acupoints,
and sometimes you couldn't.
And
there are more than two of you.
If I didn't know how many opponents there were,
my Wuhou Qimen wouldn't be worthy of its reputation.
Come out.
Good.
No wonder the village chief looks up to you.
[Fu Rong, Sword Gust Master]
I'm warmed up.
With your skills,
I don't have to be serious.
Tell me.
What do you want?
It doesn't matter.
The village chief told me
to get rid of you, Zhuge Qing of the Wuhou Sect,
if I could.
That should be true.
No matter how I look at them,
I feel like they are made by my family.
Divine Forge.
However,
such skills are rare to see.
Yeah.
He's here.
The village chief wants to talk to you.
You keep talking about the village chief.
Who is that?
Pick up the phone.
Hello.
The village chief, right?
May I help you?
Zhuge.
Hello.
Please forgive me
if my people are rude
to you.
Your people
greeted me.
Are you satisfied
with the results?
I didn't mean to provoke you.
That's just
my way of introducing myself.
It was my work, Ruhua,
that you knocked down.
How about them?
Aren't they interesting?
Zhuge.
My name is Ma Xianhong.
I sincerely invite you
to visit Biyou Village.
You asked me to fight.
Now, you're asking me to go to you.
The producers wouldn't ask me that.
The director wouldn't ask me that.
Come on. You're just a village chief.
I won't go.
Really?
That's too bad.
Please tell my people
that she's done
and she can come back.
His Divine Forge skills are so strong.
I'm getting more and more interested
in this village chief.
Wait.
What is it?
Nothing.
I changed my mind.
Take me to the village chief.
I want
to meet him.
[Ma Xianhong, Village Chief of Biyou Village]
Chen Duo.
We meet again.
You know me.
Who are you?
Don't you recognize me?
No wonder.
Chen Duo.
Why did you kill Liao?
Liao is a good man.
How could you kill him?
Because he was in my way.
I admit
Mr. Liao is a good man.
He cared about me
and taught me how to live
as a normal person.
I've always been grateful to him.
But
why did he get in my way
when I got a real chance
when someone was willing to give me this?
Why should he judge
if
I am happy?
Chen Duo.
You must have misunderstood Liao.
Come back to the company with me.
There must be room for maneuver
in this matter.
No need.
Wait.
Your voice...
Do you remember me?
How could I forget you?
You are the cause of all my misfortunes.
You're the one
who deserves to die.
It's complicated.
Chen Duo, you go.
We'll take care of this.
Chen Duo is gone.
Ms. Bao, let's go.
Don't worry, Meng.
We'll deal with Chen Duo.
Judging from Meng's movements,
he's ordinary.
I should be able
to deal with him easily.
And I've never dealt
with anyone like Qiu.
It would be nice
if Dou found me some of this type of prey next time.
It's heavy.
What are you looking for?
I'm your opponent.
It's object manipulation.
Man.
You have a good eye.
How many years have you been practicing?
More than 20 years.
More than 20 years?
You had a hard time dealing with my iron ball.
What a loser.
You have a magic weapon.
Without it,
you would've been kicked to death.
You couldn't even defend yourself against my kicking.
Tell me.
How many years have you been practicing?
I'm flattered.
I've been practicing for 20 days.
Do you have a problem with that?
Twenty days? Unbelievable.
I'll show you.
Don't say my weapon is lame.
Your gadgets and cleverness
are useless
in front of my magic weapon.
Qiu.
You're playful.
But if that hurts you,
that's not good.
Besides,
I think
they are asking for trouble.
Actually, I've already seen it.
Your protections
are for malicious attacks.
But I'll bear you no ill will.
I created
this fist technique.
Massage the acupuncture points
to make people's glands
secrete dopamine
until
they become what you are now.
Remember.
This trick
is called Massage of Love.
Chen Duo also has protection.
Why isn't it
working on Ms. Bao?
We're colleagues.
We shouldn't fight.
Be good.
Come back with us.
I won't hit you.
Are you also
from the company?
My name is Feng Baobao.
His name is Zhang Chulan.
We were ordered to bring you back to the company.
You were ordered?
Bring it on.
There is a limit to the protection of magic weapons.
Even if I could break through it,
I wouldn't have to.
The question is,
why does Chen Duo have protection?
What does she have to do
with that weapon Outsider?
Your qi is special.
Can you teach me?
You won't learn.
Why?
To learn this,
your body will rot little by little.
Do you still want to learn?
Protections
didn't work on her.
It's normal.
Your protections are automatic and lame.
[Qiu Rang, Armorer]
She's strong.
She's all right.
Are you all right, Ms. Bao?
I'm all right.
Who are you?
You're in luck today.
Prepare to be amazed.
Not everyone
can see my gilded ruyi.
And my emerald ring
can resist all attacks.
Run.
That guy
broke his protection.
He's hiding deeper than we are.
Where is Chen Duo?
She escaped.
We were this close to catching her.
But a guy with magic weapons came out of nowhere
and rescued Chen Duo.
We found out
that Chen Duo also has protection,
just like the other Outsiders.
We need to think carefully.
You broke the rules, didn't you?
We have two people
from Lubei.
I'm not.
She's from Lubei.
You can call her Baobao.
It has always been the code name
of temporary workers in Lubei.
I'm just an assistant.
Don't ask too much.
Which of you is in charge?
- He is. - She is.
The man from Luzhong
and the girl from Northeast are the only ones I haven't met.
It was my fault
that Chen Duo escaped.
I gave her time to react.
I missed the best chance to complete the task.
Meng.
You have dealt with Chen Duo.
Why did she say
you were the one who deserved to die?
There must be some misunderstanding here.
I didn't hurt Chen Duo.
We never spoke
after our first meeting.
Five years ago,
I took a task
to destroy an illegal organization called the Medicine Immortal Association.
Liao also participated
in that task.
It's said that the Medicine Immortal Association
is from a space we can't recognize.
Everything there is unconventional.
Qi operates in a way we don't understand.
It's a veritable forbidden place for Outsiders.
The Medicine Immortal Association
acts strangely.
They worship a strange kind of energy.
They take a poison of unknown origin
as their god.
And they think of it as a sacred relic
handed down from generation to generation.
The Medicine Immortal Association
brutally trains those who inherit poison arts.
They cut them off from the outside world
until they lose their sense
of being human.
In their world,
they only know poison arts.
The most outstanding one
is Chen Duo.
She was called
Saint Poison Girl.
[Saint Poison Girl]
The other members of the Immortal Medicine Association
deserve to die.
But Chen Duo is innocent.
She's a victim.
The Medicine Immortal Association made her into what she is now.
She didn't have a choice.
Girl.
Don't be afraid.
Come with me.
Liao and I took her
from the Medicine Immortal Association.
At that time,
Liao was in charge of the Bunker.
The Bunker is a research facility for special Outsiders.
He took the lead
in getting Chen Duo to the Bunker
for treatment.
Let's go.
I whine
when dealing
with dangerous tasks.
When I met Chen Duo,
I couldn't say anything.
She was never trained
to be a human
after birth.
Then,
she spent many years in the Bunker.
It was Liao...
It was Liao who made her a temporary worker.
Although she could not live
like an ordinary girl,
she was at least like a human being.
I'll be blunt.
Cut the nonsense.
I'm not interested in your story.
I just want to finish this task as soon as possible.
An order from the headquarters.
[Headquarters]
If the poison on Chen Duo spreads,
it will cause great damage.
The situation is critical.
Catching Chen Duo is of great importance.
If you encounter strong resistance or are in danger of your life,
you can decide for yourself what to do.
Although this is an order from the headquarters,
I'd like to ask for a favor.
If Chen Duo doesn't want to come back to the company with us,
please don't hurt her first.
I want to persuade her.
After all, Chen Duo is not a bad person.
Qiu. Xiao.
You've seen it.
She didn't try to kill us.
I know I'm no match for you.
If you insist on going your own way,
I will...
[Northeast]
I support Meng.
There is room for maneuver.
We'll find a way to catch her alive.
[Luzhong]
Agree.
Chen Duo.
It doesn't matter.
Maybe something more interesting will emerge.
Qiu.
Her tricks are interesting.
Only by capturing her alive
can I know her origins.
I agree.
Let's catch her alive.
Lubei's people.
What do you say?
Since it's okay with you,
it's okay with us.
The matter is complicated.
We'll only be able to figure it out if we catch her alive.
I think the headquarters wants
to complete the task
and get some information.
Ms. Bao.
What do you think?
Agree.
Thank you.
Looks like all their attention
centers on Chen Duo.
But the biggest threat is the attitude of the headquarters
towards temporary workers.
Tell me what you're thinking.
I don't treat you like a stranger.
I told you.
I think
it's complicated.
But I don't know why.
I'm just a worker.
As long as I can save Chen Duo,
I will do whatever the headquarters says.
I don't mind.
I just want to deal with a few fresh people.
I don't care
about anything else.
It seems
that they can perceive the attitude of the headquarters.
Meng. Xiao.
What do you mean?
What they mean is that
we're
being played.
What?
By whom?
The people above.
People above, come out.
I saw you.
Get down.
I'm referring
to the company,
the board of directors.
On the face of it,
this joint operation is about catching Chen Duo.
But actually, it's about temporary workers.
This is called
achieving a goal by any means.
No wonder.
The attitude of the headquarters towards us
has always been subtle.
Although temporary workers are very useful,
the headquarters
can't direct us.
Plus, we're a hidden danger
to the headquarters.
The headquarters delegated the task to us.
As long as we can satisfy the headquarters,
you're good,
I'm good,
and everyone is good.
What if the headquarters is not satisfied?
Then, all of us
will die a terrible death.
It's a pity.
But we all understand
that temporary workers are nice.
For example,
Bao.
To the headquarters,
she's more like a weapon
of the second generation
of the Xu family
than a special agent.
If that's the case,
I'm the same.
Guys.
What do you think about this?
I
don't mind.
I think it's a good thing.
I can follow people from higher levels.
In that case,
we can handle the task
and get this over with.
Wouldn't that
be better?
Anyway,
failure is better for us.
No.
Qiu meant
that he wanted the headquarters
to manage the temporary workers directly.
In that case, Ms. Bao's identity
will be exposed.
Then I'll have to run away with Ms. Bao.
Qiu.
Stop teasing Zhang Chulan.
Look at his face.
It looks terrible.
Xiao.
What do you think of the two people
from Lubei?
Sword.
Swordsmen.
It's weird.
Basically,
we don't communicate with people
from the company other than our supervisors
when we carry out our tasks.
If we need help,
we look for people outside the company
through our contacts.
However,
both of you are here.
Anyway,
you seem to be afraid
that the headquarters will take
away Baobao's management rights.
Temporary workers
are not normal people.
You seem to care
about their troubles.
I don't care about it.
Chulan.
If you have anything you want to ask,
just ask.
You don't have to beat around the bush.
And
I'm satisfied with my supervisor.
On my birthday last month,
Dou specifically arranged a task for me
to celebrate my birthday.
It's good.
I don't want to change anything.
I'm counting on you
this time.
Let's work together.
They've already made their decision.
Their discussion was just a test of each other.
I have to be more careful
with these freaks.
[Northeast]
Chen Duo showed up.
[No. 32 Duobao Road, Xiaolin Village]
She's heading to Mei Jinfeng's.
Zhang Chulan.
Look what you've done.
I want to ask Xiao to kill you.
I'm poor. I have no choice.
The car was damaged.
I lost all my travel expenses.
I have no choice
but to travel in this environment-friendly way.
Xiao.
You and Wang Zhenqiu
were in our car, too.
Can you pay half of the compensation?
Xiao.
Say something.
He's blackmailing us.
Chulan.
You'd better stay away from me,
especially when I'm upset.
Meng.
Xiao asked me to stay away from him.
Why are you riding so fast?
According to the information Erzhuang provided,
Mei Jinfeng
is an elder of the Sinister Pleasure.
Let's hurry up
and figure out
how Chen Duo got involved
with such a big name.
Jinfeng.
Please let me in.
I picked
one of your favorite flowers.
It's fresh.
[Xia Liuqing, Elder of the Sinister Pleasure]
Xia.
I know
you're good to me.
But you should know
that I am too petty
to tolerate a mistress.
Jinfeng.
After all these years,
actually,
you're not that important
to me.
Xia Liuqing.
[Mei Jinfeng, Elder of the Sinister Pleasure]
You went too far.
Jinfeng.
Why are you so angry?
You only like
the Sect Leader.
Do you know
how long
I've been single for you?
Knock it off.
Hello, Ms. Jinfeng.
Can you come with me?
After all these years,
a stranger came
to visit me.
I'm old.
I won't go anywhere.
You have to come with me.
What did you say?
Drop it, Jinfeng.
You need men
to deal with this.
Wait inside.
OK.
Not bad.
You look composed and calm.
Noblewoman.
Noblewoman?
Sir.
Forget it, girl.
I don't care
who you are
or where you come from.
Whoever comes to disturb Jinfeng
will die.
You're a poisoner.
As a poisoner,
you walked right up
to your enemy.
People nowadays
are ignorant.
You're wrong, sir.
I'm not a poisoner.
I am poison.
I don't care what you are.
To me,
you're dead meat.
You have helpers.
Leave him to us.
Chen Duo.
Do what you need to do.
Jinfeng.
Are you
with that girl?
Sir.
How did you get hurt like this?
Feng Baobao.
Zhang Chulan.
Qiu.
Why are you here?
What day is it today?
I should have thought of you
when I heard the name Mei Jinfeng.
Qiu.
You know him?
Kind of.
Xia's tricks
are funny.
It took me a long time for him to teach me.
To learn his kung fu,
I was very close to joining the Sinister Pleasure.
Well.
I should call him Master.
Qiu.
What sect are you from?
I don't
belong to any sect.
I'm sympathetic.
People are willing to teach me.
It's a magic weapon again.
Xia.
I'm not here to talk about the old days.
Where did that girl go?
I don't know.
Looks like we came here for nothing again.
What should we do with this man of the Sinister Pleasure?
I won't do anything to him.
After all, he taught me something.
Well.
If you want to deal with him,
I can't stop you.
Qiu.
What are you...?
Don't ask.
All I can tell you
is that I'm not with that girl.
I'm here to deal with her.
That's great.
Qiu.
All my life,
I have no official successors.
You're kind of my successor.
But you fooled me.
If you
have a conscience,
you should repay me.
Please.
Please get Jinfeng back.
Xia.
Get up.
If you kneel,
this will get serious.
I'm not good at dealing with serious things.
Xia.
What did that girl do
to you?
That girl
wanted to take Jinfeng away.
And she had helpers.
Their skills are average.
But they all wore
high-level magical weapons.
I have a clue.
They all seem
to come from a village
called Biyou Village.
[Lubei]
Erzhuang.
Let the headquarters look up information about Biyou Village.
I know
you'll discuss what to do with me.
If you can get Jinfeng back,
I'm at your disposal.
You're a bad man.
But you're not totally bad.
You're not my thing.
But killing you
doesn't break my principles.
Xiao.
That's a shame.
I'm not interested in him.
Qiu.
I'll leave him to you.
I want to help you.
But
saving people
is so boring.
I can only promise you
that I will try.
That's enough.
I'm too old for this.
Take it.
You learned my tricks.
But you're too playful.
How can you fight them?
This is your treasure.
What will you do
if you give it to me?
It's not
my only treasure.
I can't
take them all to the grave.
Take it.
Qiu.
You...
Don't overthink it.
I won't accept it for no reason.
When I get Mei Jinfeng back,
you will kowtow to me.
Thanks.
I have a successor.
Here's what you want.
Thank you.
Welcome back to Biyou Village.
Chen Junyan.
Are you waiting for me?
I'm dirty.
I'm going to take a shower.
Be good.
Don't follow me.
Otherwise, you'll die.
♪Standing out, second to none♪
♪I was born fearless and different♪
♪I venture into the unknown, making the world my home♪
♪Concealing my identity, seeking a life in full bloom♪
♪Journeying through challenges, I carry the weight of responsibilities♪
♪Seeking the truth, no matter the snares♪
♪I'll face the adversity of this universe♪
♪I'll command the thunder and turn rain into flowers♪
♪I won't be in anyone's shadow♪
♪Because I'm the master of my own destiny♪
♪The light behind me shines forth♪
♪Illuminating the pitch-black darkness♪
♪I say to myself♪
♪If you don't follow your heart, how will your heart follow you?♪
♪I will not forget it♪
♪My strength lies in my resilient soul♪
♪I cross mountains to see the rivers♪
♪I endure the worst and learn to be adaptive♪
♪I persevere, spending ten years honing my skills♪
♪I hear from afar♪
♪My true calling♪
♪I see hope appears before dawn♪
♪In dreams, I listen to stories untold♪
♪I let go of my mortal burdens♪
♪And I strive to become a better version of myself♪
♪The path I desire is not a stroll♪
♪The person I aim to be, I'll claim my role♪
♪Too many pursuits♪
♪Blind you from what you want the most♪
♪I'm used to setbacks♪
♪Because I'm not afraid of making mistakes♪
♪Life is unpredictable♪
♪We're all just visitors♪
♪Despite the weight on my shoulder♪
♪I don't feel exhausted♪
♪Tearing off the talisman on me♪
♪I know I won't give up♪
♪The plum will bloom despite the snow♪
♪Butterflies fly in pairs♪
♪As I look back, tears blur my vision♪
♪Turning longing into a breeze, heading to the north♪
♪I cross mountains to see the rivers♪
♪I endure the worst and learn to be adaptive♪
♪I persevere, spending ten years honing my skills♪
♪I hear from afar♪
♪My true calling♪
♪I see hope appears before dawn♪
♪In dreams, I listen to stories untold♪
♪I let go of my mortal burdens♪
♪And I strive to become a better version of myself♪
♪A competitor?♪
♪I don't care who you are♪
♪Clenching my fist at all times♪
♪On the horizon♪
♪I shine like the eternal stars♪
♪I march forward♪
♪Despite the bruises and the wounds♪
♪I'll sing with all my might♪
♪When you're with me♪
♪A competitor?♪
♪I don't care who you are♪
♪Clenching my fist at all times♪
♪On the horizon♪
♪I shine like the eternal stars♪
♪I march forward♪
♪Despite the bruises and the wounds♪
♪I'll sing with all my might♪
♪When you're with me♪