(World of Street Woman Fighter)
- Where are we?
- It's the second from the bottom.
- I see.
- You're right.
Why did they put our birth years?
Our average age is...
Why isn't there anyone from the 1980s on the other teams?
Why are they all so young?
- Aaliyah.
- She was born in 2006. Gosh.
Monika, you and I are the oldest out of everyone here.
(The BUMSUP members were born in 1986, 1987, 1988, 1989, and 1990.)
- Kaea...
- She was born in 1997?
Everyone in the ROYAL FAMILY is very young too.
They need to get lots of sleep because they're babies.
Make sure you adjust to the time difference, babies.
(The K-survival show veterans give the other dancers advice.)
- Babies.
- This is how spicy it gets.
Gosh, it's so spicy. I need water.
What are we doing?
We're off to our first shoot.
Our first shoot.
The waiting room. It is 2:00am.
It's just like the draining part of the jet lag.
This is how it feels.
(Aaliyah, the baby born in 2006, is just excited.)
Actually, we came here for the competition. To win.
It's to prove to ourselves that we're capable of doing so.
It is definitely really hard, coming into this competition.
Like being on the other side of the world.
(Wake up, warriors!)
Wake up!
Gosh, I'm sleepy.
We flew all the way here on a plane, so we're very tired.
And I do miss my family. It's so hard.
And I just feel so lonely, as well.
It's my mom. It's her birthday. Can I answer this?
(Happy birthday, Bella's mom!)
Bella's so far away.
Stop. You're going to make me cry.
You're an amazing creature. Thank you for being my daughter.
I love you. I love you so much.
Thanks for being my mom.
(A heartwarming moment)
Hi, Hendrix.
Why are you not answering me?
(Melting)
- It's because I'm out shooting.
- We're...
Say "Hi, world."
(Smiling)
I love you AG SQUAD. I hope you win.
- Hi, Hendrix.
- Okay, I love you.
(Sisterly smiles)
(Rie Hata is on a video call with her son.)
This is what our room looks like.
It says "Team Japan."
Everything about this survival show is hard and exhausting,
but my kids give me the strength to keep going here.
(During break time, Kaea is talking to her son on the phone.)
- Hi, babe. This is my youngest.
- Hi, babe.
This one.
(Blowing a kiss)
(Her son blows her a kiss back.)
I love you.
I miss him so much.
(Feeling a lump in her throat)
Okay, thank you.
Sad.
I'm here for this.
I'm not here to muck around, you know?
So...
(Kaea traveled all the way to this foreign country...)
(so that her three children could be proud of their mom as a dancer.)
Give me a kiss.
I'm doing this for them, so I can set up our lives.
I love Mom.
I'm just here to win,
and then I want to go home to my kids, you know?
And I need to make sure that I just do my best.
World of Street Woman Fighter is powered by...
product sponsorship and partnership...
with a leading K-culture brand.
(Class Mission)
It's famous for being intense.
(We either have to protect or take.)
(We can't let anyone take from us.)
(Choreography, directing)
This is my forte.
AG SQUAD's choreography? We can do it easily.
Who's the original?
Can't beat originality.
Come in and take your choreography.
I'm excited to take on their choreography.
It's ours.
They understood this choreography and just killed it.
(Main Dancer Audition results)
(Their choreography was taken.)
AG SQUAD.
Can I say one thing?
We appreciate that you guys made this choreography really shine.
Keep this noted that the Korean team was very nice when teaching us.
(Even in the heat of the fierce class competition, )
(new friendships took root.)
They're the backup dancers.
They're the trees.
Australia, tiniest bit out.
They were taking it as if we were the back dancers.
Hey, if they're trying to play the game...
(The real class wars are about to unfold.)
Same, losers.
You all want to see our photos?
(Distracted)
(Restless)
We should check the light.
Guys.
This is where I belong.
(It's the main dancer's ultimate right to name the worst dancer.)
The crew that we've chosen has made it kind of easy for us.
The worst dancer is...
(Who will be picked as the worst dancer?)
All I had in life was dance.
My confidence took a hit.
Finally, it's time for the battle...
to determine the main dancer of the leader class,
where each team's pride and each country's pride is on the line.
(The highlight of the Class Mission)
Let's go, Marlee.
- Go, Teesha!
- Teesha!
Yes, baby!
Kaea!
Go, Kaea!
- You got this!
- Let's go!
- Three, two, one. RHTokyo!
- RHTokyo!
- Honey J!
Honey J!
You're so beautiful! Gosh!
This is about to be so sick.
This is going to be intense.
This is between the leader class.
Honey J, you had made it to the final round,
but your choreography wasn't chosen.
You have to bet everything here.
Yes, I will do my best today and take the choreography.
I was very disappointed.
That was so close.
I have no choice but to accept it, though.
I just have to take the choreography.
I'm going to be the best dancer in Rie Hata's choreography.
What's done is done.
Learn the choreography with a positive attitude and...
I will.
- I'll work hard and be good.
- Just stick to what you usually do.
I have to be good. That's what a leader is supposed to do.
(The leader class began learning and practicing Rie Hata's choreography.)
The choreography wasn't that difficult.
Can you show me one more time?
- Is it one turn? Two?
- Two.
- Rie.
- Yes.
- Keep low?
- Keep low. Low there and just...
(Honey J actively asks questions as she learns Rie Hata's choreography.)
I thought I'd be able to do it with practice.
(Ibuki asks Rie Hata questions easily in Japanese.)
- Is this right?
- Yes.
How should I put it? Tilt your torso backward.
There's definitely a language barrier.
(Honey J still remains focused and dedicates herself to practice.)
It's like we're collaborating at Fair Play.
- Right.
Last year, I saw your class.
Yes, that's where I saw you first.
I felt like there was a wall.
There was a disconnect between me and the others.
- Do you guys need water?
- Yes.
(Honey J felt out of sync...)
(due to language barriers and lack of common ground.)
I feel so left out.
They talk among themselves and it's not like my English is good,
so I can't really walk up to them and join in, you know?
- Is the language barrier too high?
- I wish I was more globally famous.
That's something that was stuck in my head a lot today.
I've mainly been active within Korea,
and it really hit me hard today.
I've been stuck in my little pond this whole time.
Even if I'm...
- a good dancer in Korea, - Even if you're the best...
all of them are from abroad.
I respect you so much for realizing it...
and accepting it.
Had I been in your shoes, I might've wanted to deny it.
You're the winner of Street Woman Fighter.
That's right.
It's thanks to your hard work...
that World of Street Woman Fighter came to be.
It's thanks to your continuous work in Korea...
that your style of dance became a genre here.
Firstly, I'll do really well this time.
Rie Hata is the queen of trendiness...
- in a sense.
- That's right.
I'll show everyone tomorrow...
that I can pull off Rie Hata's choreography.
Of course. Honey J, you can totally do it.
I was so thankful for the members.
Tomorrow is an important day.
In the end, it's a fight between the main dancers.
There's a lot of control in power.
- Leejung, I'll need your help.
- Okay.
The choreography suited me well. I thought, "What? I can do this."
I must win. There's no other choice than to make it mine.
Yes.
I have a lot of pressure because I'm the leader.
And I like to show it, especially to my sister.
She'll give me her honest opinion.
Ho!
Add your own little swagger.
You don't have to look like her.
Okay.
I don't get hungry. I don't get thirsty.
I'll keep trying until I run out of time to practice.
I feel like Teesha actually does it better than Kaea.
Teesha did so well.
I'm making sure...
that I kill it in front of the judges.
I have to worry about Teesha And Rie.
Marlee has so much passion.
I can tell that she wants to win.
You know what it's like. She keeps standing next to me.
(Focused)
She seems to be thinking, "I'll memorize it first."
Marlee memorized the choreography quickly.
I bet she's practicing now.
(She's correct. Marlee is practicing.)
Hey, that's clean.
Yes. I can't see Ibuki doing that.
Yes. I don't think Ibuki will win.
Ibuki does it better than I expected.
- Ibuki...
- She's a good dancer.
She knows how to waack,
so she keeps the movements tasteful.
When I tried the choreography,
it wasn't impossible.
I think this is a good chance...
to show that I'm not only good at waacking.
So that I can be the main dancer,
I'll do my best.
Rie, are you confident...
that you'll be chosen as the main dancer?
I usually make the choreography for a K-pop song.
I gave it to someone else.
My career began as Lady Gaga's backup dancer...
at the age of 18.
Now, I work as a choreographer.
Since I'm a choreographer, I'm used to not doing the routine I made.
Thus, BTS will do my choreography and make it shine.
G-DRAGON will do my choreography and make it shine.
No matter how big the stage is, I'm a star's backup dancer.
I've worked as a dancer that way for several years.
But this time, we'll make a dance video...
in which the dancers will shine instead of the artist.
We rarely get such a chance.
It's a chance for a dancer to receive the spotlight.
This time, I made a choreography...
for the dance video for the dancers.
So I want to be the main dancer.
- She's cool.
- She's cool indeed.
Six dancers need to compete,
so three dancers will go at a time.
But the three dancers will switch positions...
and dance three times.
They're going to each have a chance to take the center.
Maybe that's why they're doing it three times.
Every time, they have someone new take the center.
The Main Dancer Audition for the leader class starts now.
You'll switch positions anyway. You need to do well now.
Why am I going first? I'm nervous.
Let's go.
Ready? Fight!
- Let's go!
I have confidence in becoming the main dancer.
Let's go, Marlee!
I felt confident.
Honey J, don't get pressured. Just have fun.
I was so desperate.
I decided to show my real self.
- Have fun.
- Hey.
(Let's focus, Janell.)
(The center of the first group, BUMSUP's Honey J)
Let's go, Honey J. Let's go.
(Concentrating)
I'll show it properly at the front.
Hey.
Let's go!
You're good. You're doing well.
Come on, Marlee! Let's go!
(Cheering)
I decided to make it powerful as if my life depended on it.
You're so cool.
Honey J, you're so cool. This is insane.
(Her power is at its max.)
- Out of us three, I'm the best.
- Let's go!
(She's the best.)
I think everyone's attention will be on me.
(Our leader is good.)
Let's do this!
You're cool!
(I have so much respect.)
It was incredible.
You did so well.
That was crazy.
(Let's go, Marlee.)
I'm ready.
I'm about to show everyone who I am.
Honey J!
Ibuki, good luck!
Come on.
I'm so focused on making sure that I shine...
amongst Ibuki and Honey J.
(Their attention is on her.)
And I think the thing that sticks out is my big hair.
(The power of curly hair)
Honey J, don't lower your energy. Keep going.
I need to do well. I can't let them get ahead.
I'll show my unique power.
She's too locked in.
(We're getting absorbed.)
But it was too small. I wish she did something bigger.
I really need to be the main dancer.
Come on, Honey J.
I'm jealous of the Americans.
They look fine even when things are a bit awkward.
(Attacking with her gaze)
(She loves it.)
It was weak.
(Screaming)
What are we talking about?
(The center of the first group, OSAKA Ojo Gang's Ibuki)
Let's go!
Honey J, it's the last round. Have fun!
One more!
Isn't it exhausting to do the dance three times?
- Let's go!
- Come on, OSAKA!
Let's go!
So that I can show my strength with hip-hop dance as well,
I'll do my best.
She's cool.
Let's go.
I'm confident that I'll catch people's eyes.
You're cool!
She's giving it a variety.
Ibuki, let's go!
(Focused)
She doesn't have power. Like, control.
(Her eyes move to another dancer.)
Hip-hop choreography isn't something that she's the strongest at.
I definitely don't think that she'll win the mission.
I'll be the main dancer no matter what.
I'll show them until the very end.
Go, Honey J! Let's go!
It's coming to an end! Let's keep running!
Right there!
Yes, Korea!
(The first group is done with the Main Dancer Audition.)
(They nailed it.)
Let's go!
Rie, please do well!
Let's go, Teesha!
Come on, Kaea.
Let's go, ladies.
Oh, Rie Hata.
She's the original choreographer, so I'm wary of her.
My biggest rival in the leader class is Rie.
Ready? Fight!
- Let's go!
The other two should do their best.
I'll show what I can do in the center.
I needed to save my energy for my turn in the center.
I was confident,
smashing it and giving it my all.
- Three, two, one.
Let's go, queen!
I'll show everyone. They'd better watch carefully.
(Absorbed)
Go, Teesha!
She has an edge.
She's unrivaled.
Yes!
(Focused)
There you go!
(Cheering)
It's insane.
I can't see the other two.
I can only see Rie.
I had more energetic and powerful moves.
Yes, Teesha!
It isn't a song where you force big movements.
She dances in a tasteful way.
(How tasteful)
Hey!
- Rie!
- Let's go, queen!
(She's so good.)
(His excitement explodes.)
Honey J has a chance of winning. Her style is different.
- Teesha.
- Teesha? This is incredible.
Come on!
- Come on, Teesha.
- Let's get it moving!
My aura and my energy give the main dancer.
I want this spot.
(That's a good pose!)
(Expectant)
Come on, Teesha!
Breathe, Teesha. Go, Teesha. Let's go!
Rie Hata looks cool, but Teesha has good energy.
Go!
(Power up!)
(Exclaiming)
(Amazed)
(Monstrous power)
Yes, Teesha!
That's good.
Teesha is good too.
It's bold.
Crazy.
(Agreeing)
The power is a little gone.
- Bye.
(Good girl)
Come on.
Go!
- Last one!
- Come on, Kaea!
- Kaea!
One more!
- One more!
- Let's go.
Breathe, Rie Hata.
This is going to be hard.
Go!
I'm the type of dancer that loves being in the middle.
It's like my place to be in the middle.
Let's go!
Go!
(Anticipating)
(Charismatic)
Check out the energy.
The red person has an aura too.
Come on.
(Getting goosebumps)
She's really good at controlling the dynamics.
Go!
For sure, I feel like I'm stronger than other leaders.
Yes, Teesha!
I'm the person who can dance my choreography most attractively.
I've got to fight harder.
(Keep moving!)
Rie Hata!
It's unique.
She has star quality.
She has the main dancer's energy.
She made it her own.
Rie Hata did so well.
It was no joke.
Everyone did well.
(I'm not going to see this.)
(They expect hardship.)
The other two were tall.
I'm very short.
No, it was really great.
You had the main dancer's energy the whole time.
It was really good.
Rie Hata and you looked really cool. It was great.
(Breathing)
It looks like we'll go once again, right?
Please. Honey J has to go again.
Marlee ate that up too.
Rie Hata was awesome.
Teesha as well.
It's fun with the leaders.
(Breathing)
Total respects.
That is just the highest level.
(Thank you)
- Yes!
- Thank you.
Kaea and Teesha,
you guys were the most clear with the choreography.
I saw every single sentence.
I was like, "I understand that. That was a move."
"That was a ticky tick and..." You know what I mean?
For some reason, I keep on finding a lot of similarities...
between your crew and their crew.
I was literally about to say that.
I think that's going to be your challenge...
because you're always going to be compared to.
Teesha ate that up.
Kaea.
Marlee, you definitely had the most personality,
the most facial expressions, the most connection.
With your competition, though,
the whole thing may have been a little too milky for me.
What I wanted was some bits of Oreos there.
Do you know what I'm saying?
Too milky. I'm like, "I want that crunch."
Do you know what I'm saying? I want that crunch.
I wanted a little more power.
Honey J, I feel like you just have the swag.
It's the Korean swag that you just carry.
I feel intimidated when I see it. Straight up.
Power. You are a powerful dancer.
I feel like what I need from you, though,
is a little bit more texture.
Ibuki too. It's like attack, attack.
The moves may have been a little too jumbled up.
I couldn't really tell what was happening sometimes.
And of course, Rie Hata,
I feel, is all the things.
Swag, presence. Also, she's so smart.
Underlying... Underneath all of the rawness,
there is still such an intentional...
"This is why I'm going to do this."
I think I want to see the queen in you, though.
We can be soft, we can be flirty.
And what I'm looking for is someone who gives me...
the entire package.
Clear for me.
They're just too similar.
There's no point.
Even though she was more powerful,
it was like Terminator or too machine-like.
She's like the daughter. The daughter of this machine.
She killed it.
Her attitude. You could see how much she wanted it.
- But her interpretation...
- Goodness.
I feel like the levels of complexity that she's showing...
The level is just higher.
You can go as hard as you want, but her level...
Who do you like?
I want to see her.
Got it.
Unfortunately,
two of you have to dance again.
Rie Hata and Teesha.
Honey J... - Honey J and Rie Hata?
These are the two dancers...
who will dance for the last time.
Rie Hata...
and
Honey J.
(Rie Hata and Honey J)
(Relieved)
Well done. You did a good job.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
It was the best.
You did good, girl.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
I suddenly felt the pressure.
I thought I had to show them something cool as the leader,
and I wanted to get the main dancer position.
I can't lose now.
I thought about how I could do it well and effectively.
The last battle of the day, ladies.
It's the last party!
- Rie Hata is the best.
- Ready?
RHTokyo is waiting.
I definitely want to become the main dancer.
Hey! Bring it up!
Do everything you want!
I was given the last chance.
I definitely should become the main dancer.
I won't give up until the end.
Whose backup dancer...
will Ibuki be?
- Let's go!
- Ready?
Okay, let's go!
Fight!
I thought I would win.
I think my dance suits the music...
and is pleasant to watch.
Since my dance could be compared to the original dancer's,
I wanted to show myself more.
(Focused)
I must take this.
I really wanted to win.
To show them the queen,
I thought I should show them something different in the intro.
- Go, Rie Hata!
- Let's go, Honey J!
Don't look at her! Just do your thing!
(Amazed)
They're like a duo.
Let's go.
Go!
Honey J, let's go!
Let's go!
I danced my best.
I danced with 200 percent power.
(Our leader is the best.)
This is dangerous.
(Everyone is shocked.)
(It's a perfect symmetry.)
(Watch the full version on "The CHOOM.")
What was that?
She's cool.
That's our queen!
- Did you see the symmetry?
- That was amazing.
It was so cool.
This is really hard.
That was so fire.
(It was a close battle until the end.)
(Feeling tension in the neck)
- I think Honey J won.
- But...
She just overpowered it.
I want Honey J to be selected.
I don't care who gets selected as long as it's not RHTokyo.
It's going to be Rie Hata.
We won this.
Rie Hata looked so cool at the end too.
So, Honey J. I feel like she...
That battle, she killed it.
I loved her emotions over her.
I do have the respect. In the room, there was commanding there.
But then someone is connected to the music at a deeper level.
I'll announce the result.
As far as Honey J goes, your spirit is just so powerful.
It's not always just about your musicality,
your timing, or your body control.
A lot of it is just aura that's unexplainable in the room.
So, great job.
(Honey J showed a powerful energy and a unique aura.)
She's amazing.
She had an amazing power.
Applause to Rie Hata...
for creating a choreography with so many peaks and valleys.
So, again, respect to the choreography.
And it felt like you were connected to the music.
The moves became bigger because of that calmness.
I liked such feelings too.
(Rie Hata had perfect control...)
(and her connection to the music stood out.)
I don't know. It's really hard.
Yes.
This is difficult.
I really can't lose.
I have to get it.
I want to become the main dancer.
I felt a strange anxiety that I'd never felt before.
(Rie Hata went to the crew area before the result was announced.)
(Patting)
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
I showed them everything.
It was the best.
Goodness.
I was so overwhelmed with emotions that tears came out.
She's crying.
- Who?
- Rie Hata.
She has a weak mental strength.
I don't want her to be under pressure.
The main dancer of the leader class...
Please.
It's Rie Hata.
(The main dancer for the leader class is Rie Hata.)
(She did it.)
(We're so happy for her.)
(Honey J couldn't make it to the main dancer.)
It's okay.
Why are you crying? Why? No.
You did a great job.
- You did a great job, too.
- Don't cry. Yes, it's okay.
What's the matter?
Why do I want to cry?
Well-deserved.
I'd also cry if I were in her shoes.
I felt pressured, so I was glad to win.
So, I just couldn't stop crying.
Thank you so much.
With all the mixed feelings, I cried.
I'll do my best to make all the dancers shine.
Thank you so much.
You're the best!
Honey J, you did an amazing job.
You looked awesome. Good job.
I'm fine.
I wanted to win so badly.
I had the opportunity to perform all the way to the end...
alongside the world-famous dancer whom I really admire.
I'm so proud of myself.
But it feels just like deja vu.
In Season One, I lost every mission...
whenever I made it to the final.
It was so disappointing.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
It's tough.
You're awesome.
Since it wasn't an easy win,
I took it very gratefully.
Now that I'm the main dancer for the leader class's music video,
I'll make something that all the dancers feel like...
they're the main dancers.
(The following day after the Main Dancer Audition)
(6 crews are back in the fight club.)
- Good morning.
- Hi.
(Everyone arrived at Crew Agit.)
Aaliyah and Vanessa. So, congratulations, ladies.
You guys made AG SQUAD proud.
Extra 100 points.
That's crazy.
So, how would you pick your worst dancer...
with the freedom of power you have?
It has definitely...
a lot to do with attitude.
But we're not going to mention that to them.
So, it may give us an easier choice.
If you guys had to choose a crew...
RHTokyo or AG SQUAD?
So, it's us, AG SQUAD, and RHTokyo.
- We're the main dancers.
- Yes, main dancers.
We all have 100 points.
- Just give them both.
- Yes.
I'm going to watch...
how hard they work during the practice.
For example, answering loudly.
(Like this)
Or leaving quickly after practice without lingering.
Leaving right away.
That's Japanese etiquette. You know that.
Make a good impression.
At this point,
let's just fully cooperate with the main dancers.
You could be an assistant or their right-hand man.
To avoid being chosen as the worst dancers,
get along with the main dancers.
Keep that in mind.
The worst dancer loses 50 points.
Our next goal is...
not to be chosen as the worst dancers.
(Of course)
What is this? Hold on.
Director's cut.
(Director's cut?)
The audio files for each class's dance video...
include the "Director's cut" part.
The main dancers will choreograph...
"Director's cut" part.
The one and only crew picked by the main dancers...
will be featured in the "Director's cut."
(The main dancers and the directors who will select "Director's cut")
(Rie Hata, Harmz, Isla, Zari, Moana, Vanessa, Aaliyah)
Four of us could be featured.
- Or you two could be featured.
- That's right.
So, they're going to go through each video and say...
"They did it the best. Put them in it."
It means five crews will compete.
We should be picked for the "Director's cut."
What? Is there more?
In the final dance video,
check the one crew the director chose.
- I see.
- So, it'll be edited out...
after we all shoot it.
The one that is selected...
would be unlikely to be the worst dancer.
Let's do our best.
I'm so confident.
I should feel more than confident being on camera.
I thought I could get this.
Yes, it's going to be me.
It's going to be me.
I'm confident that I can take the Director's cut.
I definitely know I'm not going to be the worst dancer.
We won't know until the dance video is out.
This is really something.
There will be no point in doing it if we can't take this part.
If you're chosen, will you be safe from being the worst dancer?
I think it could set the standard.
You need to perform that part really well,
not to look like a backup dancer.
Pick us. Let us take it.
(Give it to us.)
For the middle class, you're probably...
the most capable of doing the ROYAL FAMILY's choreography.
We're not going to know because they'll pick it.
You can get it. You guys can easily do the ROYAL FAMILY stuff.
We're just going to do it.
- We're just going to do us.
- So, we're, once again,
just trying to make something...
that highlights AG SQUAD for who we are as Team Australia.
I'm very confident in us being picked for this little part.
They might go like,
"Of course, AG SQUAD is going to get picked for the Director's cut."
- No, I'm going to make it fair.
- Yes.
So, it's up to them ultimately. Who wants it more?
I wonder who it will be.
(Knocking)
- Everyone.
- Yes.
I brought someone who will help our team.
My partner, Hyojin Choi, needs...
to work on the choreography of the middle class.
Hyeily!
So, Hyeily and I will shoot...
the dance video for the rookie class.
(Joining the rookie class for Team Korea)
(Hyeily, the main dancer from Season 1 for the assist class)
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm so glad you came. Thank you.
- Thanks.
- Thank you
(Middle-class dancers gathered for the first time to practice.)
Each crew stayed together. The mood was quite serious.
We all keep each other in check.
- No, you can't be friends.
- Hi.
No, you can't be friends with them.
It seemed that everyone came with a competitive spirit...
in their hearts.
This is everybody, right?
Except for ROYAL FAMILY?
Hi, everyone.
(ROYAL FAMILY, the director crew, finally came.)
Give them a round of applause.
Everyone seemed to do their best...
to respond actively.
Do we have to sit separately for the Director's cut?
- Yes.
- Lovely.
- Really?
Cool.
She said she loved that.
(Glancing)
So, we'll just explain everything.
We'll talk about the set, the vibe,
how we're going to split everyone up, and stuff like that.
(Main dancers from each class had a directors' meeting.)
We've got lots of exciting ideas.
Little surprises we had planned.
Our video is going to be a movie.
So, for the Director's cut part,
we've choreographed eight counts,
and then we left the 2nd 8 count blank.
Come together in your team and finish it how you want to.
Eight counts are choreographed, and another eight are freestyle.
The Director's cut has 2 8-counts.
The 1st 8 count is a set choreography they gave us.
And the 2nd 8 count is totally freestyle,
depending on what each crew wants to make out of it.
(Checking the Director's cut part)
(The 1st 8 count)
(The 2nd 8 count)
I just like to give something to MOTIV.
That's always the goal.
I'm pretty confident...
because our ideas and creativity...
are much higher than those of the other groups.
I think this is a big opportunity...
to show who we are,
so I really want to take the Director's cut.
I think we haven't shown...
much of anything impressive so far.
I really wanted to take this part.
So, we're about to get started with our choreography.
The concepts were focused around me and Aaliyah.
We have the two main parts that highlight the two of us.
Vanessa's long hair and nails.
My short hair and big eyes.
Some parts don't even involve me or Aaliyah.
But the objects are kind of related to us.
The point of view is Vanessa's hair.
So, Vanessa's hair is going to be...
I'm super excited again for Vanessa and me...
to showcase what we do.
It's quite easy and something that comes naturally to me.
And I love it.
(The rookie class started their practice.)
And five, six, and...
(Watching carefully)
Since there were many details, I thought...
it might be a challenge to remember the choreography.
I've never shaken my hips that much.
I've never shaken my hips that much in my life.
I haven't used my hips for a long time.
Inside of me,
Hot J instead of Lip J.
I need to awaken Hot J.
I should awaken Hot J sooner.
AG SQUAD's choreography was sexy.
But that's different from my main genre.
So, to be honest, I was worried...
and anxious.
We're very similar in style. You know, it's AG SQUAD.
I do feel quite confident and comfortable.
- It feels more comfortable now.
- Yes.
ROYAL FAMILY was impressive and doing really well.
I could see others dancing in the mirrors.
It bothered me.
(Maiya and Kylie came back to Crew Agit after practice.)
I think MOTIV might struggle with the choreographies...
only because they're not used to it.
(She saw something.)
Worst dancer nominee after the first rehearsal.
- The worst dancer?
- Nominee after the first rehearsal.
What?
Are they saying we're the worst?
No, that is crazy.
I just don't think that their feedback was valid.
So I was feeling very ripped off and betrayed.
We were thinking about attitude.
I think it's just maybe slipped up on professionalism a little bit.
We directed them to work on their...
Instead of the director's cut, they were doing...
TikToks.
When a choreographer directs you to...
do a specific task, it's very important...
that you continue to do that specific task.
It's so funny.
They're doing TikToks.
- It's so funny.
- ROYAL FAMILY.
So when I noticed they were doing TikToks...
And this one.
(Excited)
I'm watching.
And right now, I don't like that. Doing TikToks.
Yes.
It just shows us that they were...
mentally not present.
Regardless of how we act during training,
it all really does come down to how you perform.
I know that we'll be able to...
- kill it.
- This is so funny.
Holy...
(OSAKA Ojo Gang's Agit)
- Wait.
- What?
There's a piece of paper.
What is it?
What? The worst dancer nominee?
"Worst dancer nominee after the first rehearsal."
"Please do your best to avoid being titled the worst dancer. Let's go."
Wait. Is it saying that we're the nominees?
(Silence)
The worst dancer nominee. Us?
That's nonsense.
I think there were some dancers that didn't match...
ROYAL FAMILY's style of dance.
(During the middle class practice)
(Tilting)
(OSAKA Ojo Gang's middle class struggled with the choreography.)
(Watching carefully)
I knew how well she danced prior to coming onto the show.
But it's different.
Little bit less strong compared to her fellow teammates.
In terms of the choreography,
they might think we're less powerful.
That makes sense.
I was expecting it, but it's never nice to receive it.
That we're the worst.
After receiving the worst dancer nominee,
I thought I should be more enthusiastic...
to escape from that impression.
It's dangerous to be the worst dancer,
and I want to avoid that no matter what.
I decided to try harder.
It's cold. Hello.
This is Americano for you.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
Milk for Ibuki.
Thank you.
I forgot if you said iced or hot.
Hot.
She got us coffee this morning.
She was very kind to all of us.
Director.
Hello.
This is so dope. Amazing.
No matter how big the stage was,
we dancers were artists' backup dancers,
or we put on makeup on our own.
We only had that experience for many years.
And there was a makeup table for all of us.
I realized that we were making a dance video...
with the dancers in the center.
I was touched.
(Startled)
(A separate green room for the main director)
What brings you here today?
I am the main director.
There was a director's room just for me.
It felt like a special treatment.
- Hello.
- Hi.
(Here comes the director.)
Thank you for waiting.
- Nice. You look cool.
- Is it nice?
(Ibuki shows an extreme reaction toward Rie Hata's tooth gems.)
(The leader class dance video shoot begins.)
(Monitoring)
(Ibuki's right next to Rie Hata.)
- I look too sharp, don't I?
- No, it's awesome.
- Awesome?
- Awesome.
Rie Hata was my teacher.
And I was her student.
What matters the most is...
to listen to what Rie Hata says.
To avoid becoming the worst dancer.
We had a history...
as OSAKA Ojo Gang versus RHTokyo.
But from now on, I'll listen to what she says.
I'll be a good student.
My service to you.
(The rookie class dance video set)
So cute.
(Rookies, welcome.)
As you can tell right now, we're all getting ready.
It will finally come to life with...
all the hair, all the makeup, and the location.
I can't wait.
Today, I'm not Lip J. I'm going to be Hot J.
Okay. Here we go.
(Eyes focused)
We love the location. It looks great.
Oh, it's so gorgeous.
Uwa, you just have to swipe this way.
Okay.
(Uwa reflects Vanessa's feedback immediately.)
Avoiding the worst dancer title is my highest priority.
I'm going to do my best.
You want to see our photos?
(Kylie shows off the photos.)
Don't play with the duo.
No, I'm not nervous.
We did feel really confident going in there.
Look at me. Oh, my gosh.
That's how cold I was. Look. I'm trying to...
Sorry. TikTok time.
We'll begin now.
(ROYAL FAMILY won't put down their phones.)
For ROYAL FAMILY, they could lose focus sometimes.
Girls, you know what to do. Just give it all.
Can I have some lotion, please?
I think she can't understand.
(Laughing)
- Lotion.
- Guys.
Go full out, please. Just so then the camera can...
Just want to see it for the angle-wise.
It seems like they didn't understand what we were trying to do.
Let's go.
(The directors are focusing.)
(Kylie ended up falling in her part.)
- You're good.
- It's okay.
My fall could've affected the worst dancer,
which is okay because it's a fall.
Sorry, queens.
Where is it? Is it the tent?
(The middle class dancers head to the green room.)
We have to go to the backup dancer zone.
The main director zone and the backup dancer zone.
- Can I see?
- The main dancer...
What's the difference?
It's in the crew's color.
This was supposed to be my spot.
Are we not even allowed to talk to the director?
The main dancers' room was really nice.
It was very different.
(The directors head to the horseback riding track.)
We're going to be on horses today.
I know. What the heck?
There will be real live horses.
- Cool.
- I know.
Coming on the show, I never thought,
"I'm going to be riding a horse when I'm over there."
Not going to be...
(4 mysterious men appear from the other side.)
Five male dancers.
Oh, my gosh. Yes.
Shirtless. Leather pants.
Oh, my gosh. This is going to be like...
- This is crazy.
- So good.
(The male dancers are right behind them.)
- Oh, the helpers.
- Hey.
- Nice to meet you.
- Lovely to meet you. Isla.
I'm not going to lie. They were all pretty good-looking.
Nice.
(Laughing)
(They left strong impression on "Street Man Fighter.")
(The krump dancer KNUCKS of PRIME KINGZ)
(RKLS of BANK TWO BROTHERS from "Street Man Fighter")
(Dancer BOLT)
(Dancer FEELIN')
Who are these boys?
Thank you for joining us today.
(They can't stop laughing.)
That was way more fun than it should've been.
It always feels exciting, you know?
It will create a good reaction from whoever views...
our video to...
Ready, Lommel? You're going to be a movie star.
(The directors appear on horses.)
- They're shirtless?
- Sick.
They look so great.
When we first walked in, ROYAL FAMILY was...
already on top of the horses.
That was like, "That would've been really cool to do."
What the?
It's the director's chair.
- Did you have one too?
- Yes.
(I used to give orders.)
(But now, I'm a backup dancer.)
We're not even allowed to watch?
How can you do this to us?
Put more space in between, so we can watch between them.
Shame, losers.
(Tease-ya)
- Unbelievable.
- The senior.
Hey, pay attention.
- Pay attention.
- Sorry.
- Be obedient.
- Make sure to answer her.
I didn't want to become the worst dancer.
I shouldn't do anything to get on her nerves.
Let's kill this, okay?
Girls, just arms on this one.
Make sure... In line with your shoulder.
So, not like this. Not too high. Just nice and straight.
There's still a possibility of becoming the worst dancer.
So I want to do my best to the end...
with a positive attitude.
Australia, tiniest bit out. A little bit.
They were taking it as if we were the back dancers.
Australia. Spread out a little more.
Hey, they're trying to play the game.
It is what it is.
(Filming the dance with male dancers)
(Let me see.)
Oh, my goodness. KNUCKS.
(Shocked)
Ri.hey, close your eyes.
Does Ri.hey know about this?
- Of course not. How would she know?
- Oh, my gosh.
(KNUCKS and Ri.hey are a famous dancer couple.)
(Serious)
I have a role of a spy.
I'm sending it to her now.
- Isla, you know what?
- They should've done it.
- My teammate, Ri.hey's boyfriend.
- Did you see that?
(Exclaiming)
I hope she's not going to be mad at me.
(The undercover agent is reporting live from the scene.)
Ri.hey, they're taking your man.
(Screaming)
I was just looking at them. At the boys.
Is that...
I wish that would have been me.
Gosh.
They all looked good. They all looked nice.
But the one that was with Zari... I was like,
"What's your number?"
(Laughing)
(Results day of the Class Mission)
Class Mission results.
So intense.
Scary.
Gosh, I'm sweating.
I have goosebumps. I'm so excited.
Gosh, I'm so nervous.
(Here comes the host.)
(Clapping and cheering)
It feels real when he comes in.
A pride-fueled global dance battle between the fiercest women...
from around the world.
World of Street Woman Fighter. I'm the host, Sung Han Bin.
The pride of each crew is at stake in this Class Mission evaluation.
The main dancer will receive 100 bonus points,
while the worst dancer will receive 50 penalty points.
And these scores will affect the final crew rankings.
The main dancers of each class acted as the director.
In the leader class, Rie Hata of RHTokyo.
In the middle class, Isla, Moana, Harmz, Zari of ROYAL FAMILY.
In the rookie class, Aaliyah and Vanessa of AG SQUAD.
These dancers were given the ultimate power...
to pick the worst dancer of their class.
This is an important moment...
where the director's decision may change the ranking of countries.
(Clicking her tongue)
A country's ranking.
Goodness.
- This is making me so nervous.
- Yes, this is...
You know, the thing about Street Woman Fighter...
When do dancers have an opportunity...
to be the star of their own music video? Right?
To have an opportunity like this is literally once in a lifetime.
The world-renowned dancers that enter this show.
They know that, going into this show.
There needs to be something that will really surprise us.
First, you need to have the moment.
You need to have that inspiration.
I'm excited and I'm curious.
I can't wait to see yours.
Yes, me too.
I can't wait to see theirs, as well.
And the leaders'. Everyone's.
I wonder how it turned out.
The directors of each class...
will now check their class's dance video...
and choose the worst dancer.
(Nervous)
On the spot?
No, I'm scared.
Which class will be first?
First of all, which crew did the director of the rookie class...
choose to become the star of the Director's cut?
Being chosen for...
the Director's cut is the most important.
I think it will be you.
I have a good feeling about it.
Gosh, I'm a bit nervous.
Our crew has to end up in the Director's cut.
I'm confident we'll be chosen for the Director's cut.
(Rookie class practice day)
Okay, guys. Let's start.
(Cheering)
Let's go.
To not be chosen as the worst dancer,
I should always give my best in everything.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- Everyone's seen their part?
- Yes.
We'll just start by doing the Director's cut.
All right.
(Directors Vanessa and Aaliyah show them a draft of the choreography.)
(Amazed)
(Flexible)
(I recognize that choreography!)
(It was AG SQUAD's highlight move during Choreography Selection.)
(Shocked)
(They used their highlight move for the Director's cut choreography.)
(Clapping)
So nice.
It's very detailed.
(Lip J starts practicing right away.)
It's so fast.
(The rookies officially kick off their practice.)
And flip, flop.
I think the choreography is just a sketch...
and the competition is about how each crew brings it to life.
BUMSUP is definitely going to style it iconically.
I've already lost my choreography.
I have to make it onto the Director's cut.
It suits the styles that I and Kylie are used to.
Yes, perfect.
So already, we've got the upper hand.
(A mysterious warning letter)
"Worst dancer nominee after the first rehearsal. Rookie class."
What?
Are they saying that we're...
We think it's funny.
That's insane.
This is getting on my nerves.
We were just confused and found it funny.
We do things quite quickly and so...
There were times when we'd just be chilling,
as well as just playing around, having fun.
But honestly,
they haven't picked us as worst dancers yet.
They only nominated us.
We can show them...
that we're not the worst dancers in the room right now.
ROYAL FAMILY are known to be quite strong performers,
so I feel very confident.
I want us to get the Director's cut.
At all costs. We can't lose.
One, two.
I am comfortable doing these types of movements.
Flip, flop.
I keep letting go of your hand here.
To be honest, right now I'm feeling...
a bit concerned. I feel quite anxious.
I think teamwork will be crucial.
Practice!
We will work hard to master the Director's Cut and get it!
Aaliyah and I will choose the Director's cut...
based on ability,
just because it's directed by us...
so we want to make it look good.
(The rookie class video shoot location)
(Director's seat)
This is where I belong.
(Bursts out laughing)
Okay. So we're about to do the Director's cut.
RHTokyo, be ready.
(Director's cut, RHTokyo's Reina and Rico Hirai)
RHTokyo.
We're serious about getting...
the Director's cut in this mission.
The two of us kept practicing.
I want us to take the Director's cut.
I love the way they execute it.
(Keeping an eye on them)
(Director's cut, RHTokyo's Reina and Rico Hirai)
She ate.
She's like, "You out."
She was like, "You're not cutting this."
"You out."
(Tense)
There wasn't a single moment where I was blown away.
BUMSUP, let's go.
We practiced our teamwork a lot,
and we worked on our facial expressions.
Now, let's go.
(Director's Cut, BUMSUP's Lip J and Hyeily)
I love Lip J.
Literally the best vibes.
Best vibes.
I feel like they feel it through a little bit more.
All right. Let's go.
Music, please.
(Director's Cut, ROYAL FAMILY's Maiya and Kylie)
It's so gutsy.
(Focused)
I think I did really well.
They're strong.
The other teams were just like that much.
Let's go, OSAKA Ojo Gang.
Music, please.
I feel like, in a way, their lines...
are a softer version of our own.
It was a bit underwhelming.
MOTIV, your turn.
Me and Kaidi did prepare a lot for Director's cut.
(Director's cut, MOTIV's Kaidi and Abby)
The takes that me and Kaidi did felt strong.
Nice.
- Let it sit. Let it marinate.
- Okay.
I love MOTIV, as well.
But I don't love the way they did the beginning.
I did like this.
I love how gutsy they were.
I think the shape looks nice.
They finished the movements.
It's all about the tiny details.
This is hard.
Now, evaluation of the rookie class dance video will begin.
(Let's go!)
Let's go!
Vanessa has that star quality.
- And Aaliyah.
- Yes.
I want to feel it.
(Focus mode: On)
Here we go.
(Listen on Spotify)
("Flip Flop" by Gummy and SINCE, produced by Padi)
(Make some noise!)
Vanessa!
Come on, Kaidi!
Gosh!
Gosh, that's hot.
Goodness.
Yes, Lip J!
Hot J!
That's so hot.
You're killing it!
Fire!
Yes, ladies.
Gosh, you guys look so good.
- Hot girl energy!
- That's insane.
(Screaming)
(She's beautiful!)
(That's amazing!)
Goodness. Her hair is so cool!
What? Let's go.
Venessa!
Period!
Three, two, one.
Here it comes!
- This is it!
(Nervous)
I believe we have a decent chance.
I'm like 100 percent confident.
That's the Director's cut.
(Which crew won the Director's cut for the rookie class?)
(Director's cut for the rookie class, )
(RHTokyo's Reina and Rico Hirai)
(We did it!)
(Our members are the best.)
(Disappointed)
(It's too bad.)
RHTokyo got it.
Let's go!
(We won.)
(Cheers of victory)
(Director's cut, RHTokyo's Reina and Rico Hirai)
This is the BUMSUP's choreography.
This part is really nice.
Gosh, girls.
- Those two are scary.
- Yes.
They pulled it off well.
- Hot J!
- Yes!
(Explosive reactions)
(The directors are proud.)
I've been wanting to see more of her.
You killed it!
(Our rookies are good.)
This is fire!
Reina!
We're so sexy!
(Embarrassed)
Come on!
(Watch the full version on "The CHOOM.")
All right.
That was so good.
(Listen to "Flip Flop" by Gummy and SINCE, produced by Padi...)
(on Spotify.)
- Thank you.
Period.
They did that.
You guys killed it.
(They absolutely love it.)
Period.
You guys are so hot. Oh, my goodness.
- Did you see that?
- Yes!
That jiggle was scary.
- Hey.
- It came out well.
It came out so well.
The video is cool.
(Fight Judges Evaluation for the Class Mission)
Very nice.
Okay, main girls.
- This is the moment right here.
- Yes.
- This is the moment.
- Totally.
I think Aaliyah and Vanessa did a good job of giving themselves...
a really memorable moment.
Great concept.
- Absolutely.
- Okay. So...
two moments that hit us were...
- the non-dancing parts.
- The non-dancing parts.
Yes, that's so true.
- Yes.
- More of the pictures.
So, outside of BUMSUP's choreography,
they failed to impress us with a certain choreography.
- Yes.
- I totally agree.
But RHTokyo took the director's cut.
No. You guys still did well.
- This is incredible. I'm so happy.
- Thank you.
I hope we'll also get the Director's cut.
It'll be incredible if we get two.
It'll be incredible. We'll be the strongest crew.
I'm upset about the Director's cut.
Why?
Still, it's the most important...
to avoid getting picked as the worst dancer.
Directors Aaliyah and Vanessa,
please decide on the worst dancer.
- All right, guys.
- Period.
(Sighing)
ROYAL FAMILY had a big sense of presence.
- They did.
- So it can't be them.
You guys did great.
It's obviously not you guys.
I think it'll be OSAKA Ojo Gang.
I feel like it might be someone from BUMSUP.
I don't know. It can be anybody at this point.
Imagine them picking...
RHTokyo as the worst dancer.
And then there was the Director's cut.
- That'd be crazy.
Are you still thinking the same?
Yes.
I also think, strategically, RHTokyo, us, and ROYAL FAMILY...
We're among the three that are high-ranked right now.
We might give them the worst dancer...
to get rid of the points that they just received.
It might be funny...
if we gave the worst dancer to the Director's cut crew.
It'd be like, "You got the feature. But we took away your points."
Getting the Director's cut as well as the worst dancer?
That's a bit...
(Take this!)
That won't happen, right?
- That won't happen. No way.
- No way.
That won't happen.
AG SQUAD's Aaliyah and Vanessa,
please pick the worst dancer of the rookie class.
(Let's take deep breaths and relax.)
I don't know what they're thinking.
(Breathing out)
I'm really nervous.
I'm so scared.
Okay.
So...
(Could it be us?)
the worst dancer is...
(The worst dancer of the rookie class is...)
Is...
(The rookie class's worst dancer)
ROYAL FAMILY.
(They try to stay calm.)
So the reason why we ended up coming to this decision is this.
It turns out that ROYAL FAMILY... You guys ended up...
getting distracted and started doing TikTok and...
(I see.)
TikTok was a bit too much.
Did they do TikTok?
We never did TikTok.
(During the rookie class' practice)
That's so funny.
(While everyone was absorbed in practicing)
They're doing TikTok.
I heard music. I turned around and they were filming TikTok.
(Moreover)
Do you know that TikTok? It's like...
(What?)
- It's funny.
- Okay.
- Right now?
- I guess they want to film it.
I'm watching right now.
I don't like that they're doing Tiktok.
Yes, I know.
(Their passion for TikTok didn't end during the dance video shoot.)
We're singing. We're having fun, like...
That's right. That's how it is.
No, I do mind.
Parris would probably break your phone.
You don't do that on a job.
Yes. It was actually funny to watch their Director's cut.
It didn't level up. It was like, the same.
It's not just the way you dance. It's also the things...
- behind the scenes, so...
- It's crucial.
- Yes.
Attitude reasons?
It's just a little weird on my side, but...
- They gave them the reason.
- That's right.
- I personally think we slayed that.
- Yes.
Yes. It's just...
I wouldn't say that we're the worst dancers.
We were actually giving energy in the room.
Thus, the worst dancer of the Rookie Class,
ROYAL FAMILY lost 50 points.
Losing 50 points is big.
That's cruel. That'll happen to any crew that loses.
That's so dumb. Choosing us.
Wouldn't you go for a team that has zero points?
That'll put them in the negative.
No, they're trying to cut their biggest competitors.
- We're a threat to them.
- Yes.
Yes.
They want revenge. I've never seen them so serious.
They've always been playful.
Maybe they'll choose each other.
Let's watch the dance video of the middle class.
- Let's go!
(We're totally excited!)
It's our turn.
The middle class' main dancers and directors are...
ROYAL FAMILY's...
Isla, Moana, Harmz, and Zari.
Were there any difficulties about directing a video...
while leading a big group of 24 dancers?
I think all the girls that were a part of this mission...
were so strong and so efficient.
It made the process really easy.
We aren't happy with them.
(Unhappy)
(How was the middle class's practice?)
Five, six, seven.
(The middle class's group practice with 24 people)
(Full of power)
(ROYAL FAMILY is checking the dancers' choreography.)
We'll put the formation with the stickers on the board.
Then everyone can see it and go that way.
Kaleece and Alysha.
And then Bella and Mona... Fantaye?
If we watch it, the front should obviously be stronger.
- I don't think they'll accept it.
- No.
Okay. Alysha, over here. Kyra.
Ruthy and then Kaleece.
Next line, Ruu, Rena, Hyojin Choi,
no: ze, Asuka, and Hana.
And then...
- OSAKA, can you be in this corner?
- OSAKA.
And then Korea will be...
- adding on to our diagonal.
- Okay.
All Korean and Japanese dancers were in the back.
We were totally invisible.
Not at all.
We just felt like they looked like us.
We put those who looked the strongest at the front.
It was quite sad.
We're in a position where we have to work incredibly hard...
despite being invisible.
We dance as a group and there are 24 people.
We aren't very visible unless we're in the first row.
The Director's cut!
Without getting chosen, the three invisible crews will be...
in danger of becoming the worst dancer.
(Minami of OSAKA Ojo Gang)
In terms of the crew's Director's cut,
how each dancer shines...
will be important.
(OSAKA Ojo Gang comes back to the Crew Agit after practice.)
If we can get the Director's cut,
the tables will be turned.
(Spotting something)
What is it?
What? The worst dancer nominee?
"The worst dancer after the first rehearsal?"
"Do your best so that you won't get picked. Good luck?"
Don't be funny!
Of course, I'm not happy.
But I have no choice but to do my best.
We have to choose the worst after that, right?
I feel like it would motivate me if we got the Director's cut.
We really have to do our best.
Director's cut. We need to be different.
Unfortunately, we lost the choreography,
so we ended up being the backup dancers for this clip.
However, that doesn't stop AG SQUAD from shining.
We'll always give it our all no matter what. We don't back down.
Since it's the Director's cut,
I wanted our crew's unique side captured in it.
I thought it would be selected if it was a bit more unique.
We just want to showcase...
that strong and fun energy while doing something that...
I feel like the other crews don't really have.
Since we couldn't become the main dancer,
I thought, "We really shouldn't lose this opportunity."
"We should really get the Director's cut."
We're the nominee for the worst dancer,
but I think how much we could change that image...
is our challenge.
We should show them a hundred times more.
I want to do my best.
We'll start the Director's cut.
(ROYAL FAMILY is monitoring seriously.)
Who was able to execute and perform...
the eight count that we choreographed the best?
What would also fit best with the rest of the video...
that we had created and come up with?
(The crews are using the time in between to practice.)
We used props. We used the bandanas.
We thought of the camera angles when making it up.
(Meanwhile, )
(OSAKA Ojo Gang seems to be in thought.)
(Let's talk about it now!)
Could you check this?
(Kyoka approaches ROYAL FAMILY.)
(What's going on?)
(Attentive)
We want to take it like this.
(Showing them the choreography section)
Nominees for the worst dancer. We're just the nominee.
I think how we showcase our qualities in the Director's cut...
will be a great opportunity.
Honestly, I really want us to take it.
I really don't want to get this title.
Ojo Gang ladies.
Let's go.
(Let's see.)
Five, six!
(Nice)
(She gets startled by the camera as it came too close.)
(Smiling)
She looked a little bit confused.
We were given a short time for the Director's cut.
It felt like it was hard to realize that.
Last one.
One more, and tell him to go faster.
Cleanliness and maybe tidying up their moves.
Even like the cut going to the side was all good.
There were parts that stood out,
so I think it was nice in that sense.
Let's rehearse.
We'll go right away.
I really want to show them my best...
so they would want to select ours.
We shouldn't become the worst dancers.
Let's go, BUMSUP.
Let's go.
They didn't change too much of our choreography,
but it was also creative.
BUMSUP's cut was my favorite.
Nice, girls.
- Fire.
- Nice.
(Staring)
OSAKA Ojo Gang and BUMSUP...
seemed to be lacking a bit.
I thought, "Good. We would be taking it."
"RHTokyo's Director's cut"
"Free choreography section"
Lit.
I love how everyone has thought of something different.
Right.
Okay. Next one. MOTIV.
Five, six.
(Perfect synchronization)
(She noticed something.)
They're not looking at the camera.
Right.
(Fantaye is the only one looking at the camera.)
I liked it. Did you guys like it?
- Yes.
Fantaye is...
So good. She's the only one, though.
Fantaye.
That one. Yes.
Bella?
Can anybody hear me?
Can they hear you?
There's no purpose to this.
(Checking)
- Should we just keep that in mind?
- Yes.
Okay.
Fantaye was just strong.
Her presence was just right in the camera.
Whereas the other girls, I feel like they were holding back a little bit.
As well as their performance.
(Free choreography section)
AG SQUAD.
(AG SQUAD goes last.)
AG SQUAD was the original owner of this choreography.
Our style and AG SQUAD's style are very similar.
I'm very curious.
If it was dancing-wise and creativity-wise,
it would be us.
(Relaxed)
Let's go.
(Anticipating)
(AG SQUAD's Director's cut)
(Free choreography section)
That's so creative.
I feel like that first part was changed a lot.
Yes.
I couldn't really notice our first choreography that we gave.
So as much as I loved the second part,
we had to keep the first part...
because that's part of the Director's cut shoot.
Amazing work today, girls.
(All the shooting ended.)
(The ROYAL FAMILY directors monitor everything carefully.)
- I think we've decided.
- We've decided.
For Director's cut is...
Which crew will be selected for the Director's cut...
in the middle class?
We will start evaluating the dance videos...
for the middle class.
Let's go, girls.
Let's watch it.
This is exciting.
Let's go!
Ready? Fight!
(A dolphin appears.)
Good vibe.
- That's your boyfriend!
- Goodness.
Come on, hottie.
Goodness!
(It's amazing!)
(Listen on Spotify)
("Ridin'" by Lily, Jiwoo, and Kyujin)
Crazy!
Nina is the center.
They're totally in sync.
That's a huge scale.
Yes, girls!
They lined up well.
(This is it.)
Go, Bella!
(Standing ovation)
(Smiling)
(Feeling shy)
(Me too!)
Kyoka!
Kyoka looks cool!
Goodness!
(They're shocked.)
Work! Good job!
Three, two, one.
(Please let it be us.)
It's the next one.
I looked forward to getting the Director's cut.
Three, two, one.
(OSAKA Ojo Gang gets the Director's cut...)
(for the middle class.)
(We did it!)
(We got it!)
It's Ojo Gang.
(Disappointed)
(Director's Cut: Ojo Gang Ruu, Minami, Hana, Kyoka)
Goodness!
Take us to a different wicked world, yes!
Let's go!
(This is what I'm talking about.)
Let's go, Fantaye!
(They nailed it!)
Epic!
(It'll be a legend.)
Awesome! Oh, my gosh.
What the heck?
(Period!)
Congratulations!
We did it!
(Fight Judges Evaluation for the Class Mission)
(Standing ovation)
Let's go.
(Amazing quality)
Experience does matter.
The fact that ROYAL FAMILY is known to do this.
They do this.
They know how to do this.
They know how this thing should look like.
Especially the rope choreography at the end,
that just put the nail in the coffin to me.
I think nothing was missed. I have no notes.
I have nothing to say.
- That was so good.
- Well done.
We did it.
(Getting emotional)
Don't cry.
Good job, girls.
You guys shine in that. Good job.
You did an amazing job.
- We worked so hard.
- You did a great job.
We know we gave it all.
Even though we weren't chosen,
I don't have any regrets.
The crew in the Director's cut of the middle class was...
OSAKA Ojo Gang.
Thank you.
They were the worst dancer nominees.
It was so disappointing because ours was good.
When OSAKA Ojo Gang was selected,
I wasn't so happy about it.
Which section was going to fit in...
with the rest of the video was the base.
When they do it with the camera,
Kyoka fights the camera and then...
pulls on Minami.
She does the roll-ups.
It was just a fire. We just loved it.
- Thank you.
We were surprised and so happy. Thank you.
We've been through a lot,
and we didn't expect it.
So, we're really happy.
The directors of the middle class. Isla, Moana, Harmz, and Zari.
Please choose the worst dancers.
Turn around.
I don't think we stood out much.
Somehow...
I felt like we could be the worst dancers.
I was pretty nervous.
I couldn't really find RHTokyo and BUMSUP...
throughout the video.
(Unnoticeable BUMSUP and RHTokyo at the back of the group dance)
I didn't get a setup for Team Korea.
Where is RHTokyo? Where is BUMSUP?
That's the only thing that could've been better.
We had our idea.
So, we had people.
But we also could not come to a decision.
All four of us see different people and different things.
Dance-wise, we see BUMSUP is the weakest.
- Next one. Hyojin Choi.
- Yes.
In many sections, we were at the back.
Since we didn't stand out,
I was worried we might be picked as the worst dancers for the reason.
They might think we were invisible.
Performance-wise, we see that MOTIV was the weakest.
(MOTIV's shooting for the Director's cut)
(She noticed something.)
They're not looking at the camera.
If we go with the strategy,
we've got 50 points less now.
AG SQUAD is directly ahead of us.
ROYAL FAMILY.
(Losing 50 points after being chosen as the worst dancer by AG SQUAD)
(Rookie Class Worst Dancer, Maiya and Kylie of ROYAL FAMILY)
- We're coming third right now.
- Yes.
If we're thinking about playing the game strategically,
we're on top of the table right now.
Isla, Moana, Harmz, and Zari of ROYAL FAMILY.
Please choose the worst dancers of the middle class.
Okay. So.
I don't believe it'll be us.
I don't think we'll be the worst dancers.
We've chosen it. It is...
(Who is the worst dancer of the middle class?)
Isla, Moana, Harmz, and Zari of ROYAL FAMILY.
Please choose the worst dancers of the middle class.
Okay. So.
I don't believe it'll be us.
I don't think we'll be the worst dancers.
We've chosen it based on strategy.
So, it's AG SQUAD.
- I knew it would happen.
- Yes.
I saw that coming.
Now, we're second equal.
I feel like AG SQUAD just made it easy for us to do.
Yes, that's right.
We can say that it was so helpful during the whole process.
It's just that when you call us, we're going to call you.
Actually, I like to say that.
They're going to think about it strategically.
If they take our points, we take their points.
So it all comes down to the...
Yes. So, we're even now.
So, the biggest weakness of the class,
the worst dancers, is from AG SQUAD.
Alysha, Kaleece, Kyra, and Ruthy Baby.
Why do you think you're chosen as the worst dancers?
Like she said, it's a strategy.
We'll take it on the chin.
Why did you choose us?
You knew you would lose 50 points.
Are they upset?
(Yes)
It's quite interesting.
It's scary.
(Finally, here it is. The best quality ever.)
(Leader class dance video)
Oh, my gosh.
(Who will be the main director's choice...)
(to feature in the Director's cut?)
(I can't believe what I saw.)
(And)
The worst dancer I chose...
I was angry.
I felt like we did our best.
Actually, I don't think it was reasonable.
I'll beat them all.
K-pop mission?
That's my expertise.
We'll win this by all means.
We have many choreographers for K-pop.
If you guys are good dancers,
we can make it.
If you have to copy it exactly,
you have to be a B-girl.
We're able to execute just as well as you girls.
It's doable, but we don't know if you'd execute.
Lastly, we'll watch the dance video of the leader class.
Rie Hata!
I can't wait!
Let's go!
I've been waiting for it.
I hope you'll like it.
Come on, Marlee. Get that Director's cut.
Oh, my gosh.
(I'm nervous.)
We'll definitely get this.
It'll be her.
I feel like it's between me and Teesha for the Director's cut.
My expectations are really high.
And this is the leader class.
This is the only video...
where the director and the choreographer
are the same person.
So, she knows exactly how it should look...
- and how it should feel.
- Yes.
That's the difference compared to the other two videos.
Street Woman Fighter is...
a survival competition that is only for females.
So, I wanted to show...
how cool, controlled, classy,
and fantastic we are in the leader class dance video.
It might feel totally different from other videos.
(The first day of rehearsal for the leader class)
(Rehearsal of a teacher and a student)
- You're working hard.
- Ibuki. You came first.
I was trying to avoid being picked as the worst dancer.
If I were Rie Hata,
I'd choose me as the worst dancer.
My team is the only one...
that keeps attacking RHTokyo.
They might still be...
like students around the teacher.
Rie Hata will overpower them.
(RHTokyo and OSAKA Ojo Gang are competing from the beginning.)
The crew that we, OSAKA Ojo Gang,
will defeat in a Double loss...
is Team Japan, RHTokyo.
(Why did I do that back then?)
(Laughing)
Since Rie Hata became the main dancer,
it was clear what our positions were.
Rie Hata became my teacher.
I became a student.
I'm scared. I can understand...
why Gabee gave you two sets of eyelashes.
I don't want to be the worst dancer.
I believe Rie Hata plays fairly,
so I'll be fine as long as I do my part well.
We're using a conveyor belt.
It's cool!
(Ibuki reacts to Rie Hata actively.)
- I love it.
- Yes.
It looks amazing.
Everyone gave her a lot of compliments.
Did you create the whole thing?
Yes.
I like the house idea.
It's really cool.
It's personal. It's nice.
I could give her good compliments if I didn't struggle with language.
I should just focus on my performance.
And don't move your left hand.
(Ibuki asks questions in Japanese.)
(Honey J can't catch up on them.)
There is a slight delay in interpretation.
Asking something and interpreting it.
Whenever I do that, I end up causing delays.
It could make me look bad,
so I said nothing.
I'm in the front, and one, two, three.
I started missing a few things that she explained.
(Learning it quickly)
I felt like I moved half a beat slower than others.
Five, six, seven, eight.
The one who took a long time to learn the choreography was...
Honey J.
Ibuki also...
lacks power compared to other leaders.
(Watching the formation during the practice)
Maybe switch?
(Ibuki and Honey J are pushed to the back.)
My circumstances are none of Rie Hata's business.
She might think I'm not enthusiastic at all.
(Honey J practices alone even on a break.)
(Communicating in English)
I can't blame anyone,
but I feel...
pitiful in that situation.
To avoid becoming the worst dancer,
I'll have to win the director's favor.
(The second day of leader class practice)
(Honey J arrives early.)
I arrived an hour earlier than the time we agreed to meet.
I have to do my best.
(A suspicious piece of paper)
What is this?
(Honey J became the worst dancer nominee.)
It felt like a confirmation.
Even if it were me, I'd have chosen myself yesterday.
I was discouraged because I wasn't able to communicate in English.
But that's my story.
When creating a performance,
personal emotions must be excluded.
I should be more enthusiastic today.
(Ibuki also spots the same piece of paper in her Agit.)
(Ibuki also became the worst dancer nominee.)
(Ripping immediately)
(No more kind Ibuki)
I tried my best, but it didn't work.
It's easy to come up with reasons...
to make me the worst dancer.
(Worst dancer nominee 1, worst dancer nominee 2)
Everyone thinks I'm not good at hip-hop.
- Good morning.
Catering.
(Sullen)
I gave up on being a good student.
Even if I become the worst dancer,
I swear I'll stand out the most in the dance video.
(Filled with spite)
Kaea and Honey J, switch. Honey J...
Right side of me.
I can do well even in the back.
I never know what might happen in the end.
I'll have to do my best.
- Rie.
- Yes.
Can you ask where her formation is?
- Last?
(Honey J's winning strategy 2)
(Getting close to her duet partner Kaea)
Good job.
- I have a question.
- Yes.
And then...
(Honey J's winning strategy 3, studying with Ako)
- Stop?
- Yes.
This is the Director's cut.
I was thinking about moving like this.
You should use your face a lot.
- Right?
- If the result is good,
I'll be able to redeem myself.
I'll have to do my best tomorrow.
(Will the worst dancer nominees turn the tables on set?)
Did you see my camera angle?
The choreography is like this.
And I turn the camera.
I hate to be the worst dancer.
For now, the Director's cut.
I must get it.
I need to win for AG SQUAD.
So I'm not going to get the worst dancer.
I need to earn that Director's cut.
(The first Director's cut is Kaea.)
It was a bit scary because everyone was watching.
But I'm very used to shooting.
Five, six.
(Watching sharply)
(Satisfied)
She's done that many times before.
She knows how to look good.
I felt confident.
At the end of the day, she'll pick the best.
I'm used to having that...
automatic switch on, just be like,
"Give it my all and perform to the lens."
Both Teesha and I are used to it.
(Director's cut, Teesha)
Yes.
Teesha's cut will be very useful.
Yes!
(Loving it)
Everyone seems to focus on their expressions or the mood.
So I decided to focus on my moves.
I had a few plans.
Five, six.
(Director's cut, Honey J)
(It's nice.)
(Honey J changed the last ending pose.)
I think she might like it.
Isn't that awesome?
(Next is Ibuki.)
I'm not nervous.
That's the freestyle dancer's strength.
I only do my best to shine more than others in the dance video.
(The freestyle dancer's ending)
(What is that?)
Raising her leg or showing her skills.
She put on the best performance.
(The last Director's cut is Marlee.)
I was happy that I wasn't the first to go.
Because I got to see what would look good on camera.
(Marlee kept monitoring other leaders while waiting.)
Put your hands forward the camera. It looks better.
Yes. So good.
I utilized not only my dance ability,
but also my understanding of camera work.
Perfect.
She seems to have a good sense of space recognition.
I'm hoping that I will make Director's cut.
Because I don't want to be the worst dancer.
(Never)
I need storytelling eyes, expression, and energy.
Her and...
They're neck and neck.
Which crew got the Director's cut...
chosen by the leader class director?
We will now begin evaluating...
the leader class dance video.
At your service.
Show us.
- I'm so scared.
- BUMSUP.
Leader, let's go.
(Let's go.)
And?
I'm scared.
(Listen on Spotify)
("ECHO!" by HOSHI and WOOZI of SEVENTEEN)
Give me a story. Give me content.
(I can feel it.)
(Go, Kaea.)
Oh, her hair.
She looks cool in the office wear.
Let's go.
Cute.
(There's my girl.)
Honey J's face is fired up.
- That's me.
- Come on.
(Make some noise.)
Let's go.
(In awe)
I got chills right now.
You can't see me in the group shot.
So cool.
Come on, Teesha.
You and Rie are the same.
What's she doing?
Cool.
(Charismatic)
(Teesha and Ibuki's chemistry)
- You look sexy.
- That's hot.
(That's my partner.)
You ate it up.
Everyone looks good in the video.
The office girl theme is a cliche,
but it's so witty.
Let's go, Teesha.
Fire up.
You nailed it.
(The moms' chemistry)
So hot.
(I love it.)
(Pause)
What's she doing?
The conveyor belt's crazy.
That was so hard on that.
Moving on there is crazy.
- It's a good structure.
- That's nice to watch.
- Oh, my gosh.
- See that's...
Levels...
Let's go, Ibuki.
Let's go.
Let's go, Honey J.
(3 seconds before the Director's cut)
(2 seconds before the Director's cut)
(1 second before the Director's cut)
It's coming next.
- After this?
- Yes.
Okay. It's coming up.
I feel really confident in what I did.
I just hope that Rie trusts what I did.
I ate up the Director's cut.
So I really hope I do get it.
I thought I did good.
I hope I get the Director's cut.
- It's coming. Please pick me.
- Let's go.
(3 seconds before the Director's cut)
(2 seconds before the Director's cut)
(1 second before the Director's cut)
(Marlee got the leader class Director's cut.)
(Really?)
(That's our leader.)
It's Marlee.
Marlee.
(Bitter)
(Director's cut, Marlee of MOTIV)
(I'm so shy.)
Let's go.
Let's watch.
You better throw that paper...
(Eyes opening wide)
(Thrilled)
That's insane.
That's E for "ECHO!"
She's a genius.
I like how there's a lot of dancing.
It's a great video.
She did a good job of directing.
(Cheering)
That was fine.
The formation shined.
- That looks so sweet.
- That was neat.
That's so cool.
- Yes.
- Oh, my gosh.
Not yet.
- It isn't over yet.
- Is there more?
It isn't over yet.
A post-credits scene.
- Did you like it?
- Hi.
Mom, I'm hungry.
It's tteokbokki and kimbap.
- We'll enjoy the food.
- They look tasty.
Kimbap and tteokbokki.
- Hey.
- They're so tasty.
(Watch the full version on "The CHOOM.")
(Listen to "ECHO!" by HOSHI and WOOZI of SEVENTEEN, )
(produced by WOOZI on Spotify.)
It was absolutely insane.
It was like a movie.
I loved how it was like...
- storytelling.
- Yes.
It was like we were watching a movie.
But then, when she gives us the food, the paper is...
from that movie.
- "Inception." - "Inception."
She made sure each member shone.
How cool. The leaders don't disappoint.
(Throwing)
We're done! Done!
Really?
All from one brain, though? One brain?
Choreography and directing?
This was her chance to be like,
"I'm the artist."
"All of this energy that I have,"
"that I give to every other artist..."
"This is my time."
"Give me one chance."
The opportunity that was at hand...
- You didn't take it for granted.
- Yes.
And you have the skills to make it happen.
Director Rie Hata of RHTokyo,
please decide on the worst dancer.
What do you think?
Who caught your eye?
It's not going to be you.
- I hope not.
- It shouldn't be.
Maybe Ibuki.
It wasn't her style.
Strategically, a Japanese crew...
will want the other Japanese crew to go.
Let's see.
Ibuki and Honey J.
Maybe Honey J.
You're nervous, right?
Right?
Marlee did really well this time.
The facial expressions and such.
There was a possibility of changing my decision,
but other leaders stood out so much.
Compared to them, she had fewer eye-catching scenes.
Everyone did well.
She didn't stand out.
Well, each dancer's level was so high...
that I expected everyone to do more than her usual best.
I wish she had more power.
The one I chose as the worst dancer is...
Please.
I'm scared.
BUMSUP's Honey J.
(The leader class's worst dancer, BUMSUP's Honey J)
Oh, no.
- Oh, no.
- It sucks because...
they don't have any points.
It's cruel.
What an interesting woman.
You were the coolest.
She's talented but interesting.
Due to the language barrier,
Honey J must've struggled more than anyone in the group.
Despite that, she competes with her dance skills.
Honey J could've made herself shine more than the other five...
with her dance skills...
as well as her aura and sense of presence.
So I honestly think that she could've shown...
more power.
Well, my situation can't be an excuse.
Even if I say that I truly did my best...
I don't have anything more to say if it appeared that way.
(Honey J suddenly stops.)
No. Smile.
Smile.
You can cry. What's the big deal?
- Just cry.
- It's okay to cry.
(She can't suppress her tears due to the overflowing emotions.)
Oh, man.
I'm close to tears too.
Honey J probably worked as diligently as I did.
You must be upset since you've worked so hard.
It isn't about being chosen as the worst dancer.
During this process, you felt...
a sense of loneliness.
I made so much effort to keep my energy level up...
and work with them.
I continued to feel bad.
The worst dancers of the three classes...
have been decided.
The rookie class's worst dancers...
are ROYAL FAMILY's Maiya and Kylie.
The middle class's worst dancers...
are AG SQUAD's Alysha, Kyra,
Ruthy Baby, and Kaleece.
The leader class's worst dancer...
is BUMSUP's Honey J.
- We made it out alive.
- We did it.
It's cruel.
For the rookie class and the middle class,
there are 2 or 4 members.
So the focus isn't on an individual dancer's skills...
since teamwork is important.
But for the leader class, there is one member.
Getting picked would cause more damage.
Each class's worst dancer...
brought minus 50 points...
and gave the crew a fatal blow.
We're at the very bottom in terms of the score.
Of course, I'm angry.
We lost 50 points.
It's really sad and heartbreaking.
I did feel a bit bad for our crew.
RHTokyo currently has 100 points.
No points have been deducted.
However, the match isn't over.
You can get ahead of this competition...
by getting picked as the best director.
Yes. Let's go.
Who will it be?
The best director will receive a strong benefit...
that'll help the crew begin the next mission...
with an advantage.
We have minus points.
So Vanessa and I want to have an upper hand of power.
RHTokyo is so ahead right now.
So I want to win that.
Among the three classes,
which class will win the best director?
I'd pick AG SQUAD.
This is ours.
The best director of the Class Mission...
that was chosen by the fight judges is...
Now?
(RHTokyo members come together.)
Let's go, ladies.
- Go, ladies.
- Who will it be?
Who is it going to be?
It'll be annoying if it isn't Rie Hata.
- Please.
I'm scared.
I'm so nervous.
The best director is the leader class's main dancer,
RHTokyo's Rie Hata.
(The best director, RHTokyo's Rie Hata)
Rie Hata.
Well done.
This video right here?
- It's just a piece of art.
- Art.
All from one brain, though? One brain?
Choreography and directing?
Rie really made all of the leaders...
look like superstars.
I feel like Rie really just represented...
all the choreographers in the world to be like, "Hey,"
"this is what choreography is."
It's not just making dance moves.
Choreographers are directors.
(Enjoying happiness)
We all have that dream to create these high-level videos.
She had a chance. She proved it.
We had no need for any discussions or debate.
She was unanimously selected.
Thank you.
The moment my name got called,
I could feel that I received recognition.
I'm in a good mood.
Okay. Next time, we're going to take their points.
Do I agree? I don't know.
She had the creativity.
But I feel like we had on her.
I don't think there's any point in being, like,
discouraged or upset about not getting the best director.
The advantage is a plus,
so we just want to, like, move forward from that.
As a result of the Class Mission,
BUMSUP took the heavy burden...
of losing 50 points.
RHTokyo pulled themselves to a higher place...
by winning 100 points.
With the new rankings in place,
each crew must face...
the next mission for survival.
After this mission,
we'll have the first crew to be eliminated...
on World of Street Woman Fighter.
(Already?)
(An elimination?)
I don't think we'll get eliminated.
Which crew will it be?
- We're not going to be eliminated.
- No.
I didn't feel worried.
I don't think MOTIV will be on a chopping block for elimination.
We'll put our pride on the line and protect the crew,
BUMSUP.
The next mission that'll decide on the first crew to be eliminated...
- What could it be?
- What is it?
Okay. Let's proceed.
It's the World of K-pop Mission.
Here it is.
Of course, it's K-pop.
It's our mission.
- We're going to do well in this.
- K-pop.
Which crew will take...
a globally acclaimed artist's song...
and use the most charismatic concept and the most unique idea...
to complete the performance?
I have so much confidence.
I can do an amazing job on this mission.
We have two dancers who are well-known in the K-pop scene.
We'll really show them.
K-pop mission?
This is my expertise.
I'm not a dancer from Korea,
the origin of K-pop,
but I think I'm good...
at making cool K-pop choreography.
And that can feel scary.
I'm like coming into a new house.
These other crews are more familiar...
with dancing to K-pop music.
In this mission, we're really going to have to prove ourselves.
I'm nervous, but I'm also confident.
A head-on battle between countries.
You will either get eliminated...
or eliminate the other crew.
The evaluation for World of K-pop Mission...
where crews will battle against other crews...
will be made from the fight judges' evaluation...
and the global online public evaluation voting.
The right to choose the song and the matchup...
will depend on the best director of the class missions.
(Best director? Me?)
I get to decide?
I had the benefit to decide the matchup.
This was advantageous for us.
That's a mean advantage.
Very advantageous.
The mission song will be revealed.
(We're curious.)
I'm looking forward to it.
The songs.
I wonder whose songs they'll be.
The song for the aespa match...
is "Armageddon" with an explosion of intense beats and power.
"Armagdddon?" I love that music.
This is the one.
(A hip-hop dance song that blends old-school and trendy styles)
We could eat this song.
- Drama - I see.
Very iconic.
I feel like this is really us. "Drama."
("Whiplash" by aespa)
(Moving)
This is nice.
I think BUMSUP would do better...
since they have more experience...
in creating choreography for girl groups.
Gabee made this.
(This is the part.)
Whiplash
(Everyone...)
(does the move.)
Nice.
I love them.
I like all of them.
I'm not confident in winning this one.
We could make it with a different concept.
- It's going to be hard.
- I think it's going to be hard...
if we think about making something else.
It's difficult to make something new and something better...
when it already has a famous choreography.
I want to avoid them.
The songs for the JENNIE match...
(Jennie's fan is shocked.)
(Here it is.)
- Okay.
I know this song. LA.
No. I might cry.
But the main choreography...
- is too strong.
- Right?
("Like JENNIE" by Jennie)
(Who wants to rock like Jennie?)
We'll have it.
Leejung has to do this.
I wanted to do "Like JENNIE" in my class.
Shall we do it?
Let's do it.
Amazing.
This is "ExtraL."
("ExtraL" by Jennie)
(Glancing)
This is extra-large.
This is for ROYAL FAMILY.
I love Jennie.
Jennie's song would be nice.
This is going to be fun.
Come on.
Don't play.
This is going to be fun.
I'm looking forward to the last song.
- The songs for the JENNIE match...
- Let it be hip-hop.
The songs for the G-DRAGON match...
(It's G-DRAGON!)
(Yes, it's hip-hop!)
This is really nice.
Ready?
(Are you ready?)
- I am a good boy - I am a good boy
Crazy. This is crazy.
This is going to be good.
Goodness.
This is amazing.
My choreography.
(Tokyo power)
I think it would be easier and fun to choose the G-DRAGON match.
Choose this one!
(We recommend it!)
Aiki would be good with this.
I think Kyoka and Minami go well with this song.
This is the hardest song so far.
(I'm excited.)
I think aespa's songs would be better...
if you want it to be more K-pop.
But would they give it to us?
One of the two crews...
will definitely be in danger of being eliminated.
The rule of the World of K-pop Mission...
is choreography copy challenge.
Copy?
We're going to do each other's choreography.
The two crews in the match...
will each create a choreography for one part...
among the two copy challenge parts...
and copy the choreography of the opponent crew.
It's important to make a choreography...
with your crew's strength...
that the other crew cannot pull off well.
(Our strength?)
And we'll strategize on what their weakest point is.
We have to make something they cannot copy.
It's a copy challenge.
You can put about 100 turns.
I definitely don't want to go against MOTIV.
They have a great breakdancer called Logan.
I can't copy that.
I want to stop going against Rie Hata.
There's a big gap in the scores.
So I don't want to go against them.
So Rie Hata will decide who will get what song?
She gets to pick.
She gets to pick. What a shame.
I wanted everyone to show their best performance.
I wanted it to be a close battle.
I want people to think it was a relief...
that Rie Hata decided on the matchup.
(After the class mission)
We did it!
I'm the best director.
(I'm cool.)
That's...
- That's the queen.
- That's cool.
It was the best.
- It was the best.
- The jump.
Jump.
We're in first place.
That's right. Two times in a row since the battle.
First place two times in a row.
Great.
(Selected as the main dancer of the leader class)
(RHTokyo earned 100 points.)
(Rie Hata was selected as the best director...)
(while receiving high praise from the judges.)
I think the fact that we have 100 points...
will act as an advantage point.
The game has started.
The next mission is the K-pop mission.
That's my expertise!
It's time for us to shine.
How...
What?
This is so annoying.
- Aaliyah and Vanessa.
- What?
It's not a strategy to choose people...
who got points.
Why would she choose people with points?
That's what I'm saying to Maiya.
Do it to BUMSUP. Do it to Ojo Gang.
They can't...
It wasn't for strategy.
It was for a personal reason.
You've literally made us go even like...
We both have 50 now.
Because now, it's even.
Goodness.
They...
- We wanted to choose RHTokyo.
- RHTokyo.
It's hard because we couldn't...
They put in extra effort to make sure they weren't...
even like doing good.
They can't say no to that.
They came early, and they practiced.
There's no shame in our reasoning.
Honestly, I think for us, it's attitude.
They're doing TikTok.
We genuinely had our reasons.
It wasn't an emotional reason for us.
Ours didn't hurt as much because they just did it back.
We knew it was coming.
Seriously.
I was so worried that...
now we are both deducted 50 points,
and Rie Hata is still on 100.
We kind of shot ourselves in the foot.
- We're chilling.
- Yes.
- Zero points.
- Period.
Not terrible.
That's better than a negative.
I do wish maybe...
I got the Director's cut.
Give me a little something, like extra five points.
I don't know, but...
zero is better than negative.
Gosh.
I'm just glad we're safe.
We're calling Kyoka.
(They're glad.)
Kyoka.
We'll report the result.
We got...
the Director's cut!
Awesome.
She's happier than us.
It felt like we finally earned the fruits.
We finally had the results.
I was very happy.
It's a good start.
It was really nice.
There were many of your cuts.
- That's right.
- Right.
What about the score?
We have zero points. No plus points.
That's a relief.
We don't have minus points.
It's the same with MOTIV.
MOTIV has zero points.
MOTIV also has zero points.
It was a relief we didn't get minus points.
And four of us got the Director's cut.
I was really happy about that.
We shared the happiness with her.
Nothing goes our way.
(BUMSUP's Agit)
Honey J.
I hate this show.
That's right.
It makes you a fool.
It crushes your pride.
The worst dancer...
- is BUMSUP's Honey J.
- Goodness.
(BUMSUP will start the next mission with minus 50 points.)
I had a hard time.
I know it because I've experienced it before.
(Even on "Street Woman Fighter,")
(Honey J was the final worst dancer in the leader class.)
I felt very sorry for the members.
I'm really sorry.
- What are you saying?
- Why are you sorry? Please.
I know it's hard.
I feel so unmotivated.
We know how much you've tried.
There was nothing but dance in my life.
My pride was crushed,
and so was my self-confidence.
It's okay to lose.
We'll help you.
You can rest for a bit. We'll work really hard.
How many K-pop choreographers do you think are in this crew?
We can do well.
Getting rid of minus 50 points is a piece of cake. It's nothing.
We'll win 5,000 points.
Don't shed any more tears. Close your tear ducts.
Don't waste your tears.
The members comforted me.
It was a consolation.
"I'm the leader, so I shouldn't waver."
I had that resolution.
I'll come to my senses and work hard.
Let's kill everyone in this mission.
- Let's kill everyone.
- Seriously.
When I came back to the Crew Agit,
everyone was crying. It was a big mess.
I'm so annoyed.
I'll awaken the dark dragon inside me.
I'll really show them this time.
World of K-pop Mission.
(Excited)
(Revealing the list of matches for the World of K-Pop Mission)
(Decided by RHTokyo's Rie Hata, the best director)
Let's see how far they'll toy with us.
Let's go.
(Rubbing)
Let's see.
Who are we going to get? Which song are we going to get?
I feel fuzzy. We don't know who will go against who.
(What are the list of matches Rie Hata decided on?)
- AG SQUAD or BUMSUP.
- Yes.
The only tricky thing is getting AG SQUAD.
They're probably the strongest crew with our style.
- Yes.
It doesn't really matter who we get.
We're going to rip you up.
(You know about my personality, right?)
She's going to put us up with ROYAL FAMILY.
I think the whole competition wants to see that.
They're going to sit there with their popcorn.
They'll want to watch ROYAL FAMILY versus AG SQUAD.
To be honest, whatever...
Rie chooses, I know that we'll kill it.
Had I been Rie Hata,
I would've chosen MOTIV.
I also think it'll be MOTIV.
They have a hip-hop style.
They have the commercial and original style.
So I expected MOTIV and RHTokyo to compete against each other.
I think it's going to be us against OSAKA Ojo Gang.
I think that too.
Each member has unique charms.
The two crews are balanced in a similar way.
If RHTokyo chooses BUMSUP,
it'll be a face-off.
Show us the list of matches.
- Let's go!
- BUMSUP!
Come on!
Oh, my gosh!
(RHTokyo versus BUMSUP)
(Is this how it's going to be?)
- Okay.
- She doesn't let go of her target.
I had a lot of thought about it.
As RHTokyo's opponent,
I chose BUMSUP since Korea is strong in K-pop.
They're the strongest when it comes to K-pop.
They must have a lot of tips and know-how on K-pop...
as well as experience.
I'll face them fair and square.
- She knows how to be on a show.
- She must've watched the show.
Hey, let's have our revenge this time.
It's smart of her.
RHTokyo is in first place, and we're in last place.
Rie Hata bit us.
But it was a mistake.
I can't wait to see Rie's choreography.
I know. It's bound to be fun. This is the best.
If we beat BUMSUP,
we'll be the winner in all three missions.
Please.
But is it okay with the show...
if BUMSUP gets eliminated?
Even if we don't do anything,
we'll be able to beat them in a relaxed way.
Oh, snap.
She said she wanted that easy win.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Marlee.
I want to see RHTokyo and BUMSUP compete...
for G-DRAGON's song.
Wouldn't it be amazing?
I don't think Rie Hata will pick G-DRAGON.
I don't think she'll do it since she has worked with him.
All of them...
must expect me to pick G-DRAGON's song.
(Rie Hata surprises everyone by picking Jennie's song.)
I told myself that I wouldn't choose...
a match I could easily win in.
I chose Jennie's song because I haven't worked with her.
I'll challenge myself.
Jennie!
(It's lucky that we got Jennie!)
(BUMSUP is in a festive mood.)
- Yes!
- All right!
Okay.
(She's especially excited.)
I loved it.
Jennie is an artist...
with whom I've worked on for four songs.
I already have so much data.
I looked up so many interviews.
No one understands this song better than me.
I can do a great job in this match.
This is our match.
- It's the hottest.
- Yes. It's the hottest.
You can't underestimate Team Korea though. They're Koreans.
This is theirs.
Korean pop. That's K-pop.
Oh, my gosh. Gabee, we're going to kill this.
I know.
I'm so freaking excited.
Honey J, I'll avenge you. Don't worry about a thing.
I'm still torn about this one.
ROYAL FAMILY and...
(ROYAL FAMILY expected AG SQUAD to be their rival.)
(What will be Rie Hata's choice?)
AG SQUAD.
I want to see a close match between them for this mission.
(They have similar energy and vibe.)
(They picked each other as the worst dancer...)
(and ended up getting the same score.)
(With Rie Hata's decision, they'll have a rematch.)
- Oh, yes. Okay.
- I knew it.
Okay. No, it's all good.
They're going to want to prove...
- our points.
- They're going to be hungry.
For goodness' sake.
- We knew this would happen.
- Yes.
- Okay. Which song?
- Which song?
AG SQUAD.
I chose aespa.
If ROYAL FAMILY or AG SQUAD work on this song,
they'll be able to liven up the atmosphere.
We'll be able to do whatever they come up with.
We can definitely make them cool, still.
Can they do what we do?
We'll make sure that the new generation is strong...
like the old generation.
Dramamama. Yes. "Drama" is nice.
Yes. I like "Drama."
I think they'll expect...
- the same vibe.
- Yes.
I don't think we're the same.
And I think we have a lot to show.
I like that we got them...
because we can do what they can do.
I'm very confident that AG SQUAD can win.
Are you ready?
(Which crew did Rie Hata choose as OSAKA Ojo Gang's rival?)
When the crew was revealed, I went,
"We're set!"
It's good. Nice.
(She's highly satisfied with the rival crew.)
(Meanwhile, MOTIV's reactions are the opposite.)
- OSAKA Ojo Gang?
- You know what?
It's us versus OSAKA Ojo Gang.
- I'm not mad about that.
- Yes.
They'll waack.
But we knew that we were going to have them.
Hold on. We don't know which song we'll get.
Ruu, Uwa, or Ibuki...
will want a song by a female artist.
It'll be great to get a female artist.
(OSAKA Ojo Gang left the fight zone first.)
Which song do you want?
Jennie or aespa.
Is that what you want?
(I see!)
So they should challenge themselves with G-DRAGON's song.
(The two crews will compete with G-DRAGON's song.)
(No way)
- How scary!
- She's bullying us.
She's bullying us.
(We like hip-hop.)
G-DRAGON!
- We're going to slay.
- Yes, we're going to do well.
We're going to the good boys, guys.
And I think that she's a MOTIV supporter.
I think that was her doing us a favor.
I had a feeling that she wanted to give MOTIV a chance.
Okay then.
If that's their mindset, we'll be the same.
(Just you watch!)
(MOTIV will face OSAKA Ojo Gang for the G-DRAGON match.)
(MOTIV is having a meeting to decide on a part.)
Obviously, we're going to use Logistx.
I'm trying to think of something they can't do.
The "La la la" part is a buildup.
There's a lot more we can do with this.
Let's take a strategic approach.
Waacking is the only thing they can't do.
If we add a waacking move they can't do, we'll win.
Ibuki, you'll be able to show them.
(GD match, Part A of "GOOD BOY")
It has to be Part A.
I think they'll want Part A.
They won't back down...
even if their hair gets pulled out.
(Knocking)
(Startled)
- MOTIV?
- Yes?
(MOTV visits OSAKA Ojo Gang's Crew Agit.)
- Hi, girls.
- Hi.
(MOTIV versus OSAKA Ojo Gang, Who will get which part?)
Let's not talk about the part we want.
(Nodding)
So, did you hear the music?
Yes.
Which part would you like?
How about you?
(Tense)
There might be a difference in opinions.
I could feel a little bit of tension.
(A war of nerves)
The parts are very different, right?
Yes.
Do you have a preference?
How about you?
(She gets a headache.)
Okay. We can't tell them what we want.
We need them to reveal.
"So, which one do you want?"
"How about you?"
"Which part do you want?"
We kept going back and forth like that.
Neither one of us wanted to say it first.
Don't you have anything you want to do?
Maybe.
There was a bit of silence when none of us spoke.
"What will happen?"
- Shall we just tell them?
- Yes.
Okay. So, we'll go with A.
- With A?
- Yes.
(Grinning)
We want B.
(Happy)
- I'm thinking the "POWER" part.
- Yes.
For us to do?
(The negotiation for the GD match ends peacefully.)
Don't listen to this conversation.
We got A!
We won!
(They're in the best mood.)
We already won.
(We already won.)
MOTIV will be in danger if we take this part.
They're giving us Part A, which is easier for waacking.
Thank you.
You can't change the piece.
So how are they going to...
It's just funny to think about them trying to pick up my breaking moves.
That's going to be really bad for them.
They're going to do this thing.
- Whiplash.
- Right.
We should do Whiplash.
Yes, we will.
Whiplash is upbeat.
So, we felt like we could make something exciting for section B.
- Hi, girls.
- Hey.
AG SQUAD came into the room.
I was thinking, "Oh, no. What if we want the same?"
Which one do you want?
We're happy to hear what you want to do.
We thought we'd probably suit Whiplash better.
(Watching their reaction)
Okay. We can go with that.
I was a bit surprised.
We're a bit taken aback.
We'll do A, you do B, Whiplash.
- Is it okay? Are you okay with it?
- Yes.
So, which part do you want?
Which part do you prefer?
We do, "This that pretty girl mantra."
"This that flaunt you" and "down in L.A." This part.
I thought about highlighting...
the orientalism of Mantra.
This part is for copying.
(JENNIE match: Section B "Like Jennie")
It has a tempo that we can work with well.
Jennie, Jennie.
We're really good with this mood.
- Let's say it at the same time.
- Okay.
On the count of three. Okay?
- Three, two, one.
(What...)
(will be their choices?)
- A.
- B.
(This is good.)
There are two people who are well-known in K-pop.
I've never been this confident while doing the WSWF.
Honey J, I'll get revenge for you. Just wait and see.
(Negotiating the choreography copy is complete.)
Lip J, I'm so mad.
Let me know something I can say in English...
- To them?
- to dominate them.
Things you can say to dominate them.
You can find a lot of expressions here.
- What is that?
- It's an app.
- Okay.
- Here is a free talk menu.
- We can create a scenario.
- Okay.
- Look. My role is... A dancer.
- A dancer.
And the other person...
is a very rude dancer.
- Rude.
- A rude dancer.
Oh, my gosh. So rude!
(Laughing)
And I'll set a situation.
Let's begin the conversation.
Listen to what it tells us.
Okay. Bring it on.
You think you can beat me?
You must be joking.
Get ready to lose.
What? How old are you to say like that?
(What will the rude dancer say?)
How old are you to talk like that?
Age doesn't matter in dance battles.
That makes sense.
It understands us well.
You're dead.
There are stars.
- Click the star. You're going down.
- Okay.
"You're dead" might sound scary when translated literally.
"You're going down" is used when you win...
in sports or games, so it sounds more natural.
- Not to be so rude.
- You're going down.
- Yes. Right.
- It teaches me better expressions.
You should stop saying, "You're dead."
You're going down.
You're going down. We're going up.
- We're going up.
We're going up.
Finally, it's the mission we're good at.
- That's right.
- Let's stop losing.
Let's show what we're good at now.
- Yes!
- Okay!
- Let's go!
- You're going down.
You're going down.
(OSAKA Ojo Gang is taking a break.)
I practiced until the end even yesterday.
Look at that.
It looks tasty.
I'm starving, so I'd eat anything.
I want something sweet.
Let's bring it to Crew Agit to share it with everyone.
Let's eat it at Crew Agit.
- Let's eat.
- Thanks for the snack.
(Sniffing)
(Good)
I can smell apples.
I like the balance of taste between apples and coconuts.
I like that it's a healthy snack.
It's crunchy.
(Laughing)
I can't stop eating.
- Isn't it good?
- It's good.
It's so tasty, so I can't stop eating.
- Did you finish it?
- Yes.
This is so tasty.
(Recharged with tasty snacks)
Let's go back to practice.
- Who wants to practice?
- Me!
Okay. Let's do it slowly.
Five, six, seven, eight.
We really want to showcase Danica...
because she's so talented with...
her backbend and tricks on the floor,
as well as Aaliyah and Vanessa. They're very good at...
stuff on the floor.
I do feel like they would think it's challenging.
(aespa match: Section B Whiplash)
We love doing fast-tempo movements.
I feel like that would be a challenging part for AG SQUAD.
(GD match: Section A "Good Boy")
I don't think any dancers can do what I do.
No one can do Ibuki's waacking.
When OSAKA Ojo Gang watches our copy section,
they're going to feel stressed.
If you have to copy it exactly,
you have to be a B-girl.
We have worked with numerous artists,
so I'm confident we have a good understanding of K-pop.
It won't be easy to copy.
I created it, incorporating all Rie Hata's iconic movements,
so it feels like it's a package.
It'll be a real challenge to copy.
I don't think anyone can.
(The first elimination mission, World of K-pop)
(Fiery dance battles for survival or elimination)
(GD match, OSAKA Ojo Gang vs MOTIV)
We're going to win.
I don't think they're the strongest crew.
We choreographed something you'd never be able to copy.
You think you can pull up?
I'm ready to see you all try to learn our choreography.
It won't be a problem.
We can stand out even more in a K-pop mission.
Ojo? More like oh, no.
(aespa match, AG SQUAD vs ROYAL FAMILY)
We have a stronger performance average standard than AG SQUAD does.
AG SQUAD has a sense of...
an older, mature approach to the dance.
Let's put on a show. Bring it.
Let me show you who's the queen.
Being an original member of ROYAL FAMILY,
I'm not overwhelmed.
Cheers. Let's give the people what they want. Put on a show.
BUMSUP and RHTokyo.
(JENNIE match, BUMSUP vs RHTokyo)
In this K-pop mission,
I know how to win easily.
You know we're one of the strongest crews...
in this K-pop mission.
Sisters, we're sorry.
The thing is that RHTokyo is just way better than you.
What? What did she say?
You are going down.
Dramaday.me