Honor to the Exalted One,
the Worthy One, the Fully Enlightened One.
Honor to the Exalted One, the Worthy One,
the Fully Enlightened One.
Honor to the Exalted one, the Worthy One,
Ma, why are you praying here?
Do you even know whose plot this is?
Sort of.
It's a prayer for the future.
I ask the sacred beings to bring
me a plot like this one.
Oh, I think they'll grant you your wish.
For a million baht.
Ma?
Are you done?
The owners wanna pay respects.
Oh.
Hold on just a second.
This way, Ma.
You can be buried in a
shared plot like this.
And be close to your parents.
It's comfortable and reasonable.
Please don't listen to her.
I'll buy you your dream.
Getting a million is easy these days.
Get away from me.
Your cigarettes stink.
Mm-whah!
Try paying me back what I lent you, first.
You hear me, Soei?
It's a few hundred thousand, isn't it?
I don't know.
- I only remember the good things in life.
- Isn't that practical?
- Hey.
- Don't step over them.
And Sew…
Why do you always get this wrong?
You put the duck and chicken butts facing
your grandparents' faces again.
How does it go?
M?
YAFANG ZHENG QINXING ZHOU
M.
Come and help us.
I laid the mat down for you, Ma.
You must be exhausted.
Hm?
Bad boy!
Wait for the ceremony.
Qing Ming is sacred.
We honor the dead, not silly games.
Give me a break. I'm here aren't I?
His family couldn't bother.
Well, that's nice.
Very pretty.
- Yes, everybody came out today.
- I see that.
Is it hot?
Not bad actually.
I guess you won't be coming?
I'll light some incense for you.
Okay?
- Oh, Ma.
- Rainbow.
- Say hi to Ahma.
- Smile.
Say hi to Grandma.
Morning, Grandma.
- Morning…
- It's once a year, Kiang.
Good--
We honor our ancestors.
Rainbow and Pinn have
never paid their respects.
Oh.
Wait a sec.
Scatter these on top.
What a face.
Oh.
I said scatter, not dump.
Can't you even try?
Huh?
- So lazy.
- What does it matter how we do it?
The ancestors are up in the clouds, Amah.
Can you not be such a qi-chou for once?
Hm?
A good-for-nothing slacker.
Ma, you shouldn't be up there.
You could fall.
They'll be scattered by the wind anyway.
Stubborn as a mule.
Come down, please!
You're looking for trouble, Ma.
Let him do that.
Ma!
Come down before you break your neck!
- No!
- Hey, Ma!
Ma!
Someone from the family will
need to fill out some forms.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Bye, Ma.
Sis,
- you gotta go fill out the forms.
- Excuse me, nurse. We need help.
I have to go.
I need to take Rainbow to the store
I'll leave you guys money
to pay for today.
I left my bike at your house.
- I need to get it.
- Oh yeah.
Why don't I ride back
to your house with you?
And then…
I'll come back and stay with her.
That's ridiculous!
I mean, Kiang lives out in the boonies.
It'll take you too long.
I'll stay with her for now.
Alright.
- Okay.
- Go.
Out.
M!
Are you going by the MRT, Uncle?
Yeah. Why?
Could drop me off there.
Now?
Oh.
Okay. Here. Let's go.
Thanks.
See ya later, Sew.
This place is full of talismans, guys.
Ah!
Evil spirit!
I'm scared of ghosts! Take that!
- Wait, where'd it go? Where'd it go?
- A measly four viewers, today?
Ma, everyone can hear you!
Ma…
Why don't you relax?
You've been on your feet all day.
Did you read my text?
Another computer for gaming.
Why do you wanna use my card?
You have your own card, use that.
It's maxed out,
the bank threatened to freeze it.
I hope they do that!
Teach you a lesson.
And if your internet gets cut off again,
I won't pay for it.
What did you say when you decided to
quit school to become a game caster
from our living room?
You'd be rich in no-time.
You would rent your own house.
You'd give me an allowance.
I wanna to retire when I'm 60.
I know you do.
Don't kick a man when he's down.
It hurts.
When Amah went to the hospital,
she mentioned to the doctor that she's had
stomach aches and blood in her stool.
So they did tests while she was there.
This morning, I got the results.
Amah has cancer.
It's in the final stages.
She probably has 12 months.
You're dead!
Geeze,
they won't listen.
Man…
Anyway,
M, I expect you to spend time with her.
But don't mention her diagnosis.
I don't want her to worry.
What'll you give me to go see Amah?
My time is money now, yeah?
HONEYHANIYAH:
GET THE GHOST
MUIII:
THE TV'S ACTING UP AGAIN
MUIII: CAN YOU COME
TAKE A LOOK FOR AGONG?
You need to keep updating the app.
That's why it's freezing.
Uh.
Hm?
My Agong says you need to eat more.
You're too skinny.
Hm.
How do you know what he said?
All his grunts sound the same.
Actually, I made it up.
He probably said you're blocking his view.
Ah-uh.
Hey.
Whoa, Agong!
You still got it!
Your diaper feels full.
I'm gonna change it, okay?
Mm-hm.
We're going down.
You know you're a grandparent's dream,
Mui?
A graduate from nursing school.
Is that true, Agong?
Who…
do you love the most?
Seriously?
You're hurting my feelings.
Maybe I'll leave you alone tonight.
Do you ever think about
doing something else?
When do you ever have time for yourself?
Agong gave me advice once.
He said to get a high-paying easy job.
So why don't you?
I'm doing that already.
This belt is pure silver.
It's worth at least 10,000 baht.
- That's amazing. Thanks.
- Your dad's not around any more.
Thank you.
But Agong wanted you to have something.
- I'm very grateful.
- And I will keep it safe for you.
You might pawn it for a computer.
- Ma…
- Hm.
Agong was a sly fox.
He divied up his inheritance a while ago.
But he didn't want to reveal anything
until after his death.
Which means I'm the lucky
one to get all the grief.
- So…
- The flowers are here.
Did he leave me something
else for helping him?
Helping him? You?
Of course not!
He left almost everything to Mui.
Including the house.
Your dad's siblings didn't
get much either.
Agong only left them
a little bit of money.
TALAT PHLU STATION
The train heading towards
Talat Phlu Station
has departed
from
Mahachai Station.
Amah?
HOW TO MAKE MILLIONS
BEFORE GRANDMA DIES
Damn ancient.
VINTAGE-STYLE SHOPHOUSE
IN TALAT PHLU AREA,
NEAR GREAT FOOD.
CONVENIENT FOR COMMUTING,
NEAR THA PHRA STATION.
CONTACT M THANAPAT
Who's that out there?
Hello?
Amah.
It's M.
I just wanted to come and say "hi."
- Oh.
- I miss you.
You're the third.
Your uncles Kiang and
Soei came by this week.
Yeah?
What's going on?
Why the visits all of a sudden?
I came to see if your
leg's healing properly.
Open up for your only grandson?
So, how you doin'?
Have you eaten yet?
Yeah, noodles.
I got some for you too.
They're still warm.
It's not time for my meal yet.
Where did you get the noodles?
From that famous beef noodle place.
I had them specially make up
a mix of offal that you love.
You have the tendons,
tripe,
some liver and flat-iron steak too.
You won't believe how tender.
I'll fix it up.
You know, I pray to the goddess Guanyin?
I don't touch beef.
Well, what do you eat then?
Fresh fish!
- Is this Michelin-star fish?
- Fresh fish!
Who wants some hot fried fish?
With tasty sauce!
Fried fish!
Who wants some fish?
- Nice big fish!
- One, two, three, four,
- five, six, seven, eight, nine…
- And tasty sauce!
Fresh fried fish!
No grease! Just flavor! Try it!
Wo-ho-ho!
Your favorite fish from
Uncle's fish stand.
You managed that so fast.
There must not have been a line.
He had two woks going at once.
He was…
trying something new.
I've only gone to his stall
for the last 40 years.
I haven't gone blind, you know.
Huh? I only go there
because it's not greasy like this.
I'm not eating it.
If you're going to eat fried food,
you might as well have a little grease.
I got what you wanted, Amah!
It's piping hot!
I'm already full.
What did you eat?
I had the fish you bought earlier.
Oh.
Are you making some tea?
To offer to the gods, not for myself.
Let me do it for you.
Hey.
The water boiled already?
Yeah, it did.
How come I didn't hear the kettle whistle?
I used the microwave.
For the gods' tea?
What?
Take it down right now!
Why? I boiled it!
- Not the right way!
- It's good!
But this saves gas
and it's so much faster.
No, M!
Take it down!
It's not right!
Yes, it is!
The modern ways are good ways.
You offered tea to them.
- The gods don't care how it's boiled!
- If you do things just to get them done,
then don't do them at all.
I'll come back tomorrow
to boil the water right.
Just go home.
Go.
- I'll even use two kettles.
- I don't need you.
You never came to visit.
Why bother now?
Watch where you walk.
Hello.
Thanks for coming.
I'm not sure she meant to but Ms.
Mui left this.
It'd be a shame to throw it out.
Why are you so stubborn?
I don't want these things.
They were supposed to be thrown out.
Now I'm stuck with them.
If you came here to ask me
for money like the others,
the answer is no.
That's not why I'm here.
I just…
want to say you did a
great job with Agong.
You were…
the one who took care of him,
so you should be rewarded.
Here. Gimme that.
I also wanted to hear more…
about how I could get paid
for the easy work
that you mentioned.
I want to save the money I got
from selling Agong's house.
So, I'm renting this hotel
room by the month.
The rent includes breakfast
and daily housekeeping.
If I get bored, I can just move out.
You got a proper uniform for work?
I'm diggin' it.
It's not real.
It's for my OnlyFans account.
Wearing a nurse's uniform
gets me a higher rate.
Wanna subscribe?
Mm… That's alright.
Look at you all shy.
We've kissed before, remember?
When we were a lot younger
and our families would get together
to play cards at Agong's.
You and I always played house.
I was the mother,
you were the father.
And we cuddled under the blanket.
Uh, yeah.
I remember now.
We did.
So tell me why you wanna
look after your Amah?
So I can get a place of my own.
It takes so long when
you're not privileged.
Some people are just born
with a head start.
They're rich or inherit a business.
So, you think of Amah as an asset?
Hm…
That hurts.
Do you think it's so wrong…
what we're doing?
Hm?
Honestly…
I really hate Agong's kids.
They would come once
a week for 15 minutes.
So why even bother?
It's time.
Mm?
Our time is what they're
really craving the most.
It doesn't matter what we're there for.
How'd you skip over everyone else?
And get to be number one?
Do you know what…
older people want more
than anything each day
but most of their children
are not willing to offer?
To not count the minutes.
But I was with her all day.
Did you think she smelled funny…
when you were with her?
Old people just smell.
You notice it because you don't
spend enough time with her.
You'll know you have when
you stop noticing.
Agong was incontinent
but I became immune to it.
Woah!
I'll buy you back when I get the money.
So you're going to be moving in with Amah?
I'm doing what you wanted, aren't I?
Breaking into houses now?
I used the key that you gave to Ma.
What's with all this stuff?
I brought some…
and I
bought some of it.
And this is for you.
I made it selling stuff online.
Tell me why everyone's visiting now?
If all those tests say I'm fine.
I don't need all this fuss.
But the traditional methods endure.
The charcoal burning industry
at Ban Khon Huay Nang
is a mainstay of the
Nong Chang Subdistrict.
They gave Ma the
results of the tests you did.
The traditions have been
handed down for generations.
Most things look good.
The industry is steady but
faces constant challenges.
But you have cancer.
Wood and sawdust prices have
increased and added pressure.
And Ma and the uncles
don't want you to know.
Prices for other materials used in
the process have also increased.
Battery prices have
gone up in all categories
Is it serious?
- By an average of 20 percent.
- It's stage four.
And transportation costs
have continued to increase.
They've given you a year.
The industry has also come to a
crossroads between tradition and
innovation with the advent
But you don't need to listen to them.
Doctors… sometimes they think they can
predict the future. Remember what they
told Yen down the street? Six months if
she was lucky.
Of higher-performing kilns
increasing productivity and efficiency.
And now it's been ten years and she's
still bossing everyone around in that big
house of hers.
However the ancient methods attract
tourists and school groups interested in
- seeing
- I had such a great time as a kid
here. You were so good to Ma and me.
- These traditional work methods in use.
- Now I think it's time I
did something for you.
While some embrace the new technologies
and see them as a way of preserving a
- vital part
- I have time. I'd like to
spend it with you if I can.
Of the local economy,
others see them as the beginning
of the end for small family
enterprises
who are not able to compete with the
output from more efficient and numerous
- modern kilns.
- I'm off.
They used to light 100 kilns a day.
Now they are able to light 200 to 300.
As for the prices of raw materials for
the kilns, the price is higher due in
- large part
- I'll put this money
towards the utility bill.
To shipping costs,
making the charcoal stove business a
fine balancing act for all involved.
- I'll help you sell congee tomorrow.
- There is also pressure for increased
production to export the charcoal to other
regions or factories
- What time do you leave?
- 5 a.m.
- What?
Why so early?
Do you expect to sell
congee late in the day?
People eat congee at night too, you know.
You can eat congee all day.
The early bird gets the worm'.
I don't think your generation
has ever heard that saying.
Have you ever heard the saying:
“the worm that wakes up at 5
will not stay alive?“
He's the one that gets eaten first, Amah.
Hm.
You're scowling.
Why didn't you wake me up?
I'm your Amah, not an alarm clock.
I'll do this bag.
Oh, fine.
Are you hiding it because you
don't know what you're doing?
Please.
If you want,
I can deposit your money at the ATM then
you won't have to walk to the bank now.
Stop meddling.
I take this walk to the bank every month.
I thought you might like a
break from going for once.
Ngek!
- Who's Ngek?
- A friend.
Careful.
Hold this.
Thank you. Oh, Ngek.
How are you?
Did they let you come back already?
I got back yesterday.
Really?
They made me leave to give the
bed to someone worse off.
I've been hit as well.
Where is it?
Intestines.
What's the stage?
It's four.
Mine too.
Mm…
I'm here for you if you need it.
- Same to you.
- Although it must be a great
- comfort to have your grandson.
- Sure.
You are so lucky.
You see?
I think your friend is jealous.
- It's good to see you.
- Good to see you too.
You stay out here.
You'll use my bank details behind my back.
Oh so now you think your
grandson's a thief?
- You watch too much TV.
- Whatever. Stay there.
- So good to see you, ma'am.
- I would never do that, Amah.
Thank you so much.
- Are we making the usual deposit?
- Yes. We are.
Whoa, Ma.
This is bad.
The fridge smells like a garbage can.
Why do you insist on holding
on to things that are expired?
It's not expired. I can still eat it.
No wonder you've got stomach aches,
eating all this moldy stuff every day.
I'll bring it back even
if you throw it out!
How can you two bicker before breakfast?
Why are you sleeping in the living
room instead of upstairs?
Amah locks her room.
She doesn't want me in there.
You put your fancy clothes on today?
Fancy?
Hm.
Hold on.
The last button's undone.
You trying to show off?
Leave it. It's too tight.
I like it loose, so I can move.
Yeah, 'cause it's so tight.
Why are you bothering me?
Hey.
Did you steal Rainbow's sandals?
Those look way too small for you.
They fit perfect.
Perfect?
Yes.
- Thats a perfect fit?
- Go away.
I can dress myself, thank you.
A perfect fit doesn't cut off circulation.
These are my feet, not yours.
If I can get my feet in them,
they fit fine. What about your shoes?
Also a perfect fit.
So why are you dressed so nice?
She always dresses up on Sunday.
Everyone comes on Sundays.
Which you would know if you bothered.
Here we are!
I ordered this chicken
from the Montien Hotel.
It's where all the famous
people go to eat.
Whoa-ho-ho-ha!
Rainbow,
did you know…
when were growing up here,
we had a pet chicken downstairs.
- Cool, huh?
- I would like a baby chick.
- I think they're the cutest in the world.
- True!
But your aunt and your dad used to
chase that chicken around all day.
Until one Chinese New Year,
Amah had to chop him up for dinner.
Chop. Chop.
Chop.
And she made us steamed chicken
just like this one.
Except we were so sad,
we gave all our pieces to the dogs.
- You've got the memory of an elephant!
- Right, sis?
And you remember whenever Kiang
cried, he would blow snot bubbles?
- He would!
- Can you stop?
I'm not here to have my baby
listen to your stupid stories.
Why don't we look at your stickers, okay?
Relax, bro.
Passing down the family history
to the next gen is important.
Kids.
When we've finished eating,
- who's up for playing cards?
- Mm?
When's the last time we played together?
I see, you, Ma. you want to take your
boys to the cleaners, huh?
Crack open your safe,
I'm taking you to the cleaners.
- I'd like to see you try, boy.
- Ah! The big talker!
You'll have to play without us,
we have to leave.
Rainbow has a ballet
class in a little bit.
- Kiang, relax.
- Mm?
You have time for a game or
two before you have to leave.
Yeah, bro.
There's traffic to deal with.
We need to go.
Soei, you too.
You shouldn't be playing cards either.
Why not?
Because Ma needs to rest.
Ma, you still have pain in your stomach?
Yeah.
Are you hurting anywhere?
I know all about the cancer.
Huh?
M told me everything.
Well,
Amah has a right to know what's going on.
It's her body and she can make
her own decisions about it.
I'll see the doctor on my own.
I'm not going to be a burden to you.
It's not a burden.
I'm glad you know,
because I think you should
be getting treated, okay?
But they made me promise to keep it quiet.
What's that?
Don't be trying to make yourself
look like the good son.
You barely visit and you
mooch off of everyone.
Ah.
Always with the finances?
I'd pay for more things
if I had any money.
That's because you don't work.
I do work, okay? It's been
slow, so I'm not working right now!
Please don't be starting that again!
- I have a real job.
- You're not being fair, Kiang.
Construction's not steady.
- Anyway, I come here more than you do.
- You're always too busy.
My job is very demanding.
Are you saying our work doesn't count?
Mm-hm!
When I got to school,
I'll be a doctor so you can get
better and we'll play cards.
Don't worry, Ma.
My friend knows all the best doctors
who deal with important people.
I'll foot the bill for your treatments
and you will beat this thing.
You don't need to worry about me.
Don't you be stubborn about this,
when you have appointments,
I will take you.
It's my daughter's duty, Ma.
Hey.
Ma.
When I took a dump earlier,
I almost broke my neck.
I'll install some handrails
so you don't slip and fall.
Okay?
I am proud of my children
and very thankful.
Mm-hm.
No need to be so dramatic.
You'll get better soon.
Aren't you supposed to be
working at the market?
Not until later.
I'll be doing night shifts for a while.
This way I'll be able to take
Ma to her chemo in the day.
I can't just take the day off when I want.
What are you expecting from her?
Expecting?
My mother has cancer.
Don't you think I should support her?
Otherwise I'll be seen
as a terrible daughter.
This is the one and only time we do this.
I'm not coming back here.
Don't you remember what the doctor told
you about making sure you exercise?
I can walk on my own.
You took a day off work for this,
didn't you?
They'll replace you if you call too often.
Ma won't get fired.
She'll be working on the
night shift for a while.
So she can come to your appointments.
Really?
You work at night now?
Until what time?
What time, Sew?
Until dawn, Amah.
She works all night.
Oh.
That means you haven't even slept yet?
That's enough.
Get me out of here.
We're here now. Stay!
Why can't you let me do something
nice for you for once?
Because whenever I let
you do things like that
it always backfires.
Like when you dropped out of school,
to help me sell congee.
Why are you saying that was bad?
I couldn't bear to see you work so
hard while my brothers did nothing.
You broke your back for all of us
working all those long
hours with your cart.
You work harder than me.
And look where it got you.
- Tired and wet.
- If Kiang were available,
you'd be okay to come with him.
Oh…
Right.
I'll make sure he knows that.
I'm not sure he'll be free,
but I'll give him the message.
Amah's crying in the changing room.
That's impossible.
That woman's never shed a
tear for me in her life.
True.
You're always the one who sheds the tears.
All I know is the more you bicker,
the worse she is.
I'll take Amah in for
her chemo from now on.
I'll be representing our family.
- Did you turn off the lights in the house?
- Yes, I did.
- Upstairs and down?
- Yep.
Mui.
Amah.
This is Mui.
One of my cousins.
Amah, have you eaten?
Yes, thank you.
Where are you going, Amah?
I'm going to see the doctor.
I'm going to drive you there.
Thank you.
You speak teochew?
You suck-up.
You owe me one, M. I'm not a taxi.
Yeah, I got it.
Please make sure that
your documents are ready.
I think you used to
play cards with my Agong
when I was little.
You need to put your shoes
at the end of the line, M.
They'll start calling patients at eight.
We woke up at four for this?
Amah and I will go find a seat.
Wait for me here, Amah.
I'll find you a wheelchair.
Please ensure that your
documents are ready.
Next time, go in and keep her company.
You'll get huge brownie points.
Mm…
My insides feel like they're on fire.
- Hm.
- Hmpf.
Goodness.
Go put this in the cabinet.
- With the rest.
- Sure.
Hey!
- No, wait for me to help you.
- Not a chance.
When you were a kid,
you offered to let me hold your hand.
But
your eyes were glued to the television
and I banged up my shins.
I don't remember that.
I'd rather climb on my own.
Come on.
Hold out both your hands.
Mui said I'm supposed to lead the way.
That way we're sure you won't
go tumbling backwards.
- She said that, did she?
- She did.
C'mon. Hands up.
Eyes on me, then.
Careful where you step.
That's good.
Now get some rest.
Is this Uncle Soei?
Uh-huh.
Hilarious.
Hey.
You and Grandpa were pretty cool,
you look like you were having fun.
Mm-hm.
Back when you used to live here.
You were afraid of ghosts.
You would squeeze in right here
between your Agong and me every night.
I was afraid of ghosts?
Something awful.
I had to sing you at least three
lullabies to get you to sleep.
Hm?
No way.
Hopefully you outgrew all that?
Because your Agong
likes to come back and wander
around downstairs.
Every night.
If you see his ghost,
don't say anything to him.
Shit!
I thought you said you
weren't afraid any more.
I'm not afraid of ghosts.
But you're real.
I needed to pray.
I had a dream about my parents.
They came to take me to stay with them.
M?
Do you think I'm about to die?
Amah.
You worship the goddess.
It's been decades since you ate beef.
Cows should be praying to you.
You've got plenty of life left, I'm sure.
Yeah.
I guess so.
I'll go back upstairs.
- Hey, no more stairs.
- You need your sleep.
No stairs.
Save your energy.
We sleep together in here.
Come in.
So the bugs don't bite.
You're kinda taking up the whole bed.
Hmpf.
Can you scoot over, Amah?
Are you insulting me again?
That means I thank you.
Are you sure you're Chinese?
You can't understand a single word.
I'm Chinese-Thai, Amah.
Chinese-Thai.
Whatever.
I'm going to sleep now.
Okay.
Goodnight.
Amah?
Sing to me?
Keep doing this whenever you're free.
Sure thing.
You'll be out of job soon.
You're not doing it tight enough.
I'm leaving some space,
so the vinegar breathes.
The counter is now open.
Amah.
Come on. Get up.
Get up.
Are you finished?
Just a second.
Amah?
Hey.
What's wrong?
Are you in pain?
N-Not so fast.
Um…
Let's skip the market this morning.
I'm going to give you a sponge bath,
you're too warm.
I have to sell my congee.
Come on up. Bath time.
We'll turn around. Slowly.
Go on three.
One, two, three.
Up!
Alright. Arm.
Mm.
You need to get underneath too.
- I'm sticky.
- Woah!
You're taking it off?
Hm.
I wanna feel really clean everywhere.
I'm old, you know. I'm not embarrassed.
Just give me a second.
I've never done this.
Give a guy some warning.
Hm-hm.
What's with your moaning?
Shit!
What? Did you see another ghost?
Was that bump I felt your nipple?
Are you that dumb?
I've got a mole.
Who has boobs that would sag
all the way down there?
I dunno. H-How would I know?
Give me that.
You might think my knees are my boobs.
What's with the camera?
It's for watching things.
I can't watch that.
No, I mean watching you.
If you fall or faint, I'll see it.
I could come and help.
If anything bad happens to you,
I can see it right away.
Don't jinx me.
Don't worry.
Here. Check this out.
No!
You can't move the goddess like that!
Never.
Why not?
It's just wrong.
Put her back and apologize.
Right this instant.
You can't shove her around.
Where's your respect, M?
- There.
- No. Like you care. That was sloppy.
She's all crooked.
Use both your hands, gently.
Yes.
Very gently.
- Careful.
- Done.
She's all set.
Right back in the same exact spot.
It's like she never moved at all.
All done.
Easy peasy. The throne is secure.
You're done?
Ma, move away.
You hate the smell of smokes.
You should be resting.
Woah.
Hey, Ma.
The pomegranate's looking nice.
Can I?
Don't touch it. It's not yours.
It looks too good, I'm taking it.
You can't have it!
Why not?
Ooh.
It's not yours.
Well,
whose is it?
It's not yours, that's all.
Ah.
- What?
- You're saving it for your
favorite son, Mr. Money Bags.
You have something to eat?
Take a look.
Hey, M?
Did you know
that when they first met,
Ma thought Kiang's wife was a real dud.
What do you mean a dud?
Shit.
Make me explain the simplest words.
Did you sleep through school?
Huh?
A dud sucks. Like a firecracker that got
all wet or a total bore.
Ah…
When Pinn got her hooks into your uncle,
Kiang changed into a totally
different person.
He became a snob.
All about image.
Sending his kid to an
international school.
- Did you know?
- Shut your mouth, Soei.
- I can tell when you've been drinking,
- He borrowed tons of money.
- What?
- You have no filter.
I haven't finished gossiping yet.
She protects her favorite.
Fine! I'll shut my mouth.
Anyway,
my motto's always been:
live within your means and be modest.
But your favorite, he just hoards it away.
- That's enough from you.
- The guy's loaded but when people like
me need a little hand out where is he?
Eh…
I'm short about a thousand, help me out?
- Hm?
- No way.
Please?
- I spent it.
- If I find it, can I have it?
- No.
- Come on.
Mm! Liar.
- Not today, Soei!
- I'll kiss you 'til you cave.
Hm?
With Soei,
it's best when he stays away.
Why's that?
Because it means that he's okay
when he doesn't come around.
That's just how it goes.
Her kids versus grandkids.
She's loved them a lot longer.
There's a chage for extra sauce.
Can you rate your current position?
Who's your Amah's favorite?
The number one spot is either
Uncle Kiang or Uncle Soei.
One's too serious and the other's a clown.
I think I've moved ahead of my mom,
though.
Number three gets a big zero.
What about you?
How did you know you were top of the list?
Did he tell ya?
Most older people aren't
that straight forward.
But you can feel it.
Feel what?
Not the love if that's what you mean.
I just feel her sarcastic shit.
Every day.
Hm.
I was sure I snagged the spot
when Agong sang my praises.
To the rest of the clan.
Mm… I guess.
We're almost there, Ma.
It's a bit far, but the air is better.
I'm sorry I haven't brought
you here before.
Welcome to our house, Amah.
Welcome, Ma.
Show Amah the picture you drew for her.
Hm.
Careful.
Do you like it, Amah.
Very much.
Thank you.
Did you notice the bed?
We got it specially for you.
Rainbow chose the red flowers.
The TV's internet cable
You can watch the Chinese opera.
- I still have a house and business to run.
- Oh, Ma!
Pinn and I want you to sell that
house and move in with us.
Besides there's salons,
restaurants, a club.
The club has seniors activities.
There's tai-chi each morning.
What about her chemo appointments though?
The commute is tiring.
Uh…
I run my stock trading from home,
I'll be around to take care of her.
Yeah but there's her congee shop.
Her regulars are wondering
why she's not there,
- on Sundays.
- I think it's time for Ma to
be closed every day, don't you?
And I can support her.
Moving here is best.
- I can be there for her treatments.
- But you're so far from the clinic.
You'll be getting up at two in
the morning to make it work.
M.
M!
Yep?
I appreciate the work
you've been putting in.
And so…
I wanted to give you a little something
for taking care of Amah for us.
That's nice of you, Uncle.
But I'm not in it for the money.
So it wouldn't feel right.
Ma.
You raised your son right.
I will take care of my mother.
I can't burden my nephew with your care.
Ma.
Let me do what a son should.
And you locked everything up?
Of course.
Rainbow.
It's big girl time.
Please go ask Amah if she's having fun.
I'm sure she would like
you to sit with her.
Can you do that?
Okay.
Ah!
- Do you like the train, Amah?
- I love the train.
- I like riding places, don't you?
- It's so much fun!
- Such a smart, pretty granddaughter.
- You can make coffin
donations at this temple.
We'll contribute for you.
Rainbow's friend and her
mother came recently.
And her condition improved in no time.
You know what this reminds me of, Ma?
Taking the train when we were kids.
It brings back memories of
when you and Pa took us on trips.
And you were so tiny for your age.
- Me?
- Puny but quick.
- I remember Soei running all over.
- Of course, all three of you did.
May you all be blessed
- for coming to visit our temple today.
- Seven.
- Eight.
- We invite you
to fill out
Nine.
- Our coffin donation labels.
- Amah!
- Ten.
- Are you good to climb up?
- We are grateful for your donations.
- Eleven.
You can go ahead,
Uncle. We'll catch up to you.
- Thank you for coming and enjoy your stay.
- Twelve.
- Thirteen.
- So have you made up your mind yet?
Are you gonna move in with Kiang?
Be quiet, will you?
I'm counting the steps. You'll mess me up.
Why are you counting?
For the lottery.
Hm.
Do your feet hurt?
Good, Amah?
Back in the day,
when Kiang was just a kid,
we came to offer prayers here.
When it was time to leave,
his shoes were gone.
So…
I had to give him my sandals
so he didn't go home barefoot.
It was a gorgeous day.
Sunny and bright like today.
The ground was just as hot as today too.
Did he buy these to try
to make it up to you?
Mm.
Good, Rainbow.
Perfect.
- Your names?
- Let's go.
Start it with Misses…
then Mengju
Saejiew
We're going to put up our labels
and then wait for you outside.
- Your wish?
- I want to regain my health.
Okay.
I have more.
You can't rush the wishes you know.
- Oh?
- Write.
How many do you have?
I wish for my
eldest son…
my daughter…
and my youngest son…
to be healthy and strong.
- And have money and gold.
- Ah.
Any more and we'll need another label.
Only because your letters
are big as elephants.
Hm.
And…
I ask for my one and only grandson…
to have a very good job.
Alright.
I'll put it up.
Thank you.
Look, Amah.
One.
Two.
Three.
Nobody made wishes for you.
Seems that Kiang's only pretending
how much he cares.
It's all an act get on your good side.
He has a family of his own.
He has to use his wishes
for their happiness first.
You're part of his family, aren't you?
MRS. MENGJU SAEJIEW:
I WANT TO REGAIN MY HEALTH
M:
MAY AMAH WIN THE LOTTERY
Ma.
Can you try to have your things
ready to move by next Sunday?
I'll arrange the transportation.
M, wait.
I want to buy some new shoes today.
These hurt my feet too much.
Here. Start with these.
How are they?
They feel big.
- They look big.
- Yes.
Hm.
Honestly.
You might get that perfect fit after all.
Hey, M.
Uh-huh.
Maybe you're just trying to
get on my good side too, huh?
It's the same
as Kiang in a way.
Let me do what a grandson should.
You are absolutely full of it.
Ooh you're so full of it.
Telling the truth, though.
I say we try these next.
One on each foot so
you can compare.
Mm?
Oh my.
Are you taking pictures?
Sort of.
It's a filter.
Huh?
It's you only a little sparklier.
I know you.
- You're proud of your looks.
- Hm.
And when your chemo's done…
I'm pretty sure you'll look
something like this.
Ah!
What nonsense.
How? You look cool.
You look good!
And you won't have to wake up
early to do your hair any more.
You like it?
Uh-huh.
It's good to see you laugh.
Get some rest.
Go on.
Close your eyes.
I want pork. Gimme more pork.
- You only want pork?
- Get me pork and some veggies too.
You said you wanted only pork.
I meant give me a lot of pork.
Fine.
Lots of pork.
Listen and learn, M.
Keep stirring.
In the future,
my customers can be yours.
I can't wake up at four for
the rest of my life, Amah.
Can I sell at night?
As long as you remember…
that every kind of hard work
can bring a Zhuang-wen into existence.
You just have to practice your skill
with intent.
Because that will allow you
to have a comfortable life.
Like the Zhuang-wen have
done for centuries.
Don't you have to be castrated to be one?
Those are eunuchs, silly.
You really slept through school.
I'm gonna take you to the cleaners!
Oh, yeah? Try me.
Sassy!
You're on.
Un-huh. Think hard.
Should you bluff?
Does Mengju from Talat Phlu
have what it takes to be
the big winner tonight?
Shut your mouth, would you?
- You're jinxing my hand.
- Hm?
- Show it.
- Go away.
I think I see where Uncle Soei
gets his gambler's blood from.
During the ghost festival
and on Chinese New Year,
we didn't know what else to do
once we'd observed the rituals.
So we'd play cards late into the evening.
You've lived alone for a long time.
Do you ever get lonely?
I wouldn't call it loneliness.
It's part of life's process.
I do have a problem
with the day after Chinese New Year.
When all the leftovers
from the night before…
are in the fridge.
And…
I know I'm going to have
to eat them all alone.
Hm.
Back to the cards.
Go.
- Hmpf.
- You show your's first.
Okay.
Seven double score.
Let's see.
I got eight.
Double score, too.
Liar.
You're a bad, bad cheater, okay?
Double score because it's two eights.
Your customers must rob you blind
if that's how you count.
And I forgot to count this one.
I'm the winner here, Amah.
- What was it?
- Let's go.
Hand it over, I see 20 baht right there.
You scoundrel.
Taking advantage of your Amah.
Woah!
Do I complain when I have to pay you?
Nice try.
Go again?
It's a blessing to have you here.
And you're fun.
You know I'm on to your stalling tactics.
Sure.
No cheating, okay?
We'll see.
Uncle Kiang isn't answering.
He's probably upset you didn't move in.
Uncle Soei's phone is turned off.
And Ma says she has to work because
they're short-staffed.
I don't think anyone's coming today, Amah.
Then please put all the food away in the
cabinet, so the bugs don't get to it.
Okay.
Why is the lid loose?
Hey!
What happened to all my money? It's gone.
M!
Just a sec.
There's nothing in there.
I didn't touch it.
I didn't touch it!
I'm not a thief, I swear.
See?
He took the pork floss and
stole all your money.
That's why his phone's off, I guess.
Was it a lot?
Hey.
Shithead.
Have you ever even helped
Amah sell congee?
She only earns 10 to 20 baht a bag.
Do you know how many bags she has
to sell to get 200,000 baht?
Where's your conscience?
My own mother's never
told me off like this.
How much do you owe?
Huh?
A million.
A million?
So I'm…
gonna ask Ma to bail me out one last time.
Uncle.
Here.
Huh?
What's that?
Silver belt.
Should get a good price for it.
Awesome. Bring it in.
You're a lifesaver.
Disappear for a until you're sorted out.
You deserve better, M.
You take good care of Ma for us, alright?
Soei wasn't at his apartment.
His motorcycle wasn't there either.
I asked his neighbor if he'd seen him.
He said he left town for work.
Hello?
Is anyone home?
Who is that?
I'll go see.
Hello? Hello?
It must be someone Soei owes money to.
Hide somewhere.
I'll get rid of him.
Hello, ma'am.
If you're looking for Soei,
you're too late.
He's been ordained as a monk.
I'm just a humble housekeeper,
but I'm not supposed to let anyone in.
Oh.
Well, I'm not looking for
anyone named Soei, ma'am.
Oh?
I'm here about the listing
I saw for this place.
I texted the seller but he
never replied to my message.
Uh, so I thought I'd drop by.
Oh. Thank you so much.
This house isn't for sale, sir.
No.
Here's the internet post.
The seller is listed as M Thanapat, ma'am.
I don't suppose you recognize the name?
Mm…
I don't believe I know that person.
Oh.
Amah.
Is he gone?
How'd you get him to go away?
Hm.
I told him I'm the maid.
Well, you can pull it off.
You have the outfit.
And the scowl.
Now get to work,
you silly maid. Enough sitting around.
I bought you a new shirt.
It looks formal.
So you can look professional.
I dunno.
It's kind of old-fashioned.
Hm.
You know,
I think the next chemo treatment
could be the last one.
And then I'll be cured.
Then…
you won't be stuck here doing all of this.
Are you kicking me out?
When you were in elementary school,
people could see your potential.
You can do anything but you have to try.
Huh?
Put in the effort and find
yourself a proper job.
I'm just a slacker, Amah.
I can't compete in the real world.
This pomegranate tree
was planted to celebrate your birth.
It's just as old as you are.
They say that growing a pomegranate
tree brings the child good health.
When I told you it was yours,
you asked me to promise
that when the fruit
was ready, I'd keep it all for you.
Nobody else could have any.
Here.
Eat.
I don't remember that at all.
I want to say I'm sorry,
for calling you "qi-chou" all these years.
Would you let me use this as
my hang-out a bit longer?
I promise to leave when
you beat this thing.
If that's okay?
Tomorrow,
there's someone I want you to meet.
Your older brother lives in this mansion?
Why wasn't I born into this family?
Just look at this gate.
Wow.
The reason why my grandson
and I are here today,
is because I have stomach cancer.
And I'd like to get a burial
plot to increase my chances.
Only I can't afford it right now.
Can you give me a million baht?
When we lost our parents,
you basically got everything they owned.
You got several million for the house.
I got nothing.
I've never asked you for a single baht.
I got what our mother and
father wanted me to have.
You were there when this happened,
don't you forget that.
And don't you forget that I'm
the one who wiped their butts.
I never received anything from them.
Ever since I can remember,
whatever our parents had
always went to you first.
And there was nothing left over.
I did more than my duty.
And got nothing.
Why am I not entitled to something?
They respected our tradition…
and protected us.
Because that lousy husband of
yours would have squandered it.
You might think he was lousy,
But he was chosen
for me by tradition.
If you want the money so badly,
you should ask your children to help you.
Understand?
As for me,
I won't give you a single penny.
Hey, M?
Let's go back home.
And don't you bother coming
to my home ever again.
You and I don't share
the same name any more.
- Approaching Tha Phra Station.
- Amah.
- Tha Phra Station.
- Please.
We remind you to mind the gap between
the train and the platform.
Tha Phra Station.
We remind you to mind the gap between
the train and the platform.
Why do you want a big
burial plot so badly?
Because if I'm buried
on a good plot of land,
then my children will be prosperous.
People will see it and think
you guys have filial piety.
That's nonsense, Amah.
It doesn't work that way.
Your parents are buried in one of
those regular, small family plots.
But your brother still got rich.
When people die, they die. Game over.
The brain stops working.
And the body will either become part
of the earth and help flowers grow or…
become part of the stratosphere.
You don't know from a burial plot
how someone has lived. Rich or poor
doesn't make a difference.
Someday, when I am dead,
if you dump petals on my grave carelessly,
I will…
come back to haunt you.
Bring it.
Be a ghost.
I hope you come.
Only I don't think you'll
know who actually
showed up for you on Qingming.
Uncle Kiang might pay someone
to do the ritual.
I could pull your plot on Google Street
Maps and pay respects through the screen.
But if I have a beautiful burial plot,
you all might want to meet up there.
Please wait in front of
the examination room.
Have your hospital card
and identification ready.
Hello.
Please. Sit down.
Let's just see here…
After going over the results
of your mother's treatment,
we unfortunately haven't
seen any improvement.
The doctor said you're better.
You don't need any more chemo.
You told us that the chemotherapy
would get rid of the cancer.
Is it possible that the results are wrong?
He said we can treat your
pain as it comes along.
I don't need to complete the treatment?
What I'd recommend
is to spend as much time
as you can with her.
- It's alright.
- It's very important for the patient.
- The family must stay strong.
I didn't tell you.
Ngek's gone already She
died a few days ago.
She didn't finish her treatment, either.
I have a right to know.
What did he really say?
Ma, what did she say?
What did she tell you, Ma?
The rice grains have become cooked rice.
It's a saying that means accept
what can't be changed.
Baba. Mah.
Come and take me with you.
It hurts too much.
I want to join you and
Amah and the others.
Shh…
I want to
die.
I want to die.
Agong.
Help me.
Hey.
Is Ma getting worse?
They'll be running some tests.
If there's nothing new, she can go home.
Get up.
Let's talk outside for a minute, Sew.
Do you know where the
deed to her house is?
She hasn't been buried yet, Kiang.
Ma's not dead,
why are you asking about her house?
When we have buried her,
someone's going to have
to take care of it.
If we do it while Ma's alive,
it'll be much easier.
Pinn put you up to this business, right?
This…
is precisely why I don't want
to be around you guys.
I'm not gonna let my wife be treated like
she's not a member of this family.
Do you know where the deed is?
She keeps her papers,
in her bedroom closet.
Ma.
If Uncle Kiang asks her to sign
something don't let her do it.
Ma!
Are you listening to me?
Maaa?
You better do this now, Soei.
You're the best, sis.
Amah gave her house to your uncle.
Just a second.
M?
I need to go settle the bill.
Take her over to the taxi
line and wait there.
Let's go!
M!
PATIENT PICKUP AND DROP-OFF POINT
You gave your house to Soei?
Haven't you learned your lesson?
He'll always struggle
more than the others.
Because you enable him.
That's why he's such a loser.
Your parents did the same thing.
Cutting out the caregiver.
I don't have anything else to give.
You don't have to look after me any more.
I've been doing a good job, haven't I?
You have done good work.
Quite impressive, actually.
How come I'm not gonna be rewarded?
When I should be first?
Where do I stand with you?
Huh?
Tell me!
Tell me, Amah?
Stubborn fool.
I should be first.
Die! Die!
Die!
Die! Your mom's dead!
You're mine now.
Have you even been to bed yet?
Ma…
Everyone can hear you.
Huh?
You actually have viewers on at this hour?
Don't you know that expression?
The early bird gets the worm.'
Especially if the worm,
is in another time zone.
The new owner of Amah's house
is going to start renovations.
Can you go help clean it out?
Everything can just go in the garbage.
What's that face?
That's not nice.
You're almost as bad as your Uncle Kiang.
You know what he said today?
That if Ma dies,
he won't bother coming to the funeral.
It really is a blessing that neither
of us got Amah's house.
My favorite saying is "It's better to
give than to receive." And it's true.
Are you trying to cheer
yourself up or what?
Weren't you hoping for Amah's house?
Whatever gave you that idea?
Come on.
Why else would you have changed your
work schedule and gone to all
those appointments?
So that I could be with her.
That house was a little too quiet
when you went to Amah's, M.
Were you lonely?
It helped me understand,
how once we had all moved out,
she must have found that hard.
Hi.
You can bring the car into the garage.
Your room's waiting for you, Mui.
Thank you, Auntie.
Of course.
Last week, Auntie fainted.
It turns out something's
wrong with her heart.
So she asked me to come and help her.
Her only son passed away
several years ago.
And her daughter-in-law and grandkids
moved away overseas.
We could do this as a team.
I'll be her nurse around here.
You take her to all her appointments.
When she makes me her number one,
I'll give you a share.
I really thought the house would be yours.
Amah told me you worked hard.
And took good care of her.
Do you ever dream of your grandpa?
On the day that we lost him…
he was eating and choked on his food.
I could have cleared his airway.
Except I chose not to.
At the end, he was always asking me…
to let him join his ancestors.
So I have to assume he's
happy where he is.
Because he hasn't been in my dreams yet.
I humbly pay my respect to the
benevolent goddess Guanyin.
Please deliver me from sorrow and illness.
… Important thing is…
to keep up the pace.
Alright? We want the heart rate
to be somewhat elevated.
NURSING HOME
Ma, did you know?
Uncle Soei didn't take
Amah to live with him.
He put her in a nursing home.
I'm gonna go visit her.
Hello.
Nice to see you.
Hi.
- Hi!
- Hello.
Good afternoon.
Hello.
Hello. Are you visiting your family?
- Hello.
- Hi.
- You have someone here?
Yes, ma'am.
Mr. Chaiyapon,
your nephew's here to visit.
I'll be right out.
Enjoy your time.
She's asleep, so you have to be quiet.
Mm-hm.
I got everything paid off.
But there's a little left over.
I want you to have it.
You can hold on to it.
Come on. It's for you.
No one's gonna rescue you when she's gone.
Who is it?
It's your qi-chou, Amah.
Have you eaten yet, M?
That's better for showing
myself off like I want.
How about you come home with me, Amah?
I'll make you congee for breakfast.
Let's go home.
Ma…
Why are you keeping these things?
They're fine.
Anyway, I learned that from you.
What are you even doing in here.
You should be resting.
Go.
You shouldn't follow my example
when it comes to food.
Eat things that are fresh and healthy.
Because cancer can be genetic.
Oh, I know.
Sons inherit the goods.
Daughters get the genes.
Mm.
Are you guys having a moment?
Or just gossiping?
Don't let me interrupt.
Your M…
All through my illness he's
badgered me to answer…
which one of you
I love the most of all.
I don't know the answer.
But I do know
if there's someone I most want
to stay with, it's you.
MAY GOOD FORTUNE COME TO OUR FAMILIES
MAY YOU BE PROSPEROUS
- Hello, Auntie.
- Hi, M.
Happy Chinese New Year, cousin.
Amah's gonna be amazed at
how much you've grown.
Let's go see her, Rainbow.
Not sure if you know, Uncle.
Amah told me the story
of how beef used to be
her absolute favorite.
But you used to get sick a lot as a boy.
She prayed to her goddess to
boost your immune system.
In exchange for Guanyin making
you strong and healthy,
she gave up something she really loved.
Kiang.
Come inside.
You're making yourself sick with guilt.
Amah.
Kiang came to see you.
Smile.
Eh?
Amah?
Can you feel him holding your hand?
I see you have your blessings here.
M is a dedicated grandson.
Rock, oh rock…
Rock my golden master
May you grow up to be prosperous
Surrounded by servants
Waiting on your hand and foot
Rock, oh, rock…
Rock, my golden master
May you grow up to be prosperous
Surrounded by servants
Waiting on your hand and foot
Rock, oh, rock
Rock, my golden master
DAOCHAI FAMILY
I got you tripe, liver,
tendons and super tender bits of steak,
Amah.
Have you see the silver belt
that I got at Agong's funeral?
I've been looking everywhere
and I can't find it.
Hello?
Is this some kind of scam?
But… She passed away recently.
What's this about?
SAVINGS PASSBOOK
I don't remember that.
It's been open how long?
All you do is play those games.
And it makes you slow as a snail.
The bank'll close before we get there.
I only walk slow so you
don't get too tired.
I'm starting an account
at the bank for you.
Look, M.
We're going to put money in.
To celebrate your good grades.
I'm going to keep putting in
deposits throughout the year.
Can you keep putting in
money until you die?
I wanna have a million baht.
Oh.
Are you jinxing me to die?
What would you do with a million baht?
I would start by buying you a new house,
Amah.
'Cause your place is so old.
And bugs are crawling all over the food.
- Well, that's harsh.
- Just talking about it
gives me goosebumps. See?
My goodness. You got goosebumps?
You are absolutely full of it.
I'll withdraw it all and
close the account, ma'am.
M.
Knock on the coffin and tell
Amah where we're going.
Amah.
We're on our way.
We're passing your congee shop.
Amah.
We're crossing the old bridge.
We're almost at the big plot I bought you.
Amah.
You're the top of my list.
Rainbow.
What are you doing?
Here.
Go scatter the flowers for Amah.
Soei, why don't you help lay out the food?
I'm trying to win the 12,
000,000 lottery, bro.
Ooh.
There.
Do a nice job for Amah, now.
Kiang?
Ma was 78, wasn't she?
Rainbow.
- 79 on the Chinese calendar.
- Here. Lemme help.
- 78.
- Thanks.
79.
- So, 78, 79, 87.
- I'll show you how. Watch.
- 9-9-7.
- Ready?
- I think I'm gonna get one more ticket.
- Woop!
Jeez, guys.
It doesn't matter what numbers you choose.
You'll never win.
Do you have 22?
Why 22? Ma was 79.
It's from that one time when Ma took
a picture with the three of us.
Where did it say that?
Here.
Let's do the kids' ages too.
Oh. Let's use Ma's address to
her house. She would want that.
Okay.
Now one more, then we eat.