Damn it!
Let me know who
who stole my stuff,
I will break his tendon.
Madam.
I don't know if I should say this.
Since we've come this far,
what else should I say?
If we report to the government
If we report it to the government,
everyone will know it.
Maybe
relatives who hit the autumn breeze will come back.
We've been telling the public that
our family's financial unstable.
Did that bitch and her wife
Did they split up?
Yes.
The finance is unstable.
and Master was killed.
The expenses are huge.
Of course there's no property to share.
Right?
Yes.
With my skills,
to sneak into the mansion to get something.
to get something.
Now we have the seal.
You can also find a way
you can find a way
to solve it.
Xiaodie is calm and sensible.
She treats me very friendly.
You want to pretend to be her wife
and take her as your wife.
Don't be naive.
You two are totally different.
Do you misunderstand Xiaodie?
She's actually a good girl.
I really like her.
Me too.
You finally admitted
Your special towards Wang Xiaodie
is not my imagination.
Let's give Xiaodie the right to choose.
She's not Xiaodie.
She's the goddess, Tao Yao.
Okay.
The seal is not here.
It's not here.
It seems that
I have to stay in this mansion.
It's impossible to stay here.
You can go.
I need to check the bag.
Wait.
Why are you so aggressive?
I'm just following the rules.
Wang Xiaodie.
Since you want my bag,
I'll give it to you.
I don't want
these unknown treasures.
I wish your wish will come true.
I also hope
you can get the money
to spend it.
What a coincidence.
I heard that the branch of the royal mansion has caused a lot of trouble.
I came because I was worried about my brother.
Concubine Liu did go too far.
I don't care about
the Wang family's property anyway.
So you're going out without a penny.
It's more reassuring not to take some things.
But for the sake
you and Fu'an are brothers,
I have to remind you.
Greed harms people.
Stop when you're good.
Let's go.
Wait, Xiaodie.
I forgot something.
I'll wait for you at the door.
Mother.
I'm here.
Let's eat.
What's wrong?
You don't like it?
I've been eating these dishes for days.
Why don't you change the dishes?
Mother.
Father is dead now.
Those two idols were kicked out.
Our family should have a lot of money.
Why are we spending more and more money?
We're just acting for
who like to take advantage of us.
Mother.
When can we
live a good life?
What's the rush?
Look.
What is this?
This
left by your father.
The biggest bank account in the capital
in the capital
is enough for us to eat and drink for the rest of our lives.
Really?
So
when the show is over,
our good days
has just begun.
From now on, these are all yours.
Okay.
You're a drumstick.
Chicken leg?
This house wasn't this shabby before.
Maybe it was raining heavily last night
because of heavy rain.
Can you fix it today?
Let's fix it first.
If it doesn't work,
we can find an inn tonight.
Forget it then.
We are shy now.
We'd better save it.
Xiaodie, we have money.
Xiaodie, we really have money.
We have money.
Where did you get it?
This is Concubine Liu's jewelry box.
Chang Feng brought it last night.
Sure.
He's really doing big things in silence.
You're such a troublemaker.
Chang Feng.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Chang Feng.
Chang Feng, what's wrong?
Qing.
Dragonfly.
Long time no see.
You know
You haven't come to see me for so long.
Do you know how much I missed you?
Dragonfly.
Do you think I'm doing well?
I'm living on the streets.
living in the streets.
But these bitterness
can't withstand the weight of love.
It's incurable.
Qing.
Marry me then.
Let's never be apart again.
My mother said
if I get married,
I'll put the seal my father left me
as my dowry.
This seal has a lot of money
in the first bank in the capital.
I can buy a lot of delicious food.
What seal?
Is there any obvious mark?
That's...
a little bit.
A little?
But your mother won't agree to this marriage.
As long as
we can be together,
No.
she has to agree.
Dragonfly.
I want to be with you,
but reputation is important. I...
For Qing,
for you.
Where have you been
in the middle of the night?
Mother.
My daughter and Qing have become husband and wife.
I will only marry him in the future.
What?
Male.