”Three Lives, Three Worlds” by Jason Zhang
♫ Listen to the rustling of the wind ♫
♫ Whose sorrow is it trying to stir up? ♫
♫ My yearning grows so instantaneously ♫
♫ That I forget how long the night is ♫
♫ I hold the tears in my palm until they become burning hot ♫
♫ I’m only willing to be crazy for you for three lifetimes ♫
♫ Falling blossoms are everywhere, and I also smell the fragrance of the zither ♫
♫ With you, I wander the world ♫
♫  If love is too desolate, I will dream this dream with you ♫
♫ And redeem all your tears ♫
♫ No matter how far this journey will be or how long these three lifetimes will be ♫
♫ We will be hand in hand until eternity ♫
♫ Despite the miserable wind, vast fog, rolling storm, or overflowing snow ♫
♫ I will walk with you every step of the way ♫
♫ I will hold your hand, don’t be alarmed, don’t worry about tomorrow ♫
♫ Even if we are destined to wander the world ♫
♫ Never let go of each other’s hands ♫
♫ Never forget our mutual love ♫
♫ Life does not need to be too brilliant ♫
♫ Empty glories eventually become nothing, those things you persisted will leave with the wind ♫
♫ Why is love full of ups and downs? ♫
♫ How many storms do we have to face before our hearts stop wavering? ♫
♫ Let’s run through our past together ♫
♫ I’ll wait with you for the wind to stop, fog to clear, rain to end, and snow to melt ♫
♫ Before seeing the absolute beautiful moon again ♫
♫ I will still be by your side ♫
[Eternal Love]
[Episode 40]
Pure Wutong Palace is huge.
Can you even find the Courtyard of Moonlight?
I should be fine.
I'll take you.
Your Highness!
Please beg His Mighty Monarch, Your Highness!
Tell him you told me to do it!
Your Highness...
You said I told you to do it?
I...
Miao Qing, I took pity on your infatuation with His Mighty Monarch,
and you want to frame me for not being moral?!
That's not what I meant, Your Highness.
I was wrong about you.
Your Highness, I spoke without thinking just now.
Please forgive me, Your Highness.
Since His Mighty Monarch has told you to leave, don't waste time.
Leave right now.
Your Highness...
Your Highness!
Are you all right? Did it go well?
Xin Nu,
I finally know why Yue Hua is obsessed with her.
Your Highness, what do you mean?
Just now...
I just saw Bai Qian of Green Hill.
Do you know who she looks like?
She looks exactly like that mortal.
Your Highness!
What are you saying?
Su Su.
It's Su Su!
She and that Su Su look exactly alike.
Your Highness!
Just stop right here. I know the rest of the way.
Hey. I really do remember the rest of the way.
I didn't escort you here really to show you the way.
I want to ask you.
Why are you making the princess go back to the Eastern Sea?
Didn't you want her to go back, too?
Is that the only reason?
I don't know how to answer you.
As I expected.
Expect what?
I didn't forget my promise to you.
I will help you to accept a few side consorts.
It's just... you don't like that princess,
so having her go back to the Eastern Sea is for the best.
Talking about this, this princess was very scheming.
If she can drug your soup today,
she might do something even more shocking on another day.
It's better for the harem to be more peaceful.
What do you think?
I shouldn't have asked this.
When I told you to enter the room, it was to make you jealous.
I didn't expect that, from the beginning till the end,
it was just a spectacle to you.
I have no place in your heart at all.
Bai Qian,
is your heart only for that person?
How long are you going to wait for him?
I have no place in your heart at all.
Bai Qian, is your heart only for that person?
How long are you going to wait for him?
I was distinctly very drowsy earlier,
but now that I'm sleeping under this warm blanket,
I can't sleep at all.
I have no place in your heart at all.
Bai Qian,
is your heart only for that person?
Ah Yin.
Ah Yin, where are you?
♫ The wind blows the lock to my memories open ♫
♫ I remembered our past ♫
♫ We once promised in love ♫
♫ We once missed out in regret ♫
♫ Peach blossoms drift down ♫
♫ The light fragrant hiding the bitter anguish ♫
♫ The moon paints ten miles of night with light ♫
♫ It brings up the loneliness in my eyes ♫
♫ My unwillingness to leave you has been drowned by vicissitudes of life ♫
♫ Three thousand years have flown by, my heart is driven to distraction ♫
I, Li Jing, will only be with Ah Yin in my life.
If I go back on my words, may my family line be cut off and may I spend my life alone.
♫ Bleak yearning, my heart has shattered beyond repair ♫
That time you said, no matter who I am, you would always be with me.
But now...
Fine.
I will fulfill your wish.
Li Jing,
it's true that you were the only person I loved in these 140,000 years,
but time changes everything.
We can't go back.
♫ The causality cannot be determined ♫
♫ Three lifetimes’ peach blossom are tender ♫
♫ Love is hard to abandon ♫
♫ I admire a flower ♫
♫  I’m willing to spend eternity with you, watching the flowers of youth in the spring wind ♫
I can't die.
I still have thousands of people.
Mighty Monarch!
Mighty Monarch! Mighty Monarch!
Mighty Monarch, criminal Xuan Nü escaped prison last night.
She also pierced Li Yuan through the heart before she left!
What did you say? My oldest brother is dead?
Yes!
Cut off the head and hang it outside Grand Purple Palace for seven days for all to see,
then burn his body.
No matter what, he was the former Winged Monarch's oldest son.
He's also your oldest brother.
If this spread outs,
I fear a few of the generals won't be happy.
The people will talk about this, too.
His death will bring catastrophe to the Winged Realm and the entire world.
By doing this, we are already being kind to him.
Go and find the whereabouts of the princess immediately.
Bring her back to the Winged Realm at all costs.
If you encounter Xuan Nü,
no need to report to me and kill her immediately.
Bring her corpse back to the Winged Realm.
No matter what, she's the woman whom I legally married and brought into Grand Purple Palace.
When I'm dead, I want to be buried with her.
Yes.
They really flew past.
No, I must find Yan Zhi as soon as possible.
I must find her quickly.
Selling baozi!
Linhe Inn has wines and meats.
Our prices are reasonable. We don't deceive elders and children.
Don't miss it.
Sir, having a meal?
Please come in.
Sir, are you hungry?
- Yeah.
- Please come in.
Come look at this!
The jade is getting hotter.
Yan Zhi must be nearby.
We don't deceive elders and children.
Don't miss it.
Miss, are you hungry?
Sir, is there a lady nearby?
She's beautiful and pale with big eyes.
She's the same build as me.
She's looking for Yan Zhi.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Is she not here?
Miss, what's wrong with your eyes?
Should I find a physician for you?
A lowlife ruined my eyes.
Sir, please tell me!
Is that lady here?
There's someone similar who's in this store.
Take me to her!
Sure.
Watch your step.
Miss, wait a bit.
Sure.
Look. She's looking for you.
This jade is really hot.
That's right. Li Yuan was right.
The one in the front is Yan Zhi.
It's Yan Zhi!
Yan Zhi! Yan Zhi!
I'm Xuan Nü. Xuan Nü.
Xuan Nü? She's Xuan Nü?
No way! She doesn't look like that.
- Are you Second Sister-in-Law?
- Yes.
Why has your appearance become like this?
I know I look different.
It's because of Bai Qian, that lowlife.
She took away my beauty.
Yan Zhi, am I ugly?
Am I?
You're not, Second Sister-in-Law. Not at all.
Don't be afraid.
Mute, you... You can talk!
Yes. I can speak.
There's no time to explain to you right now.
Can you take care of the guests downstairs?
Okay. Okay.
Fortunately, I don't have to work today.
Take your time chatting.
There's no need for you to come out that soon.
About that...
If your second sister-in-law needs a doctor, just call me.
I will call you if I need anything. Go now.
Okay.
Yan Zhi,
who was that man?
Did you bring him along when you left the Winged Realm?
No, I left the Winged Realm alone.
Second Sister-in-Law, don't worry.
He's just an ordinary mortal.
He has been taking care of me for the past few years.
He has been taking care of you?
Yes.
Is this your child?
He's my son.
A prince?
Let me take a look at him.
Good boy. He's so obedient.
Why isn't he breathing?
There's no sign of breathing at all.
Doesn't my son look exactly like me?
Yes, he does.
I personally raised him since he was born.
It has been 300 years.
He doesn't cry or kick up a fuss.
He's very well behaved.
Yan Zhi, isn't he very well behaved?
Yes.
How could a mother not know whether her child is a boy or girl?
The child didn't grow up or cry for 300 years.
Could it be that when she gave birth to the child...
I'm afraid she's refused to accept reality since then.
That's why she...
Second Sister-in-Law,
did you find out that he doesn't cry, create a fuss and he's not breathing?
He's only asleep.
Yan Zhi, trust me.
If I can find a method, he will definitely wake up.
My son will definitely wake up.
I have been with the princess of the Winged Tribe for almost three years and there are still no clues.
Now, Xuan Nü's here with a disfigured face and an injured body.
It seems like there hasn't been any peace in the Winged Realm.
If I continue to follow her, I may be able to find out something.
This is not right.
What if Yan Zhi cures her eyes? What should I do?
Xuan Nü will recognize me.
I must not let her see my face.
Second Sister-in-Law, give it a try and check if you can see clearly.
No, it's still bloody and blurry.
This is strange.
It's just an ordinary injury.
Why can't they recover?
It's okay.
Anyway, I don't want to look at my fake face.
It's too ugly.
Sister-in-Law, don't be afraid.
I will try another method on another day.
Your eyes can be cured.
First, tell me what happened.
How did you turn out this way?
Your second older brother killed your eldest brother
and hung his head publicly outside Grand Purple Palace for several days.
His body was burned to ashes, too.
I only advised him a little, but your second older brother was furious with me.
He scolded me for birthing a stillborn and severing his lineage,
and damaged my eyes,
and wanted to drive me and my child out of the Winged Realm.
You... Why are you crying?
There is a change in my family.
My eldest brother is dead.
Li Yuan is dead?
Life and death is human nature.
Don't be sad.
All those years, I have never talked
because I didn't want to communicate with those irrelevant people.
I really didn't mean to trick you.
It's okay. It's okay.
Thank you for taking care of me for these past years.
I... I didn't do much.
I remember now.
I have some matters at the government office today.
I'm leaving first.
I thought you didn't have anything to do today.
I... I forgot about this earlier.
The people are uneasy.
The people are saying that the Old Winged Monarch will be back.
Is this true?
Wasn't Old Winged Monarch sealed by Mo Yuan at Ruoshui?
There were some movements in the Ruoshui River.
This is the sign.
If Old Monarch is released, with his temper, he will definitely fight to the death with the Heavenly Tribe.
Yes.
How many people will die again?
I'd rather die in the wilderness than to keep paying tribute to the Heavenly Tribe!
What do you think has gotten into His Majesty?
Not only does he favor Virtuous Consort Chen, he even decreed that he will not make any consort selections for the next five years.
Since Noble Consort went to the Daoist temple over a decade ago, the consorts in the harem haven't given birth to any children.
I thought His Majesty would impart his power to the crown prince.
But now, there's a Virtuous Consort Chen who's receiving favors.
If she has a good life and gives birth to another royal son, the crown prince's post will be vulnerable.
With a flick of a finger, more than ten years have passed in mortal time.
If we go back to Nine Heavens,
will the emperor blame me for ruining his original tribulation of love?
But I can't bear to hurt him,
even if this is a tribulation he has to experience.
Even if you can't bear to, you still need to.
Every time when you see me, why do you always feel uneasy?
I was momentarily absentminded.
Your Majesty, stay put.
I will get someone to clean this up.
What? You want me to give the Noble Consort a hard time?
That's right. Think of a way to make her jealous and fight for favors.
Didn't I give you some good novels?
There are many methods there.
But Noble Consort has been living in the Daoist temple for a long time.
What's there to be jealous about?
Her son has been conferred as the crown prince.
Just that should be enough to make the women in the harem jealous.
But you have been favored for a long time and there's still no direct descendant.
There's no hatred in your heart at all?
There isn't any.
Have you ever felt jealous?
I merely want to have a short fate with the emperor.
When would I find the time to be jealous?
You are really suitable to be with the emperor.
Really?
Following is following, but you two are destined to have no love fate with each other.
I know that I don't have a place in the emperor's heart
but can you help me to complete this beautiful dream?
What I need to do is to ruin your beautiful dream.
Young Highness, remember this.
You must make the emperor hate women and be totally disappointed.
Then, his task for coming to the Mortal Realm will be accomplished.
Must I do this?
Yes.
What is this?
This is the latest drama script.
The harem fighting for favor and framing Noble Consort.
Just do according to what's written here.
[Three Deities Hall]
Your Highness.
I should be greeting you instead, Older Sister.
I'm no longer the noble consort.
There's no need to greet me.
Older Sister, before I received the favors of His Majesty,
I was living in the Cold Palace and often heard stories about you.
I can finally meet this legendary person today.
I merely saw through the vanity of the world and became focused on cultivating Daoism.
Your Highness, you are exaggerating.
This is the first time we have met.
There's no need to be so formal.
By the way, Older Sister, I heard there are the best teas from the palace in this Daoist temple.
I wonder if I could ask for a cup of tea from you.
Okay. Your Highness, please come with me.
Your Majesty, Virtuous Consort has been having bad abdominal pains since an hour ago.
She fainted several times.
Why is this so?
The physician said she ate some unhygienic food.
Unhygienic food?
I heard that Virtuous Consort went to visit Noble Consort at the Daoist temple and drank some tea.
When she came back, she was in this condition.
She went to the Daoist temple?
Yes, Your Majesty.
Didn't I give instructions not to let Virtuous Consort go to the Daoist temple?
Your Majesty, who in this palace can stop Virtuous Consort other than you?
Your Majesty, you should visit her immediately.
One minute, she faints; and the next, she vomits.
What should we do?
Well.. It can't be...
Can't be what?
It can't be that Noble Consort is afraid that Virtuous Consort will give birth to a son
who'll take the crown prince's position, so she intentionally poisoned her?
How presumptuous!
How could you defame the birth mother of the crown prince?
I deserve to die! I deserve to die!
She gave birth to the crown prince.
Don't give such indiscriminate comments.
Yes.
Go with me to visit Virtuous Consort.
This act is too sinister.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
Why is your abdomen suddenly in pain?
You are perspiring a lot, too.
I heard you went to Noble Consort's Daoist temple.
Yes, I did go.
Since young, Aunt taught me that I must be worthy of my status as the monarchess of Green Hill.
How could I talk nonsense and harm a kind woman who's also religious?
Jiu'er.
This won't do.
If I do this, I will disregard and embarrass Aunt's teachings.
I must change to another method.
I did go to the Daoist temple,
but this has nothing to do with Noble Consort.
Your Majesty, please don't let your imagination run wild.
A few days ago, I sneaked off to play with water and caught a cold.
This has nothing to do with the Noble Consort.
Of course, I won't blame her.
I know her character very well,
but how could you not take care of your own health?
Did you even think about how I would feel?
I was too playful and caused you to worry.
Jiu'er,
just now, I was afraid that you would say Noble Consort harmed you.
Your Majesty, why would you speculate?
If I had really said that,
would you have believed me?
I wouldn't.
That's right.
I forgot that when I was still of the noble person rank,
you once lamented to me the heartbreak you felt with the noble consort.
You will definitely believe her and not me.
I believe the both of you.
Noble Consort has distanced herself from the world a long time ago.
As for you, you are the one I love the most, who's naturally kind and pure.
You would never harm her.
When I was walking here, I was very confused.
I clearly knew that with Noble Consort's human nature,
she would never do this.
But then, I thought that if you had any mishaps,
I will never spare anyone from the Daoist temple.
Looks like I have the ability to be an incompetent king.
Do you mean what you said?
Definitely.
Jiu'er,
if anything were to happen to you, I wouldn't be so sensible again.
Then, what if I do something wrong one day?
No matter what mistake you make,
I'll always pardon you.
Please wait two more years.
I'll do everything I can to make him hate me after those two years.
Young Highness,
don't think that just because you know me, you can prolong this.
The emperor is an immortal who has lived for hundreds of thousands of years.
Will he really remember this fate that only lasted a few days?
Who cares if it's just a few days?
I'll spend as much time as I can with him.
Fine.
I will give you two years deadline.
I will return when it's time to return.
Your Majesty.
It's late. Why did you come here?
I made some cakes.
I wanted to appreciate the moon with you.
Appreciate the moon?
Didn't you say you were unwell?
Did you forget what the imperial physician said?
That's why I sneaked here.
The imperial physician doesn't know.
Jiu'er, you seem somewhat different today.
Is that so?
Where am I different?
This past year, I kept thinking that you were troubled by something.
But tonight, I feel that you have let go of your problems in your heart.
You are finally willing to be honest and open with me.
I thought through everything.
Life is short.
Since I have you in my heart, I must treat you well.
If not, when I think back,
I will definitely regret it.
Is this true?
Since you have thought it through, come here.
Your Majesty, you must promise me.
No matter what, you must not forget these two years.
I promise you.
Yan Zhi, don't blame me for being cold-hearted.
Your father can only get stronger if I kill you.
Then, he can break from the bondage of the Donghuang Bell.
Only your father can slaughter all the people of Green Hill and get revenge for me.
Who are you? Are you from the Winged Tribe?
Do you not recognize my voice?
You're Zi Lan?!
That's right. It's me.
Why are you here?
If I weren't here,
you would've already killed Yan Zhi, who saved you!
Xuan Nü, it's been 70,000 years,
yet you're still this ungrateful!
What I do is none of your business!
Did you forget how your teacher died?
Did you forget your hatred against the Grand Purple Palace?!
Yet you're protecting the Winged Tribe's princess.
Are you not afraid of being punished?!
A traitor like you has no right talking about my punishment!
I don't know why you're trying to kill Yan Zhi!
But I'm warning you, as long as I'm here,
and you try to kill her again,
I'll make sure you know the price of betraying the Heavenly Tribe!
I won't harm you tonight
since you lost your position
and you have a child.
That's why I have a bit of compassion towards you.
Don't force me.
If you stay with Yan Zhi and treat her well, I won't touch you.
Do you understand?
I understand.
”Cold” by Aska Yang & Diamond Zhang
♫ The temperature gradually drops as night falls ♫
♫ Fallen blossoms become frost ♫
♫ In the distance, you are gazing out afar and exhausting the twilight hours ♫
♫ Without considering the difficulty of forgetting each other ♫
♫ Tender peach blossoms are cold ♫
♫ How could you bear to let go of so many uncertain hearts in the previous lifetime ♫
♫ And still show no pain, no yearning, and no signs that you were forced? ♫
♫ All are just illusions ♫
♫ During the cold night, my yearning for you runs as a river ♫
♫ And transforming into spring soil to nourish me ♫
♫ The fleeting years fill up my lover’s sleeve ♫
♫ Pieces of flowers and plants flow into the waters ♫
♫ The cold will of heaven dresses in glittering colors of flowers ♫
♫ And fall into the mortal realm to hurt my feelings ♫
♫ Calamities are easy to overcome, but trials of love are difficult to overcome ♫
♫ My depreciating heart still holds some hatred from my previous life ♫
♫ The cold three lives and three worlds are as sudden
as a dream ♫
♫ The wind dries my tears in those instantaneous years ♫
♫ If we can no longer recognize our memories ♫
♫ Then allow our love to rest deep within the dust ♫
♫ When will the cold ten miles of peach blossoms
bloom again? ♫
♫ I see a gust of wind under the tree again ♫
♫ Fallen blossoms are of love, flowing waters are of heartlessness ♫
♫ Don’t allow our past grudges, love, and hate to chill the innocence of the flower ♫
♫ My hope in this lifetime is to be with you ♫