”Three Lives, Three Worlds” by Jason Zhang
♫ Listen to the rustling of the wind ♫
♫ Whose sorrow is it trying to stir up? ♫
♫ My yearning grows so instantaneously ♫
♫ That I forget how long the night is ♫
♫ I hold the tears in my palm until they become burning hot ♫
♫ I’m only willing to be crazy for you for three lifetimes ♫
♫ Falling blossoms are everywhere, and I also smell the fragrance of the zither ♫
♫ With you, I wander the world ♫
♫  If love is too desolate, I will dream this dream with you ♫
♫ And redeem all your tears ♫
♫ No matter how far this journey will be or how long these three lifetimes will be ♫
♫ We will be hand in hand until eternity ♫
♫ Despite the miserable wind, vast fog, rolling storm, or overflowing snow ♫
♫ I will walk with you every step of the way ♫
♫ I will hold your hand, don’t be alarmed, don’t worry about tomorrow ♫
♫ Even if we are destined to wander the world ♫
♫ Even if we travel to the remotest corners of Earth ♫
♫ Never let go of each other’s hands ♫
♫ Never forget our mutual love ♫
♫ Life does not need to be too brilliant ♫
♫ Empty glories eventually become nothing, those things you persisted will leave with the wind ♫
♫ Why is love full of ups and downs? ♫
♫ How many storms do we have to face before our hearts stop wavering? ♫
♫ Let’s run through our past together ♫
♫ I’ll wait with you for the wind to stop, fog to clear, rain to end, and snow to melt ♫
♫ Before seeing the absolute beautiful moon again ♫
♫ I will still be by your side ♫
[Eternal Love]
[Episode 4]
But listen to me.
Ever since you left Grand Purple Palace,
and I was imprisoned by my father in the dungeon,
I've been thinking about you day and night.
That's when I knew my heart could never hold another person.
Although we're close, I don't have any feelings for you.
I'm sorry.
Ah Yin, listen to me.
I'm being serious.
I just want to be with you like we were in Grand Purple Palace,
drinking together, having fun, chatting about anything and everything.
But after all, you're the prince of the Winged Tribe.
Why don't you sleep in the guestroom tonight?
It's getting dark outside.
I'll see you off the mountain first thing tomorrow morning.
I didn't travel thousands of miles here just to hear those words.
I'm sorry to disappoint Your Second Highness.
How dare you, Winged Tribesman, for coming into Kunlun Void!
Seventeenth, back off.
Are you trying to protect him?
Have you forgotten your identity?
Let's not mention how your father tormented my ninth junior brother.
Even today, you dared to come to Kunlun Void to bother Seventeenth.
I can't spare you!
You're Ah Yin's senior brother, so I won't fight with you.
So what if you do?
That day in Grand Purple Palace, my junior brothers suffered losses because their magic was suppressed.
Today, I'll show you the sword techniques of Kunlun Void!
Don't! Eldest Senior Brother, forget it.
If I don't teach him a lesson, he might come to Kunlun Void to bother you again.
Eldest Senior Brother!
Even you're protecting him?
Just let him go.
Why? Have you forgotten how his father humiliated you?
When we were in Grand Purple Palace, he took great care of us.
Moreover, if not because I need to apologize to Teacher for my sins, I would have committed suicide already.
On the day we left, if he hadn't protected Seventeenth, Seventeenth would have possibly been killed.
- Really?
- Yes.
Even if that's the case, he's the prince of the Winged Tribe.
Don't forget that his father abducted you.
Hurry and leave!
Ah Yin, wait for me. I'll be back.
- Don't run!
- Eldest Senior Brother!
- Zi Lan!
- Eldest Senior Brother.
- After him!
- Yes!
Eldest Senior Brother, spare him.
I don't care anymore!
Eldest Senior Brother.
I didn't catch him, but it looked like he's gone to that sealed cave.
That cave?
Eldest Senior Brother, should I keep chasing him?
No need.
Ninth Junior Brother knows right from wrong.
If he spoke up for Li Jing, it means he's not a bad person.
We just needed to chase him off.
Eldest Senior Brother, just from afar, that cave looks threatening.
Even Teacher told us to keep away from it.
What's inside there?
That cave is the place Lord of Lingbao borrowed from Teacher.
People say that a very demonic creature lives there.
If that Winged Prince is lucky, he'll be able to avoid it.
If he's not lucky, then it'll be his inexorable doom.
High Immortal Si Yin, why did you invite me to the foot of the mountain today?
I'm free today, so I wanted to take you for a walk.
I heard that Eldest Senior Brother had a fight today.
Yes.
I heard that that person is a prince.
Since you returned from the Winged Realm, you've been studying magic and Dao philosophy everyday.
Is it because the Winged Realm is really about to rebel?
Why are you suddenly asking about this?
In the past, when I lived in Qian Qian's den manor, I occasionally heard her talk about it.
She said that the current Winged Monarch has always wanted to rebel, so a big war is unavoidable.
That's true.
However, they wouldn't be able to win.
My teacher's battle formation can annihilate their entire tribe.
- Battle formation?
- Yes.
Who is that?
- Immortal!
- You little monster, where did you come from?
Don't you know that this is the Kunlun Void?
Immortal, hurry and follow me to save His Second Highness!
- Are you talking about Li Jing?
- Yes.
Let's go. I'll come with you.
High Immortal Si Yin!
Li Jing!
Li Jing! Hurry and get up.
Your Highness! Your Highness, are you okay?
Have mercy!
Lord of Lingbao.
I'm surprised that you were promoted to a High Immortal this fast.
Your Highness.
It just happened a few days ago.
Are you here to look for Teacher?
Not really.
I've put on a seal on this phoenix.
Earlier, I sensed that something abnormal happened; hence, I came here to check.
Is this phoenix your carriage?
Not really.
The demonic character of this phoenix hasn't been eliminated yet.
I then tried borrowing the spiritual power under Kunlun Void to remove it.
I never thought that it would hurt you two instead.
High Immortal, can you just let me handle it?
Since this phoenix is yours, of course, you can.
This is the Cloud-Breaking Fan.
Although it can't compare to the Kunlun Fan of Yuqing, it's still quite useful.
Take this as my compensation for your injuries.
I can't accept it.
High Immortal, no need to be courteous. Just accept it.
Thank you, Lord.
High Immortal, please remember that the amount of power that this fan can produce is dependent on the power of its user.
Lord, don't worry. I surely won't let this fan end up in the hands of a powerful evil person.
I will take my leave then.
Your Highness!
Let's go.
- You're awake.
- Ah Yin.
It's good that you're awake. Recuperate first.
Thank you very much for blocking off that phoenix for me today.
What block?
It was actually useless.
I never thought that I would need your rescues twice today.
This is Kunlun Void.
You are the Second Prince of the Winged Realm.
Your power would surely be suppressed.
There's nothing to be embarrassed about.
Ah Yin,
thank you for coming to see me.
After getting locked up by my father, although I shamelessly came to look for you,
I then remembered...
Even I myself look down on me.
You are the seventeenth disciple of Kunlun Void,
and also a high immortal respected by many in the Four Seas and Eight Wildernesses.
What great fortune or capability do I have to make you see me again?
Stop thinking about these for now.
Anyway, that phoenix has been taken away.
Just recuperate here.
I'll go get you some more warm water.
Ah Yin!
What should I do if I want to see you again?
- See me?
- You should at least give me a way to enter Kunlun Void, right?
With this talisman, you can enter and exit Kunlun Void at ease.
Oh, right. No one in Kunlun Void knows that I'm a woman.
Hence, you must be careful not to be found by my senior brothers.
Xuan Nü, you came just in time.
Come with me. Look!
Your mother came to see you.
You unfilial daughter.
You actually came here to Kunlun Void without permission just to escape your marriage.
Come back with me. Don't bring embarrassment to your older sister here.
I won't go back! I won't marry that black bear sprite!
Do you think you're like your older sister?
She was a direct descendant. Of course, she can marry into the Bai Family of Green Hill, while I am just a concubine.
Do you understand?
With you being this lofty, you will only harm yourself in the future!
Eldest Senior Brother! Please save me!
If I don't find a person that I love, I'd rather not marry!
Auntie, look at how strongly your daughter is opposed to this marriage.
Why not just forget it?
This Daoist Priest, I'm her mother.
Taking her back to get married is just right and reasonable.
Although you are Mo Yuan's disciple, a High Immortal highly revered in all realms,
it's still unreasonable for you to hinder me like this.
I...
If this marriage gets delayed,
- are you able to bear the responsibility?
- I...
May I ask what your identity is before coming up here in Kunlun Void?
- My Eldest Senior Brother came from a very influential background.
He's the second prince of the Western Sea.
Yes.
Is he engaged?
No.
Then, seeing how you hindered me like that earlier, you must like my daughter.
- That's hard to say.
- Who knows?
You two stop your nonsense! Auntie, listen to me—
Auntie. Auntie, look.
Their relationship just started.
You mustn't directly burst the bubble.
- It's better to just let them figure it out by themselves.
- That's right.
My Eldest Senior Brother is after all a person with fame and reputation.
It's not good to directly ask him. Not good.
Once the two of them have confirmed their feelings,
are you still afraid that my Eldest Senior Brother won't go to your house to propose marriage?
Hence, in my opinion, just let Xuan Nü stay here for a while.
- By then...
- You'll naturally receive some good news.
That's right.
I'm at ease then.
- Auntie, take care.
Auntie, take care.
- Have you two fooled around enough?
- It was very urgent, Eldest Senior Brother.
That's right.
Xuan Nü, don't give it too much thought.
I have no special feelings towards you.
The two of them are just fooling around.
I didn't really put it to heart.
I'm apologizing on their behalf.
As the eldest disciple of Kunlun Void,
how could I think about marriage when I'm in the middle of cultivation?
Moreover, I would be returning to the Western Seas after my training here.
As the second prince of Western Sea, I, of course, must listen to the arrangements of my parents when it comes to marriage.
How could you two casually toy around with it?
It was just to solve an urgent problem, Eldest Senior Brother.
That's right. Stop being mad.
Of course, we know that you don't have any special desires towards Xuan Nü.
We also know that with your status, your marriage is to be bestowed.
Enough. You all go back for night lessons.
Yes.
"Ah Yin,
I only wish to make you smile.
Before leaving, I gift you this poem.
In this poem, I'm making two promises."
I gave him that talisman so he can say goodbye to me before leaving after his injuries heal.
How come he came up with this cheesy poem?
Ah Yin, is that from the second prince of the Winged Realm?
"Don't know when we will be deeply in love.
At this moment, it's hard—"
No fun.
Qian Qian, I'm so envious of you.
You were born with good looks.
If I had your face,
I'd be willing to only live a few hundred years.
You've been saying those words for a few hundred years.
I'm really envious of you!
I like your facial features and your face.
However, my parents gave me such an ugly face.
How are you ugly? I don't think so.
However, since you like my face, I'll give it to you.
- Give it to me?
- Yes.
Hey, Zhe Yan has a good skill that can change your looks.
I'll put in some good words for you to him,
- and ask him to teach it to you.
- Don't go back on your word.
Once I learn it, will I look just like you?
I think you can maintain it for a few hours.
What? I can only change my appearance occasionally?
Why do you want to constantly look like me?
Of all the Fox Tribesmen, you look the most similar to me.
Once you're grown up, you'll look even more like me.
It's just a measly spell. Don't take it too seriously.
Also, you can't use this spell to do bad things.
Karma and retribution. If you do bad, you'll be punished. Come with me!
How could I do bad?
Why?
We are the same,
but why do I have to marry a lowly bear sprite?
Ah Yin, my words today might be a bit dreary.
Can you understand me trying to completely indulge and get myself totally drunk?
Singing while drinking, still not enjoying despite forcing myself to be happy.
My clothes started to get loose, but I don't regret it.
Just for my love, I've gotten thin and haggard.
How is it dreary?
It clearly is very sad.
I'm going to my night class. Don't stop me.
Okay, I'll take it. Can you leave now?
Ah Yin, I'll see you in our next life.
He's going to commit suicide?
Li Jing!
Li Jing! Li Jing!
That weapon will only hurt him externally.
High Immortal, why don't you try to stimulate His Highness' heart?
Maybe then, he'll wake up.
Li Jing, if you can wake up, I'll agree to your request.
Once you've agreed, you can't go back on your word.
You liar!
What if I do break my word?
Then, I'll really die.
- Go, then. I'm leaving.
- Hey!
Ah Yin, I've been living for half a month in Kunlun Void,
and I've only seen you once.
I miss you so much my heart hurts.
Cut it out.
Let's not even talk about us.
How will you deal with those ladies in your inner palace?
Immediately remove them!
Really?
I, Li Jing, will only be with Ah Yin this lifetime.
If I break this promise, may I live my life alone, without any descendants.
Don't say that. Hurry and sit down.
Ah Yin, then... can you massage me?
It really hurts.
In the past, your fire qilin never spoke.
(Qilin is a specific type of the lin mythological family of one-horned beasts.)
Why did he suddenly start talking today?
He talked too much when he was younger,
so I told him to stop talking and pretend to be a mute.
Oh. I noticed that he knows you very well.
I'm sure he helped you win over a lot of women in the past.
My bone! Oh, my bone!
Don't move.
Please don't move.
Why are you looking at me that way?
I really want to be with you.
You... What nonsense do you think about all day?
You're avoiding me again!
I won't talk with you anymore.
I'm a noble disciple of Kunlun Void.
How could I stand your constant sappiness?
- But...
- I won't talk with you anymore. I'm leaving now.
You can stay here alone.
Don't let my senior brothers see you.
Kunlun Void doesn't allow cloud-riding.
Don't come again in the future.
Nobody is willing to speak in detail about Teacher and the Donghuang Bell weapon.
Forget it. I'll wait until Teacher returns from his retreat.
Ah Yin, you're always disappearing after your morning classes. I can never find you.
Did you find a good place to spend your time?
There's no such thing.
I just go help Eldest Senior Brother feed those cranes.
I know. Just like Eldest Senior Brother, you've been avoiding me.
That's not what I... I'm trying to do.
If it's not, why are you lying to me?
Sixteenth Senior Brother has always been the one to feed the cranes.
He said that you were once bullied by those cranes, so you're scared of them.
Why would you voluntarily feed them, then?
I...
Forget it. I don't want to hear it.
Fine, then.
I just go to see a friend of mine.
Friend?
Is it the one who sent you the love letter?
That's not a love letter!
It's not a love letter.
Then, can you take me with you?
Take you with me?
Your friend is also my friend.
Of course, I also want to meet him.
He has a special identity.
I know that you don't trust me and you think that my lowly status would embarrass you.
Hey, fine. Let's not talk about it anymore.
Come with me then.
Ah Yin! Look.
This is a bamboo flute I made for you.
You're always making these little toys to flatter me.
In the past, you made those little animals.
Thank you.
Oh, right. She has a rather complicated relationship with me.
You can say that she's a distant cousin of mine.
She's from the Fox Tribe. Her name is Xuan Nü.
This is the second prince of the Winged Tribe, Li Jing.
Where did this young Si Yin come from?
I can't compare to Si Yin.
But you look and feel too similar to Si Yin!
If you don't have time in the future, you can have her come over so that I'm not bored.
You!
You just want someone to keep you company. You just don't want to be bored.
Of course not.
Will you be free these days?
That's not it. I just wanted to tell you that Teacher is about to leave his retreat,
so it'll be inconvenient for me to come down the mountain.
Will you go back to Grand Purple Palace to find amusement?
I definitely won't go back!
All the beauties in the palace have left.
In the future, I'll only wait for you at Kunlun Void.
You should take this back.
There are too many new things in my room.
My eldest senior brother is getting suspicious.
Okay then.
Did you know?
A while ago, my teacher blocked my heavenly tribulation for me.
He was severely injured.
I'm very worried about him.
Ah Yin, why nine out of ten sentences you say are about Mo Yuan when you are with me?
Really? Isn't it normal for us, teacher and disciple, to be close?
Ah Yin,
it's rare for you to come off the mountain,
but you bring someone with you
so that I can't properly talk to you.
Xuan Nü is watching.
Xuan Nü, are the cranes at the back of the mountain calling?
Yes, I think so.
I have an emergency. I have to go.
- You just got here. You're leaving already?
- Yes.
My senior brothers are very cautious nowadays.
If you're bored, you can walk around.
Walk around?
I'm afraid that if I see your senior brother, he'll beat me up again.
If you're scared, then walk carefully.
I can't talk anymore. I'll leave now.
Let's go, Xuan Nü.
- Eldest Senior Brother.
You're being quite obedient today. You came back so early.
I heard the cranes calling, so I thought Teacher had returned from retreat.
It turns out Senior Brother Zi Lan was just playing with them out of boredom.
Don't worry. I'll be sure to relay your filial piety to Teacher.
That's not what I'm after.
I sincerely hope that Teacher can return from his retreat soon.
After all, if not for me, Teacher wouldn't be so injured.
Then, let's return to the main palace now.
It turns out that you abandoned me because you thought Mo Yuan was about to return.
Ah Yin, are you so impatient that you wait day and night to see him?
Xuan Nü?
Yes.
Why are you dressed like a man?
It's more convenient for me to leave the mountain like this.
Oh, that's true. The teacher and disciples at Kunlun Void are all men.
It's indeed inconvenient for a girl like you.
Earlier, I almost mistook you for Ah Yin.
Although Ah Yin and I look similar,
there is great difference in our social standings.
He's High God Mo Yuan's favorite disciple,
while I am the most insignificant immortal of Green Hill.
I'm sure you have your own charm.
Did Ah Yin ask you to come here?
No, I came specifically to come find Your Highness.
I wanted to ask you some questions face-to-face,
but I was afraid to make it awkward for Your Highness.
Just say it.
Are Your Highness and Si Yin in a relationship?
Although I have a hunch, I'm afraid to think too much about it.
But why is Your Highness waiting in Kunlun Void everyday?
Aren't you afraid the Winged Tribesmen will find out?
A relationship between the Heavenly and Winged Tribes is impossible.
Did Ah Yin tell you to say those words?
No! Don't misunderstand, Your Highness.
I have considered the questions you raised.
If Ah Yin wasn't from the Heavenly Tribe,
I would marry her and bring her into Grand Purple Palace no matter the cost.
However, as of today, I can only take it one step at a time.
I'm afraid to think too much.
If there's someone in his heart, I'm afraid it's High God Mo Yuan.
Stop talking.
Your Highness.
You're Si Yin?
Seventeenth, stop hiding.
Eldest Senior Brother.
Xuan Nü?
Why are you wearing Si Yin's clothes?
Earlier, I went for a walk at the foot of the mountain to clear my head.
I was afraid female clothes would attract too much attention and make people criticize Kunlun Void,
so I stole Si Yin's clothes.
You and Seventeenth look alike from the back.
Eldest Senior Brother, if you don't need anything, I'll leave now.
Go ahead.
[Good Tea]
[Gathering Teahouse]
Customer, here's your tea.
Does Your Highness come to the Mortal Realm often?
I frequently came in the past.
Your Highness said that you once dismissed many beauties in Grand Purple Palace for Ah Yin.
If my weight in Your Highness's heart can be half of Ah Yin's,
I would be satisified.
Xuan Nü, that night...
That night, I was just confused momentarily.
Doing such a thing is irresponsible to both her and you.
If Your Highness wants me to forget about it, then I will.
I'll pretend like it never happened.
Your Highness, stop blaming yourself.
I did it willingly.
Good.
Customer, upstairs please.
- Ah Yin!
- Young sir, who are you waiting for?
For you.
So frivolous.
You must have waited for 4 hours.
Earlier, my eldest senior brother held me back for something.
That's why I asked Xuan Nü sneak out first to keep you company.
Four hours are nothing.
We haven't seen each other in 10 days.
Has it been ten days already?
Exactly ten days.
Ah Yin, when will you finish your studies?
For a dabbler like me, at least 70,000 to 80,000 years.
Then...
It's because you want to stay by Mo Yuan's side, right?
Li Jing, what nonsense are you saying?
Did you hear someone gossiping?
Is it really just nonsense?
Who told you what exactly?
I'll head back first.
I just got here. Why are you leaving?
What's wrong with everyone?
Did you bully her?
I wouldn't dare to bully your friend.
For you.
You made this?
Thank you.
Have you been to the Junji Mountain of the Eastern Wilderness before?
- Junji Mountain of the Eastern Wilderness?
- Yes.
Whenever my senior brothers and I get a chance to play in the Mortal Realm, we'll go there.
That place is sparsely populated and has lots of animals. It's really interesting.
- Let's go together next time.
- Okay.
Let's go together next time.
What did you say? A great battle is near at hand, yet Li Jing is missing?
That's right.
I'm guessing he's probably... probably...
Say it.
I think he went to Kunlun Void.
- Kunlun Void?
- When Li Jing was in Grand Purple Palace,
he would have private meetings with that immortal called Si Yin.
With my understanding of him, I think he has left with that Heavenly Tribesman.
If that's true,
then he's no longer my son.
Your Highness, I don't understand.
You are of noble status.
Why would you spend your days in Kunlun Void, wasting your time away?
I don't understand, either.
Your Highness clearly knows that Ah Yin's favorite person is High God Mo Yuan.
Why would you keep tormenting yourself?
I know that you're still bothered by the fact that she's from the Heavenly Tribe.
I'm not from the Heavenly Tribe. I'm willing to follow Your Highness to the Winged Tribe.
Right.
You're right.
In the end, the Heavenly and Winged Tribes cannot be together.
Teacher has been in retreat for so long.
I wonder when he'll come back.
Fourth Brother, I've thought about it for a long time, and I decided that I need to tell you about something.
The second prince of Winged Tribe and I met as a coincidence, and we like each other.
Although it is prohibited for us to be together,
I have already set my heart on him.
But, as of today, our two tribes are at great odds with each other.
I'm afraid that the Winged Monarch will eventually declare war on the Heavenly Tribe.
He and I...
- Seventeenth.
- Eldest Senior Brother.
When I attacked Li Jing previously, you blamed me for going too hard.
I really regret not killing him.
Before he had a chance to abduct you, he first abducted Xuan Nü.
What did you just say?
Earlier, when I went off the mountain, I saw them strolling hand in hand.
They were acting so intimately.
It's quite strange, if I think about it.
Xuan Nü is an immortal, and Li Jing is a good-for-nothing.
How did they end up together?
Seventeenth!
High Immortal!
”Cold” by Aska Yang & Diamond Zhang
♫ The temperature gradually drops as night falls ♫
♫ Fallen blossoms become frost ♫
♫ In the distance, you are gazing out afar and exhausting the twilight hours ♫
♫ Without considering the difficulty of forgetting each other ♫
♫ Tender peach blossoms are cold ♫
♫ How could you bear to let go of so many uncertain hearts in the previous lifetime ♫
♫ And still show no pain, no yearning, and no signs that you were forced? ♫
♫ All are just illusions ♫
♫ During the cold night, my yearning for you runs as a river ♫
♫ And transforming into spring soil to nourish me ♫
♫ The fleeting years fill up my lover’s sleeve ♫
♫ Pieces of flowers and plants flow into the waters ♫
♫ The cold will of heaven dresses in glittering colors of flowers ♫
♫ And fall into the mortal realm to hurt my feelings ♫
♫ Calamities are easy to overcome, but trials of love are difficult to overcome ♫
♫ My depreciating heart still holds some hatred from my previous life ♫
♫ The cold three lives and three worlds are
as sudden as a dream ♫
♫ The wind dries my tears in those instantaneous years ♫
♫ If we can no longer recognize our memories, ♫
♫ Then allow our love to rest deep within the dust ♫
♫ When will the cold ten miles
of peach blossoms bloom again? ♫
♫ I see a gust of wind under the tree again ♫
♫ Fallen blossoms are of love, flowing waters are of heartlessness ♫
♫ Don’t allow our past grudges, love, and hate to chill the innocence of the flower ♫
♫ My hope in this lifetime is to be with you ♫