”Three Lives, Three Worlds” by Jason Zhang
♫ Listen to the rustling of the wind ♫
♫ Whose sorrow is it trying to stir up? ♫
♫ My yearning grows so instantaneously ♫
♫ That I forget how long the night is ♫
♫ I hold the tears in my palm until they become burning hot ♫
♫ I’m only willing to be crazy for you for three lifetimes ♫
♫ Falling blossoms are everywhere, and I also smell the fragrance of the zither ♫
♫ With you, I wander the world ♫
♫  If love is too desolate, I will dream this dream with you ♫
♫ And redeem all your tears ♫
♫ No matter how far this journey will be or how long these three lifetimes will be ♫
♫ We will be hand in hand until eternity ♫
♫ Despite the miserable wind, vast fog, rolling storm, or overflowing snow ♫
♫ I will walk with you every step of the way ♫
♫ I will hold your hand, don’t be alarmed, don’t worry about tomorrow ♫
♫ Even if we are destined to wander the world ♫
♫ Even if we travel to the remotest corners of Earth ♫
♫ Never let go of each other’s hands ♫
♫ Never forget our mutual love ♫
♫ Life does not need to be too brilliant ♫
♫ Empty glories eventually become nothing, those things you persisted will leave with the wind ♫
♫ Why is love full of ups and downs? ♫
♫ How many storms do we have to face before our hearts stop wavering? ♫
♫ Let’s run through our past together ♫
♫ I’ll wait with you for the wind to stop, fog to clear, rain to end, and snow to melt ♫
♫ Before seeing the absolute beautiful moon again ♫
♫ I will still be by your side ♫
[Eternal Love]
[Episode 9]
Your Second Highness.
You may all go.
Yes.
What do you think of this place?
How does it compare to Green Hill?
It's beautiful!
This is the Lotus Pond of the Heavenly Palace.
It's also the most beautiful place here.
Shao Xin, it wasn't my intention to sneak you up into the Heavenly Palace.
Give me some time to find a way to introduce you formally to everyone,
so that you can receive worship from all of the Immortals.
Your Second Highness.
Third Younger Brother.
Second Older Brother, does she come from the Green Hill Fox Den?
She's the maidservant that I just brought up.
I plan to have her serve me personally.
What's wrong, Third Younger Brother?
Since when did you show such interest to my personal maidservants?
I asked you if she came from the Green Hill Fox Den.
Did Ye Hua tell you?
So she really is Bai Qian's maidservant.
That's right.
Second Older Brother, we need to hurry.
You need to send this little Bashe snake back to Green Hill before Father Monarch returns.
No. You can't go.
I'll go.
Since I brought her up here, I won't send her back.
You can't mess around with this.
You can pick anyone, just not her!
I'm the second son of the Heavenly Monarch.
Can I not even decide who my wife and concubines should be?
After that battle 70,000 years ago, High God Mo Yuan's spirit was shattered,
and the Heavenly Realm's minor tribe leaders are growing more disgruntled with Father Monarch.
Father Monarch wanted to stabilize his throne.
That's why he formed your marriage alliance with Green Hill.
- Second Older Brother, you can't just—
- Enough!
I understand.
We can't offend Green Hill.
I'm glad you know.
It's fine if you want to force me to marry Bai Qian, but I like her maidservant.
She also needs to marry me.
You can't do that!
You haven't even married Bai Qian yet, but you've seduced her maidservant.
And you want to marry both at the same time?
Aren't you... you telling the world that Bai Qian can't even compare to a little Bashe snake?
Your Second Highness, you should just send me back.
Shao Xin, don't be afraid.
Third Younger Brother, you're right.
Please consider the big picture, Second Older Brother.
When Father Monarch returns, I will report to him and ask him to break off the engagement with Bai Qian.
Then I will officially marry my consort.
You're breaking off the engagement?
What did you say?
You want to break off the engagement?
Father Monarch, I originally thought since I was born as the prince of the Heavenly Tribe,
then my marriage will be in appearance only, for the sake of the Heavenly Tribe.
Is that not the case?
I honestly thought that before I went to Green Hill.
But once I arrived at Green Hill, I didn't see my fiancée, Bai Qian.
She left a message that she'll be in a cultivating retreat,
and left me at the Green Hill den.
Even thought I was mad,
I obeyed your instructions and kept waiting for her return.
But I waited for a month.
I think that Bai Qian of Green Hill is arrogant and despises our Heavenly Tribe.
A month is nothing.
Even if she asks you to wait for 30,000 years, you'll need to wait.
Besides, she inherited the title of the female monarch of Green Hill of Eastern Wilderness,
A prince marrying a female monarch.
How can you be unsatisfied?
But, Father Monarch, I—
Sang Ji, do you have something to say?
I...
Let me guess what you want to say.
Did you fall deeply in love with another woman in Green Hill?
I won't dare do anything that disobeys you.
Fine.
Men, bring in the little Bashe Snake that trespassed into the Heavenly Palace.
How did you get to know him in Green Hill?
Heavenly Monarch, I do not know him.
You've forgotten?
You don't need to look at her.
In the Heavenly Palace, whether you are a prince or my grandchild, you have to sever any feelings.
Marrying and having heirs are for the sake of the Heavenly Tribe and Four Seas and Eight Wildernesses,
not for personal passions.
He can't save you.
He won't dare save you either.
Heavenly Monarch, I really don't know him.
- Throw this little Bashe Snake that trespassed into our palace into the Immortal Execution Platform.
- Yes!
Mercy, Heavenly Monarch! Heavenly Monarch!
You stop right there!
I'm the one that wants to break off the engagement. It has nothing to do with Shao Xin!
What did you say?
Even though Shao Xin is Bai Qian's maidservant, she is the one I love.
I beg of you, Father Monarch.
Please allow me to break the engagement with Bai Qian and marry Shao Xin.
Things have come to this extent, yet you still want to marry her?
That's right.
For the rest of my life, I will not marry anyone else but Shao Xin.
Scoundrel.
Throw this little Bashe snake in the Demon Tower.
Without my consent, no one can go near it.
- Yes!
- Heavenly Monarch, spare my life! Heavenly Monarch!
Father Monarch, Demon Tower isn't a place that she can go.
Father Monarch.
I want to see how long she can last in there.
She even dared to seduce my son.
She didn't seduce me.
I sincerely like her!
Sang Ji,
do you want your nephew to see how disappointing you are?
Kneel here.
Ye Hua.
I'm here.
Don't be like your Second Uncle.
I have high expectations of you.
You are the future Heavenly Monarch.
In this Heavenly Palace, you can have many concubines,
but you must not have a woman who can make you lose your principles.
You are born for the Four Seas and Eight Wildernesses, not for a woman.
I understand.
Greetings, Heavenly Monarch.
Crown Prince, Your Highness.
- What do you have to say?
- Heavenly Monarch,
it is still about the Zhongrong Empire in the mortal realm.
I have handed this over to the Crown Prince.
The Fiery Golden Lion belonged to Qing Cang.
Go and subdue it to show your power to the Four Seas
as preparation for you to receive your crown prince seal in the future.
Yes.
Your Highness the Crown Prince, there's something you must remember.
What is it?
When you go and subdue the beast, do not mess with the fate of the mortals.
If an immortal were to have any relations with humans, it will mess with heavenly laws.
It won't benefit you.
The fate of mortals has always been handled by you.
I will not interfere.
I understand.
Heavenly Monarch, I have finished my homework.
In the past, Sang Ji had very high comprehension skills,
but he didn't do as well as you.
I will reward you handsomely. What do you want?
I want to see my mother.
A kind mother will bring up a useless son.
In the future you are to succeed me.
Your mother will not be able to raise you properly for sure.
She will only raise you to be indecisive and gentle.
I'm not letting you see her for your own good.
I just want to see Mother.
If I you want me to give you permission to see her,
you must achieve the High Immortal rank before you are 20,000 years old.
Heavenly Monarch, this lightning is not your average lightning.
It is heavenly lightning only immortals use for ascension.
If he cannot endure it, he will lose his life.
His Young Highness is only 20,000 years old.
Keep quiet.
Heavenly Monarch, you promised me that if I could achieve the High Immortal rank before I'm 20,000 years old,
you will allow me to see my mother.
Today, I have achieved it.
When can I see my mother?
Take Ye Hua to see his mother.
Thank you, Father Monarch.
Ye Hua.
He's my only son.
When he was born, he was already conferred as the Crown Prince.
Ever since you took him away from me 20,000 years ago,
I have never even see him once.
Why is your body full of scars when you finally show up?
Is it not his blessing to be born in the Heavenly Palace, but a misfortune?
Ye Hua is the future Heavenly Monarch.
Having heavy expectations for him is only natural.
So what if he'll be the Heavenly Monarch?
If he cannot be happy, I'd rather just give him a simple title.
Being a minor Water Monarch is better than being in this Heavenly Palace.
Mother, don't blame Father.
It's all my fault.
I clearly knew that I had to endure the heavenly tribulation,
yet I wore such plain and light-coloured clothes.
In the future, I will only wear black.
Then you won't be able to see any bloodstains so you won't be sad.
Look.
What have you become after being taught by your father and Heavenly Monarch?
Do you think by changing your clothes, you won't bleed?
You are merely hiding it, so no one can see.
Your personality of gritting your teeth and suffering everything alone will only cause you to hurt yourself.
You're awake.
Why did you come here?
I've come to bring you food.
Here.
Who was that shadow?
Why does it keep appearing recently?
Could it be something ominous?
Ye Hua, I've made you so many clothes,
but why do you only wear black all the time?
Such a heavy demeanor.
You don't look like a youth at all.
Today, I heard people in the palace saying
that Second Highness especially went to Green Hill to propose marriage,
but instead fell for the maidservant of Bai Qian.
I actually feel that it's good for Second Highness to marry a little Bashe snake.
I heard that Bai Qian from Green Hill has inherited the throne as the female monarch.
Her status is very high, and we are both her juniors.
If one day, she really enters the Heavenly Palace,
I fear that the two of us won't be able to live comfortably.
Ye Hua!
Heavenly Monarch has given orders that no one is allowed entry into the Demon Tower.
How dare you!
You dare stop me, too?
Move aside.
Move aside!
Second Highness, please conduct yourself properly.
- You!
- Second Older Brother.
Second Older Brother!
This is the decree of Father Monarch. Stop making things difficult for them.
Shao Xin is inside and I don't even know if she's still alive.
How can I be at ease?
Let me try.
The decree of Heavenly Monarch is to not allow anyone to go near,
for being afraid that someone will take the little Bashe snake away.
But he didn't say that no one is allowed to speak with her.
Am I right?
Second Older Brother, go ask and see how Miss Shao Xin is.
Then, we can discuss and plan it at length.
Don't be rash.
Shao Xin, can you hear me?
Shao Xin! Shao Xin!
Second Highness!
Shao Xin, have the vile beasts in there hurt you?
Second Highness, other than Great Lady, you treat me the best.
I've lived for 70,000 to 80,000 years.
Meeting you is my great fortune.
Second Highness!
Shao Xin! Shao Xin!
Second Older Brother! Second Older Brother!
Ye Hua, you should have taken in one or two concubines already.
Do you have any women that you like?
None.
You... just don't have any interest in women.
Yet your Second Uncle...
It was clearly a great marriage that others could only dream about.
Yet he wants to break off an engagement.
Heavenly Monarch, Second Highness asks for an audience with you.
An audience?
Didn't I tell him to lock himself in his palace to reflect on his mistakes?
- Tell him to go back.
- Heavenly Monarch,
Second Highness is kneeling outside Purple Morning Palace.
I dare not ask him to leave.
- Let him in.
- Yes.
Leave now.
You need not go out.
Yes, Mighty Monarch.
Second Uncle.
Father Monarch.
Still afraid of being embarrassed?
No need to be afraid.
Since you fell for that little Bashe snake,
you surely will be a laughingstock of the whole Four Seas and Eight Wildernesses.
What's there to fear in front of your nephew now?
Say it.
I came today to ask Father Monarch to let Shao Xin go.
No need to talk about this again.
I will never change my mind.
I beg you to stop forcing me.
If you insist on doing this,
I can only kill myself to keep her company.
Do you want to die for her?
I'm the distinguished second prince of the Heavenly Tribe,
but I can't even defend my own woman.
It's better to just die.
Okay.
That's my son.
Sang Ji, listen well.
I won't stop you if you want to die,
but the life of that little Bashe snake is still in my hands.
Go destroy your spirit by yourself.
Once you die, I have my ways to torture that little Bashe snake.
Why must you make things difficult for Shao Xin?
I just wanted to take in a concubine.
Why can't I?
I don't care if you want to take in concubines.
But just for a woman, you disobeyed me, and even wanted to die for her!
As the prince of the Heavenly Tribe, you can equally favor women,
but you can't lose the right sense of propriety just because of a woman.
I'm not intentionally making things hard for her.
It's you who harmed her.
Leave now.
Second Highness has no sense of propriety.
In just a few days, the news about him breaking off his engagement
has spread all over the Four Seas and Eight Wildernesses.
Let him break off the engagement then.
But to use a maidservant to insult my daughter is intolerable.
I cannot accept this!
Indeed.
It mustn't be accepted.
Let's go to the Heavenly Palace.
They're not coming, but we need to go there instead?!
Don't you know yet?
Your daughter, the one who's a laughingstock to the Four Seas and Eight Wildernesses,
has been living in my Peach Blossoms Forest for five days.
She doesn't want to marry him, either.
Why not use this chance for us in the Green Hill to take the initiative in breaking off this engagement?
What?
We break off the engagement?!
Right. Not only will we break it off,
we will make the Heavenly Tribe apologize to us.
You have been sleeping in ignorant bliss for five days.
Have I slept for five days?
The day after tomorrow is the day that Qing Cang will break through the bell.
I wonder if I will be able to come back.
Let me take another look of this Ten Miles of Peach Blossoms.
Your expression doesn't seem right.
Are you troubled by Sang Ji's wish to break off the engagement?
Because of Sang Ji?
I met him when I was Si Yin.
I have no opinions about him.
Hence, him breaking off of the engagement doesn't affect me.
What's there to be sad about?
That's good then. Let's go.
Fourth Older Brother, let me ask you a question.
Do you think that 70,000 years ago, if Qing Cang was not sealed,
how would the Four Seas be like now?
If Qing Cang wasn't sealed, then Mo Yuan would still be alive.
If Mo Yuan was alive, there would surely be peace in the Four Seas and Eight Wildernesses.
That's right. If Teacher were alive,
there would be peace in Four Seas.
By the way, Fourth Older Brother, where is Young Jiu?
Didn't she say she would be in the Peach Blossoms Forest these few days?
Young Jiu?
She hasn't been back for the past few days,
but she will definitely be back today.
Why must it be today?
Did you forget? Today is your birthday.
Although you have lived for more than ten thousand years,
this birthday is not something to be cherished.
But Young Jiu has been with you since she was young.
She's even more filial to you than her biological father.
Today is your birthday.
She will definitely be back.
This is really too slow.
Once I go through this forest, it will be Green Hill.
Let's go.
I... I didn't mean to trespass this forest.
I'm just using this path.
I... I'm Bai Fengjiu from Green Hill.
Don't be unreasonable.
Emperor Dong Hua?
Who are you?
Emperor Dong Hua.
What?
How long will you keep hugging me?
Are you really Emperor Dong Hua?
Don't I look like him?
You don't. I saw a painting of you in Zhe Yan's library.
You really don't look like him.
Zhe Yan?
Yes, Zhe Yan. He's the High God from Ten Miles of Peach Blossoms.
Who are you?
I'm Bai Fengjiu, the daughter of the Northern Wilderness Emperor of Green Hill, a descendant of the Nine-Tailed Fox Tribe.
I, Bai Fengjiu from Green Hill, greet Emperor Dong Hua.
So, it's the Bai family.
Someone from the Bai family is afraid of the Golden Lion?
You haven't transcended into the immortal rank yet, right?
No, I haven't.
Since you have saved me, I must reciprocate.
No need.
How can this be?
My aunt always teaches me that there is a cycle of karma in this world.
If there's a reason, there's always a cause. Favors must be returned.
Your aunt?
Bai Qian from Green Hill?
Emperor, do you know my aunt?
We met by chance several times.
Your aunt and the Heavenly Tribe have a strong affinity.
Really? Why haven't I heard her mention this?
She doesn't seem to be willing to mention the Heavenly Tribe.
Don't you know that Zhe Yan and the Fox Emperor Bai Zhi are at Heavenly Tribe right now,
asking for an explanation for your aunt?
Is that so?
How long will you keep following me?
I... I merely wanted to repay your kindness.
Emperor, I had been guarding here for almost 70,000 years.
This Donghuang Bell has never showed any abnormal activities.
But I checked the cosmic objects today,
and it seems Qing Cang will be making some activities today.
How is this possible?
Several thousand years ago, wasn't Qing Cang sealed up by High God Mo Yuan?
If what you said is true, Emperor, I fear that...
I know you can't defeat Qing Cang.
Keep watching this bell closely.
If there are any unusual changes in the next ten days,
vibrate this bell, and I will rush back immediately.
I will abide.
Remember, regardless of any unusual movements,
you must use magic to vibrate the bell.
I will abide.
Because you are a Princess from Green Hill, I will not have any disputes with you.
However, if you keep following me, I will lose my temper.
That person...?
Your Highness, he's Emperor Dong Hua.
When I went to Heavenly Palace with the Winged Monarch twenty thousand years ago,
I was fortunate to see him once.
Emperor is a top senior in Heavenly Palace.
Even the Heavenly Monarch must be very polite to him.
What is he doing here?
I have no idea.
Let's not bother about them first.
Father Monarch,
ever since the day of the Great Battle,
Eldest Brother has been missing.
Second Older Brother...
Second Older Brother is no longer who he used to be.
He still hates what you have done to his birth mother.
It has been 70,000 years and he's still not willing to come to see you.
Father Monarch,
I beg you to bless me in finding my eldest brother soon.
Third Uncle, you followed me until here.
Do you have something to say?
Do I?
I didn't notice that I'd walked here.
Third Uncle, if you want to say something, just say it.
Ye Hua,
since you've been cultivating, you've achieved a lot of achievements that others can't surpass.
You're also the current crown prince, the future heavenly monarch.
But in my eyes, you're still imperfect.
How am I imperfect?
We both are standing here now.
With one eye, we can identify the phases of the moon.
But to say that a moon is full or perfect,
you must experience the taste of love to understand the phases of life.
You lack a love tribulation.
Love?
Look at that dismissive expression of yours.
Let me ask you then.
In your eyes, what does everything that your second uncle has been doing amount to?
Spinning a cocoon around himself.
Is that so?
If you were the one asked to marry a woman whom you didn't know and hadn't seen, would you be willing?
Let me give you some random example.
If you were to marry that Bai Qian of Green Hill, what would you do?
No matter if it's Bai Qian of Green Hill or Qing Qian of White Hills, there's not much difference.
As long as Heavenly Monarch grants the marriage, I'll marry her.
Really?
Third Uncle, are you trying to sound me out?
I'm thinking of a way to save your second uncle.
I think he has really fallen in love this time.
I fear that he'll commit a huge mistake for that little Bashe snake.
Hence, you want me to marry Bai Qian of Green Hill in place of Second Uncle?
Correct.
You are the crown prince of the Heavenly Tribe.
Although you haven't officially received the crown prince stamp,
for the 20,000 years you've been handling official affairs,
the immortals of the Four Seas and Eight Wildernesses already see you as the crown prince.
Only you can pacify this matter.
Only you can replace your second uncle in placating Green Hill.
Okay.
That easy?
Don't you dare deceive me.
That Bai Qian is 90,000 years older than you.
It's just an additional person sleeping by your side.
There's nothing hard about it.
Through and through.
I'm glad you're able to see through it.
Heavenly Monarch brought up the marriage between the Heavenly Tribe and Green Hill to begin with.
Now, it led to this huge joke.
How will everyone from the Four Seas and Eight Wildernesses look at my daughter, Bai Qian, now?!
Heavenly Monarch, do you know?
After this incident, I feel ashamed to face you, Fox Emperor.
That little Bashe snake is indeed hateful.
As a maidservant of High Immortal Bai Qian,
she dared to seduce my son and scheme to be married into the Heavenly Palace.
Even if you, Fox Emperor, are able to endure it, I can't.
In my opinion, Young Fifth didn't give any importance to this marriage alliance, either.
Why not just break it off?
- How about it?
- Yes.
No.
This engagement can't be broken off.
”Cold” by Aska Yang & Diamond Zhang
♫ The temperature gradually drops as night falls ♫
♫ Fallen blossoms become frost ♫
♫ In the distance, you are gazing out afar and exhausting the twilight hours ♫
♫ Without considering the difficulty of forgetting each other ♫
♫ Tender peach blossoms are cold ♫
♫ How could you bear to let go of so many uncertain hearts in the previous lifetime ♫
♫ And still show no pain, no yearning, and no signs that you were forced? ♫
♫ All are just illusions ♫
♫ During the cold night, my yearning for you runs as a river ♫
♫ And transforming into spring soil to nourish me ♫
♫ The fleeting years fill up my lover’s sleeve ♫
♫ Pieces of flowers and plants flow into the waters ♫
♫ The cold will of heaven dresses in glittering colors of flowers ♫
♫ And fall into the mortal realm to hurt my feelings ♫
♫ Calamities are easy to overcome, but trials of love are difficult to overcome ♫
♫ My depreciating heart still holds some hatred from my previous life ♫
♫ The cold three lives and three worlds are as sudden
as a dream ♫
♫ The wind dries my tears in those instantaneous years ♫
♫ If we can no longer recognize our memories ♫
♫ Then allow our love to rest deep within the dust ♫
♫ When will the cold ten miles of peach blossoms
bloom again? ♫
♫ I see a gust of wind under the tree again ♫
♫ Fallen blossoms are of love, flowing waters are of heartlessness ♫
♫ Don’t allow our past grudges, love, and hate to chill the innocence of the flower ♫
♫ My hope in this lifetime is to be with you ♫