”Three Lives, Three Worlds” by Jason Zhang
♫ Listen to the rustling of the wind ♫
♫ Whose sorrow is it trying to stir up? ♫
♫ My yearning grows so instantaneously ♫
♫ That I forget how long the night is ♫
♫ I hold the tears in my palm until they become burning hot ♫
♫ I’m only willing to be crazy for you for three lifetimes ♫
♫ Falling blossoms are everywhere, and I also smell the fragrance of the zither ♫
♫ With you, I wander the world ♫
♫  If love is too desolate, I will dream this dream with you ♫
♫ And redeem all your tears ♫
♫ No matter how far this journey will be or how long these three lifetimes will be ♫
♫ We will be hand in hand until eternity ♫
♫ Despite the miserable wind, vast fog, rolling storm, or overflowing snow ♫
♫ I will walk with you every step of the way ♫
♫ I will hold your hand, don’t be alarmed, don’t worry about tomorrow ♫
♫ Even if we are destined to wander the world ♫
♫ Even if we travel to the remotest corners of Earth ♫
♫ Never let go of each other’s hands ♫
♫ Never forget our mutual love ♫
♫ Life does not need to be too brilliant ♫
♫ Empty glories eventually become nothing, those things you persisted will leave with the wind ♫
♫ Why is love full of ups and downs? ♫
♫ How many storms do we have to face before our hearts stop wavering? ♫
♫ Let’s run through our past together ♫
♫ I’ll wait with you for the wind to stop, fog to clear, rain to end, and snow to melt ♫
♫ Before seeing the absolute beautiful moon again ♫
♫ I will still be by your side ♫
[Eternal Love]
[Episode 33]
The person in the front shouted, "It's bad."
If you want to know what happened, listen to the next chapter.
Okay. I'm leaving.
Customers, take care. Come back next time.
- Where's Ah Li?
- Hurry. Hurry.
Where's Ah Li?
Why did he go to a brothel?
Brother, do you know where the brothel nearby is?
It's that building over there.
Thank you.
Who knew such a good looking man could be a pervert?
What kind of desperate and painful world is this?
The storyteller is not bad.
When you first hear it, it sounds interesting.
But after listening, why did you follow them to the brothel?
Just now, a fatty wanted to kiss a lady in the public.
But the lady wouldn't let the fatty kiss her.
The fatty got really mad because he didn't get it.
He beckoned a few ugly weirdos who were with him and surrounded her.
I ran downstairs to save her, but there weren't any signs of them.
An uncle nearby told me he went to a Flower Building.
(T/N: A Flower Building actually means a brothel.)
I went all over the building but didn't see any flowers.
This is a mortal saying.
Don't worry about it too much.
Then I couldn't find that fatty.
I searched all over and didn't find him, so I went into a room.
I didn't see if the person inside was a man or woman when you came.
This is our secret.
Don't tell your Father Monarch, all right?
I understand.
In ten minutes, I will return to discuss this matter in detail with you.
Your Highness, take care.
Your Highness.
I heard His Mighty Monarch is back.
He did but he just left.
He left again?
The Great Lady from Green Hill is playing in the Mortal Realm, so His Mighty Monarch is accompanying her.
She's playing in the Mortal Realm?
Doesn't that mean he'll miss the Heavenly Monarch's birthday banquet?
You don't have to worry about that. His Mighty Monarch has said that he'll definitely be there.
That's good.
I was just worried that if His Mighty Monarch stays too long in the Green Hill,
he would miss the birthday banquet of Heavenly Monarch.
Since he will return, that puts me at ease.
Don't worry. His Mighty Monarch will be in the main hall soon.
Okay. I understand.
Young sir, you are very fine-looking.
I really admire you.
You flatter me.
Your hands are also so soft and white.
I fell in love with you at first sight.
I wonder if you...
It hurts, it hurts.
You seem to be having fun teasing my wife.
You're back?
Able to make my father angry, you are quite a talent, too.
Let's not meet again. Take care.
How dare you! Do you know who I am?
- Where did you teleport him?
- No idea, either.
If you didn't come just now, I was planning to do the same.
He was being frivolous with you. Why didn't you avoid it?
He just touched me a little.
It was just a kiss.
Buy some lanterns, young sirs.
Buy some lanterns.
Gentlemen, come take a look.
Mortals pray to immortals when they buy lanterns.
If we buy them, who are we praying to?
Just as a souvenir. Did you really think that lanterns can resolve your problems?
Let's go.
Since you're both men, sharing a room shouldn't be a problem.
There are only three inns in this small town.
Owner Wang and Owner Li's inns were already fully occupied yesterday.
A guest just withdrew from our inn.
This is the only vacant room.
Do you... want to stay here for a night first?
Please bring us some hot water.
Yes.
And bring us some small dishes while you're at it.
If you can't eat, why don't you go to sleep?
I have always known your temper.
I didn't expect you to be so firm.
If you've forgotten the past, then let it be.
I hope that you will remember
and also hope that you won't ever remember.
Your Mighty Monarch.
No need to chase them.
I neglected my duty. Please forgive me.
No matter.
These people would dare attack people from the Heavenly Tribe.
Don't you plan to go after them?
They aren't real people.
They're puppets created by black magic and especially for killing.
Even if you kill them, they'll only disappear. You can't ask them anything.
Black magic? Who wants to be enemies with the Heavenly Tribe?
High Immortal Die Feng just said that
all the guests who left the Water Monarch's banquet were also ambushed by them.
I'm preparing to investigate this.
Your Mighty Monarch, the Heavenly Monarch's birthday banquet will be starting soon.
I know. You return first.
Yes.
[South Gate Stage Station]
Mother! Mother! This porridge is really thick.
Good boy.
This place's food is unappetizing,
so I borrowed their kitchen to cook.
No wonder. I thought that this porridge was the same as the one you cooked before.
In the past when I was at Junji Mountain,
I also couldn't get used to the food that the Eastern Sea princess cooked for me.
But Father Monarch never personally cooked for me.
I have some matters to attend to and need to go back to the Heavenly Palace.
Father Monarch, you need to go?
Cheng Yu said that absence makes the heart grow fonder.
You and Mother have been apart for 300 years.
You are still willing to separate?
Did you forget what today is?
What day is it?
Let me think about it.
- It's Heavenly Monarch's birthday!
- That's right.
Do you need to bring me and Mother to celebrate?
Celebrate?
Your mother doesn't really like to go to these kinds of events.
I can go alone.
Okay!
Don't worry. You just go with ease.
I'll take Mochi back.
Great Lady, you returned!
Where's His Highness the Crown Prince?
He went back to the Heavenly Palace. He has a few things to take care of for a few days.
Doesn't that mean there won't be anyone to cook?
We'll go to the marketplace this afternoon and buy some loquats.
You indeed are punctual.
Ten minutes is ten minutes.
Just now in the Mortal Realm, I also ran into those people you spoke of.
Your Highness also ran into them?
How could they dare attack Your Highness?
It wasn't against me.
They just want an immortal's life.
Then they ran into my guard Tian Shu.
Did you leave any survivors?
It's useless to spare one.
Those people were controlled by black magic.
That's right. It's black magic.
These people are from the Winged Realm.
But the Winged Realm has an alliance with the Heavenly Tribe.
Why would they do this all of a sudden?
Let's suppress this matter for now.
First, let's find the identities of the immortals that are being chased.
Yes.
Your Highness.
- His Mighty Monarch is back?
- He's back.
His Highness the Crown Prince is back.
Did Bai Qian of Green Hill return with him?
I saw it very clearly,
His Highness the Crown Prince returned alone.
When he returned, he went to Purple Morning Hall to talk to the second prince of the Western Seas.
He hasn't gone to the birthday banquet yet.
Good.
It's best that she didn't come.
This way, I can ensure that I can keep Ye Hua here tonight.
Your Highness, I'm afraid...
Don't be scared.
The Heavenly Monarch has always hated that little Bashe snake.
He doesn't even like her son Yuan Zhen.
They have finally reconciled a little these years.
Supposing that...
Yuan Zhen takes advantage of me,
Heavenly Monarch definitely won't forgive him.
So you don't need to be afraid.
I'm very important to the Heavenly Monarch.
Even if he doesn't consider the fact that he cared for me growing up,
he will take into account the sub-tribe chieftains and seek justice for me.
I am Ye Hua's side consort.
If I'm being molested by his cousin,
no matter what, it's a big problem.
Ye Hua will surely stay here in the Heavenly Palace for a few days.
For today's plan,
what's most important is to retain him in the Heavenly Palace.
Stop him from going to Green Hill to be charmed by that Nine-Tailed Fox.
You go prepare here.
I'll go look for Yuan Zhen.
I'll find a way to bring him here.
Yes, Your Highness
- Is that the Northern Sea Monarch's eldest son?
- That's right.
Look at how pitiful he is.
He has to wait here instead of going to greet him, even though he's the Heavenly Monarch's grandson.
Who let the Northern Sea Water Monarch marry that Bashe snake?
Exactly.
Who are you? Did you need me to help with something?
You should call me Consort Su Jin.
So, it's Consort Su Jin.
Greetings, Consort Su Jin.
Based on seniority, I'm your older sister-in-law.
You don't need to be so formal.
Don't listen to those maids.
So what if you live long?
What's important is that you're with the one you love.
I envy your parents' relationship.
You are right.
Oh that's right, why are you here alone?
My Father Monarch went to go greet Heavenly Monarch and told me to wait here until I'm summoned.
Is that right?
Why don't I bring you in?
How can I do that? I can't just go in without being summoned.
It's okay. He's your grandfather after all.
Besides, Heavenly Monarch has been praising you these last few days.
He said that you wrote the congratulations messages very well.
Really?
Come, follow me.
Heavenly Monarch is now at Pure Wutong Palace.
I'll take you there.
Your Highness, this place is...?
Go now. Carry him up there.
Yes.
Go now.
Take a white silk and hang it on the beam.
Yes.
Go now and scream that I was molested by the drunken Young Highness and I wanted to hang myself.
Someone, help!
Her Highness was molested by the drunken Young Highness.
She is trying to hang herself.
Someone, come quick!
Her Highness has hung herself!
Someone, help!
- Crown Prince.
- Second Uncle.
I heard that you've been living in the Green Hill lately.
The wedding must be coming soon.
I heard from Shao Xin that the woman next to you at the Eastern Sea was High Goddess Bai Qian.
At first, I thought she was joking.
I didn't expect it to be true.
I heard from Third Uncle that you are here for Heavenly Monarch's birthday banquet.
You even brought your eldest son, Yuan Zhen.
That's right.
Just now, Father Monarch even praised his intelligence.
It's a pity that no matter how smart, he's just the Northern Sea Water Monarch's son.
I fear he has no affinity with Nine Heavens.
Ye Hua. Second Older Brother. Hurry to Pure Wutong Palace.
Something happened with Yuan Zhen!
What?
- Father Monarch.
- Heavenly Monarch.
Rise.
- Thank you, Father Monarch.
- Thank you, Heavenly Monarch.
You taught your son to be like you.
Lost in lust.
Yuan Zhen, what exactly did you do?
Father Monarch, I didn't do anything!
I didn't do anything!
He trespassed into my bed chamber.
I almost...
I almost lost my chastity to him.
I disappointed your previous grace, Your Mighty Monarch.
I beg you for a piece of white silk to let me die an innocent death.
Heavenly Monarch and Your Mighty Monarch, I'm begging you to let me die.
You little scoundrel!
You beast!
Yuan Zhen wasn't sensible and did something so ugly to Side Consort Su Jin.
But I beg you to consider his youth and spare him!
I'm begging you to spare his life and punish him leniently.
Although Su Jin resisted strongly,
her chastity wasn't destroyed.
If he was someone else's son, I would have punished him with leniency,
but he's your son!
Among my three sons,
I doted on you the most.
It is also you that hurt me the most.
Who would've thought that today,
it would be your son who hurt me.
I didn't expect that, after countless years,
when I allowed you to bring your son to Heavenly Palace for the first time,
my own grandson would actually cause me to lose face in front of all my subjects during the banquet.
I admit my mistake.
Father Monarch, please don't be angry.
Yuan Zhen.
You are so young, yet you could even make such a mistake.
You forced me to re-examine you.
I previously thought that you had a kind disposition.
Heavenly Monarch, please investigate wisely.
I really didn't do anything.
Consort Su Jin wanted me to come here.
- I'm begging you to investigate this wisely...
- You scoundrel!
Which woman would frame others to destroy her chastity?
You are still quibbling at this moment?!
Men.
- Heavenly Monarch.
- Tie Yuan Zhen up with immortal locks.
Send him to the Mortal Realm to suffer tribulations for 60 years.
Afterward, relist him in the immortal ranks.
Yes.
No...
No. Father Monarch! Save me!
Father Monarch! Father Monarch!
- I really didn't do anything!
- Please retract your decree!
- Yuan Zhen is a gentle soul by nature.
He doesn't lust after women!
No one knows a son better than his father.
He wouldn't do such a thing!
Please investigate, Father Monarch!
- Please investigate, Father Monarch!
- Father Monarch, save me.
I once thought you were a gentle soul and didn't lust after women.
But you also did such a shameful thing!
Take him away!
- No! No! Father Monarch, help me!
- Yuan Zhen!
Father Monarch, help me!
Father Monarch!
Father Monarch! I really didn't do anything!
This child fell asleep so fast.
Ye Hua is lucky to have a son like you.
I beg Your Mighty Monarch to grant me death to prove my innocence.
Your Mighty Monarch!
What was that act of yours today?
What do you mean, Your Mighty Monarch?
Don't tell me... Don't tell me that you think I tarnished myself?
Which woman would do that to herself?
And I only love Your Mighty Monarch.
Don't Your Mighty Monarch know that?!
You framed Su Su the same way back then.
Do you think I couldn't see through your act?
You've wronged me!
Do you know why I kept you alive?
1. Because of the Soul-Gathering Lamp.
I spared your life because of that lamp.
2.
Because you have Su Su's eyes.
Once you're dead, Su Su's eyes will be dead, too.
But...
if you keep digging your own grave with these acts,
don't blame me for having no mercy.
Su Jin, even if you are dead,
I can find a new owner for this pair of eyes.
Your Mighty Monarch! Your Mighty Monarch!
Is the love I have for you by staying by your side for all these years really worth nothing to you?
That's right.
It means nothing.
- I think...
- Su Jin planned it.
Heavenly Monarch went along with it to bring down Second Uncle.
You're getting good at reading other people's intents.
It's a shame Yuan Zhen has bad luck.
Second Older Brother wasn't careful, either.
That year, Father Monarch demoted him to the Northern Sea because of that Bashe snake.
His relationship with his wife is getting stronger, and they are going to have a fourth child soon.
Isn't he embarrassing Father Monarch in front of the entire Four Seas and Eight Wildernesses?
Yuan Zhen has suffered for his parents.
It's fine, too.
I will go and advise Second Older Brother later to reel in his actions.
Kindness and love must be hidden.
If Father Monarch doesn't have face, he won't have a peaceful life, either.
Is there something you're not telling me, Third Uncle?
I just think it's strange.
Since you know Su Su is Bai Qian,
why don't you just bring her here to Heavenly Palace?
She's engaged to you.
Didn't I tell you she has completely forgotten about me ?
She really did?
Then, it must be High God Zhe Yan's love-forgetting medicine.
Looks like she remembered that you dug out her eyes.
That's why she totally erased you from her mind.
What do you plan on doing now that you're living in Green Hill?
I want to start over with her.
Start over?
She didn't have a single good memory of the Heavenly Palace as Su Su.
Since that's the case,
it's fine if she forgets.
I just need to take it slow and make her fall in love with me.
There won't be any barriers this time in marrying her.
That's good, too.
That's for the best.
Noble Lady, the wind has picked up.
You should go back inside.
It's been two years and His Majesty still hasn't visited me.
Everyone in the palace has heard about the rumor that the evildoers spread about you.
They say that the flower on your forehead is a demonic flower.
It's natural that His Majesty wouldn't visit after hearing about it.
So it's about the birthmark.
Aunt loves this birthmark the most.
Noble Lady, you don't need to be sad.
Rumors will eventually go away.
You're still young. You'll eventually gain his favor.
But if I don't see him,
how can I give him my heart to fulfill his wish?
Your Majesty.
Sit down.
I don't dare.
I'm allowing you to sit.
Yes.
In the end, Noble Consort was unwilling to return to the palace.
Noble Consort?
I've doted on Noble Consort since she joined the palace at the age of 15.
I didn't imagine that after giving birth to Crown Prince Yuanzhen,
she would want to become a nun.
I couldn't do anything.
I could only build her a Daoist temple in the mountains behind the imperial city
for her to devote herself to cultivation.
She seems very devoted to the Daoist study.
She lived in the Daoist temple with Yuanzhen till he turned sixteen years old
before she sent a Daoist nun to send Yuanzhen back to the palace.
She will only return on the first and fifteenth day of the month to visit her son.
She never meets with me.
She has never been willing to see me.
It is as if I don't exist.
Si Ming said that Emperor entering the Mortal Realm is to experience the six pains of life.
From the look of this, Si Ming really put a lot of effort to write this story.
Isn't he afraid the Emperor will get mad at how much suffering he experienced in the Mortal Realm
and send him down here to have a taste of it himself?
Why aren't you saying anything?
I was...
I was feeling your pain.
Noble Consort didn't treasure how much you doted on her.
She not only wasted your sincerity to her,
but also wronged the women in the palace who admire you.
Do you love me, too?
I'm your consort so, of course, I do.
I'm willing to take out my own heart for you to see who is in my heart.
You're good at sweet words.
Your Majesty smiled.
Smiling is good.
You can forget things faster if you smile.
My aunt said that time brings great changes to the world.
No matter who you are, you will eventually turn into a speck of dust,
so is there a need to think so much to make it hard for yourself?
That makes sense.
This flower... is very beautiful.
I don't know why every time I see this flower I keep finding it familiar.
Your Majesty... remembers this birthmark?
I don't know.
I just want to keep looking at it.
I don't want to look at anything else.
I also thought that it was strange,
and I thought that I had been affected by your witchcraft.
Hence, I have been avoiding you for the past two years.
I was afraid I'd keep looking for the rest of my life and never be able to let go.
Your Majesty, your tea is finished.
I'll go pour you another.
Why couldn't I say any sweet words?
I can't be like this.
I got it.
Two curses.
Mother, when is Father Monarch coming back?
I want to eat steamed mushrooms and eat cabbage and radish soup.
It should be soon.
Father Monarch, you're back!
You're back?
Didn't I tell you Ah Li is growing so he can't keep eating this?
I know.
That's why we were looking forward to you coming back to make food.
Were you really waiting for me to return?
Father Monarch! Mother's face is red.
I was just looking forward to your food.
”Cold” by Aska Yang & Diamond Zhang
♫ The temperature gradually drops as night falls ♫
♫ Fallen blossoms become frost ♫
♫ In the distance, you are gazing out afar and exhausting the twilight hours ♫
♫ Without considering the difficulty of forgetting each other ♫
♫ Tender peach blossoms are cold ♫
♫ How could you bear to let go of so many uncertain hearts in the previous lifetime ♫
♫ And still show no pain, no yearning, and no signs that you were forced? ♫
♫ All are just illusions ♫
♫ During the cold night, my yearning for you runs as a river ♫
♫ And transforming into spring soil to nourish me ♫
♫ The fleeting years fill up my lover’s sleeve ♫
♫ Pieces of flowers and plants flow into the waters ♫
♫ The cold will of heaven dresses in glittering colors of flowers ♫
♫ And fall into the mortal realm to hurt my feelings ♫
♫ Calamities are easy to overcome, but trials of love are difficult to overcome ♫
♫ My depreciating heart still holds some hatred from my previous life ♫
♫ The cold three lives and three worlds are as sudden
as a dream ♫
♫ The wind dries my tears in those instantaneous years ♫
♫ If we can no longer recognize our memories ♫
♫ Then allow our love to rest deep within the dust ♫
♫ When will the cold ten miles of peach blossoms
bloom again? ♫
♫ I see a gust of wind under the tree again ♫
♫ Fallen blossoms are of love, flowing waters are of heartlessness ♫
♫ Don’t allow our past grudges, love, and hate to chill the innocence of the flower ♫
♫ My hope in this lifetime is to be with you ♫