”Three Lives, Three Worlds” by Jason Zhang
♫ Listen to the rustling of the wind ♫
♫ Whose sorrow is it trying to stir up? ♫
♫ My yearning grows so instantaneously ♫
♫ That I forget how long the night is ♫
♫ I hold the tears in my palm until they become burning hot ♫
♫ I’m only willing to be crazy for you for three lifetimes ♫
♫ Falling blossoms are everywhere, and I also smell the fragrance of the zither ♫
♫ With you, I wander the world ♫
♫  If love is too desolate, I will dream this dream with you ♫
♫ And redeem all your tears ♫
♫ No matter how far this journey will be or how long these three lifetimes will be ♫
♫ We will be hand in hand until eternity ♫
♫ Despite the miserable wind, vast fog, rolling storm, or overflowing snow ♫
♫ I will walk with you every step of the way ♫
♫ I will hold your hand, don’t be alarmed, don’t worry about tomorrow ♫
♫ Even if we are destined to wander the world ♫
♫ Even if we travel to the remotest corners of Earth ♫
♫ Never let go of each other’s hands ♫
♫ Never forget our mutual love ♫
♫ Life does not need to be too brilliant ♫
♫ Empty glories eventually become nothing, those things you persisted will leave with the wind ♫
♫ Why is love full of ups and downs? ♫
♫ How many storms do we have to face before our hearts stop wavering? ♫
♫ Let’s run through our past together ♫
♫ I’ll wait with you for the wind to stop, fog to clear, rain to end, and snow to melt ♫
♫ Before seeing the absolute beautiful moon again ♫
♫ I will still be by your side ♫
[Eternal Love]
[Episode 57]
Could you please let us take him back and bury him at the Sea of Innocence in the Thirty-Six Heaven?
Please grant our wish, High Goddess.
Our Great Lady isn't using His Highness the Crown Prince's body for something.
Since His Highness the Crown Prince loved our Great Lady that much while living,
so what if we keep his body here?
You relied on so many people and even invited Emperor Dong Hua here.
Mi Gu,
don't say anymore.
Yes.
Great Lady.
I heard everything from every one of you.
I understand, too.
It's just that when I was Su Su,
I was once Ye Hua's wife.
Now,
Ye Hua and I are engaged.
As his wife, I still want to do one last thing for him.
Let me prepare his clothes for him and wipe his face.
Let him leave Green Hill in a clean condition.
This bow is what I'm supposed to give to the both of you as Ye Hua's wife
Stand up. We'll wait.
Thank you.
Eldest Sister-in-Lw, don't cry anymore.
The ending today
is what Ye Hua, as the crown prince of the Heavenly Tribe, did for everyone and the universe.
Stop blaming High Goddess Bai Qian.
On the contrary, it will incite feelings of animosity between the Heavenly Tribe and Green Hill.
I'm Ye Hua's mother.
He died twice for a woman.
Do you still want me to care about the friendship between the Heavenly Tribe and Green Hill?
Do you think my heart is not in pain?
Is Bai Qian the only one whose heart is breaking?
Don't be agitated, Eldest Sister-in-Law.
This is not what I meant.
Since High Goddess Bai Qian has agreed to return Ye Hua's body to us,
let's be patient and wait.
Dear distinguished guests, please have tea first.
I heard you are going to be the monarchess of Green Hill, Young Highness.
You are so young and you are going to be the monarchess of Five Wildernesses.
It's remarkable.
Originally, Aunt was going to marry into Nine Heavens.
There's no need for now.
Ye Hua, do you remember
I'd told you that I would lock you up in Green Hill
and you'll only see me every day?
But from the looks of it now,
I may not be able to do it.
It's because you are the Crown Prince of the Heavenly Tribe.
I'm the monarchess of Green Hill.
If I insist on keeping you here,
I'll let Green Hill and the Heavenly Tribe be embarrassed.
I remember you told me at that time,
you said the person you envy the most is your Second Uncle.
I didn't understand at the time.
Tell me. What is there to envy about the Water Monarch of the Northern Sea?
But I understand now.
If you weren't the crown prince of the Heavenly Tribe,
I could keep you here in Green Hill.
We could be together forever.
Tell me. Isn't my status really awkward?
When I was a mortal,
I wasn't up to par with you.
But now I'm a monarchess,
yet I can't keep you.
Tell me. Am I really that useless?
But that's all right.
I'll always remember the days we spent together.
I'll keep them in my heart.
I won't ever forget them.
All right. Let's not talk about this.
I'll tell you a secret.
Do you know?
Actually, when you were outside the Fox Den and waited for me for seven days and nights,
I was already touched.
But you also know that I can't let this go.
Ye Hua,
the truth is I'd forgiven you a long time ago.
For these past few hundreds of years,
It's been hard on you.
Ye Hua is sleeping deeply.
Please be gentle when you take him away.
First Highness.
High Goddess Bai Qian, what other instructions do you have?
May I go with you to the Sea of Innocence?
I apologize, High Goddess.
The Sea of Innocence is the sacred place of the Heavenly Tribe.
Only people from the Heavenly Tribe can go there.
High Goddess is the monarchess of Green Hill after all.
Based on etiquette, it's still best that you don't go.
After all, you two were only engaged, not married.
Aunt might not have been married to His Highness the Crown Prince, but they were deeply in love.
Why can't she go?
Forget it, Fengjiu.
It's the Heavenly Tribe's rules after all.
Aunt!
- Aunt!
- Ye Hua!
- Great Lady!
Great Lady. Come.
Fourth Uncle, take good care of Aunt.
Sure.
Young Fifth, don't cry.
[South Heavenly Gate]
Welcome His Highness the Crown Prince back to the palace!
Just now, because there were elders around, I felt bad to ask.
Moreover, all of you were giving my aunt a hard time.
It's not good for me to ask.
What do you want to ask?
Are your injures...
They're almost completely healed.
That's good. That's good.
-Then I—
- I thought you'd be asking that question.
What?
The question you asked before the battle with Qing Cang.
If...
I'm saying if, you didn't wipe off your name from the Three Lives Stone back then,
would you like me?
I would.
What did you say, Emperor?
If I didn't wipe off my name from the Three Lives Stone back then,
I would like you.
I went to the Mortal Realm for a tribulation was to give you a chance.
And even more so, to give myself a chance.
♫ I’ve liked you for a long time, ever since the moment we met ♫
♫ In the bonds of this world, I really hope time can stop ♫
♫ The pain of leaving you is like an arrow in my heart ♫
Go.
♫ In my memories, my tears drench the light breeze ♫
♫ Even if we do not end up together, and I cannot express my true feelings ♫
♫ My yearnings will still coat the moonlight and merge into the warmth of my tears ♫
♫ Perhaps the moment I fell in love with you is destined to no result ♫
♫ Even if I am like a moth chasing fire ♫
♫ Even so, I will persevere in my love for you
without complaints ♫
You came.
You came!
I've been thinking these days
would I be able to find you if my soul also dispersed?
But I am also afraid... that I'd forget you if I'm also gone.
So it'd be better for me not having my soul dispersed.
This way, I can at least see you standing in front of me... and smiling at me.
This is really nice.
Ye Hua.
Ye Hua!
Where are you, Ye Hua?
- Ye Hua!
- Get up!
Are you not able to live because Ye Hua is dead?
You've lived for so long.
Are you still not able to bear to be separated in life and death?
It's not that I can't bear it.
It's that I don't know how to bear it.
Do you know, Fourth Older Brother?
When I got drunk and broke the Soul-Gathering Lamp that day,
I suddenly remembered everything that happened 300 years ago.
At that time, I only remembered bad things about Ye Hua.
I completely forgot about how well he treated me.
Now that Ye Hua is gone,
all I can think of every day...
is everything he's done for me.
Then don't think.
Do you know, Fourth Older Brother?
When Li Jing came to find me in Green Hill that day,
I scolded him and argued with him with strong convictions.
I said that, "You keep pursuing something which you couldn't obtain all your life".
"Once you obtained it, you didn't know to treasure it."
I'm the same as him!
I only realized it now that Ye Hua is gone.
Without him,
I really can't live.
Forget it.
Go rest up first.
Ye Hua.
♫ My countenance when I met you ♫
♫ Was as cool breeze and bright moon in this seemingly familiar mundane world ♫
♫ I look around for your lingering to like the stranded time ♫
Come here, Qian Qian.
Tell me about the script you read yesterday.
♫ It’s a reunion but also as we first met ♫
Ye Hua.
♫ Counting years and months only to see your face when the flower blossoms ♫
♫ Even if we miss out on each other over and over again ♫
♫ I foresaw all of your joy and sadness ♫
What's wrong?
It's nice. It's nice.
Qian Qian, nothing happened between that puppet and me in the Mortal Realm.
I just let her take care of my sick mother.
Su Jin made the puppet.
I know.
Qian Qian,
although I grew up with Su Jin,
I only saw her as a drying rack for my brush on my table.
I've never even properly looked at her face before.
I don't care who she wants to marry.
Don't even mention that because I was romantically hurt by her, I turned to love you.
I know.
I believe everything that you say.
♫ I whirl between sleeping and waking with the image of you ♫
The second day of September is an auspicious day.
♫ The warmth is still spreading at the bottom of my heart ♫
It's a shame that we missed it.
♫ In the fleeting and chaotic time, who forgot the promise? ♫
It's fine.
♫ Half in agony, half in deep love ♫
I'm fine as long as you're here.
Any day is fine as long as I'm with you.
Are you locking me up in Green Hill?
Can I?
♫ I foresaw all of your joy and sadness ♫
♫ Three thousand flowers just to remember you ♫
Ye Hua,
your parents said that we were not married.
Hence, your corpse can't be left with me.
I don't know if this cenotaph will be of any use.
Whether it could let you hear what I say to you.
I dreamed of you tonight.
It was no different from when you were alive and with me.
You could still talk to me.
I feel that this is really good.
If you are free, come into my dreams often then.
Talk to me.
Play chess with me.
[Three Years Later]
Brat, you are the youngest monarchess in Green Hill.
When your aunt was the same age as you now, she was still studying skills in Kunlun Void.
Grandmother,
you said that Aunt doesn't want to marry anymore.
Why are you still transferring the post of the monarchess to me?
- Your aunt...
- Grandmother, no need to say anything. I understand.
What do you understand? You have never been married.
Grandmother, Aunt has been traveling all over the place with Fourth Uncle.
It's been 3 years.
Will they come back today?
I don't know.
I'm leading you to receive the homage from the people of Green Hill.
Dad, people might think you're taking me to get married.
You are going to be a monarchess soon and you are still not serious.
Look at you. You look as if you're our seniors.
I know you want to say Bai Yi resembles me in my youth the most.
Watch what you say. I gave birth to five children.
There is only one with such a temperament.
He was exactly like you when you were young.
What? You were that stubborn?
I wasn't.
All right. Let's get going.
Emperor, Si Ming secretly sent me a message the other day.
You have been representing the Heavenly Tribe in governing matters for the past three years and working very hard.
You have had insomnia for more than a month.
The Heavenly Monarch has many sons,
so why must he make you work so hard?
It's a shame.
I can only be heartbroken, but I can't help you.
Emperor,
from today on, I will be the monarchess of Green Hill.
Both Aunt and Dad had taught me.
As the monarchess of Green Hill, I can't do as I wish again.
I no longer can visit Early Dawn Palace without considering my social status.
Pour you some tea.
Spend the night with you.
Congratulations on your conferment as the monarchess of Green Hill!
Everyone from everywhere will serve and commit!
I, Star Monarch Si Ming, the subordinate of Monarch Shaoyang from Dong Hua's Purple Palace,
am instructed by Emperor to congratulate the monarchess of Green Hill for being crowned.
This is Emperor's congratulations gift.
It's the map used by the Emperor in the battle to unite Four Seas and Eight Wildernesses.
The Emperor personally drew this.
The Emperor is very generous.
The crusade map when Monarch Shaoyang from Dong Hua's Purple Palace crusaded with Father God before.
I have only heard of it.
Even the incumbent Heavenly Monarch has never seen it, either.
I thought it was just a legend.
Star Monarch, thank you for your trouble.
Did Emperor have you to relay any message along with the gift?
Emperor said you will understand when you open this map.
Tens of thousands of years ago, time brought many changes.
Everything on this map doesn't exist anymore.
Even Four Seas and Eight Wildernesses have been transformed.
Everything in the world has become insignificant.
There's nothing worth to be thought of.
These are my words for the emperor.
Bai Fengjiu of Green Hill thanks Emperor Dong Hua's gifts.
I hope Green Hill can continue to be friends with the Heavenly Tribe for many generations and be a blessing to the people.
Nice! Nice! Nice.
Let's go out for a walk.
Immortals, are you two here to have a good time in the Mortal Realm as well?
How do you know who we are?
Immortals have an aura.
It's normal that mortals can't see it,
but if I can't, it'd be a big mistake.
Let's go.
Immortals, could I borrow some money?
I saw that musical performance was great.
If I don't give them some money, I would feel bad.
It's not hard to lend you some money. You are a small immortal.
You should learn how to create things.
It's not that difficult to create some money.
Why do you want to borrow from me?
My parents were afraid I'd cause trouble so they sealed my powers.
Could I ask who you are?
This is the son of the Fox Emperor and the best looker in Four Seas and Eight Wildernesses.
How do I return this pearl to you?
No need to return it.
Look at this flying current underneath the river.
It flows day and night and never flows backward.
I think life is also like that.
We can't turn back. We can only go forward.
You're right, Fourth Older Brother.
Look at these mortals.
Being able to walk in the world only for a few decades.
They are trapped by the fate that Si Ming has arranged for them.
Some of them may be impoverished for life.
Some of them may aspire but can't spread out.
A good daughter that was raised at home may not marry someone with the same values.
But they're all living happily.
Don't you think you have it much better after seeing them?
You've gotten chatty these past 3 years.
It's to cheer you up.
But speaking of which, your complexion has gotten better.
I've been able to dream about him for the past few months.
So, of course, I'd look better.
Young Fifth, can you still distinguish reality from your dreams?
Fourth Older Brother, have you heard the story about Zhuang Zhou dreaming of becoming a butterfly?
A person named Zhuang Zhou dreamed about becoming a butterfly.
He happily flew and danced throughout the skies.
But he realized he was still a mortal when he woke up.
In the end, we don't know if he became a butterfly in his dreams
or if a butterfly dreamed about being Zhuang Zhou.
Ever since I dreamed about him for the first time three years ago,
I've thought it through.
Pretending reality as a dream
and pretending my dreams as reality
is the same either way, just a different method of living.
Husband! Husband! Don't leave me!
Husband! Husband!
I've been dedicated to you and treated your two sons like my own sons.
You can't toss me away, husband.
I'm begging you. You can't
- Husband.
- You are a widow. When you first started pestering me,
you caused me to fall out with my wife.
I thought if I married you, I'd live a happy life!
But who knew you went back on your words and seduced scum on the streets!
I've given you the letter of divorce. Stop pestering me!
Husband, don't do this! Husband!
Husband!
”Cold” by Aska Yang & Diamond Zhang
♫ The temperature gradually drops as night falls ♫
♫ Fallen blossoms become frost ♫
♫ In the distance, you are gazing out afar and exhausting the twilight hours ♫
♫ Without considering the difficulty of forgetting each other ♫
♫ Tender peach blossoms are cold ♫
♫ How could you bear to let go of so many uncertain hearts in the previous lifetime ♫
♫ And still show no pain, no yearning, and no signs that you were forced? ♫
♫ All are just illusions ♫
♫ During the cold night, my yearning for you runs as a river ♫
♫ And transforming into spring soil to nourish me ♫
♫ The fleeting years fill up my lover’s sleeve ♫
♫ Pieces of flowers and plants flow into the waters ♫
♫ The cold will of heaven dresses in glittering colors of flowers ♫
♫ And fall into the mortal realm to hurt my feelings ♫
♫ Calamities are easy to overcome, but trials of love are difficult to overcome ♫
♫ My depreciating heart still holds some hatred from
my previous life ♫
♫ The cold three lives and three worlds are as sudden
as a dream ♫
♫ The wind dries my tears in those instantaneous years ♫
♫ If we can no longer recognize our memories ♫
♫ Then allow our love to rest deep within the dust ♫
♫ When will the cold ten miles of peach blossoms
bloom again? ♫
♫ I see a gust of wind under the tree again ♫
♫ Fallen blossoms are of love, flowing waters are of heartlessness ♫
♫ Don’t allow our past grudges, love, and hate to chill the innocence of the flower ♫
♫ My hope in this lifetime is to be with you ♫