”Three Lives, Three Worlds” by Jason Zhang
♫ Listen to the rustling of the wind ♫
♫ Whose sorrow is it trying to stir up? ♫
♫ My yearning grows so instantaneously ♫
♫ That I forget how long the night is ♫
♫ I hold the tears in my palm until they become burning hot ♫
♫ I’m only willing to be crazy for you for three lifetimes ♫
♫ Falling blossoms are everywhere, and I also smell the fragrance of the zither ♫
♫ With you, I wander the world ♫
♫  If love is too desolate, I will dream this dream with you ♫
♫ And redeem all your tears ♫
♫ No matter how far this journey will be or how long these three lifetimes will be ♫
♫ We will be hand in hand until eternity ♫
♫ Despite the miserable wind, vast fog, rolling storm, or overflowing snow ♫
♫ I will walk with you every step of the way ♫
♫ I will hold your hand, don’t be alarmed, don’t worry about tomorrow ♫
♫ Even if we are destined to wander the world ♫
♫ Even if we travel to the remotest corners of Earth ♫
♫ Never let go of each other’s hands ♫
♫ Never forget our mutual love ♫
♫ Life does not need to be too brilliant ♫
♫ Empty glories eventually become nothing, those things you persisted will leave with the wind ♫
♫ Why is love full of ups and downs? ♫
♫ How many storms do we have to face before our hearts stop wavering? ♫
♫ Let’s run through our past together ♫
♫ I’ll wait with you for the wind to stop, fog to clear, rain to end, and snow to melt ♫
♫ Before seeing the absolute beautiful moon again ♫
♫ I will still be by your side ♫
[Eternal Love]
[Episode 51]
Teacher.
I tidied up the Pellet-Cultivating Room.
Thanks to your senior brothers.
Kunlun Void has returned to its original state.
Being with everyone daily, it seems like we have gone back to the past.
Frankly, I was just thinking.
This was the place where you withstood three bolts of heavenly lightning for me.
You can't remember the battle formations and spells that I taught you,
but you remembered this minor matter.
Teacher, I will never forget your kindness.
In the future, I will always be filial to you.
Filial?
Teacher, are you thirsty?
I'll go brew a pot of tea for you.
No need.
Go back to work.
All right. I won't disturb you then.
I'm leaving.
Why am I cornered by you again?
I taught you zither, painting, and calligraphy. You want to defeat me?
It won't be easy.
Fourth Older Brother, this is known as "a beaten army in total collapse."
You are pacing up and down.
You must have something to request from me, right?
You are pretty close.
Fourth Older Brother, come out with me for a while.
Kunlun Void is really your place.
You talk differently to me.
When I'm back, I will slaughter you in a round.
You are pulling this stunt again.
Don't underestimate me.
Let's go.
- Fourth Older Brother, let's go.
- Forget it.
I will set up a game and wait for you to come back.
If you lose again, you'll be unhappy and avoid me for half a month.
Fourth Older Brother, help me with a favor.
What's wrong? Weren't you serious just now?
You are now asking a favor from me?
It's a small matter.
If it involves the crown prince of the Heavenly Tribe, how can it be a small matter?
How did you know it's about him?
Other than him, I have never seen anyone who's able to make you act like a little girl.
Okay, you are the best.
It's him.
Fourth Older Brother, can you help me hide for a few hours?
I want to go to the Mortal Realm to see Ye Hua.
Are you going through all this trouble
because you're afraid your senior brothers will find out
and laugh at you for being so immersed in love?
Fourth Older Brother, looks like even you misunderstand things.
I'm not trying to hide because of my senior brothers.
I'm just worried about Teacher.
I'm worried Teacher will worry about his twin younger brother''s tribulation in the Mortal Realm,
so I want to take a look.
You also know how foul the air is in the Mortal Realm.
If Teacher goes, it will affect his recuperation.
If you think this way, you are overestimating me.
I'm so thin-skinned.
If a few hours is the time you require, I won't be able to sleep tonight.
At most, I will grant you half an hour.
Ye Hua went to the Mortal Realm just for a tribulation.
It's not a big deal and you want to follow him down there?
You are watching him too closely.
Then... it's agreed?
Half an hour at most.
Otherwise, don't blame me for personally going down to get you.
Fourth Older Brother, look.
It's snowing in Kunlun Void.
This is the first time you came together with Zhe Yan, right?
You two should go take in the view at the back of the mountain.
Kunlun Void's snow landscape is renowned in Four Seas.
Never mind the snow.
Even if it's falling fire, I'm too lazy to watch.
Half an hour and nothing more.
When I have defeated Zhe Yan, you must be back.
This is not right. If I were to calculate, the crown prince can't be more than ten years old now.
Why is she going down to the Mortal Realm?
Forget it. Let that Old Phoenix wait.
I'm going down to the Mortal Realm to take a look at the fun.
Before Luan Wuzi didn't have a 100-household estate.
- His family was so poor that they couldn't even prepare a complete set of funeral offerings.
- This mortal world
- is also snowing like in Kunlun Void.
- But he was able to propagate good morality and strictly follow the rules.
Famous among the different feudal lords of different states.
These feudal lords tried to be close to him,
a few citizens willingly submitted to him; hence, pacifying the Jin State.
He promulgated the laws, didn't engage in any malpractice, and prevented any disasters from happening.
Before Luan Wuzi didn't have a 100-household estate.
His family was so poor that they couldn't even prepare a complete set of funeral offerings.
But he was able to propagate good morality and strictly follow the rules.
Famous among the different feudal lords of different states.
These feudal lords tried to be close to him, a few citizens willingly submitted to him;
hence, pacifying the Jin State.
He promulgated the laws, didn't engage in malpractice,
and prevented any disasters from happening.
Stop. Zhaoge, stand up.
Continue to recite.
Yes.
When this reached Huanzi, he became too arrogant and conceited. Spending excessively.
Has insatiable greed.
Breaking the law and doing wild acts.
Lending with interest and amassing great wealth.
He should have suffered great disaster, but due to accumulated good karma by his father, Luan Wuzi, he was able to get a good ending.
They all said that Crown Prince Ye Hua's teachers were Spiritual Master Ci Hang and Lord of Yuanshi.
He was both knowledgeable in Daoist principles and immortal techniques.
A child genius that was never seen before in the Nine Heavens.
This knowledge in the Mortal Realm is considered too easy for him.
...and strictly follow the rules.
It's snowing!
Rice is expensive! Oil is also expensive!
The Liu Family has a disabled child!
Even if he knows so many words, without strength, what can you do?
- without strength, what can you do?
- What are you doing?
They are too undisciplined. They even dared to bully Young Master in the courtyard of the study.
That's right. We have tolerated them for many days.
Let's teach them a lesson. Let's go.
No need.
Heavenly Monarch is so cruel to his grandson.
He made him lose an arm even while undergoing tribulation in the Mortal Realm.
Even good people have to suffer.
Young Master is such a good kid.
How could God let him lose an arm?
What happened?
Something happened?
This must be a dream.
Hey.
I'm not dreaming after all.
Do you know me?
I don't.
Who are you?
How did you enter my room?
Let me tell you. I'm...
I'm originally a little immortal from Green Hill who was able to peek into Heaven's plans.
I learned that after 10 years, we are fated to be husband and wife.
I'm here today to take a look at my future husband.
I'm... your future husband?
Why the face?
Do you dislike my appearance?
You are very pretty.
Do you really mean it?
Although I haven't seen a lot of girls,
those in drawings still aren't half as beautiful as you.
Do you believe what I just said?
That we are destined to be a married couple in the future?
Yes.
I have a pearl bracelet.
If I'm not by your side, it will keep you company. Okay?
I have a jade.
It's for you.
- This is for me?
- Yes.
Thank you.
I will wear it every day.
All right. I will wear this, too.
It's agreed between us then.
You cannot marry someone else.
When I have the time, I will visit you.
I will marry you when you have grown up.
What?
I'm here just to watch some fun.
I'm surprised, I'm surprised.
Your thoughts are scarily too meticulous that you didn't even spare a child.
I'm just afraid that he'll invite unnecessary romance while here in the mortal world.
They all said that Second Sister-in-Law is the most easily jealous in our Bai Family.
How come I feel that you're worse than her?
Fourth Older Brother!
Even if I tell you, you wouldn't understand.
In Heaven and Earth, you are the one who least understands women.
Young Master, you are awake.
Green Hill?
Young Master, what are you looking for?
I'm looking for a place called Green Hill.
Green Hill?
What a strange name.
I've accompanied you in your studies every day and have never heard of it.
Young Master, stop looking.
You can ask the teacher.
That's right. I can ask the teacher.
[Moral and virtue shapes people]
You haven't heard of this, either?
I haven't.
I've read tens of thousands of books.
I have never read about Green Hill.
My dear niece, what brings you here?
Aren't you afraid that your father will beat you?
My father doesn't care about me anymore.
Did Second Older Brother finally figure it out and isn't hindering you anymore?
He isn't.
My father knows that Emperor won't accept me no matter what,
so there's no point for him to stop me.
Foolish girl.
I initially thought that you'd be fine after crying it out.
Turns out you still can't forget him.
I can't forget him.
Even if he speaks rudely to me,
even if he bullies me,
I just can't forget him.
If you are asked to forget about His Highness the Crown Prince,
can you do it?
It's my fault for not putting myself in your shoes.
You still haven't answered me.
Can you forget him?
I can't.
Old Phoenix, why are you eavesdropping on us?
Young Highness, High God Mo Yuan and I have been standing here for quite some time.
You two should have evaded.
We were having a girl talk,
but you have eavesdropped on all of it.
You are so rude.
You are finally awake?
Fengjiu, why are you being so rude to my teacher?
Please forgive me, High God.
Earlier, when I saw you standing there,
I didn't realize it.
After all... I've seen you sleeping in Splendid Flame Cave for 70,000 years.
Hence, suddenly seeing you alive and— Oh, wrong!
Suddenly seeing you bursting with life and intimidating presence,
I wasn't able to immediately get used to it.
High God, please forgive me.
It's okay.
Since you're here, too, why don't you join us for drinks?
Mo Yuan once took some tens of thousand-year-old good brew from my place.
Today's the perfect day to drink them.
Sure! Drinking wine can drown my sorrows.
Problems would just get more worrisome.
Then, I will just worry about them tomorrow.
I still remember that when you asked me for this wine,
it was for Young Fifth's birthday present. Right?
Yes.
I also recall that. It's a pity that I didn't even get to drink it
before I was caught by Teacher's admirer, High Goddess Yao Guang.
I was imprisoned in the Water Prison.
My birthday was spent in the Water Prison.
- It was really unforgettable.
- Oh?
Did that really happen between him and Yao Guang?
Let's not discuss a person who has returned to the formless mass.
I said the wrong thing.
I will punish myself with this cup of wine.
Old Phoenix, tell me about the emperor's past.
Dong Hua?
He's even worse than Mo Yuan at getting close to women.
Why doesn't he get close to women, either?
Is he a man or not?
Young Jiu, you must get this straight.
That man in your heart used to be the ruler of Heaven and Earth.
He's an outstanding man.
In any case, I also respect you for choosing such a person from thousands of others.
You are not allowed to talk bad about him.
This little brat's alcohol tolerance is nothing compared to yours.
It's good to have bad alcohol tolerance.
You will get drunk faster.
But Zhe Yan, do you know why this Emperor Dong Hua doesn't get close to women?
It's because of Four Seas and Eight Wildernesses.
Yes, it's because of the Four Seas and Eight Wildernesses.
When I came with Zhe Yan a few days ago, I could still go up the mountain freely.
With the dragon aura here now, I feel that it's hard to approach it.
So to say, High God Mo Yuan's spirit has returned to his body.
Brothers, why are you standing here?
It's nothing.
I only feel that Kunlun Void has restored its life again,
so I'm here to take a look.
High God Mo Yuan's spirit has returned to his body.
Even High God Zhe Yan, High God Bai Zhen of Green Hill, and the Great Lady are here.
I see.
Thank you for letting me know.
This man is strange.
After hearing that High God Mo Yuan is back, he doesn't look happy.
Could he be from another tribe?
Probably so.
Young Jiu.
Aunt, morning.
It's not morning anymore. Fourth Older Brother and the others have been waiting for you for a long time.
- They are waiting for me?
- That's right.
You should know that the Heavenly Tribe and Green Hill are preparing to hold the wedding between me and Ye Hua.
You are going to take over my post.
You should concentrate on more serious matters and go back to Green Hill soon.
Aunt, you want me to go back and take over your post?
In Green Hill, you're the only girl of your generation.
If you don't accept it, who would?
You want me to give up on Dong Hua, too.
I didn't say that.
If you marry into the Heavenly Tribe, you can't succeed the throne.
Because you are marrying into the Heavenly Palace, you won't be able to take care of the people in Green Hill.
But if I want to marry Emperor Dong Hua, I will marry into the Heavenly Palace, too.
I won't be able to take care of the people in Green Hill, either.
Aunt, you obviously knew about this.
Why do you still want me to take the throne?
Aunt, do you want me to remain forever in Green Hill?
Young Jiu,
just forget him.
But, Aunt, you told me last night that you can't forget Crown Prince Ye Hua, either,
because you like him.
What you can't do, why do you want me to handle it instead?
Young Jiu, listen to me.
You are not fated to be with Dong Hua.
Why must you force it?
I thought that you were on my side last night,
that even if everyone in our family wanted to lock me up,
you were the only one who could free me,
that you would let me try to make the emperor fall in love with me again.
I don't want to be the monarchess.
If I become the monarchess, I won't be able to go to Nine Heavens again!
Young Jiu!
It still doesn't work?
I merely told her to go back to Green Hill and take over the post of the monarchess,
and she started crying like this.
Between the both of you, one was enlightened too early and other too late.
Forget about this. Leave this to me.
I will escort her home safely.
Tell Second Older Brother not to pressure her too much.
Don't worry. I know what I'm doing.
You are her aunt, and you dote on her.
I'm her fourth uncle who equally dotes on her.
Zhe Yan is worried about Mo Yuan's health and needs to remain in Kunlun Void for a few more days.
I will leave first.
All right.
Do you want to see Ah Yin?
I do.
Me, too.
Perhaps, this is the last chance for me to see her.
Isn't His Highness the Crown Prince marrying her soon?
By then, the wedding invitation will be delivered to the Grand Purple Palace.
You will be able to see them.
I can't wait that long.
You can't wait that long?
Why not?
Isn't it soon?
What are you looking at?
Little girl, you are ugly when you cry.
It's a rare sight in Kunlun Void.
You said that I look ugly when I cry?
Then, I will stay here and cry till you can't take it anymore.
Cry then.
You are only making it hard for yourself.
It doesn't concern me.
Does this cave look nice?
To me, it's very nice.
Such an uninteresting person.
That's right.
Uninteresting.
I said that you are an uninteresting person.
I know.
I was talking about myself, too.
Standing in front of the cave and looking back past tens of thousands of years ago,
I just realized that my life is endless and uninteresting.
- Good boy.
- Winged Monarch.
Second Older Brother, did you meet His Highness the Crown Prince?
No.
You didn't?
Did you meet Heavenly Monarch or Emperor Dong Hua then?
Why not?
Aren't you afraid that Father will break out from Donghuang Bell and use Red Lotus Fire to destroy the Four Seas?
And that's why you went to Heavenly Tribe to discuss this?
The Winged Realm is in great chaos now.
Many sub-tribe chieftains are currently unable to suppress the mobs.
Second Older Brother, we can't delay any further.
If Father really breaks out from the Donghuang Bell,
many people will follow him.
By then, when we go to the Heavenly Tribe to plead, it will be too late.
I know.
Second Older Brother!
Say something. Let me know what's on your mind.
Or else, I'll die from anxiety.
Yan Zhi, do you know?
Ah Yin and the Crown Prince will marry soon.
They were previously engaged.
This is a marital alliance between the Heavenly Tribe and Green Hill.
This is the most prestigious marriage in Four Seas.
In the past, I thought that, as a prince of the Winged Tribe,
I would give my most beloved woman the best wedding.
But compared to Ye Hua,
that's such a joke.
Second Older Brother,
I know you only have High Goddess Bai Qian in your heart.
But...
High God Mo Yuan's spirit is back to his body now,
and Ah Yin is in Kunlun Void.
She must be extremely happy.
High God Mo Yuan's spirit is back to his body?!
That's good. Second Older Brother, let's go and tell High God Mo Yuan.
That our lives are the key to helping Father increase his power.
Tell Kunlun Void that because Eldest Brother died, Father is already stronger,
so he can't remain sealed.
We can't tell them.
Why?
Yan Zhi, have you ever thought of this?
If Father breaks out from Donghuang Bell, who will seal him?
Of course, it's High God Mo Yuan.
Donghuang Bell was created by him.
70,000 years ago, he succeeded once in sealing Father.
Naturally, it will be him again.
Think carefully again.
If Ah Yin finds out that Mo Yuan wants to seal him,
would she let her Teacher disperse his soul again?
By then, she will definitely go all out to protect her teacher.
Seeing that she's going to marry soon,
I don't want anything to happen to her at this time.
But...
As the Winged Monarch for 70,000 years,
I never did any good deed to bring blessings to my citizens and the Winged Realm.
I was wandering around the Mortal World looking for the whereabouts of Ah Yin.
As of today,
if I still don't do anything,
I will be incompetent trash.
Second Older Brother, you...
What are you talking about?
Second Older Brother, what are you doing?
Get up now.
Yan Zhi,
I'm entrusting my son to you.
In the Grand Purple Palace,
you will be the only one left with royal blood.
I'm even entrusting the Winged Realm to you today.
Second Older Brother, what are you going to do?
- Fire Kirin.
- Mighty Monarch.
Lock up the princess in Land of Extreme Coldness.
Before the issue of Donghuang Bell is concluded, don't let her out.
No, I can't leave you.
Listen to me!
I can't.
Even you don't want to acknowledge me as your monarch?
It's not that.
You grew up with me.
Other than my mother, you are my closest family.
I can only hand over Yan Zhi and the child to you so that I can be at ease.
Do you understand?
Mighty Monarch, can I find you again after I have escorted the princess there?
You can't.
When I'm dead, I want you to help Yan Zhi become the new Winged Monarchess.
You are the most auspicious deity beast in the Winged Realm.
With you by Yan Zhi's side, no one will dare to hurt Yan Zhi.
Without Father, without me, they will naturally acknowledge Yan Zhi as the Winged Monarchess.
Hurry and take the princess away!
- Yes!
- Mighty Monarch...
- Leave!
Seven days.
Give me seven days.
I will definitely succeed.
For the past few days, there has been great waves in Ruoshui.
I wonder what the reason is.
It doesn't seem that simple.
We must be careful and take precautions.
A guest is here to pay homage again.
Brew tea.
Zhe Yan, stop fooling around. Let me sleep.
I didn't have a good rest yesterday.
I'm here to find you regarding an important matter.
What important matter would you have for coming to Kunlun Void?
High God Mo Yuan has already set the date for his seclusion.
It's in seven days.
I'm going to refine some medicinal pills for him
to take into seclusion at the cave to help him with his recovery.
During this period, I want you to assist me.
Teacher is going into seclusion?
He has been back for eleven days. He should go into seclusion.
After all, the cultivation of Ye Hua was only enough to wake him up.
He's still very weak, and needs to rest and recuperate.
For the past days, you were either at the pharmacy or the Pellet-Cultivating Furnace.
You didn't even have time to drink some tea and moisten your throat.
If you have nothing to do today, go visit your teacher.
I fear when he goes into seclusion, you won't be able to see him for quite a while.
How long will Teacher be in seclusion?
It could be 10 days, or half a month, or even 10 years.
I'll go see Teacher right now.
Oh! Teacher loves peach blossoms.
I'm going to pick some to replace the ones in Teacher's room.
I love hearing you play the zither.
It always soothes me.
Can I become a high immortal faster if I listen to you play more often?
Teacher, I'm going to help Zhe Yan refine your medical pills tomorrow.
I won't be able to greet you for many days.
I'm here especially to replace your peach blossoms.
Peach blossoms wither after just one day.
I've instructed Sixteenth Senior to come and change them every day from now on.
You came just for that tonight?
Teacher, ever since you came back to Kunlun Void,
we have been very busy, so I haven't had time to have a proper chat with you.
Moreover, Zhe Yan told me that you are going into seclusion soon.
It could take ten days, half a month, or even several years,
so I wanted to come see you.
Am I bothering you?
No.
I remember when I first came to Kunlun Void, I was very childish.
I only knew that you played the zither very well,
so I bugged you to play musical pieces every day.
Do you remember?
I remember.
Speaking of which, I've never heard Ye Hua play for me.
Does Ye Hua... treat you well?
His way of treating me well is different from the way you treat me well.
In any case, he's very sincere.
That's good to hear.
It's snowing.
An unexpected mishap. An unexpected mishap.
What are you thinking about?
You are so focused.
I'm thinking about what Teacher used to say.
That the disciples from Kunlun Void love to brew peach blossom honey.
That's only to humor the kids.
It's too sweet.
Are you interested?
Is it sweet?
Then, please pack some for me.
Zhen Zhen has loved sweets ever since he was little.
When he got sick, he would only drink his medicine if it was sweet.
Zhen Zhen?
When did you get married?
He's not my child. I'm talking about High God Bai Zhen.
You are right. Compared to you, High God Bai Zhen is still a kid.
I'll pack some extra for you.
Are you cold?
I'll close the windows.
No need.
It's getting late.
You should go back to rest.
It's my fault.
I forgot you still have to recuperate.
I'll be leaving now.
”Cold” by Aska Yang & Diamond Zhang
♫ The temperature gradually drops as night falls ♫
♫ Fallen blossoms become frost ♫
♫ In the distance, you are gazing out afar and exhausting the twilight hours ♫
♫ Without considering the difficulty of forgetting each other ♫
♫ Tender peach blossoms are cold ♫
♫ How could you bear to let go of so many uncertain hearts in the previous lifetime ♫
♫ And still show no pain, no yearning, and no signs that you were forced? ♫
♫ All are just illusions ♫
♫ During the cold night, my yearning for you runs as a river ♫
♫ And transforming into spring soil to nourish me ♫
♫ The fleeting years fill up my lover’s sleeve ♫
♫ Pieces of flowers and plants flow into the waters ♫
♫ The cold will of heaven dresses in glittering colors of flowers ♫
♫ And fall into the mortal realm to hurt my feelings ♫
♫ Calamities are easy to overcome, but trials of love are difficult to overcome ♫
♫ My depreciating heart still holds some hatred from
my previous life ♫
♫ The cold three lives and three worlds are as sudden
as a dream ♫
♫ The wind dries my tears in those instantaneous years ♫
♫ If we can no longer recognize our memories ♫
♫ Then allow our love to rest deep within the dust ♫
♫ When will the cold ten miles of peach blossoms
bloom again? ♫
♫ I see a gust of wind under the tree again ♫
♫ Fallen blossoms are of love, flowing waters are of heartlessness ♫
♫ Don’t allow our past grudges, love, and hate to chill the innocence of the flower ♫
♫ My hope in this lifetime is to be with you ♫