Timing and subtitles brought to you by
My Old New Life Team@Viki.com
"Burning Tempo" - Duan Aojuan
♫  One, two, three, four  ♫
♫  Don't be afraid of the so-called star student  ♫
♫  You are also someone else's legend  ♫
♫  Don't hold back, grow with all your might  ♫
♫  Midsummer's flowers  ♫
♫  Now is the time to format your life  ♫
♫  Math and physics are not complicated  ♫
♫  Youth is full of obstacles, but we'll slowly become stronger  ♫
♫  My heart still burns passionately  ♫
♫  Follow the tempo, set yourself free  ♫
♫  The illuminated night sky guides me to success  ♫
♫  I'll accompany you as you bravely take flight  ♫
♫  My love still burns passionately   ♫
♫  Shining in the smiling eyes  ♫
♫  Let us transcend the obstacles of time  ♫
That pose doesn't look slack enough.
Let me show you how it's done.
Legs like this.
Yes.
That's the spirit. That's how you slack off right.
You know a lot about slack guys, huh?
I've never driven the car,
but I've been in the back seat.
I kinda know the drill.
Yeah? Doesn't your brother act like this a lot?
Yes. My brother likes doing this.
Acting like he doesn't care about anything.
But in fact, he's just running away from reality.
Look, he's so handsome.
So handsome. Hurry up. Take a photo.
Look.
So handsome when he's asleep.
If only he were my boyfriend.
Wake up.
Excuse me.
What's wrong, Shiyun?
Can you stop coming to my university?
It disturbs my studies.
Sit down.
How did it go?
Is this yours?
Why didn't you pass it on to him for me?
Because he has a girlfriend.
But last time, it sounded like he was single.
Please help me. I know you're close to him.
Please.
I'm visiting too often.
She doesn't even get
to hang out with her schoolmates.
Gu Xue Jiao, companionship
is the earnest declaration of love?
You totally misled me.
Is this also a part of slacking off?
It's the meaningful part.
Young man, you are playing with fire.
Just like that?
Hello, Shu Lan.
I sent you the brochure of the national contest.
Thank you so much. Love you.
Stop. We're not there yet.
Why are you studying that brochure?
To join the contest.
That's it. Talk later.
You're signing up?
Yeah.
Aren't you going to fight
a prolonged battle against the B&amp;C Motors?
I found a way to turn this prolonged battle
into a swift strike.
If I win the national contest
using your patented technology,
it will prove to all the media and experts
in the whole country
that the C1 technology rejected by B&amp;C Motors
is completely viable.
You'll sail against a gale.
Perfect.
I'm a good sailor.
Gu Xue Jiao, you got a problem with me?
Senior Brother Lin.
Don't bother to explain.
I'm the team leader
of this year's national contest.
Come to me if you want to sign up for the contest.
Why did you go to Professor Tan?
You want to take my place?
Tell you what. Only one of us
will make it into the team.
I'm not giving in.
Professor Tan didn't guarantee anything.
He wanted us to compete
for the title of team leader.
You...
You're overstepping.
You're challenging my authority.
Is it really so easy to arouse your insecurity?
Lin, your psychological resilience
requires development.
This is a healthy competition.
Competition over friendship.
You...
You really don't know your limits.
Just wait. I'll make you lose badly.
Instead of crying out,
you'd better study harder.
I'm going to ask Professor Tan a few questions.
Want to tag along?
You're trying to take my place?
Gu Xue Jiao, you don't stand a chance
against me with your tricks.
Are you busy?
No.
Are you there?
Is it too old-fashioned?
Where is everyone?
They're training with Lin Jia Dong
for the national contest.
Although we defected,
our hearts are with you.
Second that. Great disparity in strength.
I'll bring you something to eat.
I'll bring you something, too.
Actions speak louder.
- Shu Lan.
- Don't get me wrong.
I haven't had the chance to leave.
I'm applying for the postgraduate program.
I don't have the time and energy for this mess.
Of course.
I also don't want
to include the word 'lose' in my dictionary
because of you.
- Bye.
- Shu Lan.
Shu...
Brother Rui.
Wait. He's a first-year PhD.
He can't sign up for my category.
Am I really doing it alone?
Hi.
Is that too casual?
Forget it.
Come on. What does she take me for?
As long as you take part in the contest
on behalf of your school,
I'll make sure that you win first place.
That's my dear aunt. Awesome.
Have a minute?
Not interested. It's boring.
I want to be like my idol.
I'll head to conquer the stars
and the vast universe.
I get it.
But it won't hinder you.
Your idol builds rockets and Starlink.
Isn't he still making cars?
Don't set up so many limits in life.
I'm too busy.
These are the hiring stats
of your target government jobs
over the past three years.
A top finish in the national contest
would elevate your profile instantly.
You're both articulate
and strategically precise.
The professional term for my behavior
is 'selling dreams'.
But the dream I'm selling
is different from others.
It will come true for sure.
Stop. I won't join you.
You'd better stop trying to win me over.
Who said I was trying to win you over?
I have set up my team.
You are highly capable, but...
It's not like you're indispensable.
Seriously, Gu Xue Jiao?
They're not members of the lab.
Don't you know that they're not allowed in?
I have already obtained permission
from Professor Tan.
You think you'll make it without me?
Our upcoming match against our rival team
is an intelligent cybersecurity
attack-defense battle.
We must build our firewall
before the competition kicks off.
Then we must penetrate
the opponent's firewall within 30 minutes.
I've dropped the firewall building specs
in our group chat.
Why am I not in the group?
Mark my words.
Without me, you don't stand a chance.
Why are you so sure
that we can win with you?
Because the word 'lose'
doesn't exist in my dictionary.
Well,
can I join you?
I thought only your heart was with us.
I just remembered
how well you did at the Topic Selection Meeting
in your freshman year.
Of course, most importantly,
my heart is always with you.
Shouldn't a team leader
treat her members to a meal?
Makes sense.
- Let's go.
What about me?
Let's go.
Hello, passenger.
It's a pleasure to serve you.
Last digit 5438?
Stop it.
Have you developed
professional habits as a chauffeur?
Totally.
Tell you what.
I'm always thinking about serving my passengers.
- Take these.
- So many bags.
Come on.
Think about it.
Since we're doing better and better,
is it time for me to take a break?
You can't rest.
Haven't you heard?
People fall sick when they are idle.
You have a point.
The employees make money for the boss.
The money is not yours
unless you spend it today.
Let's go. Let's keep shopping somewhere else.
These are not for me,
but for our daughter.
Look.
The weather and season are about to change.
I rushed to buy her new clothes.
She hasn't been back for quite a while.
Exactly. It's been about three weeks.
Is she...
- Dating someone?
- With whom?
Lin?
They are in the same lab,
so they're together all the time.
Affection grew?
I bumped into them downstairs the other day.
Right on the spot?
If there's nothing between them,
- I'll eat my hat!
- Your hat wouldn't believe it!
Let's find her now.
- Go to her university.
- Let's go.
It locks automatically.
- My shoe almost fell off.
- Fasten your seat belt.
Come on. To our team.
Cheers!
I have to take this. Order whatever you like.
Hello.
You're a team of five now? How's it going?
How do you know?
That's why Wen Bo came so coincidentally.
You sent him back to the lab.
You said that you won over two roommates
and would take them to the lab
to give Shu Lan a jolt.
Wen Bo is the only hesitant member
on Lin Jia Dong's side.
If he hadn't seen your team spirit
with his own eyes,
how could he join you?
What an old fox.
I'm having hot pot.
Who is old?
Me. I'm old.
An old fox deserves fresh meat.
That's it. Talk later.
We didn't tell Xue Jiao
we were coming to visit.
Isn't it inappropriate?
We're checking on our daughter.
We did nothing wrong. Why are you feeling guilty?
Uncle, Auntie.
Speak properly. Play it by ear.
Lin.
Lin, what a small world.
You are...
We bought something for Xue Jiao.
I thought her dorm building was in this direction
and ended up at the lab.
She got lost.
Xue Jiao is having hot pot with her friends.
Why didn't she invite you?
She...
I guess it didn't work out.
Keep observing.
It's okay. Let's take the things to her dorm.
You are so busy. We can't trouble you.
It's okay.
- Give it to me.
- You're so busy.
Okay.
Lin.
Have you been busy?
What's that question? Of course, he's busy.
- Right?
- It's been fine.
You're not busy at all?
Yeah. Can't you be busier?
Auntie, are you trying to say something?
- Is it so obvious?
- Absolutely. Just ask him.
Then I'll cut to the chase.
Lin, do you have a girlfriend?
Are you finding me a girlfriend?
Didn't Xue Jiao tell you?
About what?
I guess it's not very clear yet.
So you're still pursuing someone?
I guess.
I just feel that Xue Jiao
is quite dependent on you.
I'm asking you that for my daughter
because I'm worried.
Of course. An excellent young man like you
wouldn't fall for someone ordinary.
She is extraordinary.
Alright. It's a huge weight off my mind.
I'm just not meant to be your mother-in-law.
Auntie.
You're meant to be.
I'm pursuing Xue Jiao.
What...
You...
Well, Lin, go about your business.
Leave us the things.
No, I'm not busy. I'll walk you to the dorm.
No need. We can go by ourselves. Go back to work.
How can I do that? Let me do it.
I got this.
Hurry up.
Isn't Xue Jiao having hot pot? Check on her.
Yeah, go ahead.
Go ahead.
Go ahead. Be bold.
Then, I'm leaving.
Go ahead.
Thank you, Uncle, Auntie.
Don't mention it.
Then I...
- I'll try harder.
- Go for it.
I knew it. You see?
You can rest assured, huh?
Our 'beast' finally found the 'beauty'.
What nonsense.
Our 'beauty' finally found a prince.
Yeah.
I knew it. You didn't even have to come.
I had to come.
Otherwise, how would I
see my wonderful son-in-law?
Yes!
- Slow down.
- Hurry up.
- Okay...
- Hurry...
Lin is such a wonderful child.
So what pot are we having?
- Spicy.
- Tomatoes and mushrooms.
You have three-grid pots?
Forget it. Let's get the dishes first.
Duck intestines.
I don't eat intestines.
- Beef tripe.
- I don't eat beef tripe. Duck blood.
- I don't eat blood.
Forget it.
That's enough for now.
Should we talk about the division of labor?
Si Qi. Applied Electronics.
You'll be in charge
of the application guarantee.
Shu Lan. Mathematics.
You'll be in charge
of encryption and decoding.
Fei Fei and I major in Software Engineering.
We'll be in charge of the offense.
So the defense...
Math is the foundation of everything. I should be the offender.
Pretty sure I beat you in Firewall
and Intrusion Detection class last semester.
But I also took that course.
Didn't I score the highest?
Ladies.
Let's talk over food.
We don't have three-grid pots.
How about a nine-grid one?
Alright.
I don't want to settle.
Wait, Shu Lan.
Wait, Fei Fei.
Si Qi, don't.
Wen Bo.
I'd better ask Lin Jia Dong if I can go back.
Wait, Wen Bo.
Excuse me. Can I refund these?
Fine, I can do it.
I'll eat.
I can help.
You come with free Flash?
Since you dashed away,
I'm flashing to chase.
Your parents came to see you.
I told them everything.
About what?
My parents came to see me.
And you told them everything?
I haven't told them anything yet.
I asked you last month.
Didn't you say that you had told them?
I was being evasive and got over it
with some excuses.
You...
You misunderstood me...
We've been together for so long.
You still won't make it public?
But I think if my parents know,
all my relatives and the whole world will know.
And I don't want our schoolmates
to think that we're having a lab romance.
What's wrong? Don't tell me
that you're feeling insecure.
I don't mind.
It's up to you when to make it public. I'm okay.
Anyway, I just said that I'm pursuing you,
and you haven't said yes.
Come on.
You're preparing for your defense.
After you graduate, I will tell the whole world
that Dr. Lin is my boyfriend.
Okay?
Alright.
It's boiling. What would you like?
I'll cook it for you.
Beef tripe.
Okay.
Guys, Si Qi brought us tea.
- Everyone gets a share.
- Thank you.
My hometown is known for tea production.
My mom heard about the contest
and sent me a lot of this year's new tea.
Here, try some.
Xue Jiao, Lin has been looking out for us.
Should we leave him a few packs?
Let's see if we can use the lab first.
I forgot to tell you.
The lab is ours during the day.
Come after 21:00 if you need to use the lab.
Says who?
Someone went for hot pot when
I was applying
to Professor Tan for lab hours.
Jia Dong, can I come back here?
We don't accept traitors.
You can't even fight for the right to use the lab.
What do we need you for?
Let's go.
Catfish effect?
No. All these brats are catfish.
Aronson effect?
No. The reward and punishment mechanism
couldn't have worked.
Bell effect?
Only Lin Zhi Hua can make it convincing.
New product at Tiantian's Tea.
I have no appetite. Can I get a hug?
What's wrong?
Can't lead the team?
I stay up late every day,
and my members are so easily agitated.
It's impossible to lead them.
It's because I've never been a leader.
Come on, leader.
Could you teach me the secret to managing a team?
My secret is to rule with absolute power.
That's not useful at all.
It's hard to manage smart people.
If you want three outstanding students
to appreciate each other and team up,
put them through hardships together.
Makes sense.
If you become a boss,
will you manipulate your employees like this?
It's not that easy to share hardships.
I can create hardships for them.
You're so sneaky.
I learned it from you.
I'm a big fox.
You're a little fox.
There's a breakthrough?
No.
There's a sick joke on the school forum,
saying that our lab is haunted at night.
Guess by what.
By what?
Dead programmers.
Don't you get it?
He's 'cursing' us.
That's so lame.
If you don't mind, please be quiet.
You may not have noticed
that someone is working here.
Can't we take a break?
Shared hardships.
We do have a common opponent.
Huge breakthrough!
Lin Jia Dong, I'm sorry.
I'm going to inspire my team
with the help of your jealousy.
I saw another post.
I can't do this anymore.
I stay up late every day.
And my teammates are useless.
Xue Jiao.
I really want to help you,
but I don't get enough sleep
and end up sleepy in class.
My attendance is in jeopardy.
- I'm so sleepy.
- I'm going to sleep.
Wait.
Is Lin Jia Dong really going to leave me alone?
Power outage. Time for bed.
Dead programmer!
Who's doing pranks in the middle of the night?
Let's find out.
I don't see well at night. Turn on the flashlight.
Shu Lan, I'll go with you.
Si Qi...
What's that?
What is that?
The lab is haunted!
Stop looking.
Hurry up.
I'll protect you.
You were the first to run away.
It's not blood. What is it?
Sodium carbonate solution turns red
with phenolphthalein solution.
Junior high chemistry.
Yeah.
Thye're quite something.
Making a huge breakthrough so soon?
- Serves you right.
- He deserves it.
So lame.
Coward.
Let's go.
I was scared awake.
What an easy enemy.
What a waste.
Professor Tan, look at my face.
She did this.
She was scared of losing
and played tricks on me.
Professor Tan, I didn't do anything.
Professor Tan, all power was down,
except for equipment electricity.
Even the security cameras went dark.
She did it to beat me up.
She had planned to eliminate the evidence.
Even my high school classmates
can pull better tricks than you.
There is no footage,
so I'm given the benefit of the doubt.
Right, Professor Tan?
Then how did I get these wounds?
Professor, punish me if you want to.
You've always been
my academic role model.
I applied to this university because of you.
But honestly, I'm very disappointed
at what Lin has done.
What did I do?
Professor, I'm quitting, too.
I wanted to win a reward and drop out.
But I didn't win any rewards
and might even be punished.
It's not worth it.
You kids are quite honest.
Professor, the power suddenly went out last night.
Lin, why did you try to scare us?
I was so scared.
It's alright, Fei Fei.
I'm here. Don't be afraid.
Professor Tan.
Professor Tan, I'll take the punishment
with all of them.
Gu Xuejiao.
Step outside first.
When will the meeting end?
It's hard to say.
Ms. Zheng is extremely busy.
You can leave her a message.
What happened to your face?
I came here because of this.
Alright.
That's it.
Where is Jia Dong?
He just left.
I asked Jia Dong what Lin Zhi Hua has been up to.
He said he wanted...
He is at the end of his rope
and is going for the prize money.
Okay. Let him know that
I won't even spare him this petty money.
Isn't Jia Dong busy with the contest?
Why did he come here?
You don't need to worry about that.
Someone will take care of it.
I'm done. The lab is yours now.
How is your team spirit burning?
What a group of passionate young people.
Just find the ignition point,
and there is no limit.
Congratulations.
It seems that I can't have hot pot with you.
But I miss you very much.
Okay, that's it.
We'll work late in the lab today. Come and visit.
Okay.
So we're all good on who's doing what, right?
Let me repeat it.
- Shu Lan...
- Stop.
It's about to boil.
Come on, ladies. Cheers.
I mean, go, leaders!
- Come on!
- Cheers!
It's still raw.
- What did you get? Beef tripe?
- Yeah.
Not bad, Wen Bo. You're pretty reliable.
Having been here for so many years,
I've never known about this small path.
Rest assured, leaders.
I'll get us back to school in record time.
I'll give you credit first.
Shall we come up with a group name?
I think an ordinary and unremarkable name
will highlight our rich connotations.
"Am I right?"
Is it good?
You have to tell us a name first.
'Am I Right' will be the name.
So not funny.
Gu Xue Jiao, what kind of members did you recruit?
We should be grateful as
long as we don't rank last.
How about 'Last-ranked Ace'?
- I like it.
- Me too.
"Last-ranked Ace."
It feels like an ant trying to shake a giant tree.
I like it.
- So that's the name.
- Okay.
Hello.
Are you back?
We're on the way.
Wen Bo showed us a shortcut outside the back gate.
You know what? We almost
sorted out the code over dinner.
I've been curious.
Do you have a boyfriend?
You vanish sometimes
and call him behind our backs.
Gu Xue Jiao, you're very fishy.
I...
It's my brother.
Ming Ze.
Ming Ze, can you hear me?
My WeChat signature
is what you said in the interview.
"Don't let others define your life."
Did you hear that? He adores you.
What are you doing?
Hand over everything you have.
Call the police.
Bro, you have your gangster rules.
It's just for the money, right?
Guys, give them the money.
Let him take it.
Bro, why don't you show me your QR code?
I'll transfer money to you.
Are you kidding me?
The guy on the back.
Yeah, you.
You're carrying a laptop, huh?
Don't even think about it.
Alright.
You have quite a backbone.
Let's see what breaks first, your bones or my bat.
Get them!
No! Don't!
No!
Don't take his bag!
Smash it!
Go!
My laptop.
You...
Xue Jiao!
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
The laptop.
Wait.
What's your problem?
Huh?
Get him!
The laptop!
Watch out!
Sorry.
Be careful.
I dare you to come back. I know kung fu. I'll...
I told you I'm fine.
How is this fine? Let me see.
Does it hurt?
Don't move.
Didn't they say they failed?
How is your head? Is it okay?
Jia Dong.
Zhi Hua.
How come you're so fast?
Gao Rui hasn't arrived yet.
I was nearby, so I came fast.
How did you get hurt so badly?
Tell him.
Ask Wen Bo.
Your trousers are dirty...
Auntie!
- Auntie!
- Jia Dong.
Jia Dong, wait.
Let me in. Let me see her.
I'm not stopping you.
But Ms. Zheng is out for business.
I asked you to vent my anger.
Why did you hurt Zhi Hua?
No, we didn't.
Minor bruises are enough.
Why did you hurt his face?
We wanted to teach him a lesson.
Okay, calm down.
We just taught him a lesson.
Do you think Lin Jia Dong
asked someone to do this?
Let me do it.
It's okay. I got this.
Do you remember Ms. Zheng from B&amp;C Motors?
The one who tried to grope you
at the dinner meeting. Right?
She exploits the team's creativity
and damages the industry.
A cancer in the industry.
She is Lin Jia Dong's aunt.
They have such similar taste.
You knew about it all along.
Why are you keeping Lin Jia Dong?
Aren't you scared that he'd sell you out?
Lin Jia Dong may like to play tricks,
but I don't think he's behind this.
He's just easily swayed
and gets manipulated.
Doting on your fans, huh?
Timing and subtitles brought to you by
My Old New Life Team@Viki.com
"I'll Wait for You at the Summit" - Yang Yuqing
♫  In a dark room  ♫
♫  Be careful when lighting a lantern  ♫
♫  To prevent an echoing sound  ♫
♫  Recalling the memories  ♫
♫  Every intertwined trail of footprints  ♫
♫  Is the journey we take towards each other  ♫
♫  Let fate run its course  ♫
♫  Let us give all our courage  ♫
♫  To journey through time with you  ♫
♫  If you can also  ♫
♫  Read the secret in my gaze  ♫
♫  You'll realize you've always been in my heart  ♫
♫  I try to open my arms  ♫
♫  Because I'm certain of this love  ♫
♫  I'll wait for you at the summit  ♫
♫  Even if the wind's harsh, it's all right  ♫
♫  There's a figure approaching  ♫
♫  I know it must be you  ♫
♫  I try to open my arms  ♫
♫  Because I'm certain of this love  ♫
♫  I'll wait for you at the summit  ♫
♫  Even if the wind's harsh, it's all right  ♫
♫  There's a figure approaching  ♫
♫  I know it must be you  ♫