Timing and subtitles brought to you by
My Old New Life Team@Viki.com
"Burning Tempo" - Duan Aojuan
♫  One, two, three, four  ♫
♫  Don't be afraid of the so-called star student  ♫
♫  You are also someone else's legend  ♫
♫  Don't hold back, grow with all your might  ♫
♫  Midsummer's flowers  ♫
♫  Now is the time to format your life  ♫
♫  Math and physics are not complicated  ♫
♫  Youth is full of obstacles, but we'll slowly become stronger  ♫
♫  My heart still burns passionately  ♫
♫  Follow the tempo, set yourself free  ♫
♫  The illuminated night sky guides me to success  ♫
♫  I'll accompany you as you bravely take flight  ♫
♫  My love still burns passionately   ♫
♫  Shining in the smiling eyes  ♫
♫  Let us transcend the obstacles of time  ♫
My dream is to go to Jinghai University.
I, Gu Xuejiao,
dreamed of becoming a star student ever since I was young.
So, I worked very hard every day to achieve my dream.
But the harder I tried, the more off-track I got...
...and thus the more disappointed I became.
That tan jock will eventually
become a foot-scratching homebody.
Compared to men's troubles,
the hardships of work is nothing.
It's a good thing that work isn't just about your resume,
but also your skills.
Today, Sister Jiao will officially enter the programming department.
From admin to the core programming department.
I'm so jealous.
Other fresh grads start off as software engineers.
But it took me five years.
September 5th, 2024.
My 28th birthday.
Gu Xuejiao, you're about to start a brand-new chapter.
Wait, you're pulling the offer?
Yes, my first degree might not meet your hiring criteria.
But I still want to fight for this opportunity.
I earned a bachelor's degree in software engineering
through a part-time correspondence program.
Please take a look.
I truly value this opportunity.
I even gave up the offer to become a full-time employee in my original position.
The truth is, you didn't pass our technical review.
I have the email. I did pass.
There is a critical bug in your code.
Can you show me the error log?
Do you think I made a mistake?
Ms. Gu, the last thing I want is to lose a talent.
So we'll help you reapply
for a full-time headcount on your original team.
Your past performance has been truly outstanding.
But your resume doesn't fit our programming department.
Forget it.
I quit.
I've got the skills.
I'll survive anywhere.
I was too impulsive. I should've negotiated my severance before quitting.
Babe,
congrats on going full-time.
We broke up ages ago.
Xuejiao,
can we get back together?
I haven't played a game in two weeks for you.
Wow, you're awesome.
Stop acting out.
People are watching.
You weren't like this before.
You changed your college application to go to the same school as me.
To avoid a long-distance relationship,
you even rejected two offers for overseas promotions. Remember?
I was always the one giving in this relationship.
I gave up so much just to be with you. And you?
That's not what you used to say.
You said I was cool and charming,
just like the male lead in a drama.
That's why I needed to snap myself out of it.
I was blinded by love and chose to stay in poverty.
We're almost 30.
To me, you'll always be 18.
I...
- Xuejiao.
- Sir...
You said we'd be together forever!
Manager Lin, thank you for walking me out.
You're Director Lin's most valued hire.
Official headcount is tight these days,
I had to kick a contractor out to make room for you.
We planted a critical bug in her code.
- That was Director Lin's idea?
- Yes.
Pull up Gu Xuejiao's program logs.
I'd like to review them.
Lin Zhihua, did I somehow offend you?
Why are you targeting me?
How is not hiring targeting you?
Why don't you take a look at yourself first?
You gave up everything for a guy, turning down promotion chances.
After five years, you're still a highly replaceable contractor.
You're almost 30.
You gave up your full-time offer because you failed the transfer.
That shows you lack priorities and crack under pressure.
You'd be a burden in the programming department anyway.
Why did you change my code?
I changed your code?
You planted a bug in my code,
so that your precious Zhou Shiyun can take the job, didn't you?
If the hiring process is unfair, I won't have it.
You won't let me go to B1 for my laptop,
how am I supposed to review your code?
Then I'll come with you. I'll be watching you.
What's happening?
Don't panic, hit the alarm button!
I was blinded by love and chose to stay in poverty.
I just want to go back ten years ago and slap myself.
Please take your seat in the exam room accordingly.
You gave up everything for a guy, turning down promotion chances.
After five years,
you're still a highly replaceable contractor.
Good luck on the exam.
You said we'd be together forever!
If Yi Tianyu hadn't shown up,
she might've gone to Jinghai University, not me.
You've got half an hour left.
Hurry up.
Wait.
Jinghai No.7 High School?
2014?
Senior year?
Oh my!
What are you doing?
What's wrong with you? Acting all jumpy.
Why do you also look like a Grade 12 student?
Babe.
You changed your college application to go to the same school as me.
To avoid a long-distance relationship,
you even rejected two offers for overseas promotions. Remember?
I was the only one giving in this relationship.
Gu Xuejiao.
What are you doing? You're taking an exam.
I...
I'm turning in my test.
She didn't finish yet.
Meet me at the pedestrian bridge.
It's so real. Too real.
If this isn't a dream, then I must be...
I'm dreaming.
Senior year was always a nightmare for me.
Since the day I started high school,
my mind drifted further away from studying.
My grades kept dropping,
that's why I kept running into setbacks later at work.
Even in a dream, I want to slap myself so bad.
For someone almost 30,
dreaming of returning to their adolescence is kind of unreasonable.
It's better to wake up now.
What are you doing?
Yi Tianyu? Why are you still haunting me in my dream?
Ex-boyfriend.
But this 18-year-old face is way too real.
You asked me out for this?
Ow, it hurts, ouch!
You asked me here so you can pinch me like this?
Ow! It hurts me, too!
It hurts me, too... I can also feel it...
This isn't a dream.
It is a dream.
No, it's not.
Is it? No?
And finally, let's take a look at September 5th's weather forecast for Jinghai.
Daytime high, 28°C.
Low, 20°C.
It'll be hot. Sun protection is advised when heading out.
Come take a look! Two pairs of socks, five yuan!
Come take a look!
I... have been reborn?
Aren't you surprised?
Who wanted to see you?
You left me this note yourself.
No wonder you turned in your exam as soon as you saw me.
You wanted to ask me out, but you were shy.
That really is my handwriting.
It's hard to deny it now.
Teacher Yin!
What? Where is she?
She's here?
Today, let me teach you a lesson.
Next time you read a note, don't just read the front.
I'm off.
Focus on your studies.
2014.
Senior year.
My 18-year-old self.
The one I kept regretting over and over again.
Gu Xuejiao.
Don't say the heavens didn't give you a chance.
Restarting the game.
Let's check my memory first.
You can predict the lottery numbers?
Seriously?
Trust me. You'll win for sure.
The red balls are 31, 24.
I don't remember the numbers at all.
Forget the double-color ball. Try something else.
Sir, I made a mistake.
I meant sports lottery.
That insane upset match with record-breaking odds.
Germany vs. Brazil in the World Cup.
Bet 7 to 1.
You'll get rich for sure.
Not happening.
- Why not?
- The World Cup is over.
Where am I supposed to bet?
September 5, 2014.
Right. Today's the placement test.
Summer's over already.
Oh! And it's my 18th birthday.
Birthday?
Birthday!
Oh, no.
Did she just scam me for a lottery ticket?
Don't tell anybody I let you play the lottery.
As reported by our station, the famous phone brand Yano
officially declared bankruptcy today.
Yano's largest parts supplier,
our city's South District Component Factory
was hit with huge order cancellations.
A large stockpile is stuck in the plant.
Insiders say
the factory's cash flow has completely dried up.
Salaries are no longer being paid.
Workers are not getting any compensation.
Coming up next, financial news.
On my 18th birthday,
Old Gu chose loyalty over severance and pay cut,
but ended up losing both his job and the compensation.
That was the starting point of our family's decline over the next ten years.
I'm not just here to change my fate,
but to help those I love live a better life.
This time, there's no way I'll let Old Gu sign that form.
Dad! I'm...
You're back.
Dad.
You signed it already?
The factory's going under...
Forget it. He won't believe me anyway.
I, I mean... We should think it over.
Nowadays, everyone uses smartphones.
Who uses keypads...
What's wrong with you, kid?
You were supporting me to stand with the factory.
What now?
Changed your mind?
Look at this phone.
I won it for you at the factory's assembly contest as your tenth birthday gift.
Eight years have passed.
Not a single issue.
So, what does that tell you?
It means some things can stand the test of time.
People can, too.
Oh, right. I've got something for you.
Wait here.
Let me get it.
Here.
Look.
Uncle Sun from the canteen heard it was your birthday
and made you a big cake.
- Let's wait for your mom and brother.
- Okay.
You get some rest. I'll make two more dishes.
Okay.
This time, I won't let Old Gu repeat the same mistake.
Who are you tying to scare standing there?
You think I don't know why you're sneaking out?
I'm just going out for a bit. Don't tell Mom and Dad.
I won't let you go.
Roller Blast beta's today! I'm the backbone of the design team!
I must be there!
You're just an intern rendering stuff. What backbone?
What is it?
What's going on?
- Did I hit anyone?
- You hit me.
Are you all right?
That punk didn't shut the window.
Look at this. It must've been the wind rattling everything.
Everything's been knocked over.
Thought it was a thief,
turns out it was just my bad luck.
You're right.
- Why did I catch up to you?
- My bad, sorry.
Gu Xuejiao, I knew you still cared about your big brother.
You covered for me at a time like this.
I'll bring you breakfast.
Bye.
Gu Xuejiao. Give me the key.
I'm in a rush.
Wait, are you crazy?
Stop. Hurry, give me that.
Today, I'll stay right here, watching you.
You're not going anywhere.
Admin, two instant noodles for No. 40!
Okay, coming.
Use the E skill.
I broke up.
I got kicked out by my landlord,
because I didn't pay the rent.
Look, just crash in my booth for now.
Gu Mingze.
This time, let me help you reinvent your life.
The key?
Gu Mingze!
Xuejiao, why did you sleep here?
Dad, Brother...
It's the weekend, he has no class,
so he went to buy us breakfast.
Who said he doesn't have class?
Teacher Xiao Gao's coming over soon to tutor him.
Those two trial lessons went well,
so your mom and I decided to hire him.
I'll skip breakfast.
Auntie Zhou's husband is having a party today,
I have work to do.
Right, Xuejiao, you sit in on the lessons with your brother.
And keep an eye on him.
Make sure he pays attention.
Teacher Xiao Gao is a top student from Jinghai University.
Last year, he helped a senior improve by 200 points in just 6 months.
It's a bargain for us.
- One payment, two senior students.
- Hurry up, Wife. The shuttle's here.
I have to go now.
- Bye-bye, Mom.
- Bye-bye.
Focus, okay?
I remember you wanted to get into Jinghai University, too.
Jinghai University.
My dream is to go to Jinghai University.
Gu Xuejiao, you used to have such ambition.
How did you go astray halfway?
If you'd worked as hard in your senior year
as when you took the correspondence program later,
you'd have reached the peak long ago.
♫  Although troubles always outnumber the solution  ♫
♫  Even if I fall, I fall with grace  ♫
♫  Whether life can be restarted   ♫
♫  I can't say for sure  ♫
♫  If I fail again, I won't be sad  ♫
♫  Even Zhao Zilong took seven tries at the Battle of Changban  ♫
♫  If there are no second chances in life  ♫
♫  Then now is the last chance  ♫
♫  No more signals of being tired and worn out  ♫
♫  No more channels of being lost and confused   ♫
♫  No more heartbeats full of fright  ♫
♫  I don't want my life to be in quotes  ♫
♫  No more invasions of laziness  ♫
♫  Let me pick up my pencil again  ♫
Star of Wisdom, hear my vow.
Let Gu Xuejiao rise again now.
With laser focus, exams I ace.
To the dream school, I claim my place.
PhD and Master's, mine to keep.
A winner's life on the main street.
♫  I'd rather be a broken piece of jade than a perfect tile  ♫
I can't remember the college entrance exam questions.
But maybe the essay topic.
I don't remember the lottery numbers.
As well as the exam questions.
Looks like in this new life, I still can't cheat.
Fine. Let's do a mock exam first.
♫  No more embraces of insecurity   ♫
♫  No more lonely noises  ♫
♫  No more invasions of laziness  ♫
I have no idea...
What are these questions about?
Gu Mingze, you finally came back.
Lin Zhihua.
Why are you targeting me? Did I somehow offend you?
You won't let me go to B1 for my laptop,
how am I supposed to review your code?
Is this the Gu residence?
Haunting me like a ghost.
What did you say?
I said, "Why didn't Senior Brother Xiao Gao come here himself, and instead had to send a sub?"
Something came up at home.
I'm covering all his gigs.
Forget him.
Let's talk about you.
So you're the idiot who failed
the college entrance exam twice in a row?
Teaching isn't something you can just wing.
Education is a matter of national importance.
If you mess me up, who's responsible?
Kiddo, you may be smart, but you're barely 20.
It's time for me, your elder sister, to teach you a lesson.
You say you're Senior Brother Xiao Gao's classmate,
so you're from Jinghai University, too?
Where's your resume and diploma?
I'm a direct-entry Ph.D. student. I haven't graduated yet.
So no diploma, right?
You could say that.
Then don't blame me for getting my revenge.
Though this is a free trial class,
Senior Brother Gao just sent some random guy over here,
isn't it kinda inappropriate?
In that case, I'll take my leave.
Wait!
You just gave up like that?
How about trying to persuade me?
Should I get on my knees, crying and begging you to give me a chance?
I won't say no to that.
Imagine a top student from Jinghai University failing a trial class.
That'd be so embarrassing, right?
You leave without even saying goodbye?
So you've always been rude.
I should just be an internet café admin with Gu Mingze.
Jiao Jiao.
Jiao Jiao, we are not in the same class this semester.
I'm going to miss you.
How could I bear to see you so sad?
Don't worry, Shiyun. I'll be back in Class One in no time.
Nothing matters more than besties, right?
Jiao Jiao, what's wrong?  You...
Who'd fall into the same trap twice?
I mean, from now on, I'm all about studying.
So you really don't want to stay in Class Eight?
No. You worked so hard to get into Class Eight.
You can't just leave. That'll be a waste.
So don't give up, Xuejiao.
I'll join your 8:00 p.m. soap-opera drama later.
Sun Tiantian!
Who are you?
I'm Gu Xuejiao. Our dads work together.
I remember now.
I baked your birthday cake base for my dad.
My dad said you were in Class Eight. I'm in Class Eight, too.
We can go to and from school together.
Sounds good!
Make way, make way!
- Watch it!
- No biking on campus!
Get out of the way!
Xuejiao, you okay?
No.
- Xuejiao, run.
- Who did that?
Xuejiao, just run. Or she'll know it's you.
I've already started over. I'm not scared of her.
Let's go.
Gu Xuejiao. Just you wait.
Don't let me get you. Or you're done for.
Classmate,
are you okay?
Get up.
Class, to encourage everyone to study harder this semester,
I've decided to rearrange your seats based on the placement test results.
I hope this new reward system will motivate you guys.
It's senior year. Time to sprint for the finish line.
Anyone whose name I call out
go into the classroom and pick your seat.
- Liu Jiaxue.
- Here.
- Xi Junyang.
- Here, ma'am.
- Bai Yubin.
- Here.
Isn't that Gu Xuejiao?
Xuejiao, aren't you afraid of offending Chen Xiao?
Don't you know she's the top dog at No. 7 High?
I know that all too well.
Then why you...
You don't get it.
The enemy of my enemy is my friend.
- Zhou Zilin.
- Here.
She dropped in the rankings and ended up in our class.
Why would I care?
I didn't say you cared.
Qi Lei.
Here!
See you later.
- Sun Tiantian.
- Here.
Isn't she Yi Tianyu's table mate?
- Gu Xuejiao.
- Teacher Yin.
Did you call the wrong name? It should've been me.
No.
You're next.
She scored higher than you. Look.
- I...
- Yi Tianyu.
- I... This...
- You're here.
She beat you by one point. That's still higher.
- Do better next time.
- Go.
- Okay.
Class, if you don't use your brain, it's just decoration.
I'm not asking you to top the whole school.
But can we at least not all fail?
How did I do worse than last time?
After all I've done,
I still became Yi Tianyu's tablemate.
You...
I knew you were staring.
Got a stiff neck?
You got a stiff neck.
Yi Tianyu!
If you don't want to study, don't bother those who do. Okay?
No, Teacher...
Turning your back on me already?
Now, turn to page two.
Study god, bless me.
Tiantian, are you crying?
Did you fail?
I'm thanking the god.
Do not disturb.
Who's that?
You don't know?
That's the legend of No. 7 High.
He went from a failing student to a top scorer in one year.
He made it to Jinghai University.
Jinghai University and Hua University
fought over him like an espionage thriller show.
Our school had someone like that?
It took some effort to get this picture.
I prayed to him for three days before the exam.
And I scored 80 in math for the very first time.
Am I lucky or what?
Yeah, right.
You just guessed right on a few multiple-choice questions.
What study god?
Said the one who scored 18.
- Let me see.
- Return it after.
He's not as handsome as me.
Tiantian.
Do you want my photo?
I'll give you mine. It's way better than his.
I'll find one for you later.
I think I have one here.
Yi Tianyu!
Let's continue.
I'll find it for you later.
Do you like it?
Did you bring me anything tasty today?
I asked you yesterday to charge the scooter's battery.
You said you would, did you forget again?
You didn't answer my calls.
I had to push it back in the rain.
I was so focused on creating this "I love Xuejiao" thing.
I didn't hear it.
Screw Yi Tianyu.
Screw the study god.
This time, I only believe in myself.
Who would've thought,
the capitalist who bullied me ten years later
is just a barista at some café now.
As long as I put in half the effort
I use to please clients at work,
I'll have him tutoring me in no time.
What are you doing?
I'm worshipping the study god.
Why waste time on these supersititons?
Let me see which demon you're worshipping.
Senior Brother Lin,
I'm sorry I failed to recognize your great talent.
I really, really hope you can help me ace my exams.
This is a café.
If you're ordering, the menu's up there.
Okay.
Will you stop?
Senior Brother Lin, I'm sincerely asking you to help...
If you're not ordering, the door's right there.
Fine.
I'll order.
I'll have a cappuccino, no sugar, for you.
How will you pay?
Pay?
I'm leaving. Bye-bye.
- Bye-bye.
- Take care.
Senior Brother Lin.
You waited the whole day?
I wasn't just waiting.
I was studying.
Senior Brother Lin, I've done a lot of reflecting the past few days.
When you came to my house, I had just flunked an exam.
So I took it out on you.
I'm terribly sorry for that.
Scold me all you want.
I was blind to your talent.
I'm deadwood.
But look how eager I am to learn.
Would you please consider being my tutor?
First,
my current student is Gu Mingze, not you.
Second, I've already spoken to his parents.
Once Gao Rui is available, he'll return to tutoring him.
I'm me. My brother is my brother.
I'm asking you to tutor me, Gu Xuejiao.
- Please step aside.
- Senior Brother Lin.
Senior Brother Lin, if you don't say yes, I won't leave.
What's that?
Senior Brother Lin!
S-Senior Brother Lin!
Senior Brother Lin, you're waiting for me. Right?
Overconfidence is an illness.
You need help.
I tested it. This is the safest speed.
I didn't expect you to value your life this much.
Burning bright in a limited life span.
So, our goals are actually the same.
You spent just one year in senior year going from flunking to the top scorer.
I want to follow in your footsteps and get into Jinghai University.
You investigated me?
It's not investigation, it's worship.
The study god of No. 7 High. A comeback legend.
Nonsense.
There's no legend.
I was just managing my scores.
Flunk when I wanted to, top when I felt like it.
S-Senior Brother Lin!
What happened to your safe speed?
Being bugged by a kid is mentally exhausting, much less safe.
If it weren't for Jinghai University, I wouldn't bother with you.
Kiddo.
I had a very good seat.
The play was very interesting.
I didn't enjoy it.
A young man and a young woman were sitting behind me.
They were talking...
Left, a bit to the left.
Yun Yun, that claw machine hack you taught me works like a charm.
Told you.
Three. Two.
One.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Shiyun, is that you?
What a coincidence. Why didn't you go home, but came here instead?
Well, there's a bookstore up ahead.
I went to buy some books.
You actually got that plushie?
That's a limited edition from the arcade down the street.
Thi-This?
Is it?
The owner probably gave it to me because I bought so many books.
What are you doing out here at this hour?
What else would I be doing?
Shiyun, don't tell my sister.
Xuejiao has been ignoring my texts recently.
How dare she? I'll talk to her when I get back.
It's fine.
She's probably in a bad mood because she did worse than Yi Tianyu this time.
She's at the bottom of the class this time?
Interesting.
You didn't know?
My mistake. Pretend you never heard.
It's all right. You're just worrying about her.
Don't worry, I won't rat you out.
Gu Xuejiao's lucky to have a friend like you.
Just keep it to yourself.
And do not tell your parents about it.
Right.
Mom and Dad don't know yet.
If they find out, they'll break her legs.
Gu Xuejiao, look at you now.
Anyway, don't say you heard it from me.
I should go home now. Bye-bye.
- Let me walk you back.
- No need.
Be careful on your way.
Bye-bye.
Gu Mingze!
It's not fair! Why do you get snacks when you study, and I don't?
You call that studying?
Of course, I'm studying!
I'm studying history, the tragic history of my dear sister.
I heard you scored even lower than Yi Tianyu.
- Dead last, huh?
- Give it back!
Isn't he the guy always showing off on the basketball court?
He's not bad.
But still a little off compared to me.
- Give it back!
- No, no, no.
Give it to me!
Don't make me hit you! Hurry up!
Hit me. Beg me.
- Beg, and I may give it back.
- Not happening, just give me that!
What's with all the noise?
Timing and subtitles brought to you by
My Old New Life Team@Viki.com
"I'll Wait for You at the Summit" - Yang Yuqing
♫  In a dark room  ♫
♫  Be careful when lighting a lantern  ♫
♫  To prevent an echoing sound  ♫
♫  Recalling the memories  ♫
♫  Every intertwined trail of footprints  ♫
♫  Is the journey we take towards each other  ♫
♫  Let fate run its course  ♫
♫  Let us give all our courage  ♫
♫  To journey through time with you  ♫
♫  If you can also  ♫
♫  Read the secret in my gaze  ♫
♫  You'll realize you've always been in my heart  ♫
♫  I try to open my arms  ♫
♫  Because I'm certain of this love  ♫
♫  I'll wait for you at the summit  ♫
♫  Even if the wind's harsh, it's all right  ♫
♫  There's a figure approaching  ♫
♫  I know it must be you   ♫
♫  I try to open my arms  ♫
♫  Because I'm certain of this love  ♫
♫  I'll wait for you at the summit  ♫
♫  Even if the wind's harsh, it's all right  ♫
♫  There's a figure approaching  ♫
♫  I know it must be you   ♫