Has it always been like this here?
Anyway,
before the Japanese started fighting,
it wasn't this lively,
nor were there this many people.
How can they still smile?
Ma'am,
look closely.
The ones smiling are all foreigners.
Fundraising for the war of resistance!
Those with money, give money!
Those with strength, give strength!
Fundraising for the war! Give money or strength!
Give strength!
What are you doing, ma'am?
Fundraising for the war!
What's wrong?
Give money or strength!
Give strength!
This is what Chinese people should be like.
Fundraising for the war! Give money or strength!
Thank you.
Unite as one! China will win!
Ma'am.
Let's go back quickly.
Master is waiting to see his eldest grandson.
Ma'am.
Here is Jurenli,
there is also Jurenli.
Where exactly is it?
Jurenli originally
had roads on all four sides.
But when I came before,
I didn't see so many people.
Not here,
not this way.
Stop! I'll beat you to death!
It seems to be just through these two doorways.
Ma'am.
So your house here,
has it just been empty like this?
Our cousin and his wife are helping to keep an eye on it.
Ma'am.
Is Number 8 Jurenli here?
I think so.
Yes,
I recognize that mailbox.
Then why does it look like this?
Let's go in and take a look first.
You're early today.
Sorry.
New people are here again?
Careful. Excuse me.
Excuse me.
Watch out.
Come.
Excuse me.
You only know how to steal all day.
Those are all counted, you know?
Don't touch anything.
Excuse me.
Looking for a room?
There's no space left.
If you want to stay,
we can only add a bed.
If you don't agree, you can leave.
No.
Excuse me, is this Number 8 Jurenli?
Yes.
Shuyuan.
What's wrong?
Sister-in-law.
Why are you here, Shuyuan?
Slow down.
Okay. Sorry.
Shuyuan.
What's going on here?
Didn't hundreds of thousands of refugees
flood into the settlement?
Yunqi couldn't bear it.
He felt sorry for them,
so he took them in,
to give them a place to stay.
Excuse me.
Mrs. Landlady,
how do you collect rent?
By head or by bed?
By head or by bed,
you'll have to add beds.
Shuyuan, he's not a tenant.
He's Yunkui's orderly, Meng Wanfu.
He escorted me all the way
from Nanjing to Shanghai.
This is my sister-in-law, Li Shuyuan.
Hello, ma'am.
Little orderly brother.
I'm sorry.
I thought you were a tenant.
Let's not just stand here.
Come in.
Take your time.
She sounds like a saint.
Yeah, sounds nice.
Didn't she just raise our rent?
Exactly.
Come, little brother.
Sister-in-law.
Don't mind them.
If you find them too noisy,
tomorrow,
I'll have Yunqi kick them all out.
No.
It's good enough to have a place to stay
at a time like this.
It's very kind of you.
This little baby,
is newly born?
Yunkui's child.
A boy or a girl?
A boy.
Oh my, look how chubby he is.
So cute.
Sister-in-law, we heard about
Brother Yunkui.
He suffered so much injustice.
But now the Zhang family has an heir.
That's wonderful.
Our Yunqi is really disappointing.
Look at him,
eating so many supplements every day,
but my belly hasn't moved at all.
Shuyuan, where is Grandfather?
And Sister Liu, where are they?
Uncle came too?
Why aren't you together?
We arrived in Shanghai together.
But we got separated entering the settlement.
But I saw them enter
the settlement.
From last night to now,
they should have arrived.
Why haven't they returned?
Could it be that it was too dark
and they were carrying so much luggage,
so they got lost?
With Aunt Liu around,
how could Master get lost?
Shuyuan,
where is Yunqi?
Call him over.
Let's discuss
where to look for them.
He went out to buy food.
I don't know why he's not back yet.
Sister-in-law, don't worry.
Don't be anxious.
Look at your face.
You must be exhausted from yesterday's journey.
Drink some hot water first.
Right.
Madam,
you haven't eaten anything on the way.
Ma'am,
where is the kitchen?
I'll go get something hot for Madam.
It's right in the back. Make yourself at home.
Okay.
Madam, I'm going.
Let me play for a while.
Come catch me!
You kids are so nice.
Take me to find my brother and sister.
Let's play this together.
Wonton.
Wonton seller, give me a bowl of wontons.
Okay.
If you have any questions,
just tell me directly.
Is this guy named Zhang crazy about making money?
Didn't he promise you
to clear out the people downstairs?
Not only did he not clear them out,
Good bird.
but it looks more and more like a market.
Baby, I told you,
the Japanese have already set their sights on this place.
They even asked me to help them.
What are you doing?
So clumsy.
I'm going upstairs.
Watch your step.
No.
Old Hu, why is there a new face?
Is this second floor a place you can come up to?
Go down.
Watch your mouth.
What do you mean?
Who are you?
Stop arguing, okay?
Baby, it's not worth getting mad at this kind of person.
Really.
I'll talk to Zhang Yunqi later.
He's still waiting for me to promote him to assistant manager.
Exactly.
He won't dare not to listen.
What are you doing?
What are you looking at?
Baby.
Bear with it for a while.
The Japanese have their eyes on this place.
No one can stay here for long.
Wait for my arrangement.
Let me tell you,
we have an agreement.
Tell me.
That imported mink coat from Wing On Company
and those London Wanlitai silk stockings,
you've promised me three times.
When are you going to buy them for me?
I'll buy them. I'll definitely buy them this time.
As long as my baby is happy.
That's more like it.
I'm leaving.
Baby.
Go back to your room.
Lock the door.
Don't worry.
Shameless.
Damn it.
Where have you been?
Why did it take so long to buy food?
Let me tell you.
Let me tell you,
the sky is falling.
The firm sent a message,
it's absolutely true.
The Japanese entered Zhonghua Gate yesterday.
Nanjing has been lost.
What do you mean?
What do you mean what do I mean?
The government bonds we bought,
they are all gone.
I told you to sell them early.
Now you can't sell them even if you want to.
I wanted to sell them early,
but who would have thought Nanjing couldn't be defended.
Resist, resist.
Who would have thought the city would fall so fast.
Whether Nanjing falls or not has nothing to do with me.
I don't care.
But the people from Nanjing are here.
What are you going to do?
What do you mean?
Your cousin-in-law is here,
and she brought a newborn baby.
Did Uncle come too?
No.
She said when they entered the concession,
they met refugees crashing the checkpoint.
Uncle and Sister-in-law Liu got separated.
Now she wants you to go back and find Uncle.
Go, go, go.
No, we made the house like this,
what should I say when I see her?
Then you should think about what to say.
Then I'll say the house is rented out,
and the rent is to subsidize the household.
Are you stupid?
How can you say that?
If it really doesn't work, we'll kick them all out.
Are you crazy?
You just invited that vixen Miss Liu in.
Can you afford to offend Manager Hu?
Do you still want to be the assistant manager?
Right, I still have something to do at the firm.
You deal with them first.
I...
Come back.
I've been dealing with them for a long time.
I ran out of words long ago.
I can't stand you acting like this when things happen.
Be a man.
Act according to circumstances.
Play the emotional card.
Go.
You are really quick.
It smells better than a chef's cooking.
It's nothing.
Yaya,
time to eat.
If you can't even tell my skills,
then you have bad eyes.
I am a chef.
Come, little friend.
Come in.
Don't be afraid. Come in.
Come.
Help uncle taste it,
okay?
Come, sister, have a piece too.
Is it good?
Let me ask you guys something.
Do you live in this building?
Then everyone in this building.
Do you both know everyone?
Okay.
You two, tell me carefully
who lives in this building,
what they do,
and what their names are.
Whoever tells me the most,
I'll give her these two pieces as a reward.
Sound good?
This is exactly like
my brother Yunkui.
Look at these eyebrows,
these eyes,
nose, and mouth.
Sister-in-law.
The child is so cute.
My brother Yunkui
finally has an heir.
has an heir.
Sister-in-law.
Sister-in-law, did I scare you?
Our Yunqi
has worried sick about the Zhang family.
His hair is falling out in handfuls.
So he wears a wig.
It is the only way.
It's been hard on you, Yunqi.
Thanks for your hard work.
Sister-in-law.
About Brother Yunkui,
we all know.
As for the words in the newspaper,
we don't believe a single word.
Those bad guys,
as soon as he is gone,
they start slinging mud.
Thank you, Shuyuan.
Can Brother Yunkui's case still be overturned?
What the newspaper said is all fake.
He's not that kind of person.
He was not a deserter.
So we definitely need to overturn it.
We must.
Yes.
We must get justice for Brother Yunkui.
I also heard
when a major general dies for the country,
besides the posthumous rank,
funeral subsidy,
public grain vouchers, and pension,
all these add up.
It's tens of thousands.
What are you talking about?
What compensation?
You told sister-in-law.
What would she think after hearing this?
Aren't I also thinking for her?
What do you mean by that?
Yunqi.
Logically, last night
Grandpa and Mrs. Liu should have arrived.
I'm afraid they didn't just get lost.
I'm worried something happened to them.
Should we inform the police station?
I don't know.
You've been in Shanghai for a long time.
And he has extensive connections.
We need to figure out something quickly.
Sister-in-law, don't worry.
Once you're settled,
I'll go find Uncle.
Okay.
Shuyuan,
how about this?
Let's
pack our things
and move to the attic,
so Sister-in-law and the kids can stay here.
No, there's no need for that.
I can just move back to the second floor.
Sister-in-law,
well,
you might not be able to stay
in your old room on the second floor.
My cousin's wife is staying there.
Yes.
She just escaped
from Zhabei a while ago.
A woman all alone,
it's so pitiful.
Your return was indeed a bit sudden.
I can't just kick her out right now
to find a place to live.
Otherwise,
could you make do in the attic
for a couple of days?
When the room is empty, you can move down.
What are you talking about?
Sister-in-law and the kid just came back,
and you want her to live in the attic?
How could you say such a thing?
Well, my cousin's wife,
I just took her in.
Are you going to drive her away?
We can't drive her away,
but we can't let Sister-in-law
live in the attic either.
Uncle is back.
How am I going to explain this to him?
Are relatives of the Zhang family relatives,
while relatives of the Li family
are not?
No, I didn't say that.
Whenever something happens,
you always talk about the Zhangs and the Lis.
How has
the Zhang family treated the Li family badly?
What are they talking about?
Her cousin's wife's house in Zhabei was bombed.
What kind of person are you?
What kind of person am I?
Aren't they talking about me?
Not you. It's that vixen upstairs.
Now she's become her cousin's wife,
I'm telling you.
You took them in,
and you drove my relatives
into a corner.
Don't say that.
Zhabei is a mess right now.
She is just a woman.
Fine, we're done for today.
I'll go find my cousin's wife right now.
I'll go live on the streets with her.
Happy now?
Look at you.
I'll give the house to the Zhang family.
Are you satisfied now?
What are you talking about?
Stop arguing.
I'll live in the attic.
No, Sister-in-law, you can't.
I'll
Sister-in-law, you are so considerate.
That's why only women understand women.
That fool Zhang Yunqi understands nothing.
I haven't finished washing the clothes.
Where is my hat?
My dishes are going to burn.
Madam, you can't
stay in the attic.
I just went up to check.
It's small, cold, and damp.
It's not good for the baby.
Let's not talk about this now.
We'll only make do for a few days.
Madam.
Sister-in-law.
Who is this?
Meng Wanfu
is Yun Kui's orderly.
Hello, Mr. Zhang.
Orderly.
You started cooking right after you arrived.
You're so familiar with this.
Sister-in-law,
I still have the same idea. I and
Zhang Yunqi.
You still haven't figured it out after all this time.
Sister-in-law said
she is willing to live in the attic.
The most urgent thing right now
is to clean up the room quickly.
Sister-in-law just gave birth.
She doesn't have the time
to chat with us here.
Clean up early so she can rest early.
Then, orderly,
come up with me.
Help me move those two big boxes.
Watch out for the glass on the stairs.
Let's go.
Yunqi,
it's like this.
On our journey from Nanjing to the concession,
we were lucky to have Wanfu with us.
He's not just Yunkui's orderly.
He's a benefactor to our Zhang family.
Benefactor.
Then, Sister-in-law,
our benefactor will also live in our house from now on.
You can't let him sleep on the street.
That's true.
But there are no rooms left.
You don't expect him
to share a room with you, do you?
The way you talk,
why is it so harsh?
Then what do you suggest?
Why don't
you make the call, Sister-in-law.
We'll listen to you.
Stop making random decisions.
Shuyuan.
With so many people in this house,
you've managed to keep everything in order.
Adding one more bed
shouldn't be a big problem.
You know this house well.
We'll listen to you. You arrange it.
Okay, sister-in-law, I'll make the arrangements.
Shuyuan,
let's remove this table
and this stove.
We can set up a bed here, it should be enough.
How can that work?
The child can't take it.
Can't take it.
Wouldn't it be warmer
for the two of them to stay together?
We're two grown men who don't even know each other.
How can we sleep together?
You'll know each other once you sleep together.
No, no, no.
Mr. Zhang, Mr. Zhang,
don't worry about me.
I saw it when I was cooking just now.
In the corner of the kitchen,
there's just enough space for a bed board.
Just give me a set of bedding, please.
We don't have any rooms left,
but we have plenty of bedding.
Let's get to work,
so sister-in-law can get some rest.
Sorry to put you through this.
Let's go.
Orderly!
Come, over here.
Sister-in-law, I'll call you when we're done.
Madam.
You know,
even though this attic has a lot of junk,
there are still some good things.
Look at this basket,
I don't know who left it here,
but I kept it.
Hang it up,
and the little one will have a place to sleep.
I cleaned all these things up.
Don't worry, it's very sturdy.
It won't fall.
Just now downstairs,
I was giving you hints and looks,
why didn't you catch on?
Look at this attic, it's cold and damp.
You're still in postpartum confinement,
how can you live here?
We came back so suddenly,
they were caught off guard too.
Be understanding,
just bear with it for a few days.
Let me tell you,
this isn't just about bearing with it for a few days.
Do you know
that the room you used to live in,
isn't at all what Li Shuyuan said,
about some refugee aunt from Zhabei
who's half dead?
Do you know who lives there?
It's Zhang Yunqi's boss's
mistress.
Your cousin,
for his own promotion,
is using your house
to house his boss's mistress.
How do you know?
How do I know?
I asked around.
The two kids downstairs
told me very clearly,
very plainly.
And I saw with my own eyes,
that little vixen and his boss.
That vixen is so coquettish,
and the boss is incredibly arrogant.
What else did the vixen say to the old man?
I want a foreign mink coat,
and I want silk stockings.
You can tell at a glance she's no good.
If it were you,
would you be so willing
to tell others about this?
For Yunqi to do this,
he must be facing some difficulties
at the foreign firm.
Yunqi is an honest man.
As you just saw,
he's just a bit henpecked.
He's an honest person.
Honest?
Are you blind?
Can't you see this couple
is playing good cop, bad cop?
They're putting on an act for you.
They take you for a fool.
Don't say that about them.
Everything will be fine when the Elder Master returns.
Madam,
there's no need to wait for the Elder Master.
Let me tell you.
What is this dump?
What are you laughing at?
It's quite a coincidence
that you bumped into them.
No, I'm talking about serious business.
Go ahead.
We don't need to wait for Great-grandfather to come back.
I know exactly how to deal with these people.
Why don't you go down right now,
keep a straight face,
and tell that couple
to kick that little vixen out.
Tell her to get lost.
If you're too embarrassed,
then just pretend you didn't hear
or see anything.
I'll go straight down there,
and give them a piece of my mind.
In no time,
I guarantee that little vixen won't be able to stay.
She'll leave immediately.
You can't do that.
If you do that,
where will Yunqi put his face?
How can he show his face at the foreign firm?
If he cared about his face,
would he let you live here?
He's not the same kind of person as you, the brigade commander,
and Great-grandfather.
Not at all.
When we meet a gentleman,
of course we treat him with respect.
When we meet this kind of petty person,
we have to use his own methods against him.
Are you too embarrassed?
Too proud to do it?
Fine, I'll go right now.
Wanfu.
Don't go.
Are you okay?
Yunqi and Shuyuan
are my family after all.
We are a family.
If you do this,
where will Great-grandfather put his dignity?
Who cares about dignity now?
Look at these roof beams, do they treat you like family?
If you don't think for yourself,
you have to think for the baby.
Don't worry about this.
I'll go.
I said don't go.
Let's find Great-grandfather first.
Fine.
Why do I even care?
I'll go find Great-grandfather.
Baby,
who is this?
It's Daddy.
After we find Daddy,
and Grandpa comes back,
we'll be reunited.
The little baby's nose, eyes, and eyebrows,
how good-looking they are.
He completely inherited
my older brother and sister-in-law's good traits.
Just now, when I was holding the baby,
I couldn't help but think,
why is their life so good?
It's too hard for us.
The problem is with you.
How is it my problem?
It's clearly your problem.
I eat sea dragon, sea horse, and fur seal penis every day,
so much of it,
how could it be my problem?
You eat sea dragon, sea horse, and fur seal penis every day,
so much of it,
and it still doesn't work,
so it's your problem.
I...
I won't talk to you about this.
But I still need to tell you something.
I don't want to hear it.
I'm not talking about the baby.
The attic.
Let me tell you,
we still need to let my sister-in-law move downstairs.
We'll move up to the attic.
Are you crazy?
You change your mind every second.
When you helped her clean the attic just now,
you were so energetic.
What do you mean I change my mind every second?
This house belongs to Uncle.
It's only right for sister-in-law to live here.
Don't forget,
we're just looking after the house for them.
Don't forget your place.
And now you want me to move up to the attic?
Don't forget
how many people live in this big house,
and I have to take care of everyone.
I'm a tall person,
crammed into the attic...
To go to the bathroom,
I'd have to go down ten thousand steps.
You really know how to care for me.
Go if you want,
I'm not going anyway.
You're just so unreasonable.
Every time I try to reason with you,
you never listen to reason.
Sister-in-law...
She is...
my own sister-in-law.
Of course she is.
Look at the way you stare at her.
If you want to fawn over her, go ahead.
If you want to suck up to her, go ahead.
What does this mean?
Bringing three mouths,
seeking refuge in our house.
No,
it should be four.
There's also your Uncle.
So I didn't get a single penny of rent,
and I have to feed several more mouths.
Li Shuyuan, you are so short-sighted.
Our Zhang family has a lot of wealth, okay?
When Uncle fled here,
he must have brought plenty of gold and valuables.
You won't lose out.
Sister-in-law is a lady from a noble family.
Well-educated and reasonable.
She respects herself.
That orderly beside her
is very annoying.
All day long,
his big eyes are darting around.
The first time I saw him, I wanted to kick him to death.
I've been watching that shorty for a while.
As soon as he came to our house,
he was jumping up and down like a monkey,
checking every room one by one.
What's he trying to do?
Is he scouting the terrain for a battle?
Keep a close eye on him.
He's harder to deal with than your sister-in-law.
Got it.
I heard your sister-in-law mention
that Uncle has all the gold and jewelry.
He must have the land deeds too.
But the problem is,
Uncle is wandering in the concessions,
and it's chaos out there.
What if...
I'm just saying what if.
What if something unexpected
happens to Uncle?
Li Shuyuan, you're out of your mind!
Where are you going?
To find Uncle.
Where will you look?
The refugee shelters.
I know the concessions best.
He's my own uncle.
I'm his own nephew.
If I don't go looking for him,
am I even human?
Now you're his own nephew.
You're more filial than his own son.
Let me tell you,
you're not going anywhere today.
I am going, and you can't stop me.
What day is it today?
Little... little guy.
Go wash your feet.
Here,
take it easy.
Brother, I have a child with me,
could I have another portion?
You can't take two portions
just for yourself.
How about this: you eat first,
then come back for more when you're done, okay?
Okay.
Thank you.
No problem.
Slow down, careful not to burn the child.
Hey, what are you doing?
Everyone is lining up.
Go line up at the back.
Okay, going.
Hurry up.
Don't rush.
Here.
Careful, don't get burned.
Next, next.
Here, this is yours.
Slow down.
Want some wontons?
Large or small?
Cigarettes, selling cigarettes!
Excuse me, coming through!
Selling flatbread!
Cigarettes, selling cigarettes!
Excuse me.
Could I ask,
why is the newspaper office closed?
It's all because of their pro-resistance articles.
The Japanese
protest to the concession authorities every day.
The French Municipal Council and the Municipal Council
reached an agreement with them.
All anti-Japanese newspapers
have suspended publication.
A janitor like me
can only sell potstickers here now.
Our president was targeted by Japanese agents
just because he published the words,
'Chinese people, Chinese newspaper, no surrender, no humiliation.'
He was targeted by Japanese agents
and shot dead
on his way home from work.
Stop!
Don't run!
National Salvation Times
is completely disbanded.
The editors are all finding their own ways out.
It will be hard for you
to find them again.
Rich or poor,
don't let the child suffer.
Come on, take it.
Take it.
Thank you.
Stop!
There's one in uniform over there.
Bring him here.
Are you a deserter?
No, I'm not a deserter.
Which unit are you from?
The 211st Regiment, 106th Brigade.
By order of the commander-in-chief,
all stragglers will be incorporated by our unit.
Let's go. Keep up.
Let's go.
Which unit?
What's your name?
Speak! Are you out of your mind?
If you don't speak, you will be treated as a deserter.
Sir,
I am a cook from the directly subordinate team of the 87th Brigade.
Kong Erbao.
The 87th Brigade.
I've collected so many stragglers.
You are the first one from the 87th Brigade.
You are very lucky.
I heard that your brigade
was wiped out during the Battle of Shanghai.
Yes.
They all died in battle.
By order of the commander-in-chief of the war zone,
our unit is responsible for incorporating all stragglers.
You should come with us.
Yes, sir.
Fall in.
Sir.
Which unit are you from?
We are the 41st Army,
transferred from Sichuan.
We walked over a thousand miles.
Before we could even sit down,
we were sent out to pick up people.
Yes, yes.
You've worked hard, sir.
Sir.
Where are we going next?
All the way north.
To the Fifth War Zone.
The Fifth War Zone.
Where exactly?
Bengbu or Xuzhou?
You're just a cook,
but you guess pretty accurately.
It's Northern Jiangsu, the Xuzhou War Zone.
To join up with Commander Sun's 141st Army.
The 141st Army.
Commander Sun.
I think his name is Sun something-yi.
Sun Huaiyi.
Yes.
I think he is your former superior.
He is now a corps commander.
The Battle of Shanghai.
Division Commander Sun planned properly and commanded well.
He is now transferred to the Fifth War Zone as the Army Commander.
Hey, you in front, walk faster!
You shouldn't have come out to do this.
You should be resting at home.
I can't stay at home anyway.
Pardon me for asking.
Where is your bracelet?
Shuyuan has been managing the whole family.
She paid for all the expenses.
With a few more mouths to feed,
we can't let her suffer a loss.
Bah!
What loss is she suffering?
This gossipy woman
is just thinking about the master's money
and title deeds.
You shouldn't have told her the truth back then.
This house is yours anyway.
If you collect the rent,
not to mention you and the kids,
the master, me, Aunt Liu,
it's enough for five of us.
Okay.
I won't say anymore.
If I say too much, I'm just an outsider.
We've put it in the newspaper
and posted missing person notices.
I've been to the police station and the refugee camp.
In this tiny concession,
where could the master go?
I heard that
recently in the concession,
the streets are full of homeless refugees.
Every night, people freeze or starve to death.
Shoushantang even has a special corpse transport team.
Every morning, they take the corpses on the road
and bury them in the wilderness.
No, no.
Madam, no.
I didn't mean that.