[Echoes of a Thousand Moons]
[Episode 16]
Boyi and Shuqi would rather starve
than eat the grain of Zhou.
They picked ferns and ate them,
and starved to death.
There you go again, saying things
I don't understand—
what "Shu," what "ferns"?
What does it mean?
Chinese patriots with lofty ideals
keep their integrity.
They would rather go to Shouyang Mountain
and live on fiddlehead
than eat Zhou Dynasty's rice,
choosing death to uphold their ideals.
Then why do I pick these fiddleheads?
It's the middle of winter—
where am I supposed
to go pick them for you?
Master, let me tell you,
if we waited to save enough money
to buy rice on the black market,
you would've starved to death long ago.
I'd rather starve than eat Japanese rice.
What Japanese rice or Chinese rice?
I only know
that I bought the rice with my money.
I got it with my life.
I only know
that people must live and eat.
Only when you eat this rice
will it taste good.
Fine, if you don't eat, I will.
Yummy.
Look at you.
Look at the way you eat.
Shameless and ignorant.
A pair of chopsticks and a mouth.
What's wrong with the way I eat?
You eat so elegantly.
Come on, eat one.
Let me see you eat one.
You can't talk about ice
to a summer bug,
nor about the sea to a frog in a well.
Why am I a bug again?
Will I always be a bug
in your eyes?
Master, let me tell you,
this "bug" is the one
who brought your family to the concession.
This "bug" is the one
who took you out of the shelter.
It's because of this "bug"
that Zhang Yunqi and his wife
don't dare bully you,
and you get to stand here scolding me.
Sure, you've got lofty principles—
you're good at talking.
By the way,
what about the travel money
you promised me for going to Wuhan?
Have you given it to me?
I haven't got a penny yet.
Well...
Meng Wanfu,
we will definitely pay you back.
The Zhang family will never owe you!
All right.
I can't explain it to you.
But I can tell you this.
I, Zhang Ruxian,
will never eat Japanese rice!
Yujiao won't,
nor will Yueming.
Stay out of the Zhang family's
business from now on.
If we starve, that's our own problem.
You old...
I can't explain it to you either.
Eat it or not.
Wanfu.
I'm not angry.
I don't care to argue with him.
Father, I'm coming in.
Father, are you hungry?
I reheated the dishes.
Come and have a bite.
I can't eat anymore.
We don't eat rice.
We eat steamed buns.
I made them with corn starch.
Don't worry.
I kneaded the dough for a long time
and picked out all the dirt
and little stones.
Father,
are you still mad at Wanfu?
Yujiao,
I might be
a pedantic
and stubborn old fool
in some people's eyes.
But a person must have integrity.
I would rather die
than submit to the Japanese.
Yes,
you're right.
But
Wanfu
almost lost his life
just to get us some food.
I know it all.
I know that
he—
though rough around the edges
and a bit slick with his words—
is not a bad person at heart.
He's quite kind.
I was just angry for a moment
and spoke too harshly.
I spoke too harshly.
It's all my fault
for losing the money and the land deed,
bringing us to this state.
Yujiao,
I've made you and Yueming suffer.
How can you blame yourself?
Besides, look at me and Yueming,
we are doing fine.
Go close the door.
Go quickly.
Look,
this "A Record of Mount Lu"
is a printed edition
from the Southern Song Dynasty.
[A Record of Mount Lu]
It is rare in the world now,
and it is my
last treasure.
[A Record of Mount Lu]
Take it and sell it.
Put it back quickly.
How can you sell it?
It's your life.
But you and Yuelin
need to live a good life—
that's what matters most to me.
As for Yunqi and his wife,
I've already seen through them.
But no matter how hard life is,
we still have to grit our teeth
and get through it.
These hard days
won't just last a day or two.
It may be a long struggle,
and it may only get harder
and harder.
Tell me, what's the use
of keeping these worldly possessions?
Find someone capable,
who understands and cherishes it,
and entrust it to him.
Protect it through these troubled times
so it can be passed down.
On one hand,
it preserves something
for Chinese culture.
On the other,
it helps us survive this crisis.
Isn't that the best of both worlds?
[A Record of Mount Lu]
Father,
who was it
that treated this book like a treasure,
holding it close to his chest
all the way from Nanjing to Shanghai?
And who,
through so many hardships,
still managed to
keep this book safely here?
I think
you are the one who understands it best.
Yujiao, Yujiao,
times are just too hard right now.
It's too hard.
Yujiao.
Dad, keep the key safe.
Make sure no one finds it.
That's true.
Let's eat.
I'm perfectly capable.
I'll find a job sooner or later.
Besides, supporting you
and taking care of Yueming
is what I should be doing anyway.
You have to have faith in me.
Right?
I do.
I believe you.
I kneaded it pretty well, didn't I?
It's delicious,
chewy,
and filling.
Father, soak it in water.
Let it soak for a while before you eat.
Has Yueming eaten?
He's already eaten.
[Street promoters wanted (men and women)]
[Publication Salespeople Wanted]
[Typist Wanted]
[Jasmine Café]
[Taikang Company]
Eat slowly; don't choke.
[Desserts, Pudding, Cakes]
Excuse me.
[Litana Patisserie]
Cigarettes!
Would you like some cigarettes, miss?
Why is this blood draw taking so long?
[Brown sugar water]
My grandpa said
blood is the vessel of the soul.
If all the blood drains away,
the soul will be gone too.
Just look at these fingernails.
If they turn white,
the soul has left.
They really are white.
Baked sweet potatoes!
[Pu-Chi Hospital]
Kid,
it's so cold out.
Why are you out here alone?
I like being outside.
Why?
Why don't you go home?
It's colder at home than it is here.
[Zeng Xuefei, Underground
Communist Party member]
How much for these two?
Four cents.
Okay.
Exact change.
Thank you.
Here.
Take it.
Warm yourself up.
Does it smell good?
Thank you.
Hurry home.
Hello, we are from the Red Cross.
We sincerely ask patriots to donate blood.
[Liangxin Blood Donation Center]
Hello, we are from the Red Cross.
We sincerely ask patriots to donate blood.
Please take a look.
Donate blood?
Yes.
For the suffering Chinese people.
Please take a look.
Where can I donate?
Turn left at the hospital lobby ahead.
[Liangxin Blood Donation Center]
There is a room with a red cross;
that's the place.
Okay, I'll go donate.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
Come, take a look, everyone.
Please lend a helping hand
and help our compatriots.
[Liangxin Blood Donation Center]
What are you doing?
Put this away.
Don't promote here.
-Are you out of your mind?
-The soldiers on the front line
- are fighting and bleeding for us
on the battlefield.
-Blood is our own blood.
[Liangxin Blood Donation Center]
-The Chinese help our compatriots.
-The money we earn is for ourselves—
-Save our fellow Chinese people.
-why should we just give it away?
Thank you, everyone.
-Please help us.
-Think about
-Please help us Chinese.
-the days of going hungry…
[Pu-Chi Hospital]
-Thank you.
-Think about your parents.
They're waiting for you at home.
Do you want money?
[Quiet Please]
Ma'am, are you here to donate blood?
May I ask where the donated blood
will be used?
Ma'am,
blood must be dedicated to patriots.
We will issue you
a Red Cross blood donation certificate.
I can't say any more.
The blood is for the frontline soldiers.
Soldiers from where?
Guerrillas around Shanghai,
and severely wounded soldiers
sent from the Xuzhou battlefield
and other battlefields.
If you can guarantee
that the donated blood
will definitely be used
on the frontline soldiers,
then I am willing to donate.
I can guarantee it.
Here's the thing,
in the concession,
anti-Japanese activities cannot be public.
Traitors and spies are everywhere.
We have to be on guard.
We can only promote
under the guise of helping refugees.
But the people of Shanghai know us.
They know it perfectly well.
So every day,
there are still many people
coming to donate blood.
Then I understand.
Thank you.
Don't worry.
What's your name, please?
Ding Yujiao.
Do you know your blood type?
Type A.
Okay.
Come.
Please clench your fist.
[Xuzhou—Northwest Army Army Barracks]
It hurts so much!
Throw me gently.
Is your matter hopeless?
There is hope.
Why didn't you say so earlier?
Can you be reinstated?
It's hard to explain in a few words.
We have to wait.
As long as there is hope.
Then why did you come back to find me
and continue to be my counselor?
About this,
we have to talk to them.
They beat us up just now,
and tied us up now.
Who knows what will happen next.
Logically speaking,
our officer should have come to
claim us long ago,
and take us back for punishment.
It's been two days.
They want money to let us go.
Our Sichuan Army is dirt poor.
We can't afford it.
If they really get desperate,
they won't do anything crazy, right?
Not likely.
It's just a few
old cotton coats and quilts.
If they say it is, then it is.
Brother,
they won't execute us, will they?
That's really unlikely.
They can't spare the bullets.
They lack bullets.
They'd have to use a sword.
Not likely.
Every unit is short of soldiers right now.
Especially wily old soldiers like you.
And they lack
experienced staff officers like you.
I've been riding horses for so many years,
but this is the first time
I've seen it from this angle.
Regimental Commander!
What's the situation?
Regimental Commander Fang
of the Sichuan Army said
we can punish them as we see fit,
and when we're done, return them to him,
and he'll punish them doubly.
Return my ass.
Stealing and robbing
strategic supplies during wartime
is punishable by death.
That's exactly what I told them.
But Regimental Commander Fang
said we are allied forces cooperating.
If we execute them,
it won't do anyone any good.
I said your men
stole dozens of our rifles,
along with cotton uniforms
and food supplies—
altogether worth about 1,000
silver dollars.
I'm demanding double compensation
plus ransom for the prisoners.
I wanted 3,000 silver dollars from him.
Regimental Commander.
[116th Brigade, 39th Division, 40th Army]
Are you afraid the Japanese won't know
I'm the Regimental Commander?
[Pang Zhonghao, Regimental Commander
of 231st Regiment]
No saluting in the trenches.
Get to work.
Yes, sir.
What did they say?
That old fox actually knows his numbers.
He said a new recruit is
worth 12 silver dollars,
a veteran 20,
and even the highest-ranking one,
a platoon leader,
all added up still wouldn't
exceed 200 in value.
When I heard that, I got angry.
I said if you dare not compensate,
we'll take this matter
to the headquarters of the 41st Army.
You, the commander, have no shame.
Let's see if the Division Commander
and Army Commander of your Sichuan Army
have any shame.
What do you think he said in the end?
He said 400 silver dollars as a package
for compensation and apology.
That's the final offer.
Take it or leave it.
They really have no shame.
How are those soldiers?
Can they take a beating?
Looking at them, they seem alright.
We can keep them or let them go.
But Regimental Commander,
having said that,
400 silver dollars is still money.
How about we...
We'll talk about it later.
Secure the front a bit more.
Clear the obstacles in front a bit more.
Yes, sir.
This is your blood donation certificate.
Thank you.
Please bend your elbow
and press for 5 to 10 minutes.
Don't rub it.
Okay.
Thank you.
My husband is on the frontline.
Donating blood to them
is like donating to my husband.
I am Zeng Xuefei.
I am Ding Yujiao.
Sit down and rest for a while.
Slow down.
Thank you.
Ms. Zeng,
you just said
people in Shanghai all know you.
You are...
We are
the Anti-Japanese Support Association.
During the Battle of Shanghai,
it was a very large social organization.
I was in charge of
the professional women's section.
Later, Shanghai fell.
On the surface, we disbanded,
but in reality,
we have been doing
the anti-war work.
No wonder I couldn't find you anywhere.
I've been looking for you for a long time.
Why?
There is a situation
I want to ask for your help.
Sure.
Tell me.
It's like this.
There is a report
that mentions
the Anti-Japanese Support Association.
Which one?
This one.
Isn't this the field hospital?
I have delivered
medicines and supplies here.
You've been there?
Yes.
There is a Doctor Chen in this hospital.
He used to be a doctor
at Renji Hospital.
Later,
he went to support the field hospital.
He happens to be my friend.
And I feel
the wounded man in this photo
looks familiar.
I feel like when the photo was taken,
I was at the scene.
Then please look carefully.
Do you still remember
this sitting man?
I seem
to have even tried to talk to him.
What did he say?
Did he say what his name was?
Is he still alive?
Why did I remember him at the time?
Because the room was
filled with cries of pain.
Even though he was badly injured,
he didn't make a sound.
He is your...
He is my husband.
I came from Nanjing to Shanghai
just to find him.
The Ministry of War said he died.
His officer also said he died.
All news reports said he died.
Even his orderly said he died.
But I don't believe it.
As soon as I saw this photo,
I knew this person was him.
They said I was mistaken,
that he was already dead.
But
only I can recognize his face.
I must find him.
If I were you,
I would do the same.
How about this.
I'll figure something out for you.
I will go look for Dr. Chen.
After the fall of Shanghai,
they should be in the countryside.
I'll go ask him
if he has seen your husband.
Is that okay?
Thank you.
Then I'll keep
this newspaper here.
The thing is,
there are too many wounded
rescued every day.
Without accurate clues,
how can he be sure
if it's your husband?
It's alright.
Tell me your husband's
specific details.
[No. 8 Juren Lane,
Route Ferguson—Ding Yujiao]
This is our home address.
Sorry to trouble you.
Thank you
for trusting me.
As soon as I have news of him,
I'll go here to find you.
[Temporary Plasma Storage Box]
Sister,
why aren't you eating
the baked sweet potato?
I want to save it for my sister.
Yueming,
that was the first time
I met Aunt Zeng Xuefei,
and also the first time I came into
contact with a Communist Party member.
It turned out that national salvation
is not just an instinct,
but more about noble beliefs
and firm actions.
Later I learned that
in the land of Southern Jiangsu
at that time,
the New Fourth Army
was using Maoshan as its heart,
turning the sparks of guerrilla
warfare into a prairie fire.
And Yan'an
was letting the Party's roots
run deep among
hundreds of millions of people.
Those were not just numbers,
but millions of figures like Zeng Xuefei,
sowing new life amidst the devastation.
Yueming, you know what?
True hope is never solitary bravery,
but the great power forged
by a nation in awakening.
Regimental Commander!
Are you an officer?
This is our Regimental Commander Pang.
Regimental Commander Pang, right?
We are practically family.
My surname is You.
No, well,
doesn't your character "Pang"
have a "Loong" in it?
Loong roams in the sky,
and I roam in the water.
Regimental Commander, I have been wronged.
My right pocket...
Yes.
[IOU]
IOU?
Due to severe cold,
body shaking uncontrollably…
Shivering.
Today I borrow 18 sets of cotton uniforms
and 5 sets of quilts…
A total of...
[IOU]
23 items. I even wrote it wrong
and crossed it out.
I will return double another day.
Zhang Yunkui, is that you?
Pang Zhonghao.
Quickly help Brigade Commander Zhang up.
Come.
Corporal Zhang.
I thought you died in Shanghai.
I didn't expect to run into you here.
During our last battle,
you cost me an entire battalion of men.
I've been thinking about
you day and night.
I don't even miss my wife
as much as I miss you.
Have you thought about me?
Yes, I have.
Pang Zhonghao, let me tell you this.
Without me,
the warlords were doomed to fall anyway.
Then did you ever think
that one day you'd fall into my hands?
You gun thief!
I could shoot you right now.
I really didn't expect this.
For 400 silver dollars,
you almost let him go?
Do you know how many lives he owes me?
Let alone 400 silver dollars,
even for 400 small yellow croakers,
you're not leaving today.
We need to settle our score today.
Report!
Regimental Commander!
Orders from Army Headquarters!
All officers at and above
the regimental level
are to attend an urgent meeting.
A large number of Japanese
motorized troops have been spotted
flanking our forces.
Our original plan has changed.
Keep a close eye on him!
If one of them escapes,
I'll break your legs.
Yes, sir!
Brigade Commander Zhang.
Keep smelling the horse manure.
Come on.
Keep a close watch on him.
Yes, sir!
We really have to execute him this time.
Li Shuyuan,
why do you have so many complaints?
It's just working as a tour guide.
Isn't it just showing people around
the scenic spots of Shanghai?
What are you so afraid of?
Being a guide
doesn't involve wind or rain,
it's easy work.
You don't have to work every day.
When there's no business,
you can come back
and take care of the family.
What are you afraid of?
If I go out to work,
who's going to manage this big house?
Besides,
I don't have much education.
If I were a tour guide,
I wouldn't even recognize
the characters on the plaques.
What if some foreign friends come?
I don't speak any foreign languages.
How could I be a tour guide?
Anyway, no matter how much they pay,
I'm not going.
I don't care.
I've already agreed with Li.
Say what you want, I'm still not going.
Hurry up and go down to get the fish.
Yunqi.
Sorry.
What kind of work
were you just talking to
Shuyuan about?
Being a guide.
These days there are more and more people
coming into the concession,
so they need someone
to take them around,
show them the sights, and introduce
the historical places and scenic spots.
If it's inconvenient for Shuyuan to go,
could I do it instead?
Are you willing to?
I'd love to.
I was wondering
if you could help introduce it to me.
It's fine.
I can introduce it to you.
That's great. Thank you.
You're welcome.
Then,
do I need to
make any preparations?
You need to
learn about Shanghai's local conditions
and customs.
Okay, local conditions and customs.
Alright, I'll go buy some books
and prepare myself.
Okay.
Do you want me to help you?
No need.
I can do it.
Okay.
Thank you.
Shuyuan!
Welcome to come again.
Hello, Miss.
Who are you looking for?
Hello.
The gentleman on the business card
has introduced me here to be a guide.
You were introduced by Mr. Li.
Yes.
The manager is busy.
Please wait in the lounge.
Thank you.
Hello.
We have an appointment with Guide Liu.
Please wait in the lounge.
Miss Liu!
This place is not bad.
Absolutely.
Thank you.
Hello, gentlemen.
I am Guide Liu Ya.
Our Guide Agency's mission is
self-respect, self-love,
and self-reliance,
and to be professional women
of a new life.
If both of you agree
and promise to respect
the dignity of us guides,
today I will lead you
on a tour of the concession.
Of course.
We are new to the concession;
please take care of us, Guide Liu.
Not at all.
This way, please.
Okay.
♪ A grand celebration commences ♪
Are you two visiting Shanghai
for the first time?
♪ Guests gather from all around ♪
It's my first time.
May I know your name?
My surname is Li.
♪ Dressed-up crowds ♪
This is my brother.
My surname is Lu.
♪ Laughing and cheering ♪
And my younger brother
just came back from studying in Europe.
♪ The gracious host warmly
introduces the guests ♪
Where did you study?
In the UK.
That's impressive.
♪ This gentleman is a hero ♪
Do you have any preferences
♪ Of noble spirit and generosity ♪
for food or cuisine?
♪ She is a lady ♪
Anything is fine.
But since we are in the concession,
♪ Of vast knowledge and many talents ♪
Guide Liu,
♪ They fell for each other
at first sight ♪
do you have any recommendations?
Tiaotougao and pepper Chicken Feet.
♪ They sit in a row ♪
Yes.
♪ The sweet words
had long been memorized ♪
These are very famous.
I heard these are for breakfast.
Yes.
♪ Spilled out like reciting a script ♪
Well, tomorrow morning,
I will take you both to try them.
Sure.
♪ Within five minutes ♪
I have a question.
Are all the guides in your travel agency
♪ Much will soon unfold ♪
as pretty as you?
♪ Stealing the show on the spot ♪
[Shanghai jiang Guide Club; Self-Love,
Self-independence, Self-esteem][
You are such a smooth talker.
♪ There's no need for an engagement ring ♪
[Be an independent woman in the new era]
Just kidding.
-My younger brother really is something.
-Hello.
♪ As they exchange them ♪
He's been
♪ They gently wear them
on each other's fingertips ♪
wanting to come to Shanghai for years now.
Okay.
Then you must stay
for a few more days this time.
♪ Easy—super quick ♪
Miss,
the manager invites you.
Okay.
Thank you.
[Shanghai jiang Guide Club; Self-Love,
Self-independence, Self-esteem]
If you two want to watch,
[Be an independent woman in the new era]
we can help get box tickets.
You are back.
Why is your nose bleeding?
Blood?
Quick.
Come.
What happened to you?
Hei San caught me again.
He hung me by the Huangpu River
for half an hour just now.
He said to me,
"Kid,
I see you really
dare not pay me back, huh?
Just showing you a chicken
being killed won't work.
If you don't pay me back,
I will tie weights to your legs
and throw you into the Huangpu River
to feed the fish."
I told you not to borrow from loan sharks.
Don't borrow from loan sharks.
See?
Now it's a matter of life and death.
It's not just a matter of
thousands or hundreds of dollars.
In a short time,
where can we get that much money?
Even if we take all the rent,
we still can't cover it.
What should we do then?
Setting a trap for Sister-in-law
to alienate her from Uncle
won't solve the immediate problem.
We need to think of something else.
What else can we think of?
Come.
Drink some brown sugar water
to replenish your blood.
I don't want to replenish my blood now.
I want to sell my blood.
With your skinny figure,
they can hardly get an ounce out of you.
What should we do then?
Don't you think
your uncle's return this time
is very strange?
Strange how?
He only wears the same two outfits.
Was he already broke?
Or maybe he was robbed
before he came back.
Impossible.
Does he have the land deed
in that box or not?
You remind me of something.
Since Uncle came back,
he's been hiding that box
like a treasure.
Shouldn't we
check out that box first?
Exactly. We...
Don't leave my sight.
What I mean is,
we have to figure out
whether there's a land deed in that box.
If there is,
we should quickly transfer it
into your name—
or destroy it
and reissue a new one.
The most important thing right now
is to sell this house
and get the money.
And if we're lucky,
maybe besides the land deed,
there are gold bars or US dollars inside.
Then all our financial problems
will be totally solved.
What kind of luck did
our Zhang family ancestors
have to have married
such a capable wife like you?
Where's Wanfu?
Inside.
Thanks.
Wanfu!
Why are you here?
I found a job.
You found a job?
A guide at Hujiang Guide Agency.
A...
Basically, I introduce Shanghai's customs
and local culture to tourists,
and tell them
where the good food and fun places are.
One yuan per hour.
One yuan?
If I speak English,
it's double pay.
This...
Look.
[Hujiang Guide Agency]
How can there be such a good thing?