deeply
I'm not sure if I can make it.
I'll try to make it.
No need.
I'll try to make it,
I'll try to make it.
If you make it myself,
It is time
Similarity
Sin
Dīn
I even gave her some good hair and makeup as compensation.
Her parents were all willing to accept it.
I don't know how Miss Liu could not think of it.
She ran away with the gift.
So you put your aunt back?
No.
I have never seen Miss Liu's family.
That night, she was standing in the wilderness.
I didn't see her.
Listen.
I'm not being selfish.
Or else, I'll give my aunt another compensation.
Master.
You're speaking the truth.
What a coincidence.
What?
Do you think you're mistaken about her?
Master, I'm really heartless.
Please investigate.
Are you heartless?
Xuan Zun.
Madam, Xuan Zun asked me to take you to Yuewu Courtyard to rest.
Yuewu Courtyard?
Of course, it's the yard of the Canglei Hall.
Xuan Zun said that you can live here from now on.
I'm not going back to Tianmu Palace anymore?
Yes. Xuan Zun said that you're in a dangerous situation.
It's dangerous to live alone.
So, you can live in Canglei Hall.
Where is Xuan Zun?
Xuan Zun is busy.
He asked me to come here.
Is he angry and doesn't want to see me?
Oh, right.
Today, Fan Jiaojiao was busy and hit Madam.
Later, I'll ask her to send her to the Hyacinth Drugstore.
Madam Ye Li can sleep better.
No need to bother. I'm fine.
But this man named Fan Jiaojiao is so stupid.
Even his bride can recognize him.
Xuan Zun must be angry.
I've lost my love for him.
It's not good. Fan Jiaojiao has to marry a bride every year.
Anyone else will get married.
He has to marry a bride every year?
Those bridegroomes are all he took away, right?
Madam, don't worry.
The Hyacinth Drugstore is under a lot of pressure.
But it's not a legal place.
You're willing to get married.
You won't have a long-term marriage.
Fan Jiaojiao is so charming.
She can make so many women marry her.
Fan Jiaojiao is one of the three great phoenixes.
He's the one who's in charge of the clinic.
He's in charge of the needle-picking.
He's been in a lot of trouble.
Fan Jiaojiao is a fairy.
He's made of white bones.
He's got a lot of blood and blood.
He's just come to needle-pick.
But he's been in a lot of trouble.
So...
So he has to marry her?
Yes.
He's been in a lot of trouble.
He can make so many women marry him.
But the Hyacinth Drugstore has been in a lot of trouble.
This garden is called Tongyou Garden.
Tongyou is a famous place in the area.
It's the center of the Hyacinth Drugstore.
There are nine exits in the garden.
The connection is the old house and the old house.
The east side is the exit of the Hyacinth Drugstore.
The west side is the prison area of the Hyacinth Drugstore.
The north side is the pet shop of the Hyacinth Drugstore.
The left side is the place of the Three Great Kings.
Of course, you don't have to know about these things.
Then what should I know?
It's your place of the Hyacinth Drugstore and the Hyacinth Drugstore.
The direction we came from is the Lingyuan Pavilion.
It's a place where the Hyacinth Drugstore is held daily.
The place where you live is opposite to it.
It's ahead.
By the way, the Hyacinth Drugstore is a little bit remote.
It's very close to the Hyacinth Drugstore.
Don't run around at night.
You might encounter unexpected things.
Is it a monster?
It might be a female demon.
I've told you before that the Hyacinth Drugstore has three Great Kings.
I've only seen one of the Immortal Army.
Who else is it?
Is it also hidden in the shop?
The path is too short.
The story is too long.
The other two women will know if they see it.
Madam Qingyue, we're here.
You'll live in the Moonless Garden.
If you need anything, just ask me.
Thank you, Madam Cang.
What's wrong?
The river is dry.
Why is there no cup with a drink?
Forget about the wrong tree.
Put on your little lily.
Who's that kid? Why is he in my room?
Do you know how to tell a story?
I don't know how to tell a story.
It's late.
Go home.
How about I tell you a story?
After that, you can leave.
You can leave.
There used to be a girl in the mortal world who didn't enter the sect.
There was a girl who didn't enter the sect.
But she was lucky.
She married a rich husband.
But she just entered the sect.
She was thrown by her husband on the hill.
She didn't ask him.
At last, this girl was in a deep sleep.
She finally met her husband.
But his husband is very cold.
Even if he was taken away by someone else,
he didn't care about her.
He didn't even want to see her.
You don't know how to tell a story.
Shut up.
That's not the case.
But she still loves her husband.
Then she was thrown by an old man.
She opened the door and found a little boy.
The little boy told her a story.
It's a story of a human head.
How many heads are in the house?
After that, the little boy ate her up.
One, two.
half and half
дом
Exam
to
No!
Madam, you are shocked.
Ning Ying.
Thank goodness you are here.
Don't be afraid, madam.
It's just a small demon.
Small demon?
That kid is a demon.
What demon is he?
He is called the Shadow Boy.
He is a demon who eats people's brains.
He was secretly thrown out of the store
by the Xuan Zongguan's hideout.
But he didn't eat his head yet.
He was caught again.
You can just hit him next time.
I can't hit him.
Then you can just listen to me.
So simple?
Didn't you say you were caught by the father and the son-in-law?
You can't be a mother-in-law?
How did you come to the hideout?
The Immortal Army brought me here.
He also said
you don't have to go back to the hideout anymore.
Just stay at the hideout.
I came to guard you.
It's late.
You should rest early.
Madam.
Is it pretty?
Why are you painting on your face?
This is a beauty.
It's not painting.
Then why is your mouth bleeding?
It's not bleeding.
It's my rabbit's mouth.
I have a pure body and blood.
I can't see anything.
I have to make my mouth look more lively.
Do you want to try?
I don't need it.
Have you ever been on a diet?
No.
I have a free and advanced cultivation.
I have never been on a diet.
Then you must try it.
I promise you will fall in love with it.
You dress so beautifully.
I think you should go see it.
I think you should go see Xuan Zeng.
Yes.
Then you should be happy.
It's time now.
Xuan Zeng just finished his meeting.
If you go to eat again,
you won't be in time.
You are right.
Then I'll go first.
Time is so scary.
Come on, drink.
Li Qingyue.
Xuan Zeng's wife.
Is Xuan Zeng in there?
Yes.
That's good.
Please let me tell you.
Wait.
You are still young.
You are not steady enough.
I'll go.
You go.
You don't even look at your face.
You are 80 years old.
Don't scare Xuan Zeng.
What's wrong with me?
I haven't seen you for a long time.
I don't look down on you.
Do you know that?
How about that?
I am a genius.
I have been a gold medalist since I was eight.
I am not a young man.
I have a long face.
I am not a gold medalist since I was 80.
But I...
I have a strong and advanced cultivation.
Now my skill is more than three years.
Do you know that?
I will go.
Really?
Two old men.
Wait.
I warn you.
You should teach an old man again.
Old man.
Come on.
Xuan Zeng.
Those two guards are still fighting outside.
It's not good for them to see this.
Why don't we take them back
and keep the power of the hidden power?
No need.
They stay here for a day.
And she can't come in.
It's good that I can see
how much she wants to see me.
Well.
Don't fight.
I can't see Xuan Zeng.
You can't see Xuan Zeng.
I will find Xuan Zeng.
What are you looking at?
What's wrong with you?
Are you still unwell?
I am unwell.
I will kill you.
Old man.
What are you doing?
I am not unwell.
I will kill you.
Old man.
Son.
Madam.
You didn't see Xuan Zeng again?
Are you hungry?
Have some fruits.
I feel Xuan Zeng is angry with me.
No.
Xuan Zeng is angry with you.
I know.
It's normal for men to see their wives
and others in the hall.
They will not be angry with each other.
But now they don't even see me.
What should I do to make them angry?
Well...
I don't know how to be a man and a woman.
I can't make up my mind.
I am the first one to get angry.
I don't have any experience.
Go out.
I won't.
Will you tell me a story?
Then I will tell you a story.
There was a woman
who was rejected by her husband.
Ming Yan.
I hit my head.
I'm sorry.
I'm back.
I hit my head.
I'm sorry.
Mr. jerk.
Mr. jerk...
Wait a minute.
Boss is going to be screwed.
He is a cop.
That's right.
Actually,
the original designer is one of us.
And Mrs.羡,
is quite ar Businessa invitation?
They all have their own human characteristic,
they probably just love people.
What's this?
A child was locked in the yard.
He ate the fruits every day.
Then the child told him his story.
There are several fruits on the table.
After that, the child told him to eat them all.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
What's wrong?
What do you want to hear?
Let me tell you.
The Li family has been training the Wei family's beautiful mother.
She is so beautiful and she is so good at it.
So she is sending her to the family.
The Wei family's mother is so good at it.
So...
What's wrong?
Xuan Zun?
Don't look at these dirty things.
Xuan Zun!
The painting of Madam is so useful.
Xuan Zun came to see you personally.
That's not true.
Xuan Zun just burned my painting because she was afraid of the evil school.
What should we do?
What should we do without the painting?
It's fine.
I have already remembered the painting's contents in my mind.
Next, I will continue to write it according to the painting.
I will write it according to the painting.
Who let you break into the window?
I...
I will ask for your help.
I thought you thought you couldn't hit me.
You came to scare me.
If Xuan Zun doesn't like it, I won't paint it again.
Xuan Zun won't be angry, right?
I'm not angry.
Xuan Zun doesn't need to be a heart-to-heart.
Think about it.
If Xuan Zun and other women are in the painting,
I will also paint the painting.
This is the reason you came to me.
Alright, Xuan Zun.
Don't be angry, okay?
Didn't I tell you to stop looking at these messy things?
The painting said that this is how you should be painted.
You...
Don't be angry.
I'm not angry.
The painting said that the most favorite thing to do is to use it.
You try to listen to those books again.
Okay, okay, okay. I won't mention it.
Say it.
What else?
Actually, I want Xuan Zun to teach me how to paint.
I teach you?
Why?
Because I don't want to cause you any trouble.
Xuan Zun is a matter of choice.
I don't want to be in danger every time I meet him.
I can only wait for Xuan Zun to save me.
I should be a heart-to-heart.
I can't just drag him away.
Is there a reason for that?
I heard that Xuan Zun and I are in the same boat.
My technique is not good.
I'm afraid that I'll die of old age.
If I practice better,
maybe I can stay longer with Xuan Zun.
Come here tomorrow. I'll teach you a technique.
Although Xuan Zun promised to teach me a technique,
I'm afraid that you still have the will to be with me and other people.
How about...
You kiss me.
I believe that you're not really angry.
Look.
He's shy.
My life is in danger.
Let's break my lips.
I can't seem to give me time and time.
bisher
A crocodile is 추가ly learned to do it.
Yong Er.
I didn't expect you to be so low-key.
I'm going to find a way to get the letter.
Go!
Xuan Zun!
It's on fire!
Xuan Zun, look!
Xuan Zun!
Look!
It's gone.
It's on fire.
Xuan Zun, you're so good!
Xuan Zun!
It's on fire.
Look!
It's gone!
I can't believe it!
I'm scared!
Look at it!
It's gone!
Mr. Li!
What's wrong?
Do you want to hear my story?
I don't want to.
No!
I can't hear it!
I've seen it clearly today.
The jade tree you've planted
is not the most common jade tree in the world.
I've taken its jade tree.
It's so new
that it's still so beautiful.
It's so beautiful.
It's gone!
Madam, have some fruits.
No.
I've only eaten fruits for a month.
Don't you feel disgusting?
No.
I've eaten this for hundreds of years.
Look,
she loves it too.
So how many fruits are there on the table?
I don't know.
How many fruits are there on the table?
There's no place
where you can cook.
There's no one to eat or cook in the storage.
How could there be a kitchen?
Shen Xian is not a common person.
Madam,
you know how good Xuan is.
If you ask for a kitchen,
he will definitely agree.
Really?
Definitely.
No.
Why?
There's no reason.
If I can win the game,
can you give me a kitchen?
You?
Save me?
Okay.
Xia Zhizhi.
Didn't you see
my wife is on the table?
Yes.
I'll change the place.
Is this okay?
What do you think?
I don't think so.
I'll think about it.
Will you win the game?
I will.
I've never lost
the game between
Mr. Jin and Brother Zhang.
Why did you say that?
You're not a mortal.
No.
Of course, Mr. Xuan is the best.
Mr. Xuan.
In our world,
we can't eat or make anything.
I think
I'm so stupid.
It must be because I lack
a source of nutrition.
If there are some
sand, river, fish,
and grilled fish,
maybe there's some progress.
Then you eat.
Sand and river,
easy to find.
It's fish, river, fish,
and sand, river, fish,
even if there's food,
we have to deal with it
to make it.
You're right.
If I can
build a kitchen in this small yard
and have some food
in the sky,
then I can eat
and cook.
Then I can
give Mr. Xuan some food.
Whatever.
Mr. Xuan agreed.
You lost.
I lost.
What about my kitchen?
Mr. Xuan.
Miss Lin'er is back.
That's all for today.
You can go back.
What?
I have to see her myself.
I have to go.
It's better to
make up for all the traces of the bamboo sword.
I'll put the bamboo sword
in the Yang Sha.
It's only needed to be re-bred
for 81 days.
Then it can be restored.
It's a good thing.
Well done.
Miss Lin'er
you've been acting
so well.
You're a good girl.
Of course
it's my daughter.
I can't be wrong.
Miss Lin'er
you've been
so hard on me.
Mr. Xuan was
so angry
that he couldn't take care of you.
It's not easy
to come back
this time.
Then what should I do
to make up for it?
Then stay in the Canglei Palace
and have some rest.
You don't have to go out.
Thank you, Mr. Xuan.
Mr. Xuan
are you there?
Madam is here.
You...
Introduce yourself.
This is
the new wife of Mr. Xuan
from Li Xingyue from Ji Yun Sect.
This is Fan Jiaojiao,
Fan Xianjun.
One of the three great kings.
You should be familiar with him.
This is his daughter.
You can call her Lin'er.
She has been with Mr. Xuan
for almost 200 years.
I see.
I'm worried that Mr. Xuan
will be thirsty
and specially prepared tea.
If you have something to discuss,
I won't go in.
I'll ask the manager
to send me in.
Let him in.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Come on.
Didn't you find me?
Why didn't you talk to me?
I came to give Mr. Xuan
some tea.
Enjoy your tea.
This is the tea house
of Lin Yuan Pavilion, right?
Yes.
Why is it cold?
It's cold tea.
You came here
to see me.
What are you doing here?
I just want to see
what kind of girl
Mr. Xuan will welcome.
I didn't welcome her.
She came back
just to report to me.
This is a little matter.
Mr. Xuan doesn't need to see me.
I didn't explain.
I know.
Now, Mr. Xuan is a little awkward.
I'll go and get you some tea.
This is the surprise
you prepared for me.
Don't worry.
I have more.
Come here.
Lin,
you are a girl.
You are always
fighting with your sword.
You are so bad.
You have to learn to be gentle and virtuous.
Look.
Wait a minute.
I have to go to the doctor.
I'll get my hair done.
I'll get some more hair.
Your father is a rich man.
He can't spend much time
in his daily life.
You should help me.
If father really has money,
why don't you buy more clothes
and give it to Mr. Xuan?
It's better to let him
talk to you
in front of Mr. Xuan.
You know that.
Why don't you tell me
what Mr. Xuan is up to?
I only knew
what Mr. Xuan is up to
after I married him.
Besides,
the jade hair is so famous
that it's so beautiful.
I forgot
when I was busy.
I forgot.
You really forgot?
Or you just kept it from me?
This is a deal.
Even if you know what to do,
Ling'er.
I was in the hall today.
But I knew
why I should marry
that girl.
It's her ability
to be so filial.
I'm so sorry.
Go.
Kill him.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.