3. Goоде
2 Night
I'm not sure if I can make it.
I'll try to make it.
The 400 series is super clear and real
You can watch Lin Jiangxian
32 years of training first
Real-time use of the old household
South convinced battery
You can watch Lin Jiangxian
Find the state
Buy the move back
Buy the move
You can watch Lin Jiangxian
The warehouse is a warehouse
I've seen my wife
Is this the warehouse of the Xuanzuanzhu?
It's totally different from what I thought
It's pretty simple
This is the yard for the wife
I don't know if Xuanzuan and I are the same
I'm not sure
I don't know
Xuanzuan doesn't live together?
Xuanzuan is a good girl
She will come after she is done
But today
Isn't it the wedding day with Xuanzuan?
Don't you need to pay for the wedding?
The house is in the house
Xuanzuan is really ugly
Please understand
This is Ningyan
She is your maid
You can take the money with you
Greetings, madam
You must tell Xuanzuan
I'll wait here
Yes
Xuanzuan
The one in Jinyun Sect has already settled down
Aren't you going to have a look?
No hurry
Hua Ruyue
Ruyue is a fairy
She is a strong man
You can take her with you
I'll kill you
Hua Ruyue
Stop
Do you think it's similar?
I don't think so
Except for the appearance
I didn't find anything similar
Up next
They are coming
Madam.
Xuan Jun, he might just...
Didn't you bring the food?
I've been waiting for a day. I'm hungry.
Sorry to make you hungry.
This is the heaven of the nine realms.
Either you get the high-class person who is born to fly,
or you are born to be the god of the world.
You eat and drink all the time.
I forgot that I have to eat.
I don't eat at all.
Not at all.
I can eat a little bit if I want to.
But I can't starve to death.
It seems that
being a god is really a good thing.
At least it won't be a problem for eating and drinking.
This fruit is so magical.
I'm hungry just now.
I'm going to eat a few bites.
I'm full.
Of course. I'm the tree spirit of the wood.
This is my fruit.
Of course it's not what those wild fruits in the mortal realm can compare to.
Wood?
Is this the legendary magic tree?
I used to practice in Mount Wuji in the past.
I opened the spiritual system.
I used to take the golden flower of the two roads.
I used to practice in the night.
I used to practice in the forest for many years.
This is a miracle.
This is natural.
Madam,
I will take care of you in the future.
Just tell me what's going on.
I really have something.
What is it?
Where is Xuan Zun?
It's the hidden thunder palace.
I'll go find him.
Madam,
the Immortal Lord of the Cangtu said that you'd better wait here.
Don't run away.
You don't understand.
I must meet Xuan Zun tonight.
Why?
The painting itself says that
if you get married and have a night of solitude,
you will be very pitiful
in the future.
I won't let you go.
Let me see.
The sky and wind are too strong.
This is the two-story hall of the Immortal Lord.
Of course, you must use some skills to repair the sword.
Which direction can you go faster?
There is no way to go down here.
You won't fly and you won't be prepared.
You'll fall down like this.
Who said I wasn't prepared?
Isn't my preparation yours?
Slow down.
Be careful.
Madam,
I can only send you here.
The Immortal Lord uses his skills
to repair the sword.
No!
The sky and wind we are in is in the north.
And the Canglei Hall is in the south.
If you go to Canglei Hall,
you only need to go south.
The path is long and you have to stay at least ten days.
Ten days is ten days.
If I don't sleep on the way,
I won't be able to go back alone.
Madam, be careful.
If you don't go to the prison and get in danger,
you can also report to the name of your great-grandma's wife.
Who hit me?
Where?
Where are you?
Go!
Where?
There is a ladder.
Where is it?
Go!
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
Woman?
Where?
Madam, open your eyes.
Don't lie to me.
Open your eyes.
Can't you see?
You can't see?
We are gambling here.
gambling?
Yes, gambling.
Many years ago, there was a woman
who played a gambling with our brother.
Who was the first to open her eyes?
Who said?
What about that woman?
That woman went home and closed her eyes.
If she opened her eyes, she would come back and tell me.
How do you know that she is not crazy about you?
No way.
We have already said it.
Yes, there is a saying.
This...
What did you say?
A word.
Four...
Four horses.
I can't catch up with them.
Brother.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's horses.
Yes, it's horses.
Not important.
The most important thing is...
You.
The most annoying woman we have.
And especially,
women who don't know how to fly.
Why don't you know how to fly?
I can't fly.
But...
No, no, no.
Why do you ask so many questions?
You said you know how to fly.
I don't know.
That's good.
Brothers, stop.
Don't move.
I am the wife of the Great City Council.
Then let's go to the hospital.
What?
I shouldn't have heard so many things.
Is the woman dead?
It seems like she has an excuse.
She dares to come here again.
Before she does,
I seem to be able to smell the smell of the White wine.
What are you talking about?
Retreat.
Is anyone here?
I am here.
Master,
I have a secret message for you.
I don't know if you remember Xiao Jing Shan.
She was the highest-growing person in the Nine Heavens.
But she was caught by Master because of the black magic.
Then she was locked up in the Sky Faction.
Until three days ago, she was released.
I am worried that she will destroy the black magic again.
Brother Fu Yan,
you are the one who is worried.
Master has set the barrier on the black magic.
Even if there is a wind blowing,
Master can also find out.
I believe you.
I just think it's better to send more people to guard.
It's more appropriate.
Someone has already gone to Tian Mu Palace.
Who is the Immortal Lord?
Ning Yan and Li Qing Yue.
Who is Ning Yan?
Who is Li Qing Yue?
Ning Yan seems to be the Immortal Lord's master.
As for Li Qing Yue,
I have never heard of her.
Well,
I heard that there is a business here.
So I came to see.
Who is it?
Master!
How dare you!
Who are you?
How dare you break into the city?
What is your intention?
I have no intention.
I just want to see Master.
You can see what you want to see.
What do you want to see?
Go out and get punished.
I forgot to introduce.
This is your master.
Li Qing Yue.
This is my master.
So this is the place of the Immortal Lord.
I would have known if I had not run around.
I would have waited for you here.
You came to the Spring House Hall.
You just want to show your face to everyone.
Let everyone know your existence.
I didn't.
I just woke up.
I don't know where I am.
I just wanted to ask someone.
But I didn't even see anyone.
I accidentally went to the Spring House Hall.
I was married to three stones yesterday.
Did the Immortal Lord save me?
The injury was good.
Thanks to the medicine that Uncle Danyang gave me.
Otherwise, I wouldn't be able to climb up.
The stone forest is not at the place of the Immortal Lord's secret palace.
Why did it appear there?
I just walked down the wrong direction
according to what you said.
Those three stones are so unreasonable.
They are so aggressive.
Didn't you meet them?
Did you get hurt?
No.
That's good.
Why did you come to the secret palace?
The Immortal Lord said that
he didn't wear the clothes that others wear.
I bought you a new set of clothes.
It's a pity that you were locked up
when you came back.
I never had a chance to give you that.
I didn't wear the clothes that the mortal world knew.
I don't know what you are thinking.
Then I will give you the clothes that you like.
Then you will like this one.
Xin Xin, you said you want to eat the small autumn fruits.
So I brought some fruits
from the small autumn mountains before I came here.
The small autumn fruits
This is my favorite fruit.
I will give you one.
Little Qiu Guo?
Then these young people are here to stimulate me.
It's fun.
What young people are they?
Didn't you say you wanted to know about Little Qiu Guo?
Xuan Zun, what's wrong?
Are you here to see me?
To send me clothes and Little Qiu Guo?
Of course not.
Xuan Zun, don't you know that you'll be sleeping alone at night?
You'll be angry and angry in the future.
Oh no!
What's wrong again?
Don't get too excited.
You're already sleeping alone.
I don't care.
I'm not sleeping at night.
Tonight is the night of the wedding, okay?
Good night.
Try to end iters feelings.
I won't create further Yue Jun 2013 nenhum.
Think about it.
I'll see you about this sphere journey.
I will study with you.
I'll wait for you on the beach andittäin then.
Now!
Then there's no need to fight anymore.
Zhangsun, you're not in a hurry.
The medicine that Madam Xuan gave you can only be strong and healthy,
but it can't repair your anger.
You should take your time.
What Uncle Danyang taught me.
I'm sorry.
Qingyue, how are you doing alone?
Aren't you going to move the house?
Wait a minute.
I'm scared.
Why aren't you getting drunk in your room?
Why should I get drunk?
You have to get drunk at the wedding night.
Why bother to meddle in the wedding?
It's not good to start right away.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong again?
I have something to say.
At this time?
Yes.
When did Madam Xuan start liking me?
Is this important?
I just want to know.
We're married.
I don't need to hide it from you.
I'm right. I'm married to a family member.
I want to live and die in the Jinyun Sect.
Because I'm too weak to be proud,
I'm just a fool to die in the Jinyun Sect.
In my life,
I've always been looking for myself.
No one ever valued me.
So I can only look for myself when I'm hurt.
I'm happy that no one shared my pain.
I'm sad that no one is suffering.
I thought that's how I've been in my life.
But I didn't expect to meet Madam Xuan.
When I fell into the cliff, someone came to save me.
I was wronged.
Someone would come out to protect me.
Even if I was hurt,
someone would take me home.
I felt that I was no longer alone.
I admit that I was just a little suspicious of Madam Xuan.
But she came out to protect me once and for all.
She made me clear myself.
Madam Xuan, I really like you.
Please forgive me.
I'm sorry I didn't know you were like this.
It's all right.
Well, I'm a little tired.
I've already finished my words.
I know that Madam Xuan didn't like this.
And I don't know what to say to you.
Ophiuchus?
Are you scared?
After Valmene,
after confident death for two of them,
it only became their detention centre.
Valmene is still around the temple place.
I'm énormément grinding down a burning stone in the mountains.
All of a sudden,
this young girl has econocentacağ筿.
We need her to come down and face this world recommendation!
In this world,
the most lonely girl is you.
I can understand.
With all these,
I have to make sure sheень.
Deeraldine company should be taken over the temple.
I should bring it out.
managed office?
I met my lady.
why do you have come here?
you told me to send some food for your lady.
for her?
how can I eat all that?
she is eating on the road.
on the road?
my lady said
they have a space at De Chang Academy
so she will go back to Tianę J deuxième.
I need to go back.
fir,
just be a decoration here.
I can't live for a few more days.
This is the rule of the gods.
Please don't make it hard for me.
How can you let the bride and groom share the rules?
The lord said that after you go back, don't run around.
He will look for you.
If he doesn't come to look for me,
I can only wait.
The rule is the same.
I will wait for you.
The gods are so hard to deal with.
When you pack up your things, I will take you out.
The wedding is coming.
You have to go back to your room.
I will wait for you.
Wait for me.
Son.
If the lord suspects Mrs. Qingyue,
shouldn't we keep her by our side?
Or did the lord find out that he is mistaken?
If I get the exact answer,
I will skip this task.
To 100,000 yuan?
Why did I take this in the first place?
This is
He is him.
Yu'er will finally return to my hall.
It's the wrong way.
The evil will rise and die.
Who are you?
Are you here?
I think I'm lost.
Do you know the way?
Don't run.
What are you doing?
They are coming.
Who are they?
The demon.
The demon?
What demon?
The demon of the human.
So many.
Run.
Don't...
Don't run.
Stop.
You are here to find someone, right?
He just went over there.
Can I ask you a way?
Is it him?
Yes.
No.
You know the wrong person.
It's not me.
It's him.
No.
I'm...
Go.
The red dress is the same as the new one.
The flower is open and the red thread is embroidered with double eyes.
The thread is broken and the thread is tangled.
The flower tied the thread is the same as the golden hair.
Why are they placed in the station
and are the two神明舞場 액?
In the same person,
the people going up,
are the same as the 자주-dessert element.
I'm sorry.
Lady Xin.
Lady Xin, are you satisfied with the look?
The wedding ceremony has begun.
No matter how much you're afraid of the wedding, you can't cry.
You can't be anxious after crying.
Remember that?
Are you ready?
Not bad.
You two are good friends.
I'll go to the kitchen.
Your family is rich.
I told you that you wouldn't be in danger.
You're still a bad wife.
What else do you want?
My lord, it's time.
Go.
Go?
The bride is here.
Let's go.
Go.
One day, two days,
the wedding ceremony is over.
Two days,
Three times,
the grand-father is rich,
the grand-father is rich.
The grand-father is rich,
Go.
Xuan Xuan.
I'm sorry.