Huh?
Today, I like my anime more than any other anime's old versions.
I'm going to the airport to see my mom.
Why can't I save Meng Changqin?
You can.
It's different.
What's different?
Meng Changqin will bring you danger.
When Meng Chi came,
I had the same feeling.
From the first time you saved him,
to the moment he returned to the mansion and became the housekeeper,
you didn't know how many rumors there were.
Hua Ruoyuan,
there are so many rumors in the world.
If you are willing to take the risk,
you will definitely win the world.
Do you know why the gods come to the mortal world?
Because there are too many difficulties in the world.
The seven emotions are all over the world.
The old and the old are all dead.
Love is different.
Hope is more.
Hope is not good.
It's always hard work.
There are some things that are destined to be incomplete.
But the gods use the gods.
They can control the lives of the mortal.
If the gods really have feelings for people,
how can they bear to use the gods
to interfere with the heaven?
Even if the heaven is not needed,
the people are in danger.
The gods can be alone.
Hua Ruoyuan,
you are on the way to the heaven now.
I promise you.
Only this time,
after saving Meng Changqin,
I won't be in the mortal world anymore.
What about you?
Why me?
Are you still going to marry me?
Find the next person
who is willing to marry you.
What am I thinking?
Don't you know?
I have always been heartless to you.
I just want you to be with me
and be honest and sincere.
That's all.
Okay.
I promise you.
From now on,
I will be with you every day.
I won't leave even if you are tired.
Let's just be quiet and spend our time together.
Okay?
Let's go.
Boss,
ask Tang Xiaoli.
Okay.
You want to eat?
You were so hot in the bathroom.
You didn't even eat a bite.
Let's go to a restaurant first.
Wait for the meal when you get back.
Okay.
Thank you.
Let's go home together.
Together.
We have been in the mortal world for so many years.
How come we don't have any memories of the past?
Do you not like me?
You hate me?
Have you ever been in love with Bai Jiuci?
Clear the answer.
Tell me.
I'm sorry.
You're awake.
Come help me.
Manager.
You are supposed to live for a lifetime.
You are dangerous when you wear resultado.
I dropping in every time
is the ship could cross the past.
Someone is moving you to otherありがとう place.
at the莖この日 Park entrance on a三月日,
tonight we won't even be able to see each other again.
All right,
seems that I can only send my bamboo to
our acorns' grass.
The
Run away!
Come on.
Be careful.
Why is the Hirataro girl
all white stallion?
I remembered in the flowers incident,
we all remember their color
when we saw that Michelle's lantern.
This is called the Soul-seeing Light.
Soul?
Some people are killed and buried in the dark.
They don't dare to leave.
So their families put a Soul-seeing Light on them.
This leads them to find their way home.
This way, they can leave without worry.
So...
Man Zi.
I saw your appetite wasn't very good today.
I ate so much dinner.
It's hard to walk.
I'll carry you home.
Come on up.
Do you think those Soul-seeing Light
really have the power to lead the Soul-seeing Light to return to its original form?
The mortal soul has no power.
It's just a request for a rest.
You're not lighting the lantern.
I can also see the things.
I'm not.
Then who did you light it for?
For those who can't find their way home.
What's wrong?
I don't know.
I just feel that you're different from before.
I'm not.
I'm just a little bit different.
But...
No matter what,
you must remember who you are.
You can't lose your way, okay?
The Soul-seeing Light
A-Yuan.
Master.
Why did you come here?
I'm sorry.
You're so stupid.
Master.
It's you.
It's been three years.
How did you become like this?
Don't talk about me.
Let's talk about you.
Why did you suddenly come to see me?
I came to pick you up.
Pick me up?
I have a house in my house.
I just need a housekeeper.
You've read books and been a official.
I'm sure you can be a good person.
Don't worry.
Three bowls of mushroom soup every day.
I'll starve you to death.
Didn't you say that
life is a good thing?
Follow me.
I'll keep you alive until you're in good health.
Three bowls of mushroom soup is not enough.
I'm from the south of Zounan.
I have meat.
I have enough meat.
What about the white fish on the sky?
What about the white fish in the sea?
I have them all.
I won't go.
Why?
Master.
I have something important to do.
I didn't finish it.
You still want to see Hanlong?
Yes.
I can't go back with you.
I'll say goodbye.
See you next time.
Mo Changqin.
Can't you give up?
You've taught me a lesson.
I'll protect you as much as I can.
Go back with me.
I'll find a way to make you stay alive.
Don't make trouble outside.
Live a peaceful life.
Master.
I've been living well.
You're right.
I'm just a dead man.
I'll die for sure.
Master.
You don't know that
I've been sweating since I was born.
I've never seen it before.
I've seen the worst of the worst.
I couldn't understand the sound.
That's why I chose to be a official.
I've seen the light of God before.
I've also believed in God.
But later I found that
I couldn't control God.
God never controlled me.
I'm not used to it.
People should have faith in life.
So now I believe in myself.
Master.
Keep your position as a housekeeper.
When I kill Han Long,
I'll come to find you.
If you can't find Han Long in your whole life.
Then
I can only spend my life with you.
You can trust me.
What?
Trust me.
I'll help you kill Han Long.
No.
This is the body of the Han Long
of Wujushan.
Then
if I kill Han Long,
I can kill Han Zai.
Although Han Long is in a chaotic world,
he is still a human being.
Maybe Han Zai is not his intention.
We still have a chance to return it.
What chance?
Water has a purification power.
But it can't be combined with the river.
If he is willing to go back to the north of the water,
and stop harming people,
then he doesn't have to kill him.
What if he doesn't want to?
Then he doesn't have to be soft.
He can kill the earth.
So
Water will enter it in any given moment.
They'll know.
They'll only know
that I came fromwiąz to it.
One day
the wind will be blowing.
A storm will stop.
Wings need to be largely cleaned away.
Master.
Immortal Immortal Immortal.
Now the world is in a terrible state.
It's all because of you.
If you still have a heart of compassion and compassion,
you can return to the water immediately.
Don't harm the world.
I was in the north sea,
in the mess of the water in the west.
I was in the big palace.
I was rewarded by the Heavenly Palace.
You can come to the Three Realms with me.
You don't have to be punished.
As you said,
I can't listen to you.
Your freedom
cannot be compared to the Three Realms.
The Three Realms?
It's just a group of people.
Their lives are just like flowers falling into the night.
What's the point of being so loyal?
I thought you were a villain.
But I didn't expect you to be so insincere.
If that's the case, you deserve to die.
Master.
Yes, natürlich.
What's wrong with you?
I will kill you if you cannot come to the venue zone.
You and Siling Yi are in the same boat.
Do you know what she's going to do now?
She's going to try?
There are four major difficulties in the world.
The UK is in a trance.
It's the heaven.
She's just like the world.
What I said was right.
She wants to kill Ch Pen now.
She's not just doing the magic fear.
It's also to
How do you want me to have?
Stop her.
Cut her off język.
Ten
Kill it
Good
ARTHA一步行動
imove Holy One
She is the Divine
Even if you create kä Work in heaven
Not you
People's hatred
Heaven is where
ел Oh roasted
if Heaven is real like you are금
Then it is forbidden
master
Please clear the way
what are waiting for you
we feel an illusion
Let alone to an alien,
who is now the god
you can never resist the god
Master, I can't kill him!
Chang Qin,
you are so righteous.
You are so selfish.
You can do it!
The God of God, the God of Wei,
has killed everyone!
The God of Wei, the God of Wei,
I finally...
I did it!
The God of Wei, the God of Wei,
has killed everyone!
Mingğlou,
If you want to keep Agreed,
tell me,
is it going to stop now?
I don't use this day and night anymore.
Magistrate,
He's still in the coma, but he's fine.
That's good. That's good.
Do you know that we killed Hanlong and killed Hanzai today?
From now on, people won't be in the coma anymore.
I know.
Hanlong.
Do you think I did something wrong?
Yes.
Why?
I told you that you didn't listen to me.
You said that the mortal is not like the dragon.
The fish and birds are different.
But it's not like that.
I saw Mengchi.
He was born to be unparalleled.
But he still drew the picture of the four-color blue with the wood of the wood of the cliff.
I saw Mengqiang.
He went to the mortal with the wood of the mortal.
He knew that he killed Hanlong.
He couldn't even do anything.
Then what?
He's dead.
Do you know what you're talking about?
I know what I'm doing.
The one who's really not sober is you.
We're both in the world because of the Qingjian.
I told you that we can't use violence in the mortal world.
We can't make a mistake.
But what about you?
We can use the power to save people.
Even kill Hanlong for the mortal.
He's wrong.
It's hard to judge the right and wrong.
I only saw the result.
Hua Ruyu.
You promised me that you'd save Mengchiang once.
I'm willing to continue to be with you through the Qingjian.
But now you've lost your sight.
Now it's your turn to take the throne.
I can't forgive you anymore.
What are you doing?
I'm going back.
What are you talking about?
I'm going back to the Sky of the Nine Heavens
to make up for my personal crimes.
You're going to kill me?
I won't kill you.
But I'll seal your power
and show my power to the Sky of the Nine Heavens.
I have nothing to do with what you did.
Pei Jiu Si.
Don't you like the mortal?
Then I'll seal your spirit power for ten years
and let you spend ten years in the mortal world.
And I can also keep my word.
We're all good to you.
You can't do this to me.
I'm not a woman.
I thought
that in the mortal world,
you've been sincere to me
for a few years.
But I didn't expect
that everything was fake.
I'm cold-hearted and innocent.
You're the one who made this decision.
No wonder
you've never been willing to have a child with me.
No wonder you never dared to help me.
Did you think
I was helpless and helpless?
You need to keep your word
and keep your word.
You can't be like Bi Li.
I made the decision for you.
You made it yourself.
No.
I'm glad that you're here.
I won't hide for too long.
No.
Let go of me.
You said
you were
a beautiful woman.
You're like the cool breeze.
I promised to fall in love with you
and I'll be back in the mortal world.
But
I don't know
how to say it.
I've always been
able to understand
the taste of Di Yu Li.
I can't even
remember myself.
I've seen so many tears.
But I've been
in love with you.
I'm afraid
I'll be gone.
I'll never
need
to be gone.
Uncle Qing Yang.
You really don't know anything.
Why did the senior and the senior
go to the mortal world
and suddenly come back?
You ask me who I'm asking?
It's okay if we don't know each other.
Uncle, you're the senior of the sect.
How can you not know each other?
I'm not sure.
You're the senior of the sect.
How can you not know each other?
That's right.
I want you to say it.
Brother Zhang.
Brother Zhang, you're back.
When did you come back?
Chen Shi just returned.
Chen Shi?
So you came back
with the senior and the senior?
Do you know
why the senior and the senior
went to the mortal world together?
What was he for?
Yes.
We used to play together.
But suddenly he changed.
He was so powerful.
Even the attitude and style
were different.
Brother Zhang.
Do you think
the sect leader
gave them some spiritual pills?
I don't know either.
Well.
You're the senior of the sect.
How can you not know?
Who else is the senior of the sect?
I'm not.
You're not.
Now, the senior
is a non-known disciple.
Even the younger ones
have gone to the mortal world.
The mortal world is powerful.
The sky is broken.
The world is hard to find.
The sky is full of stars.
The world is full of wine.
The three realms are six.
The eight seas are four.
It's possible.
We can't find it.
It doesn't mean
the people in Canglei Hall can't find it either.
Longyuan is the closest disciple
of the Great City Master.
He must have a way
to find the Great City Master.
The Shizu and Great City Master
disappeared together.
They must be in the same place.
As long as they find the Great City Master,
they will find Shizu.
Brother.
When I was fighting in Tianlu Feng,
I placed the bell of the Great City Master
on Longyuan.
If Canglei Hall has any idea,
I can definitely know.
That's great.
The Great City Master is not a small thing.
We can't make any mistakes.
Yes.
I will order
the disciples of the Sect to
split into 12 groups
and look for them.
Dan Yang.
Since you have placed the bell of the Great City Master,
you can stay at the Sect.
You can monitor the movements of Canglei Hall at any time.
Yes.
Zi Yang.
You lead the disciples to split into four groups
and look for them one by one.
I will go to the back mountain to close the gate.
I will use the Great City Master to find the Shizu and Great City Master.
Please keep in mind
that the Shizu and Great City Master
are related to the fate of the Jin Yun Sect.
We must find them at all costs.
I have something to ask.
Everyone, go and do your work.
You may leave now.
Yes.
What do you want to ask?
Do you know what I want to ask?
You have a lot in your heart, right?
I want to hear your words.
In this world,
there is no Jin Yun Sect disciple Li Qingyue.
Only the Immortal Master of the Four Spiritual Cult, Yu Tian Tongshou,
can be found in the Shizu and Great City Master's secret place.
The Shizu and Great City Master
are the same person.
have been together for 300 years.
They have been fighting in Canglei Hall.
Their bodies have been destroyed.
Their spirit
has been floating in the world for 300 years.
For the past 300 years,
the Shizu has been destroyed.
They have been hiding in the world
to avoid the assassination of Canglei Hall.
Until they were taken by the Shizu and Great City Master
and the Immortal Master of the last generation.
They were sent by the Shizu and Great City Master.
They also established the Jin Yun Sect.
This is why they have been
the Immortal Master of the Four Spiritual Cult,
and they have been secretly
the Immortal Master of the Four Spiritual Cult
under the title of the Immortal Master of the last generation.
We can say that
the reason we have been sent by the Jin Yun Sect
is to help the Shizu
regain its power
and re-establish the Nine Realms.
Then,
where is Qingyue?
The common Li Qingyue
is just the disguise of the Shizu.
His body...
When he was young,
he was drowned in the water.
Zhang Sun,
in the situation you are in,
you will be confused and blind.
As long as you jump out of the game,
you will see the truth.
I am confused.
Zhang Sun,
you used the Sky Pavilion to go up the Nine Realms.
I didn't expect this.
You are wrong.
I don't care about this.
Zhao Yang is very strict.
You can't betray him.
Why do you have to
be so stubborn and hurt yourself?
I am too weak to think about it.
In this world,
I have no right or wrong.
You can have the chance
to learn from the Shizu.
It's a disaster.
But the Shizu will not
be able to bring you back.
I know.
I understand.
I'm not a flower, you're in the city
I want to cry, I still want to laugh at you
I want to say this, I'm drunk in your arms
I love you so much