National Radio. and Telvison. Administration
I don't want this regret
to be separated.
We understand and understand you.
We will
in the future.
Yes.
Since you said
you trust us,
Then share your burden
to us.
We'll carry it together.
I've read your plan.
No problem.
For the next test,
Thank you.
Gentlemen,
Why didn't you wait for me?
What are you doing? Are you going out to set up a stall?
The army and horses are still here. Let's go first.
Be prepared.
Mr. Gu.
You've become an overnight warrior.
Working overtime.
Young people like you
Why don't you hurry up?
What can I say to you?
If you fail,
I can't proceed with my overall plan.
What are you laughing at?
Stop laughing.
Look at my age.
I have to wait for your plan.
and your plan.
Look at you.
I didn't see anything, but my face is messed up.
What are you waiting for?
Go inside. Hurry.
Let me help you.
No need.
We've checked the hardware data.
We've improved
has been improved.
What's wrong?
I don't know.
Why is it stuck?
How is it?
I come to see you.
Mr. Gu.
It doesn't look good.
It's okay.
Take a break.
Eat something.
Charge.
I brought you hot pot.
Take a break.
Don't be discouraged.
At your age,
we don't have so many tasks
to complete.
In 1978,
When Bukanski visited China,
Americans
gave us a gram of moonlight.
At that time,
my teacher
and seniors.
divide this gram
into two parts.
One should be kept
and the other part for research.
So
what you see now.
Come, sit down and talk.
In 2004,
Haoyue’s mission officially started.
At that time, Qin and I
went abroad
to study abroad.
Unexpectedly,
I suffered a lot.
On the way back,
we didn't eat anything.
It's already night after we arrived in the Sky Castle.
The canteen is closed.
We brought some cold buns and pickles.
At the old warehouse,
We can talk while eating.
Qin cried that day.
He cried and said
to go back and forth.
We must do this well.
We must use our astronaut
to the moon
and retrieve our own moon.
Actually,
Tan and I
for a lifetime.
Whether it's a failure or a zero mission,
it doesn't matter.
What matters is
to make a breakthrough
from zero to one.
In the vast sky
in the vast sea.
Looking at the rocket
A rocket with five-star red flag, a spaceship
and return safely.
That's the most important thing, right?
So our generation astronauts
always follow
international aviation technology.
chasing and chasing.
But you are different.
You have to do it.
Run side by side.
I believe one day
how far China navigation has gone,
it means
how far
in this vast universe.
Don't be afraid.
Keep going.
It's up to you.
Come on, young man.
Mr. Gu.
When you were on a mission,
when you were on a mission?
What does that mean?
Staying up late
Of course.
But back then,
not as good as you.
You had self-heated hotpot.
We were cold steamed buns and pickles.
But there's one thing.
When you reach my age,
everything that happened today
whether it's contradiction or argument,
may be
to you.
Mr. Gu,
It’s not just a quarrel.
I heard that
you did it at that time.
I heard about it too.
blood splashed on the control platform.
You beat Mr. Tan to death.
Where did you get the news?
Let's eat.
That fight
No matter who wins or loses,
But
there must be a competition between each other.
For us,
this competition
is
for each other.
This competition
regardless of the result,
There are only
between each other.
will gradually become
the bond
[between each other.]
Your badge.
I care about winning or losing.
I've been competing with Ying Ziqi for so many years.
He still owes me a championship.
What champion?
Robot Competition.
He took away my three consecutive champions.
I won with my skills.
How can you win?
You rely on the rules.
You suffered because of my dog head.
Do you admit it?
Fortunately, there are rules.
Otherwise, your dog head
would have been torn into pieces by me.
Smashed into pieces?
Let me tell you.
my dog head is broken into pieces.
I can keep fighting.
I designed it for you.
You want to use a dog head?
Yes, what do you think?
We can try.
What's going on?
When I designed my dog head,
the parts were all mixed up.
It often breaks.
So I designed
broken quarantine system.
According to the design map
the design and main system
This app
can be used in the Moon Rabbit.
and transplant the broken quarantine system.
Let's try.
I sent it.
Turn off two wheels.
The damage of the simulation institution.
Yes.
I hope nothing goes wrong again.
Don't worry. It won't happen.
You two go back.
What's going on?
The broken isolation system doesn't match the hardware.
It's not properly tested.
The core control unit is burned.
What should we do?
Jia.
I don't know what happened.
He's out.
Wu fear.
Why are you here?
I'm here to see what's going on.
We've got it.
the landing plan.
Where?
Feng Kamen.
Why there?
The landscape is more flat.
And it's one of the most ancient crash pits.
Maybe there are traces of the moon.
I heard you're still stuck.
If you need,
I can try to apply to the leader
to ask everyone to help you.
We really need it.
We're trying to re-test the software.
We need manpower.
I told you.
Look.
We brought all our assets.
As the saying goes,
there are three of us.
Let's work hard together.
OK.
I’ll apply to Mr. Gu now.
Okay.
I’ll fix the parts quickly.
Solve the software problem.
Follow me.
Let's go.
The number of tests.
099.
Patrol No.2 Moon Rabbit starts.
operator Xu Qian, Ying Ziqi, Wu fear.
Next, we will conduct full force evacuation test.
Patrol No. 2 of the Moon Rabbit.
full force evacuation test.
Success.
Good. Go on.
Go on.
Next.
Under abnormal control of the institution,
Climbing obstacles.
Turn off the left middle wheel, right middle wheel drive.
Switch to four wheels of drive.
The current force is stable.
The slope is 23.6 degrees ahead.
The largest slope is 34.2 degrees.
The mobility is stable.
The power drops by 33%.
Maintain safe pass.
Six-round Power System.
Patrol No. 2 of the Moon Rabbit has arrived at the target location.
Return the patrol.
Can you
lower your motivation?
I mean
Turn off four wheels and main arm.
Turn off four wheels and main rotation.
What do you mean?
Oh no.
We've never done
we’ve never done
to reduce so much motivation at the same time.
I haven't. Can I?
I think it's okay.
Trust it.
Hello?
What's going on over there?
Any problem?
No.
Let's continue.
Turn off the left front wheel.
Right and back wheels.
Turn off the main rod.
The power is reduced.
The slope is 20.3 degrees ahead.
The largest slope is 42.7 degrees.
The mobility is stable.
The power drops 90 percent.
The patrol will re-plan the route.
Please.
Report!
The hardware of the Rabbit Car
and all functions of software
are all set.
The internal test is completed.
Awesome.
The human heart is not old and the world is cold.
I've been working hard for you all my life.
I didn't expect you
you wouldn't even give me a bite of popsicle.
It's too cruel.
Can I have a bite?
The doctor won't let you eat.
Just bear with it.
The world is cold and people are not old-fashioned.
But Qin,
I tried my best.
After all,
you are not my direct leader.
Why don't you do it now?
Right?
It's okay.
It's not that delicious.
Give me a bite.
You ungrateful people.
You're torturing an old man.
How can you be lonely?
We have so many people here to see you.
are your children.
As long as you are healthy,
I'll buy
whatever you want.
No one can get a share.
I think it's okay.
I think you don't need to.
You have to think like this.
Consider it an investment, right?
Among us,
among us.
When you get old,
we can invite you back.
When we have children,
we'll take you as our godfather.
I agree.
I agree too.
Why do you agree
Why do you agree?
Sister Nan has to agree, right?
Of course.
Do you want a beating?
Don't let me catch you.
I'll be discharged tomorrow.
Don't pick me up.
Do you hear me?
Got it, Mr. Tan. OK, got it.
Hello?
Xu Yun?
Hello, Liu.
Long time no see.
I have good news for you.
No. 2 Moon Rabbit.
The test is completed.
We...
going to the moon again.
See who is back.
You’re back, Mr. Qin.
Mr. Qin.
Mr. Qin is back.
Hurry up.
You're all here.
Welcome home.
You're here too.
Let me help you.
It's okay to cook and clean the house Let's go
Come on. Change your shoes.
No.
I can do it myself.
Come on.
Let me help you.
Let me tell you.
I'm in charge of
in the future.
We live alone anyway.
It's not hard
It's not hard to work together.
Come on, get up.
No, it's too troublesome.
No, I can do it myself.
Stop talking.
Look at you.
I introduced an old classmate to you.
to take care of each other.
Don't dawdle.
Now,
I found a companion.
You have no choice.
You can only count on me.
You're here too.
Of course.
Why do I seriously suspect
there are no old classmates.
What you said
my neck is getting cold.
All right, stop forcing yourself.
Director Cao
is good to you and cares about you.
It's hard to say if you're good to me.
You're everywhere. Don't get involved.
You know what?
A person like you
who worked hard
for China's aviation career.
Mr. Cao represents the country
represents the astronaut center.
More importantly, it represents
for you.
Ya,
I have no choice.
Coffee is here, Mr. Tan.
Thank you.
You can't drink coffee
It stimulates the heart.
Pour him some hot water.
Gu, drink it.
Okay.
Look how obedient I am.
Egg, wake up the wine.
The wine...
No I don't drink
Give it to the kids, OK?
The wine is not here.
Wine?
The wine is not...
Gu Lifeng.
You can’t take photos like this.
Did you steal my wine?
You stole my wine while I was hospitalized.
I didn't steal your wine.
That's called strategic transfer.
I guessed it right.
You'll get back to work soon.
Don't drink.
I can't drink. I'll set it up.
Let me see.
Isn't it fun?
No.
What if you can't
drink it secretly?
That's right. Gu is right.
You...
It's impossible for you to hold it in.
Yes.
Can he bear it?
I'm telling you, I know what I'm doing.
If I lose one tael, you'll pay me one jin.
I promise you.
I'll quit drinking from now on.
When Mr. Cao says you can drink,
when Mr. Cao says you can drink.
Listen to Lord Cao. Let me speak.
Then don't ever drink it.
That won't do. You'll suffocate.
We have to drink.
Where are we from?
Mr. Qin.
These are our gratitude.
We know you used to
at the observatory before.
This thing
is our promise.
Look how much they care about you.
What?
You can't eat grapes, right?
Right.
I see.
I have something
to announce.
Next,
Haoyue No.5.
We’ll enter the activity surveillance soon.
In two days,
will launch
So,
the center has decided
to get used to it in advance.
and give Haoyue a supporting test
to gain some experience.
Activity test.
Drive a big car.
Yes.
Haoyue will pass through the black zone on the 5th.
The black zone.
We can't contact without signal.
We can use this test
to test
our new system and high-spiritual control equipment
to support the effect of Haoyue’s mission.
to complete the returning device and enter the atmosphere level for the first time.
[The remote and external test of the black barrier.]
[Global measuring Mission]
Wu fear.
Ziqi.
You two are in charge of surveying and monitoring.
Cabbage wrap.
Go to Xi’an with Qu.
Jia Jia and Ming
will wait for you there.
Okay.
This mission
is mainly for you young people.
Don't fail me.
Don't worry.
Never.
One more thing.
Haoyue No.4.
The list of the person in charge of flight control is out.
Jiajia, congratulations.
I hope you can take the responsibility.
I'll do my best.
Come on.
It’s up to you.
Congratulations, Jia.
Thank you.
Go ahead. I'll cook.
What are you busy with?
All right.
It's endless. Arrange it quickly.
I'm talking about business.
Can't we talk on the dinner table?
Okay, I'll get it ready for you.
Wait. Don't worry.
Let's go. Don't worry.
Let's go cook.
What are you shooting
Xiu
Look at you
You're here too
The shooting site is almost done
so I came here.
Well,
How is Qin?
The operation went well.
He's still recovering.
He was anxious to return to his post.
and finally let him stay in Beijing.
He will get better.
Yes.
I trust him.
Qin is a warrior.
OK.
Keep it up.
By the way,
I have a situation.
Let's have a meeting.
Let's have a meeting together.
First of all,
Thank you for your hard journey.
Secondly,
we just received a message
during our launch,
during the launch.
So our recent signal
will be disturbed.
Now,
we need to rebuild another observation point.
Send a car up.
and drive to the mountain.
Xiuxiu let's go
Leave it to us
You're prepared.
But
The mountain is high and windy.
the conditions of flying control will be harder.
So, don't be so anxious.
I'll complete the mission.
Okay.
I'll report to Gu later.
The rest of our comrades
according to the previous arrangement.
And the sun is setting soon.
There will be a storm later.
So, get ready in advance.
Look.
The legendary aerial fast food
I didn't expect there are so many kinds of species.
I'm almost done with the equipment.
Let's pack up and eat.
Okay.
Eat something.
Take a break.
and get up at night.
I think in this world,
in this world.
Look at this view.
I heard there were a lot of meteorites here.
Maybe one of your stones
came from a planet hundreds of millions years ago.
who travelled tens of thousands of light years to Earth.
What a pity.
The view is nice.
Something's wrong with him.
Exactly.
How about I send a message to Jia?
If you want to send it to Jia,
I'll send it to Sister Nan.
I'll send it when I get back to the base.
Stop talking then.
Let's do it together.
Yan.
Jia.
Sister Yan.
Qu, kimbap.
Long time no see.
I missed you so much.
Me too.
Fire! Are you done with your work?
Mr. Zhang.
How are you?
Are you tired?
You've lost weight.
No.
It's not easy for you either.
Did the landing plan torture you?
Not bad.
Song.
It's my first time sitting at 01.
It's a souvenir.
Yes.
Come on.
Come on!
Wake up.
It's mission time.
What's wrong?
My head hurts.
It's windy outside.
Don't affect the activity control.
Do the pre-launch check first.
Are you sure?
I'm fine.
Come on.
Take your temperature first.
37.5.
You have a fever.
I think it's a bit high-landed.
You might have pulmonary edema.
Your contact will take you down.
We're in double hips.
You have to go down too.
Look outside.
The road is hard.
How much time is it?
Besides,
If we go down now,
the mission will be delayed.
Our observation point is meaningless.
I'm not as weak as you think.
I can hold on.
I have to report it.
Procedure?
Calling Activity Control 1.
This is No. 1.
I'm looking for Xiu.
Okay
Xiu, it's for you.
Me?
This is number one, please speak.
Xiu.
Ying Ziqi has a fever.
High Plateau reaction.
What?
It was fine just now.
How did it burn?
There's an oxygen tank in that car.
Suck the oxygen quickly.
Can you hold on? How much is it now?
A low fever.
Probably.
It should be fine.
Xiu.
How long will it take to send someone up here?
The sandstorm has just risen.
The car can't get up.
The visibility is too low.
How about this?
Wait a minute.
I'll report to Gu.
Xiu, why don't you send...
Xiu.
I'm fine. I can hold on.
Okay, how about this?
Tell me
if anything happens.
And you two
take care of each other, okay?
Don't worry. It won't affect the mission.
Okay.
I said I'm fine.
Look at you.
You failed at the critical moment.
Take the medicine.
I'm just too healthy
I need too much oxygen.
Unlike you.
Come on.
A white chicken.
Are you really okay?
I'm fine.
I can do it.
Yes.
Attention, everyone.
This is Xi'an.
Prepare to launch in 60 seconds.
Minus 60 seconds. Ready.
Report to all activity monitoring numbers.
Activity detector 1.
The equipment parameter is normal.
Activity detector number two.
Activity detector number three.
All equipment parameters are normal.
Activity detector number four.
The equipment parameter is normal.
Activity detector 1.
The signal is normal.
Activity detector number two.
Activity detector number three.
The signal is normal.
Activity detector number four.
Ten seconds countdown.
Ten.
Nine.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Light the fire.
Take off.
Activity monitor 1.
The monitoring is normal.
Activity monitor No. 2.
Remote is normal.
Activity monitor number three.
The monitoring is normal.
Remote signal is normal.
Rocket pose is normal.
Arrow separation.
Satellites enter the designated track.
Fire!
Attention, everyone.
Two hours.
Check the data.
The next monitoring task is still a while.
Take a break.
Go.
Hurry up.
Got it.
Mr. Wu.
Drink more hot water.
Let's do it again.
It seems to be windy.
It should be windy.
Why is it suddenly windy?
Return it.
38.9 degrees.
What happened?
Lie down and take a rest.
Lie here, bro.
Attention, everyone.
This is Xi'an.
Check track data.
Real-time monitoring.
Sister Nan.
Are you done?
Can we rest now?
It's time to rest.
Looks like he's fine.
We'll continue tomorrow.
These days,
these two kids have changed a lot.
Yeah.
They've been doing well lately.
They have our style back then.
No, we have to go down.
I can do it.
[This drama has been fictified]
[Ying Deqian, He Yun]
Chen Bing.
Zhao Qiang Jun.
Wu Jianguo.
Bai.
Li Jiaming, Liu Zhenguo, Wang Jiamao, Liu Tiancheng Liu, Lan, Zhao Shufeng, Bai Yuqin, An Chengzhi.
Wang Yiqi, Feng Shuai, Tang Zixuan, Fu Jing Yun, Zheng Lin, Qin Dehang, Zhang Haoming.
Producer team.
Life Producer Zhao Xumuang
Lighting Team.
Lighter.
Recorder.
paint artist.
Producer.
The dressing team.
Data Management, Li Peiyuan, Dong Zhenzhong.
Legal team.
equipment support.
Beijing Liu Shun Glorious Film and Media Co., Ltd.
Beijing Development Video and Culture Co., Ltd.
A negative player.
Visual effects production company.
Beijing Free Circulation Digital Technology Co., Ltd.
TV producer Zhang Zheng.
Beijing Magic Power Culture Co., Ltd.
Passenger.
A composer.
Dubbing production team.
Bianjiang Studio.
Music production team.
Theme song, Mu Xing.
Singing.
Lyrics.
Poster Design Team.
Ming, thank you.
Tianjin Industrial Development Co., Ltd.
Tianjin Co., Ltd.
The PR Department of Nankai District Committee of Tianjin
The PR Department of Jinghai District Committee of Tianjin,
Elite Martial Arts, Chinese Wulin Park.
[The Fantastic Scene Area of Suizhou]
Instructor unit.
National Aeronautics Bureau News Centre
Zhengzhou New Power Film Co., Ltd.
New Power Film Co., Ltd.