(Episode 13)
Didn't you lower your value to sign a
contract with me in order to help me?
That's why all you need to do
is gratefully accept my help.
Only take what I give you.
I have another schedule,
so I should go now.
Did you come to...
love another person again?
Is there something that you want again?
Then you'd do anything else again.
What is it you're trying to say?
What I'm trying to say is...
to get what you want and
to do what you want,
you'd even abandon your own child...
Ms. Yoo Ji-na...
Who said he's my son?
Then shall I reveal it?
Go ahead.
Go ahead and reveal it all you want.
That will be the end for you, too, Jung
Hae-dang, I mean, my imitator Yoo G-na.
If I become someone despicable to the public,
then what good will that do for you?
If the public found out that I abandoned
my child in order to live well on my own,
they won't even want to think of my face.
They won't even want to
think of me, so what
makes you think they'll
want to see my imitator?
That means your worth on stage
will fall, fall, and fall.
Even though the entire world would want
to expose my past, you can't do it.
Rather, you'd have to do your best to
cover it up in order for you to live.
That's the fate of Yoo Ji-na's
imitator singer Yoo G-na.
That's the fate you must live as my shadow.
Welcome.
I won't be able to appear on TV.
Is that so?
I practiced so hard.
It's fine. You'll have
another chance next time.
Whatever I do, I don't think I'll
ever be able to break away from it.
I don't think I'll be able to change.
Is that why you look like
it's the end of the world?
- You're disappointed, huh?
- I told you to come to me at times like this.
You're very disappointed, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
If it worked out perfectly in one shot,
then anyone can go on TV, even me.
Please comfort Hae-dang a lot.
Did you come all the way
just to tell me this?
I'm sure Hae-dang is upset,
too, but when I thought
about how you'd be disappointed,
I became heartbroken.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
I'll do everything I can to
get her another opportunity.
Okay.
You should lift up your
head and look at me.
I might end as just a nightclub singer.
So what?
Will you really be by my side then?
Should we leave to the countryside?
I can teach piano to the kids
in the neighborhood, and when
the sun falls, we can hold hands
and walk along the beach.
How will we able to survive off of that?
We'll survive if we have money. If we
don't have it, we can just starve.
My benefactor left me enough
money to live off of.
We can get an oven that makes bread.
The neighborhood kids will learn piano
because they want to eat the bread.
The kids who are dressed up nicely
and have their hairs tied up neatly
by their mothers will be giggling
as they run around the piano.
Just thinking about it
makes me feel at peace.
When it's sunset, we could sit side by side
in the yard and drink aromatic coffee...
while we talk about our
tired, disappointing youth.
Will such a day really come?
All you have to do is stay by my side.
You'll still be really young then.
I'm going to live this
lifetime just for you.
Eat it with rice, too.
What are you doing here?
Your father told me to
eat ramen before I go.
Welcome, my daughter.
It's okay. It's okay.
You came here on purpose because you
thought my dad would be disappointed?
It's not even good news anyways.
I thought you'd have a hard
time telling him yourself.
What are you looking at?
It is really nice to have an agency.
Why would you bring that up now?
If you're grateful, just say so.
Or you can just admit you were touched.
If you hadn't said that, I
would've been really touched.
Go inside.
You have a warm heart.
- I'm not nice to just anyone.
- Then why are you being nice to me?
Stop fishing for compliments.
Thank you.
Don't think about anything and just get a
good rest. I'll take care of everything.
You.
Come out.
I feel apologetic towards you,
since the rookie celebrity
you're making such an effort
on can't go on TV anymore.
Instead, should I buy you a drink
at a place with a nice atmosphere?
- What?
- This is all your fault.
This is too low.
- She dared come to argue with me.
- "Dared?"
You ruined Jung Hae-dang's manners.
So you're blaming me?
Do you remember what you did to me in
your office in order to lift her spirits?
You should take out your anger on me. Why
would you block the future of a weak person?
No matter how much you try to lift
her spirits, in the entertainment
world, she'll have to crawl
on the floor in front of me.
"Crawl on the floor?"
If you truly care for her, don't
side with her in front of me.
Every time you offend me, I'll
stomp on her just for fun.
"For fun?"
Since you're showing your true
colors, you're really worth seeing.
What is it you want from me?
What do you want from me?
Is this what you want?
Fine. If you really want it
that much, I'll just do it.
You're really cruel.
How could you do this to
the woman who likes you?
What are you two doing in my yard?
She was begging earnestly
to me, but since she
didn't get things done her way, she stomped
on my weak rookie celebrity I've worked so
hard on like she was nothing but a bug.
- It's a misunderstanding.
- What?
The PD in charge cut her off
because she didn't make the
auditions, but Hyun-joon
misunderstood it as my fault.
Do you really want to die in my hands?
Go inside.
Since you bring out your true colors,
not only are you worth seeing, but
you're also a very frightening woman.
Oh, my head hurts. I won't be
able to eat dinner tonight.
Didn't you hear me tell you to go inside?
Did the PD really cut her off?
That rascal may be a mess, but he's not
someone to misjudge the situation.
You must have more trust in your
son that I thought you had.
The only thing I don't like
is the fact that he hates
me and how he's acting
arrogantly to annoy me.
He's my son, so why wouldn't
I know what he's like?
According to Park Hyun-joon,
is good at judging
the situation, these are my true colors.
How do you feel seeing them?
Were you disappointed?
Why did you block the success
of that rookie singer?
Was it a way of protesting because
Hyun-joon won't give you the time of day?
Do you want to stoop that
low to get his attention?
I don't want...
the world to see her.
Why not?
Because she'll make them think of my youth.
Because they'll realize I'm getting old.
The love from the public
is like a passing breeze.
How can you still think of
grabbing something so ephemeral?
Do you know what I threw away...
to grab something so ephemeral?
I did it because I was afraid I would
lose the love from the public.
I even broke the promise
of going back to get him.
To get who?
I can't let the public realize I'm getting
old just because of a mere imitator singer.
Don't help the singer
Ji-na is trying to block.
- What?
- Don't let her appear on TV.
Look here, Mr. Park Sung-hwan.
Do you think that makes sense?
If you're my son, just listen to me once!
I told you I don't think
of you as my father!
Now do you realize what kind
of horrible woman she is?
Even though I do, it's too late.
In any situation, I'm on her side.
In any situation?
So don't use her to pull
any funny tricks on me.
She was asking for it when she
stomped on an innocent person!
Now I realize...
that you two suit each other.
I wondered why you, someone who
will bleed blue blood when
pricked by a needle, would be
so hung up over one woman.
You two are very alike.
That must be why you love her.
Yes. That's why I love her. Are you happy?
She's not worth your love.
I don't love a woman in
order to respect her.
There are plenty of woman
in this world to respect.
Yet why do I love her?
Because she won't be
able to live without me.
Because something might happen
to her if I leave her alone.
Because my heart breaks.
Because she haunts me!
Because I can't hate her no
matter how much I try to!
How can you say that in front of me
when I'm heartbroken over dead mom?
I'm sorry, but that's the truth.
Find out the boy in this photo.
It's not easy to find
out what happened after
she ran away in the middle of the night.
I can't even found out
where she had run away to.
So how can I find out
what happened after that?
- That's why I'm asking you.
- I'm sorry.
Do whatever you need to in order
to find out about this boy.
Find out what happened to him after
that, where he is right now, and
what he's doing at the moment, even
if you have to pour money into it.
Yes, sir.
(The woman in the picture is Yoo Ji-na...
Who is the little boy with her?)
What did you do with my ring?
Are you keeping it safely?
I need to sell it to
supplement for the deficit.
We lost money because of
Bong-sun's dentist treatment.
- Leave the car at home tomorrow.
- The car?
I need to learn how to drive. My
driver's license would be a waste.
You're at an age where people stop
driving, so why would you do that?
Because I want to go for a
drive whenever I feel stuffy.
If you get into an accident, the
insurance will rise. That's all money.
Hey, do Bong-sun and I look like
money-eating machines to you?
I'm done eating.
Is there anyone who will
teach you to drive?
Of course. There's your father-in-law.
Even couples get into a fight when
they're teaching how to drive.
My friend almost got a divorce because she
learned how to drive from her husband.
That's because she's a fool.
Goodness.
Why are you driving like this? The car
isn't even budging. Step on it, will you?
- Don't talk to me.
- The sun is going to set.
Fine. I'll speed it up.
Stop! Stop! Stop!
How can you speed up at a red light?
Why are you yelling at me?
It's red! Can't you see the red light?
My feet are shaking right now.
If you yell at me, I might
crash into something.
Gosh.
The signal changed. Go.
Can't you hear the cars
behind you are honking?
Go.
That damn fool! Why does he keep
following me and honking at me?
Handle. Handle. Handle.
There's nothing in front of you,
so why are you moving to the side?
Didn't you see that car?
Jung Kang-sik, don't you dare yell at me!
Am I your wife? Why are you yelling at me?
Look to the front! Brake! Brake!
I've never seen someone with such
awful motor nerves like you.
This won't do. Just take a taxi.
I don't have the money to take a taxi.
Then just walk.
Look at the other woman. Can't
you see how well they drive?
Stop nagging and just teach me the way.
Where do I go? Left or right?
Left or right?
Just get out. I'll drive us home.
Park over there.
- Turn signals!
- Turn signals?
What's this? What's this?
How can you let go of the steering wheel?
- Calm down. Calm down.
- Okay. Calm down.
- Turn signals.
Now. Now.
No, it's too late!
You can't even switch lanes?
I can't do it with you scolding me!
- Now. Now.
- Now? Now?
- Yes. Hurry up and go in.
- I'll do it!
Today is my funeral day!
Park! Park! Park!
Brake!
Get out!
Hurry up and get out!
I said get out!
How dare you drop the honorifics!
Do you think I can keep the honorifics
with you in this situation?
Excuse me. You didn't do anything
to deserve being mad at me.
Is there anyone who knew how to
drive ever since they were born?
If I'm scared, but you yell at me,
do you think I'll be able to drive?
You should thank me for
risking my life to teach you
to drive, so why are you
yelling at me, Mrs. Baek?
Goodness. See one, and
you've seen them all.
You're a man with zero tolerance.
What? "Tolerance?"
You treat me like I'm stupid
just because I can't drive.
All you need to do is grab
the steering wheel and
put your feet on and take
your feet off the pedal.
It's much easier than riding a bicycle,
so why can't you do it, Mrs. Baek?
Goodness! You must get
an award for not knowing
how to do anything but drive, Mr. Jung!
How dare you!
I know the real you now. You conned us into
thinking you were a generous man!
It's just a show!
Goodness! I'm speechless!
Are you done talking?
Are you my husband? How
dare you yell at me!
Goodness. You're all bark and no bite.
You're good at talking, so why
are you so bad at driving?
Hey!
She'll stomp on her just for fun?
Why, that woman...
- I have good news.
- Good news?
- A PD of another program contacted me.
- Really? What program?
It's called "Star King of the King."
It's a show where people with
special talent go out on.
What do I do on the show?
You'll imitate the singing of Yoo Ji-na.
It's a show where all you have to do
is amuse people with your talent.
You need to do whatever you can
to show yourself to the world.
- I'll do it.
- Really?
It's not a music show, but I'm not in
the position to be picky right now.
I like variety shows more.
I'm really good on stage, you know?
I'll do whatever I can to amuse them.
You can't make those comments
you make in a nightclub.
- Do you think I'm stupid?
- As expected, you're brave.
You're pretty good at what you do. How
did you manage to get this chance?
The PD from the other
show felt bad about your
cancellation, so he suggested
you to another PD.
Really? I'm so grateful.
So all your hard work
wasn't useless, after all.
You're right. The entertainment
world is just another neighborhood.
Of course. If you work
hard, there will be a way.
Okay! Let's go!
- Stop it.
- How can I stop it?
Who is in charge of that program? There
should be someone higher-up than the PD.
What are you trying to do?
Stop it. Stop it. Stop it!
You weren't like this before.
What's happening to you?
Stop being arrogant and just do as I say.
Don't you understand what I said?
The time has come for me to quit.
What are you so uneasy and doubtful that
you're going crazy over
a mere imitator singer?
I don't want her to be a part of my life.
I have a bad feeling that she'll
be in every alley I go to.
I hope you can keep your dignity as a
senior in the entertainment industry.
I don't want to, so stop it.
Whether you meet the PD, one in charge,
or the entertainment director, stop it.
Just stop it!
Can you call my parents every afternoon?
- I didn't even do it during our newlywed phase.
- I just
thought they would feel reassured
if they heard your voice.
I don't have time for that.
(Yoo-jin)
Lunch was delicious today.
While we ate together, it
felt like all the years
had vanished and we were
back in the States.
Call me. I'll be waiting.
(The message will be deleted)
Why are you staggering? You're young, but
you don't have any strength in your legs.
Why? Is something wrong?
Of course not. It's nothing.
Hyun-sung ate lunch with Yoo-jun.
Did you hear that from Yoon-hee?
He talks on the phone with
Yoo-jin once per day.
Come and eat dinner.
- Who did you eat lunch with?
- The employees.
Honey. Park Hyun-sung.
Never mind.
- Why do you need your phone during dinner?
- I might get an urgent call.
I do all the hard work and
somebody gets all the credit.
What kind of hard work did you do?
Please don't let that woman meet Hyun-sung.
How can I do that?
Just tell her I'm pregnant.
You want me to lie?
Make up any excuse you can so she won't
get any funny ideas about Hyun-sung.
- What if you get caught?
- I'll just say I got a miscarriage then.
Then how about you lie
directly to grandmother?
Then she'd drag me to the
hospital to confirm it at once.
She was the first one who
lied to Yoo-jin that
you and Hyun-sung were
using separate rooms.
- What did you say?
- She's using any means to get Yoo-jin.
How can she do that when
I'm alive and well?
Hwangsung Group's second
daughter-in-law was
kicked out even though
she bore two children.
Do you think grandmother cares about you?
She'll make Hyun-sung get married
like he was never married at all.
Yoon-hee, please help me.
You're the only who can.
- Is that so?
- Of course.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Then how dare you cause a rift
between Hyun-joon and his father!
Did you hear?
How much did you hear?
I heard that you made
Hyun-joon and his father
to be on irreversible terms.
Is that not true?
Yet, you dare tell me I'm the
only one who can help you?
You did well.
Park Hyun-sung will inherit the company,
and Jo Yoo-jin will become his wife.
You've made an effort with
that shallow brain of yours
to do all the work and give
the credit to someone else.
This is why one's origin is so important.
How can you be so fearless?
No need to get up. Just
do what you were doing.
- Hello.
- You come here often.
Mrs. Sung wanted to arrange flowers.
You don't need to answer her.
What do you want to eat for dinner?
She can make everything. Tell he what you
want, and let's have a delicious dinner.
Would boiled sea bream in
soy sauce be possible?
Of course! I spent so much money to make
her learn cooking from all kinds of chefs.
What are you just standing there for?
Boil it sweetly.
Foods boiled in soy sauce must taste sweet.
I'll go change and come back.
When she first came to this house, she
couldn't even get the seasoning right.
People who eat the food can cook it.
But what could she have
eaten from her home?
Just let them be. She can clean it.
I'm going to put this in my room.
Can we talk?
Why do you keep showing up
at our house like this?
Mrs. Sung invites me.
Please refrain from doing so. It's not
polite of you to keep coming here.
If we're talking about
politeness here, you're the one
who got between Hyun-sung and me, Ms.
Ko Na-kyung.
Between Hyun-sung and you?
Na-kyung, how much do you
know about Hyun-sung?
I'm his lawful wife.
I know. That's why I'm going easy on you.
How dare you drop the honorifics.
The decision is up to Hyun-sung.
I should go. Mrs. Sung
will be looking for me.
I don't like her, so make sure she
can't come to our house anymore.
That's not something I can do.
- Are you secretly liking this?
- What?
Are you innocent then?
You're not only shallow. You're
presumptuous, too, aren't you?
Why would you mention innocence here?
Why would you eat lunch with her?
Why would you lie?
Are you digging through my phone now?
Were you happy meeting up with her?
So are you going to meet her again?
Don't you know I'm doing this
because I'm indebted to her?
She trusted me but got struck
by a bolt out of the blue.
- Don't you know my breakup with her was like ripping off flesh?
- Ripping off flesh?
If you love her so much, you should've ran
away with her. Why did you marry me then?
Do you think my father and grandmother are
the same people as they were back then?
They teamed up to make my
mom into a mental patient,
and it seemed like they were after me, too.
I married you because I was
naive and wanted to survive.
Then that should be done with.
What are you doing now?
You were the one who married me
after signing a contract that
you would only accept three
million dollars if we divorced.
Do you think that's a marriage?
It's a deal.
I'm sorry, but even when I look at your
eyes now, I have terrified thoughts.
Do you still have nothing to say to me?
What do you want to hear from me?
I told Hyun-sung about the contract.
Did he tell you that?
Why did you tell hm that?
Isn't it obvious? Because I detest you.
You scared me. I thought
you were Ko Na-kyung.
- How long will you stay here?-
Why are you curious about that?
- Don't you have any pride?
- Pride?
Are you staying here because Hyun-joon
won't look at you otherwise?
That's not something for
you to be so angry about.
Why not?
If you want to get angry, get angry at Park
Hyun-joon and move aside, so I can leave.
Why are you sticking around him
when you know he hates you?
You know he hates me, so why are you
afraid of me sticking around him?
The one with the least pride in
this family is you, Hong Yoon-hee.
- What?
- Both Mrs. Sung Kyung-ja and Ko Na-kyung have their points and opinions.
Yet, you're hiding behind Mrs. Sung and
acting like a foolish woman without a point.
A foolish woman?
Do you think I'm the one Park
Hyun-joon is crazy about?
What do you mean?
You're barking up the wrong tree.
If you have nothing to say, all you
do is nitpick people's origins.
Are we in North Korea? Why do you
keep nitpicking people's origin?
Move.
Who exactly are you crazy about?
- What are you talking about?
- Yoo Ji-na told me I'm barking up the wrong tree.
Do you believe the things she say?
So who is it, if it's not Yoo Ji-na?
Do you think it works if I'm
the only one crazy about her?
Don't worry, and do what you always do.
So you're admitting you're
crazy about someone, right?
Who is she? Should I find her?
Don't think of doing something stupid.
You said your audition
had gone well last time.
Why did your appearance
suddenly get canceled?
Yoo Ji-na said she would only appear
on the show if I didn't come out.
Why would she do that?
Hae-soo told me you two
had been close until
you two had become distant
about one year ago.
Did something happen between you two?
You don't need to know that.
(Popular singer Yoo Ji-na dating
and living with wealthy CEO)
You abandoned your child and
went out into the world,
yet you block the success of a weak person?
I got better than last time, didn't I?
You practiced a lot.
I practiced so much to
get complimented by you.
Good job. Let's call it a day.
You didn't forget about our
lunch date today, right?
- Should I turn on music for you?
- You can do whatever you want.
- Can I ask you something, madam?
- "Madam?" I don't like that.
- Then how should I address you?
- I'm not sure.
- I can't call you Ji-na when you're my mom's age.
- That's true.
Still, I don't like madam.
- Why not?
- It's not a mannerly way to address a single woman.
How did you live before you debuted?
Why do you ask?
Because I'm curious.
I guess you have a right to be.
No one is born a star.
I'll tell you later when I have the chance.
We're almost here. We'll
be getting out soon.
All you have to do is
walk straight forward.
Let me hold onto your elbow.
Like this?
It's not bad walking like this.
Won't people stare at you if you come to
places like this with someone like me?
Who cares if they stare? Why
would you worry about that?
I was worried you would be uncomfortable,
but I worried for nothing.
Why don't you appear on talk shows?
In order to give off a mysterious image.
Nothing good comes from top singers revealing
their personal life to the public.
That's why there isn't
any information about
the days before you
debuted, so I'm curious.
I told you that I would tell you later.
- Do I not deserve to be curious?
- That's not what I meant.
All I can do is listen to what
someone else tells me anyways.
It's not just you. It's because I
haven't told anyone that story yet.
- Do you have a real name?
- Real name?
When I think about your age, I don't
think Ji-na seems like your real name.
It's not my real name.
- Then what is it?
- I don't want to tell you.
Come on. A name isn't that big of a secret.
It's dowdy and ridiculous. That's
why I don't want to tell you.
How do you expect to get close to me if
you don't even tell me your real name?
Of course, I really like you.
Can you feel that I like you?
Yes, I do.
An amazing woman like you bought
clothes for a blind guy like me.
That's why it made me wonder if you have
any of your family members are blind, too.
Or else, you wouldn't have a reason
to be nice to someone like me.
That's just what I felt.
Do you have any new information?
The name of the little boy in
the photo is Lee Kyung-soo.
Lee Kyung-soo?
The townspeople say that they saw the
little boy after Yoo Ji-na came back.
Then where had she been before then?
She had gone to the city to look for work.
Then she showed up in her hometown
when the boy appeared as well?
Yes.
There's something I found
out from contacting all
the people Yoo Ji-na, I
mean Kim Hae-jung knows.
What is it?
She has a friend who is a nurse
who works in another city.
Yoo Ji-na had gone to her hospital with
the boy who had gotten into an accident.
Then something had
happened to the boy then?
The accident didn't end his
life, but he lost his vision.
I'll let you know as soon as I
find out something new about her.
How could she do that to a blind child...?
A blind child...
What are you looking at and not eating?
I don't have an appetite tonight.
I'll excuse myself first.
Why? The hot pot is delicious.
Eat a lot.
- Did something happen at work?
- Not something he would get upset over.
Did something offensive
happen outside of work?
I'm sorry, but I want to drink alone.
Are you telling me to leave?
I need to think about something.
All right then. I'll go.
It seemed like you didn't eat much during
dinner, so I prepared cheese for you.
I'm going to go to the vacation
home and rest for a few days.
Let Hyun-sung know.
The vacation home? Is there
a problem with Yoo Ji-na?
I'll pack your things for you.
I'm sure of it. There is definitely
a problem between those two.
Is that so?
If Yoo Ji-na leaves our house,
you'll forgive me, won't you?
What if that wicked woman has
completely fallen for Hyun-joon?
If father turns his back to her,
Hyun-joon won't ever look at her again.
I really hope I won't
have to see her anymore.
I'll have good news for you soon.
- If you don't?
- If I don't, I'll have to add to it.
- Add to it?
- I'll find out what's wrong.
Then I'll add to it to make
him disgusted with her.
Even after you suffered that much, you still
dare think about being smart with us?
I'm busy, so why are you
telling me to come all
the way here? You should
just tell me in Seoul.
Is there something on my face?
- Retire immediately.
- What?
Just retire and live quietly by my side.
- Why are you laughing?
- Because it's funny. Do you think you're making any sense?
- Just listen to me.
- Why would I listen to you, out of all people?
How can you be that way?
I need to go before traffic hits.
Next time, if you don't have a good reason,
don't tell me to come out this far.
Do you think it's time for you to
bet your all to get Hyun-joon?
Don't think of messing with him.
- What?
- I may despise him, but he's still my son.
- What do you mean?
- I mean you don't deserve to be near him.
What's this? Am I supposed to say
this is a tear-jerking moment?
Are you worrying about
your son's life right now?
Didn't you say so yourself that he's
the only humane one in my family?
How dare you?
How dare I?
I'm the right one for you.
Since I'm full of sins, I'll
think of repaying for them.
Retire and stay quietly by my side.
I'm sorry.
I didn't have much interest
in you from the beginning.
What?
Do you really want a taste
of this cruel world?
Please come to your senses.
Please come to your senses!
Must you really show your face on TV?
Give it up...
for my sake.
- Why are you so scared of me?
- I'm not scared of you. I'm just annoyed.
I need to practice, so get out.
What will you benefit from infuriating me?
How about we just get moderately close?
We can go back to the days
we first met each other.
"Moderately?"
By only accepting what you give me?
Do you think you'll turn into the real
thing by appearing on TV just once?
You should know your place
before you infuriate me.
What are you doing here?
You must have nothing else to do.
Don't you have any workers?
Get out. Get out at once!
This is exactly why her
manners are worsening.
Jung Hae-dang, agencies treat you
well at first, but once they
think you lost your worth, they
don't even glance your way.
Don't misunderstand.
How dare you.
You better not come here again.
Do you remember me saying I
would stomp on Jung Hae-dang
for fun every time you
defended her in front of me?
Go ahead. Go ahead and stomp on her!
You may be the son of a
wealthy CEO, but this
industry doesn't work just
because you have money.
The entertainment world is my area.
My area where I spent my youth!
Do you think this is your yard?
How dare you try to go against me.
What brings you here?
- Have you been well, Mr. Jung?
- Yes, thanks to you. How long has it been?
It's been a long time.
What are you doing here without
calling us ahead of time?
I had business in this area, so I decided
to drop by and say hello to Mr. Jung.
Oh, yes. Thank you. Please come in.
Should I call Hae-dang?
Why did she show up here out of the blue?
I came to ask you for a favor.
What favor can you possibly
ask from someone like me?
Do you know Hae-dang is
preparing to go on a show?
Yes. One show got canceled, but
she's preparing for another one.
Please stop her.
- Pardon?
- It's troublesome for me.
Is that so?
Before, you said your family was
able to live because of me, right?
Of course. Yes, that's true.
Hae-dang doing this is
awfully troublesome to me.
If you can give us a legit
reason how and why she'll become
troublesome for you, I'll stop
her with my own bare hands.
How can you speak that way to Ms.
Yoo Ji-na?
Why are you getting so angry at me?
Aren't you the one who answered Jo
Sung-taek's phone on the night he died?
No matter how much I think
of it, it's your voice.
Don't you remember that me calling?
If it wasn't you, then say so.
If it wasn't you, then say so!
Didn't you two become
distant ever since then?
It's not something you should meddle in.
Why not? It has to do with my sister.
Hae-dang has always lived with the mentality
that she would die for her sisters.
Yet, you tell me not to
meddle into her business?
How can you say something so rude, Ms.
Popular-singer-yoo-ji-na?
How dare you show up here.
Stop her from coming out on TV
because it's troublesome for you?
Do you want to die by my hands?
Take her to her room.
She has people on her side, too!
Do you want me to spread
the fact that you stole
your imitator singer's boyfriend
all over the internet?
I'm sorry, but I think
you should leave now.
What do I do?
I'm too offended to eat these.
Should I throw them away? I
can't throw away food though...
Go upstairs and give it to them. Don't
tell them where you got this from.
Mrs. Baek.
- What's this?
- Fruits.
Where did you get this from?
I forgot and bought two baskets.
Didn't you hear I don't have
the living expenses anymore?
- I did.
- So why did you forget again?
Anyways, enjoy!
I'll have to hurry up and put these
in the fridge. Oh my goodness!
These are expensive fruits!
What's this?
- She must have given you pocket money.
- Who? Who would give me pocket money?
How much is this?
One, ten, hundred, thousand, ten
thousand, hundred thousand...
Five hundred thousand dollars?
Five hundred thousand dollars!
What? You can't even count anymore.
One, ten, hundred, thousand, ten
thousand, hundred thousand...
What does this money mean?
She asked me to stop Hae-dang
from appearing on TV.
Yet, she would give you such a big amount?
She has a big hand.
I'll go change.
She must be returning it to her.
Of course she should.
Let me look at it one last
time before she returns it.
Wow. This is the first I see a
check with hundred thousand in it.
I've never seen a thousand
one before either.
Should I take a picture? We can
look at it from time to time.
Goodness!
- I'll be back.
- Okay.
Maybe that woman canceled her
TV appearance last time, too.
Oh, you're right, seeing
that she gave such a huge
amount to stop Hae-dang from
appearing on TV this time.
I think she stole
Hae-dang's boyfriend, too.
What do you mean?
Hae-sung asked, but Ji-na didn't deny it.
What? What a horrid woman!
If I had known, I would've
ripped out her hair!
Gosh! How dare she do that to Hae-dang.
- I'm going to spread this on the internet!
- Just stay still.
Right? I should just stay still
and not cause trouble, right?
You really don't know celebrities
by just looking at them.
She pretended to help out, but
she stole Hae-dang's boyfriend?
Gosh. What a scary woman.
I'm wondering if Hae-dang is suffering
a heartache just to go on TV once.
The entertainment world is frightening.
We have Mr. Park. He'll protect her.
What would we have done without him?
My goodness.
Where are you right now?
I'll come where you are.
What is it?
You're famous, so how
could you act so rudely?
I'll go wherever you are, so
tell me where you are right now.
Will you be able to come
find me if I tell you?
I'll use my navigator,
so tell me right now!
What's this?
I thought you wouldn't take it, so
I gave it to your father instead.
Did you think he would accept this?
He'll be more sorry about the
money thank you think he is.
- What?
- He doesn't have a retirement plan.
He'll become more and more miserable
living off his daughters.
Do you really want to be scolded by me?
How much do you make at
the nightclub in a month?
Give this money to your impoverished
family and be free from them.
Don't talk about my family.
All you have to boast about is the fact
that you suffered for your family.
You suffered for your siblings while
others abandon their children.
- Did you use that to seduce Park Hyun-joon?
- What did you say?
All you do is live off of singing my
songs, but I hate the way you look at me.
You're pointing out that I'm a woman
who abandoned my child, aren't you?
I don't need the tearful money you
made from abandoning your son.
If five hundred thousand dollars aren't
enough, I can give you a million dollars.
Even if you give me a million dollars,
I won't live as your shadow anymore.
Even if I have to beg for food,
I won't live as your shadow!
You said if you go under,
I'd die with you, right?
Fine. I'm glad you brought that up.
Even if we die together,
I have no intention of living as your shadow
anymore, Ms. Popular-singer-yoo-ji-na.
Hyun-joon...
Hae-dang, what are you
doing here at this hour?
(You Are Too Much)
She'll come running when I tell her to.
Am I crazy? Why would I like her?
Just date me.
Hyun-joon broke up with you?
If you're curious, sit
in that room and listen.
I'm so happy. I didn't know
such a day would come for me.
I didn't have the slightest will to live,
but now I feel like I want to live.
Just trust me.
Did you do this? It seems as if
you're searching for something.
Something is unusual, isn't it? Father
must have heard something shocking.
I had a close friend named Lee Kyung-soo.