TAXI STOP
Ugh, I feel sick.
It wasn't ours to begin with.
We will be punished for our greed.
What do we do now?
There you go again.
Now is not the time to be sulking!
Actually…
we did just find something
that he had misplaced.
At the minimum he should share
a percentage with us.
How can you just sit there
after he snatched
it back? Does that make sense to you?
We'll go ask Doctor Kang for our cut.
It's his fault for losing
it in the first place.
We just helped him locate it.
Isn't that right?
So, what are you still doing here?
Go negotiate with Doctor Kang?
Huh?
Aren't you the one that
squandered our fortune?
'Cause with taxes removed,
we could've pocketed somewhere around
eighty-three billion a piece
if you hadn't gone and lost it.
Is that what you're telling me?
I feel like you should be the one…
to try and recover some of the
cash we're losing at least.
You caused this.
They said he's staying at this hotel.
You don't have to go.
Really. I got this.
It's not worth the effort on your part.
I'll be the one to beg him,
or, if he throws me out the window,
I'll be the one to take the fall.
You should probably…
head back.
I don't want to have to see my sister.
I'm so angry at myself, so I can imagine
you guys are mad.
Sorry that Dona can be such a…
bully sometimes.
Remember when she hit me in the head?
I'm still sore.
I hope there isn't a lump.
You walked in willingly.
You can't leave now.
Ryong.
It's me and this guy Ggong.
Where are you?
Ryong.
Just one second.
- We going over the report.
- Yeah, reports, uh…
let's write our own reports.
Just send me a copy of
yours when you're done.
I
want to talk with the commander.
Take this, will you?
What?
You can tell me.
Yeah, um…
sure. Where?
I apologize.
You ought to take off, Commander.
Let's just go home, alright?
Yeah, sure.
No.
Don't go.
Okay.
Can you handle your liquor?
Sure, I like it.
- Are you good at drinking?
- I'm pretty good.
Then let's play a drinking game.
What, like whoever drinks the most
- gets Gong Ryong?
- How'd you guess?
You better slow down.
I'm so embarrassed.
If this is the way you're
starting things off,
then I'm not gonna drink.
Well, excuse me, bitch…
but, fuck that shit.
So, now we're cursing?
I also have…
horrible things to say…
just as soon as I'm drunk enough for that.
You should go curse at Gong Ryong.
He's the one that had the change of heart.
Weren't you the one who made Ryong…
be unfaithful?
Now, bottoms up.
I guess you are a bit of a drinker.
I'll take another.
Why?
You had four already.
Oh, was it?
Looks like we're even now.
Yeah, hi there.
Another bottle over here.
I wanted to talk to you sober, originally.
But I can't now.
I do want to thank you, though…
for saving Ryong.
Let's at least get that out of the way.
It all happened because
I fell for Gong Ryong.
I'm sorry.
I did make an effort to
stop that from happening,
but it didn't work.
And I truly apologize.
All the shiny new things
you can find in this hotel…
that's all that Ryong really
wants from me, you know.
He likes what I have to offer.
And Ryong wanted me so much,
that he even risked his
life to go into space.
And the Space Fertility Clinic…
he was promised by my father…
He won't want to give up on that.
You know
he's quite materialistic.
He's not compatible with
a hard-working astronaut.
He's just still in that…
early stage where he thinks
you're interesting.
It'll pass in a little while.
It'll pass in a little while, huh?
God, do you really think I'm so boring?
When you first met
he was MZ Group's future son-in-law
who spent seventy billion won
just to get into space.
But
that's not what I saw.
I saw a doctor driving around in his
junk car, tired of being broke.
I saw Ryong working his ass off so he
could to climb to the top of the ranks.
So, the compassion I have for that man…
You don't have any idea.
Never mind all that.
I want to know if you actually
think I'm boring.
Well, that's great.
Even if I drink every bottle in this bar,
you still aren't going to let Ryong go.
Yeah, well, not if I drink 'em first. So…
GONG RYONG
RYONG
Why is nobody picking up? Gosh.
Open up!
You're mine.
Hey Ryong.
You're back. Are you okay?
- Ugh, you reek of alcohol.
- Move.
Eve, are you okay?
Gosh, Ryong,
did you have so much to say that you
had to call her over here with me?
Seriously, you're…
you're so lucky you have
so many girls you can call.
Wait, uh
Hey
Hey, snap out of it,
Eve, hey! Are you okay?
- Don't touch me!
- Ah, seriously! Don't you
dare raise your voice at us.
Hey,
- are you okay?
- Just a second.
Eve, are you okay?
Huh?
Hey!
- Wait, no, what? Don't lie there.
- I should lie down too.
Right here.
- Oh, geez.
- But
why do you have to lay there?
If there's something you want to say,
say it while we're both here.
Yeah, that's why we came back here
together. So go ahead. Say what you need
- to say.
- Yeah, go ahead.
Say it.
What, so you're sleeping here tonight?
Yeah, I'm going to sleep.
Hey, I'll take you home. Come on.
- Who?
- Her?
What, are you suggesting I
sleep with the both of you?
Either that, or get out.
Just leave, then.
You've got to be kidding me…
This bed is cold.
I'm cold.
You are?
So cold.
Freezing.
There. Better?
Oh, that's great.
Ahhh, now it's warm.
Ah, so nice.
Good.
So good.
Now, she's not even answering her phone?
Where is she?
DONA
Is it the winning number for the two four
five three dash zero three lottery?
It is.
- May I ask what took you so long?
- Can I come claim the prize now?
Yes, of course.
I mean, it's a King's ransom.
We've been wondering where the winner was.
Okay. Thank you.
- So, what's happening here is…
- We just came for
breakfast. It's not what you think.
I don't care if you two slept together
or you hooked up or whatever.
Are you just going to stand there?
I didn't say you could sit.
I'm very sorry, Doctor Kang.
Guys, if anyone saw you,
I would seem like a huge jerk.
What are you doing on your knees?
Doctor Kang…
You know I'm as timid as a bird.
Hmm?
So, at first,
when I found the lottery ticket,
I wanted to find out who's it was.
And I really wanted to
return it to you, Doctor Kang.
Who was the mastermind?
Who convinced you to take my money?
I hate my life.
I swear I wanted to return it to you.
But they said, why bother returning it,
'cause it would be like…
like emptying a bottle of
water into the Han River.
Which is crazy, you know…
That awful metaphor
actually worked on me!
Yes, but who said it?
Was it you?
What?
I didn't say it.
Did Santi say, "we should become thieves?"
No.
It was Gong Ryong.
Absolutely not.
No way.
Gong Ryong, he…
hasn't done anything wrong.
The three of us had already said,
no matter what, we have to give it back.
We were all in agreement.
Then, when you were sleeping,
we left it floating right
in front of your face,
That way there was no way
you could have missed it.
We hovered it in front of you and left.
And that's it.
Period…
All right, doc?
But, I mean, Gong Ryong
he manages to find it in all that madness,
then he
comes back and just gives it to us.
I remember thinking…
is this fate?
How could it land in my hands again?
I mean, I really considered keeping it,
but I would return it.
I didn't want. I needed to.
We knew it was nearly a year old.
And that we could be completely
overreacting…
over a scrap of paper that's
past its due date.
So we wanted to check to see if it was
a valid ticket, so we called Houston.
We thought we should check.
And that's what we were discussing
in the bathroom. Alright?
It's the truth.
So you're saying
it was Gong Ryong who said,
"You'd be stupid to return it."
And instead of returning it to me after
he found it at the space station,
he returned it to you guys,
knowing it was mine.
Is that what you're saying he did?
That little punk keeps stealing my things.
You know Go-eun's right there,
so how could that boy get
a crush on the commander?
Oh, do you think we should bring her
here and talk some sense into her?
Huh? What do you think?
That Commander chick,
or whatever the hell she is…
I could take her.
Jeeze. Hey, hey, hey! Turn that off.
Oh,
let's not beat around the bush and just
get them here to ask them what's been
going on.
We don't know if Ryong has a
crush or if she seduced him.
You're right.
That day when I went to see them,
not only were they naked,
they were sharing a sleeping bag.
Naked?
- B… both of them?
- What?
Are you positive?
And you're just now saying?
Why didn't we hear
about this sooner, huh?
Why wouldn't you
share something like that?
Oh, jeeze!
SON
What's up?
Uh, so we were thinking about
the girl who saved you.
We'd like to make her
a meal to say thanks.
Could you bring her around?
You think I don't know what you're up to?
What is it you think we're up to?
I'm busy.
I'm out getting my homework checked.
Hey, you ungrateful brat!
If you knew how we felt,
you wouldn't have gotten so wasted
and said all those mean things that night!
I, just…
I'm conflicted and I think the
Commander is conflicted as well.
We don't need you adding to this mess.
Things are already so complicated,
so just back off!
Hey.
We're just trying to
make her a home cooked
meal, alright? Can you bring her?
Can you do that?
Moms…
how do you think you'd feel
if your boyfriend's ex…
talked about stuff to you that
happened when they were dating?
I know I'd feel like shit.
No guy should allow that to
happen in the first place.
That was the beginning of the end.
- Did you do that?
- Gotta go.
- Hey!
- What the hell?
- That little brat.
Later.
Right. Thank you for the report.
Gong Ryong,
so you ended up isolated when trying to
retrieve a camera cable you'd forgotten.
Yeah, see,
there was a dozen camera cables from
various countries,
not just ours, all tangled up.
So, grabbing mine was no easy task.
No matter
how well you organize them,
cables have a mind of their
own in microgravity.
Once in the sleeping bag,
you followed the survival
guidelines step by step,
according to the manual.
Yes.
Okay, so,
why didn't you remove your socks?
You risked getting frost bite.
Oh,
well… about the socks…
About the…
the socks…
I mean, as you know…
trying to put on socks in zero
gravity is quite difficult.
So even though we change
clothes every day,
we usually wear socks
for a few day in a row.
He was struggling, so we gave up on it.
I see.
I appreciate the detail with
which you wrote your report.
It'll be a great help to us.
Is that everything?
You made an incredible journey,
traveling to the brink of death.
One we'll never forget either.
But, this is where our journey ends.
You're free to leave.
Uh, Commander I still
need to speak with you.
Got it. I'll go.
With last night's team dinner serving as
the break up party for Expedition three,
you should stop seeing
the tourist in private.
It may have just been him liking you,
but it's not a good look for a commander.
People will talk.
They've already started
saying things downstairs.
You have many more competitors,
that would bring you down
to take your seat, than you do supporters.
You realize that, right?
You've worked so hard to
get to where you are.
I don't want to see your name
ruined over something trivial.
Do you think
I'm meddling in your personal life?
You know, like…
overstepping?
No, we're good.
Just,
whatever you do, don't see him. All right?
Anything else to say?
No.
So, have you given up on unrequited love?
Yeah, it's not for me, you know?
No, of course.
That's great news.
You know, mice…
haven't had sex in space,
let alone conceived or given birth,
and they're the most common
mammal in existence.
Gong Ryong,
I mean, aren't you an obstetrician?
Yeah.
So, what do you think is…
the most critical thing to consider
in conceiving life in that situation?
Why do you think mammals
aren't able to have sex?
- Yeah, let's do it together.
- Okay.
Actually, there's a pair of mice…
that might've already achieved that.
Really?
You just weren't
aware at the time.
You know when mice copulate,
there's a vaginal plug that
stays lodged an entire day.
So we can always check to see
if mice have done the deed.
Then we would know for sure.
It would be obvious.
Oh, but there are those that
don't make it obvious.
The sneaky ones.
They pretend that they didn't do it.
Plus, there are those who…
well, they're secretly in love.
What?
You're not serious, are you?
The sneaky ones.
They pretend they didn't do it.
- They're secretly in love.
I'll be joining Eve on this trip.
What are you saying?
It's where our astronauts have to live,
of course I should go to repair
the damaged station.
I sent the IOU a formal request.
The question is:
will the IOU accept a last minute request?
I don't care if you're going to repair
your relationship as colleagues or not,
as long as your missions are achieved.
Oh, Park Dong-a,
you and I still need to fill
out an incident report.
They want a detailed report on the Maru
rescue process, and ways to improve it.
Eve, you'll be included, too.
So from now on the three of us
will always be together.
So I better not see either of
you leaving work before me.
All right.
Don't stress, all right?
I won't take your Commander position here.
I can't take a younger colleague's
position, even if I do join you.
It'll take three months just
to restore the station, and…
you'll be occupying that space.
And I'll fix it.
That's the only thing I'll be doing,
so stop looking at me like that.
You find anything?
You made it, huh?
Let's begin.
Through that window over there
on the tourist's side,
we saw sparks ignite from
an undetached trunk.
The material should've burned
up and disappeared
before we entered the atmosphere,
so why would it be there still?
I was also concerned seeing how slowly
the trunk was burning, I mean…
the parachutes almost caught fire.
Has the trunk's material been changed?
The parachutes were acting
strangely as well.
Let's look at each aspect on its own.
Hey,
the three of us in here reminds me of the
old days. Come on, sit, here Dong-a.
You're right, you know?
Taking care of you was a
lot for me to handle then.
Tell me, Dong-a,
who did you like back in those days?
I wonder.
We'll forgive you if you answer honestly.
Who was it?
Seriously, ladies…
I was another woman entirely, Chief.
- There were others, you know.
- Oh yeah, there were
plenty of others, sure.
- You're really struggling here.
- Oh, come on now, Eve.
Chief.
- Such a sleazy dude.
- Hey, come on…
You were pretty sleazy from the start,
she's right.
You ladies are driving me crazy.
Is this the real reason you wanted
us three to work as a team on this?
And we're gonna destroy you, Dong-a.
This is only the beginning.
Oh, Chief.
Why don't you just apply for Station
repair duties this round?
You were an engineer first.
The three of us should go up as a team,
I think.
Do you think?
Honestly,
I was thinking about all the constant
meetings and all the reports and how it
just doesn't suit me at all.
What's the word?
We gonna go?
What do you say? You in?
Dong-a?
- Uh… hello?
- Can I join you guys?
Huh? What do you think?
- I'll see you later.
- Yes, have a good night, Doctor.
Eve! What, uh…
what're you doing here?
Uh, I actually just, well, uh…
- I just got a call from Jeon Yi-man…
- And what did he want?
Well, he reached out and asked me to come.
How's it going?
Welcome, come on in!
Wow. Already taking orders, huh?
Hello there.
Eve, look…
get in the car. Hurry.
Come on, get in the car! Right here!
What?!
Come on in!
Hey, no, come on! They'll eat you alive!
Get in! Hurry! Now, hurry up!
Will you hurry up and get in?
Ugh, damn it!
No, wait!
Yi-man's call probably alarmed you,
didn't it?
You should go get some
beer and just relax!
No, I'm not drinking.
Who said it's for you?
Did you expect us not
to offer her a drink?
Uh, I just have a meeting to be at
shortly so just one beer I think, just
- one.
- Okay, then…
- If you say so, hon'.
- Yeah, just one is fine.
- So responsible.
- Maybe we'll change your mind…
It's okay, yeah.
Don't any of you say weird stuff okay?
Like what?
- Thank you, dear, for saving our son.
- Oh…
Thank you.
And listen, you know how guys are.
They go on a little vacation, and…
land in an unfamiliar place…
and, you know, men,
they're animals and they start to feel a
kind of way when they meet someone new…
They lose their minds sometimes!
And mistakes will happen
from time to time.
Right?
Aren't you forgetting…
glasses. We can't drink from the bottles.
Glasses, go on.
- Jeeze.
- Such a brat.
Think about it, he…
he went all the way to space just before
he was supposed to get married,
I'm sure he was afraid and
had a lapse of judgment.
So please don't dwell on it. Alright?
Compared to women,
men are all quite dim-witted.
He may appear to look totally normal,
and calls himself a doctor
and yet, he still hasn't fully matured,
- making him less than ideal.
- What the?
- No,
- You were badmouthing me, weren't you?
We weren't.
Hey, hey, Ryong, your captain here is
impressive! As a fellow woman, I gotta say
- it!
- And I'd think you'd have high
standards and plenty of suitors to choose
from, right?
Oh, and I bet there's lots of guys
who want you, and you don't know it.
Heck, I'd be willing to bet there are at
least fifteen guys out there like Ryong.
Plenty, I'm sure.
So, what do you like to eat?
- What would you like?
- We'll make it special.
We heard you're going up soon.
Yeah…
actually, I eat
whatever's on my plate. So…
Nice.
- Well, we want it to be special.
- C'mon, why even ask? Just
cook everything you've got!
May I ask how old you are?
I'm 37, ma'am.
Your parents, what do they do?
They… they're still alive, right?
Actually, they passed away.
Oh, goodness.
Oh, but how you've turned
out is just amazing.
I bet they'd be proud,
if they were still around.
So, where are you from?
Well, I don't know where I came
from originally. I was adopted…
shortly after birth, in the US.
- I had adoptive parents growing up.
- Your biological parents…
left you as a little girl?
Oh, my gosh. How old were you?
You don't need to ask such
personal questions.
I was told it happened
on Christmas Eve.
Oh, well that's just sad.
It must've been chilly out.
Wait, is--
is that where you get your name, Eve?
Yes.
And that's why I hate Christmas
Eve more than anything.
Thank you for the meal.
- And,
- I don't like Christmas
- either. I'm with you.
- the good company.
Hey, Ryong, take a break, would you?
Why? I wanna have a drink, too.
Cheers.
The tofu is so good today.
Ah, I shouldn't have
had anything to drink.
Can I come with you in the taxi?
Bad idea.
Chief Kang said…
we better not be hanging out together.
Just to the front of the building?
No, we could get caught.
I'll never live it down if they
realize that I'm the sneaky rat.
Would you get canned?
Who knows?
Eve.
Do you regret what we did?
I don't know.
You don't know?
Wait, weren't you completely unbothered by
whether or not you'd live in that moment?
That's right. I almost forgot.
As the Commander, and you as the tourist,
up in space, or on Earth,
if there was gravity or there wasn't…
I forgot about everything else.
All gone.
Was I that good?
What? I'm an incredible mammal, aren't I?
Has the Maru been salvaged?
Yes, we took it back to
the MCC storage today.
I will investigate Maru with Commander
Eve and Pilot Dong-a Park and report
the errors and improvement of liftoff
and landing process of Maru.
Including trunk separation failure
during the rescue mission.
Please hurry up.
The investigation team in
Florida is ready to launch.
OBOK PUBLIC SAUNA
Hello.
Thank you.
I've never done this before.
So what do I do up there?
Uh, just look at all the people
and use your intuition.
So, copy them?
Going up there means you'll only get
to clean yourself like a cat for one
whole year, right?
- That's true.
- That's not bathing,
it's licking.
You're right. It's just licking.
- Indeed.
- You've got this.
So, take it all?
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Alright.
Good luck!
- How'd it go?
- Ah, I'm so
embarrassed, everyone was naked.
Do you remember how cold
it was for us that night?
No, I still
can't remember.
Ah,
- I'm hungry.
- So am I.
Too bad I don't know the area.
Let's just walk into whatever place
smells the best around here.
Okay.
Oh, look, there's another tray coming out.
- What?
- Oh, here it comes.
It's like you haven't eaten
for a week at least.
EVERYONE'S BAKERY
The station truly had no smell at all.
It was…
so dreary.
Wait,
is this… the smell of the loaves of bread?
Or is it the baguettes?
Is it a requirement that the food at
the Station has to be so scentless
and tasteless?
Gosh,
how can someone live a year like that?
I was only there,
what, ten days and I couldn't believe
how much I missed Earth.
I've never been up there
more than three months,
but according to some of the others,
apparently you start missing
the sound of birds after three months.
And at around the six month mark
people begin to crave
the simple sound of rain, like crazy.
It's become pretty common now to
take up recordings of nature.
But, honestly,
all I want is to grab this smell
to take with me.
And the feeling of sinking into the
hot bath at the end of the day…
I wouldn't mind taking that feeling
along with me.
And sounds of the neighborhood
that you might hear, just like…
I don't know, waiting for bread.
That'd be nice.
You know,
it's not that it's nice
'cause we're on Earth.
It's nice 'cause you're here with me.
Oh, is that so?
Well, who knew?
You know you almost died.
Does that scare you going back?
I've never really been afraid of death.
It doesn't really matter when I die,
I just…
I want to die while I'm happy.
Who wants to live beyond that?
Can I be honest with you?
That day,
had I died in that tent
I don't think I would've…
been particularly upset,
or angry about it.
I wouldn't have died alone.
All right.
There are much worse ways to go…
than dying holding your favorite person.
My whole life I've been lonely,
but I remember thinking…
this is nice.
I remember thinking…
I'll do whatever it takes to stay alive,
or keep you alive,
so together, we could eat bread
and have a bath in warm water,
and date like normal people on Earth.
And, who knows, maybe one day,
we could get married,
and have lots of kids.
We'd have around three children, hmm?
We definitely won't die
by some kind of accident.
We'll live nice healthy lives until
we're a hundred years old.
And when you die,
I'd die the very next day.
I'd live at least one day after you,
so your heart wouldn't
have to break for me.
That's what I prayed would
happen for me and you.
That's what I hoped would be the case.
I just…
I couldn't handle the
thought of dying there…
I refused to die up there with you.
So, what else did you imagine
if our relationship grew?
You mean when it grows.
- What, how, how many children, huh?
- No, if our relationship grows
Huh?
- How many kids are we having?
- Oh, I don't know.
Huh?
Not in your wildest dreams, buddy.
They're open
Let's go.
C'mon
FATHER
Yes, Father?
What the hell have you been doing with
your time for MZ to change their
primary bank?
They've switched to our biggest rivals.
Get over there and make
things right again!
Chairman Choi.
Don't you think this is a little unfair?
What?
I beg of you…
bring your business back to our bank.
Go-eun is my woman.
And I want you to give her back, too.
After you told me to
give up and surrender?
Seriously?
No one should have the balls
to tell me when to surrender.
You give up, okay?
You liked me.
You'll never be satisfied
with a jerk like Ryong.
Ryong is the one that doesn't
know when to quit.
He didn't give up when there was
no ovary and in that situation
when you said
giving up was the only answer,
the boy didn't give up, did he?
You've lost to him.
He was on the brink of freezing to death,
and he still didn't give up.
Couldn't you be more like that man?
Ryong's an asshole involved
with another woman.
Look at you, buddy.
Ryong has given up sir, on Go-eun.
You, phone Ryong.
You
Are you a cheater?
Huh?
I…
continue to value even your damn
worn socks as family treasures.
Now answer me.
Did you cheat on her?
'Cause if that's the case,
I don't care if you risked your
life to form that morula
I won't let you go near it.
I'll kick you out of the medical center
and put an end to your little
space clinic.
I'll make damn sure
you don't work on Earth either!
Chairman,
I wanted us to chat.
So,
- the thing of it is, is--
- Dad.
Let me guess,
you're taking Kang-su's word,
and suspecting Ryong?
Are you kidding?
Are the two of you still scheming even
after your little ice cream incident?
And what exactly was it this time
that made you want to blindside us?
'Cause, for your information…
Ryong and I wouldn't…
have any issues to speak of,
if that terror
Kang-su would leave us alone.
That jerk just makes me so
Do you know how apologetic to Ryong I am,
because of that!
You know at the hotel he's staying
in the room right next to ours?
Everyday he goes out and spreads rumors
that my ex-boyfriend is in the room
right next door.
He makes me out to be like I'm crazy!
Hey, don't you think you're
being a bit harsh?
What?
Is it true?
Yup,
he's in the adjacent room.
Do you have even the slightest clue
of how foul and clingy this guy is?
Who's foul?
How have I ever been foul to you?
And, look…
how he just waltzes around
the hotel in his pajamas.
Earlier in the lobby,
there were people on their hands
and knees in front of him.
Something about money.
Did you take money off of those people?
Wow, that's low, even for you.
As if the entire universe
revolves around you.
I'm not what he likes,
he likes your company
using his bank as our primary lender.
Do you even know why I ended it?
I'm embarrassed to say it.
It's because he calls himself
an astronaut yet in reality…
he's completely obsessed with fruit flies,
and attending fruit fly conferences
At parties, he actually raises money to
fund fruit fly research.
He wouldn't even come to
bed until after midnight.
He'd spend all of the time
he had for me sleeping.
Honestly, I only ever saw him in bed.
He'd be up at dawn and spend every
waking moment with fruit flies.
You said you give me attention
when you came to bed,
and you would just go to sleep instead!
How is it possible you still
haven't won a Nobel,
yet you'd rather waste your
time trying to break us up?
Oh yeah!
The one thing you can't do at the station,
that your fruit flies can't
do with you is sleep!
He only came here to sleep with me,
all right?
Stop, Go-eun.
It's all right, chairman, really.
And how dare you bring up my older brother
when you don't even know what it takes
to be one.
He's just trying to make
trouble where he can…
because I have someone else now.
His ego has been damaged.
Dad, please.
I'm not even as important
to this guy as a fruit fly!
Do you really still want me to
end up with a jerk like that?
Huh? Answer!
I can't work out the reason you would
even still wanna deal with this fruit
fly mega-jerk!
Hey.
Get out.
But… Chairman…
That Ryong asshole turned
his back on her already.
Ryong.
Shall we have lunch?
Sir, no, please…
Hey, I need you to make sure…
this fruit fly…
isn't allowed to come back here.
I'll tell him when it's the right time.
I still don't want to give you up.
Please, give my pride a break.
Okay, sure.
Are you insane?
Yo!
Damn it! Are you--
You just blindsided me again!
Damn!
Shit!
Next time just hit me!
Okay?
- Why attack my sweet girl? Jeeze!
- You think I'm the only one in
trouble at the disciplinary hearing?
I'm not going down alone.
Say that again to me, man.
You thought you were in the clear?
What, you heard about that?
Huh?
- You took it from those guys?
- Hey. Hey,
hey.
You took my money and my girl away.
You're the one who's basically a thug.
Okay.
If I get a harsher punishment
and owe hundreds
of billions in fines, thanks to you,
I'll be able to pay for them all.
So thanks a whole lot, man!
You asshole, do you
really want to start with me?
Seriously, hey!
- Hey, yourself, jerk!
- Hey, hey,
hey.
Hey.
You didn't implant Doctor Na
yet with the morula, did you?
Shithead! Hey!
Fuck you, asshole!
You better learn to filter what you say!
Can you honestly…
not separate your love life from creating
and destroying other lives?
All you do is
blindside everyone you know!
Hey, what are you doing? Doctor,
please, this just makes Miss Choi's
position harder.
- Damn it.
- Uh… please, stop this.
What does a thieving asshole like
you care if you're blindsided, huh?!
What?
- You're not worth better, you deserve it.
- No, sir, please!
Go-eun.
Using energy to hit you isn't worth it.
You guys proud?
You think you did well here?
A hearing…
to discipline Kang Kang-su will
be called in the next day.
The Inspector General is coming to
preside, so Commander, not just you,
but the entire Expedition
Three team should be there.
Okay, Chief.
Kang Kang-su stealing donated
eggs and conducting
that study using Santi's sperm,
was a deceptive act carried
out in contempt
of his fellow astronauts, also the KSA.
This thing will end Kang Kang-su's career
so cooperate with the Inspector and
answer the questions.
How did nobody else know that eggs were
implanted in the incubator up there?
We can only see if it's
been switched on or off.
And there's no way to know
what the contents are,
so we were waiting until we
got the crews report on it.
Han Si-won,
let's go to the main office
before we leave tonight.
I have something I'd like to
submit to the Inspection team.
Yes, ma'am.
Let's go have dinner together.
I can't, I still have work.
We all warned you, you know, Eve.
What do you mean?
You know the answer.
I just wanted to have dinner
and get things wrapped up.
I want to get done and get out of here.
Hey. Are you seriously ignoring me?
You don't have to be with me,
but the tourist isn't
appropriate as a match.
When you got everyone you know
telling you to avoid something,
there's a good reason.
Is this advice or a warning, Dong-a?
Seriously?
I'm running out of time here.
In a few days, I'm leaving Earth.
All of my time is precious right now.
Having to leave the person I like…
to go up to space makes every day…
just feel like I have…
some kind of set date of expiration.
Days are slipping away and I'm going nuts.
Did you have sex with him?
When was it?
After I risked it all to save you?
When you were…
completely naked and alone in the tent?
Yeah.
There's no way.
Oh.
Y'know, we're…
- really alike, you and I.
- Oh, don't make up
nonsense. You did it there?
Up in zero-g? No.
We did.
And you really expect I'll believe that
asshole managed that and even mice can't
do it?
Uh-huh.
Wow.
Wow. I didn't think you could
ever lie to me. Ouch.
Eve,
you… you've lost it, you…
You're crazy! You are!
Hey, where are you going? We were talking!
Why wouldn't you tell Doctor Ma,
then, huh?
You know,
the one who loses sleep obsessing
over how to get mice,
the representative mammal, to do it? Huh?
Why not go ahead and make
your partner's life easier?
Why just tell this crazy lie to me? Huh?
You and I are not the same.
'Cause I can play the bad guy.
And you can't pull that off,
can you?
I know you can't.
You didn't.
That's true.
It's true.
You lost.
We were first.
Aren't we just incredible?
Keep up the hard work,
you guys. Okay?
Chief.
We're running late.
I'm on my way out.
Just wait a moment.
I'M ON MY WAY OUT. JUST WAIT A MOMENT.
Do you have an umbrella?
- Chief.
- Yes?
Can you drop me back at the
center on your way home?
Just finish it tomorrow.
The flight team wants it by tonight.
Take a taxi, then.
But, it's raining. Or,
you could just loan me the company car.
You want my purse, too?
What did you say?
Why don't we stop for dinner first,
so I don't have to eat alone.
The flight team is waiting on me.
What did the general say?
Well, it's tense as we expected.
Huh?
Isn't that the Commander over there?
Looks like she doesn't have an umbrella.
We can't let her get a cold, when
she's flying so soon. Call her over.
Okay.
Gosh, aren't you cold?
You didn't have to bother. It's so close.
Yeah, you still should've borrowed
an umbrella. Why get rained on?
- There was no one left to borrow one from.
- Oh?
Did everyone quit because they hate me?
Wait.
- What's that? What happened to your neck?
- Huh?
Who did this to you?
- What, you mean that?
- Huh?
Oh, that's nothing.
- What? Yeah right, it's nothing!
- What? I don't get it!
Hey… so,
what happened to the commander who warned
me not to like her under any circumstance?
Hey, at least I didn't
call you a murderer.
And what happened to the guy
who wouldn't care if I died?
I left him in space.
Ah, I do love the sound of rain.
Wrong again.
It's not the sound of rain
that's so delightful.
The reason the rain's
delightful is because
you and me are in it together.
Fine.
It all started back then. Right. Yes,
Yes, that's right.
It started then.
Dong-a put his life on
the line to go up there.
Honestly,
we all sensed something was off,
didn't we?
Could surviving together like that have
ignited something between them when
they arrived back on Earth?
Hey, Han Si-won.
Zoom in to that thing behind
the sleeping bag.
Sleeping bag?
Yeah, hurry.
Right.
- Keep going, go on, go on.
- More?
Yes.
Isn't
that the incubator behind there?
Incubator?
- Was there an incubator there?
- I mean… that's what it looks like.
It's too dark to really see.
Give me a sec.
It is.
It's an incubator.
We stopped using that one when we switched
to the one in the observation module.
But it looks like it was switched on
right before the space debris hit.
From here, there's no way to know
what it was used for,
and communications were
cut after the debris incident so
we have no records we could check.
So, who used it?
At this rate,
all hell could break loose at tomorrow's
disciplinary hearing.
Tell me who was over that way at
the start of the debris incident.
Right.
So, on top of the seven morulae,
they had more fertilized eggs?
Get Kang-su and the tourist
up here right now.
Why the tourist?
Well,
because the tourist was loitering there
the whole time. So get him right now!
Are you two working together?
Name, Kang Kang-su.
Your astronaut qualifications
are permanently revoked.
Traitors.
We may have lost our child,
but I wanted to do everything I
could to keep the morula alive.
We're not on the same
side, we're enemies.
That's enough!
I can't believe a single
word you say anymore.
She doesn't have any family
so would it be so bad for there to be just
one person here on Earth who
is on her side no matter what?
I think we've got one!
Really?
Where are you? I'll come to you right now.