Do you know that Yuuo was taking drugs with side effects? 》
{As a family, please say a word.
;
[In interviews with investigators...] [Substantiated death due to negligence...]
"This is a case where it would be called a suicide act, or a murder act."
((TV audio: Bell's voice over the phone))
(Uzaki) Is Todoroki the victim's family?
(Todoroki) My daughter is
I was on that bus
It's not a coincidence that I handed my business card to your mother.
I went to look at the bento shop of my own volition.
I'm curious as to why that driver's son became a lawyer.
I can't help but say something like that... what?
Assuming Todoroki was the victim's family
Why am I here...
I'll tell you, follow me
Me and you too
I'm sure I'd thought a lot about that accident.
What do you think was the truth?
I don't know
But at least
The cause of the accident is currently considered to be true
That's all a lie
Is it a fact?
Driver Uzaki Yuo was the day of the accident
Break the rules set by the company
I took a drug with a strong side effect and ran the bus.
As a result, they fall into a state of confusion
A major accident
This is the fact that was established at the time.
You're stupid, there's no way your father would break the rules
I have almost the same opinion too
Asami is the same
(Asami) Yes, there is a huge darkness hidden in that accident.
Nice to meet you Uzaki-kun
Who is it?
(Kiriishi) I'm a friend, don't worry
Asami Ryoko is a detective from the First Investigation Division who provides us with internal police information.
criminal?
The accident five years ago was as you said →
I can say with certainty that it's not Uzaki Yuo's fault.
Why? Despite all that sacrifice
There is no sufficient investigation
Everything was handled by the main office.
Perhaps the police crushed it inside
That means there's something I want to hide
I can't forgive you
Minato City teamed up with the police to hide the truth.
The mayor's music club, the top of the group, must always hold something.
I'm about to grab that tail right now
Do you understand why you need it? Uzaki
If you know, grow quickly
I hope there's always a big game
(Asami) I'm looking forward to it Uzaki-kun
(Kiriishi) I don't care either way, don't get in the way
(Moderator) He said he could create a big revolution.
(Tomita) Yes, the panels developed by our company are made of wood, but they are not easily burned.
It has high heat storage properties
A new insulation panel?
Yes... this is good
(Inoo) Apparently it's selling point is that it's hard to burn even though it's wood.
Yes, it's delicious
But we've been fried in the morning...
My bad mom just really does
{What, what is this, what does it mean? 》 《You'll be given the debt as a surcharge》
"There's no way I won't give anything back."
So what kind of spark is this?
This development is pretty weird
(Tomita) Summer is easy
It's warm in winter because it stores heat
It's great if it's cool in the summer and warm in the winter
No, the development itself is amazing
The manufacturer is suspicious
This meat housing is a company
I had an incident at the agency I used to be.
Ah, he's sued, rights matters
(Takaido) I'm sure it's a company that has grown rapidly over the past few years.
Yes, one after another, patents
He rose to become a major manufacturer at an extraordinary speed.
I dig it out because it smells bad, and as expected
There have been many times in development related matters.
So I'm a habitual plagiarist
Are you sure your target's eye is here?
Makita Zaiki Store
It's a small company with a craftsmanship
The weak are the prey to the major companies. It's a typical example.
So let's start a fight
Uzaki
That's my snippet
(Tomita) The structure is made of wood fibers and a breathable sheet and board.
(Ichiya) What do you mean?
Our invention is a layer structure that maximizes this effect.
(Kumamoto) Don't be kidding me, it's all my ideas
(Kawashima) What do you do?
I'll check with Mr. Kinoshita, who is in charge.
(Kumamoto) President We're going too
No, everyone will wait here and go by myself
(Takano) It's a bit lie (Kawashima) What will happen to this?
Why do you do this?
It was Kinoshita who said he wanted to support development.
(Kinoshita) We need to check each other's perceptions.
Oh, even if you say recognition
The materials are combined according to the drawings we drew.
Please stop accusing →
That insulation panel is a new product made by our engineers.
So why do we have the exact same drawing?
I don't know
If that's the case, then maybe that's what I imitated. →
Anyway, the patent has already been obtained.
Is this the purpose from the beginning?
What does it mean? I trusted you
I don't really understand the story
Isn't it so unfair to apply for a patent?
(Ikezawa) I will make a statement as an advisory lawyer, but →
If there is an invention, it's only natural to apply... I'm not talking to you.
This is a plagiarism of technology no matter what anyone says.
(Kinoshita) President, please calm down
As for us
I would like to continue to do business with Makita.
(Ikezawa) I'm currently asking for a renovation project for public housing in the city →
That's important to your company too
Are you thinking about quitting the transaction?
(Ikezawa) Isn't this a transaction due to a good relationship?
President Makita
Can I talk a little about it?
Which one would you like?
My name is Todoroki, a lawyer.
How was Meat Housing's response?
Why the story?
I just heard from the employees.
I think you're probably in trouble
It's a great help, President Makita
No, I'm going to have it, but it's fine
Ah, what about everyone?
I went up early today
I'm just standing there and going for a drink
I see, well, they're short-tempered people
Young President
It was a wise decision
I can't shut down the company in this situation →
Kuma has three children, and her mother is sick →
Kawashima is also slushing his wife
He kept on stepping well →
The company that the previous generation left behind is not going to go bankrupt
Isn't it different?
The company he dumped and forced on me
(Ichiya) Then stop calling me that young president
Sorry
Thank you for your hard work
good work
(Takaido sings "Tonbo")
Wow, are you a mom? (Kumamoto)
The young president died of illness when he was in middle school
Well, there were many difficulties, but now he's a great manager.
What happened to your previous father?
That's right... Yes?
Why were you talking to me like this?
Have you forgotten about it yet? A little bear
I like Nagabuchi so we hit it off, right? Come on, drink more
Ah that's what I was, I know it even though I'm young →
It's good Nii-chan
But why do you want to ask about our company?
I'm studying social studies
See, all the stories of seniors in life are educational.
I like it
There are still girls like this in this era, no, no, we've only seen them for two hours.
I liked it, listen to more of our journey
♫～
♫~A hard bond
The president really loves factories →
I've been visiting factories all the time since I was a child.
(Takaido)♫~Youth Days
After I grew up, I started working for a construction material manufacturer.
If you have time, come back to the factory →
I was talking about things with my previous generation →
Looking back, we both were researching insulation.
All to develop this company.
(Kumamoto) That's when the previous generation evaporated
(Kawashima) Kuma-san Let's stop now
It's fine, so let me ask you at this point Kawashima →
I can't believe it, but suddenly she ended up making a woman and disappeared.
"Are you really going to throw it all away?"
"I'm not involved with the company anymore."
《What will you do about development?》
"We've finally made it this far."
"Wouldn't all of our employees make happy?"
"I was so interested"
Do as you please
《(Tongue click)》
(Kumamoto) Everyone is panicking
I was a bit nervous because I had a child too →
But the CEO must be the one who's hurting more than anyone else →
I'm still grudged →
Why does this happen?
But after that, everyone stood up together
The young president has reinstated the crisis
I worked for the company I worked for, quit quickly and come back, and worked as hard as I could.
Wow, he's a cool person
I'm a benefactor
If I was only thinking about myself, I should have gone to work.
But he came back for us
Kuma-san, just listening to my story makes me feel warm
In comparison, where and what did the previous generation do?
Poor Kuma-san, the young president
It's about parents and children, so it's better not to talk
Oh, good work, it's fine
Nishi-chan's Nagabuchi was the best,
What were you talking about?
Takaido This company is the best, it's super hot
You're really a good guy
(Kumamoto) Okay, I'll keep telling you more, please drink it, yes
Oh Takaido sings more
Sing, sing, sing
Thank you very much, good night
Okay, I got a lot of information out
Maybe I'll consider it at the office tomorrow
Usu, I'm happy, I'm not
Isn't it quick? Have fun, good night
Takaido It was a hot night, wasn't it?
No, there's no such company, I have to help you.
Are you still saying you're helping, this is business too
No, no, that's true, but they're nice people, so it's even more exciting.
Are you a good person, I thought it was shit
Huh? You, where are those people?
I hate that kind of ignorant people
Let's talk about how weak people can't be crushed
What is that terrible way of saying it is so passionate, you're annoying
Conversely, you're too cold
Don't get involved with drunk people
Get even more hot, Takaido
You won't get hot
Hey, is that bad?
Oshi I understand, sit down and drink again Let's talk
I can't do it, but I'm going home so do it alone today
What is it? It's so good
Don't be kidding these guys
"You don't go on this side."
ah…
(Takaido) I understand the situation
However, even if we are currently insisting on the young president of Makita, there is not enough evidence.
There is no way to prove Kazuya is a true inventor
Yes, there's no way the meat housing would allow a copy of the drawing.
Just having the same drawing is not proof
It's certainly proof of which one drew first.
The only thing that can be considered as a witness is
My father was involved in development from the beginning, but...
Even if he is now missing, and is found →
Individual testimony is unlikely to be strong evidence
After all, that's the wall
Wait a minute
What if that was found? Takaido (Takaido) Ah?
See, the bear said
Ah... Research Diary
Parents and children were always watching (Takaido)
Hey, if it's a diary, wouldn't it be worth the age?
Certainly, if your diary has ideas and dates are clearly marked
It should be objective evidence.
Uzaki's lucky punch
Who's the lucky punch?
Todoroki-san, is it okay to move a bit in your own way?
Ah, of course (Takaido)
What is it Takaido: Isn't it motivated?
Wow, we were developing insulation here.
Yes, I've had to do the test here many times
We all created it together
Amazing, so cool, bear
Right?
...Even so, Nii-chan was a lawyer.
I was wondering if I could help you after hearing about it yesterday.
Thank you, I told that person too
We're simmering, please
Yes, so I have a request
What research diary Kuma said is? Do you know where it is now?
Ah, that
Come to think of it, where is it?
(Ichiya) Hey, what are you doing?
(Kumamoto) Oh, President I've made a strong ally.
I met Nii-chan yesterday, and I'm a lawyer.
I have no intention of filing a lawsuit, please come home
Why did you want to help me...
Kuma-san, I'll do the company
But (Ichiya) That's fine
Shall we talk somewhere else?
Well, thank you Kuma-san
Oh, see you again
I can understand how I feel about the employees
However, isn't it a little too early to just accept this here?
I'll get it back for another job
Let's fight
I heard it from the bear
How much do you value this company?
So how do you win?
If you've gotten this far, it's not possible anymore
I came today to break through that
We believe the chance lies with your dad
Huh? My father has nothing to do with it
If your father is a witness, he might be able to provide strong evidence.
For example, a research diary I've been keeping for a long time
He's the guy who abandoned his company
I will never cooperate and I don't want to be furthermore.
Where is your dad going now?
i don't know
I should be living somewhere as I please
(Kawashima) Sorry
what?
I have a little something I want to talk about
Actually, I
I know where the previous generation is
First, I would like to ask you what the lawyer would need?
I'm sure they said it was about the Makita Rubber Store.
No notice of acceptance has been received
Whose behalf is it here?
You have to just do something that doesn't matter, you have to do something wrong
It's time to be taken away
It seems like there's a habit
Most of the innovations you have achieved
It would be unnatural that such similar examples exist
All discussions have already been completed, and we have won all the lawsuits →
If you're a lawyer, you'll understand this weight, right?
Please go home when you're satisfied
In the first place, there is no obligation to tell you anything
I hate that expression
yes?
(Takaido) He's very confident, but
If there are any drawings that were drawn long before the date you completed the drawings
What will happen?
That's not the case
It's just our idea
(Kinoshita) Please come home
is that so
I might win if I had a research diary
I was upset when I put on a sickle
☎I see, the key is my father after all.
Yes, but there's a place to stay
☎Go to Uzaki, where there was a harvest here too.
Huh?
Yes I understand
(Takaido) Twitch Why did you become a fireworker with this guy... Before you knew it,
I'm expecting growth, let's go Takaido
Huh? Noisy...
thank you
What kind of use do you want?
Do you know what's happening at Makita Rubber Store right now?
As you can see
I'm so busy with my own life
Assuming that the company's technology was plagiarized
His son Ichiya sued
It is being considered to wake up
I came here to be a witness.
I refuse
I did something sorry to my son
I don't have any faces to meet now
I don't remember the development details.
I don't have any intention of interacting with the company anymore
Isn't it pathetic?
What's that hiding it?
The sudden disappearance I heard about is also strange.
Isn't there a secret situation no one knows?
I'm not hiding anything
I just can't get my head turned out because of debt
I'm continuing to pay 60% interest on loan sharks
That's illegal, you're being deceived so you have to fight
I know it's illegal
That's why I'm asking what to do
No matter how impressive an invention or aspiration
Once you become the exploited
I can't get out
This also has a disgusting look
I'm scared now, I can't move
I understand, then
Please tell me the loan shark dealer
Todoroki-san, I'm going
Todoroki-san
Todoroki! Oh... That's it...
good morning
What is that injury Did you do something again?
Let's go and light Kazuya-san
I won't say anything anymore but what will I do?
Of course I'll break through the front
If you don't know, I'll say it clearly
They say they won't put the company at risk in court that can't be won.
I found a chance to win
So how?
I asked my father to be a witness.
Did you meet him?
We met and talked
If that's true, then the president will be together again with the parents and children...
Bear
Is that guy coming?
We are continuing to negotiate
That's right
There's no way it's coming
The man who abandoned his company is now
(Kawashima) President: How to say that...
I won't do a trial so please go home
You and your children have been enthusiastic about researching that insulation material
Because it was their dream
Please come home already
It is possible for parents and children to develop what they discover together
I was happy, I don't remember
But my father suddenly betrayed me
I can't forgive that
What is your purpose for speaking? Go home already!
I haven't given up on that dream yet
The dreams of two parents and children have become everyone in this company's company's dreams, right?
Nii-chan can you forgive me if I take away something so important?
Everyone who works loves the company, so what's more
You, the CEO, is so loved
This kind of company
A president like you
It should be a step forward for small and medium-sized enterprises that are being exploited!
Let's fight President →
I can't thank you for all of what's been up to now →
But this is about pride as a craftsman.
There's no chance of winning
If they cancel their contracts, we'll be on the streets.
President, please
The previous generation will surely come
So, could you please show me where we both work together again?
Kawashima
We'll do whatever we can to ourselves
I do whatever life I do
He's pushed me this far
I still can't decide
Our pride
Will you get it back?
yes
I'll entrust it to you
I asked
Leave it to me
Let's get started
Today is the date for questioning, and the witness, Makida Kazuhiko, is there?
I'm late now, so could you please leave it later?
I see
How about the defendant's agent?
It would be great if it really came
As a defendant,
(President Judge) Let's start as soon as we arrive
(Ikezawa) Exhibit 6
Is this drawing drawn by a craftsman at Makita Rubber Shop?
No drawings drawn by our technicians.
There was a report on it on the day I drew it, so it's no doubt
(Ikezawa) When is that?
It's December 15th, 2026.
The history of the email with the drawing attached is still available
(Ikezawa) So why do Makita Zaikuten have the same drawings?
I believe our original drawings have been plagiarized.
That's not possible
All of our employees and craftsmen know, so please ask.
I understand that small businesses are also difficult and difficult.
Please refrain from accusations
(Takaido) When you had dinner with Kazuya
You offered to help with development costs by paying in addition to the usual transaction.
No, I've already finished work and sometimes I drink it
I'm not talking about that
However, the transaction price has risen once since the day you eat →
This is proof that you were helping
You guys get a report of the development status →
He stolen the invention, it's not true.
So why do Makita Ruiki Store have such a similar drawing?
(Kinoshita) This is a common occurrence in this industry.
Maybe I came up with a similar product
We completed it first
First of all, the transaction price increased
I wanted to help Makita Zaikuten's business troubles.
In fact, I know the business situation very well.
I've given up on a variety of jobs to save it,
I feel like I've been given a favor back
Is that what you said? Kazuya-san Kazuya-san
That's why it was invented there.
I'd like to ask about insulation panels
Please tell us what ideas will be the origin of the invention?
Our company has been in the past few years
We were researching minerals with special properties →
The flame retardancy and the properties of wood
Furthermore, if we add the heat-generating property of the fibers
When big innovation occurs
So please tell us about the difficulties involved in developing it.
There wasn't much trouble
I knew the structure and mechanism, so I just had to steadily move towards my goals.
Don't be kidding
I've been researching since I was a child
I've finally finished it
Was there no hard work?
Don't let it be foolish too
(President Judge) Please refrain from making quiet and irregular comments
Is it okay now →
If you want to ask about development, I'll answer as many questions as I can.
(Presential Judge) Plaintiff: Any other questions? →
If not, I'll move on to interrogation with Makita Kazuhiko. Did you come? →
If you haven't come, that's all for today →
Plaintiff: Is that okay?
(Presiding Judge) Plaintiff: What do you think?
(Door opens)
It's very late
The late witness has arrived
《Listen, what are you going to do?》
"No, I'll clean up my debts"
"And then could you come to court? 》
"What's up? 》
"I'm from a law firm."
"I came here because I wanted to get Makita Kazuhiko's unnecessarily interest to be revoked."
"Ah... I don't want to cause any trouble."
《You know the money lending business law》
《(Lock)》
"Look at the situation, I'm saying I'll look sad if I don't shut up."
First of all, no money is permitted without registration.
"Interest exceeding the upper limit interest rate is of course illegal."
《Oh no 》
《Ohhh》
"Calm down, this is self-defense."
"Unregistered money lending business will be sentenced to imprisonment of up to 10 years or fined up to 30 million yen."
"Learn money is fined up to 10 million yen in prison for up to five years."
"here we go"
《What are you going to do?》
OK?
yes
Kazuhiko-san
Please tell us how you came up with insulation panels
When Kazuya was a child, we played with a bonfire and played with him.
At that time, Kazuya realized that there was a tree that was not burning.
So
I'm starting to think that maybe I could make insulation from wood.
I think Kazuya started developing the project when he was a child.
(Kazuhiko) Yes
Then my son became an adult and started developing together.
In other words, the origin of this invention is
Is there no doubt that it is with you, parents and children?
(Ikezawa) Objection, obvious guidance.
There is no evidence to prove when development begins
I got it today so I'll submit it later
Here is a new evidence:
Kazuhiko-san, this
This is the research diary you used to develop insulation panels.
Yes →
This is something I've worn every day for over 20 years
The way the drawing is completed →
I think it's written along with the date
This is the same question as the defendant just said
Please tell us about the difficulties involved in developing this insulation panel.
That's already
There are many
For example, the combination of wood and minerals
Which percentage should be increased, and how many high temperatures should be pressed?
The result will change completely →
If you increase the proportion of minerals in an attempt to prevent burning, it won't harden.
Raise the press temperature to harden it
It's going to break this time
(Kazuhiko) And then
I think it was difficult to think about how to make the heat-generating effect only in the cold season.
We have made the materials to make sure water vapor passes well according to the temperature.
Hearing my son's opinion
(Kazuhiko) This is
Thick or thin, it's not good
I've tried again and again
When was the result of that hard work and it was completed?
(Kazuhiko) I won't forget
It's June 10th, 2018
You can prove that
(Kazuhiko) Of course
The date the drawing is completed is written in the research diary.
This is proof
That concludes the interrogation
I was thrilled
(Door opens)
Thanks to that, it was helpful
It's just that I've protected my skills.
It's not you
Kazuhiko-san
To my son who has protected the company so far
Isn't it okay to express your gratitude?
What should I say now...
(Ichiya) It's fine
I feel bad when someone says something I never thought of
(Kawashima)
Please tell me the truth now
Kawashima Don't say anything bad (Kawashima) Please say it I can't stand it
I promised!
(Kawashima) Kazuya
The previous one is
He protected my old man and disappeared
What is it about?
What's the story?
My father is
A huge gambling guy
I took on a loan from a dangerous loan shark dealer.
Kazuhiko became the co-guarantor for the debt.
(Kawashima) The previous one was a classmate of my father.
Still, the previous generation said, "I hope you'll be openly at work."
"Please look forward to Kazuya" →
Sorry
In that way
I protected the company
To keep the Yakuza closer to the company
Living quietly
It's the same thing that's gone
I caused trouble to you →
That fact remains unchanged
Forget everything
Well then
Would you not do it together?
Shouldn't we do it together again?
It's just now
I want a craftsman who is knowledgeable about insulation.
It's a hassle to search
Shall we do it together?
thank you
president
good
Remove me from all staff?
(Chiga) Ah, sorry, but can you do that?
That's... That's too much
Rumors are spreading everywhere that he lost the Meat Housing trial.
You seriously undermined the trust of the agency.
That's... I only need the ones who can win
It's fine now
Uzaki What is that face so creepy, grinning
Well, I think we've come to feel like a team too
I'm feeling good about Todoroki-san Uzaki
Isn't it okay? In fact, I'm starting to look like a lawyer at my office.
Well, little Todoroki
I might have been better off going here
Uzaki I don't think so yet
Don't say that, Inoo
Huh? I just called you "Ino-san"
Don't say hard things, Inoo
Why did you put on Uzaki? It's a kind of outside training
Are you impersonating an employee? Tax audits can be called psychological warfare
Maybe it's going to be a card that will drop the soundtrack, so win no matter what.
This is your chance to cut off the mayor who was involved in covering up the bus accident.