=Our Days=
(Adapted from Lang Lang's original novel
"The Prime of the Goddess")
=Episode 24=
Please come out with me.
Ms. Xiang Qian,
please come outside with me.
What do you mean by that?
You are bullying her.
I bully her?
She came to my office suddenly
and scolded me,
and last night
you criticized me too.
I didn't write any anonymous letter.
I didn't do it,
so I have to get to the bottom of this.
Is this your attitude
of clarifying things?
You're just trying
to set a trap for her.
Alright.
If you have any proof
that I wrote the anonymous letter,
I'll take full responsibility.
But, what if it was not me?
Under the condition
of you not having any proof,
you randomly
accused me, slandered me,
and hurt me.
Don't you have to take responsibility?
Fine.
So, what do you plan to do?
Sue her?
She's lost everything.
Do you have to kick her when she's down?
Don't you have
any basic kindness left?
What unkind thing
did I do?
Do I deserve this slander and harm?
At least...
At least you haven't suffered
any big losses, right?
What do you want me to lose then?
Fine,
you want to sue, right?
Sue me too.
If you feel I've accused you,
or I've slandered you,
take your phone out now, record my words,
and use this recording to sue me.
Record it now.
Gao Ping,
I'm still your wife.
Something like this happens,
instead of supporting me,
you're defending an outsider.
Do you think it's appropriate?
I'm not defending anyone.
I just care about right and wrong.
Go ahead with the recording.
I, Gao Ping,
last night, when I didn't
have any evidence,
I asked Ms. Xiang Qian
why she'd write an anonymous letter
to frame Li Shu.
Are you satisfied?
Get ready for the meeting.
What's wrong with you?
My stomach hurts.
Are you okay?
I'll take some medicine for now.
Why does it hurt so much?
Are you okay?
Should we go to the hospital?
No, I'll take some medicine first.
Yuanyuan!
Come.
What's up?
Later, you help
to present the project to the clients.
I'll take Xiang Qian to the hospital.
Alright.
Don't be stubborn. Let's go.
Let's go.
Why are you wearing the high heels?
What is the purpose?
Did you go on a date?
No,
I was just trying
to scare someone this morning.
Scare someone?
So, do you feel upset for me?
Of course, I do.
Let's go get some good food.
Alright, we go now.
I don't want to go now.
My head still hurts.
Let's go home then.
I'll cook for you later.
How are you feeling?
Much better now.
It was a stomach spasm.
If you're sick and need to go
to the hospital,
you can just tell me directly.
You don't have to let Chai Jin call me.
My own wife is sick,
and I had to hear it from another man.
What do you think
people would say about me?
Why do you care so much
about what others think?
Yes, I care a lot.
I told you before,
I don't like people
gossiping behind my back.
And, I don't like you
using others to put pressure on me.
You come to the hospital,
I come to see you.
Isn't that normal?
So, you think
I asked Chai Jin to call you
and force you to come here?
Stop it there.
I didn't come here to argue.
If you are willing,
you can stay here as my family
and keep me company,
or go pick up the kids.
If you're not willing,
you can leave right now.
You don't have to stay here.
I go pick up the kids.
You have such a serious stomach pain.
Who's giving you
so much mental pressure?
Could it be Dr. Gao again?
What's going on
with you and Gao Ping?
A few days ago, a lady
came looking for you at the office.
Does she have something to do with him?
Are they having an affair?
Xiang Qian,
we've been friends for so many years.
There's no need for you
to hide this from me.
I
haven't found any solid proof.
I asked Gao Ping,
but he won't admit it.
He says I'm overly suspicious, sensitive,
and giving him too much pressure.
Overly suspicious?
Do you seem like a resentful wife?
Am I?
Maybe.
Don't worry.
I'll find someone
to help you check it out.
No need.
Let him finish his thesis defense first.
Don't bring this up with me now.
Speaking of this makes my stomach hurt.
At this moment, Rainbow Dove's dad
seemed to suddenly lose his temper,
charging towards Rainbow Dove
and pressing his entire body
against his son.
Rainbow Dove was startled
by the sudden attack,
and accidentally
slipped off the wall.
But, at the very moment of his fall,
Rainbow Dove's wings
spread out, and he flew up.
He flew up!
Amazing!
Cong, Qi.
Mum, mum.
You're back!
Dad is telling us a story.
Yeah,
dad's storytelling is great!
You're back.
You probably can't imagine
how excited and thrilled I was,
watching all of this from the side.
Li Shu has done her abortion,
and I took the opportunity
to do a paternity test.
That child has no
biological connection to me.
Regarding this matter
between me and Li Shu,
this is the last time I'm explaining this.
What is your intention?
Are we going to stay separated
like this forever?
It's pointless
to keep dragging things out between us.
What do you mean by that?
Are you suggesting a divorce?
So, you are...
You're waiting for me to say it?
Yes,
because I'm not in a position to say it.
Still scrolling on your phone.
Here's some milk for you.
Drink it and go to sleep.
Alright.
Stop scrolling on it.
What are you reading?
Read this.
(A commuting woman found dead after going missing
post-work, rideshare driver now under suspicion.)
Lost contact.
This is terrifying.
Why are you reading this?
Call Xiang Zhong now.
Don't overreact to it, and scare her.
I'm not overreacting.
She works late.
Call her now.
Don't simply believe the rumors.
What does this have
to do with Xiang Zhong?
Are you going to call her or not?
You...
If you make a call, Xiang Zhong...
I dialed Xiang Qian by mistake.
Don't say anything.
Hello, the number you dialed
is currently unavailable.
Something's wrong.
What's wrong?
Why...
Why can't we reach her?
You try to listen to it.
Hello, the number you dialed
is currently unavailable.
What's going on?
I have no idea.
This...
Let's stop guessing. We should hurry up.
We need to go check on her.
My shoes.
I'll get them for you.
Don't rush.
Xiang!
It's late now.
Where are you going?
I'll explain when I get back later.
Xiang Zhong.
Stop knocking.
Call her again.
Try calling Xiang Zhong again.
I tell you,
we need to make a police report now.
Make a police report?
She's missing.
Other than making a report,
what else can we do?
Make...
But it hasn't been 24 hours yet.
They...
They might not even file a report.
Oh yeah!
Doesn't Haiyang have a childhood friend
who's a cop?
Call him.
Haiyang...
But they're already divorced,
does it matter?
She's already missing!
Nothing else matters right now!
Just call him.
This...
You...
We're disturbing him.
That's fine.
He's here.
That's Haiyang's car.
Hurry up!
Haiyang.
Stay calm.
Here,
listen to me.
Here's the situation.
I had a friend
check the surveillance footage.
Xiang Zhong left
Huaqiao Subway Station at 10:10 PM,
but then she went back in.
We haven't seen her since.
That's all the information I obtained.
She went back in?
But...
The subway doesn't operate
anymore at this hour.
Where could she have gone?
Alright. No need for change.
Will anything happen to her?
You...
- What could happen?
- Don't worry.
Nothing will happen.
Both of you go back first.
I'll go check again.
No, Haiyang,
I'll go with you.
Dad, Mum!
You...
Why are you here?
What's going on?
Why aren't you answering your phone?
We were so worried!
Where have you been?
Why couldn't we reach you?
Oh, I...
I realized I lost my phone
after leaving the subway,
so I went back to look for it.
Where's your phone then?
I was too tired
and fell asleep on the way.
I don't know where I lost it.
So you lost your phone?
If it's lost, just let it go. You are...
If it's lost,
just ignore it.
You...
I have to find it if it's lost.
Dad, Mum, don't worry.
As long as she's back safely,
that's what matters,
right?
Hold on.
Why are you still
calling them Dad and Mum?
We're divorced.
It's not appropriate.
But
Haiyang has been calling us
that way for so long.
He's used to it.
It takes time for him...
That's not the case.
We're already divorced.
He shouldn't call you that way.
He's used to it already.
It's been a very long time.
There are no outsiders here.
He should change it.
But, you should give
him time to change it.
I can't tolerate it.
- Yeah, you're right.
- Let him change.
Yeah, you're right.
What makes you uncomfortable?
She's right.
Mum, don't worry. Oops...
It's fine.
My god.
Uncle, Auntie,
it's late now.
Let me take you home.
It's too dangerous to take a tricycle.
No, no need.
My dad and mum will stay here tonight.
No.
Wait, your mum and I
can go back by our tricycle.
It's late now. Let's go inside.
Deng Haiyang, what's wrong with you?
You overreacted,
and called my parents here.
It's us who called him.
We called him.
Haiyang, you take a good rest.
No problem. I will.
Be careful on the road.
Don't worry.
Sorry for the trouble.
No trouble at all.
You just watched too many dramas.
Stop watching all those things online.
What do you mean by that?
You should stop reading
all that nonsense online.
I can't go missing.
Take care.
Haiyang,
be safe on your way home.
Alright.
Alright, go in.
Why are you like this?
Why did you come out late at night?
If you come out at this late hour,
I couldn't relax as well.
Alright.
Listen, from now on,
don't involve Deng Haiyang
in my matters.
We...
We just
had no choice.
We were worried.
Well, no matter what,
don't call him again.
What's the matter?
I'm an adult.
I'm not going to go missing.
You see...
You come home too late.
It's very dangerous.
Didn't you come across the news?
These days, young women
go missing after work.
By the time they're found,
it's often too late.
Alright, stop it.
Don't say things like that.
It's too grim.
Don't tell her that.
I'm just warning her to be cautious.
It will scare her,
and she'll be even more worried.
She'll be more vigilant then.
Alright, stop it!
I got it!
I'll be careful.
She thinks we're being too controlling.
It's just that we called Deng Haiyang,
and she wasn't happy.
That's right,
you shouldn't find Deng Haiyang.
Why are you just standing there?
Wash up and go to bed.
It’s late.
We’re not staying.
We're heading back.
We’re not staying here.
We just wanted to check on you
and make sure you’re safe.
That's right.
Why leave? It’s already so late.
Alright.
Listen, after this,
you have to come home early after work,
and don't go out at night.
When you're at home,
make sure you lock the door properly.
Alright.
She was having an overtime.
She was busy,
and not going out to have fun.
Don't work overtime after this.
Alright, I won't do it anymore.
It's fine to let them cut the bonus.
Do you think she has a choice
to say no to working overtime?
I let her come home earlier.
Stop it.
I get it. Stop nagging me.
We're leaving.
Alright.
You two be safe on the way home.
Call me
when you get home.
We'll be fine.
Lock the door properly.
Your phone was lost, wasn't it?
Oh yeah.
You're right.
We'll be fine, don't worry.
Be careful
Lock the door properly.
I'll listen outside
if you lock it properly or not.
Lock it.
Why can't you sleep again?
You haven't slept too?
I was thinking...
Maybe Xiang Zhong
should live in Shanghai.
What do you think?
Living at Xiang Qian's place
isn't appropriate.
Can't you think a little?
If Xiang Zhong moves to Shanghai,
she can stay alone too.
But, we can't afford
to buy a house in Shanghai.
Well.
It's difficult discussing
anything with you
when you're half-asleep.
You're really...
Sleep faster.
Fine, I sleep.
If only our three daughters
could be like you...
Zhong.
Good morning.
Here,
you should keep the car for yourself.
I parked it at the lot over there.
I...
Forget it. I'm not good at driving.
You have a driver's license.
You just have to get used to it,
and driving yourself
would ease your parents' minds.
Alright.
Aren't you going to the training class?
Not leaving?
I'm fine, no rush.
Otherwise,
we'd be caught
in the same subway carriage.
I wouldn't know what to talk about.
You could just not talk.
(Divorce Matters)
Hello, dad.
Alright.
Come meet me at noon.
(Divorce Matters
1. Confirm the babysitter )
(2. Confirm required documents
with Attorney Wu for child's surname change.)
Xiang Qian always listens to you.
You should...
What should I say?
When you bring it up,
she would agree with you.
Xiang Qian.
Why is mum here too?
Your dad said this is important.
Very important.
What's so important?
Go ahead and tell her.
Alright, let me start.
Xiang Zhong has been
going back and forth
between Shanghai and Kunshan,
Sometimes, she has to work overtime
and go home late.
Your dad worries about her safety.
Your mum, too, feels worried
about her safety.
What does this mean?
We thought about renting a place
near her company.
Oh my god!
The housing near her company
isn't cheap.
Let her have a look.
- Take a look.
- We already found one.
- This place.
- You see.
The window faces the sun.
This is great, right?
This place
is two subway stops
from Xiang Zhong's office
and has 24-hour security.
How much is it?
3,500 yuan.
3,500 yuan?
No way.
You both must have been swindled.
You see.
The housing near her company
starts at 5,000 yuan minimum.
No, it's 3,500 yuan.
The owner
lives abroad
and doesn't know the market,
so they don't raise the rent
and have been renting at this rate.
This room just became available.
We're so lucky.
Whether it's 3,500 yuan
or 5,000 yuan,
it's up to Xiang Zhong's will.
Am I right?
You should
ask her
if she's willing
to pay for the rent each month.
Of course, we can't let Xiang Zhong
pay for it.
We'll cover it.
Yes, exactly.
Fine.
Which agency is this?
I'll talk to them this afternoon.
No need.
Deposit and three month's rent paid.
We've already signed for it.
You already signed?
So why are you discussing it with me?
I was worried
if we didn't sign instantly,
others would have
snapped it up
immediately.
This has just become available.
I told you earlier.
Every agency
promoted using the same way.
If you don't sign,
I'll lease it to someone else.
Are you signing or not?
If you don't, there are others
waiting to proceed with the payment.
This is a proper agency,
with full documentation
for the house,
and we even video-chatted
with the owner.
Xiang Qian,
don't think we're too old
to be tricked.
Not that easy.
Do you think
paying for the rent with your pension
for Xiang Zhong
will make her live there?
You should tell her
that we already paid,
and it's non-refundable.
If she doesn't want to live there,
it'll just be left empty.
No,
just don't tell her will do.
Do you think Xiang Zhong
is that oblivious?
She'll find out in a few days.
Then, just tell her the truth.
Why don't you go yourself?
I...
You're her sister, you should say it.
Why is it always my job
to say everything?
Aren't you just creating
more conflict between us?
Fine, fine.
You won't say it, right?
We'll tell her.
Go ahead.
Why are you so stubborn
with your daughter?
Can you do that?
You'll just end up arguing with her.
Let's argue then.
We're not done talking.
Where are you going?
Where am I going?
You...
I'm going to the washroom.
My little tag-along.
Hey, mum,
doing things like this
is definitely my dad's idea.
You're just making
her feel pressured.
How could she live in the apartment?
We're just worried about her safety
and also her condition.
Have some water.
Alright, I get it.
I'll go talk to her later.
I'll go act.
You went to the washroom so fast, huh?
Have you changed your mind?
No.
Well.
There's just a little left.
Don't want it anymore.
Don't waste it.
Why do you...
Mum, mum...
Let me hail a car
to take you to the subway station.
No need.
The...
The bus is convenient.
Don't waste the money.
We're not in a hurry.
Let's go.
Send me a message when you get home.
Alright.
Xiang Qian.
I almost forget something important.
Gao Ping's defense
is this Saturday, right?
That's great!
So,
on Sunday,
let's have everyone over.
Ask Xiang Zhong and Xiang Nan
back home too.
Let's have
a family celebration for Gao Ping.
It's just an oral defense,
not graduation.
What's there to celebrate?
Even without
Gao Ping's oral defense,
you all haven't visited
in weeks.
Fine,
we'll all come.
Alright, we get to go.
Be careful.
Have a good time at work.
Xiang Qian.
What happens?
I almost forgot.
Here's the loquat syrup
your dad made for Cong!
I'm so forgetful.
Before he goes to bed,
dissolve it in warm water
for Cong.
So, he doesn't get a cough
with the changing seasons.
Alright.
Can we really leave now?
Yes, yes.
Have a good time at work.
- Be careful.
- You really...
Luckily I reminded you.
You have such a short memory.
You always forget things.
But, I still remember following you.
My little tag-along,
if I didn't remind you,
you'd probably forget me, too.
You're really forgetful.
You...
Still not here?
Welcome!
Jiaqiao!
Why are you so late?
There's a traffic congestion.
Why are you suddenly
interested in an exhibition?
I helped
organize this exhibition.
You're organizing an art exhibition?
Why? Can't I?
Do I seem that unrefined
to you?
No, I don't mean that.
Let me tell you, Xiang Nan,
I'm very passionate about art now.
Here.
This is
my business partner,
Lv Liang,
and also my dear
boyfriend.
Xiang Nan, it's been
a long time since we met.
Should we go inside and talk?
Wait a minute.
Jiaqiao,
can I talk to you alone for a second?
Sure.
You go in first.
I'll come in a while.
Jiaqiao,
do you know he's my ex?
Of course, I know.
You...
So, does he know I'm your sister-in-law?
Of course, he knows.
Oh no, what's going on here?
This is just too dramatic.
Don't you think our relationship
is a bit complicated now?
Alright, calm down.
Wait,
let me ask you,
do you still have feelings for him?
I'm married, my dear sister.
Exactly!
You don't like him anymore,
and he doesn't like you too,
so you're practically strangers now.
What's complicated about that?
But...
I...
I have nothing more to talk to you.
Xiang Nan,
where are you going?
Lv Liang is still waiting for us.
Xiang Nan.
Xiang Nan, I was wrong.
What's up?
Are you mad at me, Xiang Nan?
I meant to surprise you.
Surprise?
This is more like a shock.
You're right.
I know I oversimplified it.
Don't be mad, okay?
Can I continue then?
Fine, say it.
I'm listening.
I want to get married
with Lv Liang.
Married?
Jiang Jiaqiao,
are you serious?
Do you think your brother would agree?
That's why I'm asking for your help.
You want me to help
convince your brother?
No one can do that.
Hold on.
I meant,
could you...
Could you pretend
that you don't know Lv Liang?
Like you've never met him
and never had any relationship with him?
Hold on.
You're planning to get married,
which means we'd be
living under one roof.
We'll meet each other very often.
How to pretend?
Pretend forever?
Then, let's wait
until everything is settled down.
Okay?
Jiang Jiaqiao,
are you serious?
Do you know him well?
Are you sure you want to marry him,
and it's not just a whim?
He's different
from anyone I've ever met.
I'm very certain.
I feel like you've lost
all your sense and intelligence now.
Do you realize that?
Your mind is complete mush.
This is the so-called 'lovestruck', right?
I give up on you!
Oh my goodness!
I can't handle this.
I can't help you with this too.
Do whatever you want.
Xiang Nan,
so you agree now?
Thank you.
Love you.
Hello?
Anyone here?
Lv Liang!
Didn't you say you wouldn't meet me?
I wanted to ask,
what exactly is your intention?
I'm in my thirties.
I want to date and get married.
Is that a problem?
Lv Liang, do you love her?
Do you love her brother?
Of course.
You hesitated.
Why?
I don't need to explain myself to you.
Sorry then.
Regarding Jiaqiao,
I have nothing else
to explain to you too.
Jiaqiao is a very naive person,
and she's a lovestruck girl.
You can't take advantage of her.
Why do you think
I'm taking advantage of her?
Most of your clients
were introduced by her,
including this studio
and your exhibitions.
You're all using her resources.
Are you speaking as her family?
Or did we make things
difficult for you,
letting you feel awkward
in front of your wealthy husband?
I just don't want you to hurt her.
What makes you think I'll hurt her?
Do I need to remind you who you are?
Back at that time,
I just borrowed ideas from Xu Miao
for my own graduation project.
How can you make it sound so pleasant?
That's plagiarism.
Fine.
Even if it's plagiarism,
there's no need
to judge me forever over it.
Drinking so much coffee.
Can your heart take it?
Have some of this instead,
for the vitamin C.
I'm tired.
Didn't sleep well again last night?
It seems that I have reached the age
that the sleep quality becomes terrible.
I remember you saying
you'd take time off
after Dr. Gao graduates.
Will you still take it?
Yeah, I am.
Then, submit your leave request
to me today.
Alright.
(Leave Application)
Xiang Nan,
no matter what you thought of me before,
I would never use love as a transaction.
Maybe you don't know,
but my career in Japan wasn't smooth.
Returning here, things weren't
going well either.
I was extremely depressed.
When I was at a gathering,
I met Jiaqiao.
She's someone full of enthusiasm.
She is just so contagious,
and also very proactive,
always pushing people forward.
She motivated me a lot.
Being able to have
someone who's incredibly selfless
like her is indeed difficult.
I really cherish her.
But, Jiang Hongbin
will never approve.
If I never try,
how do I know the outcome?
I can only say that you don't know him.
Lv Liang!
Lv Liang, lend me a hand.
Xiang Nan, why are you here?
Jiaqiao.
What did you buy?
Mops, dustpans,
just all the necessary stuff.
I bought all the necessary items.
Didn't I tell you I'd order these online?
You order it?
You've been saying that
for a very long time.
You always procrastinate.
Anyway, it's no trouble.
I bought them all on the way here.
Let me check it.
Let me see.
Are you okay?
I'm just kidding. Don't worry.
Oh yeah!
You can just put this over there.
I'll tidy them up later.
How strong you are!
Be careful.
Alright.
Ms. Xiang.
Did you come here
to assess him secretly?
What do you think?
Has he passed?
Jiaqiao, tell me the truth.
Did he tell you
the reason I broke up with him?
♪Something will eventually be lost♪
♪Never to be remembered♪
♪The intermittent news drifting away♪
♪And then forgotten♪
♪Who can still face life?♪
♪With the courage it gives♪
♪Whether looking down♪
♪Or holding heads high♪
♪We must stay together♪
♪Walking through the cool night breeze♪
♪Leaving not a trace of sadness♪
♪Those nights returning to moonlight♪
♪There will be someone thinking of you♪
♪Treading a path of stars and seas♪
♪Passing through the dawn♪
♪A familiar piece♪
♪A strange piece♪
♪All are fleeting encounters♪
♪Amid the midnight glimmer♪
♪Questioning the ordinary♪
♪Hands left empty
after struggling for a lifetime♪
♪How to live happily?♪
♪Under a sky full of stars♪
♪One lamp♪
♪Two people watching over each other♪
♪Living through a time full of love♪
♪Just to be able to look
into each other's eyes♪
♪Amid the midnight glimmer♪
♪Questioning the ordinary♪
♪Hands left empty
after struggling for a lifetime♪
♪How to live happily?♪
♪Under a sky full of stars♪
♪One lamp♪
♪Two people watching over each other♪
♪Living through a time full of love♪
♪Just to be able to look
into each other's eyes♪