=Our Days=
(Adapted from Lang Lang's original novel
"The Prime of the Goddess")
=Episode 19=
Got it, it's open.
Okay, thanks.
There's someone at home.
This elderly has dementia.
She can't open the door.
Who did you say have dementia?
You.
Okay, since you paid,
I'm going to go.
Thanks.
Hey, you...
Pretty strong, huh?
That darn old witch.
Bai Lifang, you have two choices.
One, I throw your things out.
Or two, you move out of here.
Put my things back in the room.
I'm sleeping there.
What are you doing?
I'm telling you right now.
Get out of my house!
This house belongs to Deng Haiyang.
I have every right to stay.
Why does it belong to Deng Haiyang?
My parents paid 60 percent
of the down payment.
I paid more than half
of the monthly payments.
With Deng Haiyang's lousy salary,
he couldn't even afford
half the bathroom!
Tell me, how does that
make it your house?
You paid the monthly payments, huh?
If I hadn't helped you get the job,
where would you have the money to pay?
That lousy job?
You think I'm happy to do it?
Do it then.
Right now, this moment, quit the job.
Okay, I will.
Get out.
I...
In your dreams.
If I leave,
you're going to hog this house.
Listen up, Xiang Zhong.
I don't care if you quit your job.
As long as you want a divorce,
it's not up to you to decide
who gets the house.
It's also not up to you
whether I stay
or leave.
Okay.
You listen to me.
Very soon,
someone's going to help you leave.
Sure, I'm waiting for it.
Let me see what you have.
Hello, officers.
Who's Xiang Zhong?
That's me.
Did you call the police?
Yes, I did.
What's the situation?
Let's talk inside.
Look.
There's this old lady in my house,
but I don't know her.
She seems to be mad
and refuses to leave.
Okay.
Wait a second, please.
Mr. Officer.
Listen,
you can't take her word for it.
You know,
you have to investigate
the truth, right?
Let's be reasonable.
- It's about reason.
- Yes.
Right?
Officers.
Look, this is my ID card,
household registration permit
and my house ownership card.
My name
is written on the ownership card.
This is my house.
Officer,
don't listen to her nonsense.
I am her mother-in-law.
I'm here to see my son.
I have a right to be here.
Please show us your ID.
Here.
My name.
My ID card.
The household registration permit
only has the names
Xiang Zhong and Deng Haiyang.
Your name isn't on it.
How can you prove
you two's relationship?
Deng Haiyang.
That's my son.
Where is he?
He... He's in the hospital.
We need proof
to show he's your son.
Wait.
I gave birth to him.
How do you want me to prove it?
Ma'am,
this is normal
police procedure.
Please understand.
I'll call him.
Make a record.
I'm calling him now.
Pick up.
He's not answering.
Hello.
The number you have dialed
cannot be reached.
(Bai Lifang)
Mr. Officer.
Why would I have her number
if I didn't know her?
You have Xiang Zhong's number,
but that doesn't prove
you're Deng Haiyang's mother.
What?
Officer,
are you telling me to go home
and look for my son's birth certificate?
Is that what you're saying?
Go on then.
Officer,
take a look at this.
You want to make a scene?
Talking nonsense,
writing posters, are you? Fine.
Head to the streets,...
That's you two in the video, right?
That's me, yes.
If what the video shows is true,
and
you can prove
that you're Deng Haiyang's mother,
then this will be
considered as a domestic dispute.
The solution is for you two
to calm yourselves down
and have a proper talk.
I can't talk to her.
Is either of you hurt?
Hurt? Who got hurt?
No one is hurt. Everybody's fine.
Are you hurt?
No.
In this situation,
we're hoping you two
could sit down
and sort through the misunderstandings.
If need be,
you could ask other family members
or friends
to be the facilitator.
There are also social workers
or neighborhood committee
that can provide counseling.
Yes,
feel free to approach us.
As for
the house occupation,
we hope you two
can resolve it reasonably.
In such a case,
we can't simply
apprehend anyone.
Right?
Here, have a read.
If it's okay,
please sign your name.
Here is your ID card.
I'll say it again.
You're family.
Why make the relationship so awkward,
right?
Talk to each other.
That wraps it up.
We'll go now.
Thank you.
Your things are here.
Thanks for coming.
Victory.
You're still too green to beat me.
Let's see who beats who in the end.
Lock it.
Lock it properly.
Lock all the doors.
Every single one.
I'm going to stay here
even if you look everything.
Let's see how long you can last.
Driver! Driver!
Li Shu.
Mrs. Gao.
You just got off work?
I can take you to
the subway station on the way.
It's okay.
The bus will be here soon.
Get in.
I'd like to talk to you.
Mrs. Gao.
I know you're busy with work.
I just want to say,
if you have the time,
you should show more concern
to Gao Ping.
Did he
drink a lot last night?
Last night, Dayuan treated us to dinner.
He officially signed
a tripartite residency agreement.
I mean, Dayuan
isn't as skilled as Gao Ping,
nor is he as nice.
We all thought
it was unfair.
Our department is well equipped
with both hardware
and software.
For someone as talented as Gao Ping,
if he had gotten the residency,
he would've achieved a lot more.
It's too bad.
Gao Ping might say it doesn't matter.
But I'm sure
he's upset about it.
Mrs. Gao,
you can drop me by the roadside.
I can cross the road.
Xiang Qian.
Did you want to talk to me
because you wanted me to leave?
Li Shu,
I'd like to thank you
for tutoring my kids.
Thank you for your concern for Gao Ping.
And thank you for liking the kids.
But for me,
I don't really like it
when there are
too many surprises in my life.
I'm just
a very normal person.
What I want is a quiet, uneventful life.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Just the same,
I'd like to thank you.
Thank you for accepting me.
I really enjoyed
the time I spent at your house.
I really like your family.
I'll be off then, Mrs. Gao.
Bye-bye.
Thank you.
You spoke to Li Shu?
I'll look for a male junior
after this.
Less problems.
Why did you look
for Li Shu in the first place then?
Because she showed a lot of interest.
And she was serious.
But most importantly,
I thought she was a lot like me.
We're trying to change our destiny
with our own hands.
Maybe that's the reason why
I'm biased toward her.
More importantly,
I hope...
I don't want you to pity her.
Because I believe
she's like me.
We hate being pitied.
Xiang Qian.
I'm already over 30.
I know the kind of person I am.
And I know what it is I want.
Have a bit more trust in me, okay?
Yu, I need a bucket of sand!
I need more bricks too.
Coming!
What are you people doing?
This is my house.
Who asked you to do this?
Stop it!
Give way.
- Mister.
- Stop building!
Stop the work.
Stop.
This is the boundary wall,
clear as day.
You won't let me use the bathroom
and kitchen, right?
Then you can forget leaving
through the main door.
Tear it down!
Are you superwoman?
Just you wait.
You think I can't climb
over it?
Are you coming out?
Very good.
Come, I'll give you a hand.
Come out.
Get out of my way!
Look.
See how nice it is to be out here?
You could jump.
But if you jumped and got hurt,
you'd have to pay
for the medical bills yourself.
It's none of my business.
Come on, I'll help you.
Listen.
If you don't come out,
you'll be walled in.
You can't blame me
for not telling you sooner.
Are you stuck?
Okay.
If you're so smart,
I suppose you don't have
to use the bathroom, ever.
I can hold it in.
Come on
Right,
you could try
and call 110 again.
Call the police to come.
See what they'd do about it.
You old hag.
You're despicable!
Stop building the wall!
This is my house!
I'm filing a complaint!
Go ahead.
Better watch your backs!
Misters, continue.
Hold on, mister.
Yes.
Here's what to do.
After you finish...
After you break the window,
I need you to build me some steps.
Okay, no problem.
If you could add an awning on top,
that would make it easier for me.
Thanks.
Stop the work!
- Miss!
- Stop the work!
What's wrong?
Any renovations
must be submitted
to the building management.
Then submit a request
for me.
It has to be approved first
before work can commence.
But this is my courtyard.
It's not affecting other people.
Someone's building a wall in my house.
Why aren't you checking that?
We'll go and take a look in front.
Hurry up then.
Let's go.
Please continue, mister. Thanks.
Okay, will do.
Do a good job, please.
Sure, no problem.
Take care.
I'm building a wall in my own house.
That's not against the rules, right?
No, it's not.
If there's a problem between you two,
you can ask the neighborhood committee
to conduct mediation.
There's no need to go to such extreme.
If I'm being extreme,
it's because she made me.
She called the police the last time.
You were here too, right?
This can't be mediated.
Besides,
she locked the bathroom
and kitchen doors
to prevent me
from using.
So why should I let her use
the main door?
No way.
Mister.
Please stack it up
all the way to this height.
Block it completely.
Hang on a minute, ma'am.
Let me talk to her.
Come on.
Hey.
Miss.
Your mother-in-law said she couldn't use
the bathroom and kitchen
because you locked them.
That's not very nice.
You do know
that my name is on the ownership card.
This is my house.
She's the one refusing to leave.
She even changed the lock.
You tell her.
Yes, okay.
I'll talk to her.
Your daughter-in-law said
her name is on the ownership card.
This is her house.
So... she has the right to stay.
This is my son's house.
Why can't I stay here?
Right, okay.
Go ask her.
What kind of mother-in-law
stays with the son
without first asking
the daughter-in-law?
It's not like I didn't want
to ask the daughter-in-law.
But look at her.
Is she a qualified daughter-in-law?
Sure, I'm not qualified.
In her eyes, no one is qualified.
No one is good enough for his son.
Are you a qualified mother-in-law then?
Gosh...
This is between you two.
Don't make it difficult for us.
Go tell her.
If she tears down the wall,
I'll stop the construction.
Ask her to move out.
Then I'll tear it down.
There's no way.
If anyone is to move, it'd be her.
This is my house.
No way.
I'm not moving.
I will never move.
Wait, I need a break.
Here.
Thanks.
Are you married?
No.
You still want to?
Yes.
Morning, pretties.
Good morning.
Morning.
Xiang Nan.
I went to my rent today
but the management said it's been paid.
Jiang probably paid it.
That's great.
But, Xiang Nan,
aren't you going to double down
on your stance
with Jiang?
Double down?
Why would she do that?
Why be enemies with money?
Am I right?
Alright, don't let it get to you.
Just accept reality.
Time to work.
Xiang Nan.
Hello?
Your dad left the hospital again.
I happened to run into him.
He said he's going to Xiang Zhong's.
I got Wang to go pick you up.
We should go and take a look.
Okay.
Excuse me, please make way. Thanks.
We are from the TV station.
Cameraman!
Why are there so many people?
What's going on?
Even a TV reporter
showed up?
Is Xiang Zhong inside?
I'll... I'll call her.
You two, wait for me here.
I'll go check it out.
No, stop.
Stay put.
I'll go and take a look, okay?
I'll check it out first.
You can't go by yourself.
We came...
We're already here.
No, don't. Listen to me.
Let me get a hold of Zhong
and find out
what's going on.
Okay, Mom?
Look after Dad.
Make sure he doesn't get involved
in case he hurt his back again.
I'll go and take a look.
You two stay here.
Be careful, you hear?
Zhong, what's going on?
There's a crowd
in front of your house.
I'm going over.
Stay here!
I'm going to take a look.
Xiang Nan told you to stay put.
Just listen to her.
You listen up.
I have to see what's up.
What is your problem? Hey!
Did you just hit me?
You...
Listen.
Call Xiang Qian.
Ask her to come. You stay here.
Fine, okay.
I'll call her.
Stop shooting.
Sorry, excuse me.
Excuse me.
This is my place.
Stop shooting!
Sorry.
The number you've dialed cannot...
Don't pass it to me.
Just leave her a message.
Okay, here.
Xiang Qian. Xiang Qian!
Call us back.
No.
Xiang Qian.
We are at Xiang Zhong's.
No need to call back.
Just get over here.
Right away.
Call us back. Call us!
Get over here!
Call us back!
Call us, okay.
Stop shooting. Break it up.
As you were, people.
Go back home and eat.
Stop shooting. There's nothing to see.
Are you people
that interested
in such a trivial matter?
Break it up.
You there, stop filming.
Please leave.
Thanks for your cooperation.
Go on, break it up.
This is a family matter.
Don't be a busybody.
Go, leave, stop shooting.
According to the "Residential Interior
Design and Renovation Measures,"
Article 5, Clause 3,
It is prohibited to expand
the original door
and window sizes
on the load-bearing wall,
or demolish the brick balcony
and concrete walls.
If there is any violation,
the competent department
may order rectification
in accordance with Article 69
of the "Construction Project Quality
Management Regulations"
and impose a fine of not less
than 50,000 yuan
and not more than 100,000 yuan.
She only demolished a wall.
Isn't the fine too much?
It's against the rules,
hence the fine.
Okay, okay, no need
to lay it out for me.
I'll just close it back up.
Xiang Zhong,
come back and stay with us for now.
No thanks.
That's my house.
Why should I let
someone else stay in it?
So you're you going
to climb up and down every day?
I can climb. Treat it like a workout.
Listen.
Your divorce case
and property dispute
will take another half a year.
Are you going to climb through windows
for six months?
I can climb for six months.
Even years.
I'm sure
I can take that old hag down.
That's enough.
No taking down anyone.
Anyway,
since Xiang Qian and Xiang Nan are here,
I have something I'd like
to discuss with you all.
If Haiyang's family
insist on getting the house,
we'll let them have it.
I don't agree.
That's my house.
No...
Let me speak.
That old hag is a lunatic.
We won't be like her.
Just get the divorce formalized.
Previously, she caused a scene
at your office.
Now she's making a mess
of the house.
Who knows
what she's going to do tomorrow?
She's a lunatic? So am I.
Let's see who bests who.
Okay, okay.
Don't be crazy now.
Don't be crazy, you hear?
You keep doing this,
who...
who's going to marry you next time?
Do you care about having a family?
I mean,
how do you expect to continue
living in Kunshan?
Hang on.
Why do I have to get married again?
Can I not be married?
Must I stay in Kunshan?
Where do you want to go then?
I have something
to tell you guys too.
I submitted my resignation letter.
Deng Haiyang's mom
kept using the job as a reason
to cut me down,
saying she's the one who got me the job.
I got in because I passed the interview.
What did it have to do with her?
Xiang Zhong,
don't you ever think of the outcome
before you do something?
Of course I do.
You're quitting
such a good job.
Where else do you expect
to find something better?
I've long been tired of this job.
What?
You think I can't find another job?
Am I that lousy?
You're over 30 years old.
Are you...
You need to have a backup plan!
Okay, let's all calm down.
Calm yourselves down.
You listen to me!
Go back there
and take back
the resignation letter!
You just think I'm incapable.
I'm not well educated,
I have no skills.
I'm just a good-for-nothing, right?
Don't say that.
Dad is just thinking for your sake.
None of you are putting yourself
in my shoes.
Why can't you
respect my decision?
Why can't you support me?
It's like you're forcing me
to stay in Kunshan.
Hey,
watch what you're saying.
No one is forcing you
to stay in Kunshan.
You went to university
in Changchun, didn't you?
After graduating,
you wanted to work in Beijing,
and we all supported you.
It was your choice
to come back to Kunshan.
I...
It's Deng Haiyang's fault.
Let's not start
shifting blame, Xiang Zhong.
Right now, you're not
a fresh graduate.
You're not starting from zero.
You've been working for years.
Now suddenly
you say you're quitting
and want to try other things?
The society is cruel.
You're going to have
to face so many challenges.
Dad is just worried for you, you know?
Fine.
Don't you worry.
Even if I get a job outside,
become a dishwasher,
I won't ask you guys
for money.
Zhong,
nowadays there are dishwashers.
They don't need you.
Shut your trap!
I just don't want her
to go wash dishes...
- Xiang Zhong!
- Hey...
Xiang Zhong!
Xiang...
Xiang Qian, this is...
I know, I know.
Xiang Qian.
I'll go. Oh, right.
Xiang Nan, come with me.
Bring your bag.
Wait...
Hurry up, Xiang Nan.
I didn't get to eat.
Zhong.
Are you sure you want to quit?
Yeah,
even if Deng Haiyang's mom
didn't complain,
I would've still resigned.
The work just feels meaningless.
There's no future.
I don't want to just get by.
Xiang Zhong.
How much do you have in your savings?
Why?
You know,
just wanted to remind you.
That mother-in-law of yours.
She's an elderly woman.
She's a retiree living off her pension.
As for you?
You're quitting your job,
and you want to hold the fort at home.
How long can you last?
I'm not dumb.
I'm going to start applying for jobs.
Where at?
I'm thinking
to do we-media that is related
to geography.
I don't really get it,
but I think you'll be good at it.
At least, it's better
than the current job.
Go then. Just do it.
Xiang Nan, help your second sister
prepare an eye-catching resume.
Didn't someone say something about
the immense work pressure
in the current society?
A person my age
would have trouble finding a job.
Xiang Zhong,
could you maybe take into consideration
my position in the family?
You want me to stand on your side
and argue with Dad?
What if they get a heart attack?
Whatever it is,
go forth and prosper, Zhong.
I'll take care of the resume for you.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Zhong.
I'm not sure if you remember.
The day
Mom and Dad brought you home.
I got home from school,
reached the front door,
and saw Dad and Mom
holding a little skinny
and dark girl
waiting for me at the door.
When I went over,
Dad said,
go on, call her big sister.
But she refused.
Really?
Then, he turned to me and said,
Xiang Qian.
From now on, you are the big sister
in this household.
You're responsible
in looking after
your two younger sisters.
When I heard that...
I was only a teenager.
I never said I wanted to take on
the responsibility.
The second year after you came home,
I'm not sure if you remember it.
You definitely won't remember.
You were still suckling at the time.
Dad and Mom
worked Monday to Friday.
On the weekends,
they'd set up a stall
at the park entrance.
They'd sell gloves, scarves
and what not.
Just so that
they could give us a better life.
One dark, cloudy day,
I brought umbrellas for them.
Then whoosh,
a strong gust of wind.
And I saw
Mom and Dad frantically
grabbing at the scarves
and gloves,
worried about losing one.
It was...
When I saw that scene,
I thought to myself.
What can I do
to help lighten their load?
That's why
you turned into a little class monitor
keeping us in check.
After we finished school,
you'd plan our daily rosters,
- remember that?
- Yeah.
Qian, you might not know.
Back then, Zhong and I
were pretty scared of you.
Mostly because you were so strict.
You'd check our homework every day.
You were more strict
than our teachers in school.
It's my first time
being the oldest sibling,
okay?
Who likes being the oldest?
How am I supposed to know
how to be the oldest?
The most common phrase
I hear is,
you're the oldest.
You have to be the role model.
You're the oldest.
You have to be
a role model for the other two.
What kind of role model?
No idea.
Seriously,
if not for you two,
I doubt
I would've studied as hard
when I was young.
Back then, I even took part
in the class leader election.
So,
you should thank us.
We were the ones who inspired you
to become a better version of yourself.
Thank you.
Yeah, thank you guys so much.
You're welcome.
It's what we do.
It was exhausting.
Why am I
telling you two this?
It's mainly spoken to Xiang Zhong.
Seriously,
if you two had seen
with me
how Dad and Mom were scrambling
in the wind,
you'd understand.
Now, you.
You're impatient and stubborn.
Who did you take after?
None other than Dad.
You've known him for 30 over years.
You should know how he is.
When he gets triggered
and starts nagging,
just keep quiet.
Right? He's only doing it for your sake.
Once he calms down,
it's all good, no?
Why must you talk back?
There's no point
in arguing,
am I right?
Besides,
they're worried
you resigned out of spite.
You know?
That you're digging your own grave.
But to me,
whether or not it's irrational,
just go ahead.
This time,
I have your back.
I support you.
I support you too.
You're a copycat.
Am I?
(Dearest, give me a bit more time. Very soon, I'll be divorced.)
(It'll be too late if it's not done by July. It won't take that long!)
What's the matter, Aunty?
Be careful.
I'm going to a resort
in Suzhou with my mentor
to go over my research.
Okay.
So...
Is Li Shu, that young lady, going too?
Gao Ping.
Despite my lack of education,
I know that
people can't be without conscience.
What are you talking about?
I'm just joking around with a friend.
Don't take it seriously.
And don't mention this
to Xiang Qian.
I know what I'm doing.
Mommy.
I did really well
in school today.
Teacher gave us
a little star.
Mommy.
I also did really well
in school today.
Teacher also praised me
and gave me a star.
Really?
Good job, you two.
Let Mommy wash my hands first.
There are germs outside.
Once I'm clean,
you can show me your stars,
okay? Come on then.
Okay.
What's that smell, Aunty?
I forgot.
I couldn't smell it at all.
You should keep watch
when you're boiling soup.
Or use the timer?
You don't seem to use it much.
Right.
I'll pay more attention next time.
My nose
couldn't pick up the smell.
It'd be too late if there was a smell.
The pot would've burned.
Yes.
What are we having tonight?
I cooked rice.
I forgot to plug it in.
Why am I so absent-minded?
Aunty.
Did something happen
back home?
You're not usually this careless.
It's nothing.
If you need anything,
don't hesitate to tell me or Gao Ping.
We'll do our best to help.
Gao Ping is...
What's up with Gao Ping?
Xiang Qian,
I want to go back.
Fang Yuan can't look after himself.
He has stomach problems.
I was going to talk to you
about it.
But I know
you need a caretaker,
someone to help out at home.
I felt bad about bringing it up.
Is it serious?
We don't know yet.
We're waiting for the report.
When you get the report,
and if it's serious,
maybe you can get him treated
in Shanghai.
There's no need.
Aunty, look.
We just started finding our rhythm
but you're leaving.
I'm quite sad about it.
But if...
you really want to go back,
let me talk to Gao Ping
tonight first.
And give us a few days
to find a replacement.
Okay?
Because the day after tomorrow...
Tomorrow and the day after,
I have to go meet clients.
I'll be busy.
It's okay with me.
Okay.
Would be best if you didn't leave.
Let me see your little stars.
There are three more here.
Here too.
Yes, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
Ms. Liu.
Whose luggage are those?
They're...
Whose? Tell me.
We're not sure.
You're not sure?
Li.
Is someone coming?
Mavis' mother is here.
Looks better than in photos.
What?
Too many gold elements.
The color of the curtains is not right.
Are you
Mavis' mother?
I'm Xu Sumin.
You can call me Elena.
Okay.
Ms. Xu,
are you planning to stay here?
Jiang didn't mention it to me.
He's been informed.
Ms. He.
Don't leave the luggage around.
Put them away.
Where should we put the luggage, madam?
In the bedroom.
Yeah, put them away
in the guest bedroom.
In the master bedroom.
Wait, I'm sorry.
The master bedroom
is where Jiang Hongbin and I stay.
I don't think it's appropriate
for you to use.
Young lady.
Without me,
Jiang Hongbin wouldn't be
where he is today.
And there wouldn't even be you.
So tell me,
is it appropriate for me
to use the master bedroom?
Bring my things up.
You guys wait here.
Hello.
The number you've dialed
is currently in use.
Jiang, what's the deal?
Your ex-wife is here.
You never said anything to me.
The cuckoo is taking over
the magpie's nest.
You need to get back home.
What do we do with the bags?
Yeah.
Take the lift to the second floor.
Go.
Good views.
Ample sunlight.
Pretty wife.
Pretty good for Jiang Hongbin.
Seems like he has
his life under control.
Ms. Xu.
Ms. He.
Come here, I'll tell you what to do.
I want all new bedding.
Clear the bathroom and closet
of all miscellaneous items.
You worked for me a long time.
You know what I'm like.
I'm a germaphobe.
Ms. He,
take the bags down.
To where exactly?
If you're unsure
how to address me,
you don't have to force yourself.
Go downstairs and make yourself
a cup of coffee
to cool off.
Ms. Xu,
let me remind you.
I don't care about your past
with Jiang Hongbin.
You two are divorced.
This
is my house, my property.
Where you are now
is my bedroom.
Please leave.
Are you sure?
Are you sure this is your house?
Are you sure
your name is on the ownership card?
My guess is...
it's not.
So what right do you have
to be giving orders?
Stop gawking, Ms. He.
Put my things away.
I said, take the bags downstairs.
Put them away.
Don't move anything.
I'm cooking soup in the kitchen.
I better go check on it.
Stop right there!
Okay.
It's fine.
I'll remove your bags
myself.
I dare you to do it.
Watch me then.
Let go.
No.
Let go!
You let go.
I said, let go!
Do you hear me?
I told you. Don't touch my stuff!
You're in trouble now, you hear?
I'll make you
and Jiang Hongbin
grovel in the mud for what happened.
If you want to cause trouble,
I'm going to call the police.
We can settle this
in the police station.
The neighborhood committee
is more useful than the police
in family disputes.
You could even ask
the property management.
Make them come, the more the merrier.
I'd like to see
what that'd do to your dear Jiang.
I'm not scared.
Crazy woman.
It works.
I left the manual
in the house.
You can re-set
the passcode on your own.
Okay, got it. Thanks, mister.
You're welcome.
Call me
if there's any problem.
Will do, thanks.
You're welcome.
Xiang Zhong.
I heard
you submitted your resignation.
I had wanted to quit.
Now your mom
can stop nagging.
I don't want
to owe your family anything.
This thing blew up to this extent.
Why didn't you
call me and tell me?
Why should I call you?
Would telling you do any good?
If it did,
would the drama have lasted so long?
Okay.
What about this?
Why don't you...
Why don't you go back home
for a few days.
I'll talk to my mom.
Once this matter is resolved,
I'll call you, okay?
What?
Are you helping your mom lure the tiger
out of the den?
What are you talking about?
I'm not after the house.
I won't give it even if you asked.
Tell your mom.
She's over 60,
and I'm in my early 30s.
Who does she think can last longer?
Must you drag this out?
I'm not the one dragging this out.
It's because your mom
won't stop pestering me.
Zhong.
Xiang Zhong!
Don't...
Something will eventually be lost
Never to be remembered
The intermittent news drifting away
And then forgotten
Who can still face life?
With the courage it gives
Whether looking down
Or holding heads high
We must stay together
Walking through the cool night breeze
Leaving not a trace of sadness
Those nights returning to moonlight
There will be someone thinking of you
Treading a path of stars and seas
Passing through the dawn
A familiar piece
A strange piece
All are fleeting encounters
Amid the midnight glimmer
Questioning the ordinary
Hands left empty
after struggling for a lifetime
How to live happily?
Under a sky full of stars
One lamp
Two people watching over each other
Living through a time full of love
Just to be able to look
into each other's eyes
Amid the midnight glimmer
Questioning the ordinary
Hands left empty
after struggling for a lifetime
How to live happily?
Under a sky full of stars
One lamp
Two people watching over each other
Living through a time full of love
Just to be able to look
into each other's eyes