=Our Days=
(Adapted from Lang Lang's original novel
"The Prime of the Goddess")
=Episode 35=
(Dad, Mom,)
(there are some things
that I can't say in person,)
(so I'll just say them
in this chat group.)
(I'm going to turn myself in.)
(Previously,)
(to partner up with Hongjiang Group,)
(we had no choice
but to follow Jiang Hongbin's orders)
(and walked into the gray zone.)
(He's now using that)
(as leverage to threaten us,)
(preventing Xiang Nan
from divorcing him.)
(There's only one way out now.)
(Which is, for me to bear the mistake)
(and undergo investigation)
(as well as accept
the subsequent punishment.)
(Please look after Qi and Cong for me.)
(They will start
primary school next year.)
(I've already found a school
and will send you the details later.)
(Xiang Zhong and Xiang Nan,)
(when I'm gone,)
(do look after Mom and Dad,)
(as well as yourselves.)
(Take good care.)
Hello, Attorney Wu.
Chai Jin has turned himself in.
(Law Firm)
(You know that)
(I've grown)
(used to being carefree.)
(Whatever I do,)
(it's for my own happiness.)
(But this time,)
(I wondered what it is)
(I could do for you and your family.)
(Turns out,)
(it felt good to think for others.)
Can Chai Jin's case
be tied
to Jiang Hongbin?
According to my understanding,
Chai Jin has a voice recording
which can prove
that Jiang Hongbin
did indeed play a role in instigating
and influencing the matter.
But to use that as evidence
to indict Jiang Hongbin,
from the perspective of
an economic investigation,
it is unlikely to work.
Which means Jiang Hongbin
would not suffer any consequences.
Yes.
However,
if your sister
decides to file for a divorce,
there will be
less worry for you.
When can I go and see him?
After the court hearing.
Please let me know
if he has any requests.
Will do.
Qian.
Qian?
Xiang Nan.
Zhong.
Dad.
Where's Xiang Qian?
Come inside, quick.
Where's your sister?
Where's Xiang Qian?
I don't know where she went.
She left a note.
It said,
she prepared a file containing
Qi and Cong's information.
She left a message
for us
and also left a USB drive for Chai Jin.
I... I'm a little worried.
Is she saying
her goodbye?
I felt she was acting weird
yesterday.
And she's not answering my calls.
That child.
What's going on?
Could something have happened?
Is that her?
Qian.
Xiang Qian.
Why didn't you pick up
our calls?
I didn't hear it.
Don't tell me you're going
to take the blame
for Chai Jin?
Yes.
That's a serious matter.
You should've discussed with us first.
Discuss what?
So many things happened
within such a short time.
The longer it goes on,
the worse the situation becomes.
So what's the situation now?
Chai Jin has turned himself in.
It's my fault.
It's all because of me.
If I didn't...
If I hadn't married that man,
things wouldn't have come to this.
Hey, hey, it's not your fault.
Don't blame yourself.
Now everyone
is getting dragged into the mire.
There, there.
Who are you looking for?
I'm looking for your boss.
May I know who you are?
On paper, I'm still his father-in-law.
Mr. Jiang is not in.
He's not in?
You didn't even check,
how do you know he's not in?
I'm very sorry.
But I can't let you in.
Why is he so afraid?
Is he scared
that I'd reveal
all the dirty things he did?
Get out of my way!
I'm sorry.
We can't let you in.
Sorry, Mr. Jiang is not in.
He's really not here.
Is he not here
or is he too scared to see me?
Please calm down, sir.
How about this?
If it's something urgent,
you could give him a call.
Is that so?
Go!
Tell your boss.
If he won't see me,
I'm going to destroy this place!
No, stop!
Don't do that!
Security!
What are you people doing?
Get Jiang Hongbin out to see me!
Call him here!
Tell him to come see me!
Step aside!
Tell him to come out!
Why are you apprehending me?
You should catch that goon named Jiang!
He's evil!
Let me go! Let me go!
What are you doing?
How could you treat an elder this way?
That's not right.
Leave us.
Sorry about that.
Mr. Xiang.
There's no use making a scene here.
Go home.
What if you injured yourself?
Think about
your daughters if not for yourself.
They'd be so worried for you.
Don't come to the office again.
Dad.
Why are you guys here?
Hang on,
why are you sitting here?
I'm asking why you guys are here?
What are you doing? Have some water.
No, no water.
Listen to me.
I'm not here to make a scene.
I just want to talk to him.
I'm willing to give up our house.
Go ahead and demolish it.
I don't care.
All I'm asking is to give Xiang Nan
back to us.
Give Chai Jin back to us.
Let our family...
He should let our family go.
Give us back our peace.
You think you can resolve this
by confronting him head on?
Hurry up and take him home.
Come on, let's go.
I didn't think... My only mistake was...
I didn't expect
him to be so evil!
Yes, he's shameless.
So there's no point
in reasoning with him.
You're just hurting yourself.
Careful.
You asked for me, Mr. Jiang?
Did my father-in-law
come and make noise
in the office again?
Go and find out,
who was it that let him in.
They're fired.
Understood.
Also, make sure
this doesn't happen again.
We're in a crucial point in time.
We must not create any bad press.
Attorney Su is here.
He's waiting for you outside.
Ask him to come in.
Okay.
Mr. Jiang.
Attorney Su.
Apologies, I've been quite busy lately.
What is it you wanted to say?
Chai Jin turned himself in.
He turned himself in?
Also,
your wife has filed for a divorce.
She has the injury report
from the hospital
and a video from that night.
Together with
the previous police report,
it's not
looking good for you.
Okay.
Thanks, Attorney Wu.
Thank you.
Got it.
Bye-bye.
Attorney Wu said
Jiang Hongbin has been informed
of Chai Jin's action.
He's agreed to the divorce.
That's great.
You're finally getting what you want.
But still, we have
to think of something.
Chai Jin is still in trouble.
There's nothing we can do
about Chai Jin.
When I first found out,
I went to consult a lawyer.
Maximum three years,
minimum one.
Since he turned himself in,
I reckon
he'd get the lightest sentence.
My thought on Chai Jin is,
on the surface,
he's helping Xiang Nan with the problem,
but in fact, he's helping you, Qian.
Listen, you two have known each other
a long time.
Have you never thought about
going further?
What...
No.
Boss Chai
changes girlfriends
like changing clothes.
When I met him,
I had the feeling
that he wasn't the type
who would get married
and start a family.
Let me tell you,
people who seem like a playboy
are actually the most loyal,
most devoted.
If he had
no feelings for you,
then why did he linger
at the hotel entrance
and not go in
when you
got married to Gao Ping?
That happened?
Now I feel
even more indebted to Boss Chai.
If not because of Jiang Hongbin,
he wouldn't be detained.
Speaking of that jerk.
If all we're getting is a divorce,
isn't that letting him off too easy?
That's just unacceptable.
He did so many bad things,
he should
bear legal repercussions,
no?
Yes, yes.
That's why we're looking for evidence.
Yeah.
I wonder if Jiang Xiaotong
could be the key.
If she's willing to help me
and testify,
we'll have one more eye witness.
I doubt it.
That's her father.
But at the time,
she had risked getting hurt
trying to save me
from her dad's clutches.
I think
she has a sense of justice.
Who knows she's willing to help us?
Okay, we could give it a try.
But where is she now?
Is she awake?
I called Jiang Jiaqiao
today.
She said Xiaotong is awake.
Despite just coming around,
Jiang Hongbin immediately transferred her
to another hospital.
As to where,
she didn't tell me.
I reckon Jiang Hongbin is afraid
that I'd meet with her.
I'll ask her again.
I think, after so many years
doing business,
Jiang Hongbin must have used
dubious methods
when handling relationships.
There has to be a slip.
That's what Chai Jin said too.
But now,
I can't see him.
I don't know
where to start investigating from.
When Jiang Hongbin's ex-wife came back
and you two had an altercation,
I went to see him, remember?
This is what he said.
When they got divorced,
he gave her everything
he was supposed to.
But his ex-wife
came back again
to ask for more money.
The reason why
he gave in to her demand was because
when he was just starting out
on his business,
he relied heavily on the ex-wife's
family background.
Judging from what we know now,
Jiang Hongbin isn't
such a nostalgic person,
but a ruthless one.
Perhaps his ex-wife
has some leverage on him.
Now that you mentioned,
thinking back,
when the ex-wife
first came home,
she was carrying
a brown Birkin bag.
Later one day,
I went to Jiang Hongbin's office.
I saw him stashing away
that bag in the cabinet.
So I wanted to take a peek
and saw
something like a document folder,
a notebook
or something similar inside.
But Jiang Hongbin came
and took the bag away,
refusing to let me see.
I also remembered something else.
The day Xu Sumin went and made a scene
at my studio,
she had said that
if I dared cross her,
she'd skewer him
alive too.
But when I asked Jiang Hongbin
about it later,
he said he's lost
the condition to negotiate.
How was he... going to win?
I thought it was odd then.
Maybe she does have
dirt on Jiang Hongbin.
Something that can incriminate him.
Yes, that's very possible.
We have to find a way
to get in touch with her.
My guess is,
she doesn't even know
that Jiang Xiaotong is in the hospital.
I'll bet.
Otherwise,
she would've rushed back here.
Mr. Wang.
Madam.
Are you here to see Mr. Jiang?
No.
Well, Mr. Jiang is going out soon.
Mr. Wang,
I came to see you.
I wanted to ask you
if you know
how to contact Xu Sumin.
What...
How to contact Mr. Jiang's ex-wife?
I'm only a driver. I wouldn't know.
Mr. Wang,
you've worked for Jiang Hongbin
a long time.
Before Xiaotong came back to China,
I'm sure you helped
deliver things to her.
Maybe there's a record of the address?
Madam,
please don't put me
in a difficult position.
I'm just a driver.
I'm the sole breadwinner
for my family.
My child is going to university.
Yes, I get it.
I really do.
But I'm out of options too.
That's why I came to you.
It's not only me...
I'm not the only one
falling victim to Jiang Hongbin.
The people around me,
my family,
they've all been hurt.
My dad too.
I saw that.
It must be hard on Mr. Xiang.
So I'm really at my wit's end.
Please help me.
Madam.
Mr. Jiang is coming down.
You should leave.
Mr. Wang.
Please help me out.
I... I'm begging you.
The elevator is coming.
You should leave.
Don't make it hard for me.
Xiang Nan.
Jiaqiao.
Sit.
I ordered coffee for you.
Sorry I'm late.
It's okay.
Is your hand better?
Yeah.
It's not the first time anyway.
How are things with Lv Liang?
We didn't keep in touch.
Jiaqiao,
I asked you out today
because I wanted to ask again
if you know where Mavis
was transferred to.
Could you help me find out?
I wanted to ask you.
Why do you want to see her?
I'm hoping
she'd agree to be my eye witness.
You want to leave my brother.
I get why.
And I support you.
If I were you,
I'd also leave him.
But he is my brother.
He's my only family
in this world.
Do you know?
How did we manage
to survive over the years?
He really suffered a lot
for my sake.
I know
he's done a lot of bad things.
Xiang Nan, I'm sorry.
I... I can't do it.
I just can't.
I'm sorry.
I really can't bring myself to.
I understand.
I really want to help you. But I...
I understand, Jiaqiao.
It's okay.
Don't feel too bad.
I'm already grateful
that you agreed to see me.
I mean it.
Jiaqiao.
I forgot to give you this.
Take these. It can help fade the scars.
Don't think too much.
When I ordered them, I wasn't planning
to ask you for help.
Xiang Nan.
It's fine.
Okay.
Go on then.
It's all good.
You're back.
Zhong.
Good news.
No idea who sent us
Xu Sumin's address.
Where's Qian?
She's packing inside.
Xiang Nan is back.
Qian,
are you really going to Canada?
Yes.
What I'm worried is that
even if Xu Sumin has proof,
she won't help us.
I don't want the trip to be for nothing.
We won't know unless we go.
Besides,
is there another way?
I'll go with you then.
You'll need a visa to go.
Thankfully,
my visa hasn't expired.
I can leave right away.
Okay.
I'll keep trying
and see if I can find Jiang Xiaotong.
If she's willing to be my eye witness,
we'll have a stronger case.
No matter who you go see,
make sure Xiang Zhong is with you.
You two do it together.
I'll look after
your kids and Mom and Dad.
Don't worry about us.
Be safe.
I know Xiang Nan's case is complicated.
I'll be counting on you, Attorney Wu.
Rest assured,
I will do my best.
You'll meet with Chai Jin soon, right?
Yes.
Tell him
to take care for me.
Certainly.
Have a safe trip.
Thanks.
Xiang Qian helped prepare
some clothes
and daily necessities
for you.
I've handed them to the guard.
Thank her for me.
So,
Xiang Nan is preparing
for the divorce lawsuit, right?
The materials and evidence
are pretty much there.
We'll be filing the case
in the next few days.
Oh, right.
Xiang Qian wrote you a letter.
She asked me to pass it to you.
(Hi, Chai Jin.)
(When I picked up the pen
to write this letter,)
(I felt really overwhelmed.)
(In my head, I went over the moments)
(from when I first started working)
(to the past decade.)
(I realized that aside from knowing)
(you don't like spicy food,)
(what you like to eat,)
(what you don't like to eat,)
(I couldn't remember it.)
(It dawned on me that
over the past 10 years,)
(your care for me
greatly overshadowed my care for you.)
(I feel ashamed.)
(You've done so much for me.)
(Just saying thank you)
(is hardly enough to compensate.)
(After your sentencing,)
(I will go visit you soonest possible.)
(There are some things
that I must say to you face to face.)
(Take care.)
Qian.
Why are you two here?
We came to see you off.
I told you there's no need.
Take this.
Bring it with you.
Yeah, we got it from Hangzhou for you.
It's really effective.
You guys went to Hangzhou?
She insisted to go.
That's for ensuring safety.
Hangzhou isn't that far.
You're going to Canada.
Right,
this.
Take the melatonin.
You haven't been sleeping well, right?
This can help with any jet lag.
Oh, there's more.
This one.
Steam eye mask.
You can use it on the flight.
It's relaxing.
Take it.
I didn't know you were
so thoughtful, Xiang Zhong.
Of course I am.
Alright.
I'll be off.
Qian, be safe.
Be safe, text us when you're there.
Hey.
Tell us when you've booked
the return flight.
We'll pick you up.
Will do.
Eat proper meals.
Eat your meals on time.
Okay.
I know, I've got it.
Do not open your door at night
for strangers.
Qian!
Thank you!
We didn't manage to give her a hug.
Right.
(To Xiang Zhong)
(Xiang Nan: Zhong,)
(I'm on the way to see Jiang Jiaqiao.)
(Xiang Zhong: Okay. I'm at the hospital)
(visiting Deng Haiyang's mom.)
That man is a local developer.
Do you know him?
He's very talented.
I recently read that he's in charge
of the old town
renovation project in Kunshan.
Is that so?
♪Was just a flash in the pan♪
I don't know him.
♪Once I believed it'd be forever♪
♪Suddenly, it's already yesterday♪
♪How many things are out of reach♪
♪Tossing and turning through the night♪
♪Tears stuck in the throat♪
♪Eyes moistened♪
♪In the end, everything fades with time♪
♪All becomes unimportant♪
♪Perhaps a sudden encounter♪
♪Will last forever♪
♪After braving storms♪
♪There is also a harbor of refuge♪
♪Stumbling all the way through♪
♪Starting and stopping,
coming and going♪
♪Life has too many twists and turns♪
♪Why bother with right or wrong♪
♪Transient or enduring♪
♪Love makes it all worthwhile♪
♪What does the wear
and tear of time mean♪
♪Both tears and laughter will shine♪
♪Even in a sigh♪
(Canada)
(Xiang Qian: I've landed. Don't worry.)
(Xiang Zhong: Everything's okay?)
(Xiang Qian: Yes, how come
you're still up?)
(Xiang Zhong: I was a little worried)
(because you haven't landed.)
(Xiang Nan: Qian, good news.)
(Jiaqiao finally gave me)
(the hospital address
where Jiang Xiaotong is.)
(Xiang Qian: That's great.)
♪How far is it still from here♪
(Xiang Nan: She said that's as far
as she could go.)
(But I think it's good enough.)
♪How much remains unreachable♪
♪How much have I gained♪
(Xiang Qian: That's right.)
(Don't meet with Jiang Xiaotong alone.)
(You two go together.)
(Xiang Zhong: Will do.)
♪And the bond that lasts forever♪
(Xiang Nan: Okay.)
(Xiang Qian: You two go to bed.)
(It's almost dawn where you are.)
(Goodnight.)
(I'll let you know the moment
I get good news.)
♪Perhaps a sudden encounter♪
♪Will last forever♪
Who are you looking for?
May I know if Xu Sumin is home?
I'm a friend of hers.
What's your name?
I'm Xiang Qian.
Tell her
Xiang Nan is my younger sister.
Please wait.
Why do you want to see our mistress?
I want to talk to her
about her daughter.
What's the matter with my daughter?
She's injured,
it's bad.
And?
You came all the way to Canada
because of my daughter?
I don't think we're that close,
are we?
Also because of my sister.
I don't give a hoot
about your sister.
Your daughter is in the same predicament
as Xiang Nan.
If you don't believe me,
go ahead and call Xiaotong.
Whenever you're ready
to talk,
I'm right here.
I'll wait by the door.
You should leave.
Call me back.
Hello?
Why isn't Mavis picking up the call?
Maybe she didn't hear it.
She hasn't called me for some time.
You know better than anyone
the state your relationship is in.
Did something happen to her?
Jiang Hongbin.
I'm warning you.
If anything is wrong with Mavis
and you didn't tell me,
I won't let you live.
What could happen to her?
Stop being paranoid.
I'm telling you.
If anything
is wrong with Mavis,
you know what I'll do.
And I'm telling you.
She is my daughter too.
I will look after her well.
You've decided to let her stay in China.
No use having afterthoughts,
is there?
You talk as if
you actually cared about her.
Call me back.
(Xiang Zhong: Qian,)
(have you met with Xu Sumin?)
(How did it go?)
(Xiang Qian: If you're going
to look for Jiang Xiaotong,)
(set a time so she can
video call her mom.)
(Xiang Zhong: When's a good time
to do the video call?)
(Xiang Qian: It's up to you guys.)
(Xiang Zhong: We'll go there now.)
(Xiang Qian:
Don't do anything reckless.)
(Xiang Zhong: Don't worry.)
(People's Hospital Outpatient)
We have no choice.
We'll have to wait till he leaves
before we can go in.
Let's just wait.
Madam, she's still here.
She's still here?
She's been waiting in front of the gate.
Madam,
should we call the police?
She's gone.
Has Mavis not called back?
Could what she said be true then?
Go, you call her.
Call that brat
until she picks up.
Mavis.
Are you feeling better?
I'm sorry.
You got hurt
because of me.
Listen.
Your mom wants to video call you.
Can you do it now?
Why did she come back?
Hang on.
You refuse to leave, huh?
I'm going to call the police.
Your daughter's calling.
Mavis.
Mavis?
Mavis,
how come you're injured?
Mom,
I really miss you.
I'm right here, Mom's right here.
My baby.
Mavis, tell me.
How do you feel right now?
What happened?
Did someone hit you?
Why won't you come and see me?
Mavis,
I really want to go see you.
But I'm unable
to leave Canada right now.
Hurry, Xiang Nan.
Open the door. Open up!
Get out here!
Jiang Hongbin,
how did you let my daughter get hurt?
Jiang...
Open the door.
Here's the thing, Xiaotong.
I have something to ask you.
Are you willing
to be my eye witness?
(Xiang Nan: Qian,
turn on the screen recording.)
Got it.
Jiang Xiaotong.
You saw Jiang Hongbin
hitting me that day,
didn't you?
That day,
it was because you saw him beating me.
So you tried to save me
and that's how you got badly injured,
right?
Yes.
That jerk Jiang Hongbin.
Mavis, Mavis!
What are you two doing here?
Give me your phone.
What do you want, Jiang Hongbin?
Step aside.
What are you doing?
Don't you dare get physical.
Don't touch her, Jiang Hongbin!
Give me the phone!
Let go, Jiang Hongbin!
No!
Let her go!
You're not having it.
There are CCTVs in the room.
Get off me!
Release her!
Your child is watching you!
Jiang Hongbin,
I'm recording this whole thing.
The CCTVs are recording.
Do you want to add
more crimes to your list?
Turn it off.
Give me your phone.
I'm telling you now, Jiang Hongbin.
We now have sufficient evidence
on you.
We'll see you in court.
Xiang Nan.
If you don't hand over your phone,
none of you
is leaving today.
I won't let you
hurt me again and again.
I can give you my phone.
But my sister has everything on record.
Take it!
I'm only asking you one thing.
Let us leave.
You want to destroy me, don't you?
You listen up.
From this day on,
you, and you,
I'll make sure every one of you
suffer forever!
How long is forever?
We'll be waiting.
Come on, Xiang Nan.
Don't waste time
on the jerk.
Mr. Jiang.
What are you people good for?
You couldn't even
keep track of a grown person.
Get lost!
Mr. Jiang...
Out!
Hello, Xiang Nan?
Hey, Qian.
We got out.
♪Something will eventually be lost♪
♪Never to be remembered♪
♪The intermittent news drifting away♪
♪And then forgotten♪
♪Who can still face life?♪
♪With the courage it gives♪
♪Whether looking down♪
♪Or holding heads high♪
♪We must stay together♪
♪Walking through the cool night breeze♪
♪Leaving not a trace of sadness♪
♪Those nights returning to moonlight♪
♪There will be someone thinking of you♪
♪Treading a path of stars and seas♪
♪Passing through the dawn♪
♪A familiar piece♪
♪A strange piece♪
♪All are fleeting encounters♪
♪Amid the midnight glimmer♪
♪Questioning the ordinary♪
♪Hands left empty
after struggling for a lifetime♪
♪How to live happily?♪
♪Under a sky full of stars♪
♪One lamp♪
♪Two people watching over each other♪
♪Living through a time full of love♪
♪Just to be able to look
into each other's eyes♪
♪Amid the midnight glimmer♪
♪Questioning the ordinary♪
♪Hands left empty
after struggling for a lifetime♪
♪How to live happily?♪
♪Under a sky full of stars♪
♪One lamp♪
♪Two people watching over each other♪
♪Living through a time full of love♪
♪Just to be able to look
into each other's eyes♪