Let me ask you something first.
Are you doing this
because Zhou Wan has been wronged,
or have you seriously considered
that this is good for Lan Yue?
I know what you're worried about.
But regardless of all that,
today, no matter who I'm doing this for,
the sustainable revenue
this plan brings
the sustainable benefits
are immeasurable in the long run.
I've thought about it.
I know
our current team
doesn't have experience
in creating independent IP.
So I'm not planning to go solo.
If you agree,
once it's settled,
I'll immediately start forming a team
to implement and execute everything.
Alright, go ahead.
Really?
No matter who you are,
get off my aunt.
Who else could I be?
I'm your closest aunt.
Actually,
I've considered
your idea before.
But I thought
building an IP system
would be too risky.
And in my current position,
it's hard to make a move.
But as you said,
building our own IP system
can bring more than
just profits.
I really want to give it a try.
I just need someone
who dares to dream and do.
Now it seems
you are the most suitable candidate.
You caught me.
I caught you once.
You've grown up.
Then go ahead and do it.
Get this matter settled as soon as possible.
I'll go convince
the board of directors.
But I can only give you
half a month.
I don't need half a month.
Ten days are enough.
So confident?
Is it because of
Zhou Wan?
I knew it.
You are so narrow-minded.
This machine is very good.
It's hard to buy.
Who is it for?
My soon-to-be ex-husband.
Let me see.
Unfinished business.
I bought it before.
I forgot.
Yeah.
What are you talking about?
You look so happy.
Talking about the ex-brother-in-law.
Meng, here.
What's this?
What's this? A birthday invitation.
Give me one.
Here you go.
An invitation?
Isn't this
the ex-brother-in-law's birthday invitation?
Ex, ex, ex...
And there's one for each of us.
Everyone has one.
Right?
He's crazy!
Are we still going?
Let's not go.
Yeah.
Is that your boyfriend?
No.
Wan, with your looks,
if that's not your boyfriend,
he must be a suitor, right?
Yeah.
No, no.
It's okay.
It's okay, Wan.
If you have a date,
you can go.
We're here.
I'll send you the list
after I sort it out.
OK.
OK, OK.
You go first.
The more, the merrier.
I won't go. Right.
Director Lu is still here.
Director Lu is not with us
because of the overtime,
is he?
Shame on you!
Look at your face!
Look, Director Lu is staring at his phone.
Maybe he has
some important work or
a date.
That's right.
It's very likely.
Who is that?
Who is he texting?
Yeah.
Sister Wan, your phone is ringing again.
Again? Who is it?
My family, my family.
Already family?
Exactly, family.
Really?
I'll go, I'll go.
I'll go sort it out.
Okay, okay.
Leave this to me.
Okay.
I'll be back.
Okay, okay.
We didn't say you wouldn't come back.
Director Jiang, you...
No, Director Jiang.
If you have a date, you can go too.
We've got this covered here.
Don't you have a date?
I... I don't have a girlfriend.
It's okay, no girlfriend.
No girlfriend, then Director Jiang,
what do you think of them?
Would you like to pick one?
Director Jiang,
are we here to chat
or to work?
To work.
Understood.
Li Xin, have you finished that yet?
She sent it to me.
I have it here.
Alright.
Sending a message is so mysterious.
I'm afraid of misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding?
What misunderstanding?
Misunderstanding our relationship.
What's our relationship?
What relationship?
You know what I mean.
You're feeling guilty.
They saw me send you a message.
So what?
We have work-related interactions, don't we?
So, are you going or not?
Going where?
Jiang Fan's birthday party. Did you forget?
Are you going or not?
Jiang Fan's birthday party.
Gu Meng doesn't even know if she's going.
Why should I go?
And it's crowded and lively.
It's her choice to make.
And it's yours.
With Gu Meng's personality,
she'll definitely go.
So, are you going or not?
Mengmeng invited me tomorrow.
If she goes,
I'll
go with her.
Why did she invite you?
What are you doing?
Watch a movie.
He even wants to control this.
He's so annoying.
I prepared
such an important gift for him,
and he did this to me.
I won't stay there
one more second tonight.
Come on.
You've bought the gift.
Don't waste your money.
I'll freshen up.
It's just your ex's birthday.
Why so serious?
That's why I'm serious.
It's his birthday.
You're just being stubborn.
What?
I'll leave after giving him the gift.
You can mail it to him.
You're doing this on purpose, Zhou Wan.
Let me ask you.
How's your life
with Lu Xixiao?
Who cooks, who washes the dishes?
Do you sleep together or separately?
Okay, okay, you win.
I'm wrong.
You're so annoying.
The movie was bad,
and now I have to see my ex.
It's okay.
Typical romance movie.
You know,
the hero blocking the knife
was just for dramatic effect.
A normal person wouldn't
just block it like that.
He would've pushed her away.
And even if he got stabbed,
it would've been in the back,
not the chest.
The hero is a cop.
Doesn't he know
a chest wound is the most dangerous?
I can't stand such a bug.
Maybe it's an instinctive reaction.
No way.
We've done interviews.
There's a special investigation.
The best state
is that the male lead directly pounces over,
knocking down his friend.
And people are instinctual animals.
Even if he values his own life
more than the female lead,
he wouldn't have done that.
Let's go.
Go.
Wait.
I'm wearing this.
I'm going to
be the most beautiful tonight.
Let's go shopping.
Go.
All are good.
Jiang Fan.
Let's cut the cake.
Cut the cake.
Thank you.
Some classmates haven't arrived yet.
Let's wait a few minutes, okay?
Okay.
We'll wait for you.
Go in and play first.
Wait a few minutes.
Okay.
I'm telling you,
Jiang Fan hates being late the most.
And I threw away the gift wrapping.
I'll make him mad.
What?
A bomb?
Are you trying to turn my birthday
into my death day?
That would be best.
How big is the bomb?
Where did you get it?
You're so generous.
Thank you, honey.
Is she your wife?
Zhou Wan.
Meimei, long time no see.
It's been a while.
Thank you.
You look great.
You scared me, Lu Xixiao.
You two came together?
No.
-We didn't come together. -Yeah.
We did.
No.
I came with Gu Meng.
No, I brought her here.
I just went to see a movie
with Gu Meng.
No.
We did.
Zhou Wan.
I heard Jiang Yan is back.
Wanwan,
are you two really together?
What about Jiang Yan?
Why do you bring up that?
Go away.
I'll go find Brother Ping.
Brother Ping.
Zhou Wan,
long time no see.
Long time no see.
Drink a bottle.
It's you who taught me to drink.
I'll drink sooner or later.
How have you been these years?
Normal life.
How about you?
I'm still the same.
Not much change here.
Sister,
there are some words
I've been holding inside for many years.
I've always wanted to tell you,
but I never found the right time.
Don't beat around the bush, Brother Ping.
Just say it.
I'll do it.
It's okay. I'll do it with you.
Then I'll say it.
After you broke up with A'Xiao,
he fell seriously ill.
He lost
so much weight.
When I went to see him,
he was locked up in his room.
He was burning up,
and talking nonsense.
He kept saying
Zhou Wan.
I only realized
he was calling your name.
I've never seen him like that.
He was almost unrecognizable.
I blamed you a lot at that time.
Because I always treated him
as my own brother.
Did you ever love him?
It's not that I didn't love him.
It's that I loved him too much.
Don't worry.
I understand.
I'm still
as tight-lipped
as I was when I was a kid.
Over the years,
I've been having a recurring dream.
He lies in front of me, bleeding,
and no matter how I call him,
he doesn't move.
I just don't want
to see that summer happen again.
I was too young
to do anything.
No matter how regretful I was,
I had to move on.
Aren't you curious
how he lived
after leaving you?
Tell me about it.
He
was decadent for a while,
and then he started to study hard.
He's smart.
He can achieve anything
he sets his mind to.
He did well in school,
and got into
a good university.
You know,
he went abroad.
He made his way
step by step on his own,
He never asked for a penny from the Lu family,
nor owed anyone a favor.
At that time,
I was particularly worried that he would force the sprouts to grow.
As a result,
he really stood up on his own.
Sister,
do you know why I
tell you all this?
Yingxiao is somewhat extreme
in his actions.
but he's not a bad person.
He never forgot you,
and always cared about you.
He pushed himself
to grow up so fast.
Why?
I believe you know the reason.
Just look at the difference
between him in the video and now.
I'll make you some honey water.
Wait for me.
Lie down.
Here we are.
Don't hold me.
I'm not drunk.
Fine.
You're not drunk but you walk like this.
I'm really drunk.
It's all your fault.
I said we should go buy a light bulb together.
Now,
They're all burned out.
What are you doing? Go to bed.
Fix the light bulbs.
My dear, come down.
Why do you have to fix it
at night?
I can't sleep if I don't fix it.
You might fall.
Come down.
I'll do it, okay?
Leave me alone.
Hold it for me.
Light it for me.
I'll fix it.
Here.
Don't shine it at me.
Shine it here.
Can you do it?
Don't you know if I can do it?
Don't worry. I just started.
I can't do it.
- Don't shake. - Jiang Fan.
Hurry up.
Are you okay, honey?
Did you hurt anywhere?
Can you sleep peacefully now?
Why are you crying?
Did you hurt?
It would be nice if we had done this earlier.
Jiang Fan.
I also want to
fix the light bulb.
pick furniture with you.
I also want to
fill this house with you.
live with you
like two fools.
But you are always not here.
You are always not here.
I'm sorry.
Honey.
It's comfortable here.
Come on.
Lean on me.
Open your mouth.
I don't want to take medicine.
It's not medicine.
Why do you always play tricks when you're drunk?
Come on.
Open your mouth.
Then feed me.
I'm feeding you.
Am I dreaming?
Lu Xixiao.
Xiao Liu.
If you think you're dreaming,
then you must be.
Does it hurt?
It hasn't hurt for a long time.
I mean back then.
I don't remember.
Why did you
take the hit for me?
Because I love you.
But you had other choices
to avoid such serious injuries.
Do you know that if it had been worse,
you might not have woken up?
Do you know that?
Enough.
Zhou Wan,
I've thought about
why I blocked that knife
for you back then.
Maybe
I just didn't want you to get hurt.
I didn't care about anything else.
I wanted you to care about me,
to be with me,
and to love me.
But you just wouldn't trust me.
When you were
with me in the hospital,
you were thinking
about breaking up with me.
I made it
very clear to you back then.
I said if you just said you love me,
I would forgive you.
But you wouldn't even
say that.
It's not like that.
I thought
if I lied to you
that I didn't love you,
you would give up.
I was wrong.
All these years,
I've been forcing myself
to leave you,
but there hasn't been a moment
when I stopped loving you.
Zhou Wan,
are you not going to sleep?
I'm going to be with you for the rest of my life.
Are you awake?
Good.
I give up, Zhou Wan.
Please give me another chance
to pursue you properly.
Okay?
Do you need help?
Forget it, just let me chase you.
Give me a chance.
It smells so good.
Did you make all of this yourself?
That's amazing.
Try some.
It's so pretty.
I can't bear to eat it.
What are you doing?
Replying to work messages.
What's going on?
I have two
important reports to submit today.
They've been texting me since this morning.
Who do you
submit your reports to?
To you.
I've approved your report.
Let's eat.
Try it.
Why aren't you eating?
I'll watch you eat.
Is it good?
Sit down.
If you like it,
you can have it every day.
Jiang Fan,
how dare you take advantage of me
when I'm drunk?
Even if we were married,
it would be illegal.
Not to mention we're divorced.
Come on,
be reasonable.
Last night,
you held me tightly
and slept in my arms.
Am I breaking the law?
Then just pretend
nothing happened.
We're already divorced.
We don't have to
be responsible for each other.
Gu Meng,
when are you going to
stop making this a big deal?
Can't we talk this out?
Jiang Fan,
you still think
I'm just being dramatic?
That's not what I meant.
I... I just mean
if you have a problem,
just say it.
Otherwise, I won't know
why you want a divorce.
That's your biggest problem.
Jiang Fan,
we've been together for ten years
and married for three.
You don't even know
what I want,
or why I want a divorce.
Forget it.
Again,
you stop halfway.
If you don't know, you can ask me.
No.
Why do you have to
keep guessing?
We are all adults.
We are tired from work every day.
If you want something,
just tell me directly.
I'll do it.
Isn't that better?
If in life,
everything has to be asked for,
I'd rather not have such a marriage.
Hello?
Why did it take so long to answer?
What are you doing?
Of course,
I'm eating.
What did you eat?
Spicy chicken, stir-fried pork,
and braised pork ribs.
Pass.
How about you?
You skipped class.
How's your painting?
Let me correct that.
I didn't skip class.
I asked my aunt for permission.
I'm on leave.
You were the one
who skipped the most classes in school.
Now you're a decent person.
Have you eaten yet?
I'm in the restaurant right now.
Restaurant?
The restaurant is so quiet.
I'm in the private room.
Do you think I can't even tell
the echo of the studio?
Wan
I brought you some fried rice.
I saw you were busy,
so I didn't bring it over.
Remember to eat it.
I'm leaving. Remember to eat it.
Thank you, Xin'er.
So you ate spicy chicken,
stir-fried pork, and braised pork ribs.
And your colleague
brought you fried rice.
Right?
Alright, alright.
You should find a restaurant
and have a proper meal.
Don't lecture me.
Zhou Wan,
put down
everything you're working on
and go eat.
Xiao Liu.
Alright.
You should also find a restaurant
and have a proper meal.
Okay?
Alright, I'll listen to you.
I'll hang up now.
Bye-bye.
Xiaoliu, come here.
Xiaoliu.
Come here.
Who let you eat my sandwich?
Back then, the project wasn't standardized.
and there were no digital archives.
It's hard to find.
It's okay. I just want to see
if there's anything
we can learn from the second phase.
I found it.
Don't worry.
I've spoken to Mr. Lu.
If there are any issues,
just have him come to me.
Okay.
Please sign here.
Shall I deliver it to your office?
No need.
I'll handle it myself.
You should be off work now.
Alright, I'll be on my way then.
The acquisition price for Jun'an Building Materials Factory
is so low.
The degree of soil pollution
exceeds the initial assessment.
Zhou Wan,
so the one you want to deal with
is Lu Zhongyue.
Is this the reason
why you think
Lu Xixiao and I are not good enough?