[Never-Ending Summer]
[Episode 7]
What are you doing out here?
I was afraid you couldn't find me.
With such a big scene,
it'd be hard not to find you.
Am I a bit underdressed?
Not at all.
You look good.
What's your problem?
Watch where you're going!
Take it easy.
Long time no see.
What makes you think
you're qualified to come
to the same party as me?
Ethan!
Don't be mad.
There are so many people here.
I'm fine.
I'm really fine.
Let me see.
Come here.
It's fine.
Don't be mad.
♪ If you had ever seen the fireflies ♪
♪ Inside my eyes ♪
Not bad.
The size looks okay.
♪ I think you would understand ♪
♪ Why I embrace the dark ♪
Do you have girls over
often at your place?
♪ People always want to reach out ♪
I have lots of girls coming over.
♪ But are afraid
to pull their hands back ♪
Beauties too.
♪ I choose to open my arms wide ♪
Stylists,
♪ And enjoy the weightlessness ♪
housekeepers,
and designers.
Xixiao,
the stylist and makeup artist are here.
Come in.
♪ If I could, I want to become ♪
♪ An astronomer ♪
Come on.
♪ Lost in your night sky ♪
♪ Then fall and fall and fall ♪
I'll charge you once it's done.
♪ Maybe it's your gravity ♪
How much?
♪ That held me back from losing control ♪
♪ When you passed by me by accident ♪
♪ I finally learned to fall ♪
♪ Countless, unforgettable ♪
♪ No time left, so I ♪
♪ Can only fall toward you ♪
♪ Too dazzling, too lonely, it's alright ♪
♪ I believe in this encounter ♪
♪ Landing in the ruins of the galaxy ♪
♪ Exchanging our comets ♪
Xixiaoao.
-Mr. Lu is looking for you.
-What's up?
♪ Suddenly I am certain ♪
I don't want to go.
♪ This mud all over me ♪
Mr. Lu Sr. is here too.
♪ Is the proof of love ♪
You should go.
I'll do it myself.
It's fine.
Thank you.
Alright, Miss Zhou.
Although Mrs. Lu had been accomplished
in the art world during her lifetime,
I think
what truly makes her blessed
is how Mr. Lu has kept
her memory alive all these years.
Yeah.
This painting of hers
would fetch a fortune
at auction, wouldn't it?
Seriously,
Mr. Lu's devotion
is worth more than gold.
Thank you.
Qilan.
Look at you.
You've got some nerve,
coming back
from abroad
without telling your family.
I'm telling you.
Since you're back,
get along well with your brother.
Nothing compares to
the family being happily together.
Xixiao.
As for you,
what's your plan
-for college?
-I'll fill you in on that later.
You really make me worry.
Dad, you go inside first.
I'll follow in a bit.
Why are you here
at this kind of occasion?
Didn't you also come all the way
back from abroad?
I came back to watch the show.
Are you staying
because you're interested
in your dad's vanity project?
I went through all that trouble
to get your paperwork done
behind your dad's back.
Qilan?
Coming.
I'm going in.
Xixiao.
Come here.
Just now outside,
did you get into an argument
with Mr. He's son?
Go over and apologize to him.
Okay?
You know what I mean.
It's no big deal.
Isn't this Lu Xixiao?
Are you yielding?
Admitting defeat?
I was wrong.
What did you say?
I can't hear you.
I was wrong.
What were you wrong about?
I was wrong for...
stopping you
when you ran the red light,
preventing you
from hitting someone
and breaking the law,
and saving your life.
I was wrong to agree to
race you when you asked,
letting you lose the race
in front of everyone
because of your poor skills.
You scratched my car,
and I shouldn't have
just smashed yours.
I should have followed the process
and asked your family for compensation.
Then we'll see
who should be apologizing,
me or you, He Wenhui.
Lu Xixiao.
Can't you speak nicely?
Is that how you apologize?
Just putting on a show.
That's enough.
It's just a little friction
between our dads over business.
Now both of them
are in a somewhat awkward position.
They're using us as an excuse
to talk again.
Can't you see
the situation?
You really think I came to apologize?
Get lost.
Go away.
See? Aren't they getting along fine?
Come on.
If you keep making a fuss,
who do you think
will look worse—
you in your dad's eyes,
or me in mine?
You're not any better than me.
We're the same,
playing the good kids here.
We're not the same.
I've asked around.
He Wenhui, you aren't afraid of anyone—
except your dad.
I'm not afraid.
Fine.
Since that's the case,
why are you still
putting on this act here?
What's the point?
It's all for a painting.
I'll settle the score
with Luo He another time.
Get lost.
Don't touch me.
I can walk.
♪ I'mma take a frozen heart ♪
♪ Someone's gonna make it ♪
♪ In the building of my broken part ♪
♪ Someone's gonna fix it ♪
♪ I'm the only one guy
with the ten things crime ♪
♪ I deserve a sanction in my mind ♪
♪ Nescience doesn't mean ♪
♪ That I can fly ♪
♪ Long time no see ♪
♪ You haven't been here ♪
♪ Stop watch has seen the changes ♪
♪ I'm sure you won't forget ♪
♪ The door you ever knocked ♪
♪ So I sent you a clock ♪
♪ To recover the deadlock ♪
♪ It's like I'm losing my sword ♪
Did he cause you trouble again?
♪ Chop off the line
between the loving core ♪
♪ I'mma take a frozen heart ♪
Did he bother you?
♪ Someone's gonna make it ♪
So beautiful.
♪ In the building of my broken part ♪
♪ Someone's gonna fix it ♪
♪ I'm the only one guy
with the ten things crime ♪
Thank you.
♪ I deserve a sanction in my mind ♪
♪ Nescience doesn't mean that I can fly ♪
♪ But I never seem to close ♪
♪ The dormer lock ♪
As expected of the Lu family,
inviting so many distinguished guests
to put on such a grand event.
♪ Tell you starts were above the floor ♪
You must've put a lot of effort into this.
I just helped out a bit.
Looks like it won't be long before
we officially address you
as Mrs. Lu.
Thank you.
Cheers.
We just came out like this?
What's there to stay for inside?
I've arranged something for you out here.
How is it?
Didn't you want to hear it?
I arranged a solo for you.
This is too extravagant.
They had a performance
scheduled tonight anyway,
but the song you want
wasn't on the setlist.
I didn't want you to come for nothing.
Thank you.
Come.
Can you dance?
I'll teach you.
Come on.
Take it slow.
Follow my steps.
It's a bit hard.
♪ The narcissus rides a carp,
drifting away in sadness ♪
Take it slow.
♪ Deep green lurks beneath the sea,
stirring the nebula ♪
Do you know why
they aren't playing this piece today?
This song
♪ On countless nights, we move forward ♪
tells a love story, right?
Maybe they thought
it didn't fit the occasion?
♪ Seeking, waking up and collecting ♪
The story goes that
two people who shouldn't
be together
♪ Crazy love ♪
met and still fell in love.
♪ Say yes, let's start fresh ♪
The woman eventually hurt
the man who deeply loved her.
But this man
still tried to protect her
and died.
♪ The first night, my sunset ♪
How foolish.
No.
♪ The whole world, the two of us♪
I watched the interview.
The composer said
that in the story, the man believed
♪ The city doesn't sleep, ups and downs ♪
until the very end that it was fate—
even if it was a wrong fate.
♪ Breathing at midnight ♪
♪ Someone lights the fire ♪
♪ The love burns each other ♪
♪ My organs ♪
♪ Every midnight ♪
♪ Being played ♪
♪ One, two, three, four, five ♪
♪ Let's dance ♪
♪ Follow your steps ♪
♪ One, two, three, four, five ♪
♪ Close my eyes and count ♪
♪ Open your eyes and see me ♪
♪ One, two, three, four, five ♪
♪ Let's dance ♪
♪ Follow your steps ♪
♪ One, two, three, four, five ♪
♪ Close my eyes and count ♪
You dance well.
Before it actually happens,
it's still not too late
for me to stop, right?
If one day I hurt you,
what would you do?
Nothing.
Hello, everyone.
Welcome, all guests,
to my house.
Today is Lanyue Group's
40th anniversary celebration.
Thank you.
Speaking of Lanyue Group,
I believe many of you here
are our partners.
You have developed
and grown with us.
The man standing on the left off stage
is my father.
Lanyue Group
was painstakingly
built by him
from the ground up.
So the responsibility on me
is even greater.
Well, now,
everyone, please look at
this painting behind me.
This painting
is a very important work
by my son Xixiao's
late mother.
It's also a piece I have
treasured for many years.
Let's go
somewhere
without people we don't like.
The name of this work is
"Midsummer".
It's "Never-Ending Summer".
Wait here for a second.
And this is not a
single piece.
It's a series.
Hello, Dr. Chen?
I have good news.
Your grandma's test results
are out.
Her indicators are quite ideal.
If a matching kidney is found,
surgery can be considered.
Really?
This series
includes four works:
Spring, Summer, Autumn, and Winter.
When can the surgery be done?
The surgery has to wait
for a matching kidney donor.
But regarding the cost,
you need to be mentally prepared.
How much is the cost?
300,000.
Hello,
please show your invitation.
I was invited by the Lu family.
Mrs. Lu said she doesn't know you.
To be continued.
The passion and bravery in this painting
are the most moving things about her.
Zhou Wan?
When do I need to pay?
The artwork "Never-Ending Summer"
represents her lifetime
passion in the world.
If you don't have an invitation,
we'll have to ask you to leave.
Once a kidney donor matches,
surgery must be done immediately.
The sooner the better.
If you still don't cooperate,
then we'll have to...
Excuse me,
everyone.
I came here
to find someone.
Many of you here probably
know her.
She is the hostess
of this banquet,
Ms. Guo Xiangling.
You.
-Looking for you.
Or perhaps,
I should call you...
Mom.
Mom?
-Mom?
T-This... She...
She has a daughter?
What did I say?
Your father's event
always has some drama.
My name is Zhou Wan.
"Wan" as in drawing
a bow like a full moon.
I'm a student at Yangming High School.
My father passed away early.
Since I was little,
I've never experienced motherly love.
My family's condition isn't good either.
It's hard to maintain our current life.
For all of this,
I want to thank Ms. Guo Xiangling.
Without her,
I wouldn't be who I am today.
I want to thank her
for...
Zhou Wan.
Ms. Guo, thank you for
supporting my studies
anonymously all these years.
I'm grateful for her kindness.
I'd even say
she means more to me than
my own mother.
Come on. Go on up.
No.
What are you doing here?
Didn't I make it clear to you?
My dad's insurance money
belongs to me in the first place.
300,000.
Grandma needs it for her surgery.
Say something.
Thank you. Thank you all.
This is truly unexpected.
I never thought
you'd come find me here.
But...
I'm truly touched.
Thank you all.
I know
my actions today are a bit abrupt.
I hope you'll understand.
I came here
just to tell everyone
that over the years, Ms. Guo
has had a very hard time.
She's a very kind
and warm-hearted lady.
And it's precisely because of
her kindness and warmth
that I gathered the courage to stand here.
I think there's no
better place than this
to show everyone
my gratitude to her.
If you want to ruin yourself,
don't drag me down with you.
Get up quickly.
-Then finish this show with me.
-Get up.
Mom.
Today is truly such a surprise,
and I'm so touched.
Actually, I never thought
about getting any return.
I only hope
you have a bright future
and a beautiful life.
Thank you.
Dear visitors,
Pingchuan Art Museum
is now officially closed
for the day.
[Pingchuan Art Museum]
If you are still inside,
please take your belongings
and follow the staff's guidance
to exit in an orderly manner.
[Joint Exhibition of Famous Artists]
During your departure,
please watch your step
and avoid crowding.
Jiang Yan.
Grandma.
Why are you here so late?
Is Zhou Wan not here?
No.
She brought me lunch at noon
and left, saying she had things to do.
Why?
Is Wan okay?
She's fine.
Maybe her phone died.
I won't disturb your rest then.
Are you going back?
Wait a moment.
Please do me a favor
and take this lunchbox back for me.
Alright?
Besides,
there's something inside the bag.
I don't know what it is,
but it looks quite formal.
Take it back too.
[Invitation]
[Lu Zhongyue]
Lu Family Banquet?
Zhou Wan, what exactly is
your relationship with Lu Xixiao?
Zhou Wan.
You asked me this afternoon
if you ever hurt me one day,
what I would do.
You already knew what you were
going to do, didn't you?
So let me answer you now.
You've always known better than anyone
how to hurt me.
Lu Xixiao...
Didn't you say you were leaving?
Zhou Wan, I know you too well.
What you said
at the banquet just now,
what between you and that woman...
You just wanted to use me
to get close to her.
Didn't you?
Did you think I would
believe those words?
You approached me
and slowly made me trust you.
You slowly made me feel
like this world
wasn't that bad.
Why?
Turn around and look at me!
I'm sorry.
Do you really want
to be my sister that badly?
♪ Should I chase freedom all alone ♪
♪ Find an excuse, heed what I've known ♪
♪ Every time I stop and stay ♪
♪ For reasons that fade away ♪
♪ Are you out there waiting for me ♪
In all the time we spent together,
was there ever a moment
♪ Through the dark, bravely, steadily ♪
when you actually liked me?
♪ If I could run and land with you ♪
I never thought about it.
♪ After the long night ♪
♪ I'll find my way, no more lost inside ♪
♪ Thinking about ♪
♪ Fulfilling the last promise ♪
♪ We've both held fragility ♪
♪ Talked through our misery ♪
♪ This time
I'm holding tight to your will ♪
♪ Lighting up all the sparks ♪
♪ Hoping it doesn't slip away ♪
♪ In this boring universe ♪
♪ Drifting day by day ♪
♪ Until the day I choose
to break away for you ♪
♪ And that's enough to do ♪
♪ Falling into your tenderness ♪
♪ Slowly being saved ♪
♪ After the long night ♪
♪ I'll find my way, no more lost inside ♪
♪ Thinking about ♪
♪ Fulfilling the last promise ♪
♪ We've both held fragility ♪
♪ Talked through our misery ♪
♪ This time
I'm holding tight to your will ♪
♪ Lighting up all the sparks ♪
♪ Hoping it doesn't slip away ♪
♪ In this boring universe ♪
♪ Drifting day by day ♪
♪ Until the day I choose
to break away for you ♪
♪ And that's enough to do ♪
♪ Falling into your tenderness ♪
♪ Slowly being saved ♪
Not everyone
can be Cinderella.
Only you know
if the shoe fits.
What are you here for?
Xixiao's aunt invites you
to breakfast tomorrow.
Since you've made a scene,
there has to be a follow-up.
I'm not going.
What?
Is Lu Xixiao mad at you?
I thought you came to me
to talk about money.
Anything else, forget it.
You should've
thought about the consequences
when you went crazy like that.
As long as you can pay the money back,
I don't care about the consequences.
Fine.
Let's put on a good show then.
Tomorrow,
you will do whatever I say.
You'll say that from now on,
you're leaving Pingchuan
and never coming back.
If you can do that,
I'll give you the money.
Why should I believe you?
You still owe me that 300,000.
I can go.
But Grandma's follow-up dialysis
costs 6,000.
You have to give me that first.
6,000?
Starting tomorrow,
stay out of my sight.
Okay?
She is...
Guo Yan.
My mom.
Thanks.
You must have a lot of questions.
It's okay if you don't want to talk.
After my dad passed away,
she left.
And she never came back.
When she left,
she took all the money we had.
That could be
Grandma's lifesaving money now.
She told me
she didn't have it easy either,
saying she was very poor.
But you saw the truth.
So,
is she the reason
you got close to Lu Xixiao?
If I said yes,
would you also think
I'm a bad person?
Also?
Who else thinks you're a bad person?
Zhou Wan,
you're not a bad person.
Maybe others don't get it,
but I do.
No one would want anything
to do with
someone who
abandoned them unless they
had no other choice.
I'll keep your secret.
Just like when we were kids.
Thanks.
I didn't tell him.
Xixiao,
what's your plan
for college?
I thought Auntie
already told you.
She's been busy and hasn't
had the chance.
Come.
Since you're here,
tell me yourself.
I plan to
study art abroad.
I'll apply to my mom's alma mater.
Study art?
This is not a whim.
I've already figured out what to study.
I think college isn't
something to take lightly,
so I feel
it's necessary to choose a
major I'm interested in.
Since I have
decided to stay now,
I'll spend a year properly preparing
and applying seriously.
Why haven't you mentioned this before?
Why do you want
to study art all of a sudden?
That's just because you didn't know.
Dad, Zhongyue.
Here's the thing.
When Xixiao first told me,
I didn't believe him either.
But then he showed me
his portfolio.
And I remembered
that when he was little, he did
take art classes for a while.
So I thought it was worth a shot.
It wasn't long,
but I did take art lessons
when I was little.
And that's when
I started thinking...
What you think and what you do
are two different things.
You know?
You act like you're so into
art all the time, don't you?
How dare you!
Alright.
Alright, alright, alright.
Come on, don't be mad.
Sit down. Just sit down.
Your dad isn't really mad.
He just thinks you could
study painting anytime.
Look,
you're about to go abroad
to study finance.
You're leaving this summer.
When you come back,
you can study whatever you want,
play whatever you want.
Isn't that great?
I've already made up my mind.
[The guest is here.]
Our guest is here.
No fighting in front of
the guest, okay?
Zhou Wan,
you finally came.
You didn't stay for dinner yesterday.
Mrs. Lu, well,
you did something good
and didn't even take credit.
Am I not supposed to
call you Mrs. Lu yet?
You should.
Why not?
I've been waiting for you
to call me that for a long time.
Come.
Sit down and eat.
Another set of cutlery, please.
Hello, Grandpa.
Hello, Uncle.
Hello, Aunt Guo.
Why are you just standing there?
Say hi to your brother.
Hi, brother.