[Never-Ending Summer]
[Episode 14]
[In Loving Memory]
This photo of your grandma is really nice.
Looking at the album, I just realized
that over the years we've been neighbors,
we've long been like family.
In the past,
when I was too busy
to manage things,
your grandma would go to the school
to pick up Yan for me
and help him with his meals.
A few times when I came back,
Yan had already
fallen asleep at your place.
Did that really happen?
Your grandma
always used her own way
to take care of everyone.
Zhou Wan.
[In Loving Memory]
We came to say goodbye
to your grandma.
Who said you could come in here?
Rude girl.
You don't even know how to say thank you.
Arrange them properly.
Mr. Fang.
The wreaths have been set up.
All right.
You all go out.
Let's go.
Wan.
Ms. Jiang.
Let me handle this here.
Thank you for your hard work.
Take a rest.
Okay.
Call us if you need anything.
Thank you, Ms. Jiang.
Sorry for the trouble.
[With Deepest Sympathy]
My condolences.
Sir, why are you here?
The neighbors told me.
I've known Fen for so long,
how could I not come?
I have some business to attend to,
so I'll get going.
I'll see you out.
You don't have to pay rent
for the next few months.
I'll tell Luo He later.
I guess that kid
has been causing you
a lot of trouble lately.
It's fine.
I've already saved up.
9,000.
[With Deepest Sympathy]
3,000 a month.
I've already given it to Luo He.
How much?
9,000.
What's wrong?
Boss.
[Please Respect the Deceased.
No Smoking in the Memorial Hall.]
Nothing.
If you need anything in the future,
contact me directly.
[Pingchuan Funeral Services Center]
Mr. Fang.
Look at this girl.
She has no manners at all.
We sent two wreaths,
and she didn't even say thank you.
Shut up.
[Pingchuan Funeral Services Center]
Remember, I owe Fen
for what she's done for me.
Take care, Mr. Fang.
[Fondly Remembering Huang Xuefen]
With such a grand setup, no one showed up.
[Pingchuan Funeral Services Center]
Bro.
Let's go.
My condolences.
I have something to give you.
What is this?
See for yourself.
[With Deepest Sympathy]
Do I look good?
Yes.
Ma'am, look here.
Okay, I look here, right?
I'll take off my coat.
Wait a moment.
No rush, Ma'am.
I didn't expect
to be fashionable right before the end
and record such a video.
Well,
it's just in case
I leave too suddenly
and don't have time to say goodbye.
So I want to say a few words first,
but the premise is no crying.
Especially you, Kang.
Don't cry.
-At your age...
-I'm smiling.
-You look ugly when you cry.
-I’m smiling.
In my life,
I've experienced storms,
suffered hardships,
and enjoyed blessings.
There might be regrets,
but life overall
has been happy.
Now that I'm leaving,
the only one I can't let go of,
needless to say,
as everyone knows,
is my precious Wan.
A smart, kind,
and sensitive child.
Because of me,
she inevitably
missed out on a lot.
Wan,
although there are many things
you don't tell me.
But I'm not confused.
I understand it all.
I know
what you have done for me
and how much you have sacrificed.
Now that I'm gone,
don't treat this
as a sad farewell.
You should know
that this farewell
is also the beginning of
another chapter in your life.
Child,
I hope you
will go to college and study hard.
You should
go see the world outside.
Try things
you've always wanted to try
but never dared to.
You only live once.
I hope you
can live a wonderful life.
I hope you can live
the life you want the most.
I won't leave.
I will always
watch you with a smile
and keep you company.
My darling Wan.
Is it done?
Did I say it okay?
Yes, very well.
Good.
[In Loving Memory]
I can go back by myself.
Just for one night.
I want to be alone for a while.
Actually, I can keep you company.
Give it to me.
I will take care of her.
Okay.
Then I will come over
first thing tomorrow morning.
I can wear this for the toasts, right?
Yes.
Let me try it on.
Okay.
Xixiao.
You are finally back.
Why did you call me back in such a hurry?
Your dad is worried.
Don't worry.
He has told me everything.
He introduced you
to some foreign friends.
When the time comes,
your basic necessities...
As soon as you board the plane,
I'll send her the money.
This way, Zhou Wan's grandma
can have her surgery sooner.
Okay?
Her grandma is dead.
What?
Her grandma is dead?
That's impossible.
How could it be so sudden?
She had such a hard life.
It's a relief in a way.
Is Zhou Wan doing okay?
For her grandma's funeral,
I need to attend in person.
No need.
The funeral is already over.
I know you hate me,
but I'm human too.
My sadness isn't fake.
Xixiao.
After you leave,
I will still send
the money to Wan.
Xixiao.
Mom.
Otherwise,
we should bring Zhou Wan here.
I am really worried about her.
Don't worry.
Wan will take good care of herself.
Before we leave,
go see her more.
Jiang Yan.
It's time to rest.
Zhou Wan.
I brought you some noodles, Zhou Wan.
Zhou Wan!
Zhou Wan! Zhou Wan!
Zhou Wan.
[Outpatient Registration; Cashier]
Luckily, it was found in time
and didn't damage the nerves.
After the treatment,
the poisoning symptoms
have significantly eased.
Don't worry.
The fact that she woke up
means it's nothing serious.
She needs to rest for the next few days
and get plenty of nutrients.
We'll keep her
under observation for a few days.
If there are no further symptoms,
she can be discharged.
Okay.
Thank you, Doctor.
Zhou Wan.
How do you feel?
How are you feeling?
I wasn't trying to kill myself.
I know.
I was just a bit tired.
I know that too.
You should go back first.
I want to rest for a bit.
I'm not leaving.
Let me think.
I got one.
What's between five and seven?
Six.
Between five and seven is "and".
Isn't it funny?
Not funny.
Funny.
Let me think of another one.
This one is definitely funny.
Some people fart really loud.
Do you know why?
Why?
Because when they fart,
they are wearing bell-bottoms.
This one is funny, right?
Not funny.
If it's not funny,
why are you laughing so loud?
Wan didn't laugh.
I think it's very funny.
Then you tell one.
Let's see how funny your joke is.
[Inpatient Building]
I'm sorry.
I didn't take good care of Zhou Wan.
The person you should apologize to is her.
My eyes hurt.
Can you close the curtains?
Discharge procedures are all done.
I want to stay for a few more days.
Why do you want to stay in the hospital?
It's so much better to go home.
And there are other patients
coming in.
It's comfortable here.
And I really don't have
the energy to move.
Drink this before you sleep.
I don't want to drink.
Don't force me to make you drink. Come on.
I said I don't want to drink.
I want to sleep.
Get up.
Zhou Wan.
Let's go get some sun.
Come on.
I don't want to.
If you don't get some sun,
you'll get moldy.
Come out and get some fresh air with me.
What are you doing?
-Let’s go out for some fresh air.
-I said I was sleepy.
You are sleepy?
Then go downstairs
and sleep leaning on me.
Just get some fresh air
with me downstairs, okay?
-Let’s go. Get up.
-Can you leave me alone?
Zhou Wan,
do you think
your grandma would want to see
you like this?
What can I do?
-You don't get any sunlight all day...
-Tell me. What can I do?
...and you hardly eat anything.
-What can I do?
-You don’t even drink water.
Who would want to see
you like this?
I can't be the way
you want me to be anymore.
Everyone comes to
the hospital every day...
-...to care about you.
-When I don't want to smile...
-...stop forcing me to smile.
-Who do you think wants to see...
...you like this?
I can't be the way
you want me to be anymore.
Aren't you good at pretending?
-Go on.
-I can’t.
Pretend you are fine alone.
-Pretend you're doing great all alone.
-My dad passed away.
My grandma passed away too.
I have nothing left.
I really can't do it anymore.
I can't pretend anymore.
I'm only 18.
I'm sorry.
Zhou Wan.
I was wrong. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'll accompany you to grow up.
You'll sleep here tonight.
What about you?
I'll sleep on the sofa.
You can see me
as soon as you open the door.
Come on.
You haven't slept well
these past few days.
Get a good night's sleep tonight.
Alright.
Go to sleep now.
I left a change of clothes
there for you.
Thank you.
Let me do it.
It's fine.
Go take a seat.
I'll come get you when it's done.
It's raining heavily outside.
The delivery guy spilled our food.
So we won't be eating anytime soon.
Have a glass of water first.
Thank you.
It's okay.
We can order something else.
See what you want to eat.
Anything is fine.
This one?
Okay.
What else do you want to do today?
I don't know either.
Look at how heavily it's raining.
How about when the rain stops,
we go for a walk?
Gu Meng just told Jiang Fan
that she wants to see you too.
Sure.
Then let's wait for the rain to stop,
and we'll go for a stroll.
For now,
I need to find something for you to do.
Why?
Because we need to make your mind stop.
If it doesn't stop, you'll keep thinking.
And if you keep thinking,
you'll keep being sad.
You seem to know it well.
When my mom passed away,
I suddenly became all alone too.
I was like this back then,
just about like you are now.
You were so little then.
But I still got through it, didn't I?
It's okay.
I'm here with you.
My heart hurts so much.
As time goes by,
will it hurt less?
But I really miss Grandma.
She actually just
stepped out of time.
She returned to the universe's
most primitive components.
Molecules.
Atoms.
In the future,
she will slowly return to you
in another form.
Actually, you can think of it this way.
When it rains heavily
or the wind blows hard in the future,
she can be the big tree
that shelters you from the wind and rain.
When winter comes,
she can also be the sweater
that keeps you warm.
She just left you temporarily
as your grandma.
She will always be with you in the future.
You know what?
I had a very cute puppy
when I was a kid.
When it passed away,
this is what my mother told me.
When my mother passed away,
I still believed in it.
My mother once told me
to believe in the power of belief.
Your grandma will accompany you
in the future
at any time
and in any form.
I would too.
Do you believe in wishes?
No.
Before I was 9,
I made a wish every birthday.
I would write my wishes
on a piece of paper
and hide them under my pillow.
Dad said
if I was a good child,
my wishes would come true.
Sometimes they did,
sometimes they didn't.
I asked my dad why.
Guess what he said.
What did he say?
He said it was because I didn't blow out
all the candles at once.
After I turned 9,
I never made a wish again.
That birthday,
I blew really hard.
I hoped my wish would come true.
I wished
that my dad would stop coughing.
What about now?
Now that I'm grown up,
I don't believe in that stuff anymore.
If tomorrow was your birthday
and you could make one wish,
what would it be?
I really want a bicycle.
Once, after school,
there was a heavy rain.
I didn't have an umbrella,
didn't want to bother anyone,
and couldn't reach Grandma.
So I ran all the way home
in the rain.
After that,
I got really sick.
It was awful.
I only had one thought in my head:
If only
I had a bicycle.
Then I could have gotten home earlier.
You only have a birthday once a year,
and you just want a bicycle?
It's an obsession from my childhood.
Starting tomorrow,
I want to pull myself together
and get back to a normal life.
I'll go back to working at the arcade.
I also want to move back.
But don't worry,
I'll be okay.
Okay.
There are so many seagulls.