Yes.
Does she really think that
she can handle everything
just by talking
after being away from Lan Yue for years?
What a joke!
I know.
With the current performance of the first phase,
no one will forget
who actually built it up.
Right?
She wants to, but who doesn't?
The point is whether I'm willing to.
Alright.
I have something to do.
Okay, bye.
Come in.
What do you want?
I'm here to return this.
After this summer,
I'll go to Beijing.
My mom and I
can't keep in touch with the Lu family.
We can't take anything from them.
Besides, I don't need it.
You came to me
just to
tell me this?
Sit.
You chose
computer science in university, right?
You'd better change to architecture.
I'll arrange it.
Don't worry
about the tuition.
Okay?
I know
I have made you and your mother
suffer a lot.
But I'm your father.
I know
what you want to learn.
So what?
If you really
cared about our life,
it wouldn't have
turned out like this.
You were young back then.
You didn't understand.
You didn't know
what was going on.
You used to...
Alright, alright.
Son,
there's no need to
argue about right and wrong today.
The past
is the past.
What you should focus on now
is your future.
You got into Huaqing University
on your own merit.
So from now on,
you should study harder.
You can't be like
A'Xiao,
who ruined his future
for some little love.
You are a man.
You are an adult.
I'm telling you,
career is more important to a man
than his life.
This fountain pen
is specially customized
for you by your father.
Your name is engraved on it.
Take it.
I believe one day
you will use it.
I know you are a good boy.
Come on.
Have a drink.
No.
You're an adult now.
Take it.
Give it a try.
Come on.
I wish your career
sails smoothly.
Cheers.
Are you alright?
What's going on? What's the situation?
There might be a fire.
Please come out with us first.
Shouldn't you
check on your boss first?
Hurry up!
Let's go.
Mr. Lu.
What's going on?
The situation is unclear.
But we've already
called the fire department.
Let's get out of here.
Where's Lu Xixiao?
Where is he?
He...
Go!
Find A'Xiao!
Find him!
A'Xiao!
Find A'Xiao!
Zhou Wan, are you crazy?
Let's run away together.
Lu Xixiao.
Stop here. Hurry up.
You two go there.
This way. You two go there.
You come with me.
We still can't find A'Xiao.
He might have run away in the chaos.
But
I found Miss Zhou's figure
in the surveillance footage before the power outage.
Keep looking for him.
Whether it's the airport or the train station,
you must find them.
Did you hear me?
Yes, sir.
Find Lu Xixiao,
and bring Zhou Wan back too.
Go.
This has nothing to do with Zhou Wan.
What do you mean?
You're here today
to set me up.
You're trying to help Zhou Wan
get rid of
the Lu Family, right?
It's not
entirely false.
Do you know
what I'll lose?
Well done, Jiang Yan.
I shouldn't have
treated you like a child.
Tomorrow,
General Manager Chang,
who runs a home brand, will hold a family banquet for me.
Compared to A'Xiao,
I think you are more qualified
to be my son
and go to the banquet with me.
You're doing this
because he ran away, right?
You should think
that since Lu Xixiao failed,
you got a chance
to prove yourself.
What if I don't want
this chance?
I'll pick you up tomorrow.
Wait for me here.
Excuse me, two tickets.
Where to?
We want to see snow.
The nearest train will depart in ten minutes.
Only standing tickets are left.
Okay.
Beer, beverages, mineral water,
peanuts, seeds, grilled fish slices.
Come on, put your legs away.
I had a beautiful dream.
What dream did you have?
A dream as beautiful as mine.
Look.
Thank you.
I'm starting.
Three,
two, one.
You didn't say two, one.
You cheated.
You cheated, you're a scoundrel.
Wait, you'll mess it up for him.
Who let you cheat first?
I've finished dismantling.
I'm starting to assemble now.
Starting to assemble now.
You need to take apart the body.
I've taken it all apart.
Okay.
What do you mean?
I've finished putting it together.
You've finished taking it apart,
so you've finished putting it together?
Did you take it apart?
I did.
I just emptied it all out.
Watch the video.
I've finished taking it apart.
After tearing it open,
stuff it in like this.
What's wrong?
You've got it stuck.
Wait a moment.
Don't rush.
Don't pull it out forcefully.
No need to do it this way.
Like this.
Let's go.
I'll carry you.
There's a supermarket ahead. I'll take you there.
Congratulations.
Congratulations to both of you.
Bride and groom.
Tomorrow, bride,
when you walk in
through this door,
the groom should hold the bouquet in his hand...
It's like a fairy tale.
Then hold her hand.
In fairy tales,
the hero and heroine
overcome all kinds of difficulties
and finally get together.
It's a happy ending.
Do you take
this girl
to be your wife?
Yes.
Good.
In sickness and in health,
for richer or poorer...
Although this is not
the ending of our story,
I do.
Good.
I'm already very happy.
Me too.
Good.
And then?
I have something to tell you.
Go ahead.
Let's date, Lu Xixiao.
I want to date you.
Lu Xixiao.
Okay.
Groom,
do you take this woman
to be your lawful wedded wife?
I do.
In sickness and in health,
for richer or poorer,
till death do you part?
I do.
Bride, do you take him?
Okay.
Groom, please kneel on one knee
and present your bouquet to the bride.
Okay, bride.
You can help the groom up.
Applause.
[But you know what?]
[All fairy tales]
[are fake.]
[Grandma.]
[The princes and princesses in the storybooks]
[all live]
[happily ever after.]
Is that true?
What's in the book must be true.
Isn't this a moral kidnapping?
Mom, don't leave me.
The factory has a problem.
Why are you the only one to take responsibility?
What about the promise you made to me before we got married?
What did you say?
After getting married,
we would live a good life.
You wouldn't have to do anything,
no worries,
and we'd live in a big house.
Wasn't that
what you promised me?
I believed our family
would make it through this.
All these years,
wasn't it all
for this factory?
Are fairy tales
all lies?
Yes.
Fairy tales are all lies.
General Manager Chang.
General Manager Lu.
Welcome.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
My pleasure.
Come here.
My son is just
a bit shy.
He's introverted.
Is this the one who got a recommendation to Huaqing?
Yes.
Good.
He's really good-looking.
Mr. Lu, you're so lucky.
Come, have a seat.
Sit down, come on.
Come, sit.
Did you see
the look in General Manager Chang's eyes?
Son,
you did a good job today.
General Manager Chang said he admired you.
He just flattered you.
Chang Kan Home Furnishings
has grown to this scale today.
Who does he need to flatter?
And General Manager Chang
is a man of his word.
I've never seen him
flattering Lu Xixiao.
Have you noticed
when you talked about
the integration of
home furnishings and real estate,
his eyes were shining
when he looked at you?
He admires you so much.
He can't wait for you
to become a member of his family.
Unfortunately,
you are always
my son.
Since he's satisfied,
we're quits.
Look at what you said.
Quits?
Am I not your father?
What I'm doing for you now
is all for your
future.
right?
Come back more often.
Have dinner with me more often.
Okay?
My boy.
Secretary.
Tell the cook
to prepare some good dishes.
I'm going to have a good dinner
with my son tonight.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Lu.
No need, I'm going home.
Why are you going home?
Isn't my home your home too?
Just stay at home.
Mr. Lu, shall we set off now?
Please fasten your seatbelt.
Hello, sir.
I'd like to check in.
Okay, check-in, right?
One room.
A deluxe king room
is 498 yuan per night.
Two standard rooms.
A standard room is 300 yuan.
Two rooms, right?
Okay, your ID card.
Can I swipe the card?
Yes, you can.
Sorry, sir.
This card cannot be used.
It cannot be used?
Yes.
Try this one.
Alright.
This one cannot be used either.
Your card has been...
It's okay.
I have cash.
But for such an expensive hotel,
we might not be able to afford it.
Let's think of another way.
Let's go out and look again.
As long as we are together, it's fine.
Right.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
After you.
Okay.
What's the situation
with the middle schools around here?
I'm planning to rent long-term.
My child will take the entrance exam next year.
I need to consider
his schooling.
Yes, that's a big deal.
Where did you go?
Why are you dressed like this?
I attended an event with a teacher.
It required formal attire.
The food is in the kitchen.
Go grab a bite.
I've already eaten.
You guys are always getting gold medals.
That's impressive.
Yeah.
No. 2 and No. 3 Middle Schools
are both close by.
Yangming High School
is also top-notch.
My son just graduated
from Yangming High School this year.
Really?
Which university did he get into?
He didn't take the Gaokao.
He won an award in a national competition,
and got a direct recommendation to Huaqing University.
That's like the top scorer in Gaokao.
But he didn't take the Gaokao.
How can he be considered
the top scorer without a score?
That's even better than a top student.
Why didn't you say so earlier?
This house of yours
is a treasure spot.
We can even benefit
from the top student's good luck.
This room
has the best lighting
in the entire house.
It's warm in winter and cool in summer.
It's good for the child's eyes
for his eyes.
My son is about
to go to college.
There will be fewer and fewer days
we can spend together.
If I didn't want to spend more time with him,
I wouldn't even be willing
to rent out
my own house.
So many awards.
You're such a good mom.
You've done a great job.
He has trophies
besides these certificates.
He's excellent.
I don't want to rent it.
What?
My son doesn't want to rent it.
Don't worry, son.
We'll rent a better one
in Beijing.
After you graduate and start working...
I said I don't want to rent it.
Can't you understand?
Can you ask me
what I think?
Do you ever care about me?
Am I not your son?
Get out!
I...
I'm sorry.
You can have a look again.
I don't want it.
Take your son to see a doctor.
He's sick.
I'm so sorry.
Why?
I didn't have time
to take your measurements,
so I brought you
A'Xiao's coat.
Try it on.
Lu Xixiao,
why am I always
just a substitute for you?
[Have a try while it's hot.]
[It's delicious.]
With this money,
we can last a little longer.
We have to
be frugal these days.
The trees are still green here.
It won't snow here
in a short time.
We should go
further north.
Go further north?
Which way is north?
North is that way.
That way?
Let's go, head north.
Boss,
I need to repair my bike.
Do you have any
used motorcycles here?
Used?
Well, that bunch over there.
They're all second-hand.
All of these?
You want to buy such a broken one?
No.
If I can fix one,
can you sell it to me at a discount?
You're so capable.
I take these apart
to sell the parts.
If you really can fix it,
I'll give you the cost price.
Okay?
Take a look.
Uncle,
how much did you pay for it?
I paid 200 yuan
for scrap metal.
You were going to
recycle it.
If it can be fixed,
could you
give us a discount?
Miss,
I've got costs to cover.
200 yuan isn't much.
Please,
just 50 yuan off.
Just 50.
Fine.
Could you
throw in two extra oil drums?
Fine,
if you can really fix it,
I'll give you two extra oil drums.
Okay?
Okay, thank you.
Thank you, sir.
This...
So fast?
That's not the one.
Thank you, sir.
Sir.
You said it yourself.
You said this one
and that one is all used.
Listen to me.
No.
Go, go, stop.
Go where you want to go.
But we do need to
plan carefully.
Although the money
we have now
can last for a while,
we'd better find a place
where we can work
to exchange for accommodation.
Work to exchange for accommodation?
What does it mean?
Of course, you can work to exchange for accommodation.
But
I have to tell you in advance.
I provide three meals and accommodation,
but the environment is not very good.
You need to clean up
by yourselves.
Come in.
There are two beds.
Two beds.
That's great.
We can cook.
Look, we can cook.
It's not bad.
Sir, can we live here for a long time?
You can stay here
as long as you want.
But you should know that
the yard
has been deserted for a long time.
You need to spend some time
to clean it up.
A'Xiao, show them out.
- OK. - This way.
Slow down.
The car is over here.
Welcome to come again.
Here.
Did you have fun?
Yes.
Bye.
This is the puppy
left by a client
left behind.
A puppy.
You two
are both so young.
I was young too.
So you two
must cherish each other
and cherish this time.
Shake hands.
The noodles are ready, Zhou Wan.
-Let's eat. -Shake hands.
You're looking at it, not me.
Right?
It looks like you.
Really.
Jin.
Yellow.
Six.
Zhou Xiaoliu.
Zhou Xiaoliu, Zhou Xiaoliu.
Cover yourself with the quilt.
Have a try, Zhou Wan.
It smells so good.
Have a try.
Eat this.
Give me the bowl.
How is it?
It's the best time to eat instant noodles.
Refill.
Why aren't you eating?
I'm eating.
I'll eat this.
Go quickly.
Go eat leaning on something.
I heard
it'll be a while before it snows.
I've already made a list
of things we need for the next few days.
Let's go to the supermarket
to buy them.
Okay.
And we can buy some books.
Buy books?
Why?
I want to study for another year.
Another year?
Why do you suddenly want to do that?
Grandma always wanted me
to go to university
and see more of the world.
I want to fulfill her wish.
Okay.
No problem.
What about you?
Do you want to study for another year with me?
What are your plans?
I'll follow your lead.
You'll follow my lead?
Just follow my lead.
Do whatever I say.
What are you laughing at?
I just think
that seeing you plan
our life like this,
I'll definitely be
under your control in the future.
Who wants to control you?
If you don't control me, who will?
You've eaten all the noodles.
do you care about me?
I do.
But honestly,
I've never really been interested
in this world,
or had any dreams for the future.
I thought it was all pretty meaningless.
But
now that
I'm with you,
I feel excited
when I think about the future.
I never
make promises
like
forever.
But this time,
I really want to tell you,
Zhou Wan,
let's spend every summer
together,
Okay?
And every winter.
You scared me.
Every season.
I thought you wouldn't say yes.
The admission score of the Academy of Fine Arts
isn't very high.
Why do you choose
such a difficult one?
I set the expected value higher
so I can be more confident.
I can't be your junior.
I've been
your teacher.
That's different.
How?
We're different.
Behave yourself.
If I make progress,
I'll get a reward.
What reward?
If I improve by a certain amount,
you have to give me a kiss.
This is a bookstore.
Go away.
Read your own book.
Hello?
Hello, A'Xiao.
Where are you?
I'm at the bookstore.
I'm buying books for Zhou Wan.
She'll read them during her study year.
What?
Are you serious?
What's wrong?
Why?
You don't have to do this.
Just wait for a while.
No matter where you want to study,
art or auto repair,
your dad can
to study.
Because I don't just
want to date her.
I want to be with her,
and stay by her side.
Only in this way,
can our life trajectories
be on the same line.
I want to be with her
honestly.
Do you understand?
Who says I don't?
I know Zhou Wan is special,
and you really like her.
What's that saying online?
Not afraid to enter the world with pure feelings.
With such a wild heart,
can he really settle down
and study hard?
Yes,
he promised me.
Don't be fooled by his appearance.
He is actually
the most devoted person.
Once he makes up his mind,
he'll stick to it for life.
His devotion has nothing
to do with his study,
right?
He never
cared about anyone before.
But now that he has Zhou Wan,
everything has changed.
He told me
he's gonna study hard
and go to college
with Zhou Wan in the same city.
He's been without a mom since he was little,
and he doesn't
even have a relationship with his dad.
I couldn't really
convince him before,
but now that I've heard
his plan,
I think it's good.
So, sister,
you should
treat him well.
I'm talking to my bestie on the phone.
Don't interrupt.
They are together.
Can't you two
make a phone call together in the shop?
This is our little dog,
Zhou Xiaoliu.
See?
Xiaoliu.
Hello.
Is he handsome?
This is my sister.
Is she pretty?
Show me yours first.
I'll show you first.
You first, you first.
Show me yours first.
How about this?
Count to three.
Three, two, one.
What a coincidence.
Do you know what I'm going to give you?
Of course I don't know.
Of course I don't know either.
Then why would...
I know.
Because we are
destined.