ALL DEPICTED EVENTS ARE FICTIONAL
You called me
to say "sweet dreams," right?
I know what you're trying to do.
Qin, what do you think of Duang?
I'm worried about Qin.
I'm worried he'd choose that person.
You even got a teddy.
From an old fling.
I've devoted my love to him,
and I'll never give up.
QIN VIEWED YOUR STORY
Hey!
Someone named Qin liked my Story.
Qin liked my Story.
I'm back at my place. Where are you?
The problem isn't Duang.
You don't let anyone in.
So much so, I feel bad for him.
This is who I am.
I'm not pushing anyone away.
Right.
That means
you're opening up to the guy, correct?
Qin!
Are you tired? I bought you a drink.
I danced so poorly.
I mean, I tried,
but it looked like I didn't, right?
He really did work hard.
It's true, though.
You should be proud of him.
TWO WEEKS LATER
Hello.
An Americano, please.
Okay, coming right up.
I gave it to him,
the first puppy to ever
order an Americano while smiling.
I guess he doesn't need us anymore.
He vanished into thin air during break.
Now, he's out here smiling
and ordering a cup of coffee.
'Cause I'm in love, and I can't help it.
Gosh, stop it. Update us.
- How are things?
- I'd rather not say.
- Then shut your mouth!
- Hey!
Let me have my moment.
I want to tell you about the huge leap.
The huge leap?
- Don't tell me you're dating.
- Not yet.
What?
- So you're seeing each other more often?
- Not exactly.
What the hell?
I don't want to make Qin
feel uncomfortable.
- This is more than I expected.
- Right.
So what? Can you tell us now?
Here it is.
Qin has been replying to my messages.
He answers three messages a day.
This is so special! Take a look.
- WHERE ARE YOU?
- HOME
- GOOD LUCK.
- MM.
Clear as day.
Don't give me that condescending look.
I'm not done.
Guys, we were this close!
Hey.
Hey there.
What song are you listening to?
Here.
I got you an Americano.
You liked my IG Story too?
Hey!
There!
You're being obvious.
How suspicious!
You're flustered, aren't you?
I'm also flustered.
You smiled!
I finally saw you smile!
Let's go practice!
I'm down for over 1,000 practices!
No, one million practices! Let's go.
Time to dance!
Qin smiled at me.
It was the first time ever.
Right…
I'm just getting started. Let me continue.
Qin.
Anyone who gets to date you
will be so freaking lucky.
Am I close to becoming your boyfriend?
Stop it.
You're annoyed?
Listen. They say that
painting or coloring something
can relieve stress and help us calm down.
So, shall we?
I'm done.
You feel me?
I was on a da-te with Qin.
What the hell is a "da-te"?
Spell it.
Why didn't you say the actual word?
- Yeah.
- A date.
It's not considered a date.
So I called it a da-te.
So detailed with your story.
Are you done?
No.
What's this song?
What is this song?
It's…
"Fa Khruem Khruem" by Scrubb.
What are you doing out here?
Well…
I'm here waiting for you.
I missed you.
This time, can I drive you home?
For real?
If that's the case…
can I carry your bag for you?
wanna watch a movie with me?
But not today.
I got everything.
I've made a huge leap.
Duang, you're embarrassing us.
Yeah.
Guys.
Today, I'm having
dinner with Qin after class.
I'll also be driving him to his place.
- Then, I'll ask him to watch a movie.
- Right.
I've got popcorn and everything ready too.
Your Americano is ready!
I'm off to see Qin now!
Qin!
That'll be 60 baht.
Those guys are paying.
What?
Come on.
He's so uniquely cringe,
yet he wants to be with Qin.
Hey, that hurt.
What you looking at?
Why are you wearing these pants?
I ran out of clean clothes.
And you like wearing them?
Didn't you hear me?
Well…
Can you not wear them?
Are you nuts?
Fine.
Stop staring at my legs.
I'm sorry.
I'll stop staring.
But I'll be busy at noon,
helping with my friends' project.
No need to tell me that.
I have to. I don't want you to be lonely.
Stop this.
It's because I like you.
Just go away already.
I'll text you.
Duang!
Gam! I was just about to call.
Thanks for helping with the group project.
No worries, we're friends.
You're so sweet, you know that?
- You're always nice to everyone.
- Right.
Let's head inside,
so you can get ready.
Come and sit here.
And, Duang, this is Yim,
your modeling partner for the shoot.
Hi, Duang.
You're so handsome.
You also look great.
- She's actually partnering with me?
- Come on!
Everyone thinks you're cute.
Don't be so humble.
What? Me?
Gam, the way you talk…
It's not a different Duang, right?
Duang. It's you, the one and only.
Come on, time for makeup.
Sweetie, make sure
he looks nice and handsome, okay?
Got it?
Nook,
this way.
- Hello.
- Hi.
We're doing a promo shoot
for the university t-shirt.
I want you to look charming and bright.
As for you, be cool and be yourself, okay?
I'm counting on you.
After you're done, go get changed there.
- Sure.
- Okay.
Can I get a quick shot of you
for the student union?
- Sure thing!
- Okay. This background will do.
You're too far apart!
Can you guys get a bit closer?
There you go.
This one's a video, okay? Closer.
Okay, rolling.
Some physical contact, maybe?
- Physical?
- Yes, like… Yeah! Like that!
Make it look like you guys are close.
Nice and cute.
Okay.
I'm sorry, Duang.
Ready?
Make yourselves look adorable and lively.
One, two, three!
YOUR CLASS IS OVER, RIGHT?
I'M WAITING FOR YOU AT THE SAME SPOT.
Hey, guys. Care for some food?
Let's go.
I'm busy.
Qin.
Have you seen this? It's your lover boy.
See?
All you've been doing
is playing hard to get.
See what happened?
He did what he was told to.
Don't make it a big deal.
But you don't care about
any of this anyway, right?
It's work.
Don't tell me
you can actually get jealous? What?
Isn't this a surprise?
I'm gonna go.
- What?
- See you.
Already?
See? You showed him the post,
and he just left.
He's gone.
I bet he's going to see Duang.
True.
I think the lover boy has
managed to chip away at his walls.
Yeah.
Cool.
Is he coming?
- Who?
- Is Qin coming?
"Is he? Is he coming?"
Gosh, you guys are useless!
Duang!
Gam asked me to bring you this iPad.
Oh, Yim!
Thank you.
I thought Gam would bring it to me.
It's fine.
It's on the way to my building.
Is this your friend?
Yeah. We were modeling together.
Yim, this is Jamie,
and that's Pae.
Hello.
Ask her to come eat with us.
Yim, do you want to eat with us
if you're free? It's on me.
Big spender. I'd like that.
Duang.
Qin!
Are you hungry?
Let's go eat.
Garlic shrimp?
These guys are coming with us, though.
Is it cool with you?
Anything goes.
You're Qin, right?
I'm Yim.
Your friend is very handsome, Duang.
You might not remember me,
but back at Freshy Night,
you looked really cool.
But how do you know Duang and his friends?
You guys are
in different faculties, right?
I missed you so much!
Duang is killing it today.
He's absolutely on fire!
How do you want me to respond?
Anything.
I want a heartwarming response.
I missed you too.
Is that heartwarming enough?
This… My heart's about to burst!
You guys are really funny.
Since when were we trying to be funny?
Honestly, Jamie, we should tell her.
It'll be disastrous if we don't.
I know, but it'll be fine.
Let me enjoy this.
Shall we get going?
Let's go eat!
Thank you!
No need to rub it in.
What do we do now?
What are you waiting for?
Qin!
Sit with me in the back.
I really want to sit next to you.
Let me take care of your stuff.
Are you watching any good shows
or movies these days?
If you are, I'd love some recommendations.
I do. I want to watch A Star Is Born.
Qin and I
are going to watch it at his place.
However, he's been busy, so we
haven't had a chance to watch it. Right?
What's the film about?
It's a romantic drama film
about two singers.
I want to see it as well.
You definitely should.
I think it'll be good.
We can talk about it
after I watch it with Qin.
Will you be free soon?
I want to watch it with you.
I have to focus on driving now.
I can't wait to look at you face-to-face.
Don't miss me just yet, okay?
Eyes on the road.
Sure thing.
Duang, you're so polite
when you talk to your friends.
I'm trying to win Qin.
Isn't that right?
But you're failing.
I'm so sorry.
Qin, I'm sorry.
How about we swap seats right away?
It's okay.
Seats don't matter.
I'm really sorry, Qin.
Sorry for what?
Gosh, you're so unique.
Just shut it.
Clueless!
Good grief, you're in trouble now!
Right?
Hello!
You're here with so…
Take a seat! So many of you.
Have a seat.
All right.
Don't look so confused!
This is your seat,
at the end of the table.
- Isn't this a good spot?
- Thank you, ma'am.
Isn't this nice?
What are you guys having?
The usual? Garlic shrimp?
As for you?
Gosh, you forgot already?
Basil with crispy pork belly.
I was about to say that!
- Make it two!
- Okay. Got it.
I'll also have garlic shrimp.
Sit tight.
Your food will be ready shortly.
Thank you for inviting me.
I'm so glad I'm here again.
I didn't expect you to say yes.
And,
I was so freaking excited
during the photoshoot.
Really?
I wasn't nervous at all
since everyone was so nice.
Gam and Yim, I mean.
Yeah, I can tell.
Hey, should we watch a movie?
I really wanna watch one with you.
Are you sleepy?
We can watch one later, you know?
Are you asleep?
Qin.
What?
That's strange.
What's going on?
What is it?
Is he sulking? What's he upset about?
What is it about?
Was it about Yim apologizing?
Were you jealous over me?
Nothing's going on with Yim.
We just met at the photoshoot.
And I only invited her to a meal
because I wanted to thank her
for returning my iPad.
I forgot it earlier.
Please don't be upset with me.
Fine.
How are you feeling right now?
Yim's pretty cute. She'd be good for you.
Don't say that. Let's make up.
Let's make up.
Make up for what? I'm not mad.
Where are you going?
Bathroom.
Okay, don't take too long.
I'll make popcorn. Hurry back, okay?
You're so freaking cute, that it hurts.
Are you over the thing with Yim and me?
Are we gonna watch the movie?
Let's finish it, so you can go.
Let's watch then.
You didn't wash your face properly.
Stop talking in that tone.
Just say it if you like it.
No one else is here,
so what's with the act?
It's not like that.
So what is it?
Isn't that too close?
Oh, you!
Don't speak like that often.
Why? Are you saying
it makes your heart race?
Am I right?
If you admit it,
I'll only use that tone sometimes.
You're so cute.
Shut up.
You're so freaking cute.
You're the cutest.
Shall we clink our glasses together?
What's your name?
It's Mar.
What?
Hey.
Is he alive?
He's alive.
What was that?
I thought it was a mosquito.
What's up with you?
What? Just spit it out.
Why are you zoning out?
It's hard to explain.
All right, whatever.
Wait! Sit down.
You fucking bastard.
Why did you call me that?
My heart is only this tiny.
Hey, for real. What's going on?
Don't force me!
I'm out.
Pae…
Can you just listen?
If you mess around with me one more time,
I'll take that ice
and throw it in your face.
You got nothing good to say to me.
Who taught you to talk like that?
Fine.
I've been waiting for someone
at the same place and time.
I don't remember how many nights I waited,
but they never came.
Hey!
Are we losing a player
to the lover boy squad?
Lover boy, my ass. Not in my book.
I won't lose my heart to a game
'cause players never fall in love.
That was so fucking dramatic.
I can't even spell the damn word.
Does it start with an L or an R? R…
You can't spell
because you're a dumbass, Jettana.
We're late.
Let's get to class,
so you can sharpen your skills for once.
Prachai, did you ever love me--
You're making me sad.
- Stop acting and go to class.
- Come back to me!
Do you know that
skeletons of different ages
look different?
The same goes for different genders.
Now…
What's wrong with you, Duang?
When I watched a movie with Qin yesterday,
he kinda acted jealous of Yim and me.
That's when you realized?
Part of me worried he might overthink it,
but another part of me was like,
"Shit, that means he has feelings for me."
Today's practice is gonna be so awkward!
Isn't it too late to be awkward?
You've been through
practice after practice,
Lover boy of Nakhon Pathom.
Top dog, second to none.
You're all alone on the podium!
Right, Duang.
Don't forget our meeting tonight
after practice.
Hey. Did you even hear what I said?
Duang.
And did you hear what I said, Jettana?
Yes, Professor.
Have you ever paid attention to me?
- I'm listening, sir.
- You think you're so smart?
Stand up and answer my question.
How about this? If you get this right,
everyone can go home.
The class will be over.
The question is,
what is the motto of Phrae province?
Jeez, Professor.
Who could even answer that?
We're all from Nakhon Pathom.
The knowledgeable one could.
"Mo hom fabric and teak wood.
Place of Phra Lo's love.
Home of Cho Hae.
Famed Phae Mueang Phi.
The generous people of Phrae."
Jettana, are you from Phrae?
No, I'm not.
Shit, you're clever.
I'm Jettana, the Encyclopedia.
Professor, don't forget your promise.
I keep my promises.
I'm a man of my word.
Fine, class is over, you suckers!
- "Famed Phae Mueang Phi!"
- Shit, you're awesome!
See you later.
Bye, the Encyclopedia.
Not a dictionary, it's an encyclopedia!
One, two…
- One…
- Swoosh.
- Touch.
- Step.
Yay!
My boys are growing up!
True.
You guys are doing amazing,
especially when you dance.
Duang, you keep getting better and better.
Hey, your making me blush, Alice.
I gotta give all the credits to Qin.
With an instructor like Qin,
anyone would have crushed it.
I asked a senior to do the choreography,
but Duang worked hard too.
I see.
Wait, I'm sensing some chemistry here.
Is there anything I should know?
Well, silly you!
Alice, what could there be?
- There's none.
- Right, there's none.
I think I'm losing it.
Right, are we done?
If we are, I'll head out.
Yeah, go ahead.
Excuse me, Alice.
- Bye, Tinn.
- All right.
Hey. Do you wanna
go grab something to eat?
I already have plans.
With your friends, right?
I almost had a heart attack.
Do you mind if I ask where?
I'd say I do mind.
Please tell me.
A bar near the university.
I'm going there myself.
X's bar, right?
Yes.
- Do you want me--
- No need.
My friends are picking me up.
We can just go there together
since we're going to the same place.
It's more economical that way.
Why can't we?
Then I'll just walk you downstairs.
No need. And don't follow me.
How will I get out of here then?
Hello, Funan. What's up?
Right, what are you up to?
Dance practice?
That's done for the day. What's up?
You've been practicing for ages.
When is your show?
Pretty soon. Are you gonna come watch?
Can I?
Dad asked you to come.
- Gosh, Mr. Know-It-All.
- All right.
I'll keep you posted. Anything else?
Nope. Right, how's my place?
Your place is spotless.
If that's all, I'll hang up.
All right.
You good?
I'm fine. I just wanted to come.
Do you wanna be here,
or do you wanna get drunk?
Hold up.
Is this a matter of the heart?
What did Duang do?
Nothing.
What? So what's up with you?
All right, let's cheers.
- Let's go.
- Come on.
- Cheers.
Thank you for coming.
You're here, Smile?
- Happy birthday, buddy.
- Thank you.
Took you long enough.
Come. Take a seat.
Come sit here.
- Yo.
- Come on.
What's up?
How are things at your shop?
I'm sorry. I had a ton of customers.
- It's fine.
- That's why I'm late.
- You're here now.
- Right.
- X! Hello!
- Hi.
Smile!
My fraternity bro! I've missed you.
Give me a hug!
You guys, get away from me.
Come and take a seat.
Here.
- Ready?
- Come on.
- Cheers!
- All right.
- Thank you so much, guys
- Right.
Cheers!
Thank you.
Who are you looking for?
That's Qin.
You're not going to say hi to him?
No, he's with his friends.
Since when did you
start caring about that?
He said he'd be at the same bar as me,
but wouldn't let me take him.
In a way, he told me to stay away.
It's like he was pushing me away.
You get upset too easily.
What are you guys talking about?
It's about someone
Duang is trying to win over.
Really? Who is it?
See those three guys
sitting at the counter?
The one in the white.
- There.
- Yeah.
Why? He likes him?
What?
It's nothing.
Where are you going?
Answering a phone call.
Duang.
- Gam?
- Hi.
My friend in the white top
has a crush on you.
Three of them are wearing white.
Ying!
You're single, right?
Can you give her your contact info?
I'm sorry, Gam, but I like someone else.
It's fine.
- I'll see you later.
- Okay.
I'll go cheer her up.
I'm also single, by the way.
- Sheesh.
- My buddy's single.
Come on. It's dangerous around here.
Where's Qin?
His friends are still there.
So he's probably still here.
Maybe he's in the bathroom.
I'll be right back then.
I'll be back, guys. Give me a moment.
- Hey!
- Back off.
Are you all right?
I don't want to talk to you.
- All right, let's make a toast.
- Let's.
- Jamie, come on.
- Let's go.
- Cheers.
- Bottoms up.
Easy.
- Are you drunk?
- No, I'm not.
- Come on. Keep 'em coming.
- One more.
Come on, one more!
- One more!
- I've had enough.
I want to draw something.
- Do you have a pen?
- Of course I do.
- What are you doing?
- A sketch.
- A sketch?
- Right now?
- What's gotten into you?
- Of what?
I don't know.
I'm making a sketch
of the sun and the moon.
The sun and the moon?
You can still sketch?
He's in one of his moods.
Check it out. It's done!
Hey, this is beautiful.
Come on, take a look.
What do you think?
I'm a man who studies Decorative Arts,
and so did you guys, right?
You're still a kid.
Why shoot me down?
- Right.
- Let me take a photo.
Here you go. Take a photo of me?
No, the paper towel.
Three, two… Cheese!
There you go.
Let me see that again.
Not bad for being drunk.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Do you want to get a tattoo of this?
Yeah! Get a tattoo.
He runs a tattoo shop.
- Do it.
- No, I'd rather not.
- What?
- Want a tattoo?
- Don't chicken out.
- Come on, don't.
Sheesh.
I'm not chickening out.
Here's the deal.
I usually charge 4,000 baht per tattoo.
I'll give you two tattoos for 3,200 baht.
- Interested?
- This is a steal at this rate.
You can't say no.
- Yeah.
- Do it.
- Guys, let's not.
- Why?
He's just one massive chicken.
I'd better tell my friends at uni.
Duang's a chicken.
He's too weak to get a tattoo.
- Sheesh.
- Yeah.
I'm down! It's just a tattoo.
I'll pay in advance too.
See you tomorrow at noon.
Hell ya!
- Seriously?
- Are you?
- Yes, I am.
- Perfect.
There you go! A real man pays up!
Here we go!
He's actually serious.
He's doing it for real.
He actually paid him.
- Wanna to get tattoo?
- He paid.
- Why the long face?
- Come on, kiddo.
Drink up.
- Let's keep it going.
- Okay.
Kiddo, are you good?
Hey, come on.
Where have you been?
Everyone's gone?
Obviously!
You've been gone for ages.
It was just a quick visit.
Sheesh!
The state he's in…
What should we do with him?
Duang!
Qin.
Qin!
- Hey. I've got an idea.
- What is it?
Take Duang to Qin's place.
Hey!
You're such a genius.
- You carry him.
- What?
Come on, help me out!
Gosh.
His face is about to hit the floor.
Hold him, come on!
What?
He's so heavy.
Qin…
Where does Qin live? Duang, do you know?
I do. I'll show you the way.
One, three, four, five.
- One, three…
- How cool is this?
He's completely hammered,
but he got us here.
This is it!
The guard recognized Duang,
so he let us in.
I'm sorry, Qin.
Duang refused to tell us
where his keycard is.
And we couldn't find it.
Can we drop him off here?
I'm staying with my partner,
so I can't bring him to my place.
What about you, Jamie?
This warrior has to go to war.
The night isn't over for me, Qin.
- Please take him.
Hey, Duang.
You're here.
Qin!
Are you the real Qin?
If he crosses the line,
feel free to smack him.
Why are you so adorable?
Are you the real one?
Are you?
If it weren't for us,
he'd have to wait until his next life
to stay over at Qin's.
Wait, Jamie.
Duang's room doesn't need a keycard.
Come on, it was fine.
It worked out, didn't it?
- Let's go.
- How did you go from stupid to smart?
- What?
- Nothing.
Hey.
You're looking at me?
I'm thinking about what to do with you.
Why are you mad at me?
Can you please tell me?
I won't do it again.
Not now. You're drunk.
I've sobered up.
I'm actually not mad at you.
You didn't do anything wrong.
I simply…
don't like it when
I can't control my emotions.
I love it when I've got nobody by my side.
It's stable, safe…
and there's not much to think about.
It's because of me, isn't it?
Yes.
I won't do it again.
You've done nothing, so why say that?
What did you say?
Nothing.
I think…
I'm going to take a shower.
I have a headache.
You don't say.
You were drinking like a fool.
So harsh.
Go shower already.
So you can go to bed.
I still love you when you're harsh.
Get going.
Hey!
I'm not wearing any underwear.
That hurt!
By the way,
we look like the characters
from Bananas in Pyjamas.
Hello, B1.
You've sobered up, B2?
Do you want to go home then?
I still can't walk straight.
Qin.
I'm not drunk, by the way.
I like you.
My feelings are
still the same as on the first day.
I'm not here to pressure you.
I just want you to know that
nothing has changed.
I'm prepared to love you
with everything I have.
Hey, you.
That hurt!
My bad. I was caught off guard.
Took you a while.
Those were some mad blows.
It's fine. Since you're awake,
I was thinking we could cuddle
and sleep a bit more.
Please?
Hey!
We don't have dance practice today.
Since we're free, should we go out?
Like, we can go on a date or something.
Who says I'm free?
I have plans.
Wanna come with?
Yes!
I wanna come with!
You!
Qin asked me out!
FIRE TIGER RAMEN
Hey, wanna grab a bite first?
No, we're gonna be late.
For what?
I thought you were shopping.
Or are you meeting someone?
I'm not meeting anyone. You are.
I'm down! It's just a tattoo.
I'll pay in advance too.
See you tomorrow at noon.
There you go!
A real man pays up!
Holy shit.
You knew about that?
The whole bar heard.
Show-offs gotta show up.
Oh, man!
I can just skip it. It wasn't much.
It's still money.
Can I not go? I'm afraid of needles!
Come on.
Hey!
How do you know about this place?
I confirmed two designs.
So?
I can just do one, right?
It's such a shame
the other one is so pretty.
- I'm just showing you, not asking--
- I'll do it.
I'm not forcing you or anything.
You can't force me.
You're really here.
Thought you'd chicken out.
Jeez, bro. I already paid.
Don't want to waste your money?
Are you each getting one?
You actually managed
to find someone else, huh?
All right, where do you want it?
Inner ankle, please. What about you, Qin?
Left ankle, please.
Then I'm gonna do mine on my right ankle.
Okay, great.
Excuse me while I prepare the equipment.
Hey, you.
Hey. I think I'll pass out for sure.
It's not gonna hurt.
Just like a car crash.
How does that not hurt?
I read about it. Ankles don't hurt.
Really?
Yeah.
Did you do any research?
I'm sorry.
Should I go first since you're so scared?
Not a chance. I wanna go first.
If it's too much, you won't have to do it.
Is it gonna hurt?
Not too much. Easy.
Ready?
- I am.
- Okay.
Here we go.
- I haven't started.
- Right.
Three, two…
Wanna hold it?
Hold still.
That hurts.
No shit, it's a tattoo.
Of course it hurts.
Here comes the color.
It will hurt a little.
Is it gonna hurt a lot?
A little more than earlier.
Like an ant bite?
Like a colony.
Almost done.
Just a little more.
Done.
There you go.
That's pretty.
Here. Let me wipe it clean.
The sun looks good on you.
Come on. Let me cover it up.
And don't get it wet for about a day.
Okay.
What do you say, Qin? Ready for yours?
Sure.
I can feel it.
Ouch, Smile, slow down!
Qin, does it hurt?
No.
- How do you feel, Qin? Still good?
- I'm fine.
See? He doesn't even feel it.
No way. I'm sure he can feel it too.
- How do you know that?
- Smile! Be gentle!
Just a little bit more.
Excuse me, Qin.
You get up. Let him back on the bed.
- Why are you whining?
- It just hurts thinking he's in pain.
Okay then.
You're worried, huh?
- Or is this your ankle?
- It's Qin's.
Did it hurt?
What?
Why are you guys here?
You're the ones who told Qin
where the shop is!
What?
You're nuts. I never told him it was here.
- Was it you?
- Bro, what?
Are you done?
That's right, I am.
Damn, that sucks.
We came to watch you get tattooed.
Did you get both designs?
Both designs, my ass.
Qin got one of them.
Noob.
Don't get me started.
It was like being slashed by a knife!
Was it that bad, Qin?
Or is he just being extra?
It didn't really hurt.
Yikes! What a noob.
Hey, fam.
- The whole squad is here.
- Hi.
Hi, there.
Want a tattoo? I'll design one for you.
I have to pass. My mom won't let me.
What about you, Jamie?
Let me think about it.
It's permanent, man.
I think to think a lot.
Enough with the excuses.
You're just a chicken, Jettana.
You too, Prachai.
What?
I just really love my mom,
unlike you, chicken.
Yeah, at least I'm not you,
a drunk show-off.
In your face, sucker!
How about this?
To prove you're not chickens,
I'll do it for free.
That's a steal.
Mommy?
Have you eaten?
Papa!
I miss you!
What a bunch of chickens.
Unlike me, who's as strong as a dog!
A whiny one, sure.
Whining like a dog.
- Thank you, Smile. Bye.
- Bye.
Smile.
See ya.
Go home!
Why are you taking me back to your place?
Got something planned?
I have parents, you know?
Go home then.
But my parents told me,
"If you love someone,
try spending the night
in their room first."
I brought you here because it's late.
If you wanna go, be my guest.
No way! I'm staying.
Then I'll take a shower.
Do you need a hand?
Sure.
Don't do this to me.
I could literally die.
You haven't even won me over.
Are you really dying?
I'd better hurry then.
That's Qin! He's here!
Qin is here!
I want to practice dance.
I've dedicated
too much time to basketball.
Shaking in your boots?
Will you be mad at me if I fail miserably?
If you fuck up and
embarrass yourself in front of everyone,
I'll stay on the sinking ship with you.
We'll fuck up together. Okay?
I'm so lucky that I've been
giving it my all just to love you.