ALL DEPICTED EVENTS ARE FICTIONAL
A shark washes ashore
I forgot.
I won't get to see Qin during break.
Qin, please practice
with him during the break.
- And you're here by yourself?
- Do you see anybody else?
I need some advice.
I'm serious about my singing.
I can't sing, and I don't know what to do.
I don't want to burden you.
Do you want to
practice singing at my place?
You invited me to your place?
What are you looking at?
I've never been here.
It's nothing special.
Your room smells nice.
And yours is disgusting.
Don't make assumptions
if you haven't been to my place.
You even got a teddy. It's so adorable!
From an old fling.
And you kept it? You still have feelings.
An old fling. We parted ways ages ago.
The teddy did nothing wrong.
Why should I throw it away?
That cuts deep.
Something like that.
How did I do?
You did fine.
Was it out of tune?
Not really.
Do you have a prize for me?
You're crossing the line.
Let's call it a day. It's getting late.
Thank you.
Back to your house.
I live in a condo, not a house.
Whatever. Go to your condo already.
It's my older brother's, not mine.
His name is Funan.
He's not as cute as me.
But he lives at home.
Did I ask?
Just leave. I don't care.
Both my house and condo
are so far from here.
Would it be okay
if I spent the night here?
No.
Without hesitation? I understand.
Being here is beyond my wildest dreams.
Actually, you're worried
I'll do nasty things to you, right?
So dramatic.
Hey, let me see it.
Hey.
You're worried about me.
I'm counting to ten.
Get out of my room,
or I won't let you back in.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight. Seven.
Six.
Five.
Do you want me to send you flying out?
I'll get to stay longer, right?
A perfect dodge.
Okay! I'll leave now!
Next time, let me stay over.
I wasn't finished.
I made you blush, didn't I?
Mom?
Hello, Mom?
Hello, Duang.
You called me. You miss me, don't you?
Of course, I do!
You're on your semester break, right?
Come home and see me?
I'm actually thinking of coming home.
I really miss you, Mom.
What? Really?
How about coming home right now?
I'll make your favorite soup.
I'd better get going then.
I'll be there in a flash.
Why are you smiling?
You didn't get up when I woke you up
for our workout.
Now that you're home,
won't you workout with me?
Look at Funan, he came.
You'd better take care of
your health, all right?
That's right.
It was too early.
I just wanted to sleep in,
now that I'm home, Dad.
What's on your phone?
Why were you smiling?
Let me see it.
Nope. It was nothing.
I was doomscrolling.
That's not a good way to spend your time.
You've always been like this.
You're being too laid-back, Duang.
Why not stay home for your break?
I told Mom I have an event at university.
An event? What is it?
Why does it have to take place
during the break?
I asked Mom, and she told me to ask you.
Are you hiding something from u?
Or have you been doing
something pointless?
Nope. I wasn't lying.
It's not anything pointless either.
I'm actually working
on a university project.
My seniors needed my help.
Can you really trust the seniors?
He's right. Can you trust them?
You shouldn't listen
to what they say too much.
I know! I'm a grown-up now.
I know my way around things.
Come here, you.
You know, yet you're so forgetful.
Last month,
you forgot to pay the electricity bill.
What would you do
if it weren't for your brother?
I'm a lost cause.
Mom!
- I have something to tell you!
- Duang!
What are you cooking?
It smells delightful!
Dad, I'm going to take a shower.
Hey, Funan!
Mom!
What is it, Duang?
Dad and Funan are picking on me.
What? Why the outburst?
They always tease you, no?
Who made all of this? It looks so tasty.
You said that you wanted
Betong chicken and spicy salad.
- So I made it all just for you.
- You're right.
I love you so much, Mom.
Eat up and enjoy, Duang.
Qin?
- Are you back from the condo?
- Hello, son.
Here. Have some fruit.
Here you go, son.
Thank you.
- Here's yours, honey.
- Thank you, sweetie.
This is Betong chicken.
Although it doesn't look lovely,
it sure is tasty,
just like me.
Then there's spicy salad with salted egg,
my favorite.
I'm about to have breakfast.
I wish you were here with me.
Glued to your phone, I see.
Are you glued to the phone
or someone you're talking to?
I want to know who it is now.
I'd introduce the person to you,
but I'm not sure if they'll say yes.
What? Are you taking this one seriously?
As seriously as I'll ever be, Mom!
Duang. You scared me.
PODDUANG
HAVE YOU EATEN?
Qin.
Finish the fruit first
before looking at your phone.
Yes.
Was it a friend from university?
Have you made a lot of friends there?
You should invite some over.
We can cook for them.
- Not many.
- That's okay, son.
But choose your friends carefully.
For the sake of your future,
having good connections
goes a long way.
Yes.
Of course I have.
I'd have starved
if I'd waited for you to ask.
Qin.
I'm sorry.
Sweetie, it's okay. He's probably done.
Qin, we're heading out.
Would you like to join us?
I'll stay. Go ahead.
You're not going to ask
where we're off to?
Where are you off to?
To our office, of course.
Qin, it's probably about time.
You should come with us
when you have the chance.
Maybe later. I have rehearsal.
You do realize what we're doing
is for your future, right?
I know you're into fragrances.
Yes.
I've seen you working in
the fragrance industry since I was little.
Of course I'm passionate about it.
Duang.
Living alone,
do you manage to eat properly?
I skip meals when I get lazy or forget.
But I keep Funan's room clean.
You can see for yourself.
I believe you, Duang.
If you need anything,
you have to tell me, okay?
You'll be the first to know, I promise.
Pinky promise.
- Promise.
Promise. Promise.
Promise.
- Promise.
By the way, on Instagram,
your friend tagged you.
You've been singing?
The seniors needed my help.
Hey, Mom showed me the video.
You have a natural gift for singing.
You should've studied voice.
Jazz suits me better.
Okay, that's fine.
When you're close to graduating,
I'll have you train
at my friend's record label.
Sweetie, I think it's too soon.
Qin is just a freshman.
We should let him choose
what he wants to study.
I just want to
pave the way for his career.
What are you having, Qin?
Do you know what I want to enjoy?
I want to enjoy a meal with you.
Anyone but you.
- Ouch!
- Duang?
- Duang!
- My chest hurts!
What's wrong? Where does it hurt?
That's your heart!
- Honey! Duang is in pain!
- Duang!
He can't breathe!
I told you to take care of your health.
- It hurts here.
- Told you!
- Here.
- I told you so.
- Use me as an example.
- He fell.
- Duang fell.
- Does it hurt that bad, son?
It's that bad.
- Let's get him to a hospital.
- Yes?
- Which hospital?
- Get the phone!
He has insurance.
Yeah.
I'm upset. I haven't been home in ages.
The moment I saw my dad,
he turned into a grumbling machine,
complaining I hadn't been exercising
and asking why I'm staying home for break.
When I told him about the event,
he told me I was being nonsensical.
Funan too.
Complaining that
I forgot to pay the electricity bill.
Making me feel like I'm always wrong.
Don't beat yourself up.
They're worried about you.
They're treating me like I'm a baby boy.
I'm not a kid anymore, am I?
You're the youngest son.
No matter what,
your mom will always see you as her baby.
What would you know, American boy?
No use in rambling.
I wish they'd let me fly
on my own like you.
It's okay.
Don't be upset.
Let's change the subject. I want to brag.
- About Qin?
- It's Qin.
What? You knew?
I didn't even have to guess. That's it.
Wait, I didn't even get to talk about it!
Jamie, are you listening to me?
I don't wanna hear it, Duang.
That's it. I'm having a drink.
What are you doing?
Have you gone to bed?
WANNA MEET UP TOMORROW?
EVERYONE IS COMING
CALLING
You called me?
It was an accident.
Right, an accident.
Just tell me if you miss me.
You should get your brain checked.
You're making me blush.
All I have in my brain is you.
What did you do today?
I stayed at home.
I stayed at home, too!
But Funan is so annoying.
- Your older brother?
- You remember?
He has a weird name.
My parents are archaeologists.
That's why they named us after old coins.
Funan.
Duang, short for Podduang.
Your name is also weird.
I've never heard it before.
It's Qin. How is it strange?
Does it mean something?
The meaning is twofold.
It either means "to criticize"
or "beauty."
Yours is the latter.
Your name means "beauty."
Glass half full, or glass half empty.
My mom says it's natural
to have good and bad sides.
Sounds sophisticated and extraordinary.
You called me
to say "sweet dreams," right?
I know what you're trying to do.
Suit yourself.
I miss you to death, you know?
- I'm hanging up.
- Wait.
Okay, see you tomorrow, babe. Good night.
Come on. I wasn't done talking!
Don't forget to dream of me
so that you'll have good dreams.
"To criticize" and "beauty."
I like both meanings.
What? You're leaving already?
Got a hot date with a girl?
- A little bird told me that.
- You're partially right.
But I'm not a girl.
Seriously?
My heart longs for this person.
Gender isn't my concern.
Don't forget to introduce them to me.
Just you wait.
- Duang.
- Yes?
Where are you off to?
To dance practice.
- Dance practice.
- Wait.
What dance?
It's for the event I told you about.
My professor knows about it too.
I'm not doing anything bad.
Moreover, I made a promise
to do my very best.
So I have to practice a lot.
In that case,
I'll have Funan drive you there.
- Funan, drive him to--
- Dad, no need.
I can drive.
Also, you're sending Funan
to keep tabs on me, aren't you?
It's just an ordinary event.
I'll send you pictures later.
Duang, when you do something,
be passionate and serious about it.
Don't slack off too much, okay?
Yes, I know that, Dad.
I know I need to keep my word.
If I don't,
I'll seem unreliable and incompetent.
I'm worried about you.
Right.
- I'll be going now. Bye-bye.
- Get going, son.
- Drive safely.
- Thank you.
You called me, Dad?
Come.
I want you to talk to your brother
and warn him not to slack off too much.
I thought it'd be something else.
I've been telling him that.
He's gotten a lot better lately.
He's still young. Keep an eye on him.
He said that the event he's working on
involves dancing.
All right, Dad.
I slowed down the music.
The seniors helped with the choreography
to match the slower tempo.
Let's give it a go.
One, two, three,
- Three…
- Four.
One more time.
Your hands go like this, an L shape.
Three and four.
My arms are killing me.
Get down. Two fingers, then bam, bam.
I need to film a video for my parents!
All good? You got it memorized, yeah?
I do. Okay.
Three, four, five, and six.
Seven, eight…
Hey!
You okay?
Let's call it a day.
Why? I was just about to nail it.
Stop. Do as I say.
KATE TEAW
ORIGINAL THAI BOAT NOODLE
How was practice?
DAD: GOOD MORNING
Your body not cooperating?
FUNAN: 272
Aren't you gonna eat?
I…
I'd like to apologize to you.
I did so poorly.
I mean, I tried,
but it looked like I didn't, right?
I'm not good at this.
Take your time. You weren't born a dancer.
Maybe I'm not trying hard enough.
I could see that you were trying.
Dig in already.
You can have this too!
Finish it. I'll order another one.
Let me drive you home.
What's up with your tone?
Someone here likes it.
But he keeps his mouth shut.
You think so?
Wanna pry it open?
So lame.
Jamie.
Jamie, come here!
Warrior, come this way.
Come here.
Here's your secret weapon.
A drink, please.
Wait. Your buddy, Duang,
isn't here with you?
No. He's on a lover-boy mission.
He's got someone?
No, he's trying to win his crush's heart.
Okay.
And what about you?
What's the plan tonight?
Who's on your radar?
No one so far.
Today, I'm going for an ambush.
I'm diving in headfirst.
All right! That's my bro.
"If you give someone a fish,
all they'll have is that fish.
But if you teach someone how to fish,
they'll always have fish."
You serious?
This is who I am. Here, bottoms up.
I was in the washroom.
Go and get him.
He never picks the same person twice,
so you've got nothing to worry about.
If you can get him, that is.
Shall we clink our glasses together?
What's your name?
It's Mar.
It's supposed to be "Mars." With an 'S'.
Mars. It's the name of a planet.
And?
My nickname, my real name,
or my stage name?
What's your real name?
Jettana.
Let's take a photo.
Hey, let me join you.
Yeah, that's the one.
Let me see.
Go sit with your friends.
- Hey, guys.
- Hello.
Hello.
I know you're on break, but we can't rest.
That's why we're having
group practice today.
What's the plan for today, Coach?
Don't be so hasty now, okay?
The tournament is soon, Coach.
We need to move.
Fine. This will be a practice
you'll never forget.
We'll start by running five laps
around the court.
Chop-chop!
- Come on!
- All right.
- Guys.
- Let's go.
You'll be busy next semester.
Are you up for this, Qin?
Yeah, you're usually not this busy.
Suddenly, you wanna be involved.
I made my promise. I won't back out.
Right. What about your lover boy?
Can he finally dance now?
He's got practice today. He'll manage.
Hey! We've got slackers! Extra lap then!
Shit! I wonder who the slackers are!
You dare ask me that?
Still there?
- Sorry.
- We're sorry.
Go! Come on!
After them.
I think I'm getting better.
Don't you agree?
I wasn't watching.
Ask him.
Jamie.
Don't ask me.
- You guys!
- Fine.
Do it again. I'll watch this time.
By the way,
you're actually serious about this.
I just thought it was for Qin.
I just want to do my part.
I don't want to embarrass Qin.
Sheesh!
You said that like you were his boyfriend.
Did I? I sounded like his boyfriend?
Duang, that doesn't mean
that you are, come on.
That already confirms it.
Do you really think Qin will say yes?
Why wouldn't he want me? Hello!
Anyone who says no is missing out!
- I'm that cool.
- Who told you that?
I can say that to myself.
Where is Qin, by the way?
Why did he leave you to practice alone?
Right.
He said he was busy.
I forgot to ask him. Let me send him a DM.
No need.
My dear Qin! I'll be there in a flash!
Duang isn't coming today?
How would I know?
We're not a thing.
Currently, you're not.
What about in the future?
No idea.
Duang is a nice guy, you know?
He cares not only about you,
but also about us.
People try hard to impress.
What?
I like to take my time.
Taking too long can be bad.
A fighter can become a quitter.
That's not my concern.
If he wants to love-bomb me
and change when I say yes…
what's the point then?
I don't think
Duang is that type of person.
Yeah.
You're being judgmental.
The problem isn't Duang.
You don't let anyone in.
So much so, I feel bad for him.
This is who I am.
I'm not pushing anyone away.
Right.
That means
you're opening up to the guy, correct?
This lover boy what it takes, doesn't he?
Yeah.
Qin!
Here, Tong, Kim.
Are you tired? I bought you a drink.
I'm not thirsty.
Then I'll drink it. I'm tired now too.
Right.
I saw you on Tong's Story,
so I rushed over.
Duang!
Duang, you should be a runner
if you're gonna be this fast.
If you said your dad was The Flash,
I'd freaking believe you.
Qin!
Tired from practice?
Talking about yourself?
See that?
Qin,
could there be a "we" with us now?
I would wuv that.
Qin, I awweady followed you.
Would you follow me back?
You bastard!
You jerk.
It took ages for him to follow me.
Why did you let him get so close to you?
I'm sulky now.
Duang, what the hell?
You took so long to get to the point.
Let's go eat at Yang Noey.
I'm hungry, and running didn't help.
Spit it out.
If you go, I go.
What are you doing?
Nope, nothing.
HI, TONG. CAN YOU MEET ME
BEHIND THE UNIVERSITY?
Damn, she hit me up again.
She wants to meet.
My bad, Qin. Take care of him for me.
- Peace out.
- What?
Kim, let's go.
Good luck.
You know,
the practice room
is so lonely without you.
I really miss you.
Are you lonely without me?
So, how was practice?
Aren't you blushing a tiny bit?
I asked how was practice?
- Let's pretend I didn't say that.
- What?
I was just playing hard to get.
I'll show you.
Give me a sec.
Hold on.
- Let's go.
- Ready?
- Ready.
- Go.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Enough.
All right, I believe you.
I worked so hard at practice.
Just ask Pae and Jamie.
It's true.
He really did work hard.
I swear on the Tiger Adventure.
My bad, bro.
It's true, though.
You should be proud of him.
Give me your keys then.
I'll drive.
No way. You're tired from practice.
Are we going or what?
Duang is the bottom.
Seriously, both of you are handsome.
But the shipper told me that
a sweet face like this is the bottom.
I think Qin is cuter.
That doesn't matter, does it?
You are really cute, though.
Whatever. Suit yourself.
The way you're talking,
are you interested in me now?
Give me the keys.
Qin's so freaking adorable.
See? Duang is the bottom.
Pae, seriously?
- How much?
- It's 200 baht.
Then you're the top.
Qin! Wait for me.
YANG NOEY
Oops!
Oopsie.
- Pae.
- That's enough.
Save some for yourself.
They're having a moment.
Duang, don't die on us.
Your smile needs a doctor.
There's no pork left.
You…
What?
You're just so cute. I can't take it.
Jamie.
I can't take it either.
Gimme all the pork you want.
Thank you.
Hey, why are you doing that for them?
Ugh.
Can't you use chopsticks?
Qin!
My best bro.
What a small world.
Yeah, hey.
Can I sit with you guys?
And you're here all by yourself?
I got the date wrong.
Come sit with us.
Qin's friend is also mine.
Facts.
Can I have this stool?
I'm not holding back then.
Waiter, one plate, one spoon,
and one pair of chopsticks, please.
- Where are you going?
- To get dessert.
I'll come with you.
Sup, bro?
Cho, are you Qin's school friend?
Yeah, we were in marching band together.
So how was Qin back then?
Studious,
good-looking, athletic,
and the teachers' pet.
- How flawless of you, Qin.
- Yeah.
So were you a hot guy?
That's enough. I'm sitting right here.
He was so freaking hot.
But he didn't care about anyone,
except my friend, Tiw.
Just let me talk about him.
It was a long time ago.
And you two already broke up.
We didn't break up or anything.
Fine, you didn't.
But here's something spicy.
No way!
Tiw, my friend, gave Qin a teddy bear
in front of everyone at school.
He wanted everyone to know Qin was his.
Right. It's all in the past.
Let's talk about something else.
That's right!
But…
If you want to get back with him,
just tell me.
Shut up and finish your food.
You're still as harsh as ever, I see.
Duang needs your help.
Qin, is the grass jelly good?
It's decent.
Do you want more?
- Let--
- What do you think of Duang?
Shit.
Duang and Qin are…
It's what you're thinking.
Ding, ding.
Damn. I'm so sorry.
It's okay! It's fine.
Right.
So, Qin, what do you think of Duang?
I'll get you another bowl.
Duang is too naive, Qin.
You've got to spell it out for him.
- He's extremely clueless.
- Yeah.
Isn't that right?
Clueless.
Hey, I think I should leave.
I'll pay you later. Just tell me how much.
Wait.
Pay up right now. It's 319 baht.
It's 319 baht…
There!
Hey, wait!
What are you doing? Follow him!
- There goes your 319 baht.
- It's fine. We'll split it.
Guys. I've got to go now.
I gotta talk to my crush.
Qin, I'm completely hammered.
We didn't drink.
You're so pretentious.
What a cheeky little guy.
You caught me.
Would it kill you to be nice to me?
Qin smiled!
You lied to me again. You're a bad friend.
Stop fighting. I have to go as well.
I'll take you home.
I called a ride.
Qin already called his ride,
but I haven't.
Take me home instead.
Are you Qin?
- Then no.
- What?
Well then…
Qin, let me use your name for a bit.
Duang, call me Qin.
I'm going.
Bye-bye.
I should go home as well.
My name is Qin.
- So take me home.
- Hell no.
What do you mean? I'm Qin now.
- You're so pretentious. Just go home!
- We're friends.
We're on a break. Tit for tat.
Fair's fair.
Duang!
Why are you following me?
It's none of your business.
Fine, damn it.
Just get outta here.
Don't try to act tough with me, Duang.
A stranger
addressing someone inappropriately…
How ill-mannered.
If I were not this well-behaved…
What would you have done?
Look what you did to me!
I'd soak my shoes in water
and kick the shit out of you.
- Get ready for it.
- Go away!
What did I do to upset you?
You leaned on Qin's shoulder.
And you talked to him too much!
You're hitting on him
when you know I like him!
Gosh. This is hilarious.
Why are you this upset?
Stop laughing, damn it.
Instead of being mad at me,
you should think about Qin's teddy.
Right?
Yeah, you're right.
I don't know what to do next.
He still has that teddy.
So you're taking it out on me?
Qin…
What the hell are you saying?
Stop crying like a wet puppy.
Hush!
Quiet now.
At first, I didn't think
his walls were that high.
I thought I could get over them.
I guess I was delusional.
But you're the first
to stand up to his walls.
Does keeping that teddy
really mean nothing at all?
So you're giving up?
I'm worried about Qin.
I'm worried he'd choose that person.
I'm worried he'll just flat out reject me.
I don't know what I'm supposed to do now.
I told you not to get your hopes up.
I really didn't see this coming.
Let me ask you something.
In the next two years,
will you treat him the same way you did
at the BBQ place?
What does that have to do
with what I said?
- Were you listening to me?
- Come on.
Answer me.
I've devoted my love to him,
and I'll never give up.
All I care about is
whether he likes something
or wants something…
If he wants me to
grill some pork for him, I'll do it.
If he wants me to peel shrimp, I will.
If he no longer wants it…
I'll stop.
That's how I see it.
Warrior, I hate you.
Trying to be emotional.
That's it.
Keep it going.
If something bothers you,
just vent with me.
Shit. Something big is coming.
What?
Seven-one-five-three.
What are you saying?
Hey, my ride is here.
What? Aren't I driving you?
Bye! Be seeing you!
Call me if you need me!
- Don't overthink it.
- What?
Jamie! You idiot.
This is Yim,
your modeling partner for the shoot.
All you've been doing
is playing hard to get. And see?
He seemed jealous of Yim and me.
You just realized it?
Were you jealous?
You're here to shop, right?
Or to meet someone?
I'm not meeting anyone. You are.
My parents told me, "If you love someone,
try spending the night
in their room first."