It's like this. It's like this.
What are you talking about?
I don't know.
Zhang Chunji.
Or should I call you Li Guixiang now?
I'm Li Gui Xiang.
I'm not Jang Chun-pil.
Don’t deny it.
I saw you in the Xie family.
You got the wrong person.
Here.
Be careful.
I'm fine.
This old man
is looking for trouble.
Be careful.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
What a coincidence!
She asked for leave at home.
because she's afraid
we go to her employer's house to make trouble?
Look at her reaction.
She clearly knows we're following her.
Slow down.
You can stop here.
Don't you have to go to work?
Be careful.
Do you still have money?
Mom.
Don't you have a salary?
Why do you keep asking me for money?
I don't even have money to get married.
I bought you your favorite ribs.
Take it back.
No.
You pass by your brother's shop at work.
Give it to him.
Why didn't you tell me?
Are you going to say I'm biased again?
Why don't you take any loss?
You know I'm at a disadvantage.
Son.
How have you been these days?
I'm fine.
Son.
Take care of yourself no matter how busy you are.
Did you bring the money?
Anything else?
No.
I really don't have any.
Ask my sister for more.
I've asked your sister for it.
She's gone too.
I have no choice.
That's all, son.
Jang Chun-pil values her son so much.
Her daughter will make a scene if she knows.
Why don't we make Chi-zi more confused?
I'm leaving, mom.
Did you win
Did you win?
No.
Time's up.
She should get off work.
Give it back to me.
Put it down.
What are you doing?
All these years,
you kept asking me for money.
And then?
I gave the money to my brother.
How could you be so biased?
Zhang Chunji did so much for Du Lan.
He shouldn’t be short of money.
Why am I in such a mess?
I looked into her son's financial situation.
and owed a lot of external debts.
Zhang Chunji spent all his money
for this son.
You can't take it if you buy it.
If you buy it...
Don't take it away.
Why?
I bought this.
Give it back to me.
Since she is so short of money,
should we remind her
not to leave Jinshan behind.
Let them bite the dog.
the evidence
the evidence.
Du Lan, a famous entrepreneur.
Du Lan.
It’s her.
You must be tired.
Don't go upstairs.
Go back and rest.
Okay.
Rest early.
Mingcheng Community.
Please
please come and have a look.
Hello Fei
Yes.
Ask the team
to help us.
Find someone.
Mingcheng Community.
Captain.
How is it?
Did you find him?
The police confirmed
The car disappeared after this intersection.
But
There are several forks here.
Please
Let's split up.
It saves time.
Boss.
Did you mobilize the rescue team?
I borrowed someone to look for someone.
Is she that important?
Yes.
Why don't you just give it to the police?
Besides,
this is not how we use our family’s public welfare power.
Besides, you’re looking for an unknown woman.
Simyeon is not an unknown person.
Xie’s illegitimate daughter.
Brother.
I’m also an illegitimate son of the Jin family.
In your eyes,
I'm also an unknown person?
I can't give him
I really can't give you anything.
You're awake.
Where am I?
On the boat.
They're selling us.
What should we do?
What should I do?
I'm scared.
What should we do?
Do you want to escape?
Yes!
Help!
Hello?
Shut up!
Someone died.
Who's dead?
I'll kill you if you shout again.
I think she's really dead.
I'm scared.
Don't be afraid.
What are you doing?
Stop fighting!
I am...
Mr. Jin.
Actor.
Choi Yiliang as Wang Xinyan.
Yufeng plays Jin Xyan.
I play Jin Yetlei.
Mr. Hu plays Xie Haiming.
Jinyang as Du Lan.
She Yitong plays Wang Yumei.
Han Shuo as Fang Tonbin.
Zhiyao plays Xiao Lele.
Jiang Jian as Chen Ming.
Chow Qianxiao plays Lin Ke.
Chiu Chi-ying as Zhang Chun-pil.
Xi Mingyuan as Liu Qi.
Mary plays Yiyi Chen.
Jeremy Ding plays Xie Xuan.
Hao Zhenjun as Mr. Li.
Sheng Zihang plays Jin Xueyan.
Yang Haochen as Jin Yetlei.
Suo Bei as Mr. Lin.
Jinxingxuan plays student A.
WD as Student C.
I play student B.
Kong Ying as Jin Xyan's mother.
Li Xiaodong as the mechanic.
Chen Tianyi as Student D.
Xiaohong Xu plays the host
Hu Jianyang as a couple.
Nie Xu as Mr. Jiang.
Zhang Ki Ruo as Mr. Du Lan.
Gu Biao as Subordinate A.
Zhang Qiu as the HR director.
Mr. Sun plays a motorcycle man.
Li Jiaojiao as CFO.
Han Xiaotao as a security guard.
Gu Biao as Secretary.
Wu Gui Song as a doctor.
as a doctor.
Chang Peng Yu, Hao Ji, Ya Jie, Lu Yuechao, Zhu Li. Feng Yulong, Sun Yulei, Xu Longgang, Wang Qin.
Pang Tuojing He Qinhao Ling Bo Bai Shuo Yuan Yao Luhui, Yi Yundi, Zheng Shiyi, Chen Jianhao. Wu Yiting.
Xu Zifu, Zhang Bohai, Confucian, Ke Qiaoyi, Hu Rui, Wang Shuyue, Wang Yaoya Huang Peishan
Li Pilshen Wu Yaohua, Peng Yuting, Wang Ling, Wang Ling, Xie Jia Yu, Luo Jing, Yang Shunan, Yang Shao Yu.
Lin Lele, Liao Yajun, Liang Fen Su Lun, Qin Jiaozhen, Xie Jia Wen, Li Renjie
Li Jiahe, Guo Xianqing, Wu Yiling, Chen Yiting. Ruan Qinghua Xin Xiangkun Lin Fu Liu Meiling Tu Zhi.
William from Jongting, Victoria, Chen Wei, Chen Zhao Xiang, Huang Yawei, Huang Zihao, Huang Lin, Song He.
Xu Yating, Wang Shenru, He Lingyuan, Zhong Lun Army. Cai Jiarong, Kang Rou, Feng Chengxuan, Chen Jiahui. Jeremy Wu.
Lam Sulun, Li Yinzhi, Cai Yuting, Zheng Zhijun Wu Meng Yu, Cai Guowei, Lian Junda, Li Yating Li Lijiao.
Li Yixiao Huang Jingwen Chen Shunbao Li Wenwei Lin Jiarong, Luo Yimao, Li Shu, Xie Yijun. Wang Meiling.
Zhou Zi Han, Ding Li, Zhang Jingjing, Wang Jing Jiang Tingting, Liu Yinghui, Lv Sha, Li Dechao Hsu Shaw-hong
Lai Xinchen Huang Weijun Wang Haoxiang Zhao Zhaozheng Xiao Xiu Chao, Liu Chunlong, Min Yuqiang, Mute Ru Zhu Linghua.
Chen Ping Tang Zhenzhu Fei Tianfeng Fan Chenxi Chu Yongji, Ma Yi, Wang Can Ya, Wang Zhenyu Li Juan.
You Kailong, Li Fa, Liu Bin Hao, Luo Hongming. Xu Jie, Xu Tenbin, Liu Dongdong, Shen Pengcheng Gao Zhao Qiu.
Sun and Lou Huaixian, Gao Kezhong, Wang Yong, Zhang Ze, Li Jin Teng, Huang Qiluo, Sun Meng Hu, Li Gang Lin.
Wang Changpeng, Wang Songlin, Zhong Minghua, Wang Xinyu Yang Ping, Zou Daqin, Zhang Chao, Yang Shuai, Meng Chong
Jin Yaqian, Luo Jing
Staff.
Director Zhang Yutong, Xu Jie
Director Zhao Xi Xi, Zhang Xiaoqi
Writer Seo Chen-yup
The director team.
Director Zhao Xi Xi, Zhang Xiaoqi
Record: Liang Yuwei.
[Actor Arrangement, Xiao Wei]
Actor assistant director, Qian Hanchen.
Actor assistant director Yang Hao
Director of Production, Wang Dianhong.
Lixiong Lu Guofu, a foreign producer.
The commander-in-chief, Xi Mingyuan.
[Living Producer Shu Xin Sheng]
Car Supervisor Cheung.
Action Producer Zhou Qingzhong
Photography team.
Photographer Dong Jian Ning
Photographer Zhong Chongmin Wang Chunxuan
focus Li Zhan Peng Zeng Lijun
Photographer assistant, Wu Lei.
Lighting Team.
Lighting instructor Chen Yanfeng.
The lighter, Chen Huibin.
Chen Junhui.
Action group.
Action consultant, Li Xinquan.
Action instructor Li Gangkun Duan XianDong
Hang, clap, Li Xinliang.
The recording team.
The recording team leader, Bai Wei.
Recording, Hua Chengwei, Cai Wenyuan.
Art team.
art instructor, Liu Yixiang.
Art Yang Xiaohua, Liu Min.
Props team.
It's a prop play. Li Yiming.
Leader of decoration, Ge Jianjun.
decorations, Tian Bao,
Lu Qiuhao.
Li Chunming.
Vice-monitor Chen Weiquan.
The styling and makeup team.
styling instructor Fan Tie Suo.
Makeup instructor, Chen Youjun.
Makeup team leader, Yang Cha Ping.
Makeup artist, Hou Xiangwei.
The main focus of dressing is Lin Xiaofei.
Makeup assistant Jane Zhang.
Costume team.
[Costume Team Leader, Lee Myung-Ryu, Jang Deok-taek]
The editing team.
Producer Zhang Xu
Live editing Zhang Xu
DIT JANG JUNG
Behind the Scenes, Tu Jingyi.
The venue team.
Roson, the manager of the field.
Driver team.
Hello. Hello.
Late production.
Beijing Movie and Culture Co., Ltd.
Producer Chen Yan
Producer Zhang Xu ZHANG XU
Translating assistant JANG Juni.
The post-production plan Liu Tong Liu Toning
Packaging.
Passenger Ma Hao Ma hao
Voice design, Li Juan.
Charmer, Ne Yiping.
Special effects.
Beijing Peking Digital Technology Co., Ltd.
VFX Supervisor. Video Director Chi Chai Xun
Production. Supervisor Production Director Chen Xiaolei, Chen Xiaolei, Chen Xaielei.
3D Director. Three-dimensional Director Chen Chung-gun Chen Zonghui.
Matthemove. Artist Senior stalker. Hu Xiaoyong.
Fx Artist special effects. Wang Cong. Wang Conng.
Spinne Making. Altis Stage Producer Wu Ning wu
Animator Directors Animation Director Sun Shiyang Sunshining
Music copyright provided
Music Label.
Music Director: Lei Lei
Original music: Fun-Z
Heart Tou.
Singer: Mr Lei/Yang Siu Hui
Lyrics: Jay/Lei
Composition: Jay/Mr. Lei
Arrangement: Mix Seul
Mixed/Mother belt: Jay
Production team: Ballinllab
Music label: Voice recipe.
Fiction plot.
Singer: Jiang Kuan
Lyrics: Zhao Nan
Lyrics: Start.
Producer: Mr. Lei
Producer: Power
[Music/Mother belt: Tan Xiaolun]
Guitar: Fun-Z
Harmony: Fun-Z.
Plan: Yu Qingmu
Linyuan
Singer: Yu Youyou
Lyrics: Tang SiMiao
Lyrics: Haya.
OP: Star Entertainment
Cooperation Music Label: Voice recipe.
The Devil is Not Guilty.
Singer: Xin Yu
Lyrics: Wang Ying
Composition: G.G Zhang Siyuan.
Copyright provided: Qi Yin Da Music Copyright platform
Cooperation Music Label: Music recipe.
"Coming for You".
[Singer: Seon-woo]
[Lyrics: Taek-egg]
OP: Star Entertainment
Copyright provided: Qi Nenda Music Copyright platform
Cooperation music label: musician recipe.
Puzzle.
Composition: Yu Tong.
Arrangement: I like it.
Mix: Vitamin.
OP/SP: Video Music.
Cooperation Music Label: Voice recipe.
Singer: Xu Chenye
Lyrics: Xu Chenye
[Composition: Xu Chenye]
Producer Director Chen Yan
The teaser producer Li Juan
Poster Producer Shao Wenyan
Voice director, Fu Bowen.
Dubbing Top, Yan Xi.
Xinyan Li Jiasi.
Jin Yuyan. Ma Yufei.
Jin Yetlei, Yue Zhihang.
Zhang Chunji, Xiaotang.
Jin Moyan Zhang Rulin.
Du Lan, Xiaotang,
LuJiu.
PR company.
Fantasy (Beijing) Cultural Communication Co., Ltd.
GM Wu Jialin.
Project Director, Qiu Xiao.
PR Plan, Liu Qian, Li Jingyu.
Director of Media, Liu Man.
Media, Jie Yu.
Design and song in pairs.
Director of editing, Wang Zhen.
Business Director, Zhang Jianjie.
Ming Xie.
Indian Bay.
Ningbo Nade Art Museum.
Ningbo Nation Art Communication Center
Ningbo East Qinhe Lake and wait for the wind to come to the hotel.
Oasis western food (Dongqian Lake)
Let's go, THE Dramar.
[White Goblin Tea]
[The People's Government of Qiu Village]
Xiangshan Xilain Hotel.
Zhejiang Baoyun Biology Co., Ltd.
Garden is luxurious, Ningbo and Garden Villa.
Baolong Xinda Cultural Creation, Jiangcheng.
Fenghua District Agrict Holdings.
Ningbo Mushang Holdings Co., Ltd.
Xiang Shang Space Business Management Co., Ltd.
Zhejiang, Bowan Provincial Tourism Resort.
Ningbo Yi Fule Biology Co., Ltd.
Ningbo Boyang Family Spinning Group Co., Ltd.
Peking Tracker also Movie Culture Co., Ltd.
Shanghai Pineapple's Hai Culture and Art Co., Ltd.
Beijing Briannan Culture Co., Ltd.
Co-produced products.
Chengdu bridge Culture Co., Ltd.
Ningbo Yan Culture Co., Ltd.
Huaxiong Culture Co., Ltd.
Production Company.
Beijing Movie and Culture Co., Ltd.
Ningbo Three-Shi-Seven-Text Cultural Art Co., Ltd.