My daughter’s boyfriend should be someone who can protect her.
But I’m sure I can protect Mudmee, sir.
Do you think they’re real?
Long-distance relationships.
I’ve made up my mind.
I will study in Bangkok with you.
I’m afraid of not trying my best.
It’s better than letting you go without trying to do anything.
What do you think I should do, sir?
Tell her as soon as possible.
I believe she will understand eventually.
Please excuse me.
Worry about yourself first.
Your pre-test result is out.
It calculates the likelihood that you will be accepted into your preferred faculty.
I got 23%.
It’s better than last time.
You got only 18% before.
But I have only a few months left.
The exam is approaching.
Don’t stress.
You still have time.
You just need to work harder.
Don’t lose hope yet.
Our stage play has come back around, guys.
This year we will perform Beauty and the Beast.
Atom.
Should we work on the props together again?
Good idea.
I remember it was quite fun last year.
And the one voted to be the scary and hideous beast is…
Half.
What?
Me?
Wait.
Who voted for me?
Did you, Atom?
Cut that.
And we have two candidates for our Beauty: Fahsai and Ipad.
We’re gonna have an audition to see who has better chemistry with our Beast.
Listen.
Yes?
I heard the climax of this play is the real-kiss scene.
What?
Watch out, girl. You might lose your Beast to one of the Beauties.
Kiss. Kiss.
Director.
Can I also audition for the female lead?
What?
Why?
What are you guys waiting for? Give her a big clap.
This is the script for the audition.
It’s a romantic scene where the Beast shows Belle his library.
Ah.
And then Genie comes out of the oil lamp.
That’s Aladdin.
Is it the one with the seven dwarfs?
That’s Snow White.
Are you okay, girl?
Gosh.
What am I gonna do?
I am too nervous to do anything right.
It’s alright.
Let’s see how they do first.
Wow, this is beautiful.
You have tons of books here.
These books are all yours.
I’m so delighted.
Look. I like to read that book so much.
Do you want that one? I’ll grab it for you.
It’s my favorite book.
I really like this chapter.
Thank you so much.
You’ve got a problem. Look at your competition.
They’re acting like they want an award.
Mudmee, it’s your turn now.
So? Do you want to sit this one out?
No!
Mudmee, stand by right here.
Wait, wait.
You, a heartless man.
You judge people by their appearances.
You deserve to be cursed.
Which chapter are those lines from?
You acted like you didn’t want the role at first.
Look how happy you are now.
I’m just doing what the script says.
Yeah?
Does the script tell you to give them heart eyes too?
Does it say you must hold their hands?
Mudmee.
A round of applause, guys.
This is the Beauty that we’re looking for.
But she just went off-script.
It’s all from her inner feelings.
That’s true.
But the Beauty and the Beast are supposed to fight just like this.
Mudmee, I chose you to play Beauty.
Give her a big hand, guys.
These are the test examples from the last five years for each subject.
Five years?
I don’t think it’s enough.
I want 10 years.
20 years.
30 years.
100 years is fine too.
Calm down, okay?
Why are you so hyped up?
Well…
It’s my only chance to study with Kongthap.
I want to do my best.
So I won’t regret it later.
Nice to hear that.
But I’m telling you this.
You get to spend a high school life only once too.
I don’t want you to regret it later.
Keep going.
Kongthap.
Wanna join me?
Are you done studying?
No.
I just wanna keep someone company
so he doesn’t have to eat alone.
Thanks.
What are you drawing?
A rose.
Similar to last year.
Can I try?
Are you sure you can do it?
Come on.
My skills must have improved over the past year.
If you don’t believe me, watch.
You’re supposed to draw a rose, not an earthworm.
Seriously?
Earthworm?
I’m sorry.
That’s my maximum improvement.
But I can eat vegetables now.
If you don’t believe me, watch.
I’m fine.
Is yours too spicy though?
I can cook a new flavor for you.
It’s alright.
My skills have improved over the past year too.
You’re good.
Kongthap.
I need to go back to studying.
Atom.
Since we’re not performing in the stage play this year,
should we go check out the school festival?
But I haven’t finished my study yet.
It’s fine. It’s just one day.
It’s our last year of high school.
Come with me.
Fine.
I will.
Okay.
We are going to rehearse this scene.
You guys run lines one last time.
Are you okay?
If not, it’s not too late to withdraw now.
I’m fine.
I’m nervous.
But with you here, I feel a lot more relieved.
Alright, guys.
Ready?
You can start now.
The stars are beautiful tonight.
Right.
I just realized now how beautiful my castle is.
That’s called the Leo constellation.
Belle…
I…
You should tell her as soon as possible.
I believe she will understand eventually.
Half.
What’s the matter?
I’m sorry, I forgot my line.
Come on, Half.
The feeling was just right.
May I have some time to read the lines once again?
(...ongthap)
Your friend, Atom?
Good evening, ma’am.
I’m Kongthap.
I’m Atom’s friend.
Atom.
Don’t you have school today?
Ah.
I do, Mom.
But we’re having a festival today.
That’s why I’m looking extra handsome.
Do you have to do a stage play this year?
I don’t, this year.
Half does though.
I’ll be there just to look around.
By yourself?
No.
With a friend.
Atom.
Is there anything you wanna tell me?
Hm?
Uh…
Uh, I’m late.
I gotta go.
I’m meeting a friend.
I’m off now.
Atom.
Travel safe, son.
Text me when you’re at school.
Yes, Mom.
My energy has been boosted.
Which booth should we start?
Hi, guys.
Hey, Khao-pan.
Wanna test your dart skills?
Hit five balloons, you get the prize.
You also get to choose the one you want.
Wanna try it? I’m paying.
Oh, please.
No.
I’m not gonna hit anything.
Don’t waste your money.
How do you know?
Try it. Have you ever tried it before?
I haven’t.
But I told you it’s a waste of money.
It’s our last year here.
You’re allowed to do anything you want.
Alright.
Yes!
Here are your prizes.
May I please have a carrot and a cabbage?
Hey!
It’s fine. Just eat.
Are you guys ready?
We are!
Make some noise.
Everyone, please gather round.
Your friend has so many jobs.
Please welcome our special guest today,
Chinzhilla!
Hey.
Really?
I want to hear some noise.
If you’re ready, let’s have fun together.
Just by the look of you
Just when you walk past me
Just by being close to you and hearing your voice
It shakes my heart
But you let me down
When you told me
That we can’t be together
Because of what you heard about me
- Some say I’m like that - Some say I’m like that
Some say I’m like this
Some say I’m a bad guy
But we haven’t even talked
So you think I’m a bad guy
Though you haven’t really looked
I dare you to look at me
You already judge me
Based on other people’s words
So you think I’m a bad guy
Though you haven’t really looked
I dare you to look at me
You already judge me
Based on other people’s words
You say you don’t trust my words, I wanna cry
You say they’re all lies
You think I’m a liar, a deceiver,
Why don’t you listen to me
Some say I’m like that
Some say I’m like this
Some say I’m a bad guy
But we haven’t even talked
So you think I’m a bad guy
Though you haven’t really looked
I dare you to look at me
You already judge me
Based on other people’s words
So you think I’m a bad guy
Though you haven’t really looked
I dare you to look at me
You already judge me
Based on other people’s words
You two stand by.
Once the team is ready, I’ll come back for you.
Okay.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
Half, you okay? Is something bothering you?
Ah.
It’s just nerves.
Should we rehearse one last time?
Of course.
Is there anything you want to tell me?
Do you want to rehearse the stargazing scene?
No.
I’m asking you, Half.
We’ve known each other quite long.
I can tell when something is bothering you.
I…
(Beauty and the Beast)
Half.
Listen to me.
You can tell me.
I’m up for anything.
I’m…
not attending the same university as you.
Why not?
I looked up many institutes.
In the end,
a different university's program is more appealing to me.
That’s fine.
We don’t have to study at the same university.
Right?
But the university I chose is in Chiang Mai.
We will be quite far away from each other.
Mudmee, I’m sorry.
This is not your fault.
It’s good to know what you like and want to study.
Don’t you believe me?
Really, I’m okay.
I’m sorry I can’t keep the promise.
We can still meet up or call each other.
You keep reading the lines.
I’m gonna go fix my makeup.
So when Tan comes back, I will be ready.
Been a while since I last danced.
That really made me sweat.
We still have time to hit a couple of booths.
Should we hurry?
One second.
Crap!
My mom is calling.
Answer her.
Hello, Mom.
What’s up?
(I have a half day off today and I don’t have any plans.)
(I’m thinking of dropping by your school event.)
What?
Don’t think that’s a good idea.
There's nothing to see here.
(But I’ve already arrived.)
What?
Where are you?
I’ll come to you.
(I’m at the fountain.)
Okay, Mom.
I will…
Hello.
Seriously? It has to die now?
You can borrow mine.
No.
You cannot get involved in this.
She suddenly called. There must be something going on.
You should go then.
I can go watch the play by myself.
I’m sorry.
Hi, ma’am.
Uh…
Atom’s phone died.
I think he’s coming back here soon.
Kongthap, you and Atom are close, aren’t you?
Hey!
That’s right, ma’am.
How long have you guys been close?
Since Grade 11.
So it’s you who inspired Atom to study harder.
No, ma’am.
It’s Atom himself who wants to study hard.
I heard you two are applying to the same university in Bangkok.
Is that right?
That’s right, ma’am.
Then you must know this.
Atom’s father left us when Atom was a child.
I’ve been working so hard that Atom has to be alone frequently.
He might act tough and independent,
but I know he wants someone to be with him all the time.
Deep down, he’s afraid that someone he loves will abandon him like his father did.
Atom being easily scared is partly my fault.
As for the university in Bangkok, he is working on it extremely hard.
I'm concerned that if he doesn't get in, he may become discouraged
or think everyone leaves him behind.
Worse, he might be too afraid to open his heart to anyone again.
Don’t worry, ma’am.
Atom is a strong person.
He’s helped me many times.
I think he gets that from you.
Kongthap, do you think he can get into that university in Bangkok?
I do, ma’am.
I’m sure he can make it.
Even if he can’t, he will be fine
because he will still have me.
I’m at ease now.
Even though he can’t make it, I know now that someone is right by his side, supporting him.
Atom.
I’m so sorry.
My friend just texted me asking if I wanted to join her for a meal.
I think I’m gonna go.
But you just got here.
Oh, please. My business here is done.
You two enjoy the rest of the day.
Did you find her in the library?
She’s not there.
Where the heck did she go?
Gosh.
Don’t tell me she’s too nervous to get on stage again.
No.
It’s my fault actually.
I’ll go look for her.
Guys, I am so sorry.
I fell asleep in the bathroom.
Gosh, don’t do that to us.
I really am sorry.
All right, time to stand by.
The hall is full of audience now.
Okay.
Let’s go.
Again, I’m sorry.
The play is starting in five minutes.
So? Did you memorize all the lines?
I am sorry, Mudmee.
Don’t be.
I should thank you for telling me honestly.
I admire your dedication to your future goals and I want to do the same.
For our future.
Then, should we make the most of our time today
while we get to spend it together?
Okay?
Hey.
I’m nervous
and I’m not even on the stage this year.
Are you sad that you don’t get to play this year?
No.
I’m glad that those two will have a special moment like we did.
(Once upon a time,)
(an angel cursed and turned an unkind prince into a beast)
(to teach him the value of true love.)
It’s not like everyone is as brave as you.
I thought you were more considerate of other people’s feelings.
Now I know I thought wrong.
(One day, the beast encountered Beauty who saw his kindness hidden inside.)
Hey, are you okay?
Rock, Paper, Scissors.
I’ve liked you for so long.
You remember it wrong, don't you?
You don’t have to remember anything anymore
because from now on, I will forget everything about you too.
It’s good.
(As time went by, the two of them started to open up to each other.)
(Until love bloomed.)
Look at that shooting star.
I like you, Mudmee.
(With the miracle of love…)
Please stay with me.
- Please wake up.
- (The beast turned into a gorgeous prince in the end.)
Wake up.
(The two of them lived happily ever after.)
I’m totally a fan.
Half!
Mudmee!
Can I ask you one thing?
Of course.
Will you promise if you have some free time, you will come see me?
If we really can’t meet up, let’s call each other instead.
I promise.
What about you?
Do you want me to make any promise?
Promise me that you will smile for me like this forever.
I promise.
Kongthap, I thought Mudmee would get stage fright again.
Turned out the applause was louder than when we performed last year.
So did you get to do everything you wanted today?
Actually,
there’s still one thing left.
What is it?
My pre-test score isn't as good as I said.
I have a 23% chance to get in.
I’ll try my best anyway.
Don’t you worry.
Atom.
Did you fill out the wrong faculty code?
You’re enrolling in Food Business.
But this is Hotel Business.
Hey!
I did input the wrong code.
Do it again. You can check online.
Gosh.
Can you check for me?
I’m too afraid.
Hey!
Why so quiet?
Atom.
Congratulations.
You have a 55% chance to get in.
Let me see.
Jeez!
You’re right.
Gosh.
Now we have a chance to study together.
Hello.
(Where are you?)
(The wrap-up fireworks are about to start.)
Okay.
We will be there.
Half told us to go down for the fireworks.
Oh.
Right.
Should we go now?
Or we might not get the spots.
Let’s go.
Dang.
Is it locked?
Kongthap, the door is locked.
I’m calling someone for help.
Kongthap.
No one will come help us.
People must be ready to see the fireworks now.
Should we see the fireworks from here then?
We can call someone after.
You being here with me is already enough.
Let go.
Kongthap.
Is there anything you haven’t done today?
There’s one thing, actually.
What is it?
All these times, you’ve been the one to make the first move.
This time, let me be the one to do it.
(I wish we could celebrate together like this again next year.)
(Sadhu.)
Did you guys bring your token?
We won’t get to see it again for ten years.
I looked into some dormitories around the university.
Once we get accepted, will you share it with me?
Atom, I’d like to know if Kongthap is dating someone.
If I can choose, I expect a competent and smart person.
Just like Thap.
I’m sorry, ma’am, that I’m not that.
But I’ll try my best.
Please don’t make us stop seeing each other.