[A Love Story of Oiled Paper Umbrella]
[Episode 8]
[Celestial Master's Mansion]
Every time...
Every time Situ Hanshan was about to be caught,
there was always purple fog.
There's no doubt, then.
It must have been his accomplice who did it.
No.
In my opinion,
it was not his accomplice.
Then, what is it?
Junior.
Junior, bad news!
Bad news!
What's going on? Why are you in such a panic?
Cr...
You...
-Here comes the Crown Prince!
-What?
The Crown Prince?
Greetings, Your Highness.
Goddess.
I finally found you.
Your Highness.
You...
Leave.
Junior.
Let's go.
I came here
because I wanted to see you.
How are your hands?
Thank you for your concern.
My hands are
much better.
This is a special medicine prescribed by the imperial physician.
It specializes in minor injuries and bruises.
Take it.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Thank you for taking all the trouble to deliver it.
Changle City is in danger.
Your Highness, why are you here
instead of staying in the palace?
Greetings, Your Highness.
Nan, you came at the right time.
I'm here
just to
thank you
for saving my life last time.
I didn't see you in the umbrella shop.
That's why I came to the Celestial Master's Mansion to look for you.
Protecting the Crown Prince
is Meng Xizhou's
and my duty.
Your Highness, I appreciate your kindness.
It's just…
it's too dangerous outside.
It is.
But the Celestial Master's Mansion
is very safe.
That's right.
I'm here on my mother's order.
First, I'm holding a banquet to express my gratitude.
Second, I'm here to reserve umbrellas.
Reserve umbrellas?
In three days,
it's my Grand Coming-of-Age Ceremony.
By then, we'll
need 33
Royal tribute umbrellas.
The royal tribute umbrellas?
Then, wouldn't it make Nan
the imperial-appointed umbrella maker?
Of course.
Thirty-three.
I can't even finish them in three months,
let alone three days.
Impossible.
It's easy.
In your umbrella shop,
you must have many ready-made umbrella frames.
No…
Yes!
That's it, then.
Yes,
but…
they've been reserved from long before.
Just deliver those past the deadline.
Don't worry.
All the compensation
will be
paid by me.
All you need to do
is paste the Ministry of Rites paper
on the ready-made umbrella frames.
That's all.
You will be in charge of everything?
Then, it'll be easy.
My disciple!
We must take this order.
Even so,
if you fail,
you'll be executed.
Executed?
I'm in charge of this matter.
Don't worry.
No one will give you trouble.
Your Highness,
you are such a great friend.
With your words,
we can rest assured.
Right?
Greetings, Your Highness.
What?
We are ordered by the Emperor
to escort you back to the palace.
Did you tell His Majesty?
Nan Fengyi.
Are you trying to chase me away?
Your Highness.
His Majesty said
that if you're done with your business,
you should hurry back to the palace.
Please, Your Highness.
All right.
Two days later,
Meng Xizhou,
bring the tribute umbrellas
to the palace for an inspection.
See you then.
-Why her?
-Okay.
This is the order from Her Majesty and me.
Who dares to disobey?
My disciple,
it doesn't matter who's delivering them.
Your Highness,
buy me some delicious food by then.
Let's go, Your Highness.
Take care.
See you in the palace.
Nan Fengyi.
Don't you think
you acted very impolitely?
Can't you see what he means?
We risked our lives to save him.
He repaid us with even more kindness.
What's the problem?
Don't you know he likes you?
♫The wind hesitates, not daring to smooth the furrowed brow♫
♫The rain hesitates, reluctant to burden the tear-streaked eyes beneath the umbrella♫
That's perfect.
♫The closer you are to me, the clearer the pain becomes♫
In that case,
I'll be the Crown Princess,
and the future Empress.
Then, you'll be the future Empress's master.
♫The most painful separation means you can't even miss her♫
Everyone can benefit from it.
Isn't it a good thing?
♫In silence, the world's grudges weave a web of entanglement♫
♫Under the clouds, the smoke from cooking rises and spreads freely♫
♫It's the love doomed by fate♫
Why are you angry?
Why?
♫Under the umbrella, your profile is gently framed by the soft strands of your hair♫
Nan Fengyi
likes you.
♫Should my heart belong to someone for ten thousand years♫
Nonsense.
♫Through endless lifetimes, softly and quietly, it flows on♫
He can fool others,
but not me.
What do you mean?
Actually, it's easy to
get someone aloof like us.
Sometimes,
we act distant
just because we're afraid of getting hurt.
You obviously care about me and worry about me,
but you always push me far away.
Master,
do you have feelings for…
No.
I just don't want to add unnecessary emotional turmoil for myself.
You have to take the initiative to eat
what you love to eat.
You have to take the initiative to chase
someone you like.
Let's go. I'll buy you a drink.
Okay.
[Nan's Umbrella Shop]
Today,
you didn't take me to patrol.
And you stayed in your room since you came back.
What are you doing?
Your injuries haven't recovered.
Why should I take you out?
Look.
My hands are much better now.
It seems the medicine from the Crown Prince
is quite effective.
Tell me.
Are you jealous?
You think too much.
My umbrella.
Before, Li Bai wrote a poem for his wife.
Today, my disciple
repairs my umbrella.
As your master,
I'm really...
really touched.
Don't make random analogies.
The romantic relationship between them
is not the same as ours.
Master, do you know?
This umbrella
is the only thing
my father left to me.
Its power is weak,
but
it has improved a lot
by following me.
With it by my side,
it feels like
my father is still by my side.
So...
no matter
how tattered and ragged it becomes,
I will never abandon it.
If your little umbrella is broken again,
come to me. I'll repair it.
What are you doing?
Let go!
Thank you, Master.
It's great
to have you.
It's not a big deal.
As a girl,
♫What is love, and how many can truly understand it?♫
don't act like you're so easy.
♫In the moment of writing, thousands of thoughts surge through my mind♫
♫Ink stains the paper, words not from the heart♫
♫I collide with the clock of fate♫
Master, what do you mean?
♫Your glance makes the moonlight surge♫
If you have seen the galaxy,
you won't care if a star is bright or not.
♫Your eyes mirror my flustered face♫
Don't act like
you're all so grateful
just because of a little favor from others.
♫How I wish this life could freeze in this moment♫
♫The impulse that pauses for you♫
Why do I feel you're more jealous?
♫My solitary courage and your smile♫
♫Unfamiliar with the ways of the world♫
It's just what's on my mind.
Since you are my disciple,
♫Love, at its deepest, is understood most by the lovers♫
I'll say more.
Okay.
♫The most unique, composed, and touching feelings♫
Master, tell me the truth.
Do you feel inferior
♫Are the special affection you've given me♫
compared to the Crown Prince?
♫Your gaze can't resist it, and my heart aches so deeply♫
Of course not.
Do you dare to look into my eyes
♫My tear stains, and you can't bear them♫
and say it again?
Yi, bring in the tribute umbrellas.
♫Though there are a thousand trials, I'll still seek this possibility♫
Yi!
Bring in the tribute umbrellas!
Let's go.
♫I'm waiting to be reborn in the wasteland in our next life♫
Yi, I've finished these over here.
Bring in those over there.
Master.
Don't get wet.
My legs are short,
so I can't walk fast. That's why I came a litte late.
It's raining heavily.
Why did you come out?
I want to say,
even if I've seen the galaxy,
♫The wind hesitates, not daring to smooth the furrowed brow♫
my favorite star
in my heart
is also the brightest one.
♫The rain hesitates, reluctant to burden the tear-streaked eyes beneath the umbrella♫
♫The closer you are to me, the clearer the pain becomes♫
So what if you have to cultivate?
I can wait for you.
♫The most painful separation means you can't even miss her♫
After you master the Big Dipper Primordial Spell…
It has nothing to do with that.
♫In silence, the world's grudges weave a web of entanglement♫
I don't like you.
But if you don't like me,
♫Under the clouds, the smoke from cooking rises and spreads freely♫
why do you hate to see it when others like me?
♫It's the love doomed by fate♫
You don't allow others to like you.
♫Under the umbrella, your profile is gently framed by the soft strands of your hair♫
That's not true!
♫Should my heart belong to someone for ten thousand years♫
Have you forgotten
what you said the first time I took you
♫Through endless lifetimes, softly and quietly, it flows on♫
to the stable of the Court of Judicature and Revision?
I
have a psychological flaw.
Over the years,
♫I won't lose you♫
I've admired quite a few men,
♫I'll sacrifice myself to help you♫
but as soon as they
showed any feelings for me,
♫With a single lamp and a thousand books, alone I'm restless through the night♫
I'd lose interest
or even feel disgusted.
So,
if you want to keep me as a friend,
♫Give me a fleeting moment of rain, to be held captive by your side♫
you should be cautious about
confessing your love to me.
So,
if I show you my feelings,
would you be turned off
or disgusted?
Yes.
I'll be turned off.
Forget it.
I'm destined not to be loved by anyone.
I can't blame anyone else.
Shall I give it a try?
♫The wind hesitates, not daring to smooth the furrowed brow♫
If you try it,
it'll be all over.
♫The rain hesitates, reluctant to burden the tear-streaked eyes beneath the umbrella♫
In the fire at the Court of Judicature and Revision,
you risked your life to save people.
That made me fall in love with you.
♫The closer you are to me, the clearer the pain becomes♫
You're confident and outgoing.
You have all kinds of thoughts.
All those bring much joy
to my gloomy and boring life.
♫The most painful separation means you can't even miss her♫
♫In silence, the world's grudges weave a web of entanglement♫
I…
♫Under the clouds, the smoke from cooking rises and spreads freely♫
I like you.
♫It's the love doomed by fate♫
♫Under the umbrella, your profile is gently framed by the soft strands of your hair♫
Now, do you
♫Should my heart belong to someone for ten thousand years♫
feel…
turned off?
♫Through endless lifetimes, softly and quietly, it flows on♫
Are you disgusted?
♫I won't lose you♫
You...
seemed to be an exception.
♫I'll sacrifice myself to help you♫
♫With a single lamp and a thousand books, alone I'm restless through the night♫
♫Give me a fleeting moment of rain, to be held captive by your side♫
♫Under the umbrella, your profile is gently framed by the soft strands of your hair♫
♫Should my heart belong to someone for ten thousand years♫
♫Through endless lifetimes, softly and quietly, it flows on♫
Why did I vomit?
Master.
♫I won't lose you♫
I'm so sleepy.
♫I'll sacrifice myself to help you♫
Sure enough.
♫With a single lamp and a thousand books, alone I'm restless through the night♫
I'm not an exception.
♫Give me a fleeting moment of rain, to be held captive by your side♫
Lord Situ,
just to get rid of Nan Fengyi,
you need to use half of your Demon Pill.
Is it worth it?
Only in this way
can I eliminate the biggest obstacle for my master
in the future.
Take care.
You drank too much
last night.
Yes.
After drinking,
I can't remember anything.
Do you remember
it rained last night?
It rained?
Really?
I...
I can't remember clearly.
I went back to my room and slept after drinking, right?
What?
What...
What else happened?
Well,
do you feel dizzy
or nauseous?
The horse is steady.
No.
I'm not dizzy at all.
Nothing happened.
Good.
After you enter the palace,
don't forget the rules.
Also,
what I told you before…
If I find the Puppet Spirit,
I'll send the paperman to inform you immediately.
I'll have a way to deal with it.
Okay.
You're Meng Xizhou from Nan's Umbrella Shop, right?
She's from the Empress' palace.
Yes, it's me.
This is the sample of the tribute umbrella?
You must be the Goddess the Crown Prince mentioned.
Come with me to pay homage to Her Majesty
and have the tribute umbrella checked.
Puppet…
Puppet Spirits!
Go and report to Master
that there are Puppet Spirits in the palace.
-Okay.
-Go!
Oh no.
My Qi Core is leading too fast.
The Demon-Recognizing Pupils are disappearing.
I need to find out which palace they belong to first.
Oh no.
My Demon-Recognizing Pupils are not working.
They're all dressed up the same.
Which one is the Puppet Spirit?
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Over there.
They are all Puppet Spirits.
I know.
Wait for me here.
Don't expose yourself.
The one at the corner.
Yes.
Isn't this the Crown Prince's lunch box?
And these delicacies are all
the ones the Crown Prince treated me to.
They are going to the Eastern Palace!
The person they want to harm
is the Crown Prince!
[Eastern Palace]
What happened?
Something is wrong here.
You...
Go and help the Crown Prince to put on the clothes.
Yes.
Your Highness.
My belt is too loose.
Tighten it up.
Yes.
Do you think I can't tell
if you pretend to be a servant?
Nan Fengyi!
Nan Fengyi?
Situ Hanshan.
Your Majesty, you've been so tired that you're even ill
because of Situ Hanshan.
After drinking the tranquilizing soup,
you can have a good sleep.
Tomorrow,
you can attend the Crown Prince's
Grand Coming-of-Age Ceremony radiantly.
You're right.
Tonight,
I won't see anyone.
Your Majesty!
No, I'm not seeing anyone.
The Eastern Palace…
Puppet Spirits are found in the Eastern Palace!
What about the Celestial Master's Mansion?
Someone has been sent to inform them.
Isn't the Crown Prince in danger?
Nan Fengyi's speculation was right.
He said there had been some abnormalities in the palace
and asked me to strengthen the security.
I didn't expect these demons
to come to target the Crown Prince.
Let's go.
Let's take a look.
Your Majesty.
The Celestial Master's Mansion will help control the situation of the Eastern Palace.
You're not fulled recovered, and your status is distinguished.
It's better not to go there rashly.
This is an important matter.
If I don't see who this demon is,
I can't rest assured.
Your Majesty,
don't worry too much.
His Majesty is the Emperor,
so demons dare not approach him.
Nan Fengyi, what are you doing?
Goddess!
Today, I will kill Situ Hanshan
to avenge my brother.
Situ Hanshan?
No.
He is the Crown Prince!
What's wrong with you?
Hurry up!
Greetings, Your Majesty.
What?
Did the Celestial Master's Mansion only send the two of you?
Where is Du Fenglei?
Your Majesty,
we are taking shifts nearby,
so we rushed here to protect you.
Lord Du will be here soon.
There are demons in the Eastern Palace.
You can't go in there.
Li Hong'an.
How is the Crown Prince now?
Your Majesty,
Nan Fengyi and Master Meng from the Court of Judicature and Revision
are killing demons and saving the Crown Prince inside.
No.
Your Majesty,
why don't you send us to investigate first?
Please wait here.
No.
I'm worried.
At least I need to know
what demon is inside.
Your Majesty,
don't worry.
My junior and I can take two of them each.
Follow me.
I'll protect you.
Guo Ji.
Good!
How can you let His Majesty go in there?
I...
Go!
Hurry!
I'm not Situ Hanshan.
I'm going to kill you
to avenge my friend!
Nan Fengyi!
You...
Nan Fengyi?
Yes.
Move!
How dare you!
This is the Crown Prince,
my son!
Get…
Oh no.
Master is about to unleash his internal power!
Protect me!
Nan Fengyi!
Your Highness, go!
-He's the Puppet Spirit!
-Nan Fengyi!
Hurry!
Go over there.
-Go!
-Nan Fengyi!
Nan Fengyi!
Nan Fengyi.
I'm Chirp.
Master.
Calm down.
Chirp.
It's me.
Nan Fengyi!
You...
♫The wind hesitates, not daring to smooth the furrowed brow♫
Are you a demon?
Your Majesty.
I'll take him back to the Celestial Master's Mansion immediately.
Your Majesty,
♫The rain hesitates, reluctant to burden the tear-streaked eyes beneath the umbrella♫
there must be a misunderstanding.
I'm not a demon.
Nan Fengyi, you...
Your Majesty.
After I bring him back,
♫The closer you are to me, the clearer the pain becomes♫
I'll find out
whether he is a human or a demon.
Fine.
Take him back and interrogate him carefully.
♫The most painful separation means you can't even miss her♫
Yes
Protect His Majesty!
♫In silence, the world's grudges weave a web of entanglement♫
♫Under the clouds, the smoke from cooking rises and spreads freely♫
If I don't go back with him now,
I'll fall into his trap, and you'll also be implicated.
♫It's the love doomed by fate♫
♫Under the umbrella, your profile is gently framed by the soft strands of your hair♫
Master.
I trust you.
♫Should my heart belong to someone for ten thousand years♫
You're not a demon.
♫Through endless lifetimes, softly and quietly, it flows on♫
And there is even less of a chance that you'd hurt the Crown Prince.
As long as you trust me,
♫I won't lose you♫
that's enough.
♫I'll sacrifice myself to help you♫
♫With a single lamp and a thousand books, alone I'm restless through the night♫
Master.
♫Give me a fleeting moment of rain, to be held captive by your side♫
Actually, last night,
I vomited because I was drunk.
I remember
everything you said.
Master.
I will definitely prove your innocence.
I've worked with the Celestial Master's Mansion for a long time.
How could you misjudge me like this?
I really admire you.
Bah!
If you're not a demon,
why do you have scales on your neck?
Do you think we're stupid?
Also,
confess honestly:
Why did you try to kill the Crown Prince?
Where on earth is
Situ Hanshan hiding?
Situ Hanshan was sowing discord
in order to achieve the greater conspiracy.
Fine.
Even if I believe
that it was his scheme, as you said,
how do you explain
your demon body?
See?
Can't explain, huh?
You admitted it, didn't you?
How long can a demon
show its true form in this formation?
Even if you are the Demon King,
inside the Demon Refining Pagoda,
you'll definitely show your true form
within three days.
Okay.
In three days,
you can see if I'm a human or a demon.
You still don't admit it?
Listen.
The more you struggle,
the more it will backfire in the Demon Refining Pagoda.
I advise you
to tell us Situ Hanshan's whereabouts.
Then, I can spare you
from these tortures.
You just want to take the hard way, huh?
Stop!
-My lord.
Master.
Stop torturing him.
Just lock him here for three days.
Master.
Since it's such a good opportunity,
if we can't get anything from him,
then...
All right.
You may leave.
Yes.
Although I didn't see it with my own eyes,
I'm still willing
to believe that you are not a demon.
In three days,
the truth will be out.
Master,
I vomited because I was drunk.
I remember
everything you said.
Chirp.
Wait for me.
Master,
don't be too soft-hearted.
Nan Fengyi
has been pretending to be a human for so long,
but he's actually a demon.
After he's been turned to its true form,
let's torture him.
I don't believe he still won't confess
where Situ Hanshan is by then.
It's not that simple.
Tomorrow is
the Crown Prince's Grand Coming-of-Age Ceremony.
We must be cautious.
Investigate Nan Fengyi…
and his father,
Nan Sixu.