♪Who can distinguish between
a traitor and a warrior♪
♪Mistaking hypocrisy for modesty♪
♪Who is sincere or insincere♪
♪A heart inexplicably lost♪
♪Who says morning dew and twilight
are hard to understand♪
♪Love is the only explanation♪
♪The given heart will be redeemed finally♪
=Fateful Love=
=Episode 4=
“Can I... kiss you?”
(Xiaoshi Market)
♪I can no longer see, hear, or touch♪
This place looks so beautiful.
Look at those lanterns
and the little rabbits.
I want to take a photo here.
Here?
You take it for me.
Hurry up.
Okay.
♪I can no longer recall, retrieve, or polish♪
♪those beautiful and warm♪
Three, two, one.
♪false and hollow conversations♪
Is it good?
Look.
Good.
Is it okay?
Let's take a selfie here.
Okay.
♪Those lost, missed♪
♪and abandoned plots keep unfolding♪
♪Exhausted, I walk on the old road♪
♪Listening to the most familiar song♪
You.
♪But I can't feel or call out that♪
♪simple me from the past♪
♪want to return to the original point♪
♪want to go back to the beginning♪
♪The dark road is too long, too much confusion♪
♪No lighthouse guides me♪
♪See the windless place stirring up waves♪
♪See love, hate, sorrow, joy overturn♪
♪Hazy moonlight or tears♪
♪blurred too much of the past♪
I'm so tired.
You have played the game.
Is there anything else you want to do,
Miss?
Nothing now.
Am I on the edge of danger
and testing the limits crazily?
You have some self-awareness.
♪Under the neon lights,
the crowd keeps crossing paths♪
Gu Suizhi,
I have a question for you.
Go ahead.
Once I complete the agreement,
what will happen?
♪Listening to the most familiar song♪
When you were on a business trip,
I was waiting for you to
come home every day.
I feel like I'm a bit
falling for you.
- You…
- Don't speak yet.
If I'm the only one falling in love,
isn't that a bit of a loss?
Who said you're the only one?
If I don't,
you pretended to have a leg injury
for two months.
Why should I play along with you?
My leg
seems
fine suddenly.
Look.
♪Hazy moonlight or tears♪
♪blurred too much of the past♪
Then,
the second question.
Can I…
♪from the layers of the disguised shell♪
♪How to break♪
♪karma hard to redeem♪
kiss you?
♪I want to return to the original point♪
♪want to return to the beginning♪
♪The dark road is too long, too much confusion♪
♪No lighthouse guides me♪
♪See the windless place stirring up waves♪
♪See love, hate, sorrow, joy overturn♪
(Goodbye,)
(Gu Suizhi.)
♪blurred too much of the past♪
You mean Gu Suizhi
forced your Dad to death.
(Yuanbao Pavilion)
He still wants to deceive you for a lifetime?
He's gone too far.
Cursing won't help either.
The key now is
I need to rely on myself to
open the Yuanbao Pavilion.
This is the best revenge against him.
But look at us now,
we don't have that much money,
nor do we have fame.
This first step might be difficult to take.
Without money, we can save up.
Without fame,
we can fight our way out.
(Yuanbao Pavilion)
Look over there.
- That…
- Let's take a look.
Look, they are stone gambling.
Let's take a look.
Stop.
Expert,
with your unique perspective,
please give me an evaluation.
About this stone of mine,
and its quality,
how much is it worth now?
This is top grade.
At least three million yuan.
If its quality and size
were a bit better,
it'd be worth eight to ten million yuan.
Everyone, hear that?
I won't repeat it.
I don't plan to make a second cut.
I'm only selling it
at one million yuan now.
If you're interested,
take it now.
However,
I only accept
cash transactions.
Offer price.
I offer 1.5 million yuan.
Great!
I offer two million yuan.
I want to buy it for my granddaughter,
as part of her dowry.
This is clearly a veteran expert.
What a keen eye!
Insightful!
Deal.
This material is not worth it at all.
What is she talking about?
This material is clearly
made of two pieces.
In other words, there are two raw stones.
There isn't much jadeite in it.
How is this possible?
They expose the good material outside.
The middle parts are joined together.
This way, it looks like
a complete piece of old mine icy jadeite.
Little girl,
what is your identity?
At such a young age,
you can say a few nice words,
how dare you speak so arrogantly here?
In stone gambling,
once you place your bet,
you must accept the outcome.
That's right. That's the rule.
Everyone,
how about this?
My friend will make a cut.
If, as Mr. Sun said,
I'll buy this stone at four million yuan.
But if, as my friend said,
please return the two million yuan
to this old gentleman.
Please.
This is not emerald green.
Instead, it appears whitish.
A bet is a bet, accept the loss.
Return the money to the gentleman.
Sir,
sorry.
I just interrupted your business.
Not at all.
If it weren't for you just now,
I would have suffered a great loss.
Young girls,
you must be experts, too.
Which shop are you from?
I'll visit you another day
to express my gratitude.
It's just a small effort, Sir.
Welcome to our Yuanbao Pavilion.
So, all this time,
you are making a name for your shop.
But you don't have to
ruin my business, right?
Two beautiful ladies,
you look unfamiliar.
Is this your first day
in the antique business?
Old man,
I'll let you off the hook today.
But as for you two beautiful ladies,
I'd like to have a good chat with you.
Why?
Are you planning to retaliate after
deliberately selling counterfeits?
Retaliate?
Today, I will teach you
the rules of entering the antique business.
Go.
♪I can no longer see, hear, or touch♪
♪that colorful river♪
♪as if only distorted shapes
remain in the pupils♪
♪Lost warmth, black and white♪
♪I can no longer recall, retrieve, or polish♪
♪those beautiful and warm♪
♪false and hollow conversations♪
♪I get used to silence♪
♪want to return to the original point♪
♪want to go back to the beginning♪
♪The dark road is too long, and tears♪
♪blur too much of the past♪
♪How to break free♪
♪from the layers of the disguised shell♪
♪How to break♪
♪karma hard to redeem♪
♪I want to return to the original point♪
♪want to return to the beginning♪
♪The dark road is too long, too much confusion♪
♪blurs too much of the past♪
(The right of communication
through information network of the production)
(is exclusively owned
by Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd.)