♪Who can distinguish between
a traitor and a warrior♪
♪Mistaking hypocrisy for modesty♪
♪Who is sincere or insincere♪
♪A heart inexplicably lost♪
♪Who says morning dew and twilight
are hard to understand♪
♪Love is the only explanation♪
♪The given heart will be redeemed finally♪
=Fateful Love=
=Episode 9=
"Why Do You Always Appear?"
Dad, I want to play with this.
- Want to go up?
- Yes.
- Come, let me help you.
- Okay.
Be careful.
Shall we get it running first?
Watching you.
So dangerous.
Wipe off your sweat.
You are so naughty.
Why don't you criticize him?
Just let him do what he wants.
Don't let him fall.
Don't worry about it.
Dad,
Mom,
today is your wedding anniversary again.
I come to see you.
These seventeen years
have been hard on you.
I don't know if you
still hold any resentment.
In these seventeen years,
everything I have done
has been for revenge.
I won't stop.
But the only person
I don't want to hurt is Shu.
No one can forgive
what her father did,
but I hope
she never finds out about this.
(Guxin Store)
Tomorrow,
I plan to
send Ban Xiuchun
to Germany
for a one-year market arrangement.
The Guxin Store
will be under my management again.
Everyone,
do you have any objections?
- No.
It's a demotion instead of a promotion.
This is to eliminate dissenters,
to kick the Young Master's
power out of Shangqing.
But you know,
in the six months since
the Young Master took charge,
we've made the most money.
In my opinion, who would refuse money?
- Exactly.
- Indeed.
- Everyone,
- Who would refuse money.
do you have any objections
about the resolutions of today's meeting?
I have an objection.
Ban Xiuchun?
Uncle,
you should make way.
This seat should be taken by me.
This is outrageous behavior.
Here
is not a place for your jokes.
This is the record of Guxin Store's
smuggled cultural relics
over the past three years.
If it were to be exposed,
everyone
can't escape, right?
This…
This is not a place for your nonsense.
You need to understand,
You
are just the Young Master.
But don't forget,
Guxin Store
is not your place to decide.
It's not your place either, Uncle.
Do you remember what happened
seventeen years ago?
Only the one who holds the
ancestral Luminous Jade can wield power.
How much longer can this fake
ancestral jade help you cover up?
If you go for a fight to the death,
be careful not to ruin the rest of your life.
You…
How do you know?
Because I have already found
the Guardian of the Luminous Jade.
The real ancestral jade
is with her.
Impossible.
Uncle,
you are truly a master of strategy,
but all in vain.
Alright.
Everyone has worked hard today.
Meeting is over.
In a few days,
I'll invite you to attend Guxin Store's
voting to decide the successor.
Who dares to leave?
Old Master, Old Master!
Old Master!
- Old Master!
- Uncle,
you just recovered.
You'd better not to get angry.
By the way,
The ticket
to Germany,
keep it for yourself.
I will send someone
to take good care of you.
Meeting is over.
This…
Let's go.
Let's go, let's go.
Young Master,
how is it going?
That's good.
We are burning our boats this time.
Ban Ling has already
been sent abroad by me.
Forge the share transfer document.
In three days,
the voting for the successor will be held.
Once you inherit Guxin Store,
Gu Suizhi can do anything to you.
He is the greatest hidden danger.
He must be dead.
Mr. Jin,
you don't need to avoid me.
The Young Master has told me
what my father did.
I've found the way to apologize.
Young Master…
Since what my father did
is so unacceptable in the industry,
as his daughter,
I should repay on behalf of him.
Repay?
Don't do anything foolish.
Even if it's a life debt,
- how will you repay it?
- Life debt?
You are cheating me?
Mr. Jin,
I'm sorry,
but now,
only you can tell me the truth.
I beg you.
Please tell me.
Shu,
what happened?
My father
is a person from Guxin Store.
The Ruan Family has been
the Jade Guardian of the Ban Family.
But seventeen years ago,
it was he who betrayed your parents,
and caused your parents
to die tragically, right?
Who told you these?
So it's true?
Why did he do this?
He was influenced by my Uncle
Ban Ling's manipulation.
To obtain the Luminous Jade
and acquire Guxin Store,
Ban Ling devised this entire plan.
Your father
has been tormented by guilt ever since,
which led to his depression.
So that's how it is.
This is the truth.
That fake Ban Xiuchun
didn't want you to return to Guxin Store
to reclaim your identity,
so he deceived me.
And you didn't want me to find out
my father is a murderer,
so you kept it from me.
Shu,
this has nothing to do with you.
I shouldn't have dragged you into this.
You did nothing wrong.
It is the fault of our Ruan Family.
Mr. Gu,
no,
Mr. Ban,
I apologize on behalf of my father
to all of you.
Shu.
Don't follow me.
I'm begging you.
Dad,
have you ever regretted it?
You must regret it a lot, right?
No wonder
I rarely saw you smile afterward.
It's so ridiculous
that I took the person
who has always protected me as my enemy.
♪as if only distorted shapes
remain in the pupils♪
Dad,
how should I face him in the future?
Can you teach me, please?
♪false and hollow conversations♪
♪I get used to silence♪
♪Through the closed window,
the cold rain blurs♪
♪Under the neon lights,
the crowd keeps crossing paths♪
♪Those lost, missed♪
♪and abandoned plots keep unfolding♪
♪Exhausted, I walk on the old road♪
♪Listening to the most familiar song♪
♪But I can't feel or call out that♪
♪simple me from the past♪
♪want to return to the original point♪
♪want to go back to the beginning♪
♪The dark road is too long, too much confusion♪
♪No lighthouse guides me♪
♪See the windless place stirring up waves♪
♪See love, hate, sorrow, joy overturn♪
♪Hazy moonlight or tears♪
♪blurred too much of the past♪
Gu Suizhi,
why do you always
appear when
I'm at my most embarrassed.
I said before,
as long as you need me,
I will always be here.
♪want to go back to the beginning♪
♪The dark road is too long, too much confusion♪
You are drunk.
If I'm not drunk,
I will never have the courage to do this.
♪See love, hate, sorrow, joy overturn♪
♪Hazy moonlight or tears♪
♪blurred too much of the past♪
♪want to return to the original point♪
♪want to go back to the beginning♪
♪The dark road is too long, too much confusion♪
♪No lighthouse guides me♪
♪See the windless place stirring up waves♪
♪See love, hate, sorrow, joy overturn♪
♪Hazy moonlight or tears♪
♪blurred too much of the past♪
♪I can no longer see, hear, or touch♪
♪that colorful river♪
♪as if only distorted shapes
remain in the pupils♪
♪Lost warmth, black and white♪
♪I can no longer recall, retrieve, or polish♪
♪those beautiful and warm♪
♪false and hollow conversations♪
♪I get used to silence♪
♪want to return to the original point♪
♪want to go back to the beginning♪
♪The dark road is too long, and tears♪
♪blur too much of the past♪
♪How to break free♪
♪from the layers of the disguised shell♪
♪How to break♪
♪karma hard to redeem♪
♪I want to return to the original point♪
♪want to return to the beginning♪
♪The dark road is too long, too much confusion♪
♪blurs too much of the past♪
(The right of communication
through information network of the production)
(is exclusively owned
by Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd.)