DESTINED WITH YOU
EPISODE 9
Gosh.
It looks pretty.
Thank you for your hard work.
The signboard will be done
tomorrow afternoon.
I'll call you when it's up.
Okay.
I'll take pictures for my report.
It's cool.
Why are the lights off?
This shouldn't happen
during the festival, sir.
Sir?
Goodness.
UNKNOWN
Hello?
Hello--
What's happening?
UNKNOWN
Are you okay?
Hey.
-What?
-I'll move your washing machine. Let's go.
To my place?
Yes.
Won't that be a bit weird?
Why? I'm just a friend to you.
Well, that's true.
Can you open the door?
I moved the washing machine,
moved the bed,
and changed the lights. Done, right?
-All good?
-Yes, it's all good.
Here, raspberry wine.
I have no use for it, but…
Do you want some ramyeon?
Gosh, you startled me.
I don't have any other food,
so I thought
I'd make you ramyeon at least.
I have a blind date.
At this hour?
The Tax Department is busy.
Seung-yeon asked to meet
at night after her work.
What should I do?
Take it off now. I'll wash it.
Okay.
-Quickly.
-Okay.
-We must wash it fast.
-Let me…
I don't look suitable
for a blind date, do I?
The shirt's too dirty.
Right.
So why did you spill it?
Hey.
Can I hug you?
What are you saying?
What kind of man asks that beforehand?
That's why you've been alone forever.
Don't ever ask that to Seung-yeon.
It's so lame.
How could you two keep this a secret?
My son is sick.
But I was unaware of it.
Does this make sense?
You could wake him up.
Keep your voice down.
Mother, go home and get some rest.
I'm not going anywhere.
You go home if you want to.
I'll stay here.
Why would you lash out at her?
You should be thankful
that she found Sin-yu in the parking lot.
You go too. I don't want to see you.
You kept this from me.
How could you not tell me
that Sin-yu was sick?
He told me not to.
He didn't want to worry you.
He didn't tell me either.
My poor boy.
It must've been so hard
dealing with this all alone.
Hong-jo.
LEE HONG-JO, GREENWAY BUILDING DIVISION
Are you inside?
Hong-jo.
I was worried.
Your phone rang, but you didn't pick up.
I was lying down.
What's wrong? Are you sick?
Can…
Can I ask you a favor?
I ran out of painkillers,
but I didn't have the energy
to go buy some.
Will you be fine with that?
Yes.
I just feel chilly and a bit feverish.
Right.
I brought some sleeping pills
just in case.
You need to sleep soundly.
Thank you.
Jae-gyeong's on my list of suspects too.
It's easy for him to steal your pajamas.
I have a question.
Why were you in the park just now?
To check on the festival.
You checked it yourself?
I actually do quite a lot
of miscellaneous things.
Sin-yu asked
if I'd agree to set up a CCTV.
Did you agree to it as well?
No. He didn't tell me about that.
I didn't agree with the CCTV.
I don't understand why he's asking
such a favor worrying about you.
I wanted to talk about it,
but he's on sick leave,
so I couldn't meet him.
Do you know why
he's on sick leave?
No.
You should go sleep now.
I won't go down until you're asleep.
Go down first.
I'll think about setting up a CCTV myself.
And if anything happens,
tell me first.
I will.
Finish up the medicine
if you're still unwell tomorrow.
I brought a hot-water bottle.
I'll heat this up and leave.
JANG SIN-YU
Due to the illness's nature,
he might develop cerebral infarction.
But the affected area isn't large
this time, so he'll recover soon.
It's just a temporary TIA.
He was very lucky.
Why can't he wake up?
He's been sleeping for two days.
It might be due to
accumulated fatigue or stress.
Will Sin-yu be fine?
I told you not to say something ominous.
Is something wrong with you?
Hong-jo?
Come here.
Okay.
"Festival." I edited them all.
-Thank you.
-Welcome.
MR. KWON JAE-GYEONG
How are you feeling?
Hello, Gyu-hyeon.
Yes.
No. Yes.
Sin-yu. You're awake.
Are you okay?
Why won't you speak?
Look at me.
You recognize me, right?
Stop making a fuss.
Sin-yu.
How are you feeling?
Can you sit upright?
That was such a long sleep.
I was worried sick.
Look at my face.
I've aged so much in a few days.
It's not time for you
to be worrying about your face.
His face has become half its size.
His face was always small.
He takes after me and has a small head.
Having a small head
isn't something to brag about.
Back in the day,
a small head meant a small brain.
What you said
is insulating.
You mean "insulting."
GROOT
Are you in hospital?
Why won't you read my texts?
Reply when you read this.
GROOT
ARE YOU IN HOSPITAL?
WHY WON'T YOU READ MY TEXTS?
REPLY WHEN YOU READ THIS.
ARE YOU IN HOSPITAL?
WHY WON'T YOU READ MY TEXTS?
REPLY WHEN YOU READ THIS.
I guess you were worried.
Of course I was. You thought I wasn't?
I'm upset with you.
The first thing you look for
isn't your mom, dad,
me, nor Na-yeon.
It's your phone.
Aren't you busy?
That's not important.
When you're discharged, let's go skiing.
I want to see snow with you.
You can go now.
What do you mean?
I meant we should go together.
I meant you should leave.
It's cold. You should've dressed warmly.
You texted me a lot.
You told me to contact you
via the in-house email or messenger only.
There's an exception to everything.
You told me not to get closer.
What happened?
I don't remember.
Did your illness become worse?
What illness do you have?
I got sick from the AC.
It's so cold.
Stop fooling around, will you?
Do you know how worried I was?
And yet, you came empty-handed.
I'll buy you something before I leave.
I got to see you, so it's fine.
Actually, I didn't come here
to check on you.
I came here to get the wooden box.
Why?
I'm concerned about the curse doll.
I know what you're thinking.
But I've had this illness before that.
Wasn't it getting better
before it suddenly got worse?
-I want to check something.
-Don't.
Can't you just give it to me when I ask?
You said it was mine
and that I had to deal with it anyway.
Did anything happen?
Nothing happened.
When are you getting discharged?
I don't want to.
So you would keep worrying about me.
You're perfectly fine,
seeing how you're speaking nonsense.
Did you change the passcode to your place?
I didn't.
I know it's rude to go
to your house when you're not there,
but please excuse me.
I'll go with you.
You can't. You're sick.
Go back in now.
I don't want to.
Do you want to catch a cold
as well? Go in quickly.
I have things left to say.
I think you can stop taking pictures now.
I'm so glad that you woke up.
Hong-jo cleared up my misunderstanding.
I was still going to wait
until you contacted me first.
Isn't it good that I'm impatient?
It would've been bad
if I hadn't found you.
You should thank me.
Right. Did you hear
about our travel plans afterward?
Yes, I did.
I hope you get discharged quickly.
I bought some porridge. Let's eat.
I didn't eat dinner
because I wanted to eat with you.
SPELLS OF THE HEAVENS
"If someone is cursed by this spell
with strong and malicious energy,
their soul and body will be destroyed."
COMMANDMENTS
"If you cast the spell
with hatred and resentment
that cannot be spoken out,
a disaster would assuredly be unleashed."
LOVE DESTRUCTION SPELL
"Make a straw doll
and dress it with the clothes
of someone you love."
"Put a black cloth on its head and write
the name of the person you want to curse."
"Pierce it with needles
as many as the person's age."
Do you think Sin-yu's sick
because of this curse?
You believe in spells.
Ghosts exist for those who can see them.
They don't exist for those who can't.
I should try it again.
What are you doing?
It's so dark and spooky in here.
Did you bring it?
What do you need this for?
You don't need to know.
What a pervert.
I didn't tell you to do that.
Give it back.
Do you think I did
all the things until now
because you told me to?
If it wasn't because I told you to,
why did you do those things?
It was my plan.
Oh, my.
I wonder what plan that is.
Just shut up and cooperate.
You're insane.
Why would I cooperate with you?
It's fun.
Compared to drama or romance,
a thriller's more exciting.
So what do you want me to do?
BUYONGJAE FESTIVAL
Checked.
I have things left to say.
I can't go to work this week.
I need to go on a trip
after I get discharged.
Have a safe trip.
Don't you want to know with whom?
Why are you asking me that?
If you tell me not to go,
I won't go.
Rest well in Jeju Island.
When we come back,
pack up and move back into our house.
Resting for a few days isn't enough.
Maybe Sin-yu and I should stay there
for a month.
Why would Sin-yu live with you?
He should live with Na-yeon if anything.
Moving in together before getting married?
I'm too worried
about him staying alone.
Since we're at it, let's decide now.
Move into our house or live with Na-yeon.
Na-yeon doesn't know how to do anything.
If he lives with me, I can cook for him.
Don't you think so?
Do you believe in past lives?
He's not fully recovered.
Call Dr. Kim right now.
We need another checkup.
No. There's no need.
Why suddenly bring up past lives?
To the interested parties
and citizens of Onju
who graced us with your presence
despite the cold,
I sincerely express my gratitude.
Onju's fireworks festival
started in mid-Joseon dynasty
right here in Buyongjae
and has been passed down until now.
It's a traditional event
with a long history.
It has beauty incomparable
to modern fireworks.
With the fireworks
to light up the cold winter night,
I hope you wrap up this year well.
Now,
let the 30th Buyongjae Fireworks Festival
commence.
Get ready.
Sir, start lighting them up.
Okay, I'll ignite them.
GROOT
Look at that.
How pretty.
You didn't go on the trip.
Didn't you call to stop me from going?
That's right.
I called to stop you from going.
But I didn't expect you
to come all the way here.
Spells do work after all.
I tried it again.
I wanted to check if it worked or not.
It doesn't matter…
whether spells work or not.
I love you.
Let's run away.
It doesn't matter where.
Anywhere's fine.
Be careful.
I am being careful.
-Why is this so heavy?
-I know, right?
Goodness.
What was that?
Let's go quickly.
Quickly.
Hurry up.
Let's go quickly.
-Let me go.
-Don't do this.
I told you to let me go.
If you don't, I'll make them beat you up.
What is happening?
Please let me in.
I need to meet my mother.
Allow me to meet her.
I said you cannot go into her room.
I heard her illness got worse.
What if she passes away?
Your mother…
does not wish to see you.
That…
That cannot be true.
Sir.
My deepest condolences.
She has passed away.
Poor madam.
Poor madam!
How dare you smile?
Yes.
Don't cry.
Rather, get angry like now.
You don't study hard.
So you haven't seen
what your mother wrote.
She put a letter in your book.
Go and read it now.
CHILDREN'S FIRST TEXTBOOK
I dreamed about you even at dawn.
The fact that I could see you
in my dreams at least,
made me foolishly happy.
My precious son.
I miss you so much that it hurts.
But I was worried
about you catching my illness,
so I couldn't see you.
So,
please understand
why I'm doing this.
It was a short life,
but every day was joyful because of you.
My life
couldn't have been
happier.
You're the crybaby.
Did you read your mother's letter?
How dare a low being
like you talk to me informally?
You must not know who I am.
I'm the son of this town's governor.
I see.
Goodbye.
-But, sir.
-What?
Aren't you taking your books?
CHILDREN'S FIRST TEXTBOOK
That's a nice bow.
How dare you?
I know you waited for me
to thank me about your mother's letter.
I am grateful for that.
But I would've read it anyway.
I just had to open my book.
But you wouldn't have.
-What?
-I can tell.
You don't look like you study.
Hey, stop right there.
I placed first in school.
And what's that about my looks?
Here. Take this.
Wow.
It's a worm.
Don't touch it.
Don't. What are you doing?
Throw it away now.
-It's good for your health. Try it.
-No.
-Here.
-Stop.
-Boo!
-I told you to stop.
My father told me
to prepare for the state exam.
I'm very conflicted.
I'm talented both in studies
and martial arts.
So it's hard to decide what to do.
You have no talent in studies.
You always fail your tests in school.
Can you see my future?
What happens if I choose
to join the military?
Will I become a general?
What is it?
Will I be stuck as a foot soldier?
No. You'll work your way up.
Can you really ride it alone?
Yes.
Aren't you afraid?
I'm not.
Let's go.
Did you do your coming-of-age ceremony?
You have no idea
how much I've waited to be an adult.
How do I look?
I tied my hair in a top knot
and wore a gat for the first time.
I'm surprised.
You look so great.
That's a relief.
I wanted you to think that today.
Today is a very special day for us.
It might be for you
who did the coming-of-age ceremony.
But to me,
it's just a normal day like any other day.
You foresee others' futures so well,
but you have no idea
what will happen to you.
You don't know
what will happen to me either.
I know.
Because I'll do it.
For example…
Something like this.
Your face is as red as an apple.
It's because of the sunset.
You're lying.
DESTINED WITH YOU
There's one more person
who remembers the past life.
I've loved her since long ago.
Wait for me.
You're just confused.
We can't break up that easily.
Snap out of it.
Don't get shaken up by Sin-yu.
Come to me.
The view, the feel.
Everything felt real.
But why am I the only one who sees
and remembers it?
Subtitle translation by: Kim Yeeun