I still don't know where Fabad can escape.
I still can't take care of my own things.
No matter what
We will take Mara with us.
Put down the gun, Fabad.
C
Did you shoot him?
I do my duty
Are you ready to shoot the man into the water?
Couldn't find him.
Tomorrow the king will come in and take over your assets.
All Chaiyaram premises
Ask Mom and everyone to put their personal belongings out.
Grab some too. I'll be ready.
They both got six.
It's been a week already. Tomorrow morning, وہ will come to pick you up.
O
No, no one can stop me.
Root pequeña bay Is something wrong, Madam Mai?
Y gives size
An important letter came to Mala. Malacha's mother is not dead yet.
But no
Know where it is if I know anything more than this.
I will send the news quickly.
Take good care of yourself and my grandchild.
Next Saturday I will be giving a thank you party to the writers.
cream
and the people who support us
I want you to...
Then the girls in the group went to welcome us.
We are not green women.
Those people will help me become a handsome wife with good looks and money.
Choose whether to love your dignity or preserve your drama.
hold
We'll be right back.
Thank you.
Thank You
have watched
Tune in next time.
Words for younger brother love older brother
Yes, sir.
In my mind I say
to whisper
You keep reservations.
Aren't you ready to come today?
I saw that you went to see a friend who was sick.
Have you ever gone to see the drama that Soi acted in?
At the Kasem Friday Theater
beautiful
Beautiful as rumored
But I heard from the doctor that no one dared to interfere.
Because you are taking care of me.
I take care of you like a younger sister.
Today
Please let me take care of you.
Drink a little more in front of the necklace.
Sak told me that her theater was in bad shape.
I can help.
thank you very much
I can't drink anymore.
So, one last glass.
We'll be right
back.
I'll be back first.
Just now, Sak told me that if I could take care of her,
Oh, he's happy.
Now he has to run for representative again. He's still busy.
Look ahead.
If you were mine, you wouldn't have to.
What are you afraid of?
Because I never let my people suffer.
If
Don't do anything to me.
Who came to knock on the door?
Today instead, I have a study job at Baksaeng.
is...
What are you doing here?
What are you doing?
chain
How are you?
light
How to lift?
Soi, I'm sorry.
Lady, I went to work so I came back late.
Is the chain coming?
Thank you. I drink.
This!
That first, that first
Can you handle it?
Sit first, sit first
Thank you.
Please subscribe
and
press the bell
button.
Subtitles provided by the Amara.org community
I'm sorry.
Sorry I'm late.
Don't be afraid.
It's safe.
Safe today, another day.
In the end, they saw me as a woman.
Dancing and eating
There's no dignity.
I'm making everyone suffer.
that you do
Because she is saving the theater.
It's not her duty.
I am tired
do
Why is it this difficult?
I will do
Can you do that?
I promise I'll be with you.
I'll be there to help you.
We fight together.
Why do you again?
She is still the same as she never chose to care for the devil.
I can do it right away.
I love you
Thank you.
Sorry, I lied to myself.
Really not
Haven't you given up waiting to come and hunt yet?
Do you think that without him, he would turn and look at you?
O
Please wake up.
If someone doesn't love you, they won't love you.
I don't want Maram to love me.
I just stay close to him.
I just want to take care of him.
It's the two of us.
I'm stupid.
Just focusing on people who don't love us.
And then I lie to myself that this is all I'm happy about.
I'm not lying to myself.
alley
Where else will you go if you're drunk like this?
I'm going to find Mala.
Mala, what are you sending after me? What's going on?
climb
What did you do that day, sir?
Follow me because of this.
What news did he send you?
Here comes this story
Why did you lie to me?
- Then why does Mr. Flag say these things? nunca
Ah!
Don't look at the bishop.
Who sent you the letter?
Lady Grandma made me fat so he didn't make me feel dizzy.
It shows that Lady Grandma already knows about this.
And does anyone else know this?
I do not know
But what did you do, sir?
That my little brother lied to everyone that Mr.
It's already finished.
What exactly happened that night?
So our friendship with you
It ends here.
It's up to His Majesty.
But now Faban must hurry and get away from here.
I hope it will come.
We'll go back and take Mara with us.
Not Faban
We'll take Mara with us.
Put down the gun, don't force me to do this.
This
Come on, I'm ready.
Shoot now.
very much
We die here too.
We won't go anywhere.
Pamara is not going for us.
Trust me, Your Majesty.
I will take it out of the country first.
Wait for the matter to calm down and then return to Mala.
Mom promised to take good care of Mala.
Is it because of this reason?
The one you made us leave behind Because you still love Mal.
Where are you?
Yes, the cover
Looking at it, I still love Mala.
But it was nothing more than friendship to look at.
There is a cover for the baht.
Looking at the contract
that he would take good care of Mala
Not arrested but must stay until Faba returns.
If we run away
Chaichon definitely won't let us go.
Because we were accidentally outside the country.
It's even easier to manage us.
And if it happens that we make everyone believe
that His Majesty is dead
They will stop chasing Your Majesty.
Ugh!
Take good care of yourself
Please take care of Mala.
You gathered together, I did my duty.
Sir!
Take the boat out and search everywhere.
yes!
I know Chayon won't let me go. Until the man will
end
That I had to lie to you Because I'm worried about you.
Thank you very much
Can you promise me?
that this matter will be kept a secret
Don't tell anyone at all.
Even so
because he was in trouble with Phansak
So where is this man now?
I'm trying to investigate. But there was no news at all.
It shows that the man has sent the news to Father.
Mala, the man didn't send you news.
For fear that you will be harmed
Sir, I am very worried about you.
I promise you, sir, that I will take good care of you until
that he will return
When did it happen?
No one can tell this story.
You have to take good care of yourself and your child.
I believe that you will be together.
complete family
father mother child
Don't you ever chase me again.
Why are you coming in at this late hour?
alley
You're ready, he just brought things for you.
I'll be back soon.
thank you very much
What's yours?
Are you drunk here?
Go to bed. No need to change the subject.
Why did you let him into the house?
Have you forgotten in just a few months that he killed Tonch?
Wow
Not like that, please.
Today I fell down.
Just returned from the hospital this evening.
I think you should be more concerned about Mala than her.
It's me.
Really? Is it a big deal?
I don't mind much.
But Soi was already very drunk.
You should go to bed. Go.
You go back first.
It's like, come on, man.
Are you going to get back together with him?
What is this stuff?
He just did this, forgive him.
Is that good?
That is me
It took a long time to forgive.
I'm very drunk. Go to bed.
Do you know what I have to leave behind?
What do I have to leave behind to take care of me?
It can't be compared to him, can it?
My love doesn't have any parts, right?
Go, don't talk, go, go to bed, go.
Go up to the room, walk carefully, alley, walk carefully.
Don't answer me at all.
Why did you let him into the house?
Soi, why did you drink until you were so drunk?
I told you and didn't tell you.
I don't know.
I'm here.
Are you awake?
I'm coming.
I'm hungry.
Mr. Kun Malala
Khun Mala went out to the hospital early this morning with the captain.
yes
Is the captain ready?
Khun Mala, didn't he press on that captain, Khun Soi?
I really don't understand. Why did you come?
It's that easy to forget.
Well, I just heard that Khun Mala complained that she was disappointed.
I need it since last night.
The captain stopped by to bring medicine for the itching, so he took him to see a doctor.
Come on, don't be afraid.
I'll see the doctor soon.
Really cute.
My husband is very worried about people.
Taking care of his wife is not far away at all.
Not your husband.
He's just a friend.
Please come and see Dr.Wan.
I told you so That I won't let you mess around.
My
release
I can take care of Mala myself.
How do you care for Mala to hurt like this?
You got drunk and argued with Mala last night, right Mala?
I got a stomach ache.
Mara told you?
I expected Kanmara himself.
He makes amends for the three of you.
that you didn't mean to
So you took this opportunity to come in and mess with me.
Wow!
I'm really asking.
Are you not ashamed of yourself?
kill his husband
And before this, he still came to visit his friend's wife.
What you think is up to you.
But the only person who could stop me was Mara.
He won't stop you because he's infatuated with you.
Where are you going?
I told you to go back.
I love you.
It's a good day.
It's
a
day when I have a lot of work to do.
I'm going to have a good breakfast.
I'm going to
have
a good breakfast.
Text by Nicolai Winther
In the movie, Khao Chao, a foreigner, Prachai
He has been waiting for you for a long time.
Today she made an appointment with him quickly.
Why don't you go?
My story
release
So how can you see that I'm here?
People like you, if you don't fight with Mala, you stay at home.
he
If there's a problem, you're not at the theater, you're here.
Did you quarrel with Mala?
I went to borrow Brother Waen's car.
It is used to transport Mala until Mala is born.
Mala will be able to stop messing with you again.
The person he doesn't love Anyway, he doesn't love me.
As for the person he loves, how wrong has he done?
He forgives
I think
If there is no Than Chai Ram
I will go back to Mala's side like before.
On
But no.
People who come to give opportunities
not me
So can you give me a chance?
Thank you for
watch!
30g butter
1 tsp salt
1 tsp sugar
1 tsp vanilla extract
1 tsp vanilla sugar
mix well
After 1 hour
I'll see you next time.
Welcome, Ms.
Soi.
Soi isn't at the theater?
Mr. Soi hasn't been to the theater since morning.
Yes.
Today I have an appointment with the owner of the leather strap.
Khun Kanya went out to follow him and another person disappeared.
Until the owner of our movie line couldn't take it and went back first.
What's wrong with you?
Soi hasn't been here since this morning.
Together
Do you often have meals at the theater these days?
Why do you drink so often?
Isn't it our party?
It is a party for the tattoo breeders.
He sent us to receive his guests.
For סaca to help promote the theater further.
- Is racon really bad?
- Mr. Soi never told you.
- But these days, Racon has 2 rounds per week left.
- People who watch movies can talk a lot.
- until some of us began to be afraid
- How long will Racon continue to play?
- She went back to wait at the Rakon station first.
- In case you get any news about Soi.
Now, I'll ask another way.
Yes, sir.
equation
Please, please, Mara.
go
Where are you going?
Go find an alley.
Please accept it.
Miss Mara
It's about to rain. Where are you going?
I'll go find the alley.
You can stay with Kranok.
I saw that I had severe morning sickness.
Go Som
Please accept it.
thank you
Yes, yes.
Just go out.
Pull up!
Oh, my God.
hair
person
Oh, my ears?
Go call him.
You, sir.
g
The alcohol is rancid.
It's better.
You, sir.
You, I greet you, I love you, how are you?
It's full of blood.
You greeted you.
alley alley
what happened
Last night she was drunk.
then crashed the car
Slowly, slowly
Last night I drove really well.
A tow truck came out and cut in front of me.
What's wrong with them?
Why
What's wrong with someone?
Malay
horse
Come
Don't be afraid.
you are safe
Is it a child?
How are you?
- Is your child safe?
Is your child safe?
The child is no longer with you.
Som died in the scene.
Oh, my
God.
n
Nam Luat said that it was raining, so the road moved.
Yes.
That driver was drunk.
I heard locals say that the driver was drunk.
Why did he do this?
Because of his irresponsibility, two lives were lost.
must die
Is he in this hospital too?
Please take me to him.
I will take the matter to the end.
You don't have to go.
I'll handle the case myself.
We'll bring Grandma Nai Somma now.
But I want to see his face
key
Take me out to him now.
Hurry up
It's hot.
It's
hot.
It's hot.
That is, it was raining a lot. Can't see anything
So I'm really sorry. It came.
Younger father
Sir, is that person Soi?
O
I thank you.
I haven't been here. I am really sorry
I am sorry
Why, why does it have to be a slave?
Are you getting drunk again?
Didn't I tell you that I want to eat?
Have you seen what it's like?
No, I didn't, Mala. I'm really sorry.
Really determined
Mala, it is an accident.
No one wants it to happen.
I know
Just like this would be fate.
that I used to do with Soi
From now on, let us be free from all karma once and for all.
Don't bother honoring him again.
Key, please take me back to my room.
key
Royal, I really didn't mean to, thank you.
royal
The royal don't let go.
His Majesty the King
Nationality
I love
you so much!
I love you too!
Why, child?
Mother Bones, it's yours.
Said mother when she stabs her child
Ah, stabbed the child?
Duh!
Soi's case
I'll leave it to you to take care of it.
I don't take issue with anything.
Let's let it end.
And what about making merit for your children?
I'd like to ask you to prepare some things.
Please go up and rest first.
I prepared porridge for you.
Eat first.
I am not hungry yet
Please give MLA some time.
Then almost Dhamma Boon Chao Jiw Mara has you do it.
What is it?
Maraja dances for the soul of his child. With the role of Mrs. Montho Kla
I'm thinking about Indrajit.
Has the government already made him black?
I will handle that matter myself.
As for the year of the cloth and dress
I'm going to borrow from the Maharasok Division.
I haven't played the role of Nang Monto in a long time.
But that's okay.
You'll probably be able to practice a bit.
Mara will perform the role of Mrs. Montho herself.
Personally, Phra Mara asked me to contact the people of the Sod Theater Division.
Why?
Mara said
He won't mess with you anymore.
Subtitles made by DimaTorzok
Mrs. Montho Si's side
Saopa
Listen to me dear child.
Just to star in the ground.
Nachiwan
And then Mrs. Chaemjan Ral
Thinking of Lord Uma
Mrs. Nontho Chuengwaj
Wow, that's Luk Or Lu.
Mother is not dead anymore.
Oh no!
With my mother used to win.
Phra Umadevi Ong
Mother, graciously
Give a blessing
Give your mother's fortune
It's auspicious.
Songprasit Kas
Irachan is a friendly person.
Even if anyone dies
With a weapon
Drink and eat without end of life
creative
Father will free you and survive.
Dangerous effects
Which, my dear child,
The students were taught at the time.
This
Invited to come and drink water.
of Channani, don't
got worried
© transcript Emily Beynon
From Joe...
Teachers are interested in a group of teachers.
Would you like to perform at my theater?
The teaching unit reported the news.
Tonight, the national recovery team
Will be returning from Penang.
Listen carefully, this is the only job you can do.
Mr. Phraraj, Mr. Phraraj, sir.
Try looking at the news in the book unit.
You
I feel bad.
B
Subtitle Volunteer
Yang
madder
Thank you for watching.
Thank you.