What?
This is just a screen.
These images are computer-generated.
Computer-generated?
All of this?
-Welcome home.
-I'm back!
-Here, I got this.
-Thanks.
Oh! I'm starving!
Usagi?
Arisu…
I missed you.
So much.
I'm sorry.
Let's go home.
Okay. Yeah.
Sorry.
It's you!
Whoa! Easy!
Why are you with Usagi?
-Stop it!
-You killed her!
-All this is your fault!
-Calm down!
-Come on!
-Arisu, stop it!
-Wait!
-Ryuji?
-Ryuji, are you all right?
-Hold on. There you go.
He's been fighting by my side
this whole time.
Usagi…
If he hadn't been there,
I wouldn't have made it this far.
-But what he did is--
-What he did is save my life!
What he did is bring us back together.
Registration is now closed.
Ten participants confirmed.
Ten participants?
But there are only nine of us here.
What do you think it means?
-A child.
-Huh?
A child.
What?
The doctor said you're pregnant, Usagi.
I… I'm pregnant?
You're carrying our baby.
Oh…
So that's why it's ten people. The baby.
Hey, kid, nice one!
But… a child in this situation is…
The game will now begin.
It's about to start.
Please put on your wristbands and collars.
Game. Possible Futures.
Game rules.
There are a total of 25 rooms,
arranged in five vertical columns
and five horizontal rows.
Each round, players must roll the dice
found on the platform
in the center of the room.
The resulting number determines how many
people can advance to the next chamber.
Repeat until you reach the exit.
You have a maximum of 15 rounds.
EXIT
However, those players who do not
advance because of the dice roll
cannot move.
A lockdown will activate,
forcing the player to stay.
FORCED STAY
To lift the lockdown,
two players must use their wristbands
on either side of the locked room.
UNLOCKED
Each player has been allocated 15 points.
To pass from one chamber to another,
one player must spend one point
and hold their wristband up to the door.
If you wish to return
to the room you just left,
you must wait for one round
before being allowed to do so.
Regardless of whether you remain
in a chamber by choice or by force,
one point will be deducted
from your total each round.
If a player's points reach zero,
they will be eliminated.
The walls of each chamber will display
images of your possible future.
The future you choose
from among those images
will become your reality
once you reach the exit.
We get to choose our own future…
THE FUTURE THAT WILL COME TO PASS
Proceed according to the dice roll
and choose your future
as you search for the exit.
Maybe the best strategy would be
to team up and work together.
Hey, you two. What are your names?
-I'm Sohta. This is my sister.
-Yuna.
I'm Arisu.
This is Sachiko, Rei,
Tetsu, and Nobu.
Begin. Roll the dice
and select the room you wish to enter.
The time limit is three minutes.
So the dice and the doors
are connected by color.
All right!
Dice games are sorta my specialty.
So then, you're a gambler too, are you?
Round one. Start.
Okay. Let's do this.
Are these really visions of our future?
All of this? No way.
Here we go! Come on, baby! Yeah!
-I hit the jackpot! Wow!
-You won!
Thank you for the meal.
What?
No way, seriously?
Look. I'm pretty sure
the future is different on each wall.
Ah! Fuck this!
Shit!
So our futures change depending
on which door we pass through…
Please, just read it, sir.
This again, Matsuyama?
I've had about enough of this nonsense.
No, Professor, please!
Just read the abstract! Anything!
If I quit my research now,
it'll be all for nothing!
No one's going to take this seriously.
Least of all the academic world.
At least read a couple of pages, please.
Maybe a magazine on the occult
would be more suitable?
Over here! Look at Mommy!
Smile!
Beautiful day, too.
Oh yeah, isn't it perfect?
I don't know about you guys,
but if that's the future, I choose blue.
Me too.
But we can't all go through.
Only seven of us are allowed.
Why doesn't one person take yellow?
-Yeah!
-Nice shot, Hida!
All right!
From what I see, yellow looks okay.
No. We should probably try
to minimize wasting points.
I'm pretty sure
that's the key to the game.
So we stick together.
We move through
as a group if we can, right?
Yeah… We can't all go through
blue, so let's split into two groups
and take the doors
with the largest numbers.
Sohta and Yuna.
You two will be on a team with Rei.
I want you three…
to go to the room east of here, D3.
The rest of us will go north, to C2.
That way we can all meet up again
to the northeast, in D2.
D3.
That's great!
-Yuna? Yuna?
-Ken? Is that you?
I didn't even see you come in!
This is my brother.
-Ken is a classmate from university.
-We can do that.
-Hi, I'm Ken.
-Hey there.
Plus, the red door isn't a problem for us.
See you!
One minute remaining.
-So that's the plan.
-Let's go.
You all trust this guy,
no questions asked?
If you don't like his plan,
try a different door.
Please hold your wristbands
up to your chosen door
to proceed to the next room.
Let's do it. It's time.
We'll see you guys in D2.
Okay.
I'm Rei Morikage.
RÉSUMÉ
REI MORIKAGE
I've loved anime ever since I was a kid
and… that inspires my drawings.
How quickly are you able to draw?
At the moment, it takes me
around three days to fill a page.
C2 is a minus one point room.
Please select the player
whose point will be deducted.
What do they mean, "minus one point?"
It means that some of these rooms
can remove points from us.
But we won't know how many points
until we're already in.
Which complicates things.
We took from Arisu's points last time,
so now we can take from mine.
Round two. Start.
Now, roll the dice and select
the room you wish to enter.
We can't go back the way we came
without waiting a round.
There are three rooms we can enter.
That's why there are three dice.
Okay! Stand aside.
Three, one, five?
If this shows the future we're gonna face,
then I wanna choose the blue door again.
MOVIE TICKET
EVERYBODY LOVES FAMILY!
-We should do this more often.
-I've been wanting to see this.
Huh.
CLASS 1 ARCHITECT
DESIGN DRAWING EXAM
Huh?
You're going to study
to become an architect?
What?
If you encountered bullying among
your students, what would you do?
Mr. Hida? What do you think?
-Sir, I would take a measured approach.
-This future could really be mine?
I'd listen to both sides.
I don't wanna choose the red door.
Hey. There's a seminar
you might like. Interested?
SKILL DEVELOPMENT SEMINAR
Ah, no, I'll pass.
-I don't have the time.
-But it's like investing in your future!
Time well spent, don't you think?
At least give it a chance.
Would you write your name, please.
All right, thank you.
Please take a seat in any available chair.
D2, where we're planning
to meet up, is behind the red door.
So I'll take that one.
I'll meet up with Rei
and the rest of the group.
Then I'm going with you.
Then as for the rest of you,
go through the blue one, okay?
To room C1.
Well done, Matsuyama!
The research funding you were hoping for!
-Is this really happening?
-It is. Congratulations.
Thank you so much.
I'll meet up with you later.
Well…
Let's go.
TO: YUZUHA ARISU
THANK YOU FOR THE OTHER DAY
CAN WE MEET?
I'm getting a weird feeling
from this game.
Is it actually reading all our minds?
Does it know what we're thinking?
All twos.
I'm going to head north to room D2.
Ideally, I'd like
the three of us to go together.
But we have to split into two groups.
That sounds good.
The two of us will go… east, to E3.
Right.
JOB OFFER CONFIRMATION
Oh my gosh!
-Whoa, this is so good!
-Hey, are you listening to me?
Rei. Let's meet up in room D2, as planned.
Roger that.
-All right.
-That's a relief.
Yeah.
Round three. Start.
Huh?
One and two?
Usagi counts as two people here.
So she has to go to D1.
And only one of us can go through to E2.
That means no matter what we do,
someone has to stay behind.
Attention, everyone.
This is Morikage.
She'll be starting today.
I look forward to working with you all.
I'm Rei Morikage.
It's nice to meet you.
Well, I guess it is what it is.
I'd like you to begin with this cut.
I'll stay behind this time.
What?
You have a baby who needs you.
-But…
-Rei…
I owe you one for the zombie thing.
Hmm.
Usagi, you meet up
with Sachiko and the others.
Sachiko, can you hear me?
Yeah, I can hear you.
How many people can go on to D1?
-Who gives a rat's ass…
-Four. We all can.
-But when you drink…
-That's great. Then do it.
-All of you go east to D1.
-All you ever do is nag.
-Would you keep your voice down?
-I want you to meet Usagi there.
Oh, sorry, I wouldn't wanna be heard…
-That's not what I meant.
-Who cares what you meant?
Got it.
Sohta, Yuna,
could you stay where you are for a minute?
Usagi and I will move this round.
And Rei's staying behind.
I want you to go back to D3 next round.
We can lift Rei's lockdown
and get her out.
Afterward, we'll meet up in E3.
It's probably best if we coordinate.
We should stay? Okay, will do.
All right, let's all go to D1 together.
Are you suggesting that because
Arisu said we should move as a group?
-Well, I mean--
-Listen.
We're supposed to be looking for the exit.
If we split up,
we might be able to find it faster.
And besides,
shouldn't we get to know
our futures a little better?
Mr. Matsuyama!
These numbers are incredible.
I think this data is enough to prove
your hypothesis, Mr. Matsuyama.
You did it! You did it!
And you get to sell these bottles
for not one, but 3,000 apiece!
Listen, if you don't like it,
the door is right there.
Only those who are super committed
to becoming entrepreneurs
should come with me.
You. Why are you here?
I'm here to develop my potential!
Very good, that's right!
In that case, your challenge will be
to sell this water for 30,000 a bottle.
You understand
why you need to sell it, don't you?
TRUE AWAKENING
LUCKY WATER
-Excuse me.
-Uh… no thanks.
No, thank you.
It's impossible!
-I need my money back!
-Are you serious?
It's all here in black and white, kid!
Absolutely no returns!
-Excuse me.
-What?
I'm so sorry, sir.
-He's drunk.
-Why are you apologizing, bitch?
-I asked you a question.
-Stop!
-What are you doing?
-Sir! You can't do that!
REJECTION LETTER
-You're hired.
-I am?
We look forward to working with you.
Thank you so much.
-Thank you for being here.
-I really appreciate it.
If it were me, I would put the exit
as far away as I could.
It makes sense for it to be in a corner.
It's a good point.
It might be worth trying once, at least.
All right.
Fine. We'll check the corner rooms
by splitting into two groups.
But also,
Arisu's plan is too good to ignore.
So we'll do both.
Let's you and I go through this door.
That way, I can meet up with Usagi,
and you can try your plan,
and hopefully, you find the exit.
Yeah, all right.
And we'll go this way. To B1.
Sound good?
Uh, yeah.
-We should break up.
-What?
I don't love you anymore.
Did I do something wrong, Ken?
-Did I hurt you?
-Look, Sohta.
I'm sorry.
No, wait! Please, Ken! Please!
Please stay!
We're… well, we're getting married!
We're hoping for your blessing.
Yeah! Of course.
-Yeah!
-Congratulations, sis.
-Thank you.
-Thank you so much.
Whoa, that lake is so freaking big. Look!
-Ah!
-Yuna, come on, it's a dam, not a lake.
That's a dam?
-It's a reservoir created by a dam.
-Come on, Dad!
Well, that makes Yuna half-right!
You see, I'm half-right!
You're pretty excited today.
Well, yeah, duh!
It's been so long since
we've had a vacation, all four of us!
-I love it!
-Me too!
We did everything we could.
I'm so sorry. Your parents
didn't make it out of surgery.
Hold your wristband up to your chosen door
and proceed to the next room.
Sohta, are you sure?
Lockdown.
You are completely useless!
No!
What is this?
1 ROOM
Point deduction confirmed.
Round four. Start.
-Let me roll the dice.
-Mm-hm.
If we wanna get to the corner,
we need to head west.
But only one person can go.
I don't think
it's a good idea to split up.
Let's try B2.
-You did it!
-Uh…
-You got the job!
-Nobu, you got the job?
-Congrats, man!
-That's amazing!
-Great job, dude!
-Nobu.
Nice work!
Did you hear me?
-Yeah.
-You did it! You got the job!
Nobu, you got the job? Congrats, man!
That's amazing! Great job!
Let's stay here
so we can release Rei from lockdown.
I'm still going next door
to the corner room.
And if it's a trap? What then?
I've still got 15 points.
I'll be fine.
Sohta?
I need to know what you rolled.
Sohta? Yuna?
You're in E3 now, right?
Can you move to D3?
We need to get Rei out.
Understood.
Are you sure?
Hey, look.
The green door leads to a corner room.
And maybe that's where the exit is.
I don't know Arisu well,
but if he had to choose between
saving us or Usagi,
no way he's giving up her or his kid.
We need to make sure that's our future.
We need to move forward for Mom and Dad.
Let's go.
Mm-hm.
Here we go.
Rei?
You okay?
I'm going crazy in here! Hurry up, please!
Sohta and his sister
are heading to D3 now.
They'll get you out.
Help me, please!
-Congrats, man!
-Great job!
Hey!
Let's go, come on.
I'll use my points for the door.
To Nobu! The kid
who can sell even the weirdest water!
Drink this and I'll buy one! Go on!
Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug!
Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug!
-Come on man, you got it! Chug!
-Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug!
-More! Get this guy another!
-Keep going!
Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug!
-Why do…
-Nobu's got a drink
-Yeah!
-Got his glass, filled it up!
-Keep going!
-Drink it down, drink it down
Drink it down
No more, please! I'm dying.
He says he doesn't wanna drink!
Drink it down, drink, drink it down
Drink, drink it down
-Drink it down!
-Drink! Drink!
Drink it down, ya gotta drink it down
Ya gotta drink it down
Ya gotta drink, drink
Drink it down, ya gotta drink--
Whoa!
-So gross!
-Crazy!
Sorry, I…
Here!
-Eat shit!
-Eat shit! Eat shit!
Eat shit! Eat shit! Eat shit!
Eat shit! Eat shit…
I'm sorry. I'm leaving!
Hey!
Nobu!
What the hell is going on?
So I guess it's just me now…
6 ROOM
NOBUAKI HIDA: 13
A1 is a minus six point room.
Are you kidding?
It's not the exit.
And there's only one other door,
because it's the corner room!
E5 is a minus four point room.
No…
4 ROOM
SOHTA ITSUKI: 13, YUNA ITSUKI: 14
Damn it.
We'll use my points.
But…
Point deduction confirmed.
It's okay.
Round five. Start.
Rei. Are you out?
No, I'm still trapped!
And I lost another point!
What?
-Come on in!
-Thanks! Here, for you!
-A housewarming gift.
-What is it?
-You shouldn't have!
-Ta-da!
-Sohta? Yuna?
-It's cute.
-Where are you?
-Sohta, you've got great taste!
Oh, this is far from over!
-Sohta? Yuna!
-You are completely useless!
Sohta! Yuna!
Oh, this is far from over!
-You are completely useless!
-That's it.
They made their choice.
Instead of helping each other out,
humans will choose
whatever's best for them.
We're all selfish.
Get out! Just get out!
Wait! Just let me explain! Please!
FROM: MOM
PLEASE JUST CALL ONCE
Oh, this is far from over!
You are completely useless!
Come to think of it… how is Mom?
I wonder how she is.
Oh shit.
Gimme another bag.
And this stuff's even better,
man, trust me.
No freaking way.
Didn't it show me throwing it all away?
No!
Ah, shit!
Help me!
Mom?
What happened?
Your mother suffered
a cerebral hemorrhage.
Mom, no…
Nobu?
Even if she recovers, your mother
will need around-the-clock care.
No, it can't be true.
Usagi.
I'm going to D3 next to get Rei out
of lockdown. I need you to stay put.
Got it.
Ryuji.
Can you hear me? Anything over there?
E1 was a minus one point room, that's all.
-And no exit?
-No.
No… no way…
They're lying!
Huh?
No way…
Impossible.
No way!
Mom, please…
It's all my fault.
I'm… I'm… I'm sorry.
Oh, this is far from over!
D2 UNLOCKED
Huh?
Room D2 has been unlocked.
Rei. You can leave now.
Let's meet up next round.
All right.
Thank you.
4 ROOM
TETSU SHIMAZAKI: 12
B3 is a minus four point room.
Minus four?
Point deduction confirmed.
-Tetsu? Nobu?
-Huh?
Nobu! Are you there?
Hey, don't worry. It's all right.
I still have some points left.
Point deduction confirmed.
Ah! Fuck!
Fuckin' hell!
Hey. Sorry I'm late.
That's okay.
Yukiko?
Hey, Yukiko.
Yeah?
Wanna go to the aquarium
for our anniversary?
Why there?
Because I've never been.
What? Not even as a kid?
Nope.
Sure!
Long time no see. You look good.
Would you look at you?
Wow!
Yeah, I'm working
at a construction company.
I can change.
What? Really?
I swear I can change, Yukiko.
No!
-Welcome.
Welcome.
I've been waiting for you.
Sorry I'm late.
I didn't think you would show up.
What? As if I would miss this!
-Hey.
-Hmm?
Would you like me to build you a house?
For me?
Uh-huh. What kind would you want?
-Hm… a big house.
-Yeah?
-Lots of space.
-Uh-huh.
A3 is a minus eight point room.
Your points total is now zero.
Game over.
I'm done.
Police. We have a warrant
to search the premises.
Found it!
-What are you doing?
-Nothing.
-I'm fine.
-I knew it. I knew you wouldn't change!
Get off me!
You're the one who doesn't trust me!
I did trust you!
I trusted you!
That's why it hurts so much!
Okay. I'm done.
This is my future, I guess. Huh.
It's my fault. I did this.
Nobu?
Why don't you tell me what happened?
Talk to me, please.
Don't come in.
Just tell me. I'm on your side.
No matter what happens, keep living.
I will, Mom.
I promise I will.
-Would you like to say a few words?
-Sure. Thank you.
I've just been appointed here.
My name is Nobuaki Hida.
And my mother's a teacher.
She's the one who inspired
me to be one too.
I'm looking forward to working
with all of you. Thank you.
NOBUAKI HIDA
Hold your wristband up to your chosen door
and proceed to the next room.
I need to go find Tetsu.
Nobu?
Nobu, tell us where you are. Nobu?
1 ROOM
NOBUAKI HIDA: 4
Nobu?
Huh? Yeah. Sachiko?
Are you all right?
I came back.
I'm back in room B1.
But Tetsu and I got separated.
Did you go to the corner room,
A1? That might be the exit.
Yeah. But there was nothing there.
We're in C1.
We're right next to you, okay?
We can meet up with you next round,
so stay where you are.
-Sound good?
-Okay.
Round seven. Start.
Oh no…
Only one each.
We'll have to split up.
Usagi. I'm in D3 now.
I finally met up with Rei.
If there's no exit in the A1 corner room,
then A5 and E5 are
the corners we have left.
The exit is probably in one of those.
But first,
let's look for Sohta and the others.
Got it.
You wanna do another interview?
I've been…
well, compiling my research, actually.
Near-death experiences?
I didn't think my story
was that interesting.
No, of course it is.
Look, I wanna thank you.
Can I buy you dinner?
Um, let me think about that.
Come with me.
We're going to the land of death.
In the final game, I want you to kill her.
Then your work here will be finished.
If you kill Usagi,
I promise to grant your wish.
I promise you will learn
about who governs the afterlife.
about the land of the dead.
Ryuji, are you there?
Ryuji?
-Ryuji!
-Hold your wristband up…
Yeah, I hear you.
-Proceed to the next room.
-We should meet back up.
Make sure we meet up in B4.
Oh! Sweet, thanks! Thanks so much.
-Nobu!
-I'm so happy to see you!
-Are you okay?
-Glad you're all right.
B1 is a minus one point room.
Better use my points here.
We still need to find Tetsu!
Tetsu? Tetsu.
Tetsu? Can you hear us, Tetsu?
Tetsu?
Round eight. Start.
Sohta!
-Oh, wow!
-Wow! It is yummy!
No!
Come to Mommy!
Hold your wristband up to your chosen door
and proceed to the next room.
Yuna.
Sohta!
Yuna?
Yuna!
Sohta! I can't get through.
It won't let me in!
-Sohta!
-Yuna!
-B4 is a minus two point room.
-What?
2 ROOM
Your points total is now zero.
Game over.
Sohta! Sohta! Sohta…
Sohta. No, no…
No, please. Please. I…
I… I…
-Yuna.
-Please… Please, please…
-This was a minus two room.
-No…
What? No, no…
No. No!
-No, no, no…
-I'm so sorry.
No, no…
-I can't keep my promise to you.
-No!
No! Sohta! Open the door!
Someone, please let me in! Please!
No! No!
No! Please don't leave me! Please!
Don't go! Please!
No, no, no, please!
Wait. Don't go, please…
Please! No, please, please…
No, please!
Please… No! No!
-Find happiness. I love you.
-No!
Wait! Please don't go!
Don't leave me! Sohta!
Sohta, don't go! Please!
No! No!
Please, no.
No, no, no…
Please… please…
YUZUHA ARISU: 9, RYUJI MATSUYAMA: 7
NOBUAKI HIDA: 3, SACHIKO MAKINO: 11
Sohta is…
Yeah.
I don't know where Tetsu is, either.
Tetsu?
Tetsu, are you there?
It's because I left him behind.
Behind?
We don't know for sure that he died.
He's just not answering you, that's all.
B4 is a minus two room.
Rei.
I want you to go south.
Take Yuna and head to C5.
Looking at the rounds,
Yuna and her brother
must have passed through E5.
If E5 wasn't the exit, that means
A5 is the only corner room left.
Right.
I'll meet up with everyone in B4,
and then we'll head to A5.
It's the last corner room.
It has to be the exit.
Yuna.
You're gonna have
to go with Rei to the exit.
Yuna. We have to go.
Let's get going. Okay?
Yuna.
Hold your wristband up to your chosen door
and proceed to the next room.
Yuna, come on. Let's go.
Sohta? Sohta!
-Yuna!
You can't be in here!
You have to go with Rei!
-Yuna! Come with me! Hurry!
-Yuna!
-This door's gonna close!
-Get back!
-The player left in this room…
-No!
…will be under lockdown.
B4 is a minus two point room.
Please select the player
whose points will be deducted.
Point deduction confirmed.
B3 is a minus four point room.
We're losing four points.
We should deduct from my pool.
Point deduction confirmed.
Round ten. Start.
Oh no…
Usagi.
How's it going over there?
We're in room B3 right now.
But the numbers on the dice are
making us split up three ways.
On top of that, one of the four of us
will have to stay here.
And we don't know what happened to Tetsu.
He isn't in B4. So that must mean…
That must mean he's in A3.
Tetsu…
If he's in there…
that room might deduct a lot of points.
What are we supposed to do?
One of you will have to go in there.
Another to the confirmed minus two.
Another goes further away from the exit.
And one person…
will have to choose a lockdown.
Hey!
Shut up, you stupid bitch!
Please!
-Stop!
-Get back here! You're worthless!
-Worthless! Had enough?
-Stop!
Come with me.
We're going to the land of death.
Think of something.
Come on, think.
Think.
EXIT