Your Majesty, is something the matter?
It's nothing.
What is it?
We've finally found out
the whereabouts of that big shot.
Big shot?
Shin?
Yes.
He's been missing for the past six months.
It turns out he'd been training
under Ohki.
Training? Under Ohki?
That's right, Your Majesty.
But Ohki put Shin in a stateless zone
and left him there to restore order
on his own.
The last place in the plains
where the lost tribes end up.
The killings continue,
fighting each other over trivial domains.
A crazy lawless zone.
A task to restore order.
Ohki's test for Shin
to become a 100-man commander.
If he's still alive, that is.
He's alive.
He'll come back and appear before us
bigger than ever.
En.
We did it.
Sure did.
We've restored order in the crazy plains!
The Warring States Period.
Seven states were at war
on the great continent for 500 years.
After his first battle at Dakan Plains,
Shin asked Ohki to train him
so he could become a great general.
In response, Ohki gave Shin
an ordeal to overcome.
A test to restore order in the plains
where there was endless tribal conflict.
Shin backed up the weakest tribe.
Gaining their trust, his troops
finally restored order in the plains.
Now that Shin was ready,
Ohki promised to take him in for training.
At that very moment,
near the border of Qin,
a bigger threat than the Battle
of Dakan Plains was approaching.
244 B.C.
QIN STATE, NORTHWESTERN REGION
BORDER TOWN, KANSUI
Dad, look.
Lots of flags.
Enemies.
They're enemies.
The Zhao Army is here!
Hold on tight.
QIN STATE, KING'S CAPITAL, XIANYANG
Zhao broke into our state?
Kansui, the northeastern border town.
There are at least 100,000 men.
So many?
This is bad.
General Hyoko is away
with his army on an expedition to Han.
No troops or generals nearby.
Bring Army Commander Shoheikun here.
But, Your Majesty, if we do,
Ryofui and his men will take advantage.
No time for arguments.
It's Zhao with a murderous grudge
against us after the Chohei Massacre.
THE COUNCIL ROOM
INSIDE THE ROYAL PALACE
Fifty thousand have surrounded Kansui.
Fifty thousand more are following.
Of all states,
Zhao holds the biggest grudge.
Grudge?
Ten, don't you know about
the Chohei Massacre?
What's that?
STRATEGIST CANDIDATE
AND AIDE OF SHOHEIKUN, MOKI
Hakuki, one of the Six Great Generals,
won the Battle of Chohei 16 years ago.
The Zhao troops surrendered.
But General Hakuki massacred them
by burying them alive.
Four hundred thousand men.
Four hundred thousand?
Then how come we let Zhao
break in so easily?
Up until now,
we weren't aware of
any generals who could lead big armies.
Generals?
With no general to lead his men,
there would be no armies.
Like our Six Great Generals,
Zhao once had the Three Great Heavens
but not anymore.
So, how?
I guess
it means a new general has appeared.
How smooth, Fuki.
You've brought them down already.
CHOSO ARMY'S
ADJUTANT COMMANDER OF ZHAO, FUKI
Let me take the rest.
Do as you please.
Mangoku.
CHOSO ARMY'S
ADJUTANT COMMANDER OF ZHAO, MANGOKU
I shall repay you, Qin!
For what you did to
my people of 400,000 in Chohei.
I am at your service.
Chancellor Ryofui has arrived.
How surprising it is
to see Zhao making a move.
Times are urgent,
but there is a disorder of precedence.
It'll bring distortion to the battlefield.
Shobunkun.
You're in my place.
Work together now.
Step down.
Urgent message!
Kansui Castle has been taken!
Kansui.
The lord of the castle and its people
were beheaded and left in a blood pool.
Recruit soldiers and form an army at once.
An emergency call is pretty unusual.
There's trouble somewhere.
TERRITORY OF QIN STATE, JOTO VILLAGE
Good thing we were here,
the soldiers of the Battle of Dakan.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Stop your whining.
Guys, let's get going.
Bito.
Here.
Wow! A good luck charm.
Come back safely.
I will.
Bihei, your brother beat you to it.
Shut up.
Bihei.
Huh?
Tohbi.
Please come back home safely.
Sure.
I'll make it back bigger than ever.
The Zhao Army is now headed towards Bayo.
How many are in Bayo?
Bayo is a large castle.
There must be approximately
150,000 people altogether.
Your Majesty,
Bayo is the key to our front line.
If it falls to the Zhao Army,
they will penetrate deep into our state.
If both Kansui and Bayo fall,
they'll come straight here to Xianyang.
What are our strategists doing?
Still no word from the Council Room?
Hundred thousand Zhao Army.
80,000 Qin Army on their way to Bayo.
We're short of 20,000 men.
Won't that be a problem?
It won't matter as much.
I beg to differ.
Their military force is greater.
If the careful King of Zhao made a move,
he must be confident.
At least 100,000 of these men
are most likely to be well trained
while our 80,000 men we gathered up
worked as peasants until yesterday.
A big difference in power.
It all depends on the leader
of the Qin Army.
Only the General's ability
can compensate for the difference.
Now that all our generals are away,
it's a blessing in disguise that
you stayed here in Xianyang, Mobu.
Leave it to me.
Your Majesty, please appoint Mobu
as commander-in-chief of Qin.
Please do not.
Do I hear a noise from the rear,
Shobunkun?
It's not wise to make Mobu
the commander-in-chief.
Want to get killed?
Stop, Mobu.
Shobunkun has been a true warrior
since the reign of King Sho.
He's the most experienced here.
Shobunkun.
Share with us your ideas.
There are two kinds of power in warfare.
The offensive
and the defensive.
I take it that Mobu specializes
in offensive skills.
When it comes to the offensive,
Mobu may be the best man in Qin.
But…
I'm afraid I must say
he lacks defensive skills.
This battle is crucial
to the survival of Qin.
Our fate cannot be in your hands.
Old man.
Are those your last words?
Hold your horses, Mobu.
He has a point there.
But Shobunkun.
Who else in our state of Qin
can save us from this crisis?
There's one man
who's been away from battle,
resting his wings.
Offensive and defensive.
The best warrior of Qin
who has a combination of both.
The only man.
No.
It can't be.
It's been a while
since things have gotten lively here.
Gentlemen.
How have you been?
Shin.
What is it, Mobu?
You're interrupting the discussion.
Buzz off.
But I was summoned here
to participate in the discussion.
Bullshit.
Who in the world would summon you?
I did.
What for?
To offer him the top position.
General Ohki as our commander-in-chief?
Please explain, Shoheikun.
I had already made a request
to General Ohki.
But receiving no answer, I asked Mobu.
Two to choose from.
Which will be the commander-in-chief?
General Ohki, of course.
Expect me to step down so easily?
Shoheikun.
I am your army leader.
My decision will not be overturned.
General Ohki is our commander-in-chief.
I will not recognize
a relic of the past like you.
That's too bad because
I recognize your abilities
to a certain degree.
Now, gentlemen, would you mind
stepping out for a moment?
Why is that?
You are now the center of the discussion.
First, I must be appointed
as commander-in-chief by the King himself.
Shall we go, Chancellor?
What is it, Ohki?
Why clear the room just to speak to me?
King Sei.
Your great-grandfather, King Sho,
was a great king.
I'm aware of that.
What's unfortunate
is that you haven't had the chance
to see him for yourself.
Because you had been taken hostage
by Zhao up until seven years ago.
Hostage?
I suspect
no king has ever experienced
such pain and hatred as you.
Ohki.
What's your point?
There's something I'd like to confirm.
The reason why
you wish to unify all of China.
I made a promise.
A promise?
That's right.
A promise to someone.
My father, being of royal blood,
was taken hostage by the Zhao
enemy state in exchange for a truce.
That was when I was born.
With Ryofui's help,
my father escaped back to Qin
while I was left to rot
in the gutters of Kantan.
ZHAO STATE, KING'S CAPITAL, KANTAN
SEVEN YEARS AGO
After the Chohei Massacre,
all the anger was directed at me,
Qin's royal blood.
While I was in Kantan,
I became the target of violence
from every man and woman in the city.
You thief!
Until the day I met her.
Stop!
That was the first time
anyone had ever saved me.
Her name was Shika,
a black-market merchant.
Black-market merchant?
Since my father escaped to Qin,
I was left to starve.
I lived my life like a slave.
But one day,
my world suddenly turned around.
King Sho passed
and your father was to become king.
Which meant that you were
the next heir to the throne.
That's why they had to
bring me back to Qin at all costs,
and a black-market merchant was hired.
They're geniuses when it comes to
smuggling goods to other states.
I see.
But entrusting an important heir
to a black-market merchant
is a risky plan, don't you think?
There was no time.
The King of Zhao knew
if I were to become king,
that would mean trouble to him.
I had to escape
before he had his men kill me.
Why did a black-market merchant agree
to take on such a perilous mission?
I know. It's a wonder.
You have angry eyes.
Don't you like the moon?
I didn't like the moon.
I hated it.
When you've hit rock bottom,
it looks brighter than usual.
As if it's laughing at you.
That made me angry.
But someone told me
that wasn't true at all.
My father, who found and raised me…
he would say,
"When the moon looks brighter than usual,
it's trying to cheer you up
so you won't be discouraged."
Shika, I must thank you for two things.
For saving me and telling me
the secret about the moon.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I've turned down the job.
No need to risk our lives
for a filthy kid.
Boss! I hope you're not having
second thoughts.
I'm not having second thoughts.
My mind is set.
You again.
No.
Go away!
Wait, Your Highness!
We have come for you.
We apologize for
the hardships we've caused.
It's time to return to Qin.
Please come with us.
Qin?
King Sho has passed
and your father is the crown prince.
You are now the heir to the throne.
Please wait. Now's our chance to escape!
No way!
You won't make it out of the city.
Bastard, you just turned us down.
We've decided to take the job.
I, the notorious Shika,
will help His Highness go back to Qin.
Shika bribed the guards at each checkpoint
and laid the groundwork.
Where the guards were familiar
with Shika, I hid inside the load.
She was smart with the guards.
Next!
Shika.
Who's the stranger?
Never seen his face before.
We're shorthanded,
so I hired him at the village.
Turns out he's no use.
Can I leave him here?
No, you can't! Go!
We passed the third checkpoint.
There was just one more to go.
He hasn't been eating.
If you don't eat,
you won't make it to Qin.
Why would you risk your life
to save a man like me?
Amon and I were war orphans.
We were about to starve to death
when a black-market merchant saved us.
That's the man I call father,
who told me the secret about the moon.
Amon and I,
we'll never forget the warmth
of his hands that reached out to us.
Unfortunately, he died
when I was ten years old.
I cried and told him I hadn't repaid him.
He smiled on his deathbed and said,
"Repay by giving kindness
to the next person in need."
That's why I am reaching out to you now.
Fine. Good to go!
Thanks a lot.
That was our last gate.
Qin's straight ahead of us.
Thanks, Shika.
Thank me when we've finished
delivering him safely.
What is this?
Just testing.
Didn't make a sound.
Your Highness!
Can't move. Pull it out.
How courageous of you
to have endured the pain.
Here.
How could he stay so calm?
We're almost there.
We should be safe now.
Enjoy your rich life, future king.
Who's going to be king?
What is it?
You'll never be king.
-Your Highness!
-We have no time for this.
Leave it to me.
Who's going to be king?
You were abandoned by your parents.
There's not a soul who needs you.
Stop.
There's no place for you in Qin.
Besides,
no one wants a broken king.
Your Highness!
Wait.
What's the matter? You're almost home.
Go away!
Your Highness!
I can't go back.
There's a reason I can't.
Don't.
I don't feel pain.
Not just that.
There's no taste, no smell.
I don't feel hot or cold at all.
That can't be.
I'm broken.
That's why
I'm not fit to be king.
After beatings
and receiving so much hatred,
I've become numb.
I wanted to be king.
A king to guide my people.
You'll be king.
I'll help you.
If you don't feel pain,
I'll feel it for you.
Taste.
Smell. Everything.
But don't worry.
You're not numb at all.
That night when we saw the moon,
you felt its brightness.
I'll be with you.
Together,
we shall go back to Qin.
Let's go.
Hey, what's up with that kid?
Don't worry. He's fine now.
A signal fire!
They're coming after us.
Hurry. Ditch our things.
They're right behind us!
Still far from our rendezvous point.
Your Highness! Keep your head down.
Watch out!
Shika!
Behind the shield!
Enemy from the side.
Still four hours away from our rendezvous.
Damn it, we're doomed!
Don't give up, Amon!
We have arrows and a horse that's running.
Never say die!
Shika's right.
Our soldiers may be coming for us.
Focus on getting closer to Qin!
That's the spirit.
I see you've truly awoken.
Thanks to you.
There's Eisei! Kill him!
Your Highness! Forgive me!
Doken!
Your Highness.
A cloud of dust ahead. Our soldiers!
We're almost there!
Idiot! You stay down!
I can't!
-Down!
-Amon!
Forgive me.
It's okay. It's Shika's decision.
But let me say this. You go back to Qin.
Go back
and become a real king!
Amon.
Amon!
Hold the reins, please.
My hand.
Hurry!
Quick. There are more coming!
Got it.
Shika, are you alright?
Don't look back!
Focus or our cart will tip over.
I'm not done yet!
Shika!
Don't look!
Leave her. Kill Eisei!
I won't let you!
Never!
Qin's cavalry is here!
Your Highness!
Take him down!
We made it, Shika!
Shika!
Shika.
Wake up!
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
Thanks to you all, I can go back to Qin.
Thanks to you all,
I can become king.
You were born under an unlucky star
and were made to walk the path
no other royalty would ever tread.
No future king
has ever experienced such pain.
No one.
That's why
I know…
you'll be the greatest king ever.
Yes.
I definitely will.
I promise.
Your Highness.
I'm glad.
Free of your inner demons.
Your eyes.
They're so beautiful.
Shika.
No, Shika.
Shika!
That was my first promise.
Not only for Shika
but for those who died protecting me,
I must put an end to this war-torn era.
This is why
I am on a journey
that no one's dared to go on.
Will you kill me?
In that case,
I won't die without a fight.
To honor those who died protecting me.
Including Hyo.
Ethnic groups can only coexist
after blood has been shed.
Years of discrimination
and resentment can't be erased.
Yotanwa.
Join me on a journey.
A journey that no one's dared to go on.
At the end, there'll be light.
A unified China?
Do you think the other states
will agree with your idea?
If they don't, I'll have to use force.
I will be
the first emperor to unify our world.
I now see how determined you are.
King Eisei.
Come out, Shin.
Shin, my boy.
Call everyone back.
Commence the appointment ceremony.
Sure thing.
Actually,
I have something important
to convey to you.
What is it?
A message from King Sho
to you, King Eisei.
From King Sho?
The Zhao Army has already invaded Kansui.
Its people were massacred,
the place destroyed.
And now, our key defensive front, Bayo,
is under attack.
If they get past Bayo,
this bloodbath will spread
all over our state.
Qin's fate lies in your hands!
General Ohki.
I appoint you as our commander-in-chief.
Save Bayo
and demolish the Zhao Army
once and for all.
I, Ohki,
am at your service.
THE QIN ARMY'S CAMPSITE
45 KM SOUTHWEST OF BAYO
-They're all losers.
-Who needs them?
Form a "Go"! Squad Leaders assemble.
-Hey, Ryusen.
-Let’s team up.
No, pick me.
Oh no!
The Go making's begun.
Where are you, Shin?
Enough men for a 100-man unit.
Shin! You're supposed to be
our 100-man commander.
Our 100-man commander has arrived!
Hey!
You're all here.
Shin!
Hairo.
Don't care if they're roughnecks.
Gather up some tough ones.
Leave it to me.
Yeah, I think I see the chemistry here.
Twenty teams of Go roughnecks.
You guys are my commemorable
first 100-man unit.
That kid is our commander?
Bro, I'll bet you can beat him.
We don't belong to any other large units.
But we're a special 100-man unit
under General Ohki.
Under General Ohki?
I have no idea what we are
or what we're supposed to do.
All I can say is this.
If our general made us independent,
we'll be posted to a major battlefield.
We may even be ordered
to make a surprise attack.
Then we'll score big time
and make military exploits.
Most of us survived
the Battle of Dakan Plains.
We can confront any enemy
if we stick together.
Tomorrow, we will finally reach Bayo.
You sons of bitches!
We'll take down the Zhao Army
and score big time!
Is he the Shin we know?
He's amazing.
The kid grew up in six months.
I've been permitted
to have two vice commanders.
Vice Commander En.
Let's kick ass!
Who's the other?
That person's not here yet.
There she comes.
Yes!
Our reliable companion.
We've missed you.
Welcome back, Kyokai.
That's what I mean.
Alright!
My 100-man unit is complete!
I'll get you!
Your moves are better.
Right?
Give it back.
Show me your move.
That thing you did
when we were surrounded.
To-on, tan-tan
You're stupid after all.
In ancient times,
priestesses would do a sword dance
to calm the raging gods.
The Shiyu turned this into
a killing method.
They summon the gods
and in their intoxication,
they would kill while dancing.
This is the "Priestess Dance"
of the Shiyu.
What kind of gods do they summon?
No idea.
It's so unfair!
How come you guys get help from a god?
We're not the only ones.
Some masters of martial arts
can do the same
without knowing it.
But what's more terrifying
are those who host a god within.
Within?
That's right.
We called them
Bushin "War God".
"Bushin"?
Why did you decide to participate, Ohki?
Because of King Eisei's past story.
I too, must come face to face
with my past.
What do you mean?
I'm talking about Bayo.
I see.
I remember now.
Bayo was the castle
you, Kyo, and I had once taken
from the state of Zhao.
That's why
you cannot give up the land
where Kyo fell.
But who in the world was that brute
that defeated Kyo?
He seemed like "war" in disguise.
His name was Hoken.
No, don't go there. He's already dead.
Let us put the incident behind us.
For good.
BAYO CASTLE
Peasant soldiers, don't fall behind!
Deserters?
Yeah.
No deserters from our unit,
but rumor has it there are many elsewhere.
It was a last-minute call
and most of them are rookie soldiers.
The Zhao Army is invincible.
Some say Bayo is under siege
and they're waiting for us
to fall into their ambush.
There'll be more deserters
as we approach the battlefield.
Cowards everywhere.
There'd better be none in our unit!
Wimps!
Say that again.
Never heard of kid commanders.
No need to get excited.
Who do they think they are?
Ignore them.
They're grouchy,
but you can trust their skills.
What we need to think about is
whether we can fight in this situation.
This isn't good, Commander Shin.
Our men's morale is getting low.
Damn.
Our cavalry.
General Ohki.
-It's him.
-General Ohki.
All armies…
forward.
He's awesome.
The greatest general on Earth!
Qin's cavalry!
All armies, halt!
They're here.
It's the Qin Army!
-Defensive line formation.
-Yes, sir!
They're changing formation.
Advance to the right!
Huh?
Moving away from Bayo?
They're moving to the side.
Given up their castle.
They're trying to lure us away.
Choso.
Well done, Fuki and Mangoku.
CHOSO ARMY'S STRATEGIST OF ZHAO, CHOSO
They feared our powerful cavalry
and avoided battle in the plains.
South from here is Kan Plains,
where our mobility will be obstructed.
If we stay and focus on Bayo, it will mean
turning our backs to Ohki.
That's not very wise.
No choice but to tag along.
We knew he'd choose Kan Plains
as our battlefield.
KAN PLAINS
15 KM SOUTH OF BAYO
Master Shoheikun predicts
it'll be this area.
He always tells us
the best way to learn
is to see and know the battlefield.
That's why I come here discreetly
and see for myself.
Ten.
You should see it, too.
See what real war is like.
The Zhao Army has followed us here.
Yes, they have. They're all pumped up.
Very pumped up?
Very pumped up.
-Very, very pumped up?
-Very, very pumped up.
-Very, very--
-My Lord.
We must get in position.
I wish you luck.
Yes, sir!
Damn! We're not at the front.
Both finished positioning.
The main attack from Zhao
will be by Mangoku's 40,000 army.
Their aim is to penetrate through
our side.
KANOH - MANGOKU
Meanwhile, our 30,000 right army
is on guard,
but Mangoku likes to push deep
into his opponent's camp.
A strategist known for "suicide attacks".
He'll come for our side,
closer to the central army.
On the other hand, we have
our 10,000 left army led by Kanoh.
KANOH
Just 10,000?
Yes, because it's General Ohki's
private army.
Six thousand of Ohki's men led by Kanoh,
together with 4,000 of Shobunkun's.
OHKI ARMY'S
LEADER OF THE LEFT ARMY ATTACK UNIT, KANOH
Our left army is an elite mercenary unit.
THE 1000-MAN COMMANDERS OF QIN
HEKI - SHOKAKU
On the other hand,
Fuki leads an army of 20,000.
Fuki has an eye for tactics
and the equal intellect of a strategist.
He can push and pull
and deploy formations accordingly.
He won't let us come close easily.
Because of the high hills
on the left side of the battlefield,
his army looks isolated.
It'll be easy to attack but hard to target
the central army from the side.
So, the outcome of this battle
depends on the right army, Moki?
Yes, for the Zhao Army.
But Qin's main force is the central army.
Mobu's 20,000 men with Ohki's 20,000
make 40,000.
While Zhao's central army consists of
Choso's 40,000 men.
Judging from his ability,
Choso must be the commander-in-chief.
The same number of men
in both central armies.
Yes, in numbers.
But most of Qin's men
are peasant soldiers.
The difference in military forces
won't matter.
It'll be the General's capability.
Their ability will decide the day.
Charge!
-They're off.
-Our central army.
Show us what you've got, Mobu.
Shield wall!
He's vicious.
No command for us yet.
Can't wait to get in there.
Zhao's right army!
Mangoku Army has charged.
We exceed in power and numbers.
They'll lose their men in vain
if they force their way in.
Now what will you do, Ohki?
That's our left army!
Heki.
Their left army has made a move.
Their left, too?
They must be crazy
to charge at Fuki head-on.
Ohki.
What are you up to?
Their left army is moving in.
They're outnumbered.
Go with the plan.
Yes, sir.
Forward!
They're daunted by us.
Thanks to General Ohki,
their morale is boosting.
Central and right are competing.
Come on!
Call us in.
Shin, my boy.
General Ohki!
I will give you a mission.
Show me what you've learned.
Sure. Leave it to me!
No "Yes, sir"?
As you can see,
10,000 men of our left army
have initiated an attack on
the 20,000 Zhao Army led by Fuki.
This will be
the most important battle
at this early stage.
With all due respect,
our left army doesn't have
any terrain advantage out there.
To fight efficiently,
it's standard tactics
to take away areas
that hold terrain advantage.
I know.
We made sacrifices to take
the enemy's hill at Dakan.
But there's a better way
than taking advantageous locations.
To kill competent enemy generals
one by one.
Fuki, who is now leading
his 20,000 right army,
is talented in warfare analysis.
As the battle reaches its climax,
generals like him will become
like thorns in our sides.
That is why
Fuki must be the first to go.
However, Fuki is a great warrior
and above all,
he has twice as many men as our left army.
It will not be easy.
So,
this is where Shin's 100-man unit
comes in.
Your unit will charge from the side
where both armies are fighting
and amidst the confusion,
you will take Fuki's head.
But that's impossible, sir!
It'll be a suicide mission.
What do you say, Shin?
Do you agree with En?
There's one thing I noticed
while training in the plains.
Hundred men in a huge army
are like tiny beans.
Still, a tiny bean
has a strength of its own.
It can slip through gaps.
Together, they're unbreakable.
If our 100-man unit
stick together and fight,
we can take down a 20,000-man commander.
Our 100-man special unit
will take on the mission.
You seem to have learned
a thing or two, Shin, my boy.
Now, here's your reward.
I will grant you a name for your unit.
A name?
As of now, you will call your unit…
Hishin Unit.
Fly like an arrow
and thrust deep into enemy headquarters.
This battle is crucial.
No failure is to be tolerated.
I'll be counting on you.
Commander Shin of the Hishin Unit.
What is it?
I see a line of men between
the left and central armies.
Great eye-sight.
No, it can't be!
Their headquarters is beyond that cliff.
Look.
The Qin Army is pressing hard!
Alright.
Move back the front line.
The left and right armies in position!
Yes, sir!
Retreat!
Zhao Army, retreat!
Back off!
They're retreating.
We were pressing hard,
but there wasn't much of a resistance.
Go after them!
Get them!
Hold it! Hold your positions!
Heki Unit, halt!
Our left army seems to be in danger.
They're being lured.
Half of our left's vigor
is driven by ability.
The other half
is a trap of Fuki's.
Flank their left army from both sides.
Kill them all.
Heki! We're surrounded from both sides.
Archers, shoot!
It's a trap!
There's no time for unnecessary combat.
Run straight to the general
in column formation.
But the moment we break in,
they'll put up their defenses.
There's also a cliff
in front of their headquarters.
When we get past this,
our army will move in.
Then we'll attack Fuki from the side.
To open up a breach, we need power.
Hairo's friend, Ryusen.
Yeah, he's twice as strong as I am.
Right, Ryusen?
Hey, Ryusen, you don't look so good.
No kidding.
You're scared.
I don't blame him.
He told me his first child
was born last month.
That goes for us all.
We've all got someone waiting.
Back to our topic.
Our Hishin Unit is an arrow.
We can fly and take down our enemy
or we'll get smashed to pieces and die.
If we fail, all the men
in the left army will die.
Then everyone waiting for us
back home will die, too.
If we lose this war,
the Zhao Army will come rushing in.
Then, like the people of Kansui,
every man, woman, and kid will be
killed and left in a pool of blood.
Ryusen.
The same will happen to your kid.
That's the kind of war it is.
Let's go, Commander.
Together, we'll score a victory.
Now!
Enemy attack!
There!
Ryusen!
-Moron, don't go alone!
-Does he have a death wish?
Hishin Unit!
Charge!
We're in!
Shin!
Enemy attack!
Enemy attack from the left!
The left?
Which unit?
We don't know.
Make way! Urgent message!
Hundred enemy troops from the left.
They've reached our second line.
All this way with just 100?
They seem to be acting solo.
What's going on?
I see.
I get it now.
So, you're after my head.
Interesting.
Well then, let's see you try, Ohki.
Go up that cliff!
Shin of the Hishin Unit.
Time for your ordeal.
Enemies!
Can't get any closer!
There's more. Throw them off!
There's more gathered down there.
Damn.
No good. We're surrounded.
Commander Shin.
Let's split.
Split?
We'll only run out of strength and die.
We should send out a crack team instead.
But the rest of you will die.
Our aim is to behead Fuki.
Then it'll be our victory.
We can stall the enemy here
while you go up the cliff.
I'd gladly stay behind for our victory.
Me, too.
Me, too. Someone has to stay
and lead our unit.
I'll stay behind.
Guys.
We need to win, right?
When you break through, we'll disengage.
Leave these guys to me and En.
Yugi.
Hurry, Commander Shin.
En, we'll go,
but survive this no matter what.
Of course.
We'll all survive.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Yugi.
I'll see you later.
Sure. Take Fuki's head for us.
We will.
Let's go.
-Yeah!
They've split the unit.
En and Yugi are waiting.
Hang in there, you sons of bitches!
What? A detached force?
Take out the leader!
Shin!
No, you won't!
Stop everyone!
Crush them!
Bring it!
Reporting!
Some from the enemy unit
are approaching the clifftop.
Our garrisons?
They're at battle.
They're just peasant soldiers.
An easy 100-man unit. Wipe them out!
Enemies!
I see him.
No way we're going to get in.
Even in small numbers,
they've become unstoppable.
I must say I admire Fuki's skill
at destroying half of Qin's left army.
But he paid the price
by letting the Hishin Unit in deep.
Fuki excels in long-distance combat
but not in short distance combat.
For the Hishin Unit,
the real battle is yet to come.
Shin, you're the one who said
we're like an arrow.
Right.
Now's the time to show them
that our Hishin Unit is no ordinary arrow!
Sure is!
You're kidding.
Let's go then!
You're crazy.
Crazy!
What's the commotion?
I'll cover you.
Run like mad and go take Fuki's head!
Go, Shin!
Be careful!
The general's guards are tough.
I know.
Don't let them near our headquarters!
Run!
We broke through!
Bodyguards, line formation!
From the side!
Bro!
Go, Shin!
Go!
Bihei! Bito!
Heki!
You're finished.
Central army, forward!
Their central army is moving.
We're done!
Hang in there!
-Go, Shin!
-Sure!
Go!
Damn, the closer I get,
the tougher they get.
Fuki!
I'll cover you.
A split second.
That's all I need.
Can't hold them back.
These guards won't budge!
Come on!
We're at our limits!
Dammit!
We can close in and finish them off.
Stop wasting time
on those peasant soldiers!
This is the first time I've ever
let an enemy come this close.
Could such a small unit
have come all this way here by luck?
Break into headquarters?
My plan was to surround
Qin's left army and destroy them.
But if I hadn't moved both wings,
they couldn't have come this far.
Impossible!
Was I led into moving both wings?
If their army of 10,000 were to come
charging at our 20,000,
I would move both wings to surround them.
Is that why Ohki made his left army
come at us?
The advance of that small unit
was no coincidence.
I'd been caught in Ohki's scheme
from the very start!
You're a genius manipulating
the battlefield without leading it.
That's because, surprisingly,
I don't dislike it.
Long-distance combat, that is.
Kyokai!
Retreat.
Sir?
Retreat!
Pull back!
Fuki! Too late for that!
There's no getting away.
General Fuki.
Shin, go!
There goes our Lord's arrow!
I got him.
Hey, kid.
Did our Lord name your unit?
Hishin Unit.
Zhao General Fuki's head
has been taken by Shin of the Hishin Unit!
Zhao General Fuki's head has been
taken by Shin of the Hishin Unit!
Well done, Shin of the Hishin Unit.
You're a real commander now.
Shin.
Qin's flag is hoisted on enemy camp.
Their general's down.
Shin! You did it!
Yes!
General Fuki is killed!
Our right army is defeated.
Not yet.
Our battle isn't over.
There's a man
who'll lead us to our victory.
All armies! Move our headquarters.
Which way?
Backward.
They're retreating.
This isn't good.
They're headed to the mountains,
where they can ambush us,
unlike in the plains.
The Zhao Army has fled.
Who are you?
Lord Riboku, our seat has been taken.
No need to be alarmed.
We've come to watch.
Would you allow us to join you?
Well, well.
They've retreated too easily.
Toh.
Was there another strategist
besides Choso?
No, My Lord. Not that I recall.
Something smells fishy.
Is it a trap?
We'll let this one go.
Nevertheless,
we must find out
who this mystery commander is.
For now, we shall move along with them.
Let's get them.
Our lord will decide.
We'll go tomorrow.
We'll leave at sunrise.
One thing.
You must promise me this.
The farthest you can go
is up to where you see Zhao's
former headquarters mountaintop.
All of you.
-Never ever break this promise.
-Understood, sir!
Our Hishin Unit…
Lost 31 men.
What's with the glum face?
Smile for them.
They'd be happier that way.
Right.
He's right.
General Ohki!
Shin, my boy.
Do you know why I gave your unit a name?
So it can be called?
So people can remember
our allies as well as our enemies.
Our enemies?
Every soldier in the Zhao Army
should know by now
that the one who killed Fuki
was Shin of the Hishin Unit.
But that's not all.
Fuki was a renowned general.
Since you defeated him,
your name will spread across all of China.
Though,
it'll only take a while
until everyone forgets you.
But if my name and our unit's name
come up every time…
then,
the name will be known
across all of China.
Yeah!
Let's make it happen!
Well done, all of you. I commend you.
Let me explain for those
who missed what happened.
Do Fuki.
Not again.
Give me a break.
Enough. I'll ask Shin.
Yeah, you drunkard.
Sit down, will you?
Don't you want to see it?
You missed it.
Cut it out.
You're really something.
Bito.
A year ago, you were
the stupidest slave in our village.
Now, you're a 100-man commander
and took the head of our enemy.
I'm not stupid.
When we get home, you'll be a hero.
Yeah, everyone in our Hishin Unit
will be heroes.
Right. Us too?
Absolutely.
What is it?
We're tired of seeing it.
Okay, enough is enough.
What, Bihei?
Who the hell are you?
Which unit?
Please stop.
Don't ignore us.
Enemy attack! Sound the alarm!
We found out who Zhao's
commander-in-chief is.
Who is it?
A man called Hoken.
Hoken? Who is he, Shoheikun?
I've never heard of him.
No, it can't be.
Impossible.
What is it, Shobunkun?
What do you know?
Hoken is the name of the man
who killed the Great General Kyo
nine years ago.
However,
he was supposed to have been slain
by Ohki.
What do you mean?
Didn't Kyo, one of Qin's
Six Great Generals, die from an illness?
Back then,
Kyo had become a symbolic figure
of our Six Great Generals.
But then,
she was suddenly killed by an unknown man.
We couldn't admit it.
So, Ohki and I decided
to have Kyo die of an illness.
Shobunkun.
You will pay for twisting the facts.
But first, you must tell us
what kind of man Hoken is.
He is
not the kind of warrior who leads men.
He is a complete individual.
Or rather, the man is
a result of a horrifyingly pure
"art of war".
This guy's dangerous. Be careful!
I'll stop him.
Run!
-Yugi.
-Bro!
Yukaku!
This can't be happening.
You bastard!
Stop! He's no match for you.
Shut up!
Perhaps Ohki had known from the beginning.
That's why he took the post
of commander-in-chief.
But then why would Hoken
become the commander of Zhao now?
Could it be?
Hoken has come to destroy Ohki.
Most likely, Your Majesty.
This is a fateful battle
that goes back nine years.
A war of vengeance.
-Shin!
-Commander!
He dodged Kyokai's blow!
Who the hell are you?
I am Hoken, Bushin "War God".
"Bushin"?
Defeating an invincible equestrian tribe
one-sidedly?
Looks like there's quite a monster
lurking around
in this state of Zhao.
ORIGINAL STORY BY YASUHISA HARA