PREVIOUSLY
Would you like to play karuta with us?
At last. At last we have
five members, Miss Oe!
Now we can play team games.
Let's all go to Omi Shrine!
What was that all about?
When a game begins, I just get all dizzy.
Like the yips?
I'm thinking I could act as manager.
FALL STUDY CAMP
2–4 NOVEMBER
There's a study camp
over the long weekend in November.
So you can all improve even more,
I'm planning a karuta training camp
for the long weekend this fall.
KARUTA CLUB TRAINING CAMP
2–4 NOVEMBER
What the hell?!
Man, I'm hungry.
After all those snacks you ate?
-What's this?
-Gotta have fireworks at training camp!
I've got rockets, and…
Is this school that's hosting us
a big deal, then?
Yeah. It's a powerhouse
rivalling the champions, Mizusawa.
They're always vying for the top ranks.
Their karuta club may well have
the longest history in Tokyo.
I'm sure there'll be plenty
for you to learn from them.
Right.
How much longer do we have to walk?
It's just past this shrine.
Let's go say hello to the god first.
Yes, Miss Oe.
Are you okay?
Thank you.
I always tell you to say
if you're frazzled.
No, no.
If I can't play karuta,
I mustn't hassle you in any other way.
Why the vegetables?
That's a secret.
What was that?
A bird?
Deep in the mountains
Parting red leaves underfoot
Crying, a deer's voice
Imparts on me the sorrow
That always comes with autumn
That's right, Mr. Okuyama.
So that was a deer just now?
-Is that what deer sound like?
-Yes.
HOKUOH HIGH SCHOOL
We're finally here.
It really does look the part
for boys' boarding school dorms.
Listen up, guys.
For the next three days,
it'll be nothing but learning.
Let's steal whatever we can!
Okay, say it with me.
Let's go, Umezono!
-Come on.
-What's it like inside?
Yeah.
Huh?
Where were you all?
Hey.
Say it with me!
CHIHAYAFURU: FULL CIRCLE
Hello?
POEM FOUR:
DEEP IN THE MOUNTAINS
Oh?
Is nobody here?
Louder!
Yes, sir!
Seventy-five!
HOKUOH
Kinashi!
-Long time no see, Miss Oe.
-It's been a while.
Thank you for letting us join you.
Umezono in the house, guys!
Fall in!
Greeting!
Welcome to Hokuoh High School
Competitive Karuta Club!
Thank you.
Sho Okuyama, club president.
Going for hill sprints, Mr. Lanky.
All right. Off you go.
-Hokuoh!
-Off you go.
What about introductions?
Now, you guys from Umezono
aren't to waste a second either.
Get changed in there.
Yes, sir.
-On the double!
-Yes, sir!
I'd expect no less of Hokuoh!
You've taken it to the next level.
We alumni take it in turns to supervise.
The spirit of Hokuoh lives forever!
Miss Oe?
The endurance to fight to the end!
The explosiveness to react!
Let's beat three seconds! Three!
The core strength to reach the cards.
Near Mount Arima
As Ina's bamboo grass fields
Rustle in the breeze
Shall I ever forget you?
I do not believe I will
Five sets of sweeping,
focusing on your abs.
And this will be the year
we shut our enemies at Mizusawa up!
Team games right after this.
-Yes, sir!
-What?
No break?
-It makes our training look like a joke.
-Let's rest.
This is the new Umezono's first team game.
There's something nice about that.
You call it a team game,
but isn't it basically
just four singles games?
It's basically just singles games,
you say?
Pardon?
It seems to me
that you don't understand team games.
Are you sure about him reading?
Yes.
He's a good reader.
Well, it works in our favor,
but it's the best of five to win it.
Play as normal.
So you'd stand a better chance
with five players.
To tell you the truth, there's
a particular reason he can't play.
Now please begin.
Let's have a good game.
In Naniwa Bay
Behold how the flower blooms
After winter's sleep
And now, with spring's arrival
It reveals its full glory
-Let's go, Hokuoh!
-Right!
What was that?
They're so loud.
And now, with spring's arrival
It reveals its full glory
Got it too!
So fast!
Next time.
Two in a row!
Nice! Still in the lead.
Another! Get a flow going!
Snatched it again!
I'm still leading!
So this is Hokuoh.
Let's all win again.
I knew playing with four would be tough.
Though the people know this place
As a mount of recluses
O thread of my life
If you must end, so be it
For should I survive
Thank you.
Hokuoh win four!
Nice!
HOKUOH A LOSSES: 0-4
UMEZONO LOSSES: 4-0
The new generation's just as strong.
Traditional schools have
a deep talent pool.
And Tokyo's full of guys like them.
Hokuoh's club president
is the one to watch out for.
Is he the one I played?
Who was in the center, shouting?
Yes.
Both of his parents were top players.
He's a bona fide thoroughbred.
He was educated in karuta from a young age
and reached A-class
in his first year at middle school.
Along with Kenshin Orie of Mizusawa,
he's one of the top prospects.
So he is someone special.
He can't sleep with a different pillow,
so he brought his own here.
He doesn't like red bean paste,
so he only eats the skin of dorayaki.
And to keep his hair glossy,
he orders his favorite shampoo
from the salon.
Due to his smart aura,
Mr. Kuroda calls him Okita Soji--
Hold on.
You know way too much about him.
Well, Sho is
my younger brother, after all.
Huh?
Younger brother? What?
You mean you're twins?
What the hell? Why didn't you say before?
Well,
because you didn't ask?
DAD
Hello. What's up?
Meguru?
You forgot your electronic dictionary.
And your charger.
Um…
Right. It's fine. I can borrow one.
You can? That's good.
You didn't read my texts,
so I thought you must be busy,
but I didn't want you to be in a fix.
Right. Thanks.
Also, I don't think I'll be able to talk
on the phone or text while I'm here.
It's a schedule from hell.
I feel for you. Got it.
Class starts in a minute,
so I'll head back now.
Thanks again.
-What is it?
-Just come.
What is it?
Why, Haruma?
Why are you here?
Why? Because I'm a member
of Umezono Karuta Club.
You never told me that.
Well, you didn't ask.
There's that Haruma speak again.
-You're going home, then?
-Huh? What?
I can't have you here.
I'm Hokuoh's ace. The club president.
If I'm gonna lead that army in there,
I need to be the toughest at all times.
Plus, I told everyone
my whole family's A-class.
But I'm C-class.
Exactly.
There is no C-class Haruma.
I'll lose my standing if this gets out.
All right.
I promise not to tell anyone else
that I'm your big brother.
That way I can stay, right?
If they start suspecting,
you go straight home.
Got it.
As you heard,
please keep the twin thing a secret
from the Hokuoh people.
I think you're allowed
to be more angry
at your brother, though, Haru Bun.
There's no need for anger.
Sho is truly remarkable.
He was a great player
from such a young age.
I'm not sure
if that's relevant to anything.
Oh no! It's time I started making dinner.
-Let me--
-Don't be silly.
At least let me do this much.
I'm already such a nuisance to everyone.
I couldn't even play in the team game.
Now, then…
You sure are a good reader, Miss Oe.
-It caught me off guard.
-No, no.
Have you taken your grading?
You always seemed
to put effort into reading.
Well, between family stuff,
finding a job, and COVID,
it ended up on the back burner.
I get that.
But it's a waste to leave it like that.
Maybe so.
Something smells good. Garlic?
Oh no!
Ow! Huh? Miss Oe?
I'm so sorry I left it all to you!
No, not at all. It's fine. I'm used to it.
No, we can't have that.
Now, tell me whatever you need me to do.
May I leave this onion to you, then?
Of course you may.
-If you'd be so kind.
-Right.
-Dice it?
-Yes, please.
You dice the veggies in your curry, then?
No. I'm actually a chunky veggie person.
Oh?
My little brother's eating with us today,
so I'm making his favorite keema curry.
-Aren't you the considerate big brother?
-No, not at all.
Was it circumstances like these
that inspired "Deep in the mountains"
1,000 years ago?
As the poet walked over a silent mountain?
Did you interpret it as a person
who's walking, Mr. Okuyama?
Is that wrong?
In waka, where a poem is separated
can change its meaning.
Deep in the mountains
Parting red leaves underfoot
Crying, a deer's voice
Imparts on me the sorrow
That always comes with autumn
In this poem,
if we break after
"parting red leaves underfoot,"
then it's a person who's walking.
If we break after
"crying, a deer's voice,"
then who is it who's walking?
The deer!
That's right!
That makes sense!
Being able to read so few words
in so many ways is waka's appeal.
It is.
I thought I knew a thing or two
about this,
but you're something else.
You're too kind.
So, Mr. Okuyama,
you're a chunky veggie person, you say?
I am.
Hokuoh win four!
Hokuoh win four.
Nice!
They thrashed us.
I feel bad for letting Hokuoh down.
What makes them different?
They're so different,
I don't know where to begin.
Why do they yell so much?
I couldn't shout that loud.
There are only four of us. I think
our problems begin before the yelling.
We need to do something.
Huh? What's up, Haru Bun?
Oh, nothing.
Everyone! Dinner's ready!
Thank you!
I got seconds!
This keema curry's crazy good.
I never knew curry could taste like this.
Everyone! There's plenty more
for second helpings!
Thank you!
-Big helping, please.
-Sure.
OKUYAMA
-There you are.
-"Okuyama."
All right! We've finished tidying up.
-Just baths then bed now.
-Yes.
-There are fireworks.
-No, we're not doing that now.
Let's go, Hokuoh!
Huh? They're still practicing?
At Hokuoh, we all do chores like sorting
the cards and cleaning the mats together.
My mother taught me
that little actions like this
can build into something bigger
and bless me later.
You might call it investing in virtue,
Miss Aizawa!
Investing in virtue?
It's kind of amazing, this sense of unity.
Team games are most certainly not
just a bunch of singles games.
We work together outside of games,
coordinate with
and understand one another.
By doing so, each individual
can push past their limits.
A C-class beating an A-class
is by no means unusual in a team game.
Low conquers high.
That's what makes team games interesting.
Indeed.
Excuse me.
Would you mind letting us do it?
Please.
Do we use seven?
Yeah. Zero, one, three, four, and seven.
Right.
-I've finished this one.
-You're done already?
Please help me, Haruma.
-Sure.
-Thanks.
-Follow the grain of the mats.
-Okay.
All right, this is the last one!
Everybody coordinate.
Three, two, one!
I'm beat.
So it's not just about the matches, huh?
We didn't play as a team today.
Tomorrow, we're gonna
put up a good fight for sure.
Yeah?
-You too, Haruma.
-No, no.
I'm not a player.
That doesn't matter.
That's right.
DAD
HAPPY STUDYING!
DON'T WORRY ABOUT REPLYING
I'M SORRY
-I'm back.
-Hi.
What's this?
Oh yeah. I was gonna talk to you
about that when you got home, Toko.
GRADE: D
DEVIATION VALUE: 63.2
Oh boy. Lib arts are through the floor.
-Let's talk to the cram school, maybe.
-The bath's ready.
You okay?
Sorry.
There really is something sad
about a deer's cry, isn't there?
Like in "Deep in the mountains."
Yes.
Separated from the rest of its herd,
a deer cries out in loneliness.
That's one interpretation of the poem.
Is that right?
I wonder if the one crying just now
was separated from its herd as well?
What? She's not at the study camp?
What do you mean?
Well, she's actually been absent a lot
as of late
and canceled the camp at the last minute,
so we've been concerned ourselves.
I see. Thank you.
Yes. I understand.
Okay. Goodbye.
Where is she?
She won't answer the phone.
She's not reading texts.
The police!
Meguru's a high-schooler now.
It's not like back then.
Let's wait a little longer.
Yeah?
Hokuoh win four.
Nice!
-Let's take a break.
-Yes, sir!
Thank you.
This feels more like teaching a class
than getting some practice, huh?
Keep your voice down, Sho.
I said it out loud on purpose.
Sho, there's something written
on that bottle.
HARUMA
Cute handwriting.
-You got a kid brother or something?
-Huh?
Well, yeah.
I bet he's a solid karuta player.
Of course he is.
He's an Okuyama, after all.
Haruma.
Yes? What is it?
He's a Haruma too, right?
Don't know his family name though.
It's Okuyama.
What?
Well, it was written on his bandana, see.
Talk about a coincidence!
That's crazy.
I've been thinking about this for a while,
but let's look for another member
once we're back in Tokyo.
Huh?
Carrying on like this
is just too reckless.
We can't expect to win team games
with just four people.
And the Musashino Tournament is coming up.
Then Haruma can--
I mean,
I'd also like to play with Haru Bun
if possible.
But there's only so much time
till the Tokyo qualifier,
and I'm not sure we can afford
to just sit around hoping
that Haru Bun's dizziness
will be cured at some point.
For sure.
You might be right, Sota.
This can't have been an easy decision
for you to make.
Haruma.
Go home like you promised.
Huh?
-I didn't tell anyone else.
-It's still gonna come out.
-But--
-You're a nuisance to Umezono too.
-What?
-Come on, man.
You can't even play matches.
And they're trying their damnedest
with just four people.
You must know how tough it is
to win three games with four players.
They're so admirable it makes me cry.
Don't you feel bad at all?
I feel… really bad.
What Umezono really want
isn't a damn manager.
It's a fifth player!
Read between the lines.
They're all just too nice to say it.
I see.
I suppose… you're right.
Okay, back to it!
-Right.
-Okay.
Huh? The reader's not here.
Where'd Haruma go?
Sota.
-Have you seen Haruma?
-Huh? He wasn't in the bathroom.
-That's weird.
-Huh?
Haru Bun!
Hey! Haruma!
Mr. Okuyama?
Haru Bun?
Where could he have gone?
Did you find him?
Sota?
"I'm sorry I didn't realize.
I've been a nuisance."
I HOPE YOU FIND A NEW MEMBER
AND GO ON TO GREATER THINGS.
THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING.
I'm sorry, Haru Bun.
I'm sorry, everyone.
-There's no need for that.
-It's not your fault.
That's right, Sota.
He could still be nearby.
I'll go and check.
I'll take another look around.
-Yeah.
-Go sit down, Sota.
Can I have a word?
Change the practice schedule?
Yeah. We'll forget the team games
and do singles instead today.
-Huh?
-What?
I mean, there are only four of you,
so team games are worthless to us.
-You can't be serious.
-Wait.
That's just rude.
-They have a right to practice too.
-No.
We're talking about beating Mizusawa here.
-We don't have time for this.
-All the same…
What, then? Keep playing a team of four?
SOTA:
WHERE ARE YOU, HARU BUN?!
CHIERI:
PICK UP, HARUMA
MEGURU: WHERE ARE YOU, HARU BUN?
WE'RE ALL WORRIED
CHIERI
SOTA
FUKI
MEGURU AIZAWA
-We'll train together--
-This isn't training--
Excuse me.
Aizawa? What is it?
You know something about it, don't you?
About Haru Bun leaving.
I mean,
he is your--
Whoa, hold on.
He is your big brother, after all.
Mr. Okuyama?
Miss Oe.
There are… lots of different ways
to interpret poems, aren't there?
Including "Deep in the mountains."
Yes. That's right.
I always wondered if,
deep in those mountains,
it really was just a deer
that was crying out of loneliness.
Miss Oe.
I…
CHIERI
Where'd you go, dummy?
I said to say if you get frazzled.
What am I supposed to do without you?
I'm sorry, Haru Bun.
We'd be lost without the Karuta Professor.
You've taught me so much.
I want to pay you back somehow.
Come back, Haruma.
You said before
that there's no need to rush.
We'll wait as long as it takes.
Let's play karuta!
All five of us together.
Haruma gave up fighting
when he couldn't beat me anymore.
Haruma
doesn't want to fight anyone.
He just wants to be helpful.
His brother should understand that.
It's you who doesn't understand.
If you want to be helpful in karuta,
winning is everything.
Did you say something to Haru Bun?
He can't play matches. What difference
does it make if he's here or not?
Seriously.
Let's start stretching, everyone.
Then singles games. Let's get ready.
All right.
Come on, let's go.
Yes, sir.
Please…
please let me play karuta too!
Is it all right
if I join you?
Of course it is!
-You're drenched!
-We were waiting.
Haruma. I'm sorry.
We can't play a team game together
without you here.
That's right.
I'm sorry I kept you.
Thank you.
Okay, then.
Now there are five of you, there's
no reason not to play a team game.
Let's do it.
Right!
Please deal the cards.
Let's have a good game.
You're not taking a single hand.
Haruma.
Don't push yourself.
I'm fine.
I want to push myself.
In Naniwa Bay
Behold how the flower blooms
After winter's sleep
And now, with spring's arrival
It reveals its full glory
Let's go, Hokuoh!
Right!
And now, with spring's arrival
It reveals its full glory
-Keep this going, Hokuoh.
-Right!
See? You were better off quitting.
One hand.
Just one hand.
I do not lament
From a moonstruck reverie
But I blame these tears
That's ten in a row.
Haru Bun!
Let's go!
That's the first time they've yelled.
Let's go, Haruma!
Go for it, Haruma!
The next one's yours, Haru Bun.
Guys!
Let's go, Umezono!
Right!
You think that's gonna make you win?
No.
All I want to do…
is win against myself.
I wonder if the one crying just now
was separated from its herd as well?
CRYING, A DEER'S VOICE
That one will be just fine now.
Because it found the courage
to cry out, "Here I am!"
I'm sure its voice will be heard.
Heard by whom?
Its new friends.
Then may the waves overcome
Suenomatsuyama
Deep in the mountains
Parting red leaves underfoot
Crying, a deer's voice
Got it!
I got it!
Nice!
I took it too.
Me too!
-Me too.
-Got it too.
Nice!
Got it!
-I see.
-The streak's on!
Nice!
So that's how it works.
And another. Let's take the next one too.
Right!
These shouts aren't something you force.
They just come out!
Let's go, Umezono!
Right!
Low can conquer high in team games.
And that means…
strength you can't muster on your own
can be brought out by others.
Me too.
Nice!
Team games
are amazing!
Thank you.
-Hokuoh. Let's break that down.
-Right.
That was amazing!
You okay?
Way to go, Haruma.
You played a whole game, Haruma!
It's thanks to all of you.
You did great.
-We all got "Deep in the mountains."
-Yeah.
Sorry about before, guys.
He really is my big brother.
Just for the record.
-Really?
-Everyone.
You were magnificent!
Thank you.
Miss Oe.
Thanks to you,
my dizziness has improved a little.
Thank you.
My pleasure.
And thank you.
KOMANO PHARMACY
Is that right?
You're working hard at a training camp?
That takes me back.
And about that movie we were
going to see together next week.
Could we make it the following week?
Of course. Why though?
There's… a karuta reading seminar
that day.
Huh?
You mean…?
I'm thinking… of taking another shot
at being a professional reader.
I see.
You're starting over?
Seeing those kids, it makes me
realize I have to go for them too.
The things I've left undone.
Right.
Good luck, Kana.
Yeah.
Come to think of it…
What?
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
COMPETITIVE KARUTA CLUB
Well, I didn't think it was worth
bringing up before, but…
Yes?
Sorry, Chieri.
STRAWBERRY MILK
NATURAL MINERAL WATER
I pressed the wrong one!
You're up.
And you, Shirano?
Oh, I just…
heard the stars out here were beautiful.
Stars?
I can't see a single one.
Nope.
It was worth coming, then.
Huh?
Oh?
You always drink water.
I pressed the wrong button.
Wanna swap, then?
What?
I like those, believe it or not.
Here. One man's trash.
Thanks.
Looking back, though,
all we've done at this camp
is play karuta.
Like, was it worth the long trip?
Exactly.
Even so, for some reason,
I feel like I'll never forget it.
Even those stars we couldn't see.
I doubt I'll forget it too.
There you are! What are you doing here?
Huh? Why…?
I woke up, and you weren't there.
-I was looking for you.
-You're all up too?
For the fireworks.
-We forgot to do them, didn't we?
-Yeah.
We found an open space over there.
Shall we?
-Okay. Let's go.
-Let's go.
What have you got in there again?
Huh?
I thought you didn't like sweet stuff.
Well,
I guess you wouldn't know.
Huh?
What? There are no hebidama in here.
What are hebidama?
You might be surprised at what I like.
Huh? What do you mean? Sweet stuff?
Crap! Meguru!
Meguru! We overslept!
Wake up!
What happened to my alarm?
And what time is it?
Hold on.
It's not charged!
Sorry! I thought you had enough,
so I switched them.
Miss Aizawa? I'm coming in.
Okay.
Huh?
Mom?
Toko!
Subtitle translation by: Lewis Williams