PREVIOUSLY
Please show me that people who find
their treasure in karuta
are guaranteed to have a bright future
waiting for them in ten years' time.
All right. I'll do it.
I'll be your evidence!
I will devote myself to it.
I want to join too. The karuta club.
Maybe I could play it too.
Miss Aizawa has withdrawn her resignation!
Thank you for having me.
At last. At last we have
five members, Miss Oe! Thank you.
Now we can play team games.
Let's all go to Omi Shrine!
None of this will happen
if you don't learn the poems.
There'll be a test next week.
Huh?!
UMEZONO HIGH SCHOOL
CHOOSE THE CORRECT SECOND HALF
Okay, time's up.
Okay.
-Here you are.
-Okay.
Amazing work, Mr. Okuyama.
Thank you.
Mr. Shirano, very good.
Miss Aizawa... Oh!
Not bad.
You all did brilliantly!
What the heck is this?
I'm sorry!
After all the help I gave you!
Sorry, Haruma!
Hey! Miss Murata!
Please wait! Miss Murata!
Right. Left.
Right.
Okay, let's hydrate.
I guess
this is how school clubs have to be.
Your sweeps have all improved.
Water! Excuse me!
What?
I wonder if we'll make it at this rate.
Everyone, fundamentals
are obviously important.
235 DAYS UNTIL THE TOKYO QUALIFIER
But the most effective way to practice
is by playing actual games.
We'll play practice games
as much as time allows on weekdays
and enter tournaments on the weekends
to build up your match experience.
Yes, Miss Oe.
Miss Oe?
Yes?
Wouldn't everyone improve quicker
if we joined a karuta society
as well as this club?
A karuta society?
Is that sort of like
what we'd call a gym in boxing?
Precisely, Mr. Shirano.
All the good players
belong to a karuta society.
No idea where we'd find one.
I've never even heard of them either.
Don't you worry.
I found a karuta society
that's just right for all of you.
CHIHAYAFURU: FULL CIRCLE
POEM THREE:
AT THIS PRESENT MOMENT
Here it is.
Fuchu Yugiri-kai.
We're here a little early.
Hello.
-Please, come on in.
-Thank you.
Since we're here, shall we wait inside?
Yes, Miss Oe.
-Thank you very much.
-Please.
Thank you very much.
-I wonder what it'll be like.
-Yeah.
Here we are!
Wait for me, please.
I'm sorry, Miss Oe.
-What for?
-The shoes.
Sorry.
It's a ritual of sorts for me.
Ritual?
My mother taught me
that little actions like this
can build into something bigger
and bless me later.
You might call it
investing in virtue, Miss Aizawa!
That's easy to understand.
Not that I have any evidence!
No, that's all right.
Excuse me.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
-Shall we take a seat?
-Yes.
Let's.
-Miss Oe.
-Yes?
What's the president like?
Let me see.
Like a reliable big brother, perhaps.
We eat meat buns on Mondays
We eat meat buns on Tuesdays too
Huh? Meat Bun's not here yet.
Meat Bun's not here.
Meat Bun?
Who was that?
Who said Meat Bun?
Got you!
Hey, at least call me Master Meat Bun.
Master Meat Bun.
That's better!
Get ready. We'll start right away.
-Yes, Master Meat bun!
-Okay. Hey, Kana! Sorry I kept you.
Meat Bun!
Oh, President Nishida, I mean.
Thank you so much
for helping our students.
I ain't decided to help them yet.
They have to pass our entrance test first.
What?
Another test?
That's right.
There's a lot of you,
so I'll make an exception
and see you two-by-two.
Starting with you two.
Okay.
To qualify for entry,
you need to take three hands from me.
Three?
Just three out of 50?
You got it.
Maybe even we could pull that off, then?
There are two of us.
Now, wouldn't that be nice?
All right! Let's do this!
Kana, do the honors?
Leave it to me.
In Naniwa Bay
Behold how the flower blooms
After winter's sleep
That's my Kana. What a voice.
And now, with spring's arrival
It reveals its full glory
Blown just a little
See how the plants of autumn…
He's fast!
Awesome.
There ya go!
Huh? You touched the wrong card!
What? You need to study more.
That's a watari-te, isn't it?
Watari-te?
Right. Mr. Orie told me about this.
This is the boundary
that separates your area
from your opponent's.
You're allowed to touch any cards that are
in the same area as the correct one.
I see.
That rule allows a player
to sweep away two cards
before a distinguishing syllable is read.
YO NO NAKA WA
YO NO NAKA YO
No way.
The mountain hamlet…
-Sorry.
-No, I'm sorry.
Alrighty.
-No fair.
-What?
-No fair!
What?
-That's not fair!
-What?
Kakoi-te.
Kakoi-te?
A move for guarding cards
that take a long time to be identified.
You're kidding me.
I've not seen any of these techniques.
He's just too good.
Mr. Yusei Nishida.
A top player, even at the national level.
What? We have to take
three cards from him?
At least let me get this one.
FOR BEHIND A SINGLE CLOUD
THE MOON THAT NIGHT DID VANISH
There it is!
His hands are so low.
He snuck his in under hers to take it.
Well, little lady?
Still think you can pull it off?
All right!
-You touched the wrong card.
-What?
Wrong card.
Thank you.
We didn't win a single hand.
There are two of you.
You should have used your heads more.
You're a great reader.
You must be qualified.
No, not all. I'm really not very...
Are you...?!
So what are we going to do?
In the end, only Shirano passed.
Sorry.
And as for you, Okuyama,
you had a problem
none of us could've expected.
Behold how the flower blooms
After winter's sleep
And now, with spring's arrival…
Whoa. Wait up, Kana. Stop there.
What's up, Haruma?
I'm terribly sorry.
This always happens to me
when I play a match.
What? Are you putting me on?
No, I wouldn't dream of it.
It's just, I really can't help it.
Right. Got you.
Sorry, Kana. Once more from the top.
-Sorry.
-If you would.
In Naniwa Bay…
-What's going on?
-What is this?
I like you.
Do it again--
Meat Bun!
Okay.
I'm so sorry.
No, that's not what I meant.
-Sit down.
-I've disgraced myself.
Still,
what was that all about?
The thing is, I'm not even sure myself.
When a game begins,
I just get all dizzy for some reason.
Dizzy?
Like the yips?
Perhaps.
The yips?
It's a psychological thing
where your body won't do what you tell it.
You see it in baseball.
And in boxing.
Don't worry about
getting into the society though.
I'm already a member of another one.
What?
-You are?
-Why didn't you say?
Well… you didn't ask.
Hold on.
So what class are you?
Well, I'm sort of C-class.
-No wonder you know so much.
-That's really good!
Or at least I might be,
if only I could play matches.
As such, I'm thinking I could
act as manager for the time being.
I can practice just fine.
And I do know a thing or two about karuta.
That is, if you'd all be happy
with that, of course.
Of course we would be. Right?
It would be my honor!
In any case,
we need the two of you
to get into the Yugiri-kai somehow.
Shall we see what Miss Oe says?
Oh, about her…
-Yes.
-What? Is something up with her?
It's just, when we came
to practice at lunch…
Beyond Mount Oe
Goes the road to Ikuno
The journey is long
And my eyes are yet to spy
Amanohashidate
Miss Oe.
Oh, Miss Murata and Mr. Okuyama.
How nice to see you.
-Did something good happen?
-Can you tell?
Just about.
It was just like a dream!
I mean, the one and only Izumi Nakanishi
deigned to grace me with some pointers
to improve my reading!
Izumi Nakanishi?
Izumi Nakanishi…
-You mean the professional reader?
-Yes, that's right!
Like a wizard?
-You're thinking of a different word.
-Huh?
It's a kind of specialist who has
the highest level of skill for a reader.
There are only seven
in the whole of Japan.
Moreover,
I have even been blessed
with an invitation to dinner.
Thank you, Meat Bun!
Blessings be upon the Yugiri-kai!
Okay, let's forget about Miss Oe for now.
-Right.
-What do we do, then?
I have an idea.
PRACTICE SCHEDULE
I planned your training
in advance of your retest in two weeks.
We're going to overcome each of the issues
President Nishida brought up.
It will also prepare us
for the All Japan Championship.
You're right.
As Haru Bun says,
let's do anything we can.
You said "Haru Bun."
-Oh!
-Sorry.
I mixed "Meat Bun" with "Haruma"!
-Not at all.
Just a little more, everyone. Keep it up.
Your memory's good. You know the poems.
But you don't move your body.
Did you attack my territory once
in that game just now? Huh?
Your body's axis is weak,
so you unconsciously don't reach out.
Start by building your strength
and doing core exercises!
I can't do it anymore.
I didn't expect this in karuta.
Firstly, "mu."
"Mu" is for muscular.
-Muscular?
-Yes.
Next, "su." A dream of su.
You're the opposite.
You move well,
and I can't fault your reflexes. But!
You don't know the cards' position at all
and constantly touch the wrong ones.
And it's all down to your shoddy knowledge
of the actual poems.
Go back and learn them!
Memorization is fundamental.
Momo, tago, fu, kaku, ima wa. Time!
-You passed.
-All right!
Fifteen seconds to go.
What was this one again?
What was it?
And this is a cultural club?
It's a sports club at this point!
Meguru, your bath's ready.
Meguru?
I'm opening the door.
Megu--
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
I signed this for you.
Right.
Hey, I didn't know you
were in a karuta club.
I just forgot to leave it.
Oh, really?
OKONOMIYAKI NISHIDA
Whenever I have business in Tokyo,
I always stop by
at Mr. Nishida's Yugiri-kai
and this restaurant of his.
Right!
Right?!
-Here.
-Thank you ever so much.
I've read all of your essays.
I know you're a leading researcher
of classical literature by day.
You're too kind.
I'm just a slave to the classics.
Actually,
I once applied
to work at your research institute.
But it wasn't meant to be, unfortunately.
Oh! We must have had
no eye for talent, then.
Don't be absurd.
I just wasn't good enough.
Okay, yours is all done, Izumin.
Oh, here it is!
The house specialty, yaemugura-yaki.
You can't get it anywhere in Kyoto.
-Here.
-Thanks.
And now…
These two go so well together,
they must have been married
in a past life.
Try it.
Don't mind if I do.
I… don't suppose there were
any other shortcomings in my recitals?
Your speaking volume,
rhythm, sense of stability,
use of pauses,
understanding of the waka themselves,
they're all at a very high level.
Really?
-However…
-However?
…your nasal sonants
aren't quite there yet.
My nasal sonants?
Ga-gi-gu-ge-go.
If a reader
can't pronounce them correctly,
I don't consider them a true reader,
even if I recognize their other talents.
Could you… tell me a good way
to practice them at all?
Let me see.
I would recommend… that thing?
Yeah, that.
-Huh?
-Yeah.
That!
Has brought me to understand
How empty I was before
Loud the crickets chirp
On this dark and frosty night…
Thank you.
Only one sleeve over me
Will I sleep alone tonight?
-Miss Oe?
-Yes, Mr. Okuyama?
Do you think you could teach me
how to be a reader?
Yes. What?
You're not able to be here
every day when we practice,
and I thought I might like to make myself
at least a little useful at those times.
Of course. I'd do so gladly,
if I'll suffice as a teacher.
-Thank you very much.
-The pleasure's all mine.
Aw, man…
How do you guys remember the poems?
Miss Aizawa?
I use these.
What is this?
For some reason,
each card has its own unique number.
I never noticed these before.
That's the poem number.
-Poem number?
-Yeah.
Poems in the Hyakunin Isshu are
sorted chronologically by number.
"In the autumn field," thought
to have been composed circa 600,
is the oldest poem and so is Poem 1.
Composed circa 1200,
"The emperor's court" is Poem 100.
Maybe even I could remember them
using that method.
Miss Aizawa, you can't mean
that you didn't learn them
through the second halves or wordplay,
but through the poem numbers?
Yes. I thought it'd be more efficient.
What have I done?
Is that bad?
Yes. No, I don't mean that.
What a novel approach.
Genius, even? Wait. No, not that.
But it's better than not learning…
No. Permitting this will disgrace me.
-She's speaking out loud.
-No, I can't overlook this.
Let's study the backgrounds to the poems.
I'll take responsibility
for teaching it all from the ground up.
What?!
REACTION BALL: AIZAWA
(GOAL: TEN CATCHES)
Here we go!
What is this? It goes different ways.
Miss Aizawa!
-You too, Haruma!
-Me too?
COMPETITIVE KARUTA CLUB
Parted we may be
But if on Mount Inaba
I hear the pine trees
Tell me that you wait for me
I shall hasten to return
"Parted We May Be" is a farewell poem.
It means, "If you're waiting for me,
I'll come straight home,"
and has been used as an incantation
since ancient times.
Here we go.
-Bring it on.
-Okay.
Nice.
Yes!
All right.
Bad luck! Here it comes.
Okay.
I borrowed them from the baseball club.
-Is this "borrowing"?
-As long as I give them back--
-Oh crap!
-Those balls!
-I wondered where they were.
-I only borrowed them.
Well, I guess it doesn't matter.
But what did you want them for?
Want to play baseball again?
We used them for karuta practice.
You're in the karuta club, Chieri?
I am.
I wondered why you left so suddenly.
Karuta club, huh?
That really doesn't suit you.
Shut up.
I like it.
More than baseball?
That's right.
Even more than baseball.
You're lying for sure.
You're the last person who'd say that.
You're baseball crazy.
Shut up!
-Hey, quit it!
-Shut up!
-Hey, Chieri!
-Miss Murata!
-Excuse me.
-Man!
Are you okay?
Why wouldn't I be? Let's go.
At this present time
If I can see you no longer
I wish for a way
I could tell you in person
That I'll cease to think of you
Fujiwara no Michimasa had been
in an unacceptable love affair,
and he put the thoughts
he was unable to express in this poem.
"With great sadness,
I am giving up on you."
"If only I could express my regret
to you in person."
Miss Murata.
Huh?
You…
What?
Maybe you should…
You're right.
What is this?
It's a good poem, isn't it?
It's all Michimasa's fault.
Sorry, Miss Oe.
I'm leaving early today.
Miss Murata was devoted to being
a pitcher ever since she was a kid.
She and her childhood friend,
Mr. Yuki Nagashima,
were batterymates since Little League.
What? Is that the same Nagashima
who's with me in Class B?
Yes, that Mr. Nagashima.
I see.
They both dreamed
of going to Koshien together
after they started at Umezono.
Boys and girls can't play together
in high-school baseball,
but they believed
that rule would change one day.
Nice pitch!
One more time!
Little by little, though,
the situation changed.
She went to practice each morning,
went through the same drills,
only for the gap between the boys and her
to keep widening.
Despite that, she managed
to hang in there somehow
because of her promise to Mr. Nagashima.
Then, one day…
Haruma!
I'm sick of baseball.
I'm quitting.
See you later.
The physical difference was just too much.
Knowing Miss Murata, though,
that doesn't explain everything.
Her answer changed every time I asked,
and in the end,
she would just make a joke out of it.
Even I don't know the true reason.
I see.
CRAM SCHOOL
I have to get going now.
You've got it rough.
Sorry. Can I leave the books to you?
See you tomorrow, then.
-See you.
-Goodbye.
Hey, Haruma.
Yes?
Do you think
Miss Murata went straight home?
-Lift the bat up high.
-High?
-Lower your hips more.
-Right.
Look forward and tuck in your chin.
-Tuck in my chin?
-That's it.
Imagine you're smacking down
from high to low.
How do I swing it from here?
-The balls are coming!
-What? I can't do this!
And the next one. Swing!
Look at the ball and don't think.
Swing!
-Empty your head.
-I don't think I'll hit any.
Swing!
How am I going to face
the clubroom tomorrow?
Nothing's changed from before.
That reminds me.
Here. I came to give you this.
I know what Miss Oe says,
but it's better than not knowing them.
Some people are visual learners,
so I tried making illustrations.
Did you do all this yourself?
Well, you know,
the numbers worked for me.
You really are
a master artist, aren't you?
I'll have it back, then!
No! It's mine!
I won't give it--
Thanks.
-Yeah.
-For not asking any questions.
Yeah.
I'll tell you all about it
once I've got my head straight.
Just give me a little bit of time?
Yeah.
PRACTICE SCHEDULE
President Nishida is a top player,
the kind who is invited to title matches.
And you need to take three hands from him.
To put it another way,
you only need three.
If you narrow down the cards
you'll go for and forget the rest,
you both stand more than a chance.
Fifteen seconds to go.
Meguru.
President Nishida gave us a hint too.
"If you're working as a pair,
use your heads more."
With that in mind, I spoke with Miss Oe,
and we devised a strategy.
FRIEND CARDS
Friend cards?
CRAM SCHOOL
There's a study camp
over the long weekend in November.
It will be very important for your exams,
so be sure to join us.
SPECIAL FALL STUDY CAMP
This means, "If I were a bird,
I could fly all over the world."
"Chi ha" is crimson. Chi ha.
WORK
Full marks!
I did it!
Straight.
CRAM SCHOOL
Right.
Take a deep breath
and read it out in a relaxed way.
Right.
After the shower
The dew still has not dried up
WORK
I'd like to quit.
What? You're leaving? Really?
You're kidding!
Please reconsider!
I'll up your pay!
I've already made up my mind.
I'm sorry.
-I did it!
-Congratulations!
Incredible!
To a heart that wata no hara speaks of.
What? Yes!
Miss Murata.
Okay.
You know what the coach told me?
"Nagashima has the skills
to be on the starting team."
"There's just one problem."
He's too hung up on being in a battery
with you.
"He refuses to work with anyone but you."
"You understand what I'm trying
to say here, don't you, Murata?"
"Be the club manager."
That's what he said.
That's why I decided
I might as well just quit.
Yuki…
doesn't know any of this.
Because if he did,
I'm sure he'd stop playing baseball.
That's the kind of guy he is.
At this present time
If I can see you no longer
I wish for a way
I could tell you in person
That I'll cease to think of you
If only I could express
My regret to you in person.
That's why Yuki
absolutely can't know about it.
Karuta's something else, isn't it?
I was really inspired
back when I first saw Sota compete.
I feel bad for saying this,
but that pink-haired girl who beat Sota
really inspired me too.
Boy or girl, it really doesn't matter.
Is there any other kind of sport
like that?
Just you wait, competitive karuta.
I'm gonna be Queen of Karuta
and take all the masters down.
Cold and unfeeling
A cuckoo cries out
With nothing but the dawn moon
Remaining still in the sky
Thick patches of weeds
I see not a single soul
But autumn is surely here
At this present time
I hit it!
Meguru. You hit it!
-I hit it!
-You hit it!
Awesome.
FUCHU YUGIRI-KAI
Shall I drop it to two hands?
Three is just fine.
And in return,
if we win,
you show us your high-school yearbook.
Huh? What kind of a deal is that?
I want to find
an embarrassing photo of you.
-Whoa, hang on there--
-Is that a no?
There's no way
you'd lose to the likes of us, right?
All right!
In Naniwa Bay
Behold how the flower blooms
After winter's sleep
And now, with spring's arrival
It reveals its full glory
All right. It's just another game.
And now, with spring's arrival
It reveals its full glory
Fleeing solitude
I step outside of my home…
Well, that was a given.
Of course.
This is fine though.
I spoke with Miss Oe,
and we devised a strategy.
The key to victory
is this.
FRIEND CARDS
Friend cards start the same way
before they can be distinguished.
For instance, poems that can be
distinguished by their third syllable…
IMA WA
…like "At This Present Time"
and "You Said You Would Come"…
IMA KO
…are friend cards
that are especially ripe for watari-te.
Decide who will take each card
and go for both the moment you hear "ima."
That way, you can be
one step ahead of President Nishida.
The leaves of the maple tree
At this present time
If I can see you no longer
I wish for a way
We did it!
-Yes!
-You did it!
It worked.
Looks like you didn't waste
the past two weeks.
Of course not.
The match is
only just getting started though.
All right.
Come on!
That's what I'm talkin' about!
Your specialty card is "After the shower"
and yours is "Going round the path," yes?
President Nishida will react to both
on hearing the opening "M" consonant.
As such, you'll split them between you.
MU
ME
Nothing but this ritual
Reminds me it is summer
After the shower
The dew still has not dried up
On the fern pine's leaves
Got it!
Nice cover!
Very nice!
She swept it out of his territory.
One more hand.
Awesome!
That one hand's a long way off.
Hang in there.
Cards distinguished on the sixth syllable
are great mountain cards.
President Nishida is sure
to use kakoi-te for them.
You favor different hands,
so reach out from both sides.
I see not a single soul
But autumn is surely here
Night fades into dawn
Then an opening is sure to appear
in President Nishida's guard.
That's when…
I call it the double kakoi-te breaker,
type zero!
How edgy.
We did it!
We did it, Meguru!
We did, Chieri!
Thank you.
You got me!
You both qualify for the Yugiri-kai!
-We did it!
-You did it!
You did! Amazing work, you two!
-We did it!
-I knew you could!
-They did it, Miss Oe!
-Yes!
Although "After the shower"
and "Going round the Path"
aren't friend cards, technically speaking.
That's right.
Looks like the two of them are though.
Friends, I mean.
CLOSED FOR PRIVATE EVENT
Right. Yeah.
Yeah. I won't be too late.
See you.
-Hey, Meguru! Did you see the yearbook?
-Huh?
The president hasn't changed a bit!
It's totally hilarious!
I can't wait to show you.
Fuki, show Meguru the yearbook.
-Okay.
-One egg mix, Meat Bun!
Hey! You're ordering extra
'cause it's on me!
Of course I am!
Why, you…
COMPETITIVE KARUTA CLUB
ALL JAPAN VICTORY
BECOME A PRO READER AND READ THE POEMS
AT CHIHAYA'S QUEEN GAME
KANADE OE
Miss Oe.
Who is this Chihaya person?
Chihaya…
KARUTA QUEEN!
CHIHAYA AYASE
…is this person right here.
COMPETITIVE KARUTA EXPERIENCE
I've seen her somewhere…
Your attention, please, everyone.
So you can all improve even more,
I'm planning a karuta training camp
for the long weekend this fall.
What?!
A famous club has kindly allowed us
to join them on their training camp.
It's the perfect chance to soak up
all of their knowledge.
Please discuss it with your parents.
-Thank you.
-For three days?
Thank you for waiting. The yakisoba.
Thank you.
SPECIAL FALL STUDY CAMP
2–4 NOVEMBER
KARUTA CLUB TRAINING CAMP
What the hell?!
Subtitle translation by: Lewis Williams