=Have a Crush on You=
=Episode 5=
Cerebral parasitic disease
is quite rare.
Why did you come here?
Don't you know that
the other side is occupied?
Go back and rest well.
Dr. Ruan,
you're pretty bold.
You operated on the patient before
the attending doctor arrived.
It was an emergency.
His intracranial pressure
kept rising non-stop.
Why didn't you inject him with Mannitol?
We've already done that.
If we inject him with Mannitol
within a short period again,
he might experience kidney failure.
If so, why didn't you wait for me?
Who will bear the responsibility
if something happens to the patient?
(Door's open.)
(2012 Jiangzhou, China)
I can't stand it anymore.
Be careful.
I'm sure my heel is bleeding.
Let me take a look.
It's fine.
Let me clean it for you.
It's fine. I can do it myself.
What are you saying? I have to do it.
Give me your foot.
Bear with it.
The person who designed high heels
must be out to torture people.
Your heel is already bleeding.
Precisely.
This is my last time wearing high heels.
I won't wear it again.
You only did it for the wedding, right?
The wedding was tiring.
I smiled the entire day.
My face is numb now.
I don't think I can smile now.
You're smiling right now.
I will never hold a wedding again.
Again?
Don't tell me you want to
hold another wedding?
With whom?
Give me the other foot.
It doesn't hurt anymore.
Done.
I'll get you your slippers.
Leave it over there. I'll clean it up.
Here.
Go and take a bath.
I'll change the band-aid for you
once you're done.
Untie this for me.
Hello?
(Hello, Dr. Ning.)
(Are you busy?)
(We have an emergency over here.)
(We require your assistance.)
What's going on?
(The patient has
intracranial hemorrhage.)
(It's pretty severe.)
What about the other doctors?
(Those on duty are already here.)
(But we lack manpower.)
You guys lack manpower?
(That's right.)
Do you guys know what day it is today?
(Dr. Ning,)
(I know today's your wedding day.)
(But this is an emergency.)
(Please come here immediately.)
Fine.
Alright, I understand.
I'll head there immediately.
Liuzheng,
the ER needs me.
I have to go.
Go to sleep after you're done bathing.
Don't wait for me.
I'll be done in a second!
(Beiya Hospital)
(Medical Staff Passage)
(Operating Room)
Periosteal elevator.
I'm done. It's your turn to bathe.
Where did he go?
Where are you?
Are you playing hide-and-seek with me?
Ready or not, here I come.
I saw you!
Ning?
I don't feel like playing anymore.
Show yourself.
Where did he go?
(Ruan Liuzheng)
(Unanswered calls,
Ruan Liuzheng 4)
(Sorry.)
(The number you have dialed)
(is currently unavailable.)
(Please call again later.)
Scissors.
Ready the tray.
(Sorry.)
(The number you have dialed)
(is currently unavailable.)
(Please call again later.)
(Door's open.)
(Happiness)
You're awake?
Where did you go?
You didn't answer my calls.
I could only access your voicemail.
What did you do last night?
Didn't I tell you already?
The ER needed me
last night.
When did you tell me that?
When you were bathing.
The ER needs me.
I have to go.
Go to sleep after you're done bathing.
Don't wait for me.
I'll be done in a second!
I thought you told me to hurry up.
The hospital told me to hurry up.
Did you sleep here the entire night?
Isn't it cold?
My heart feels colder.
Come. Let's go inside.
I'll cuddle you.
You must be hungry.
I'll cook something for you.
It's okay.
Sit down. I'll be done in a second.
Just sit here.
How many eggs would you like?
One is enough.
(2019 Beiya Hospital, Jiangzhou, China)
Morning, Deputy Manager Ning.
- Morning, Deputy Manager Ning.
- Morning.
Morning, Deputy Manager Ning.
Morning.
(Beiya Hospital)
Hello, mister.
I was here first.
I was trying to reverse my car
and park into the spot.
Didn't you see my car?
Do you understand the meaning of
first come first served?
Sorry about that. I didn't see you.
Sorry about that.
Hurry and shift your car.
Hey, come back!
You don't plan on shifting your car?
I have an emergency.
Find another parking spot.
Do you think you're the only one
with an emergency here?
Come back!
Are you even a man?
What kind of person is this?
Dr. Cheng!
You're back?
I'm back.
Bai, Fan.
How did your teaching
at the subordinate unit go?
My students were very passionate.
Didn't you take the chance to make
one of your students your girlfriend?
All of them were guys.
I have to tell you something then.
Two gorgeous ladies
joined our department
while you were away.
Really?
The Department of Neurosurgery
finally has girls now?
One of them is gentle
while the other is feisty.
Both of them are good-looking.
Since I just came back,
you guys should introduce me
in a grand manner later.
- Sure.
Just leave it to me.
I'll leave it to you guys.
Make it grand, okay?
Let's go and get changed.
Let's go.
Dr. Ding,
why are you late today?
Don't bring it up.
A despicable guy
stole my parking spot just now.
It was so infuriating.
If I see him again,
I'll crack his head open
with my high heels.
Don't be angry.
I'll crack his head open for you
if you see him again.
Nice. It's a promise then.
By the way,
let me introduce an expert to you.
Dr. Cheng?
This is our attending doctor,
Dr. Cheng Zhouyu.
He just came back from his
teaching duty
at a subordinate unit.
His skills are superb.
He's only second to Dr. Ning.
Second to Dr. Ning?
They're evenly matched.
That's right.
He's one of the
main forces of our hospital.
We meet again.
Yeah.
Do you two know each other?
We do.
Didn't you say
you wanted to crack
his head open for me?
Take this for me. Go ahead.
There was a misunderstanding
at the car park just now.
Is this the feisty one
or the gentle one?
This is the feisty one.
She's amazing, right?
She's the feisty one?
What about the gentle one?
She went to do her rounds with Dr. Ning.
She's doing her rounds?
You guys should go on your rounds too.
I'll wait for Ning to return.
Let's go.
The patient in Bed tenth
is recovering well.
Observe his condition.
The crucial period is three days
after the operation.
Keep an eye on the patient's condition.
Okay.
Resume your work.
What are you doing?
Hello, Deputy Manager Ning.
Hello.
We have to keep our distance.
But why?
Ding Yiyuan is keeping
a close eye on me.
Do you think I'll have it easy
if she finds out about our relationship?
What's there to be afraid of?
Why can't we disclose
our divorce to other people?
It might not matter to you.
But have you considered my feelings?
An ex-wife as the student
of her ex-husband?
Even a terrible student can
write a drama based on that.
You're out of your mind.
(Nurse Station)
Why did you come back?
I've already been away for two months.
Of course I need to come back.
I heard that you took in
a female student.
And, she's quite beautiful.
Who did you hear that from?
That doesn't matter.
How old is she?
Is she taken?
She's not suitable for you.
How would you know when
we haven't met each other yet?
What if she likes someone like me?
Which part of you is likable?
Your smelly feet?
Wear your shoes.
Compliment me
when you introduce me to her later.
Don't forget. You owe me a girlfriend.
I owe you a girlfriend?
When?
Weren't you the one
who introduced Ruan to me back then?
Ruan?
Do you think she'll fall for
a person like you?
I don't care.
I'm busy every day even though
I'm at this age.
I just expect
to get a girlfriend within our department now.
Dr. Ruan.
I'll introduce an expert to you later.
He was away on a teaching trip
before this.
He just came back.
Sure.
Listen.
His skills are on par with Dr. Ning.
However, his temper is much better.
Is that so?
Listen to me.
It's impossible between you two.
Why's that?
Just listen to me.
Wait...
Dr. Cheng,
this is Dr. Ruan Liuzheng,
who was just transferred
to our hospital.
Dr. Ruan,
don't tell me you want
to crack his head open too?
Is she
your new student?
Not bad at all.
It's your second time.
Second time?
Come here.
Listen.
They're just
faking it.
How's your delegation?
Is there something
you need to share with us?
About the removal of
the fourth intracranial tumor,
check out this image.
Which image?
I'll search it for you.
Only you and Tan Ya knew about
what happened between us.
Do not tell anyone about it, understood?
But why?
You'll cause unnecessary trouble.
What's with that sound?
I'll take it as a yes then.
It depends on my mood.
What?
You want to negotiate a deal with me?
Let me think about it first.
I'll tell you when I'm done.
Don't go overboard.
Ning,
you knew that I liked
Ruan from the start, right?
Since you two are already divorced,
I think...
What are you up to?
Do you think it's appropriate for you
to steal her under my nose?
Ding Yiyuan looks like
a better match for you.
Not at all.
(2012 Jiangzhou, China)
Can you stop laughing?
That means you guys haven't done that
even until now?
He's been busy with the wedding
and surgeries.
He's not concerned about that yet.
Besides, my girl,
both of us study medicine.
There's no taboo.
Listen.
For the most part,
the stability of a wedding
depends on
the private life of the couple.
Really?
What?
Do you need me to explain it to you
loud and clear?
From a physiological structure
or gender relations?
Listen to me!
No, thanks!
Liuzheng.
I heard from my mother
that the Great Migration
in Africa is amazing.
For our honeymoon,
why don't we head to Africa?
I wish to witness
the Great Migration too.
It's decided then.
What's the matter?
What are you watching?
I'm watching how the lions
are hunting down their prey.
Do you want to join me?
Okay.
Wait for me.
(2019 Beiya Hospital, Jiangzhou, China)
Where did he go
this early in the morning?
Didn't he tell you before he left?
The patient is already anesthetized.
He didn't answer my calls at all.
I'll kick him when he comes back.
We're running out of time.
Bai,
why don't you join me?
I can't. I have
another surgery to handle.
You, come with me.
Okay.
Vital signs.
All vital signs are normal.
Why are you still standing here?
You will do the craniotomy.
Me?
That's right.
Aren't you the assistant
for this surgery?
You may begin.
I'll assist you.
Okay.
Scalpel.
Steady your hands.
Be more stable with them.
(During the Operation)
Don't shake your hands.
Drill.
Find the correct position.
Periosteal elevator.
Craniotomy completed.
The tumor is pretty deep inside.
The situation is very complicated.
I'll try my best to hurry up.
Bipolar ESU.
What can I do?
Hold the brain spatula.
Okay.
Adjust your position
according to what I do.
Periosteal elevator.
Dr. Ruan, steady your hands.
It all depends on you now.
I got sweat in my left eye.
Wipe it for me.
Don't move, Dr. Ruan.
You should know the consequences
if you damage the brain tissues.
Steady your hands.
Hemostat.
You can remove the brain spatula now.
I'll leave the rest to you now.
Me?
Alright.
Thread and forceps.
Mr. Ning,
I'm so sorry.
Who are you?
I'm Wu Xiaofan.
So, you're Wu Xiaofan from
Beiya's Department of Neurosurgery?
Mr. Ning, I didn't do it on purpose.
I fell unconscious after drinking
soy milk this morning.
You fell unconscious?
Did someone drug you?
No.
No one drugged me.
What did you do last night?
I was on duty last night.
I only slept for two hours.
You should thank Dr. Ruan.
She salvaged the situation for you.
Dr. Ruan, thank you so much.
Luckily, you're here today.
Do not do this again.
Remember that.
I understand.
I won't do it again.
Let's go.
I'm lucky to have you here today.
He kicked you on the operation table?
He couldn't.
I'm very agile.
Mr. Ning is extremely particular.
He doesn't allow anyone
to commit mistakes during work,
not even himself.
I was always scared out of my wits
when I was under him.
However, my skills
did grow at a rapid rate too.
By the way, Dr. Ruan,
I forgot to congratulate you.
If Dr. Ning allowed you to
operate on the patient,
that means he has
acknowledged your capability.
Really?
Of course.
Didn't you realize something?
His attitude toward you changed
ever since you won the bet
against Dr. Ding.
My hand with the brain spatula
shook a little during the surgery.
Really?
Did Mr. Ning say anything?
He said nothing.
It's better if he reprimands you.
It's the worst when
he doesn't say anything.
But you don't need to be too worried.
Maybe everything's fine.
We'll know when the patient is awake.
I'll head upstairs first.
Deputy Manager Ning,
the patient who went through
the surgery last night is awake.
Do you want to take a look?
Okay.
Doctor.
He's awake?
He's still quite weak.
Dad, the doctor is here.
Can you hear me?
I'll perform a simple checkup for you.
Doctor, how's my father?
What's your name?
His name is Li Pingshun.
I just wanted to test his reaction.
What's your name?
Li Pingshun.
Can you raise your hand?
Raise your right hand for me.
Okay.
What about your left hand?
(When I was at the operation table,)
(my hand with the brain spatula
shook a little.)
(Maybe everything's fine.)
(We'll know when the patient is awake.)
Dad, use some strength.
Put your back into it.
A little more.
Dad, use some strength.
Come on.
I can't raise my hand.
Doctor, what's going on?
Can he still move his hands?
We'll observe him for a little longer.
Dad, don't panic.
It's fine.
Calm down.
Head Nurse,
if he's still like this
in the afternoon,
arrange another
brain CT scan for him.
Okay.
Calm down.
Thank you, Doctor.
Dad, it's fine.
Alright, no problem.
Wait for me to get off work.
Okay.
I'm entering the elevator.
Talk to you later.
Goodbye.
What are you looking at?
Wait.
She's crying.
Aren't you going to console her?
I thought you took her as your student
because you wanted to make it up to her.
So, you're still trying to torment her?
Who's tormenting her?
All of us had been through this process.
She's a female doctor after all.
What's wrong with female doctors?
Are you belittling them?
If she wants to work in this field,
she has to bear the pressure alone.
You're actually lecturing me right now?
She's your ex-wife.
I couldn't care less.
Dad,
stop drinking.
It's fine. I feel much better.
Excuse me,
kin of Patient 16.
Dad.
Dr. Ruan.
Come here for a second.
I have something to tell you.
Son.
I think the drip is finished.
Let me check.
Check the IV drip.
It's not finished yet.
Li Pingshun,
can you shake my hand?
This is great.
Thank you.
This is a good thing. Don't cry.
Please rest well.
Thank you, doctor.
What's wrong?
I thought I made him a cripple.
That's normal after surgery.
You're a doctor, you know?
Why are you behaving like a fool?
What's the matter?
Doctor.
My sister's urine bag fell off.
What should I do?
Dr. Ding, let me do it.
It's fine. I'll do it.
Doctor,
sorry about that.
It's fine.
Please wash your hands.
Tell her to be
more gentle next time.
- Okay.
- Keep an eye on her.
Thank you.
No problem.
Be more careful.
Stop bumping into others.
You bumped into me first.
You're blind.
What did you rub on my robe?
95% of it is water.
1.1% of it is inorganic salt.
When you don't have disinfectant
to use in the wilderness,
you can use it to clean wounds.
But there's one thing
you need to take note of.
You can only use the middle section.
Ding Yiyuan! Come back!
Don't shout in the hospital.
Qian,
that student of yours, Ding Yiyuan,
why aren't you disciplining her?
What's wrong with her?
She's a great student.
She doesn't respect her senior at all.
She's lucky that she's not my student.
If not, I'll teach her a lesson.
You want to teach her a lesson?
Listen.
Her father
is the hospital's vice president.
Mind your own hygiene.
You shouldn't use so much strength
in the restroom.
Vice president?
You meant Vice President Ding?
(2012 Jiangzhou, China)
Can we make it in time?
What time is the flight?
We can.
But we have to hurry.
Wait, why do you bring
so many pajamas with you?
I'm wearing them in turns.
My manager gave me the notice
out of the blue.
He only approved my leave this morning.
I love sudden trips like this.
Is there anything else
you want to bring?
Forget about me.
Just pack your own belongings.
Is this considered our honeymoon?
No. Honeymoon is more official.
Wait.
Bring your own bag.
Okay.
Forget about the rest. Take your phone.
Great timing.
I just bought a swimsuit,
and I haven't worn it before.
Do you wish to see it?
What? Are you going to wear it now?
Did you bring your swimsuit?
Nope. I only brought my swimming trunks.
Is that okay with you?
Hello?
Got it.
Alright.
What's wrong?
A patient requires emergency surgery.
I'm responsible for him.
I have to rush back.
Mister,
drive us to Beiya Hospital.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
We can go there next time.
You owe me one.
Alright, I owe you one.
♪White clouds will never
miss out on clear skies♪
♪As we waited, we deserve the embrace♪
♪However, we never♪
♪Chose to stay♪
♪We only care about the future♪
♪While the present slips past us♪
♪Before choosing a direction
at the next crossroad♪
♪I let go of your hand out of habit♪
♪Two hearts anticipate approaching each other♪
♪Yet suffer in regrets♪
♪Choosing a direction
at the next crossroad♪
♪Is like tearing the universe apart♪
♪Losing oneself in regret♪
♪Saving oneself with silence♪
♪Before choosing a direction
at the next crossroad♪
♪I let go of your hand out of habit♪
♪Two hearts anticipate approaching each other♪
♪Yet suffer in regrets♪
♪Choosing a direction
at the next crossroad♪
♪Is like tearing the universe apart♪
♪Losing oneself in regret♪
♪Saving oneself with silence♪
♪Choosing a direction
at the next crossroad♪
♪Is like tearing the universe apart♪
♪Losing oneself in regret♪
♪Saving oneself with silence♪
♪That won't do♪