If you really want to be on my side,
prove yourself through
the Task Force.
I'm a businesswoman.
Take and give.
If you prove yourself, I'll be the one
to support you.
Yes.
I understand.
Creating a task force with the
VIP Management Team means
she'll be stopping me publicly.
It seems like Ms. Na is
on the President's side.
I don't like what she's doing lately.
If Ms. Na continues this,
we can't tolerate it.
I'll try talking to her.
My sister's declaring war.
I can't let her take control.
Starting today,
we'll be operating under
the Task Force System.
Let's do our bests.
So we'll be creating
a league just for them.
Social status and reputation...
There might be a strong backlash
without objective standards.
There are a lot of objective
standards we could use.
Level of education,
background, and assets.
Why not figure who's
born legitimately or not?
Just like during Silla era...
Let's come up with the
first round of criteria
and select among the
Black Diamond members.
You have to strike them hard first.
You have to make
an impact at the get-go
to leave an impression.
It has to be memorable for everyone
so others will desperately
try to be one of the 99.
Please think about it on your
own and share your ideas.
The Prestige Team will narrow
down the list for the first round.
No.
I think it'd be more
efficient if we did it.
The VIP Management Team
has more information
on the Black Diamond members.
We've been managing
them until recently.
We'll have to research
everyone individually.
We'll be faster at it, too.
The two teams will
proceed together then.
That's a better way to collect
various opinions and ideas
many people agree on.
Okay then.
That'd be all for today's meeting.
Yes.
Ms. Na, let's talk for a second.
Why is the mood of
this team so cold?
I know, right?
It's like a battlefield.
See you.
Will you tell them today?
Thanks for the hard work.
Likewise.
I'll be seeing you often.
I know.
I know this is uncomfortable.
When the Task Force System ends,
I'll make sure the
VIP Management Team
won't experience any disadvantages.
And I'll make sure you don't suffer
at work because of me.
So please stop now.
Stop what?
Getting involved in the
higher-ups' drama.
You wouldn't have if
it weren't for me.
The VP will try to fight
with full force.
Then you'd get hurt, too.
Don't pretend you care.
I'll manage my own business.
We'll have to see who gets hurt.
VP won't be the only one
to fight full force.
I might end up attacking you.
I think you're mistaken.
You're doing that already.
And I'll surely fight back.
Okay.
But why are you...
insisting on being on the VP's side?
What's going on between you two?
Ms. Na, I have something to tell you.
It hasn't been that long since you
became the team leader.
I'm sorry.
Have you decided to quit?
I'll stay until the end of
the Task Force project.
You must've contemplated
a long time for this decision.
But please reconsider once more.
I'll put the resignation
process on hold for now.
I hope you change your mind.
For both our team and me,
you're an irreplaceable person.
Aigoo.
This lady shops with
her lover so much that
even her lover became a VIP now.
They'll get busted any day since
they're so blatant about it.
He's the president
of Songdam Group.
Of course, he should be included.
He was on probation
for assault five years ago.
I think we should leave him out.
But he's No. 3 in the
Black Diamond list.
The Black Society is
a social group all about
social status and reputation.
President Lee Sang Won even
received a prison sentence
due to a case related to a gang.
We'll leave him out.
Let's do that.
I heard he'll be appointed the
president of Hangook University.
His wife has been bragging all over.
There's barely any
information on Lee Soo Jung.
Lee Soo Jung?
I've never seen her before.
Have you?
No.
Aigoo, someone that the VIP
Management Team doesn't know.
Which store does she frequent?
The Samsung store.
No way I wouldn't know
someone from a prominent family.
What's going on?
One of us should know her
if she's a Black Diamond member.
This member doesn't
qualify. Let's move on.
- Do you know her?
- Yes.
Next person.
We should clarify the
reason for exclusion.
She lives mostly abroad.
If she spends this
much living abroad,
she must spend a ton
whenever she visits.
The VIP Management Team
should've done this alone.
Why call us?
We showed them who's boss today.
This is Na Jung Sun.
Yes.
Got it.
I asked you to come
because of the Black Society
launching event.
Launching event?
This is the concept I decided on.
A fundraiser for the
members' unwed children?
The Black Society
members will become
core figures in politics
and financial circles.
And marriage connections are
one of their biggest interests.
So the purpose of this event is...
It's sort of a matchmaking market.
This world is smaller than
you think, and rumors spread fast.
Opportunities to meet
different candidates are limited.
But if they get a chance like this,
the prominent families in Korea
would kill to get their
children involved.
Of course,
we must know exactly
what they want
and find perfect matches
for them, right?
You'll need this person for that.
Meet with her.
Yes.
Yes, we will.
Take Manager Ha Yoo Ri
to the meeting.
She'd love to come with you.
Since Manager Ha is a
new face who showed up
out of nowhere.
Yes, ma'am.
Hey.
Song Yi Young?
- Do you know her?
- Of course!
She's known as "Midas Song."
The most coveted matchmaker
among the rich ladies.
I heard there isn't a single couple
who didn't go through her
in the world of high society.
So host a party to get
the young wealthy
elites to hooked up?
How provocative. Impactful.
Those rich bastards
are about to join forces
and become even richer.
Geez, darn capitalism.
Mi Na resigned.
So...
she decided to quit?
Yes.
She's seen it all. It's about
time she's sick of it all.
It's a relief if she's
quitting voluntarily,
but if she's not...
Seriously.
Shouldn't the government
support her?
Working while raising kids
shouldn't be a mission impossible.
I know.
If a new level is created,
we'll need a separate
system managing
those members electronically.
We also need a system
to share the information
with the collaborating companies.
Sharing members' information
with other companies
may take time due to security issues.
Which team would be
managing the electronic system?
Prestige team will.
Have you talked it
over with Ms. Na?
That's what Mr. Park wants.
I'll report that to our team as well.
Yes.
Please share the
timeline with us then.
Yes.
Thank you.
I didn't think she'd be like this.
She's acting all high
and mighty already...
She didn't even get the
manager title on her own.
She's way below you in
terms of competence.
It's okay.
You won't have to deal with
this bulls*** much longer.
Let's go.
- This week's system...
- I'll do it.
- On the weekend?
- Yes.
Okay then. Mr. Lee will be on it.
And by chance...
let me do overtime
if there's extra work.
Okay then.
What's this now?
Acting like a workaholic?
I'm the breadwinner now.
I'll make an extra penny.
Aigoo...
Give me any unwanted tasks.
But pay me.
- 20% off.
- Okay, 30%.
You owe me 50,000 won.
- Sorry, forget it.
- Every single penny counts.
I think everything's clean enough.
Please double-check the
number of desserts and wine...
Hi.
Long time no see.
Madam!
How perfect.
You have time, right?
Yes.
It's the customers'
assessment of Joyful Time.
The Conversation Room
got a low rating.
Seriously, Ma Sang Woo...
The AI broke down,
so we used Sang Woo
as AI that day.
I told him to do well,
but he made every kid cry.
I saw your future self, and
you looked happy.
You'll be happy for sure.
What?
Is something wrong?
No.
So, dear...
how have you been?
Yes, pretty good.
In the meantime, it looks like
you became a hotshot.
So hot!
Wow, you became
a totally different person.
I read the article and...
realized that I've
embarrassing myself
with a wealthy elite's daughter.
What's it like...
to have a wealthy dad
all of a sudden?
Are you happy?
I don't know.
Yes, well...
You think money would
fix everything,
but it doesn't.
But still...
it's better than not having any.
Don't you think?
There are lots of nice things here.
May I help you?
Why don't you choose for me?
- Me?
- Let's see...
how much you improved.
Show me what you got.
Yes.
How about something like this?
You have good taste.
The glossy reinforced glass and
stainless steel frame suits
other built-in appliances.
It's our most popular product lately.
We'll visit you on the
day you mentioned
and consult you in person.
Thank you.
All right! Let's go.
Yes, ma'am.
The coffee here is still bitter.
Nothing beats instant coffee.
I wondered about you since
I haven't seen you in a while.
Just because...
Shopping isn't as fun
as it used to be.
I visited my daughter
in Canada recently
and she said...
"You lived your whole life,
trying to satisfy everyone.
But why do you still
worry about others
when you have money?"
When I heard that I felt...
kind of...
s***ty.
Like you said last time,
people judge based
on what they see.
That's right.
But you do look the part.
For some reason,
you became more
sophisticated somehow.
Not at all.
Is it because you're a
wealthy elite's daughter?
You're definitely different.
You already...
became one of them.
How about a drink tonight?
- Dad.
- Yes?
- Are we moving?
- No.
Wait...
- Are we moving?
- I don't know.
I don't know.
Hold this.
Let go.
40 cm.
What are you doing?
I want to change the layout
of Young Joon's room.
I hear changing the layout
for kids improves
their thinking skills.
Do this now?
No, after I quit.
The desk... He'll start
elementary school.
We should get him
a bigger desk, too.
Do it later. You're still working.
Aren't you tired after
working all day?
It's okay.
All right, let's take it slow.
We still have a lot of time,
Ms. Song Mi Na.
That's why.
I'm afraid I'd have too much time.
You're right, let's do it later.
No need to rush.
Young Joon! Seo Joon!
Hey!
Young Joon!
You don't look so happy.
Am I just imagining it?
I just...
don't feel so good today.
Is it me?
No.
It's just...
about work.
Do you want to play?
Loser pays.
Yes!
1:0.
Here I go!
You have to aim this way.
Not that way.
Ice water if you're hot?
How childish.
Geez...
Hold on a sec.
I don't think tying your
hair up will do much.
Hold on a sec!
Okay.
Finally scored!
You finally scored.
So...
is this the last round?
Okay, the last one.
So...
thanks for the drinks.
Are you that happy?
I won.
It feels so great to win.
It's been a while.
To be honest,
I've been feeling very small lately.
I used to think
that I'm the most
successful person
in this whole world at one point.
But...
I'm so pitiful these days.
Earlier today,
I saw Jung Sun in the
team leader's office
and I thought...
"I could've
been where she is
right now."
Since when did I become this?
Will I keep getting smaller
for the rest of my life?
That's why I felt sad.
Is this why people say
looks are deceiving?
I never thought you became small.
But I like that you
just told me that.
Makes you feel human.
You know what?
I contemplated whether I should
text you or not
a million times today.
I worried I'd get rejected again.
I act cool,
but it's all an act.
And...
you're finally feeling small now?
You have a long way to go.
Everyone else became
small way before.
Humans are meant to be pathetic.
Here.
Jin Ho.
Do you want to date me?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You want to date me?
Yes.
With me?
Really?
Why?
I'll think about it.
Think about it then.
Mom, I decided to quit my job.
Aigoo, good thinking.
It's not like your husband
doesn't make money.
I never knew why
you were so antsy.
Just raise your children well.
Kids are important, not work.
You're upsetting me
if you say that, Mom.
I've been trying so hard to
stay there. How about...
all the time I spent trying?
No, that's not what I meant.
You've had it tough
raising kids while working.
Mi Na, are you crying?
No.
Byung Hoon is here.
I'll call you later.
Chairman always favored
Jae Woong since he was a kid.
He always gave him
whatever's best
and whatever's the most expensive.
Father gave me this
position just to scare him
for the time being.
I know that, too.
But I'm not interested
in being used
as a puppet like that at all.
That won't be fun at all.
I'll be attacking Jae Woong.
Too many people belong
to Jae Woong right now.
In order to make people
listen to me,
I should scrape what's there
and set things up again.
Don't you think that
might be too risky?
I know Jae Woong well.
I should attack him
before I get attacked.
So...
which path would you
choose, Mr. Choi?
Are you feeling sick?
It's not a big deal.
I think I have heartburn from
stressing out lately.
It happens sometimes. It's fine.
It's because you have
to keep seeing him.
You should take care
of your health.
You don't seem so well lately.
Thank you.
We're here because we need your
help for our upcoming event.
Ms. Ha Tae Young told me about it.
I heard over 85% of the
couples you matched
end up getting married.
We'd do our best, so this
collaboration would be
a great opportunity for both of us.
Actually, high society couples are
easier to match than
ordinary couples.
You simply have to consider
the material conditions.
Since feelings can be eliminated,
it's more likely that
it'd be successful.
Information is everything to us.
We need an accurate database
to raise the success rate.
So I'm curious about
the two people who are present.
You're the son of the
Foreign Minister Ma, right?
Well, the thing is...
And you're VP
Ha Jae Woong's daughter.
If I'm allowed to
interview these two,
I'll take on the project.
Go ahead.
All I need to do is
answer a few questions.
I'll do it, too.
She wanted to know
everything including
the number of spoons
in our house.
Well done.
You don't have to do it...
if you don't want to.
I want to be helpful.
This is not an interrogation.
Don't be so nervous.
Okay.
Ms. Ha Yoo Ri.
You grew up in the care of
On Hye Sun until you were 28.
When VP Ha Jae Woong of Sung Un
turned out to be your birth father,
you're living under his roof.
Your mother has been
in the nursing home
and passed away recently.
Since VP and his wife
have no children,
Mr. Ha legally adopted you
recently into Ha family registry.
This info pops up just by
searching the internet.
I'll ask you what I want to know
starting now.
What are you looking for
in your future spouse?
I'm not sure.
Just...
someone warm and kind.
That's what On Yoo Ri wants.
Don't you think what
Ha Yoo Ri wants
should be a bit different?
Let me ask you again.
The terms of condition
that Ha Yoo Ri wants...
in a spouse.
What is that?
I'll do it.
I think it's best if Ms. Na
doesn't see you right now.
Here's some painkiller.
Take some for now.
Thank you.
If you send me the
contract, I'll review it
and get in touch with you.
Thank you.
Well, then.
Just one second.
Do you happen to know
Ms. Lee Soo Jung?
She's one of our VIP customers,
but our database had
no information on her.
I thought you might know her.
She's the chairwoman
of the LN Foundation.
You don't have to know
more about her, though.
It'd be tough for her to join
the Black Society anyway.
What do you mean by that?
She's the mistress of
VP Ha Jae Woong of Sung Un.
Pardon?
Even his wife knows
but plays ignorant.
A long-term relationship.
I see.
What are you thinking about?
It's nothing.
Doesn't Sang Woo...
take excellent care of Ms. Na?
Could he be interested in Ms. Na?
Not sure.
Where are we?
The hospital.
I'm fine. I feel better with medicine.
It'll get worse over time.
Thank you, Sang Woo...
for taking care of me so much.
She's the mistress of
VP Ha Jae Woong of Sung Un.
This member doesn't
qualify. Let's move on.
There's probably...
a lot she doesn't know yet.
You should help her
a lot, Soo Yeon.
When I was in middle school,
you told me that...
tigers drop their cubs off the cliff
and keep the ones that survive.
Our family is like that, too.
Shouldn't we apply the
same rule for her, too...
to be fair?
She's definitely your granddaughter.
Rules have to be fair.
If you belong to the Ha family,
you should know how to
gather your own food.
Don't worry, Father.
I'm sure she'd be good at it.
Yes, I'll keep that in mind.
All of you, keep that in mind.
Yes, sir.
Father, have some more fish.
When are you going
back to Boston?
Probably in two weeks or so.
Why don't you guys hang
out before you leave?
When's a good time?
Are you too busy?
Excuse me...
would you like to visit Mom
at the mausoleum sometime?
You didn't get to come
to the funeral.
I think I should make this clear.
To me, your mom is
someone I knew briefly in my 20's.
No more or less than that.
Since you joined the family,
it'd be better for you if you
remove her trace as
much as possible.
Mr. Lee will drive you home.
Happy birthday.
Let's have a meal together today.
You must be hungry.
I'm excited.
I don't know if it's any good.
Thank you so much.
It's good.
Eat a lot.
It's been ten years
someone made me seaweed soup
on my birthday.
Since Mom got hospitalized,
I had no energy to
celebrate my birthday.
Thank you.
I prayed that...
we get to celebrate my
next birthday together.
There's...
a place I want to go to.
Looks delicious.
Everyone, eat as much as you want.
If you sneak alcohol, you're
walking home. Got that?
- Yes, sir!
- Let's eat!
How can you work hard
if you eat like that?
Eat more, okay?
So you can climb your way up.
You're the only one
who cares for me.
What are you thinking about?
Didn't you come to
clear your head?
I know.
The harder I try to clear my head,
the more it gets filled.
How about that bastard?
We're done emotionally,
but we're still together on paper.
Before this...
when I saw women who won't
divorce their cheating husbands,
I thought, "Why hold onto
a dead relationship?"
I couldn't understand it.
But I understand now.
All I have left is hatred.
If I'm going to be unhappy,
I want him to be as
miserable as possible.
It's because it's still not over.
The tip of that knife will
get dull someday.
See the end to it.
You don't know what's at the end,
but it won't be over
until you see the end.
I'll step out for a second.
Mom...
Is it nice over there?
I...
I feel so lonely...
because you're gone.
Now I have a larger family than
just the two of us, but...
I'm lonelier for some reason.
But don't worry too much.
I'll be okay...
since I have him.
Yes, Mother.
I made kimchi.
I'd like to bring you some.
Meet me in front of the
house when I call you.
No, Mother...
No one's home right now.
I'll pick it up later.
Are you out with Jung Sun?
I'll leave it with the security.
Pick it up later.
It'll taste bad if you
leave it out too long.
You have to put it in the fridge now.
There's no room in our fridge.
No.
It's heavy. I'll stop by to get it later.
It's okay. It's not that heavy.
Don't. Please stay home.
I'll call you back after I'm done.
Okay then.
You should go.
Mother is waiting.
Come on in.
Take this with you.
Kimchi turned out well this year.
I gave you plenty.
Give it to your father-in-law, too.
I wonder if he'll like it.
How's Jung Sun feeling these days?
She didn't look so well
last time I saw her.
I found a good herbal
medicine place.
Tell her to come by,
so we can go together.
Mother.
I have something to tell you.
I'm sorry.
What kind of nonsense is this...
Why are you guys getting divorced?
My friend said she
might get a divorce.
Her husband cheated on her,
but he wants to get a divorce.
By chance...
are you seeing another woman?
You're not, are you?
How could you...
Gosh...
How could you do that?
How could you?
You saw how I lived!
How could you do that?
How could you?
She's the mistress of
VP Ha Jae Woong of Sung Un.
Even his wife knows
but plays ignorant.
A long-term relationship.
You don't know what
you've done, do you?
Yes, you couldn't have
done it if you knew.
When you first brought
Jung Sun home,
I was so relieved.
It was because she's
so kind and lovely,
but that wasn't the only reason.
It seemed like she
meant a world to you.
That's why.
I thought, "With her...
he won't live an
unstable life like mine.
He'd live a more grounded life."
That made me so happy.
Yes.
You probably think your
passion is love now.
You know you're
jumping into the fire,
but you can't help it.
Who could I blame?
You just took after your parents.
But you...
lost the whole world
because of momentary feelings.
Right now,
you don't know what you've lost.
You don't know what you've lost.
Thank you for meeting me.
Talk to me.
Last time, you mentioned...
the relationship between the
VP and Park Sung Joon.
Does it have to do with
someone named Lee Soo Jung?
You came to me faster
than I thought.
Park Sung Joon...
takes care of my
husband's mistresses.
He pays them off,
makes them sign
a confidentiality agreement.
Stuff like that.
He's gotten rid of quite a few.
He's pretty good and tidy at his job.
You seem shocked already.
My husband doesn't
trust other people.
But...
I guess he trusts
Mr. Park quite a bit.
My husband...
has stocks under borrowed
names to own more shares.
Mr. Park manages them for him.
Lee Soo Jung and Mr. Park
own them as well.
You didn't know anything
about your husband.
Are you interested in revealing that?
If you reveal...
both adultery and
borrowed-name stocks,
Mr. Park and On Yoo Ri
will both crumble.
Don't you want to...
destroy both of them?
That means the VP will crumble, too.
Park Sung Joon...
takes care of my
husband's mistresses.
He's gotten rid of quite a few.
My husband...
has stocks under borrowed
names to own more shares.
Mr. Park manages them for him.
Lee Soo Jung and Mr. Park
own them as well.
With all that smile on your face
Thinking there's no turning back
And Ill be shameless
Waiting for Hades waltz with you
I want to push you
in the darkness
What a shame on you
I have no idea who you are.
How far will you go?
I wish you'd go all the way.
Let's talk after the event tonight.
- Do you want to grab dinner after?
- Depending on how it goes.
Can't you divorce him?
You two are finished.
Don't come to me again
with stuff like this.
It's none of your business.
- Jung Sun.
- What do I do?
Jung Sun!
Wake up!
With all that smile on your face