What was that?!
You're so dramatic!
He didn't do anything wrong
to me, okay?
I mean, sure, he's a liar.
I'm 100% sure he's not
the Matt I spoke to online.
That's what I said.
Because with Online Matt,
I didn't feel what I felt
with the real Matt.
Why didn't you tell me
you were scammed?
Cha brought it up?
Why are you hiding
so much from us?
Don't tell Aunt Marian
about the scam. Okay?
Especially Dad.
Dude, what? It's too much.
I promise,
I'll come clean by then.
Why do you have to
wait for JR to confess?
What you two are doing
to Cha is mean.
Yeah. Tomorrow I will
tell her everything.
I can't lie anymore, bro.
I'm here at the coffee farm
to meet with Cha.
I will tell her the truth.
Bro, wait!
I thought we had a deal.
Bro, this is the right thing
to do, okay?
Don't worry,
I'll take accountability.
I'm sorry.
Matt!
[CALL DROPS]
Cha!
I think I've already
been cursed.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to tell you everything.
Ah...
You're Cha's suitor.
- Huh? He's not my suitor!
- No.
We're friends.
Have some coffee.
Oh, okay.
Sit down, Matt.
- Have coffee.
- Matt, right?
- That's his name.
- Okay.
Do you want bread?
Someone's here to help you, Cha.
Have some bread.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[GIGGLING] Sorry.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
Knock, knock.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, Cha.
I said, knock, knock.
- Huh?
- Knock, knock.
Uh, who's there?
What kind of coffee
do we have to drink now?
What?
Macchiato.
Why macchiato?
Because makakaya-to
(we can do this).
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
Macchiato.
We can do it.
We can do this.
Are you serious?
[CHUCKLES]
That was horrible.
[CHUCKLES] Really?
Okay, here.
That's all you got?
I got one more.
Knock, knock.
Who's there?
What kind of coffee
is very small?
Very small?
What?
Think about it.
You don't know?
- Nope.
- It's...
Kape-ranggot.
(Small)
[MATT CHUCKLES]
Wait, where did you get that?
[CHUCKLES]
I can't tell you!
- Nice, huh?
- You can't use that anymore.
- Yes, I can.
- No, you can't.
- You can't.
- It's been dried.
You can't grind that anymore.
It's just one piece.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Oh, boy.
Okay, I have one.
What?
What kind of coffee imitates?
I know you already know,
but just pretend you don't.
What?
Kape-cat. (Copycat)
[SARCASTIC LAUGH]
Hey! That was funny!
Compared to your macchiato joke.
What?
- What? [GIGGLES]
- Nothing.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WOMAN] Mr. Corpuz
has spoken to us.
He said that
he won't be renewing
our lease of contract here.
He's considering selling
this property.
What?
But this is where
we operate our businesses.
Exactly.
He didn't mention that to us.
I'm sure he'll
speak to you next.
I just hope he doesn't
evict us immediately.
I hope he gives us enough time.
People can't just
lose their jobs.
This is important
to our daughter.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Let me help you!
- Oh.
- You're our boss for today!
[CHUCKLES] Aw, thank you.
If I get used to this,
I won't let you go home anymore.
[CHA CHUCKLES]
You should get some rest.
- Alright.
- We got it here.
Thank you so much, kids.
You two are such a blessing.
Of course.
It's drying.
Oh, you know what you're doing.
Yes, let's keep drying these.
Of course. We were trained
at work for things like this.
Uh, where can I get
cell service here?
Oh, over on that hill.
Okay, thanks.
Alright. I'll leave you to it.
I'll join you later.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Get rid of all the green ones.
- I know, Cha.
Even the damaged ones.
And the stem.
Just like that.
Here's some more.
[ROOSTER CROWS]
[WHIMSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[WHIMSICAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
What are you doing?
[MATT LAUGHS]
Huh?
Nothing, just being
your human umbrella.
To protect you from the sun.
You don't need to protect me.
I'm used to the heat.
Maybe you're not used to it,
Mr. Rich Kid.
Huh? No way!
I'm not rich.
Okay. Come over here.
- Why?
- Just come here.
Right here!
- Just stand here.
- Why?
- Stay there.
- Okay.
I'll be your human umbrella.
It would be nice
if you actually covered me.
Am I not?
Not really.
[LAUGHS] Sorry.
- Oh, boy.
- Look.
Uh, Cha, you know...
I think you can only
shield a kid.
Seriously?
- What?
- A kid?
- Yeah, that'll work.
- Really?
- Oh, okay... [CHUCKLES]
- It fits you.
- Really, Matt?
- Because you're small... Ow!
[CHA GIGGLES]
Oh, okay!
[EXCLAIMS, GIGGLES]
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
And that will be our marketing
campaign for next year.
So, no questions, I guess?
JR is in a rush to finish.
Uh, I really have to go, Dad.
You've been distracted
the entire meeting.
We have one last meeting
with Matt.
Uh... Yeah. I forgot.
I have to talk to him.
Looks like this meeting is done.
I think so.
Okay. LVS, JR, meeting with
Matt in 30 minutes.
You good?
- Yeah.
- Okay. Thank you!
- Thank you!
- Thank you, sir.
I'll just prepare his materials.
There's strong reception
over here, kids!
Over here, Matt!
I got a few bars here!
"Matt! Don't tell Cha yet!"
"It'll kill me if you do!"
The signal's good here, Matt.
Hey, Matt!
You only have five minutes.
Set up over there!
You don't have to do this, Cha.
I know you're tired
from harvesting.
Come on, it's the least
I can do for you.
It's okay. I can do this.
- Give it to me.
- I got this.
- Give it to me, Matt.
- It's okay.
Don't make this difficult!
Don't worry, I won't go
through your messages.
Give it to me.
Geez.
Matt...
What?
Why?
- Why?
- Why what?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Why do you have
adult videos here?
That's not true!
[GIGGLES]
I saw it.
- The signal's strong!
- Set up already!
- Okay. I'm on it.
- Okay.
The signal's good here.
Hold it up like this.
Like that. Look at this.
There you go.
Wait. I'll set up here.
Alright.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Your arm might get sore.
I'll be okay!
- Okay.
- Just do your thing.
You became
a human umbrella for me,
so I'll be your human cell site.
Wait, let me connect
to my mobile hotspot.
Okay.
Matt has found signal
to access the internet.
He's about to enter
the meeting room.
So that's why I couldn't
reach him.
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
What did she say?
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
I haven't told her yet.
Good.
Thank you.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
[LEANDRO]
What are you talking about?
Uh... Legacy concerns.
Okay. Let's start
the meeting now
so you can loop me in on that.
[MARIAN] Uh...
We can't hear you.
Son? Uh...
Ma? Hold on.
Let me check my signal.
Cha, they said
my video is frozen.
[MATT] I'm frozen.
Hold on, Ma.
Please give me a minute.
- Is that rock stable?
- How about this?
[DIDAY] Careful.
How about now? Better?
Yes, that's good.
Better?
["BIGLAAN" BY DONNY
PANGILINAN PLAYING]
[MATT] Alright!
Good afternoon, team.
I'm pleased to report
that I have spoken...
...to the manager
of Magandang Bahay
and they have confirmed
their agreement
to purchase from that batch.
Now, we will not incur losses
nor do we have spoilage
of the fresh produce.
By the way, what are you doing
there at the coffee farm?
Um...
I'm here to fix something.
Have you fixed it?
Not yet.
But don't worry.
I'll fix it.
Anyway, while we're here,
I would actually like
to make a suggestion
to purchase some of our beans
right here from this farm.
Their traditional methods
of doing things
will actually add an
additional layer of flavor
to our coffee,
which we can include in the menu
of the Legacy café.
Sounds good.
That's aligned with
our branding...
...of using home-grown beans.
That's correct.
Miss Diday!
- Miss Diday, did you hear that?
- Yes.
Looks like you'll have
a new customer!
- Oh my!
- Don't move too much.
He might get disconnected.
[DIDAY] Hold it higher.
Yes, that's it!
Stay still.
["BIGLAAN" CONTINUES]
- O-Ow...
- Okay.
See? I told you not to do that.
Now your shoulder is sore.
But it's all worth it.
Miss Diday gained
a new customer.
Acting tough, huh?
[CHA CHUCKLES]
Here. Let me.
Okay.
Ow.
Does it hurt here?
Mm-hmm.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Sorry.
No, please continue.
Add more pressure.
[CHUCKLES] Okay.
Feel that? It's a little...
- Stiff? [CHUCKLES]
- Yeah.
Why are you so kind
and helpful to me, Matt?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Don't you want that?
No, I like it, of course.
But...
Are you trying to
make it up to me?
Kinda.
Is that really all?
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
What do you want me to say?
What are you supposed to say?
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JR]
Let's just tell her when...
No, bro.
If you really like her,
face her.
You clean up your own mess.
Not me.
Wait, bro. Please. Matt.
Remember this scar?
So, please...
Give this to me.
I really like this girl, okay?
[MATT]
How about this?
I'll convince Cha to meet you
and have dinner with you.
But you have to
confess everything after that.
[POIGNANT MUSIC PLAYING]
[DIDAY]
You remind me of me and Odeng.
We started out as friends too.
He was already helping
my father at the farm.
Um...
Cha?
Hm?
I...
I-I know someone.
I think you'll get along well.
[SULLEN MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS SHARPLY]
Who is it?
A friend of mine.
But he's more like
a brother to me.
Hm, really?
Yeah.
His name is JR.
Well, he's uh...
He's sweet...
generous, spontaneous...
He's fun to be with.
Is he from La Union too?
- Yeah.
- Hm.
JR Valdez.
Your boss' son?
Mm-hmm.
Seriously? I don't like him.
He thinks too highly of himself.
Cha.
He's just...
He's often misunderstood, but...
He's nice.
Of course, you'll defend him.
He's like a brother to you.
I'm just saying...
You'll never know unless
you give it a chance, right?
Who knows?
Maybe you'll click with him.
I think you'd make a great pair.
Are you giving me away?
["HELLO MY LOVE"
INSTRUMENTAL PLAYING]
Why?
Are you mine to give away?
["HELLO MY LOVE"
INSTRUMENTAL CONTINUES]
Oh! Looks like she said yes!
Said yes to what?
Maxie's talking about that guy.
I know what you and JR
were talking about
during the meeting.
I hope you've
told her the truth.
Actually, on the way home,
I forgot to tell her.
Matteo, be honest with me.
Can't you tell her because
you're afraid to lose her?
You deserve to be happy.
You really do.
And I just want you to know,
I promise I will never
hold you back.
Oh, Matt...
Your future girlfriend
will be very lucky.
I just know it.
Matt is lying to me.
How can you be sure
that he is Online Matt?
Matt is low-key
setting me up with his friend.
Why all of a sudden?
Cha?
Hello, Matt?
I want to meet your friend.
You mean JR?
Yes.
I want to be introduced.