Happy anniversary, love.
- Ow!
- What's wrong with you?
Someone catfished as me.
They used my pictures.
A girl claimed we
were in the talking stage.
So Christine thought
I was cheating on her.
"A liar and a two-timer."
Was the girl
who slapped you pretty?
No.
You cheaters will get
your karma too!
Even if you delete
your account...
- You can't fool me again!
- I will find you.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
"Cheater caught in the act.
Busted!"
(QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey!
- Ow! That hurt!
- (CHRISTINE] Oh!
"That's what cheaters get!"
- What's your problem?
- You're my problem!
(CHRISTINE] Wait.
Who are you?!
Who are you?
She's my girlfriend. Why?
- (MATT] Ow! That hurt!
- (CHRISTINE] Oh!
(MATT] What's your problem?
Do you know about this?
Why is our daughter here?
W-Who's that guy with her?
Look. Why didn't we know
about this?
- Honey, wait. Calm down.
- Where is that?
Relax. Calm down.
I'll handle this. Don't get mad.
(QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
Maria Czarina
Theresa Fontanilla!
Who is this?
Who's this guy?
(CHUCKLES] Serves him right.
(MARIAN] No!
We are not taking this
sitting down.
My son is not a cheater.
Now I understand
why he looks like that.
This... This is cyber libel.
This is bullying.
I'll call Mr. dela Cruz,
He's the head
of the NBI Cybercrime.
Ma, I've reported it already.
(VIVIAN] "Serves him right"?
Who is this guy you assaulted?
I just met him online, Ma.
You met online, but you
went on a date with him?!
Oh, no, Pa. It's not a date.
J-Just a meet-up.
(VIVIAN] Meet-up?
Meet-up, hangout, chill...
You just reworded it.
It's still a date.
Cha, seriously?
At the very least, you should've
brought Maxie with you.
You shouldn't meet up
with someone you don't know
by yourself.
What if something
happened to you?
Ma, I'm totally fine, look.
Don't you trust me?
If you want my trust,
you shouldn't be lying to me.
(MATT] Sir.
I'm so sorry
for this misunderstanding.
I really hope this viral video
won't affect our product launch.
I'm going to monitor the cafe
with JR today.
What? I'm going too?
Uh... Yes, Dad.
I'll go with Matt.
Good. It's settled then.
I'm sorry, Ma.
I'm sorry, Pa.
That's enough.
She already apologized.
I want to give you
a piece of my mind too,
but it seems you've had
enough of scolding already.
Besides, you'll be late.
Here's your lunch.
Thank you.
(MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Let me just fix that.
Sorry again, Ma.
Sorry, Pa. I'll get going now.
(PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
(SMACKS]
Your acting is good.
Sir, don't worry.
I got this.
I'll find that guy.
Actually, he deleted
his account,
but luckily,
I took a screenshot.
I already have a clue
about his identity.
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
(WOMAN] Just wipe it up.
- (MATT] Good day!
- Hello.
- I just wanted to ask...
- Hm?
I have a picture of a surfboard.
Is this where you make
boards like this?
Hmm, it seems like
it came from here.
- This?
- Yes.
Do you know who ordered it?
Ah, well, I'm not sure.
But we have an inventory inside.
Do you want me to check?
- Please do.
- Alright, wait a moment.
- Thank you.
- Alright.
Are my braids even?
Cha, we'll be able to pay
all our dues, right?
I'm worried we might have
to close.
Yes! That's why we're doing
manual deliveries, right?
And I've already talked to them,
they agreed to accept
a one-month payment for now.
You know, I'm just scared
we might lose our jobs.
Hey, you know what?
Why don't you pursue your
dream of becoming a drag queen?
- Hey!
- What?
It sounds like you're hinting
I should find a new job.
No, don't overthink it.
(MAN] Hi, free sample.
Sure.
Oh! Coffee!
- Coffee?
- Yes, coffee!
- In fairness, it's good.
- Is it good?
- Yes.
- It's coffee.
It's really good.
(QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
(GROANS]
- It's coffee.
- You're about to finish it.
Okay, okay.
Hold this.
Hold this!
Why? Hey!
Oh my gosh, what are you doing?
- Let me borrow this.
- Whoa.
Hey, give that back to me, okay?
(QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Alright.
Yup, sir, so...
Well...
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
- I'm from La Union.
- Okay.
I studied in Manila,
so maybe that's why
you don't recognize me.
Is that so?
Okay, let me see.
It looks like this design.
It's...
Leandro Valdez.
What? Sir Leandro?
Leandro Valdez Jr.
Yes, that's the design, right?
Yup, that's the one.
That's him.
Anyway, I'll leave you to it.
(PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
(PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
(BARISTA]
Any additional orders?
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
(PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
"Lega-cee: Your refreshing
coffee by the sea."
(BARISTA] Good day, madam.
Great coffee is our legacy.
What's your order, ma'am?
That one.
Hmm. Tall or short?
Just short.
- Short?
- M-mmh.
One short Lega-cee coffee for...
For?
- Your name, ma'am.
- Oh, my name?
- Melody.
(PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Here's your receipt. Thank you.
(PLAYFUL MUSIC SWELLS]
- (MAN] Sir.
- (CHA] Crap!
Oh, where's JR?
(MAN] Wait, sir, I'll call him.
(BARISTA] One Lega-cee
coffee for Melody!
(CHA] Crap!
- (BARISTA] Miss Melody!
- Melody?!
Oh my goodness!
(BARISTA] Miss Melody!
(WHISPERS] Wait!
- Sir!
- Miss Melody!
I'm here, sir! I'm Melody.
Miss Melody?
Miss Melody! Ready to go!
(PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Melody?
- Melody.
- For me?
- Yes, Miss Melody.
- I didn't order this.
- Someone bought you this.
- It's not mine.
- It's for you.
(PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Alright, thanks!
Long time no see.
Hello.
(PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Who are you?
Wow.
I'm the guy you slapped,
remember?
Ah!
Ah, sorry.
I don't talk to strangers,
and if I recall correctly,
you're a cheater.
- I move on fast from cheaters.
- I'm not a cheater.
- I don't know who you are.
- That's what they always say.
If you don't believe me,
that's not my problem,
but seriously, I don't know you.
Mm-hmm.
Ugh!
Why? Why?
(CHA COUGHS]
Is this cough syrup?
Excuse me, this is a one
star drink. It's really sour.
It's so sour. It's so...
Please, be quiet!
What are you doing?
There are customers here! Shh!
Is it my fault it's sour?
- It's not even sour.
- Really?
Really? Is this juice or coffee?
- Hold on.
- Let go of me.
Miss, if you're bitter,
don't take it out on our drink.
(SCOFFS] I'm not bitter,
your drink's bitter.
- Really? You're not bitter?
- Yes! Yes!
Then why are you here
badmouthing our drink?
Miss, come on.
- Don't...
- You know, you're funny.
It's always the ones who lie
who are the boldest
and the most daring, right?
Miss, again, it's not me.
- I don't know who you are.
- Hey, you!
- I can prove it.
- Mr. Matt Flores,
you cheaters...
will get a bald spot.
Their drinks are sour.
Don't order if you can't
handle sour! One star at best!
(MARIAN] Matty.
- Matty.
- Ma.
Dinner with LVS tonight.
He wants to celebrate
your MBA graduation.
Okay.
Have you seen JR?
I've been looking for him.
I've been looking for him too.
(GASPS]
(TROPICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
This is so good!
(WAVES LAPPING]
- (LEANDRO] Congrats, Matt!
- (MATT] Thank you, sir!
Do we really have to celebrate?
(MARIAN] Of course, you're going
to do great things.
That's for sure.
(JR] Of course, you're going to
be another asset in the company.
- See?
- Congratulations, bro!
I can't wait for you to
be my boss instead of Dad.
Speaking of Dad,
if he was here, your dad
would be so proud.
Hey. Are you okay?
Yeah.
But just the fact that
you're here and proud,
that's enough, Ma.
Okay.
- Help me with...
- Before we eat,
I would just like to say
thank you again, sir.
Thank you so much,
from when I started college
to now with my MBA,
- I'm a proud VGC scholar.
- You're welcome.
Yes, thank you, Leandro.
Thank you for everything.
You've helped us so much.
No problem.
You guys worked hard for it.
And besides, it's always good
to invest in people.
(SNAPS FINGERS]
JR.
- Hmm? Yes.
- (LEANDRO] Are you listening?
This is what I mean
when I say good leadership.
Look, the company will
benefit from Matt's MBA.
I actually offered JR
the MBA scholarship,
but he didn't want to.
He just wants to surf.
Well, congratulations to me too.
All I got was another lecture
from Dad.
You think I didn't notice
you weren't at Legacy earlier?
I was there, Dad.
Right, bro?
(STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Yes.
(STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
(LEANDRO CHUCKLING,
CLAPPING]
You two...
Stop covering for JR.
And Matt...
Everybody knows
when you're lying.
And you...
Don't drag Matt into your mess.
Your nose always
causes us trouble. Tsk.
Here.
What's wrong?
This surfboard is yours, right?
(MATT] JR.
I'm sorry.
Why did you use
my pictures to catfish?
You even said you would help me.
What was that all about?
I'm sorry. Okay?
Sorry? Seriously?
Do you want me to beg?
Bro, I got canceled
because of you.
Well, bad publicity
is still publicity.
Christine and I broke up.
(JR] At least, you found out
that you're not meant
for each other.
I got slapped... twice!
Now, you have red cheeks to
match your red nose. Perfect!
Bro, please be serious.
Why did it have to be me?
Seriously?
(MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Well, if I had used
my real identity,
I would have had
zero chance with her.
I can't believe it.
This is so stupid.
Exactly. I'm stupid.
I'm not as good or
as impressive as you.
Maybe I don't feel like
being myself is worth anything.
(MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I just wanted to be seen
by the girl I like.
And if I have to use you
just to be seen by her...
You're crazy.
When she meets you,
even if you're a fool...
she'll be interested in you.
(SCOFFS]
Nope. She got turned off
when she found out
I'm Leandro Valdez Sr.'s son.
Wait.
Did you tell Cha that
you weren't the one
she was chatting with?
Bro, please.
Don't tell her, okay?
Bro.
Bro, wait, hold on.
Just let me think.
Please.
She's too important, okay?
(EXHALES SHARPLY]
Or better yet,
let's just keep it up.
Let's just tell her later
when...
No, no.
(MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
If you really like her,
face her.
You clean up your own mess.
Not me.
(BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
(CHA] Ugh.
Dear, go to sleep now.
I'll sleep after this.
(BRIGHT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Oh my, it fell on the floor!
(CHA] Mommy...
I'm sorry.
I just didn't want you
to worry about me.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Your father is the one
you should worry about.
He almost exploded with anger
when he saw the viral video.
Don't wait for him to get angry.
You know how he is.
All hell breaks loose
when he gets angry.
Even his hair falls out.
(CHUCKLES]
How about you?
Are you angry?
(SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Slight.
Because you're so gullible.
That's why you easily
get fooled.
You know, trust...
That has to be earned.
It shouldn't be given for free.
Mommy...
I've learned my lesson.
- Are you sure?
- (CHA] Yes!
- Yes?
- Sure!
Very, very, very sure.
Okay. Come here.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
(MAN 1] Sir, the rumor's true.
It's really good.
- Good morning, team!
- Put that away.
- What's up?
- (MAN 2] Sir. (CHUCKLES]
- Good morning.
- Thank you.
- Uh, sir...
- Yep?
Our sales have been declining
in the last few days.
- Hm?
- Here.
(QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
Was this during
the last three days?
Yes, sir.
How did this happen?
Apparently, someone copied us.
And theirs is cheaper.
(QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Thank you, ma'am!
Please post about us
on social media.
Thank you.
Thank you, sir!
Post about us, okay?
Please use the hashtag,
#CORANGEbyAyat.
- Where can I get these?
- Girls, thank you so much.
- Thank you.
- Bring your friends next time.
- See? Thank you!
- Thank you so much.
Please come again!
(SQUEALING] Yes, please!
I told you, didn't I?
(MAXIE] Girl, look.
("NAMUMULA" INSTRUMENTAL
PLAYING]
(MAXIE] Would you like to order?
("NAMUMULA" INSTRUMENTAL
CONTINUES]
Hm?
I don't need your apology.
If you want our new drink,
Co-range,
go line up over there.
And no cheater's discount
for you, okay?
I understand.
Look, what happened to you
was wrong.
And I know you don't want
to hear this from me,
but you really deserve
an apology for what happened.
What's that? A bribe?
Just please give me
a chance to explain myself.
Cha.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Hm?
It was a confusing night for me.
I knew that something was wrong
between me and Christine.
I just didn't know what it was.
Your slap was
a blessing in disguise.
Blessing?
Yeah.
She took it as a sign
to pursue her calling
as a missionary.
(SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Look.
I'm very sorry.
And I hope you can give me
another chance.
Please?
(SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
We're closed.
I know. I came
from work, too.
I was just hoping
you were still here.
For what?
Nothing. I just want
to chat with you.
That girl in the viral video
slapped you, right?
So why are you still with her?
She's also a victim
of catfishing, Ma.
Oh my god.
Do you like her?
(UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]