[English subtitles are available]
[Moon Love]
[Girl Missing]
As the saying goes,
"Nothing ventured, nothing gained."
Let me give it a try this time.
Where are you going?
It's so late. Why are you still on the streets?
Well, I want to help you
find Miss Zixi of the Wen family
to prove
that her missing has nothing to do with you.
Help me?
Why are you so confident you'll be able to help me?
I'll know only if I give it a try.
Besides,
I suspect this case has something to do with the renegade immortal.
Aren't you afraid of the renegade immortal?
Why do you still want to find the renegade immortal?
That's because
I want to help you solve this tricky case.
Let's make an agreement.
If I can find vital clues to the case,
you will allow me...
To stay in Imperial Censor's Mansion?
Dream on!
My Lord.
I think the agreement has been made.
Don't go back on your word.
[Episode 4]
Anyone here?
Any immortal here?
Please say something. Don't scare me.
Are you a mortal or an immortal? Tell me your name.
Brother Xie.
Why do you guys
like to come here late at night ?
I came to Imperial Censor's Mansion not long ago.
And then such a big case happened.
I must investigate it carefully.
In Qingzhou City,
there are very few officials
as responsible as you.
When I was investigating just now,
I found a suspicious person.
So,
I followed her all the way.
I've caught her.
Is it me?
You live in the morgue
and now you're investigating the case in the middle of the night.
You're really different from others.
Actually,
I'm doing this because I want to stay in Imperial Censor's Mansion.
If I can solve this case,
it means I'll do His Lordship a big favor.
Then
he won't refuse to let me stay in Imperial Censor's Mansion.
You want to stay in Imperial Censor's Mansion?
There seems to be nothing unusual here.
There is only
a shoe
and a lamp.
If no one else saw them
and only the two Wen sisters were chosen,
I'm afraid
the two sisters really turned against each other.
Don't scare people.
What's wrong, Zhaoyan?
There's
no one else here.
Nothing.
Brother Xie.
Go on with your patrol.
I'll go somewhere else and have a check.
Zixi.
Zixi, where are you?
Are you playing hide-and-seek with me?
If you are, please show up now.
We're all very worried about you.
Zixi.
If Wen Zimo harmed Wen Zixi,
how come she is here looking for her sister in the middle of the night?
Stop!
Are you okay?
Don't be afraid.
It was
just a strange wind.
Let me help you up.
The past of the renegade immortal
must have something to do with the Chuxiu House.
To find out what happened in Chuxiu House in the past,
I'll have to go to Imperial Censor's Mansion and find related documents.
[Imperial Censor's Mansion]
My Lord.
My Lord!
Oh no.
I shouldn't have let His Lordship go earlier just now.
It's so late now.
His Lordship won't come out to see me.
What's the matter?
My Lord.
You heard me?
My Lord, I have something urgent to tell you.
You may not believe it,
but I think
Miss Wen's missing
has something to do with the renegade immortal.
My Lord.
I've told you many times
that you can't just vanish
and then pop up.
Oftentimes, you suddenly fly up to the sky
and scare people.
People will know you're a god if you do it too often.
You are Moon God.
You observed the mortal world for so long in the heaven.
Can't you learn
how to be an ordinary mortal?
I...
My Lord.
People in Qingzhou City worship Moon God,
but if Moon God really shows up in front of them,
they'll be shocked.
Immortals and mortals are different.
Can't you be like me?
Look at me.
I never let others know my identity.
Are you done?
In a word,
you can never let any mortal know your identity.
More importantly, you can never let them know you're Moon God.
Oh no.
I violated the heavenly rule.
Miss Zhaoyan now knows I'm from the heaven.
Why was she there?
My Lord, why didn't you tell me earlier?
What are you afraid of?
She knows who we are now. So what?
I've violated the heavenly rule.
I'll be killed because of it.
Of course you don't have to be afraid at all.
But I'm just a tree.
How can I not be afraid?
I have an idea.
If we kill her,
then no one will know who we are.
My Lord.
Don't joke about it.
His Lordship
is Moon God.
I though it should be Moon Goddess.
So the imperial censor is Moon God.
My goodness.
In that case,
His Lordship is the one who gave me the eyes.
I said so many stupid things.
Will His Lordship
stop blessing me because of that?
Are you really Moon Goddess?
My Lord.
You're indeed Moon God.
But
shouldn't Moon God be in the heaven?
How come you are...
I got it.
You must have done something bad
so you were sent to the mortal world
as a punishment.
None of your business.
Well.
I have only one chance
to return the eyes
in my life.
No matter what,
I need to stay with His Lordship.
[Chuxiu House]
Miss Immortal?
Are you here?
Please show up.
I want to ask you some questions.
Why are you always here?
[Yiling]
Have you ever seen Zixi?
You know where she is, right?
Can you tell me where she is?
Zimo?
God bless us.
Don't let Zixi enter the palace.
Sister, here.
[Zimo]
You think
Zimo wanted to hurt Zixi?
So you think you are protecting Zixi?
But the two sisters are very close.
You know that Zimo has been looking for Zixi
these days.
Why do you think Zimo wanted to hurt Zixi?
Is it because you experienced something similar in the past?
Yiling.
Yiling, wake up.
Wake up!
So,
in your memory,
your roommate Tianyu
left you in the fire
and ran away.
And you were stuck here
because of your hatred.
Miss Immortal.
Please tell me where Zixi is first.
She has nothing to do with what happened to you in the past.
How about this?
Tell me where she is.
I'll help you
to get over the past.
The selection of imperial concubines is very important.
The Wen family will be punished if Miss Wen can't be found.
You don't want to
hurt innocent people,
right?
[Imperial Censor's Mansion]
So the living hall of Imperial Censor's Mansion
is in this style.
It's totally different from the style of the bedrooms.
Zhaoyan.
[List of Candidates for Imperial Concubines]
This might help you.
[Xiayan]
[Tianyu]
So that renegade immortal's name is Yiling.
[Yiling]
In the spring of Year Thirty-Three,
when the final selection of imperial concubines was going to held in Shengjing,
Chuxiu House caught fire.
[Yiling]
The fire burnt down a room in the house.
It was found that Yiling, a candidate for the imperial concubines, lived in the room
and that the fire was caused when she was burning joss papers.
Yiling died in the fire.
Her roommate Tianyu survived.
Tianyu was Yiling's roommate.
Tianyu
didn't enter the palace after the accident.
Thank you, Brother Xie.
Thank you very much.
This is very important to me.
I'm glad it can help you.
Well,
let’s investigate it together.
If I suddenly tell Brother Xie
that I want to investigate Yiling's case,
he'll definitely suspect me.
Don't bother.
You should keep looking for Zixi.
But
isn't this a clue to Zixi's case?
It's a long story.
I'll explain to you later.
Bye.
My Lord.
I think I saw Miss Zhaoyan.
Is she here to ask you
about Moon God?
I won't be afraid if she asks me about that.
My Lord.
I'm not afraid of her.
But she knows our identities now.
How about we stay away from her
to avoid any trouble?
She's not capable enough to get us into trouble.
Besides, she sneaked into Imperial Censor's Mansion.
I'll punish her for that.
Yun Zhaoyan!
Come out!
Hurry!
[List of Candidates for Imperial Concubines]
I...
I'm here to find clues to the Wen family's case.
[List of Candidates for Imperial Concubines]
Don't worry.
I didn't tell anyone about your identity.
But don't forget your promise.
[List of Candidates for Imperial Concubines]
Now I have got a clue.
I'll continue to investigate the case now.
Just pretend
you never saw me today.
You...
My Lord.
So Miss Zhaoyan
came to investigate the Wen family's case.
She knows she's not welcome here,
but still took the risk and came in.
Looks like Miss Zhaoyan
is very determined to stay in our mansion.
My Lord.
If she can solve the case
and become your subordinate,
then she'll never tell anyone about our identities.
You're talking nonsense too.
This is where Tianyu lives.
It seems that
she's not leading a very decent life.
Have a seat.
Excuse me.
Are you Tianyu?
Who are you?
You just take me as someone from Imperial Censor's Mansion.
[Tianyu]
I'm here to ask you some questions.
Do you remember
Yiling from ten years ago?
Why are you asking this?
Back then,
you and she shared one room in Chuxiu House.
I'm sure you know
what happened in that fire accident, right?
I don't remember any of it.
Miss, please leave.
Let me tell you,
Yiling is still in Chuxiu House.
No way.
Tianyu.
You didn’t get to enter the palace
because of the burns
on your hands, right?
Trust me.
Yiling has been waiting for you in Chuxiu House.
Stop talking nonsense.
Otherwise, I'll teach you a lesson.
I'm not lying.
Yiling wants to know
why you left her and ran away.
She...
She's still blaming me?
She is still blaming me. I knew it.
That fire was an accident.
I didn't abandon Yiling.
Tianyu.
Yiling still cannot get over the past
so she has been stuck in Chuxiu House all the time.
I'm sure you know that
Zixi, second daughter of the Wen family
went missing in Chuxiu House.
It's very possible that her disappearance has something to do with Yiling.
You're the only one
who's able to save her.
What can I do?
I'm sure you have a lot
to tell Yiling.
Trust me this time.
I'll take you to her.
Yiling.
Yiling, wake up.
I'll get someone to put out the fire.
Hang in there. Wait for me.
After that accident,
this place
was made into Jing'an Hall
[Jing'an Hall]
in memory of Yiling.
I see.
Since then,
you've never come back?
I'm too ashamed of myself to come back.
I'm afraid
Yiling doesn't want to see me.
[Jing'an Hall]
Yiling.
I think you've recognized her.
Tianyu.
Yiling is right in front of you.
She has been waiting for your explanation.
Over the past ten years,
she has been stuck in Chuxiu House.
She couldn't let it go.
Yiling.
Yiling, are you really here?
It's been ten years.
I missed you so much, but I didn't dare to think of you too much.
I didn't dare to come to Jing'an Hall.
Your memorial tablet is here.
I was afraid you didn't want to see me.
This place
is like a prison.
We've been imprisoned here for our entire lives.
I didn't abandon you back then.
I went to find someone to put out the fire.
But I was too late.
I got these scars on my hands
at that time.
All these years,
I rarely go out
because of these scars.
I do odd jobs
for a living.
Yiling.
Don't let the hatred in the past
bother you anymore.
Fire!
Help!
Why is there such a big fire?
Zixi is in Jing'an Hall?
Where is Zixi?
Zixi...
Zixi is inside.
Zixi!
I'm coming.
Zixi, are you here?
Zixi!
Tianyu.
Bring people to put out the fire.
I'll go save them.
Zixi!
Zixi! Zixi!
Are you here?
Zixi.
Zixi's here!
Zixi!
Zixi.
I've finally found you.
Wake up, Zixi.
Wake up, Zixi!
Now.
We have to get her out first.
Come.
Zimo!
Keep going.
Take my sister out first.
Wait for me.
I'm coming.
Hang in there.
I didn't abandon you back then.
I went to find someone to put out the fire.
But I was too late.
Be careful.
Why is the fire so big?
Help!
My Lord.
♫It's hard to distinguish what's good and what's evil, and it's hard to love or hate someone♫
♫We meet and part, coming to nothing♫
♫Regardless of the chaos and fate♫
♫I only love you with deep affection♫
♫I'm a lonely person and tears trickle down my face♫
♫I dare not face so much sorrow♫
♫Puzzled, I'm too sad to play the guqin under the moon♫
[Jing'an Hall]
♫I want to hear you talk about romantic things♫
Zixi.
Sister.
Don't be afraid.
I'm here.
It's all my fault.
You are a lively girl
who dislikes restrictions.
I'm afraid that if you live in the palace,
you'll have a hard time.
So I made a wish to the Buddha statue,
saying that I hope you won't be selected to enter the palace.
Luckily, I found you.
Sister.
I accidentally fell into the basement.
It has nothing to do with you.
The reason why
I wanted us to enter the palace together
is because I don't want to be apart from you.
Okay.
I'll always be with you.
Here, Zixi.
[Jing'an Hall]
Yiling.
I failed to save you from the fire back then.
Today, I saved the Wen sisters.
I think
I can let it go now.
Yiling.
Let it go.
I'm free now.
I hope you can be free, too.
♫In my dream♫
♫I jumped and forgot myself♫
♫Hearing whispers of mountains and rivers in the mortal world♫
♫The sea is infinite, and I returned to this old place♫
♫Mayflies are most afraid of being affectionate♫
♫They spend the rest of their lives separately♫
God Taiyin.
Return to your position.
[Waxing Crescent Moon]
My Lord.
Looks like the moon phase is a little fuller.
[Chuxiu House]
This is great.
Miss Zhaoyan found Miss Wen.
Thanks to her, the rumors won't be able to bother you anymore.
My Lord.
Miss Zhaoyan
is really like what her name suggests.
She is as bright as the sunrise.
Let's go.
Shouldn't we wait for Miss Zhaoyan?
No need.
My Lord.
As promised,
you have to let Miss Zhaoyan stay in Imperial Censor's Mansion.
She helped you.
You have to keep your promise.
Am I right, My Lord?
Let's go.
I don't want to see any light anymore.
My Lord, you...
My Lord.
Will you keep your promise?
I will go to Imperial Censor's Mansion and stay there.
My Lord, check this out.
Why did I have such a dream?
My Lord.
You can have dreams?
It's probably because Yun Zhaoyan
has been pestering me these days.
That's why I had a nightmare.
As a saying goes, "In the night,
you'll dream about what you were thinking in the day."
Shut up.
My Lord.
A lady surnamed Yun
asked someone to send a message to you.
Why is it her again?
My Lord.
Miss Zhaoyan
went to see a girl
who got hurt in the fire accident
a few years ago in Chuxiu House.
I think she might
have found some clues.
Are you really not going to
to have a check
according to Miss Zhaoyan's message?
She's full of nonsense.
Who knows whether she's lying or not?
I won't go.
Zhaoyan.
You're finally back.
I heard that something bad had happened to Miss Zimo.
I was worried you would be in danger too.
Have you found any clues?
I'm fine.
And I did find some clues.
Brother Xie.
Please help me investigate someone.
Why are you following me?
My Lord, it's not safe outside tonight.
I dare not go back to the morgue alone.
Do you want to spend the night
in Imperial Censor's Mansion again?
Don't be afraid.
I've sent
a group of soldiers to patrol.
No place is safer
than Qingzhou City tonight.
Besides, you've been with me for so long.
No renegade immortal will dare to approach you again.
Fine.
You are right.