[English subtitles are available]
[Moon Love]
[Episode 24]
[Xiaoxiang Pavilion]
My Lord.
It seems that
it's not proper for us to go in and disturb them.
Zhaoyan,
sorry.
Being with me
makes you full of regrets.
In Qingzhou City,
I clearly remember
what we did and where we did it.
Being able to meet you
has made up for all my regrets.
Yun Zhaoyan,
we will meet again.
Trust me.
[Governor's Mansion]
Mr. Governor,
Lord Ren and Miss Yun sent this.
They left without leaving a word.
It seems that Ren Shique
really left.
I did tell you to retreat to the mountains and forests,
but I...
I was just saying.
Now that you've left,
what's the fun
of me being the Governor here?
My Lord,
are you really not going to
give it back to him face-to-face?
No. Forget it.
If I go to him when he's like that,
it might cause trouble.
My Lord, what's wrong?
Didn't you say
men and women who make wishes on the Broken Bridge
would part in the end?
I've made a wish to the moon.
The Moon God will hear my prayers.
My Lord, you've said goodbye
to everyone else.
Now,
say goodbye to me.
But
I have a little wish
that I haven't told you yet.
You have more wishes than others.
What is it?
I'm sorry that I'm not able to see
where you're going.
You can't
go to that place casually.
You're right.
Yun Zhaoyan,
you are the biggest challenge I've faced
since I came to the mortal world.
Remember,
don't be afraid of what your eyes give you.
And cherish yourself
who has these eyes.
After a hundred or a thousand years,
I will forget you completely.
In my long life,
you're like a grain of sand
that has leaked through my fingers.
That's the best.
I hope when you
occasionally think of me a few years later,
you'll take me
as an ordinary mortal
who has made a wish
under your radiance.
Forget it.
You have been complaining about the Moon God's eyes for ten years.
Look, among all the people of Qingzhou City,
you are the most disrespectful to me.
My Lord.
You...
You should go.
My Lord, we meet again.
♫It's hard to distinguish what's good and what's evil, and it's hard to love or hate someone♫
It's you?
♫We meet and part, coming to nothing♫
♫Regardless of the chaos and fate♫
My Lord.
♫I only love you with deep affection♫
♫I'm a lonely person and tears trickle down my face♫
♫I dare not face so much sorrow♫
She's from the Imperial Censor's Mansion.
♫Puzzled, I'm too sad to play the guqin under the moon♫
You should apologize to her.
♫I want to hear you talk about romantic things♫
♫In the cold moonlight, I'm willing to go to you♫
♫In the dim worldly affairs, my heart warms for one person♫
♫I'd rather endure numerous hardships with all my courage♫
I brought her in.
♫I won't retreat, I'll swallow the regrets♫
I will invite her back soon.
♫In the cold moonlight, I put on clothes for you♫
Yun Zhaoyan,
I've developed worldly desires for you.
♫The brush strokes may fade, but the love remains unchanged♫
♫We keep each other company hand in hand, leaving everything behind♫
Watch out.
♫We live a happy and leisurely life in this world♫
Looks like this distance
is the safest.
Yun Zhaoyan.
With me by your side,
you don't have to fear anything.
♫I'm a lonely person and tears trickle down my face♫
♫I dare not face so much sorrow♫
♫Puzzled, I'm too sad to play the guqin under the moon♫
♫I want to tell you my love♫
♫In the cold moonlight, I'm willing to go to you♫
In the center of the Mirror Pool is the heart of the moon.
There,
are kept
♫In the dim worldly affairs, my heart warms for one person♫
all the wishes of those who pray to the moon.
On this moon,
♫I'd rather endure numerous hardships with all my courage♫
I've lived for hundreds of years,
but I've never fulfilled anyone's wish.
♫I won't retreat, I'll swallow the regrets♫
Except you.
♫In the cold moonlight, I put on clothes for you♫
♫The brush strokes may fade, but the love remains unchanged♫
♫We keep each other company hand in hand, leaving everything behind♫
So,
♫We live a happy and leisurely life in this world♫
I've been to
where His Lordship is staying long ago.
[One year later]
I got it!
I've got something, too.
Guigui, you ruined my plan again.
I ruined your plan?
If His Lordship hadn't assigned me here
to help guard Qingzhou for you,
do you think I want to
fish with an old man like you every day?
Old man?
Are you calling me, a man in the prime of life, an old man?
Yes, I was talking about you.
You...
You've been with Ren Shique for more than ten years, right?
He is the Moon God.
I wonder which one between us is older.
Keep your voice down.
The real identity of Ren Shique and my age
are both unspeakable.
I can hold my tongue,
only if you pour your basket of fish
back.
You...
You are unreasonable!
I'm not fishing today!
If you dare to leave, I'll deduct your salary!
You're no longer the City Governor.
Why are you still trying to exercise your authority?
[Governor's Mansion]
Governor!
Governor.
[March 3]
Governor, bad news.
The former Governor quarreled with someone by the lake.
It seems serious.
No need to report such trivial matters again.
How about the areas around Qingzhou? Are they okay?
After last year's
tidal disruption near the city,
nothing abnormal happened again.
Okay.
Remember to patrol every night,
just like when the Imperial Censor was here.
Yes, Governor.
Qing.
Honey.
You've been reading for a long time.
Your back will hurt again if you keep sitting on like this.
Let me help you out for a walk.
Be careful.
Qing.
[Holding the Jade]
You've been pregnant for months.
Are you still going to deal with the affairs in the mansion?
The people of Qingzhou City love me so much.
Of course I can't escape.
Honey, don't worry.
I've been practicing martial arts since I was young.
I'm very strong.
You're going to be a mother,
yet you are still so careless.
By the way, Honey,
do you know what day it is today?
Today?
Today
is the 15th.
The Moon Worship Ceremony is coming soon.
Yes.
It's been a year since Ren Shique left.
And Zhaoyan has been waiting for him for a year.
Stop following me.
I haven't slept all night.
Let me have a good sleep.
Yun Zhaoyan.
Aren't you getting up yet?
My Lord?
Yun Zhaoyan.
Not only are your eyes special,
but your ears can also hear strange sounds now.
It's been more than 300 days
since I met His Lordship.
I wonder if His Lordship is doing well
on the moon.
I want to see him so bad.
Another day when His Lordship is
not in the Imperial Censor's Mansion.
Miss Zhaoyan.
Guigui?
Shouldn't you
be fishing
with the Governor at this hour?
He's really not worth my friendship.
The Immortal Wu Tu you mentioned before
should be very similar to the Governor, right?
It turns out to it's a thousand years of fate.
What fate?
If I hadn't disobeyed two bans of the Heaven Emperor
to help you and God,
I wouldn't have ended up in the mortal world
and be stuck with the Governor every day.
Guigui.
What are you thinking about?
I'm thinking about a selfless Laurel God.
To make a good love story come true,
he plunged into deep distress.
What a touching story!
Guigui.
I brought you soup.
I'm coming.
It seems
there's more to it than the distress.
Miss Zhaoyan, I'm leaving.
Wait.
I have something to ask you.
Have you
heard His Lordship's voice recently?
Miss Zhaoyan, you'd better not overthink.
Yeah.
I was overthinking.
How could His Lordship come back?
Do you know me?
I remember faintly.
Faintly?
It seems that Chang Xi
left you that memory, anyway.
It's hard to say goodbye.
The memories of the Moon Palace
are precious to me.
But going to the Moon Palace is already a blessing.
I won't leak it out.
Are you sure you're ready
to be separated from Chang Xi for a long time?
His life is still long,
while yours is fleeting.
Do you still want to be alone,
waiting for
a result in an indefinite future?
When I decided to be together with His Lordship, alive or not,
the results don't matter anymore.
Because we have love and courage in our hearts,
no matter how hard it is, we'll go on together.
Every moment I spent with my loved one,
the warmth of our holding hands,
and the heartbeats when we looked at each other
will all become the reasons for us to stick to it.
It seems that
you're not afraid of those renegade immortals anymore.
They look scary,
and they always appear out of nowhere,
but I know
they are kind people with obsessions.
If I can help them get over their emotional knots,
I'll be doing something good within my capability.
But sometimes,
you need to learn to go easy on yourself.
Go easy on yourself…
You little girl.
In the end,
are you talking about you and that guy,
or are you talking about me and Kui Ji?
Actually,
your love for Kui Ji
is no weaker than His Lordship's love for her, right?
You let her exist forever in the form of petals
because you hope
the thoughts in your heart will never disappear.
Am I right?
Are you, a mortal girl,
instructing me?
I dare not.
I'm just talking about the perfectly happy things in the mortal world.
Perfectly happy things?
What is
a perfectly happy thing in this world?
You need to have the courage to be kind
and wait quietly.
The perfectly happy things that belong to you will come eventually.
It seems that Chang Xi
picked the right girl.
I've been limited by my status,
so I had too much love that I couldn't protect.
You should
be happier than me.
Kui Ji,
this is where we met and got to know each other.
Our son Chang Xi
has got his happiness.
You can rest in peace now.
Kui Ji,
you've been trapped by Chang Xi and me all your life.
Now,
go to the place
where you can feel the most happiness and liberty.
You're back so early today.
People all like happiness in perfection.
So, naturally, they love the full moon.
But I
am waiting for the dark moon every month.
I wonder
how His Lordship is doing now?
I fell on your boat.
Why didn't you even give me a hand?
You're a man.
How can you be so delicate?
But you...
Why are you here at this hour?
To see the moon.
Oh.
Did you make a wish to the Moon God again?
My Lord, why are you here?
I still have unfulfilled wishes in the mortal world.
I need your help.
You mean…
you've become a renegade immortal?
Hush.
Don't tell anyone.
Only you can see me.
I sneaked down.
What?
Are you still afraid of renegade immortals?
Of course not.
♫I'm willing to become a breeze in the world♫
♫I'll be with you in a dream♫
♫Maybe in this life I came to meet you♫
♫So we should sing for the world♫
♫Although the world is beautiful♫
♫I'm only moved by you♫
Daohuang, you sure know how to be kind.
How dare you extend a red thread to the mortal world
so that the secluded Moon Palace can be traced now?
Now, God Taiyin left the palace by that.
Do you admit your crime?
Heaven Emperor.
Now, there's a new renegade immortal of the moon phase,
and the world is peaceful,
why should we even trap
God Taiyin, whose heart is already in the mortal world?
When did you two become of one mind?
Heaven Emperor, didn't you hint it to me
after you came back from the mortal world?
Why did you go back on your word?
Nothing here has changed.
After you left,
Guigui took care of everything every day.
Come here.
My Lord, why are you doing this?
Hush. Don't talk for now.
But you're a renegade immortal.
They can't see you.
Yes.
But...
I sneaked down from the Moon Palace,
so it's better not to show up
openly in front of everyone.
Zhaoyan,
you'll cover for me, right?
I will.
My Lord, look!
It's the full moon. The full moon is out!
Hurry!
My…
My Lord.
Tell me now.
How did you escape from the Moon Palace?
I should thank the renegade immortal Daohuang for that.
Now that the world is peaceful,
will you go back again?
There are still renegade immortals wandering in the mortal world.
I will be by your side.
However,
I have something unfinished.
What is it?
Ren Shique?
My Lord, you're back.
My Lord.
You lied to me.
I...
Stop running!
You are the Imperial Censor. How could you fool me?
I will not let you off this time.
My Lord.
I want to be with you forever.
All my life.
Forever.
Okay.
♫It's hard to distinguish what's good and what's evil, and it's hard to love or hate someone♫
Then, let's
be together forever.
♫We meet and part, coming to nothing♫
♫Regardless of the chaos and fate♫
[Huixin Hall]
This is the story of me, Yun Zhaoyan.
His Lordship and I have been parted in life and separated by death.
♫I only love you with deep affection♫
[Huixin Hall]
We've also been through thick and thin in the world.
We could finally be together at this moment.
♫I'm a lonely person and tears trickle down my face♫
The moon appeared in Qingzhou again and protected the mortal world
♫I dare not face so much sorrow♫
[Liked by Many Customers]
because I barged in.
Because of the love from the moon,
♫Puzzled, I'm too sad to play the guqin under the moon♫
I was able to keep my true heart
and live a peaceful life.
Now that I recall everything in the past,
♫I want to hear you talk about romantic things♫
I feel if one does good deeds for others,
you will be repaid with love.
Be careful.
♫In the cold moonlight, I'm alone in the long night♫
May all the lovers in the world
can be as happy as you're shone by the moonlight
or the morning sun.
♫The bitterness of lovesickness is only related to you♫
♫We feel lonely at different places, seeming to be separated by a tall mountain♫
♫In the vast galaxy, we are unwilling to part, and everything's fallen into the darkness♫
♫In the cold moonlight, the flower petals have fallen♫
♫In the pervading mist, who can I express my bitterness to♫
♫May a turn in fate bring fulfillment to our love♫
♫Don't let the entanglement between us turn into nothing♫
♫In the cold moonlight, I'm willing to go to you♫
♫In the dim worldly affairs, my heart warms for one person♫
♫I'd rather endure numerous hardships with all my courage♫
♫I won't retreat, I'll swallow the regrets♫
♫In the cold moonlight, I put on clothes for you♫
♫The brush strokes may fade, but the love remains unchanged♫
♫We keep each other company hand in hand, leaving everything behind♫
♫We live a happy and leisurely life in this world♫