@sevirous: I’m okay.
My body’s just a bit sore.
@sevirous:
Because I fell for you.
Sevi’s amazing, huh?
You want to know why?
It’s because he’s inspired…
Because of you.
- Really?
- Really!
I think he really likes you.
I’m really nervous.
Believe in yourself.
That’s why you’re
the only one for me.
Just one word from you
and I feel more confident.
Wear this for Game 2, okay?
I don’t think I can, Sev.
I’m sorry.
Is this okay?
You know I can’t
ruin the surprise.
Don’t worry about it.
It will all be worth it once
he sees your banner.
Elyse?
- Hi, Dad.
- Hi.
We’re just—
Working on a new project.
Can I take a look at it?
Don’t be shy.
I just want to see it.
Alfred?
You’re here.
Come, I’ll prepare your food.
I’ll win this for you.
I like you, Sevi.
It looks good, right?
Yes.
- Can you taste it?
- Sure.
That’s a mouthful!
Why the hell is this so salty?
Huh?
It tastes like seawater.
Seawater?
Yes!
I guess I put a lot of salt…
You think?
Is this what you're
going to feed Sevi?
He might just go home instead.
What are we going to do?
Should we just order out?
But I do want to make an effort
and I’m sure Sevi
would appreciate it.
Let’s add cream.
Let’s add more cream
to lessen the saltiness.
Think you can fix it?
Oh, shoot.
Oh my god, he’s here.
- What are we going to do?
- Cream?
- Good evening, sir.
I don’t know.
He’s coming. He’s right there.
Ma’am Elyse, Sir Sevi is here.
Hi, Sevi.
- Hi, Ely.
- Hi, Sev.
Thank you.
Are your parents home?
Mommy’s still at work
and Daddy’s out of the country.
And…
we cooked…
something.
Really?
You know how to cook now?
Awesome! I’m starving.
Come on, let’s eat.
This smells good.
You really cooked this?
I think I’m craving
Chinese food.
- Yes. That’s a good idea.
- Right? Let’s just order.
Let’s order instead.
Huh?
Why?
It actually looks good
and there's a lot of it.
Plus, I'm sure it's tasty
because you made it.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Why not?
I’m sure this is delicious.
Come on, let’s eat.
Oh my!
Why isn't he saying anything?
Nothing? Really?
He’ll just cough about it?
How...
How is it?
It... It’s fine.
It’s okay.
Give it a try.
You try it, Ely.
I already tried it a while ago.
Thank you.
Why does it taste like this?
This is so embarrassing!
What did you put in this?
Oops, my ride's here.
I have to go.
Enjoy your meal, guys.
What?
But I have to go, Ely.
Bye now. Don’t poison
yourselves, okay?
Sevi, enjoy the food.
Let’s just order instead?
Huh? No.
I don’t want to waste
the food you cooked.
I’ll eat this. I’ll even
finish the whole bowl.
Don’t. Don’t.
So good!
Can I take some
home for my family?
I think I can’t finish it all.
Have you guys kissed yet?
Oh boy, you have
to be prepared, girl.
I heard that the Panthers
are good kissers.
Yes! Based on my experience,
it’s true.
You’ll have to hold your own.
Are Panthers really
good kissers?
Kissable lips.
Am I really that handsome
that you can’t help
but stare at me?
Do you want to go...
What?
Nevermind.
Come on, tell me.
Do you want to go to my room?
Why?
I don’t want to.
- Huh?
- What are we going to do there?
You don’t want to see my room?
This is your only chance.
Only chance?
Why?
Well, my dad comes
back next week.
So you can't come here anymore.
What do you have in your room?
Nothing.
I just want to show you.
Can't you just
show me a picture?
I mean, I think it’s better
to see it in person.
I want to show you
my safe space.
Well?
Let’s go?
Sure, but just for a bit, okay?
Okay.
Come on.
This way.
Come on…
I’m all good.
I can see it from here.
Come on, please.
You look so awkward
just standing there.
You don’t want to see my place?
It'd be more awkward
if I went in there.
Why don’t you want to come in?
What, you probably think
we’re doing something else, huh?
Huh?
No.
Okay then, so come on.
You can sit there.
Come on.
Okay, let’s go.
Huh?
Wait...
Wait, but we just got here.
Please?
Are you okay?
Do you need anything?
I’m good.
Are you sure?
Because you seem tense.
Huh?
No, I’m not.
Okay…
I wanted to ask, are you
still sad about the game?
Sevi…
Can you answer me, please?
Are you still sad
about the game?
What game?
Your game.
Gosh, Sevi, are you okay?
I just— Sorry.
I haven’t thought
about it actually.
But yes, I’m still sad about it.
But...
It’s just how it is.
I can’t do anything about it.
It must be hard to leave...
Leave? Sure, let’s go.
Wait! No.
No. I meant,
leave the team.
I know this was your last year
and I still hope
that you know that
you were a great captain.
Thanks.
Can you look at me, please?
Come on,
let’s go back downstairs.
Huh?
I need to go home soon.
Wait, but it’s still so early.
At least just
a couple more minutes.
Please?
Sevi…
Have you ever tried kissing?
Yes.
What the hell?
Really?
With who?
Just some random people...
but I’ve forgotten about it,
so there’s no need to ask.
But I’m curious.
I haven’t had my first kiss yet.
Your curtains are really nice.
A nice pink color.
It matches the pillowcases
and the bed sheets.
Even that flower over there.
You can’t even look at me, huh?
Hey…
Are you mad?
Well, this...
You’re not taking me seriously.
This is an important
matter to me.
I’m sorry.
Okay, I’ll be serious now.
So...
When are we allowed to kiss?
Why do you want to kiss?
Why?
You don’t want to?
Should I just find another guy
to satisfy my curiosities?
Okay.
All right then.
If that’s what you want.
I’m just kidding!
I’m just kidding.
So?
Can I kiss you?
But I don’t know
how to do it, though.
Oh my god! Here it goes.
I’m sorry,
I’m not so good at this.
I’m sorry.
It’s getting...
I don’t have a watch, it’s...
It’s getting late.
You’re right.
Should I have Roel
take you home?
Now?
Okay.
Let’s go.
[Phone notification]
@sevirous:
Hey. Still up?
@elydezma:
Yup. I can’t sleep.
@sevirous: Why can’t you sleep?
Am I on your mind?
@elydezma:
As if.
I’m going to sleep in a while.
@sevirous:
Lucky you for feeling sleepy.
I’ll sleep later, I still want
to think about you.
@elydezma:
Okay, Mr. Corny and dramatic.
I’m also thinking of you.
But you should sleep now.
You have a quiz tomorrow, right?
@sevirous:
You should sleep now, too.
Don’t think about me too much,
you might dream about me.
Good night, babe.
@elydezma:
Are you going out?
Yes, Mommy.
I’m going to meet Sevi.
Okay. Enjoy, sweetheart.
- Take care.
- Thank you, Mommy. Bye.
@sevirous: I’m on my way
to the cafe. See you!
@elydezma: I’m about to
leave the house too!
See you and take care.
- Elyse…
- Daddy!
- Hello!
- Hi!
You’re home early.
I thought you were
coming home next week.
How was your trip?
Well, unfortunately,
the deal didn’t push through.
They just wasted my time.
You? Why are you
so dressed up?
You seem to be
going out a lot lately.
I’m not going anywhere, Dad.
I’m just
trying on a dress
that Ida bought me.
Did I miss anything
while I was gone?
No.
Everything’s good, Dad.
I’ve just been focused
on my finals
‘cause cheer training
is finished.
That’s good to hear.
Just make sure nothing
is distracting you
from your studies, okay?
Okay. Yes, Dad.
I’ll just go up. I’m...
I’m tired.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Ely, I just got here.
Want me to order for you?
I’m sure you’d like
a matcha drink.
Oh, you’re still at home?
Yes. Sev...
I can’t make it anymore,
I’m sorry.
Why, what happened?
My dad came home
earlier than expected
and he was in a really bad mood.
Honestly,
I was so scared to
ask permission to go out.
He might get suspicious of us.
I’m really sorry, Sev.
You’re already there.
I’m really sorry
for making you wait.
Please don’t be mad at me.
Relax, Ely. It’s okay.
I understand.
And...
It’s a good thing
you didn’t leave.
Really?
You’re not mad?
You don’t want
to break up with me?
Why would I break up with you?
It’s nothing serious.
Besides,
we can meet up next time.
Thank you, Sev.
I’m really lucky to have you.
You really are.
You’re so full
of yourself again!
Stop!
Don’t worry,
things we’ll get better.
He’s right.
I’m the lucky one.
Enjoy golfing with your buddies.
Make sure you score big, Dad.
I will.
So what time do you plan
to come home?
Most likely late at night.
I’ll have dinner in the club
and then have drinks after.
You know how it goes.
- Okay.
- I shall go ahead.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
- Bye, Daddy.
Love you.
- Bye.
- Okay.
- Bye!
- Love you.
- Love you, Dad.
- Let’s go.
- Mommy...
Can I meet someone today?
Someone?
Okay, just as long
as you bring Roel
and you have to text me
when you get there, okay?
- Okay.
- Don’t forget to update me.
- I’ll just go up.
Thank you, Mommy.
@elydezma: It’s my free day
today! Let’s meet?
[phone notification]
@sevirous:
Sure! I know you miss me.
- Your coffee, sir.
- Thank you.
Hi, Daddy.
I’m planning on going
Christmas shopping today.
Is that okay?
It’s all right.
Really?
Just go easy
on the spending, okay?
Okay.
And have Roel go with you.
Surely. Take care.
- Hi!
- Babe!
- I missed you.
- I missed you, too.
I can stay before dinner today.
Won’t your dad look for you?
No, I told him
I’ll go Christmas shopping
and he knows how long
that’s gonna take.
And I want to buy Sofia a gift.
You don’t have to, babe.
No, I want to. I insist.
Let’s go?
I want to show you this.
What do you think?
You think Sofia will like it?
Of course.
She’s like a little Elyse.
She's also into clothes.
Well, I am very proud of her
because at such a young age,
she already has
a sense of fashion.
What do you think about this?
I don’t think
that’s going to fit her.
This isn’t for Sofia.
This is for my friend’s
soon-to-be baby.
I see.
Sevi has a pregnant friend?
Who could it be?
Sevi and I look like
a married couple here.
Hey!
Why are you laughing, babe?
It’s nothing.
Here.
Taste this.
Good, right?
That’s my favorite.
Tasty, right?
You can’t do anything right,
you son of a bitch!
I’m your father!
Have you forgotten
everything I’ve done for you?
Even your fucking law school.
That’s why you
don’t have the right
to fucking raise
your voice at me.
That’s your
obligation as a parent.
Don’t throw that shit
against me.
You son of a bitch,
you still have the nerve
to talk back?
- Daddy!
- Alfred!
Alfred!
- What!
- Stop it!
- Stop!
- Answer me!
Don’t hurt him!
Shan.
Alfred!
Come on…
Don’t you dare
show your face to me!
Enough!
That’s enough.
Shan…
I’m fine, Ely.
Don’t worry about me.
I’m fine.
No, you’re not fine!
Why do you guys
always have to fight?
Can’t you just stop?
He’s not the person
you think he is, Elyse.
What?
I feel so conflicted, Shan.
I know Dad is strict but he’s
been a good father to me.
But then, I’ve seen him
repeatedly hit you.
I don’t know what to feel.
Listen, Ely…
As long as
he’s treating you right,
you don’t have to worry.
But the moment
he lays his hand on you
or Auntie Erin...
I’m gonna get you out
of this fucking house.
What…
What are you saying?
- He’s our dad—
- He’s your dad!
What?
I don’t consider him
as my family anymore.
Why...
Hi Sevi.
Have you tried
braised beef stew?
I know a good place in España
where we can get it.
I promise you’ll like it.
I don’t know what that is
but I look forward to it.
Are you okay?
You seem a bit sad.
Did something happen?
Should I tell him what happened?
No. I don’t want
to burden him
with my family problems.
I’m just tired.
I was reviewing earlier
because I have finals coming up.
Okay then.
Well, don’t forget
to rest, okay?
That’s why I’m really glad
we went on our date earlier.
It really helped me to destress.
If you need to destress again,
just give me a call,
and I’ll be there.
In a jiffy.
By the way,
our first monthsary
is coming up.
Is it okay if
we celebrate at my place?
You know… I want to
introduce you to my family...
officially.
My— Sevi...
I would love to.
Really?
Okay, I’ll tell Mama then.
I really hope that she likes me.
Please, Mama already knows you.
And she’s okay with you.
I’m sure she’ll like you.
Ely, are you sure
you want to ride a jeepney?
Because we can book
a ride or take a taxi.
Or you can call Roel,
and we can ask him
to give us a ride.
Sevi, chill. It’s okay.
It’s not comfortable
in a jeepney.
It’s usually cramped,
and there’s no air conditioning.
Isn’t it your
first time riding one?
Yes, but
that’s why
I want to experience it.
Besides, Roel dropped off
Mommy and Daddy at the airport.
They have a business trip, so...
I can hang out longer
at your place.
Come on, let’s go.
How much do I need?
Is this enough?
This is too much.
And the driver might get mad
because he won’t have
any change for that.
Don’t worry, I have change.
Okay.
Hold on,
let’s wait for a jeepney.
Boss!
We’ll ride, boss.
Well?
Aren’t we going to ride?
Come on, let’s go.
Elyse…
Come in.
Wear my slippers first.
Okay.
I’m sorry.
Our house is small.
Your home looks
so cozy and warm.
Do you feel hot?
No! I mean that
it looks very homey.
Where have you been?
Hanging out somewhere again?
I just bought something outside.
Steven, my girlfriend, Elyse.
This is Steven, Elyse.
- My brother.
- Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Hey!
What are you doing?
Is she your godmother?
Just give a handshake.
You don’t have to be mad.
You keep hitting me,
if I get back at you…
Come on.
Hi, Elyse!
Welcome to our home.
Sorry, I’m not done cooking yet.
Hello, Princess.
Hi, little princess.
It’s nice to see you again.
And it’s okay, Auntie.
I’m still not used
to you calling me Auntie.
But you know, Elyse,
I’m really happy
you visited us here.
Thank you.
All right. I’ll finish cooking
so we can all eat already.
Sevi, take care of Elyse.
Feel at home, okay?
- Steven, watch over your sister
- Sure.
- All right.
- What do you want to eat?
Are you okay?
I’m okay.
Wow, you bought so much, Elyse.
Thank you!
You didn’t have to go
through all the trouble,
but thanks a lot! Thank you!
Of course.
Sofia, you have a new dress.
It’s from Elyse.
Look, it suits you perfectly.
Go on, show it to them.
- Wow!
- Looks great.
- Wow, I’ve got a new outfit!
- Yes.
- Thank you, Princess.
- It suits you.
- It suits you perfectly, see?
- You look so pretty.
- Thank you.
Of course, there’s something
for you too, Steven.
Wow!
Thank you, Elyse.
Thanks for the gift.
You’re better at
choosing gifts than Sevi.
Watch your mouth.
You two, enough now.
Just keep eating.
Glad you guys liked the gifts.
Thank you.
Sevi, can you pass me the water?
Where’s your papa, by the way?
Oh no, what did I even ask?
He and Mama are separated.
Now, I don’t know where he went.
I’m sorry. I didn’t know.
Papa’s also an engineer,
that’s why Sevi
took engineering too.
Hey! Nobody asked you.
Just keep eating.
Okay, let’s just eat.
Elyse, don’t be shy. Eat more.
I cooked a lot.
Here, try the chicken.
- Ma—
- Go ahead. Don’t be shy.
. - Ma, give me some chicken.
- Eat your vegetables.
Give Sofia some vegetables, too.
Eat your veggies, okay?
Sofia, eat veggies.
Yum!
Feed her properly...
I did…
Very good.
Welcome to my world.
What do you think?
It’s clean.
I thought it would be some
chaotic college room vibe.
Huh?
I'm actually tidy with my stuff.
I sweep almost every day.
Oh, really?
I was wondering,
did you choose engineering
because of your dad?
We don’t have to talk about it
if you’re not comfortable.
I understand.
Yes.
When I was a kid,
he used to take me
to the site all the time.
That’s when I started
liking engineering.
He became my role model too.
But, well...
He and Mama split up.
If you don’t mind...
what happened?
They said they
weren't compatible.
Funny, right?
They were together for years,
had three kids,
and then they realized
they weren't compatible?
Ridiculous, don’t you think?
Did they end on
good terms at least?
Seems so.
Mama helped him pack.
How do you feel about your dad?
Of course, I’m pissed.
He’s really something.
He was able to leave
his children that easily.
He hasn’t even visited us.
He can’t even show up,
not even to help
with school expenses.
Nothing at all.
He left everything to Mama.
But,
at least I’m about to graduate.
I’ll finally be able
to help Mama.
I’m really sorry
that happened, Sev.
That’s why,
If we have a problem,
let’s sort it out
right away, okay?
No walking out
without saying anything.
I won’t do that to you.
I promise.
You know...
I just realized…
We haven’t said
the three words yet.
Three words?
What three words?
Three little ducks?
Whatever.
What three words?
Go to hell?
Sebastian, you’re so annoying.
Ely.
What?
I love you.
I love you, too.
Happy monthsary!
This one’s for Sofia.
Merry Christmas, Ely!
Is it cold there in Japan?
Merry Christmas, babe.
And yes, it’s so cold.
It’s snowing here.
I’m excited to show you
my Christmas gift for you.
I got you an omamori
and it’s for
good success in life
because I wish you
good success in life.
And I also got myself one, too.
You don’t need that.
I’m the one bringing
you luck in life.
You’re so full of yourself.
I love you.
- Take care over there.
- I love you, too.
Don’t forget to say thank you.
Wow!
Come and greet Elyse.
- Happy New Year!
Hi! Hi, everyone!
- Happy New Year, Princess!
Happy New Year, Pretty Elyse!
Happy New Year!
What do you mean, pretty?
Why? It’s true.
Here’s our good luck charm.
Wow!
- Here are the fruits.
- Mama…
Hello, Elyse. Happy New Year!
Hi, Auntie. Happy New Year!
Be careful over there,
and when you get here,
come visit us right away, okay?
Happy New Year!
Happy New Year, babe.
I miss you.
Happy New Year! We should
make a new year’s wish.
Yup?
I’m manifesting
that you graduate and
pass your board exams.
Okay,
my wish is
that you’ll always be happy,
and that you
won’t break up with me.
That’s not going to happen.
- I love you.
- I love you, babe.
See you soon. Take care.
Let’s all eat!
Hurry, sit down and eat.
@elydezma: I’m in the hospital
for Mom’s regular check-up.
We just finished.
I’m free after.
Let’s meet up?
Why isn’t he replying?
Is he busy or something?
Hello? Steven.
Is your brother home?
Sevi left to meet some girl.
A girl?
Okay. I got to go. Bye.
Yes, babe?
Come on, babe, let’s go back…
Babe!
What the actual fuck?
Is he cheating on me?
What the hell?
Babe…
Is that Sevi?
Why is he here?
Jeez!
Sebastian!
Who the hell is that woman...
Hello!
What the fuck?
That’s Yanna! Hiro’s ex!
Elyse, this is Yanna.
Yanna, this is Elyse.
Your girlfriend sure
rushed over here quickly...
Babe.
Fuck, Yanna,
stop with the teasing already.
Did you get her pregnant?
Hey!
Of course not.
Yes.
Sevi is the father.
Huh?
I’m kidding!
Chill guys, look at your faces.
You’re both so angry.
You’re going to make me
give birth any minute now!
This girl always annoys
the hell out of me!
Here’s the thing, Elyse...
Kierra called
the other day because
Yanna’s stomach was hurting.
Then they rushed her
to the hospital
because her due date
is getting close.
So, I’m the one watching
over her now.
And later, Sam and the
others will be coming.
This isn’t for Sofia.
This is for my friend’s
soon-to-be baby.
Is she the one you mentioned
who's about to give birth soon?
Wait…
Does Hiro know about this?
If you're planning to tell him,
don't even bother.
He already knows
he’s not the one
who got me pregnant,
that’s why…
That’s why we’re not
talking anymore.
So you cheated on him?
If that’s what you
want to think, go ahead.
Just let me be, okay?
Only my close friends
know about this.
Stay out of it, all right?
I wasn’t even planning to.
And don’t be mad at Sevi.
I blackmailed him
into not telling anyone.
Not even you.
That I’m pregnant.
But...
Your boyfriend is really sweet.
He’s really caring.
Can I borrow him for now?
You fucking bitch...
Damn it, Yanna, stop it already.
- Hey, I’m pregnant…
- Yanna!
- We’re here!
- Hey!
Finally.
Elyse? You’re here.
Hi!
I heard about you and Sevi.
Guys,
this is Elyse. My girlfriend.
Hi, Elyse. Hi!
Kierra is coming too,
she’s just finishing something.
You know, Sevi can’t stop
talking about you.
Yes, Luna told me.
What have you been
telling her, Luna?
And now, my friends aren’t
paying attention to me anymore.
- Hey…
- Come on…
Baby girl, come out
to the outside world.
We want to meet you already.
Hey!
Yes, we’ve been
waiting for so long.
Hey, don’t pressure me.
It’s getting painful...
Oh no...
Help me.
Take it easy. Slowly…
Thank you.
Sevi’s always like that.
He takes care of everyone.
For sure, when you're
in labor in the future,
he’ll take care of you
ten times more.
Hey, Elyse needs
to graduate first
before that, and I need
to work to be successful
so I can marry her.
Then we can have five kids.
Oh…
Huh?
Five? Really?
Six is fine too,
so someone can sub.
What...
Are you sure?
Want to switch places?
You think this is easy?
Ask her, come on.
Just one is already so hard.
I’ll let her decide then.
I’m included in
Sevi’s future plans.
That makes me happy.
Baby! Come out now.
You know,
I’m still upset or annoyed
that you didn’t reply
to my messages earlier.
Like...
I understand that you
can’t tell me about Yanna.
But at least tell me
where you are.
I’m sorry.
It’s my fault.
I promise it won’t happen again.
Okay.
You’re forgiven.
Are you sure
you’re not mad anymore?
Will you hug me?
Okay.
Here’s my
Valentine’s gift for you.
Brownies!
I baked that.
Thanks! I’m sure it’s delicious.
And here’s my gift for you.
Wow!
Oh my god!
It’s so pretty.
Just like you.
A letter?
What’s this?
Roses are red, violets are blue.
Something’s not dead,
it’s my love for you!
Happy Valentine’s Day, Elyse.
I love you!
Engineer Camero.
Only if I get lucky.
If not, I’ll just become
your non-showbiz boyfriend.
Thank you.
Thanks for everything, amore.
Te amo.
Why are you swearing?
Huh?
No, stupid!
That means
I love you in Spanish.
I thought I heard you say,
eff ‘em all.
Eff ‘em all?
Te amo, too.
Stop! Don’t say it like that.
You know, it would be nice
if we could live together.
Then we could laugh
like this all the time.
And when we do move in together,
I want a painting just like that
in our living room.
Sure.
You know what..
You can also be displayed here.
Because...
you’re a masterpiece, too.
Wow! You really are
something, Camero.
Such a sweet-talker.
Once I have a job,
I can move out
of my parents’ house
and live with you.
We can do that, right?
Of course.
And I'll save up for all of that
since I'm the first one
to get a job.
Then, I'll get a condo,
one that's close to the office
so I won't have to commute.
I’m so excited
for our future, babe.
So am I.
Ma...
It’s okay.
Don’t cry anymore.
Oh come on, I’m just
really happy for you.
You’ve finally graduated.
I should take a picture
of you guys.
Okay.
- Yes.
- I’ll hold this.
One wacky shot.
Nice!
Okay…
One, two, three…
So sweet…
Let’s take a selfie!
I’m so proud of you,
you know that?
You graduated on time.
You’re even the captain
of the Panthers.
My god, why is my boyfriend
so perfect?
Okay, enough with
the compliments;
you're making me blush.
But...
Wait for me, okay?
I promise that after I graduate,
I’ll introduce you to my dad.
Just two more years.
Of course.
And in those two years,
I'll work really hard
so I have a good face
to show your dad
when you introduce me.
I know that you’ll do great
in the real world.
Thank you.
But…
I’m already feeling nervous
about the board exams.
I need to pass it right away
so I can start earning
a decent salary.
I'm sure that you'll pass,
it's you we're talking about!
And then after that,
you’ll be the one who designs
the most iconic skyscraper
in the Manila skyline.
I hope so...
I really hope so.
But, don’t leave, okay?
Just stay here.
Don't worry,
I’ll always be here for you.
And I’ll celebrate
every milestone with you.
Okay?
I promise.
Okay.
So?
Can I kiss you?
But I don’t know
how to do it, though.
Shit!
She’s getting closer.
What should I do?
Is this really happening?
Okay, calm down, Sevi.
A smack? So cute.
I’m sorry,
I’m not so good at this.
I’m sorry.
Shit…
Fine, let’s do this.
Sir, are you okay?
I’m more than okay.
I had no idea that it was
possible to be this happy.
Okay, sir, get up now
so you can go home.
Roel’s waiting for you.
I’m sorry.
What if I have
a boyfriend right now?
I have something for you.
What’s this?
I call this
the Ely-mergency kit.
We can do anything we want.
Anything?
Yes.
Anything.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Never introduce
someone to your family
unless you're 100% sure
about the person.