You seem to have enjoyed
seeing my big bird.
FYI,
it’s a baby bird.
You know, big bird
doesn’t like liars.
He’s an angry bird now.
Surprise!
Happy birthday, Ely!
I’m sorry. Don’t you like it?
I didn’t expect you to
remember my birthday.
- Happy birthday!
- Ida?
The best surprise ever.
Maybe I’m just not good for him.
But you left without
saying anything.
Cheer up.
I have a surprise for you.
Shan! Hiro!
Maybe leaving again
is the best thing.
Even if it means losing you forever.
I thought you and
Elyse were okay?
I thought so too.
But then she suddenly left.
This is my advance
birthday gift for you.
I can’t accept this, Austin.
You are just a colleague to me.
- You can leave first, Miss Ledezma.
- Thanks.
That's what you're good at anyway.
I haven’t had sex in like four years.
Am I dying?
You know—
I haven’t had sex in
like four years.
Am I dying?
You know what,
Ely, just get dressed.
I’ll be outside.
Okay, daddy.
You know, my head
really fucking hurts.
That’s what you get for
drinking so much.
Just keep drinking until
your liver gives up.
You're so mean, you know?
My head already hurts, and
you're making it worse.
Your head hurts?
Then just chop it off.
Just kidding! Come on!
Have some breakfast so
you can take your medicine.
I'll help you tidy that up.
That looks good.
Where should I put this?
Wait! Don't touch that?
Why?
It's embarrassing.
Now you’re shy?
When you almost stripped
in front of me last night?
I don’t remember.
You don’t remember, or are
you just pretending not to?
Shut up!
Hey! Don't—
I will get that.
Who is this from?
That?
It's from Austin.
Austin?
He gave you a ring?
It’s his birthday gift to me.
He insisted that I accept it.
But don't worry,
I'm going to return it.
Never mind.
Let’s just pawn it.
Let’s not waste it.
Wait.
Where's your birthday
gift for me?
I already threw it away.
What? Why did you do that?
How dare you throw it away!
What did you do with it?
I pawned it off already.
Pawned?
What did you buy?
Is this house clothes or
for going out?
Sevi! What is it?
A ring.
He bought you a what?
A ring! I mean—
He didn’t tell me what
kind of ring it was.
All he said was, it’s a ring.
Oh my god!
Wait, should I start
dieting already?
I’m going to start preparing as
your maid of honor!
Ida, we don’t even have a
label yet, remember?
What? No label?
None.
But look at you, you’re all smiles.
See? I know you, Ely.
I know you.
Elyse,
Dad and I are going to Aruga
resort for a site visit.
Our business partners are
also going to be there.
Are you coming with us?
Honestly, no.
But because I'm professional
I'll fulfill my CEO duties.
Well, yes, sure.
I would love to tour our
business partners around.
Okay then. Come with us.
No, we should take
the company car.
Okay.
Also, Austin—
I can't take this.
I don't want other people to
get the wrong idea.
You're single, right?
Yes. I'm single, but—
Then I can still court you.
Austin, just take it.
Well?
I'll wait for you.
I don't trust that guy.
I know you’ve known each other
for a long time, Ely, but—
I just have a really bad
feeling about him.
Just be extra careful.
Yes.
- Well, that’s pretty good.
- I love that.
Finally, they’re here.
- Good morning!
- Finally!
- Hi!
- How’s it going?
- Good to see you here.
- You’ve arrived, Mr. Guerrero.
- Hi, good morning sir.
- Good morning.
Engineer.
Good morning, sir.
Good morning.
Okay, take it slow. There you go…
Come on.
It’s okay.
It’s fine. Come on!
We would like to see
the site today.
Sure, sir! Engineer Lavin,
the hard hats, please.
Sir.
Thank you.
Let me help you,
I'll put it on for you.
I can do it for myself.
No, let me.
There, gently, you might
hurt yourself.
Okay? There you go.
I guess you were
right, Anthony—
It looks like Miss Ledezma and
Austin are getting close.
No, it’s not. It’s not—
I'm still courting her, sir.
Hopefully, she will say yes.
Does Miss Ledezma not
have a boyfriend?
No! She told me she was single.
Excuse me, everyone,
I just have to take this call.
Engineer Lavin,
you handle it first.
Come on!
Come on, guys! Let’s go.
Let’s go?
Excuse me,
I’ll just get some water,
you can go ahead.
Single?
Well, we didn’t talk about
anything yet.
What should I say?
I didn’t want to assume.
Look…
There are rumors going around in
the company about me and Austin.
That's why I returned the ring,
to make it stop—
Do you like him?
Of course not.
You’re the man that I like.
You’re not single anymore, okay?
Do you understand?
Does it mean we're in a
relationship now?
Don't you want to?
Of course, I do.
Since day one—
I’ve missed you so much.
As you can see everyone,
the progress of our resort
is already significant.
Nice! Impressive!
Yes.
So, if you guys are ready,
allow me to guide you
to the gazebo so you can
chill and relax.
Hold on. We haven’t
seen the satellite office yet.
Good thing you mentioned it.
He’s right.
Sir, maybe you'd like to
have a snack first.
Me? I'm fine, I'm still full.
Maybe you'd like to see
the pool?
Of course, the weather
is so nice today—
and of course, we all
need some vitamin D.
Maybe you’d like to
sunbathe first?
It's noon, Engineer Lavin,
do you want us to
get heatstroke?
Of course, I’m just joking, sir!
That was a test.
Don’t be silly, Engineer.
Excuse me sir, I have to
take this call.
- Okay.
- Please excuse me.
Shall we, Engineer?
Yes, follow me.
Okay.
Is it okay to do this here?
I don’t care.
Get down.
Engineer Camero?
Engineer Camero!
I think Sir Anthony and the
others want to see the office!
Can we go in?
It looks like something fell.
I think they’re chasing after a rat.
Hold on, just fixing things.
Engineer Camero!
Can we come in?
Come in!
Please come in.
So, this is the satellite office?
You seem to be very hardworking,
Engineer Camero.
Your desk is a mess, and your
clothes are all wrinkled.
You must be very hands-on here.
Yes, very hands-on, sir!
Yes, sir! He’s actually working
on a lot of things,
especially in the office!
Elyse, are you okay?
Why are you sweating?
And what's that red mark
on your neck?
Sevi! He gave me love bites!
Are those insect bites?
Engineer Camero?
We might need to check
the surroundings.
There might be a lot of
insects here later!
And we might need to do
fumigation, Miss Ledezma?
That's right.
Noted on that, sir.
- Shall we go outside?
- Yes sir!
If you guys will follow me,
I’ll take you guys to the
gazebo for some snacks.
Come on.
Let’s go.
Stay for a while.
Let’s have lunch first.
I really need to go back to
the office, I’m sorry.
But don’t worry, I promise
I won’t skip any meals.
You promise, right?
Take pictures of your meals.
Then what? Are you gonna call
me a hamster again?
Wow! Seriously, master—
Why are you calling our
amazing boss a hamster?
That's right.
Engineer Camero!
Have you eaten lunch?
Did you eat what I brought?
This girl is still
preparing lunch for Sevi?
How persistent. Maybe she
wants to change careers.
She should just be a chef then.
No, I'm still full.
I gave it to Theo earlier.
It was good!
Looking forward to next time.
Elyse, let's go.
Daddy's waiting for us,
we need to leave now.
Okay.
Engineer Lavin,
Engineer Camero—
Thank you for accommodating us
even with your busy schedules.
We’re going now.
Ely—
See you later tonight, babe.
See you later, babe.
Hey.
Did you sleep enough last night?
Of course, you wore me out.
Elyse, look.
What do you think?
Wow!
This is really beautiful.
Is this your project?
It’s Theo’s project,
Luna made the design.
This is the house I'm having built.
So, it’s your future house?
Our future house.
Really?
Sevi, you’re not joking
with me, are you?
I wouldn’t joke about
things like this.
Do you want to make
any changes?
Nothing. It’s perfect.
Where is this located?
My father left me some land.
It’s just nearby, close to our office.
That’s great.
Oh, right, I haven’t told you—
Mama and Papa got back together.
What? Really?
Oh my god!
Wait, that’s really great
to hear!
So, are you okay with
your dad now?
We’re okay.
As long as Mama’s happy,
I’m fine with it.
And I did see how sincere he
was when he talked to me.
I can also see that he’s really
trying to make it up to us.
I told you, I can forgive easily.
You really have a big heart, Sev.
I’m really happy to hear that
your family is back together again.
But it won’t be the same
with my family.
It sucks being a Ledezma.
Sev?
Do you want to change
your last name to mine?
Amora Elyse Ledezma—
Will you marry me?
Of course!
Yes! Yes, I will!
I will!
I’m freaking engaged, Ida!
You’re engaged?
Oh my god!
Oh my god, I’m so happy
for you, Ely!  Congratulations!
Thank you.
You were right!
It was an engagement ring.
It was well worth assuming.
And it was also worth it to get
my nails done for this occasion!
You know— With Sevi,
everything feels so sure.
I always feel like I’m over
the moon, you know?
But I can’t tell anyone yet
about the engagement party.
Because, his family doesn’t know yet.
You’re the only one
who knows, actually.
Wow, what an honor.
Of course, because—
You’re my maid of honor.
What?
- Really?
- Yes.
Thank you, Ely.
Of course, girl.
Who else would I choose?
You’re my bestie!
- Period.
- Duh!
I also need to talk to Shan.
I’m sure he’ll be thrilled to
hear about this.
So, do you and Sevi already
have plans
for the kind of wedding
you want?
We haven’t talked about it yet.
But I know for sure it’s going
to be a big celebration.
But unlike my debut,
I only want family and
close friends to be there—
You know, the people that
witnessed our love story.
That’s beautiful, Ely!
I’m so excited to do
wedding planning with you!
Future Mrs. Camero.
Let me see that again.
- It’s so pretty, right?
- Oh my god.
Let’s bill out, guys.
Should I use my card?
Guys, I got this. My treat.
- What?
- This is a miracle.
Why are you treating us?
Really?
Sevi, this isn’t the Sevi I know.
This isn’t the friend I know.
Give our friend back!
You guys are crazy.
Something good must
have happened?
Your smile is different!
Sevirous?
You and Elyse got back together?
Oh my god, they got
back together!
Elyse and I got back together!
Congratulations!
No wonder he's so happy at work.
He’s full of energy.
Love really does wonders.
Another broken heart has risen.
Thank you, guys!
I’m really so happy.
Oh my gosh,
what’s going on these days?
Is it the comeback of the exes?
Because first, it was
you and Kalix,
and now it’s Sevi and Elyse.
I think it’s just the season
for soft-heartedness.
Just kidding!
No, but you know what they say,
right? Life is full of surprises.
So, I think those foolish
decisions we made back then,
that’s what led to the better—
Better life?
Better life!
So, think about it, if I didn’t accept
that project with Kalix in Tagaytay—
we wouldn’t get back together.
If he didn’t play house
with his ex,
they wouldn’t have gotten
back together!
In short, does that mean we all
have to act foolish?
Yes.
Moral— lesson?
That’s right, Ke, because—
love is illogical.
He said, love is illogical.
Shit, he’s speaking English.
English.
Is it because Elyse speaks English?
Wow, I’m not used to that.
English.
Can you handle him?
You guys are nuts!
By the way—  I’ll speak English.
By the way, you bring Elyse to
Sam’s bar this weekend.
‘Cause we’re there—
- and we wanna have fun.
- Yes.
You know? We can bond with her.
Spend time?
Yes. I’ll bring Kalix, too.
- So he’s happy.
- Yes, we’re all happy.
Okay. I’ll bring Elyse and—
Elyse and I will announce something.
- What?
- English.
Shit! What is it?
Wait, let me think.
Is it— Is it what I think it is?
- I’ll tell you guys in the weekend.
- Wow!
One more!
I’ll tell you guys in
the weekend.
Oh my god, cheers!
Cheers!
- It’s almost finished.
- I’m drunk.
As you can see,
we are going to reinforce
the foundation
of our sea-facing wing,
to combat wind load,
especially during storms.
How did you know that these
changes are necessary?
Didn't we have this assessed
even before the
construction started?
Because I’m an engineer, sir.
Well, that’s my man!
So, where’s the proposal for this?
I’m sure it will incur
additional costs.
Well, Austin, it was
emailed last week.
Maybe you forgot or your
EA forgot to print it for you.
Well, I would’ve appreciated it
if Engineer Camero
had told me that
the last time we were together
on site, a few days ago.
Right?
I’ll take note of that, sir.
Are there any further questions?
No, I’m good.
No, that is all.
Thank you, everyone.
Meeting is adjourned.
Thank you, Engineer Camero.
Congratulations on
your engagement,
Sir Austin and Miss Ledezma.
What?
Because you have an
engagement ring.
Thank you.
Okay, excuse me, everyone.
But I would like to clarify
that I am not engaged with
Mr. Austin Guerrero,
nor am I in a romantic
relationship with him.
We are business partners and
that is all. Thank you.
That Austin is such an idiot,
such a moron!
And his questions in the meeting
earlier were really dumb.
He’s also being way too
presumptuous with you.
Just ignore him, don’t mind him.
But also next time— you should
answer him with respect.
I know him, okay?
He can turn things around on
you if you’re rude to him.
Maybe I should corner him.
Theo and I can handle him.
Sevi.
Don’t worry. I’m kidding!
If that were true, everyone mad at me
would’ve teamed up against me by now.
And they’re a lot!
They should create a group chat
and add Austin.
Do you know what they
should name their group?
What?
“The men who were jealous of me”.
Kalix is the president, Hiro
will be the vice president—
and they should make
Austin the treasurer.
Wait. Even Hiro?
Yes, you have no idea.
About earlier,
I’m sorry.
Sorry for what?
Sorry for not announcing our
engagement to everyone.
I know that if we announce it,
the rumors between me
and Austin will stop.
But I do need to be careful
because some business partners
might think malicious
things about you.
You know? And—
I don’t want people to think
that you got the job just
because you’re dating me.
And another thing—
I don’t want our engagement
to outshine all of the great
things that you’ve done as
head engineer of the project.
Come on,
I understand that.
I’m actually lucky that
you're overprotective of me.
And that Austin—
Let him spread rumors about me.
What matters is that
I’m the one you chose.
That’s just how it is when
you're more handsome and
better at what you do.
Wow!
But seriously—
no matter what lies he spreads,
he won’t find anything against me.
You know me, Ely.
I’m honest with my work.
Of course.
And that is one of the most
attractive things about
you that I love.
See?
So pretty!
Guys, drink as much as you want!
Just order any food and
drinks that you like.
Let’s make the most of it
because after this night—
we’ll need to go back to dieting
for Kalix and Luna’s wedding.
- Yes!
Except for Luna, okay? Pregnant
women aren’t allowed to drink!
Yes, she’s right.
You shouldn’t drink. Let me know
if you want anything else.
I’ll get it for you.
Really now?
All right, I want you to get
drunk so that tonight,
we’ll go wild!
No, as long as I see you guys
drunk, I’ll be happy.
Wait! Where are Via and Arkin?
Via messaged me—
They’re going to be late
because they’re still
at the studio.
Such a singer!
Before anything else, guys,
let’s cheers for the
newly engaged—
and to make the pregnant
one jealous.
- Cheers!
Cheers! Congratulations!
There might be someone else
getting married soon,
you better start talking.
Actually…
Oh my god!
Hey!
- Hey!
- Congrats!
Shit! Are you guys serious?
I already said, yes.
Hey! Ely…
Congratulations!
Thank you.
Engineer Camero, congratulations!
Thanks, Captain Juarez!
You’re all invited, guys.
We’ll send the details soon.
There you go, I’m getting married!
I hope your boys won’t be
jealous of me anymore!
Not anymore?
What a waste that the other
guy isn’t here to hear it.
- Right, Sam?
- Don’t worry, Sev.
By the way, I invited Shan.
Is that fine?
I guess, it’s okay.
Right, guys?
No.
Awkward.
He’s actually here already.
He’s just parking.
Wow!
Everyone is getting married!
Isn’t this crazy?
Yes!
Let’s toast to that!
To true love!
- To true love!
Babe—
Take it easy, you might get
drunk all of a sudden.
No, it’s okay.
Do you get drunk easily?
Good. Because I have some
questions prepared for you.
Is Sevi good at kissing?
I’m not drunk yet.
Still, you have to answer.
Yanna, you jerk.
I know.
Are you?
- Am I?
- Are you?
Yes, he is.
And pretty good in bed too.
That's info I didn’t want to know.
Good thing your brother isn’t here!
But does your brother know
you’re getting married?
We’re just about to tell him.
So, if I suddenly disappear,
call the police right
away, okay?
Look at Sevi’s face.
You look like—
Looks like Elyse is drunk, guys?
Kalix looks drunk too, right?
No, I’m not drunk. I’m just tipsy.
- Really?
- Yes.
Not drunk, huh?
Let’s see…
Is Sevi your first kiss? Hey!
- Yes, he is.
- Why?
But I know I’m not his.
But you know what? —
He wouldn’t tell me.
So, I don’t know.
Oh no! Yanna seems so quiet.
- Huh?
- Wait, why?
What? I think I’m drunk already.
Come on. Let’s go home, babe.
OMG. Are we going to do babe time?
Yes.
- We are going to do babe time.
- Babe time?
Okay, wait. I’ll say bye to them.
Yes bro, you should
bring her home.
- Bye-bye!
- Careful, Ely.
- Hi!
I just want to say—
that I had so much fun
with you guys.
Really great time, you know?
And Luna, honestly—
I am so sorry that I was
jealous of you.
And Kierra…
Still a little awkward. But you
know what, I still love you!
And Via, she’s in the bathroom—
And you know what?
She is an amazing
and patient person. Like what?
- And Sam, I love you, my friend
- I love you.
And Yanna…
I fucking hate you.
But I still love you.
Same!
I love you guys.
- I love you.
- I love you
Baby!
Come here, baby!
Are we going to go?
We’re going to do babe time.
Sevi—
Your friends are wonderful.
Let’s go.
- Okay, babe time.
- I’ll take this one home now.
Boys!
The drunk girl is finally awake!
Sit down.
Eat first so you can take your
medicine for your headache.
What happened last night?
Huh? You don’t remember?
No!
All I remember is—
is dancing.
Yanna has a video,
she sent it to me last night.
Huh?
That bitch!
Bitch?
Do you know you said
'I love you' to her last night?
You know what? I’m—
I’m never drinking again!
But I did have a lot of fun, too.
You know—
I don’t think that I’ve been
this happy in a while.
Don’t worry.
From now on, there will be
more happy days than sad ones.
Yes.
Eat now.
Wait. One second. Someone’s calling.
It’s Austin.
Should I just decline his call?
Answer it, it might be important.
Okay.
I think this will just be quick.
Hello?
Elyse, emergency meeting!
Something happened in Batangas.
One of the guest villas collapsed!
Five workers were rushed to the
hospital with serious injuries.
What?
What happened?
I’ll explain further
but it looks like Engineer
Camero has been negligent.
Fuck, this will lead to
a major lawsuit, Elyse.
Based on our initial findings—
the collapse was due to
substandard materials.
How did this happen?
Maybe our head engineer
here can explain.
These are information
sheets of the seven workers—
who were on site at the
guest villas
on the day of the accident.
The soon-to-be-married
couple is here.