ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND INCIDENTS ARE FICTITIOUS
Chairman?
Are you there?
So?
How's the kid?
Is she dead?
She's in surgery,
but it's not looking good.
Did you check the security camera footage?
I told the police
they were down for maintenance
and deleted the footage but…
But what?
I don't think it was suicide.
If she got in
via the Equal Opportunity System,
it doesn't matter if she dies or not.
What's important to us
isn't who died,
but who killed.
Listen carefully, Mr. Yoon.
What happened tonight
must be treated like it never happened.
Say the dead student took her own life…
due to the stress of studying.
Many students in Korea
kill themselves for that reason.
It's not even newsworthy.
Do you get what I'm saying?
Yes.
But there's…
a little problem.
A witness?
No. It's good.
I'll handle that kid.
We have similar names.
KIM HAE-IN
Someone, help!
Is anyone there?
Help! Someone's dying!
Help!
So, someone fell…
Gosh…
From the rooftop.
She was bleeding.
I'd never seen
anything like that in my life.
I was so scared and shocked.
Oh, no…
Calm down.
So you're sure you saw
someone else on the rooftop?
What a long day.
It's almost time for school,
so why hasn't she left yet?
What? Why is she coming
from that way and not from home?
Hey.
What do you want?
What else?
You didn't answer your phone,
so I got anxious and came over.
Are you just coming home now?
My phone's off because the battery died,
and I was at a hospital all night…
It's none of your business.
What did you come all the way here for?
You're not here to see my dad
because of what I did to Na-yeon, are you?
Goodness. What are you talking about?
I'm here because I have business with you,
and I want to ask you what happened.
What did you do to win the chairman over
when I couldn't
with money or connections?
He said, one word from you,
and he'll let Na-yeon
into Cheongdam International High School.
What?
We'll drop the lawsuit.
And I'll tell your school
it was a misunderstanding on our part.
What on earth are you…
Mr. Kim.
Can you grab me the thing?
Yes, ma'am.
All is well as long as
we get what we want.
If my Na-yeon can get into CIHS,
there's no reason for us
to be at each other's throats.
So will you please put in
a good word with the chairman for her?
I spent a lot of money to get her a spot,
but if my husband's business
is to flourish,
we need to make connections…
I don't have to say any more, right?
Right? Will you help us out?
Dad.
You didn't go to work?
Where in the world have you been?
I stayed at a friend's place.
We studied together and I dozed off.
Who's the woman
I saw you talking to outside?
And what's that in your hand?
Well…
It's nothing.
I'm tired and sleepy.
You should go to work.
Stop right there!
You didn't call,
so I was worried all night.
Do you think saying nothing happened
makes it okay?
If you went out
and got into trouble without me knowing…
What do you want me to say?
-How dare you--
-I get it.
If I get in trouble,
we have no money or connections
to solve the problem.
Even if I do get in trouble,
I'll take care of it myself,
so mind your own business.
You…
MISSED CALL
SOLVING ONE PROBLEM WON'T MAKE
YOUR MISERABLE LIFE BETTER.
CALL ME WHEN YOU GET THIS.
My life is already bleak and miserable,
and this is making it even worse.
Hello?
The doctor says…
there's no hope.
And the school…
says it's suicide
due to stress about her grades
when she's not even dead yet.
But to see that she has friends
who came to cheer her on…
I'm so very grateful.
Stay strong, ma'am.
Hae-in will get better.
But, ma'am…
Did someone other than me visit her?
What?
You just said her friends came by.
Oh.
One student from
Cheongdam International High School
came by before you did.
They said they are
Hae-in's closest friend in school.
A Cheongdam student…
said they were her friend?
What is it?
There are no such things as friends there.
DO NOT ENTER - OPEN CASE
The cafeteria. That's where we can eat.
What else is there?
Seo Do-eon?
What?
Never mind.
What you have seen so far
are the school's main buildings.
The annex over there
is where Chemistry, Biology, Humanities,
and some other departments are.
You'll figure things out in a few days.
Do I have to explain?
What?
Aren't you going to give me a full tour?
This is…
I'm volunteering
because I'm being reprimanded,
but I have
a strong sense of responsibility.
I'll give you an important tip
about life here
which is a hundred times more valuable
than a tour.
So shall we say we're even?
Students here
have a rank that's invisible.
We're divided
based on our parents' assets.
That's not how you eat that.
You've never had it before,
so you don't know.
You can't do what you never learned.
Why's he always like that?
We could do without him.
He ruins the atmosphere.
That's why retaliation or insubordination
are never tolerated.
You can't even afford to hire a lawyer.
You leech off of us
because you can't afford the tuition,
let alone get your name up here.
GENEROUS BENEFACTORS
(HONORS CLUB)
Well, you can sue.
If you have the money to.
You know my dad's a senior judge, right?
The queen of our school hates
impudent students the most.
-Gosh.
-Be quiet.
You.
Point at your name.
Where is it?
Well…
OVER 100 MILLION WON: GOLD CLUB
Oh. Way down there.
That's your position.
Don't you think…
it's a bit too shabby to brag…
in front of that leech?
So aside from everything else,
shouldn't you know where you stand here?
To not end up like that?
That's it?
My dad owns
a cosmetic surgery clinic in Apgujeong.
I heard you studied in the U.K.
So I guess you really don't know anything
about our school.
If your dad owns a cosmetic clinic…
it means you're on the bottom rung here.
Think you can manage?
The Office of Education
wants us to increase the ratio
of Equal Opportunity students?
To three or four percent per year,
-so up to three students.
-Come on.
-Show me.
-Hold him tighter.
Will you show me?
I apologize.
I heard you made the starting lineup.
Congratulations.
The apple doesn't fall far from the tree.
Your father must be proud.
Well, yes. Thank you.
Good.
What's so good about it?
-Let's have a look.
-Hey.
NAME, STUDENT NUMBER, NOTES
EQUAL OPPORTUNITY SYSTEM:
HWANG MIN-SU, KIM MIN-GYEOM
Today, we'll talk about
teenager suicide prevention.
I'd like to touch on
controlling your emotions.
Being honest and open about how you feel.
In other words, mind control
is most important when preventing teen…
Guys.
Am I boring you?
-Yes.
-It's no fun.
Why must we even listen to this?
"Why?"
Recently, one of your classmates
jumped from the school rooftop.
She's still in a coma.
This talk is to help prevent
such an unfortunate incident
from happening again--
What if it's not unfortunate?
What?
I think what happened
is prevention enough.
Everyone will have learned by now.
Should we leave too?
It's insane.
Did you hear about Kim Hye-in?
-What?
-She's packing her stuff?
Isn't she leaving
because she's embarrassed?
I would, if I were her.
I'd be so ashamed.
Move.
Kim Hye-in.
What is it now?
You really don't know what you did wrong.
It's not that you lied
about being rich when you're not.
Feeling embarrassed about it
and trying to cover it up
is what you did wrong.
My family's not that well-off,
but I never felt embarrassed about
the environment I was brought up in.
Did I ever ask?
What a joke.
Why that little…
Hey, guys.
Listen.
Hye-in was forced to transfer to
Cheongdam International High.
No way.
Is she not lying again?
Did you have to quit working too?
What CIHS student works part-time?
I'm a CIHS student now,
so I should act accordingly.
My goodness.
How great could a high school be?
Do you know that
scholarship students there
get so many various benefits?
The school chairman said
Equal Opportunity students like me
get their college enrollment fee
and tuition paid in full.
They even send us
to quarterly language courses abroad.
People really do love free handouts.
It's not a free handout. It's a benefit.
The first day I was there,
do you know what I saw
that shocked me to the core?
What did you see?
Forget it.
What's the point in telling you?
Anyway, my going to that school
could be a once-in-a-lifetime benefit
and chance to change my life,
so I decided to bet
my life on that school.
Don't be so cynical.
Why would you say I was cynical?
It feels like a loss on my part.
With you gone, who will give me
free expired convenience store food?
The nighttime part-time slot
that used to be mine.
Are you not interested?
I don't want to hear
another word about that.
You finish your story.
You and the school chairman.
What deal did you make…
for the once-in-a-lifetime chance
to come to you?
There was an extra opening
in the Equal Opportunity System.
There was no deal.
You said he contacted you first.
He didn't?
Oh, right.
I withdrew the money I was saving up
for college.
I won't need it once I start
at Cheongdam International.
For the first and last time,
I'll treat you to pork belly.
Let's go eat.
What?
Pork belly?
Kim Hye-in, you…
You have great presence of mind
and sense of reason.
Let's go right away.
-Pork belly.
-Are you that happy?
-You bet.
You're happy a younger person's buying?
I'm hungry,
but let's just say
you're older than me today.
You haven't showered today.
But you love me.
Thank you.
KIM HYE-IN
Do you have something in mind?
Oh, well…
Oh.
Those pumps.
How much were these Mary Jane shoes?
Those? They were 900,000,
maybe 800,000 won.
Their shoes are at least a million won.
Would you like to try them on?
-They cost 1.4 million--
-I know.
That's the pair that costs
1.45 million won, right?
I don't need to try them on.
Give me that pair.
I splurged.
If I make minimum wage,
it's worth 158 hours of work.
I should've just bought
ten 140,000 won pairs.
I must be out of my mind.
No.
A uniform of this caliber
deserves shoes like these.
As it's the standard.
Are you looking for something
in particular?
Oh, no.
You're a CIHS student.
Why not buy one? It doesn't cost much.
You won't want to wear
just any jacket over that uniform.
That's true,
but I already spent a lot today.
Oh.
Can I just try it on?
Yes, of course you can.
I'll take that for you.
Let me help.
Would you like to try this one?
It suits you well.
Would you like to try this on too?
Okay.
Gosh.
-Sorry.
-What are you…
What was that about?
Just saying sorry doesn't make it okay.
Oh, no.
Shoot.
The shoes are fine, fortunately.
Gosh, it's so annoying.
Oh?
THE UNIFORM YOU GOT IN EXCHANGE
FOR MURDER SUITS YOU WELL
Gosh.
That girl from earlier?
Hey, excuse me.
Sorry.
Shit.
Where on earth did she go?
I feel weird and awful now.
Oh. Right.
My shoes.
What?
Where are my shoes?
I'm sure I left them here.
It's not like they could've just run off.
Where did they go?
Hey.
What?
I should ask you that.
Who are you?
You're wearing my uniform.
And you're asking who I am?
Shouldn't you deny it first?
What are you on about?
Are you a transfer?
Don't you know who I am?
You. I'll let you off today
because I'm in a bad mood.
Stay out of my sight at school.
You little piece of shit.
"Shit?"
How dare that thief say that to me?
You can't just walk off.
What are you doing? Are you insane?
Even prison food's a waste on you.
I'll educate you with my own hands,
so keep on talking.
EPILOGUE
I should go now.
Okay. Thanks for coming, Min-sol.
Oh, right. Ma'am.
The other Cheongdam High student
you said came by.
Do you know their name?
Well,
I don't remember their family name.
Oh, their name was…
What?