(Episode 1 The break is the new start)
Where have you been?
Why so serious?
Have I done anything wrong?
I've been waiting for 20 minutes.
I was talking to my friends.
After school, you should leave earlier.
If you want to talk to your friends,
you can talk to them tomorrow.
I thought something happened to you.
You wouldn't pick up your phone.
I was worried about you.
It's not a big deal.
What if you meet bad people?
I'm talking to you now.
I'm sorry.
It won't happen again.
What?
Well...
If you want to stay in Taiwan,
you need to speak Chinese.
It's too hard.
I insist.
You have promised.
Promise it is, then.
Fine, I will behave.
Can we go eat now?
Okay.
What do you want to eat?
Steak.
Let's go then.
Jerry, let's go.
Kai, you're so good now.
Back then, you wouldn't even get on a scooter.
What?
Auntie's scooter is very cool.
It's because I'm cool.
Look at you.
Overtake me.
Fine, I'm coming.
We're almost there.
It's here.
Kai, get down.
Wait there.
Wait for me.
Kai.
We're going to the beach. Are you happy?
I'm happy.
Come.
Hold this.
Need a hand?
No.
- Kai, wait for me.
- You're too slow. Hurry up.
- Don't run.
Kai is from here, indeed.
Why are you so stubborn?
Just talk to him.
I want to talk,
but where is he?
You're just too arrogant.
It's not your business.
It is.
Kai, wait for us.
Kai.
He runs way too fast.
(PAPA & DADDY 2)
(Episode 1)
Can you tilt a little?
Right.
Okay.
I'm gonna toss you.
If you miss him that much, go bring him back.
He won't respond to my texts nor my calls.
I can only look
at Alex's feed
to see what they are up to.
Alex said that
she has never seen Jerry acting like this.
He is this mad because he cares.
Why don't you start with Kai?
And do what?
Think about it.
Jimmy's teacher.
What's going on with him again?
I need to answer the phone.
Hello.
I don't want to bother you.
I'm so sorry.
I got it.
Jimmy's teacher said
he's in class for a few minutes
and went to the toilet,
but never came back to class.
It turned out he went to play basketball
with friends from another class
in the playground.
Really?
The teacher must be shocked.
Do you guys get along well?
He seems easy-going,
so he shouldn't be rebellious.
But we have never lived together before.
Sometimes I just don't know
how to deal with him.
Maybe I'm just not used to it yet.
Be his friend.
Try to understand him.
It's going to be okay.
You can do it.
Now I am worried about...
Jerry.
Then take Jimmy to Hualien with you.
Let everyone talk things through.
It's been three months.
Jerry might have stopped being mad.
I can't do that.
Jimmy wants to stay in Taiwan.
He must get used to the life here.
He can't stop going to school.
The key to making Jimmy stay in Taiwan
is to talk things through with Jerry.
Studying is not important at all.
I know but...
I can't.
- Let's eat.
- Jimmy can't be running around.
Come.
You worked hard. Let's eat.
Hualien is not far. It won't take long.
Right?
Damian
I know you're on a no-carb diet.
I prepared a healthy meal for you.
Very thoughtful of you.
Thank you.
You name is Wei?
Wei in first tone.
Wei that means formidable.
Wei.
Thank you so much.
How's your work here?
It's quite alright.
I really like you
and Celine.
I feel as if everyone were my family.
We are family.
I will go pick a bottle of wine.
Alright.
Let's fly.
I'll hold you up.
Go.
Go to the right.
Yes.
Faster.
Yes! Awesome, bro!
Go.
How is school lately?
Nothing new.
Can we just talk later?
Scott woke up early just to play with me.
Stop playing for a minute.
I have something to tell you.
It won't take long.
Sorry. I gotta go.
Talk to you later.
I will go to Hualien tomorrow.
In the meantime,
you need to stay at your aunt's.
Are you going to see Jerry?
Yes.
I will go to bring him and Kai back.
I want to go with you.
You can't. You need to go to school.
Please.
Fine.
I will apply for a leave for you.
Yes.
However, you still
need to take homework with you.
No problem.
Have you been in contact
with you mother lately?
Last time I called her, Adam picked up.
He said Mom was trying on wedding dresses.
After that, Mom called but I missed it.
What about your friends in the US?
Do you miss them?
We talk online.
They've transferred to other schools.
Okay.
Go on with your game then.
What is it?
What song are you listenning to?
Want to hear it?
Of course.
It's a new song.
It's good, right?
Not bad.
Awesome.
Keep dancing.
Pan, who's this kid?
He's so cute.
He's my grandson.
His name is Kai.
He is your son's child?
Yes.
That's such a surprise.
Your son is still young.
And his son is this big.
What about his wife?
They're usually in Taipei.
Thet are very busy.
Eat dumplings first.
Is that so?
Right.
The child looks like his mother, right?
He doesn't look so much like your son.
Is that so?
He's young. You can't see it yet.
Pan.
I will go boil dumplings.
You're so cute.
Come, come.
I have something for you.
Here.
You can have it.
Aw, he's such a good kid.
I still have more.
Come, come.
I give you all. All of this is for you.
Say "Thank you."
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You got so many candies.
Hey, cabbage dumplings are done.
Dumplings are ready.
Please do me a favor.
Be careful with the plate.
Kai knows how to serve too.
It's for this table.
Thank you very much.
Good boy.
Come get your candy.
He's so cute.
Good boy. Eat the candy now.
Hello to all the fans.
Hello, hello.
Is everyone here?
Okay, let's get started then.
Hello.
This person beside me
has travelled around the world.
Wherever he went, he used Airbnb.
The wild child who has lived
almost everywhere in the world
is my best friend who grew up with me.
And this is our guest chef for today.
Hello, Jerry's fans.
I am Gao Daxia.
Today, I bring you local food.
A small thing I learned
from an owner of a place
on Airbnb.
And then he mixed work with life.
I envy him so much.
That's why we should toast him.
Let's toast.
Wait. What to say when you toast?
Nu mita.
Is that correct?
Isn't it uwaken nu mita?
That's right.
Are you the local man
or am I?
I was testing you.
Testing me?
Yes.
OK.
To my viewers,
uwaken nu mita.
Let's get to the point of today.
Today I bring you Chicken Thigh Steak.
- Chicken Thigh Steak.
- That's right.
Mix it with ailanthus-like prickly ash.
Ailanthus-like prickly ash?
- Then, we will grill it like Australians do.
- I've never heard of it.
Right. It also got a name that
means birds wouldn't step on it.
Birds wouldn't step on it.
Why wouldn't birds step on it?
Because its leaves have thorns on the back,
so birds wouldn't step on it.
Come see, guys.
Ailanthus-like prickly ash
has small thorns,
so birds wouldn't step on them.
Now everyone gets it, right?
You're so good at cutting that.
How many times have I told you
not to let Kai have candies?
He won't sleep soundly at night.
It's not like he has it every day.
It's not that bad.
Right?
No means no.
If you are like this,
how can I trust you with Kai?
Papa, it's so hot.
Why are you sweating so much?
I remember that I didn't
put on this thick sweater
for him this morning.
It's cold today.
Children shouldn't get sick, you know?
That's right. Hualien's sun can't be trusted.
The temperature outside is really low.
What kind of grandparents
are you guys?
You two grew up like this too, didn't you?
You're one to talk.
There was this really hot summer.
She didn't turn on the AC,
and told us to keep calm to feel cool.
Right. I sweated a lot that day.
The next morning, I was covered in rash.
I thought I was having a fever.
Is there something wrong
with Kai's genes?
He doesn't look like you one bit.
Mom, why are you
talking about this in front of him?
Young kids wouldn't understand this.
Which words can't he understand?
Is he really your child?
Alright.
You two stop talking.
No. You want to know too, don't you?
Damian.
Daddy.
Mr. and Mrs. Pan.
Stand still.
Don't move.
Yes.
I can't believe it.
It's been three months and you just came.
Baby.
Don't call me Baby.
Why didn't you tell me you have a child?
Do you remember six years ago?
We broke up because
I wanted a kid, didn't we?
It wasn't easy to get back together.
Sasa told me
not to tell you
about the kid that I had in America.
Sasa knows?
I made a promise to Jerry.
During these two years,
we won't dream about having kids.
We're going to enjoy our lives for now.
He really loves you.
Also, it's me who decided to have a kid.
He doesn't have to help me take care of it.
Just staying by my side is enough.
Do you really think it will be that easy?
What if the child cries at night?
Can he ignore that?
We can just find a helper.
It's no big deal.
No problem.
Don't tell him you already had a kid.
Why?
I don't want secrets between us.
You two just got back together.
Jerry is very sensitive
when it comes to children.
I think you should
keep it to yourself for now.
Also,
You are not in touch with Jimmy anyway.
You don't really have to mention it.
It's called concealing for one's own good.
Actually, I was struggling too.
To be honest, I'm in Taiwan now,
but Jimmy and his mom live in America.
We can never end up together,
so...
When you told me you were once married,
you should mention that too.
Those are two different topics.
When I married Kate,
I was very young.
I didn't even know what I wanted.
When I realized I was into men,
Kate was already pregnant.
She was devastated.
And she didn't want
anything to do with me again.
So, I respect her decision.
Actually, all these years,
I've been feeling I owe it to them.
To me, the past
is really painful.
Despite that,
you still should have told me.
You didn't trust me, did you?
It's not that.
I was afraid that I'd lose you.
What an excuse.
Baby.
What do I have to do to make you forgive me?
I really miss you and Kai.
I mean it.
Alright.
I'll think about forgiving you later.
But you need to give me some time
to get to know Jimmy.
If it's possible,
let him go back to America.
He grew up there anyway.
Also,
you need to explain to my parents
who he is.
Baby.
What about me now?
- Stay there.
- Baby.
Do you know who your mommy is?
I don't have a mommy.
I only have dads.
That's alright.
We are family,
so you can think of my mom as your mom.
Okay.
Cool.
Good brother.
It'll be cooler
if you say bro.
Bro.
Dumplings are ready.
You understand Chinese too?
You are Damian's relative, right?
You look very handsome.
Relative?
I'm his son.
Kai, what does he mean?
He's my bro.
Dad, Mom.
He doesn't get to come here a lot,
so I will take to to the night market.
We'll come back a bit late.
What does bro mean?
It means older brother.
Bro means good friend,
or best friend, or something like that.
That's right.
He is my friend's son.
Alright, let's go.
Let's go.
Go, go, go.
Don't wait up.
He's my brother.
We will be a bit late.
We'll eat before we come back.
Bro.
Brother.
Take the smaller one. It's better.
This one.
Thank you. Bye-bye.
Thank you.
Hold it well.
Try again.
Thank you.
I don't want it.
I do.
No.
There?
Yes.
Excuse me. Can you take a picture for us?
Sweep it?
Picture.
Take a picture.
That's right. Can you?
OK.
Thank you.
You just came back from America?
Yes.
Which state?
California.
I've been there.
I love the beaches there
because everyone can just wear bikinis
and walk around.
Such freedom.
Your shape is great.
Your skin color looks healthy.
You can wear little.
Wear little?
What does it mean?
He means your skin looks healthy.
You must look good in swimsuits.
Don't interrupt.
It's rude.
You Mandarin is broken.
I am just helping.
I told you to practice Mandarin.
I don't have any ill intent.
I'm sorry.
That's okay.
Thank you for the photo.
Papa, what does good shape mean?
Thanks.
I'm sorry.
Baby.
I'm really sorry
that I hurt you.
I'm sorry too.
I know Jimmy means a lot to you.
But...
Give me a little more time
to learn about him.
I know.
I'm trying to adjust too.
I already told Kate
to come
and take Jimmy.
Does Jimmy know?
He doesn't.
I'll just tell him when Kate comes.
Papa, there are mosquitoes.
Where? Let me see.
Come sit.
Where did you get bitten.
Here?
Don't scratch it.
I will apply ointment for you
to stop the itching.
Okay?
Hello, my fans.
Today, we're taking you
to Mrs. Pan's Dumpling Shop,
the most famous dumpling place in Hualien.
These two beside me
are masters of dumpling making.
Hello, everyone.
Our Mrs. Pan's Dumpling Shop
is in Hualien.
We have parking spaces available
and it's convenient to get here.
As for our dumplings,
they are all hand-made,
with fresh ingredients.
Please come when you have a chance.
Moreover,
and it's very important.
Our Jerry had all these dumplings growing up.
See? He's tall and handsome, right?
Madam, why are you so sweet?
No. She's my mother.
Right.
I bet you all know now
who I got this from.
That's right.
So, remember.
If you guys come to Hualien,
don't forget to come to
Mrs. Pan's Dumpling Shop.
Please come.
Mom, look.
Everybody says you're so cute.
There're so many comments.
Live streaming is so hard.
We've been preparing since this morning.
It's so tiring.
Do you realize how good he is now?
My son, you must be so tired.
I'm not as tired as you two.
But, Damian, you made my face look so big.
No. That's not possible.
No. That's very small.
It's my face that is big
like a pancake.
That's right.
He made Jerry look the best, didn't he?
It's because of love.
- I can't believe you.
- Pan.
There are customers.
Welcome.
Come and have some dumplings.
Right.
Please come in and sit here.
Hello. Welcome.
See for yourself.
I want to take a photo with you.
Of course, you can.
So cool.
Go away.
Great.
It looks good. Thank you.
I'm a big fan of yours.
Alright.
Please sit there. Thank you.
Please sit.
Go back first.
I will take care of the rest.
Your mom has been busy all day.
You take care of it then.
Okay, no problem.
Be careful.
Alright.
Tell me when you get home.
Okay.
Is it good?
Very good.
My mom doesn't cook.
There's love here.
You're so lucky.
Do you miss your mom?
If you miss her,
why don't you go back to her?
Why are you staying in Taiwan?
She's getting married.
I don't like it.
What else do you like to eat?
Tell me.
I'll make it for you.
Steak.
Alright.
I'll make it for you.
You're so kind.
I like you.
Baby.
Kate's flight will land tomorrow.
She wants to come to Hualien,
so I will pick her up tomorrow.
Why so sudden?
She'll busy doing taxes.
And there's also her wedding.
It seems like Jimmy doesn't want his mom
to get married.
That's right.
But I believe Kate can find a way.
Will she be unhappy?
She won't.
Don't overthink it.
Well...
Are you unhappy?
How can I be unhappy?
I love Jimmy so much.
So, even though he goes back to America,
how I love and care about him
will never change.
Now I hope you don't blame yourself,
Okay?
But...
I have something to ask you.
What is it?
Is it possible not to let your parents
meet Kate?
An.
C, h, u, a, n. Chuan.
M, a, o. Mao.
An chuan mao (helmet)?
Doesn't it mean cat?
Jerry.
Mom, didn't you go to the shop with Dad?
Why are you still here?
I have something to ask you.
Come here.
Jimmy and Damian,
how exactly are they related?
Why does Kai call him big brother?
He's Damian's son.
Son?
Biological son?
Isn't he gay?
He had Jimmy while he was still in America.
Could he change just like that?
Sexuality can be fluid.
Well...
did you know it all along?
I did.
Are you stupid?
You help raise his kid.
You're so stupid.
Mom, don't say such hurtful things.
So...
Will this kid stay here?
No, he won't.
He will go back soon.
Really?
Alright, Dad is waiting for you.
Hurry up and go.
Just don't let him take advantage of you.
What if Damian goes back to dating women?
What will you do
when that time comes?
Mom, don't worry. That's not happening.
Hurry and go.
I will...