♪The golden phoenix is flying
in the colorful sky♪
♪Such a rare and perfect match♪
♪I won't be oppressed by the palace rules♪
♪Love and time are rarely aligned♪
♪But it's such a perfect match♪
♪Long live the Queen? I prefer a sweet smile♪
♪One is willing to tolerate
while the other is willing to hit♪
♪Bring it on, my rival♪
♪No might can fly up to the sky♪
♪It doesn't affect my elegance at all♪
♪Great at writing family rules♪
♪And bullying the imperial bodyguards♪
♪When I turn around and flash my smile,
tears will be shed♪
♪I'm here to annoy you♪
♪The Queen has arrived!
Nothing is a big deal to me♪
♪Shouldering the responsibility
as your virtuous and capable wife♪
♪The Queen has arrived!
She brings happiness to all♪
♪Just have fun in the world! I won't turn back♪
♪What a perfect match♪
[Adapted from Jinjiang Wenxuecheng's
"Queen Liu Heipang", written by Ge Yang]
[The Legendary Life of Queen Lau]
[Episode 9]
[This work is fictitious.
Any resemblance to reality is coincidental]
Sufang.
Sufang!
Shen Ao?
Yunchong?
Chai?
Jing?
What are you doing?
Haven't we all eaten already?
What is this?
Your Majesty.
We were having a chat,
and we thought we were really grateful
for everything Your Majesty has done for us.
Therefore,
it's time we repay your kindness.
What about giving you a beautiful face?
A beautiful face?
Are you trying to do something to my face?
No!
Get your hands off me now!
Sorry, Your Majesty.
This is not up to you.
I can't hold it any longer. I'll leave it to you.
Let me go.
-I don't want plastic surgery.
-You're right.
It was all an act.
We wanted to give you a lesson.
You better stop...
Stop dreaming.
You'll do it.
You're so cruel.
How dare you add poison to the dishes?
I...
Shen Ao, you should do it.
You do it.
I can't hold it any longer either.
Why don't you go with them?
Don't you remember, Your Majesty?
I didn't eat the food you cooked.
Come here.
Your Majesty.
Don't be scared.
What you need now is just a short nap.
You will wake up
with a beautiful face.
It might hurt a little,
but it's fine.
You're so tough,
so it won't hurt you much.
Here.
Are you serious, Shen Ao?
I would never lie to Your Majesty.
(I managed to hide from Yu Changya)
(but ran right into this group of madmen.)
(It seems like)
(they're not as good a physician
as that darned Yu.)
Hurry up!
Let me go now.
I'm beautiful enough.
I don't need any surgery.
You're just a quack
who knows nothing about aesthetic.
How can you give me a pretty face?
Let me go now.
Your Majesty.
Did you just call me a quack?
She called me a quack.
And she said I knew nothing about aesthetic.
Let me go now.
Hold her.
Let me go.
Xuan, help!
Xuan!
(Why is she wailing so painfully?)
(Yunchong and the rest must have gone overboard.)
(I did tell them)
(to go easy on this.)
(Wait.)
(Jinfeng is a smart woman.)
(What if this is just a trap?)
(If I go in now,)
(I'll fall right into her trap.)
(What do I do now?)
Xuan!
Your Majesty.
It's no use to keep calling for His Majesty.
To tell you the truth,
this is His Majesty's order.
He told you to do this?
Otherwise, I wouldn't have dared do this.
It's him.
He actually went to this extent
just to give me a hard time.
He wants to mess with my face.
That's too much.
Let me go.
Get your hands off me!
Now!
He has to pay for this!
Shen Ao.
-Your Majesty.
-Let me out now.
Let me out. Now!
-Let me go.
-Your Majesty.
Calm down, Your Majesty.
Let me go!
Calm down!
Your Majesty.
Impulse is the devil.
Get out of my sight now!
Duan Yunzhang.
You just wait.
Your Majesty.
Jinfeng.
I was looking for you.
I was looking for you too. Are you all right?
I'm fine,
but you're not.
Stand right there.
Protect His Majesty.
I'll kill you today.
[Lingshu Academy]
What are you doing?
Have a seat first.
What's the point of sitting down?
If you dislike me so much,
you should just avoid the Xiangluo Hall.
Why did you have to drive me into a corner?
Stand right there.
You have to do this to me, huh?
Wait.
What is she talking about?
Can you please calm down?
Fine, Duan Yunzhang.
You're not admitting it, right?
I'll calm down after I take my revenge.
You shrew.
Duan Yunzhang!
Duan Yunzhang,
stand right there!
I must make you pay for what you've done today.
How dare you!
Fine. Keep running.
You can keep running.
Eat this.
Shuan.
What's wrong?
Get up now!
Where's Jinfeng?
Duan Yunzhang.
-Let me go.
-You first.
-Let me go now.
-Go away!
-Let go now!
-You first.
It hurts.
Don't touch me.
No way.
Isn't that Yunzhang?
Your Majesty.
Why...
Help!
I'm coming, Your Majesty.
I dare you to take another step forward.
Take another step forward
and you'll end up just like Shuan.
I can't do this any longer.
-How useless. Let me do it.
-Help His Majesty.
You should do it.
What a useless bunch.
Yunzhang, I'm coming.
Yunzhang...
I... I can't hold it any longer.
You need to help yourself.
How useless...
They really are your good friends, huh?
What about this?
Let's each take a step back.
Or we'll both end up bald.
You'll get bald first.
Sure.
I'll count to three.
No, I'll count first.
You do it, then.
Three. Two. One.
You're so cunning!
You're so scheming.
You're despicable.
Look who's talking.
Did you learn this from your mother?
I learned it from your mother.
You're just as terrible as your father.
It's easy for one
to get addicted to skincare.
It feels weird
not using the facial mask for a day.
I know.
Those are really good stuff
from Imperial Physician Shen.
I immediately recommended it to Your Majesty
once I realized how effective this is.
That's right.
You're just as mean as your father.
I dare you to say that again.
Your father is mean, and you're meaner.
Both your father and you are mean.
How dare you! I won't allow you
to badmouth my father like that.
I said...
Jinfeng, Yunzhang.
What are you doing?
You're embarrassing yourselves.
Let go of each other now.
Let go.
Jinfeng.
Do you mind explaining to me
what exactly happened?
If you can't explain yourself,
I'll punish you for harming the Emperor.
Let Duan...
I think His Majesty owes me an explanation too.
Why was I drugged and brought to Lingshu Academy?
Why was Shen Ao trying to give me plastic surgery?
Really?
That's absurd.
Ridiculous!
Shen Ao.
How dare you!
Your Majesty.
It was my own idea.
I wanted to make Her Majesty prettier.
Really?
You're just the head of Lingshu Academy.
How dare you do that?
Shen Ao.
That wasn't what you said just now.
You said this was His Majesty's order.
That's right.
It was my order.
Since you refuse to leave the palace
and I'm going to keep seeing you in the future,
naturally, I'd like to see you
with a prettier face.
Your Majesty
has gone quite far.
But...
I understand where you're coming from.
That's mean.
You're too mean.
I thought
we could each mind our own businesses.
Now, it seems like
not only do I hate you,
but you also loathe me.
We should probably just go separate ways.
Jinfeng.
Don't get mad.
Look.
Zhang is feeling guilty about what he did.
What about this? Leave this matter to me.
Both of you
have had enough of fighting.
I'll take revenge on your behalf.
I'll remove Shen Ao from his position
as the head of Lingshu Academy.
What about that?
There's no need for that.
Duan Yunzhang, I'm telling you.
If someone doesn't like me,
be he a deity or an emperor,
I won't beg for his attention.
You don't have to put in so much effort,
ordering your stupid officials
to chase me out of the palace.
I'll go back and pack things up now.
It's not somewhere I want to stay either.
Zhang.
Say something.
Go after her.
[Divorce Agreement]
Your Majesty.
Are you really leaving?
Yes.
I must leave.
It's just a palace.
Who cares about staying here?
My beloved consort, help me draft the agreement.
I must divorce the Emperor today.
I'm going back to Xianpa Village
to live a happy and carefree life.
It still feels wrong to me.
There has never been a divorce
between the Emperor and the Queen.
Besides, Father keeps you in the palace,
so I'm sure he expects you to do our family proud.
Father doesn't care about my well-being,
so why should I care about anything else?
You can be the Queen.
You can make our family proud.
Are you kidding me?
Not everyone can be the Queen.
It's not completely impossible.
You're Liu Xie's daughter too.
If you become the Queen,
Liu Xie will be pleased as well.
It's getting more and more absurd.
Forget it.
Baiyu.
This is a serious question.
Do you know where Liu Xie is keeping my mother?
I need to save her.
I have no idea.
I should've guessed.
I will ask Liu Xie myself.
Your Majesty.
This is bad.
Your Big Baby is missing.
Big Baby?
It's a giant spider.
A giant spider?
Miss.
It's fine.
My beloved consort, it doesn't bite.
Your Majesty.
I think it's Big Baby.
It's dead.
Your Majesty.
I'll get someone to bury it.
Take it once a day.
One drop at a time.
Overdosing on this will affect your health.
Whoever finishes the entire bottle in one go
will lose his or her life.
Are you sure it's fine to take a drop of this?
It's absolutely fine.
Don't worry, Your Majesty.
(Is Shen Ao trying to hurt Duan Yunzhang?)
(Although Duan Yunzhang wasn't exactly kind to me,)
(I can't just stand by and watch
as someone tries to kill him.)
(Donghao Empire will be doomed)
(if they lose their emperor.)
(Whatever.)
(I'll consider this a charity.)
My beloved consort.
Prepare the divorce agreement.
I need to run an errand.
(What's going on?)
[Xuanchen Hall]
Is His Majesty in there?
Your Majesty.
His Majesty is not around.
When will His Majesty be back?
I have no idea.
I'll wait for him inside.
Your Majesty.
I heard that you've got food poisoning.
Are you feeling better now?
Thanks for Your Majesty's concern.
We have gotten much better
after taking the medicine we got from Shen Ao.
I heard that Her Majesty
is leaving the palace tonight.
I was so excited when I heard that.
Why are you excited
about the Queen leaving the palace?
I'm happy for Your Majesty.
Your Majesty's wish has been answered,
and we'll be able to restore peace in the palace.
How nice is that.
Not to mention,
I was the one who came up with the idea
about how to make Her Majesty
leave the palace willingly.
You were the one
who suggested doing plastic surgery?
When I went to Xianpa Village,
I was told
that Her Majesty hated plastic surgery the most.
I simply made use of the information I got.
I told you to find a way
to make her leave the palace,
but I didn't tell you to bring up plastic surgery.
You look like you need plastic surgery too.
Why don't I do something to your face?
Please, don't.
I don't need any plastic surgery.
I beg for your forgiveness, Your Majesty.
Leave.
Yes.
How reckless.
It's getting late.
Why is he not back yet?
I'm in a hurry to leave.
Your Majesty.
Are you really leaving?
Of course!
He hates me so much
that he wanted to give me plastic surgery.
Why should I stay here any longer?
Forget it. I'm leaving.
I'm going to leave him a note
and that's the best I can do.
(Isn't this the box he kept his letters in)
(when I first came to the palace?)
(Why is it here?)
[To Xuan]
(Aren't these letters from me?)
(I thought I had destroyed all of them
at the Astronomical Observatory.)
(Someone has glued them back together.)
Sufang.
Who sent me back here when I got drunk
at the Astronomical Observatory the other day?
Your Majesty.
To be honest with you,
it was His Majesty who sent you back.
His Majesty?
No way.
How could it be him?
I've always wanted
to tell Your Majesty about this,
but Your Majesty said
that you wanted to turn over a new leaf,
and no longer wanted to have anything to do
with His Majesty.
So I...
What a weird guy.
He said one thing
but did another.
I'm so confused right now.
What does he actually want?
I think
His Majesty can be haughty sometimes,
but he's also soft-hearted.
He's not a bad person.
Your Majesty.
Why don't you stay here for now?
I don't care if he's a good guy or a bad guy.
I'm leaving regardless.
Assassin?
And he dares to run!
Stand right there.
Stand right there!
Help!
Help! There's an assassin!
Your Majesty.
Sufang, go and get help.
I'll go after him.
Be careful, Your Majesty.
[Greatest virtue
has the characteristic of water]
I can finally have peace of mind.
It's so quiet.
So calm.
I've always known that the imperial capital
is the most boring place in the world.
How did Liu Jinfeng manage to influence me?
Stand right there!
Stop running!
Help! There's an assassin.
Help. Quick!
Your Majesty.
Tang.
There's an assassin.
Ask someone to catch him now.
He's a man in black.
I've been patrolling this area,
but I haven't seen any man in black.
There was definitely a man in black.
I came after him all the way here.
You have to search every corner.
Every single corner.
Your Majesty.
You said that you were leaving this afternoon.
And now you're talking about a man in black.
Are you trying
to make up an excuse so you can stay here longer?
You played a prank on me,
and I'm kind enough
to let the matter go.
How dare you question me now?
Fine.
This is none of my business.
If you don't want to search the place,
then it's up to you.
Your Majesty.
The four of you, find the man in black now.
Yes.
The rest of you, come with me.
Both of you
will bring some men to the Qingchi Palace
to protect His Majesty.
Yes.
His Majesty is at the Qingchi Palace?
He's at the Qingchi Palace.
I've been waiting for him the entire evening.
You...
[Qingchi Palace]
I have something to tell His Majesty.
His Majesty said
that he wouldn't meet anyone now.
It's going to be a short one.
I told you His Majesty isn't seeing anyone now.
Brat.
Haven't you heard of this old saying?
An old saying?
No, I haven't.
Stay out of the couple's business.
Move.
Duan Yunzhang.
Duan Yun...
Isn't he here?
What's with that smell?
Duan Yunzhang, come out now.
I have something to tell you.
I'll leave right after that.
Duan Yunzhang.
Get up.
What's wrong, Duan Yunzhang?
Duan Yunzhang.
[Xuanchen Hall]
Your Majesty.
What happened to Zhang?
Imperial Physician Shen
is treating His Majesty now.
He said that His Majesty
got poisoned.
-Poisoned?
This...
How did that happen?
Jinfeng.
Did you do anything to His Majesty?
I didn't.
This has nothing to do with me.
We all know
that His Majesty and you aren't on good terms.
You're almost like irreconcilable enemies.
Perhaps you were upset with what happened
and decided to hurt His Majesty.
Why would I do that?
I'm leaving.
Do I need to do that?
If you're leaving,
why were you at the Qingchi Palace?
She's right.
How do you explain that?
I went to the Qingchi Palace
because I wanted to warn him
that Shen Ao is trying to hurt him.
I want him to stay alert.
Shen Ao?
What is this?
Didn't Shen Ao
give me some special medicine?
According to him,
it was to cure His Majesty's asthma.
When I was packing today,
I accidentally knocked it over.
I realized that it was poison.
That was why I went to the Xuanchen Hall,
intending to tell him about this.
I kept waiting, but he never showed up.
Then, came a man in black.
I chased after the man in black
and came to the Qingchi Palace.
I've searched the entire place
and found no man she mentioned.
Commander Su.
You couldn't find him,
but it doesn't mean he's not here.
Your Majesty,
I can be the witness.
I did see a man in black
at the Xuanchen Hall.
I got it.
Shen Ao.
It was Shen Ao.
He was the man in black.
Shen Ao first poisoned His Majesty.
Then, he clad in black
and lured me to Qingchi Palace.
He wanted to frame me.
How can you justify that?
Shen Ao, you're here just in time.
Tell them what happened.
Your Majesty.
I fed His Majesty
with the antidote I developed.
His Majesty
will regain his consciousness very soon.
That's good to hear.
Regarding the man in black
Your Majesty was talking about,
forgive me for my lack of knowledge,
but I have no idea who that is.
Fine.
You don't have to admit
that you were the man in black.
What about the special medicine?
Your Majesty must have forgotten
about my advice.
Take the medicine one time a day.
One drop at a time.
Taking a low dosage won't do any harm,
but if you take the entire bottle in one go,
it will cost your life.
My spider barely touched the medicine,
and it died.
I can't explain that.
Perhaps Your Majesty can talk to His Majesty.
After all, he was the one
who told me to pass the medicine to Your Majesty.
What did you say?
His Majesty suspected
that Your Majesty came here with a hidden agenda,
intending to do harm to him.
Therefore, he tried different methods,
hoping that you would take the bait
so that he could catch you red-handed.
That medicine
is one of His Majesty's many baits.
Your Majesty had not taken any action.
You were leaving today,
and you finally couldn't hold it back any longer.
You were the one who hurt His Majesty.
I didn't poison His Majesty.
We can find out easily
whether you did it or not.
Your Majesty,
I have a suggestion.
Why not leave the Queen
to the Court of Judicial Review?
The Court of Judicial Review?
Are you putting me in jail?
Your Majesty,
I swear I didn't poison His Majesty.
I saved him when I reached the Qingchi Palace.
How could I possibly poison him?
I'm leaving soon.
I'm really innocent.
This...
Your Majesty.
His Majesty is awake.
He's awake?
That's great.
Thank Heaven.
Thanks for watching over us.
-Thanks for watching over us.
-Your Majesty.
Now that His Majesty is awake,
you can ask him personally.
Let him tell you if I was the one who saved him.
Zhang.
Are you all right?
Are you feeling discomfort?
I'm fine.
Sorry to have worried you, Mother.
I'm glad that you're all right.
Duan Yunzhang.
Tell them
that I was the one who saved you
at the Qingchi Palace just now.
I didn't do anything to hurt you.
Saved me? Hurt me?
What are you saying?
Shen Ao said that you passed out
because you were poisoned.
And he insisted that I was the one
who poisoned you.
You poisoned me?
That's impossible.
It's utter nonsense.
Tell them now.
I think we can skip that.
From my vague memory,
I remember that you gave me a pill
when I was in Qingchi Palace.
Perhaps that was the poison.
Poison? Really?
When did I ever give you any pills?
Duan Yunzhang, how could you lie?
Tang.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Bring the Queen to the Western Cold Palace.
Cold Palace?
Are you mad, Duan Yunzhang?
The Queen is suspected of poisoning me.
I'm going to put you in detention
before I find out the truth.
We'll talk again
after they search the Xiangluo Hall.
Please come with me, Your Majesty.
I'm not going.
Let me go.
Let's settle this once and for all.
-You can't tell right from wrong...
-Sorry, Your Majesty.
You accused the innocent.
Let me go now!
It's just the Cold Palace.
I can walk.
Your Majesty.
(I'm sorry you have to put up with this, Jinfeng.)
Repaying kindness with evil.
A foolish emperor.
He should've just chased me out of the palace.
What is wrong with him?
Your Majesty.
We've arrived at the Western Cold Palace.
[Cold Palace]
Keep a close eye on Her Majesty.
Don't let her out,
especially tonight.
Understand?
What a shabby place.
How can anyone live here?
Stop pulling a long face.
At least, we get a roof over our heads.
Leave the stuff here.
Let's clean this place.
Search the place.
Leave no stone unturned.
Shen Ao.
Look everywhere.
Find out if she's keeping any illegal drugs.
I'll do all I can
to ensure Your Majesty's safety.
Yunchong.
Let's wait outside.
Yes, Yunzhang.
Come with me.
Search over there.
You guys come with me.
Go there.
Your Majesty,
I managed to carry out my task
and found the poison.
Shuan.
Well done.
Where did you find it?
Your Majesty.
Her Majesty kept the poison
in between the drawers of the cabinet.
It took me a while to find it.
Are you sure it's not a mistake?
Of course not.
I checked it.
It contains aconitine.
Whoever consumes this will pass out
and experience difficulty in breathing
and numbness in their limbs.
That's exactly what happened to Your Majesty.
Indeed.
You have great attention to detail.
She hid it so well
and you could still discover it.
I didn't know my sister-in-law...
Liu Jinfeng is this vicious.
I'm glad that we found evidence.
Thanks, Shen Ao.
It's my duty
to share Your Majesty's burden.
I don't deserve a compliment.
I'm talking about the crime you committed.
You poisoned me
and did everything you could to forge evidence,
just so you could frame the Queen.
It must be tough for you.
This...
Wait, Yunzhang.
What's going on?
The Queen
never gave me anything.
About the pill,
it was a story I fabricated.
I'm so sorry
to have caused such a fuss.
Shen Ao.
I didn't believe it
when His Majesty told me what happened.
You have always been
His Majesty's favorite.
What is going on?
Your Majesty,
have you always suspected Shen Ao?
Your Majesty.
I did
find the poison
in Her Majesty's chamber.
Even if Her Majesty
didn't feed Your Majesty with the poison,
it could also be someone else
who poisoned Your Majesty,
then hid the poison in Her Majesty's chamber.
Why did Your Majesty insist
that I was the one who did it?
Shen Ao.
You still refuse to admit it.
Do you think
this is the only evidence I have?
This all happened because of a coincidence.
[The Guide of Acupuncture]
I noticed that your fingers
carried a faint smell.
I wasn't too bothered by it.
I simply thought
that you were working on some new medicine.
It smelt exactly like the incense
I used when I was taking bath in Qingchi Palace.
Why did you want to kill me?
Or is someone else behind this?
I...
Let me go.
What are you doing?
Or she'll die.
Shen Ao.
You won't be able to get away.
Let her go now!
So Your Majesty has got everything prepared.
Shen Ao.
Tell me who the mastermind is,
and I'll spare you.
You know how I am.
I always keep my words.
(It was Father who ordered him to kill His Majesty.)
(No.)
(I can't let him own up that Father is behind this.)
Young Lady.
Your Majesty,
poisoning you was my own idea.
That's enough.
Shuan.
Get the imperial physician here.
It's fine, Your Majesty.
Let me finish my words.
My father
was once an imperial physician
of the Lingshu Academy too.
Your Majesty's mother, Consort Li,
fell into the water.
She had already passed away
when they finally got her out.
My father was sentenced to death
because he failed to save her.
My mother later died of depression.
I got kicked around by my relatives.
I had to live under others' roofs
and I had experienced
all the good and bad of this world.
I became an imperial physician
because I was still holding grudges.
I had never intended
to tell Your Majesty any of this.
Now I'm saying this
because I want Your Majesty to know
how much my family had suffered.
I hope that Your Majesty would watch
what you do in the future.
This is my way
to avenge my parents.
There's one more thing.
Your Majesty trusted the wrong person,
hence giving me the chance to betray you.
Your Majesty is the ruler of the country.
You should take this as a lesson
and watch carefully who you trust.
Take care, Your Majesty.
Shen Ao!
Your Majesty,
I've searched the Lingshu Academy.
I didn't find any suspicious letters.
I think
even if Shen Ao was telling the truth,
it doesn't prove
that there was no one behind this.
I'm sure it was Liu Xie.
It wasn't him.
Do you remember how I wanted to kill Liu Xie
at Qingchi Palace the other day?
My original plan
was to finish the first glass of wine
and then drop the second glass.
That was the secret sign.
However, someone hit the glass with a stone.
Wasn't the person sent by Liu Xie?
Now,
I realized that the guy wasn't trying
to ruin my plan.
Instead, he was trying to save me.
How is that possible?
It was Shen Ao.
Before Shen Ao took his own life,
he told me that when he found out
I was going to kill Liu Xie,
he approached Liu Xie.
He proposed to work with him.
He said that he would poison me.
When I finished the first glass of wine,
I would die on the spot.
Then,
not only could Liu Xie survive,
but he could also use Shen Ao to get rid of me.
Later, Liu Xie would pretend
to be investigating the cause of my death,
and that would save Shen Ao too.
Little did they know,
someone knocked over the poisoned wine.
Shen Ao said he never saw this coming
and Liu Xie was the only one
who would be capable of doing this.
Shen Ao's way more meticulous
than we thought.
Why did Liu Xie do this, then?
Since he had agreed to work with Shen Ao,
why did he try to save Your Majesty?
He doesn't look like a kind man.
I have no idea what Liu Xie is planning too.
Perhaps he wanted to keep me alive
for a while more.
I have got a lot on my mind now.
I would like to take a walk.
Don't follow me.
Shen Ao.
Do you know
that Taiyuan Pond used to be very deep?
After Mother fell into the pond,
they filled it to make it shallower.
You don't call this a pond.
Why don't they just fill it up completely?
Why didn't they
fill the pond sooner?
Now I know
why you were always staring at the pond.
So when
we were having drinks here,
you were only thinking about how to kill me.
If you really wanted to take my life,
why didn't you use
a more poisonous incense?
How could you say
that you know what you were doing?
I think
you were too careless.
You were really careless.
Later, I wondered
if I had really done something wrong.
Otherwise,
why didn't Father bless me with success?
I guess this is why.
That should be the reason.
♪The moon reflected
upon the surface of the lake♪
♪Let go of your thoughts♪
♪Swallows returning to their nests
in the evening♪
♪The soothing cicada sound♪
♪A crowded corner in the marketplace♪
♪People are having fun♪
♪Lingering emotions
and relationships of the world♪
♪You will soon find out♪
♪The moon reflected
upon the surface of the lake♪
♪Let go of your thoughts♪
♪Swallows returning to their nests
in the evening♪
♪The soothing cicada sound♪
♪A crowded corner in the marketplace♪
♪People are having fun♪
♪Lingering emotions
and relationships of the world♪
♪You will soon find out♪
♪I fall for you too early♪
♪And miss your hug♪
♪That's why I fuss over♪
♪The minute troubles with you♪
♪If I said I saw it coming♪
♪My heart wouldn't be left empty♪
♪Washing away the dust and imperial robe♪
♪I'll wait for your arrival in silence♪
[Adapted from Jinjiang Wenxuecheng's
"Queen Liu Heipang", written by Ge Yang]