♪The golden phoenix is flying
in the colorful sky♪
♪Such a rare and perfect match♪
♪I won't be oppressed by the palace rules♪
♪Love and time are rarely aligned♪
♪But it's such a perfect match♪
♪Long live the Queen? I prefer a sweet smile♪
♪One is willing to tolerate
while the other is willing to hit♪
♪Bring it on, my rival♪
♪No might can fly up to the sky♪
♪It doesn't affect my elegance at all♪
♪Great at writing family rules♪
♪And bullying the imperial bodyguards♪
♪When I turn around and flash my smile,
tears will be shed♪
♪I'm here to annoy you♪
♪The Queen has arrived!
Nothing is a big deal to me♪
♪Shouldering the responsibility
as your virtuous and capable wife♪
♪The Queen has arrived!
She brings happiness to all♪
♪Just have fun in the world! I won't turn back♪
♪What a perfect match♪
[Adapted from Jinjiang Wenxuecheng's
"Queen Liu Heipang", written by Ge Yang]
[The Legendary Life of Queen Lau]
[Episode 11]
[This work is fictitious.
Any resemblance to reality is coincidental]
Your Majesty,
are you really not going
to let Her Majesty attend
your birthday banquet this year?
This year's birthday banquet
is different from the previous years'.
It isn't just a feast this time.
It may not be a good thing for her to show up.
So are you saying you'll let Her Majesty...
Stop asking too many questions.
A tyrant! A bully! Unreasonable!
A fatuous ruler!
Your Majesty,
you've been scolding him all day.
Did I get to scold him?
He already left before I did.
I can't scold him in person.
Can't I scold his substitute?
All right.
I'll pretend I don't hear anything.
Your Majesty,
this clay doll looks like you.
Are you molding yourself and the Emperor?
Stop right there!
I'm not, so don't overthink.
I'm molding a couple of clay dolls
because Yunyan insisted.
I need some favor from her.
So I reluctantly agreed to do this.
Your Majesty,
what favor are you asking from Princess Yunyan?
I'm thinking of asking Yunyan
to bring some maidservants here
to renovate the Western Cold Palace
starting tomorrow.
A renovation?
But didn't we just repair the roof?
That's not enough.
I've thought about this for a while now.
Since Duan Yunzhang is not letting us out of here,
we'll just turn Western Cold Palace into a place
where even deities would refuse to leave.
[Taihe Hall]
The auspicious hour has arrived!
May the ceremony begins!
Your Majesty,
I'm afraid the Grand Chancellor won't be coming.
Let's wait a little longer.
Wait again?
We mustn't miss the auspicious hour.
If Your Majesty's
coming-of-age ceremony is delayed,
your officials can't afford
to bear the responsibility.
Your Majesty,
how about this?
Allow me to put on the crown for you
on behalf of the Grand Chancellor.
What do you think?
Don't bother.
I shall wait for the Grand Chancellor's arrival
no matter what.
Zhang,
are you not going to proceed with the ceremony
if the Grand Chancellor doesn't come today?
Grand Tutor Wei is the Emperor's teacher.
Listen to me
and let him put the crown on you.
Mother, don't persuade me.
I've made up my mind.
Pass my order.
We shall pick another auspicious day
for the coming-of-age ceremony.
The Grand Chancellor has arrived!
My apologies for coming late.
I hope for Your Majesty's pardon.
[Taihe Hall]
On this auspicious day,
the crown is added.
It brings glory to the ancestors.
May the Emperor's coming-of-age ceremony
brings the will to enrich the people
and prosperity to the country.
Blessings for all over the world
throughout the ages!
To celebrate the success
of the Western Cold Palace's renovation,
everyone can enjoy an unlimited supply
of liquor and meat skewers!
We may have missed out
on the Emperor's birthday this year.
But I didn't expect we get
to eat to our hearts' content here!
Yunzhang deals with many problems every day
that he overlooked things here.
Today, my sister-in-law will treat
everyone well!
Make yourself at home!
Raise your wine cup
and drink it all!
We still have many meat skewers.
Don't be shy!
[Yufang Garden]
We wish Your Majesty perpetual peace
and long life.
[Yufang Garden]
Please rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I treat
all of you as my family.
So you can drop the formalities.
Please take your seat.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Prince Yunchong presented
a handmade Iron Peach Leaf Fan.
I made this personally for you.
It's called Iron Peach Leaf Fan.
I hope it can protect you.
I hope your life is smooth sailing
and I wish Your Majesty longevity.
You're too kind.
Take a seat.
Princess Yunyan presented
a pair of happy couple figurines.
Why is Princess Yunyan not here
on my birthday?
I heard
Princess Yunyan went to the Western Cold Palace.
To meet the Queen?
Do you want me
to send someone to fetch Princess Yunyan here?
No need.
Let her bother the Queen would be good.
Let's continue.
The officials' presents are as below.
Scholar Xu presented a jade pillow.
Grand Protector Liu presented one pearl.
Censor Wang presented
a gilded pheasant enamel amphora.
[Yufang Garden]
I wish Your Majesty good health
and the Donghao Empire prosperity and peace.
Grand Chancellor,
what is this?
This is a gift I prepared for Your Majesty.
[Gift List]
You can pick
any items you want from the gift booklet.
You're so generous.
There are more gifts on this list
than all the officials' presents combined.
Don't let it trouble you.
I've received a lot of gifts
in recent years.
These are just nothing compared to what I have.
I don't feel any losses
even if I give them all to you, Your Majesty.
What did he mean by that?
Is he showing off
that he has amassed great wealth?
Don't worry.
He behaved so insolently.
His Majesty will punish him severely.
If he gets even unruly, just have his head.
Thank you for your generosity.
But I don't need these.
All these are good items.
Won't it be a pity
if you don't want them?
I only want one thing.
Something that was originally mine.
I wonder if you're willing to give it to me.
What are you going to do
if I refuse?
[Yufang Garden]
I shall fight you for it until the end.
From today on, I shall ever obey you.
Let alone allow you to abuse your power
to cover up the truth.
You of all people?
I may not be able to do it today.
I shall wait for next year.
Even if I still can't do it next year,
I shall wait for the coming years.
As long as I'm alive,
I'll never give up.
Aren't you afraid
that I never intend
to let you live until that day?
Insolence!
I am.
I'm terrified.
But after giving it some thought,
if my words can never carry
any weight in the future,
I'd rather die.
It's your birthday today.
So I can't humiliate you here.
What you're asking from me is nothing more
than taking over the reins.
Correct?
Correct.
How about this?
[Yufang Garden]
The imperial examination is after half a month.
I'm sure
you know better than me
about the Late Emperor's will.
I don't have to repeat
what's written in the posthumous edict.
Are you saying
if I can accomplish what's stipulated
in the Late Emperor's posthumous edict
and rank in the top three in the examination,
you'll hand over the reins to me?
Exactly.
You won't pull any kind of tricks, will you?
You're right about that.
I've always acted and spoken as I wanted.
I might deny
what I've said after a while.
My, my. What should I do about it?
Something bad had happened!
Thick smoke is billowing
around Western Cold Palace!
A fire must have broken out!
Guards!
Put out the fire!
Yes, Your Majesty!
Come and have some more.
Sister-in-law,
let me light the crackers to get rid of bad luck.
Hurry, light it over there.
All right.
Let's roast more.
Sister-in-law,
come and watch!
It's great!
Sister-in-law, look!
This one looks wonderful!
I want to eat that.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
What are you doing here?
You're loud and unruly.
Where are your manners?
What a rare guest.
Instead of celebrating your birthday,
what are you doing at this Cold Palace?
Don't tell me you're here to congratulate me
on the completion of my new abode
and ask for some meat skewers?
What new abode?
This isn't the Cold Palace.
It's obviously a warm palace.
Mother, you know me better.
I was thinking since I'm going
to stay here for a long time,
I'll have to make it more comfortable to stay.
We rushed here because we thought
a fire broke out at the Cold Palace.
We didn't expect
you would be mingling around
and behaving presumptuously!
You show no respect to your masters.
Mother,
it's not that serious.
We were just having a good time
at Sister-in-law's new abode.
I think you did well in renovating the palace.
Of course.
Do you know how much effort
I've spent to renovate...
Since the Queen's suspicion
of harming the Emperor
has been cleared,
doesn't that mean
Her Majesty can leave the Cold Palace now?
What do you mean?
Of course.
Liu Xie,
I don't want to move out of the Cold Palace.
I just finished renovating this place.
I haven't spent a night here yet.
Enough.
As the Queen,
you should share His Majesty's worries.
The Cold Palace isn't for you.
How about this?
You'll go to the Imperial Academy
as His Majesty's study companion.
Study companion?
If the Queen becomes the study companion,
won't it affect Yunzhang's studies?
I didn't know Your Majesty
would get affected that easily.
Liu Xie,
I don't want to go to the Imperial Academy.
All right. I agree.
From tomorrow on,
the Queen shall come with me
to the Imperial Academy.
I said I'm not going
and I'm not moving out.
Didn't you hear what I said?
About the terms of passing the reins to me,
I shall accept them.
Great.
I shall wait and see, then.
I'm not going, and I'm not moving out.
Do you hear me?
I just renovated the Cold Palace.
Are you listening to what I said?
-Shut up.
Let's go.
Mother.
It's all right. Everyone can get up now.
But you better listen.
Don't try to seduce me.
I'll never like both of you.
Young Lady,
I brought you a bowl of ginseng soup.
go to sleep after you drink it.
I'm not in the mood to drink it.
Young Lady,
if you're not upset,
you should've attended
His Majesty's birthday banquet.
He already said
not to have any ideas about him.
I'm not going to bring contempt to myself.
How about just giving up
and living happily
like Her Majesty the Queen?
Like her?
She stays at the Cold Palace.
What's so happy about that?
The maidservants said
it's lively at the Western Cold Palace.
Her Majesty has so many interesting ideas.
What's the use of having many interesting ideas?
Father dotes on her
and lets her be the Queen.
But she took it for granted.
If it were me...
What would you do if it were you?
I have no idea either.
In any case, I'd obey Father.
You are such an amazing lady.
Whenever I see you standing
together with the Queen,
I always have the wrong impression,
thinking that you are the Queen instead.
After all, when it comes
to appearance and upbringing,
you are more fitting
as the motherly model of the nation.
The Queen has arrived!
Your Majesty, why are you here?
Could it be that His Majesty...
Why?
Why can't I return?
This is my Xiangluo Hall.
Or...
do you not want me to return at all?
I was...
Did anything happen?
Yes, Baiyu.
When I wasn't around,
you sure did a lot of things.
I don't understand what you're saying.
Baiyu,
do you have feelings for His Majesty
and intend to be the Queen?
No, not at all.
Why would I?
That's impossible.
Impossible.
Sufang.
Her Majesty and I saw
how you tried to seduce His Majesty.
You can't deny that.
Young Lady,
just tell Her Majesty
that you've given up on His Majesty.
What are you saying?
That's right.
I do fancy His Majesty.
Besides, I think I'm more suitable
to be the Queen than you.
How dare you...
Your Majesty, she actually admitted it.
So now we know.
Since this is the case,
Xiangluo Hall has no place for you
if you want to keep staying in the palace.
To the Cold Palace, you go.
You...
Do you find it unbelievable?
Baiyu, haven't you heard
that women who went to the Cold Palace
cut ties with their pasts
to be born again.
They'll return for a payback.
But don't worry.
I've already renovated the Cold Palace.
Are you surprised?
Is it unexpected?
Your Majesty.
Young Lady...
Young Lady doesn't like His Majesty at all.
She was speaking nonsense.
Please show us mercy.
Have mercy on us.
Fengyue, get up.
No need to beg her.
It's just the Cold Palace.
Let's go.
I'll go.
Your Majesty,
are you sure you want to do this?
What else can I do?
Didn't you see what happened tonight?
It was such a great barbecue gathering.
It ended just like that.
In any case, there's no turning back now.
We'll just settle it like this for now.
Your Majesty,
why are you taking out all these books?
Tie, you're so forgetful.
You saw how His Majesty
angrily denounced Liu Xie just now.
He made Liu Xie agree in just a few words.
As long His Majesty ranks in the top three
in the imperial examination,
he'll pass the reins to His Majesty.
Look how forgetful I am.
Your Majesty,
eat more.
Liu Xie is a cunning man.
Are you sure he won't go back on his words?
He agreed to crown me
during my coming-of-age ceremony
when I forced him.
So I have to accept his notion this time.
When I have ranked in the top three,
let's see what he has to say.
So I planned
to spend my time at the Imperial Academy
and the study at all times.
Yunzhang,
focus on your studies.
Leave Sister-in-law to us.
We'll make sure she doesn't pull any tricks.
What does this have to do with the Queen?
You're such a fool.
This is Scorpion Liu's trick
to let the Queen be His Majesty's study companion.
Even if she does pull some tricks,
I won't be bothered by it.
Your Majesty, you're indeed wise!
Your Majesty, bad news!
Something bad had happened.
The Queen...
What?
Did she refuse to move out?
No, not that.
She moved back into Xiangluo Hall.
But she banished Miss Baiyu
to the Cold Palace.
What?
That's not something Jinfeng would do.
Yunzhang,
I heard
when a woman stays at the Western Cold Palace,
their temperament will change drastically.
It looks like it's not baseless at all.
You must be careful.
Did she think a small stick like this
would bother me?
Dream on.
Shuan,
don't bother relaying news like this to me
in the future.
I don't want to hear any of it.
Yes, Your Majesty.
This place may look decent.
But it's still the Cold Palace.
Young Lady,
the Queen is too much.
Why don't we return
to the Grand Chancellor's Residence?
We can't.
Father told me to stay in the palace,
so I can't go back.
I can't leave.
Fengyue,
what's going on?
I heard
many concubines and maidservants died
at the Cold Palace.
Could that be their spirits
making all the noise?
Don't scare me!
Feng... Fengyue,
go and check it out.
-I'm scared.
-It's all right.
Go now.
Fengyue, leave.
Liu Baiyu.
Why are you here at this late hour?
What...
What do you want to do?
We're both Father's daughters.
You better don't do anything reckless.
I especially prepared this rat poison.
Rat poison?
Liu Baiyu,
you'll get what you wished for.
You want to be the Queen, don't you?
I can help you fulfill your wish.
The Queen?
Did you see
how scared you were just now?
This rat poison
is for the rats here.
I was putting an act at Xiangluo Hall just now.
You fell for it, didn't you?
Others may see it as me oppressing you.
But the truth is I was supporting you.
My goal
is to help you gain sympathy and love from others.
I'm sure you're putting an act now.
I won't believe you.
I'm not lying to you now.
I'll just make it clearer.
I'll take today's incident, for example.
I realized
that as long as I'm in the Imperial Palace,
I'll have no human rights and freedom.
I'll always be ordered about
by Liu Xie and Duan Yunzhang.
So I've decided
to fight back.
I'll make them fight among themselves
while I control my own fate.
I want those who want to stay to remain here,
while those who want otherwise to go.
What do you mean?
That means to let you stay here,
so I can leave.
Your method is too inefficient.
I need to help you to speed it up.
The earlier you become the Queen,
the sooner I can leave the palace.
Are you serious
about helping me?
Don't you like His Majesty at all?
How do I put this?
Duan Yunzhang does have his strengths.
He's serious about being an emperor.
He's studious and not a fool.
He's also polite to the servants.
He is good-looking too.
But what's the point of all these?
He prefers fine liquor and women,
while I prefer a simple life.
We're not fated to be together.
Why are you still hesitating?
You're just scared of Liu Xie, right?
In any case, Liu Xie only needs a daughter
to become the Queen.
There's no difference
if either one of us becomes one.
Besides, you're more obedient.
Are you serious?
As long as we join hands,
we will make it.
What should we do now?
No need to whisper. There's no one else here.
Oh, you're right.
We must have a plan first.
When he shows up,
I'll slap you.
After that, you'll go into his arms
and cry...
[Imperial Academy]
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Can I get up now?
Rise.
(She's behaving strangely today.)
What brings you two here?
We're also His Majesty's study companions.
Oh, it's your side job.
I won't let you snatch my position that easily.
These two may not have
good academic achievements,
but they're better than you
when it comes to literacy.
Yes, you're right.
I know we have a huge gap between us.
So to catch up with you,
I have a study companion too.
A study companion like you
have a study companion too?
Greetings, Your Majesty.
What were you doing?
Why are you only here now?
Are you my study companion
or am I your study companion?
Why are you talking lasciviously?
Are you trying to seduce His Majesty?
I...
(What are these two up to?)
(Are they trying to disrupt my studies)
(by delaying me with their disputes?)
(I'll never fall for that.)
Stop looking! Hold this!
Wait, why is he...
Remember this.
I'm now the jealous queen who's bullying you,
while you're the damsel
waiting for His Majesty to save you.
Just wait and see.
His Majesty will take pity on you,
help you, and fall in love with you.
Let's go to class.
All right.
Hurry up, Baiyu!
Stop wasting time!
I'll get a seat for you.
Let's go.
I...
There's a rat!
Where is it?
Over there.
It ran away.
Baiyu,
you better study well
since you have got a nice spot.
Sister-in-law,
this is my seat.
Is your name written on it?
It's against the rules.
What rules?
Liu Baiyu, you better get up.
What are you doing?
You fox!
Who are you calling a fox?
She's here to disrupt Yunzhang's studies!
Can't she just sit here?
This seat doesn't have your name on it.
Stay away from here.
-But...
-Don't touch me!
I must sit here.
You're making a scene
and disrupting His Majesty from studying.
I didn't do that.
Sister-in-law, I must sit here.
Just sit over there.
I'm here to help Yunzhang with his studies.
-Don't come any closer!
-No!
I'm here to help Yunzhang with his studies!
Why can't you sit there?
Is this seat made of gold?
I'm really here to help Yunzhang with his studies!
Enough talking!
Your Highness!
Who is fighting here?
Grand Tutor Wei.
She...
Your Majesty.
As the Queen of the nation
and a woman of nobility,
how can you openly bully the prince
in the academy?
Moreover,
he's your brother-in-law.
That's not what happened, Grand Tutor Wei.
Let me explain.
It's just a misunderstanding.
Explain what?
Facts speak louder than words.
I've long heard
that the Queen is ungrateful, eccentric,
and deviant.
I didn't believe it.
After seeing you today,
you're such a disappointment.
I feel sorry and hurt for you.
Did you think I dare not punish you
because you're the Queen?
No.
You may be the Queen.
But
even if your father,
the Grand Chancellor, is here,
he'll still have to give me some face.
It would be best if one mends their ways.
Put out your hand.
I won't admit it!
Even if I did something wrong,
it's all because I love His Majesty too much.
You love me too much?
I'll say it again.
Put out your hand.
Your Majesty,
I may not be partial to anyone in my duties.
I do know
the justification
that a pampered wife is a virtuous wife.
So you'll have to bear the punishment
of having your palm being hit
on Her Majesty's behalf.
Thank you for coming to my rescue, Your Majesty.
Do it.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Stop hitting him!
Who are you?
Grand Tutor Wei,
I'm Her Majesty's study companion.
May I be bold to say this?
It is inappropriate
for you to do this.
I can't believe a mere study companion
is trying to question me.
Please enlighten me, then.
What was your original aspiration
as a grand tutor?
Original aspiration?
My original aspiration is based on,
"There'll be fire if you strike the stone,
and there'll be no smoke if you don't."
Since the Late Emperor
entrusted the Imperial Academy
to me
and bestowed me this Imperial Ruler,
I shall not be unworthy of the Late Emperor.
I'll always use it
to beat you into shape
and help you have an upright and clear sight.
What an abusive way to help one
have an upright and clear sight.
Her Majesty is indeed wrong
to make a scene in the academy.
But you declared Her Majesty guilty
entirely based on what you saw
without finding the cause.
May I be bold to ask if you have a clear sight?
You advised His Majesty to pamper his wife.
But His Majesty and Her Majesty
are not getting along.
Yet, you let His Majesty take the punishment
on Her Majesty's behalf
just because you wish to do so.
May I be bold to ask again
if your conduct is upright?
"There'll be fire if you strike the stone,
and there'll be no smoke if you don't"
is a metaphor used by Mr. Dongye
to advise students to study.
What he's trying to express is
that knowledge comes from learning.
Knowledge doesn't come without effort.
He's trying to emphasize
that one can only gain knowledge from studying.
One does not gain knowledge from beating.
Grand Tutor Wei,
you take its meaning out of context
as a teacher at the palace.
Do you not do enough scholarly research?
Who exactly are you?
I'm Liu Baiyu.
Apart from her study companion,
I'm also Her Majesty's elder sister.
Enough.
Grand Tutor Wei, punish me if you want.
If you don't, let's start the class.
Stop wasting time.
Your Majesty,
didn't you see how Baiyu helped you?
I didn't have to be punished.
It's all because of you.
It's all right.
Go back to your seats
and get back to study!
Here.
Sister-in-law,
where should I sit then?
You can sit anywhere you want.
Don't be seen.
Don't let the Consort Dowager sees us.
All right.
Sister-in-law!
[Chonghua Hall]
Yunyan?
What brings you to Chonghua Hall?
I injured Yunchong
at the Imperial Academy during the day.
So I come to see how he's doing.
Yunyan!
Please let me see Yunchong.
Huh? What?
Stop me from going in.
Yunzhang is here.
Your brother.
No!
I will never let you get close
to Yunchong today!
(Why is she here?)
(Don't tell me she's waiting especially for me.)
Princess Yunyan,
just let me see him.
Liu Jinfeng,
I've misjudged you.
I never knew you could be this ruthless.
Not only did you banish your sister
to the Cold Palace,
but you also picked on my brother.
I will never give you the chance
to bully him again!
Yunyan,
do you really think I'm a ruthless person?
Do you really think I wanted
to send my sister to the Cold Palace?
It's all your brother, the Emperor's fault.
(My fault?)
(Why is it my fault?)
I hated Duan Yunzhang.
But when I see him and Baiyu
exchanging flirty glances at each other,
I get so upset.
I get jealous.
I couldn't even control myself.
What else could I do?
(Don't tell me she really fell in love with me)
(as she said at the Imperial Academy)
(during the day?)
[Chonghua Hall]
Why are you causing a ruckus at this late hour?
You were punished on my behalf today.
Take these medicinal herbs.
What?
Yunzhang,
you were punished in her stead?
No such thing.
Don't listen to her nonsense.
What evil thoughts are you thinking
for banishing your sister to the Cold Palace?
Did you just scold me?
You were all smiles with her
but so fierce with me.
Could it be that you're feeling sorry for her?
Could it be that you want
to go to the Cold Palace to see her?
Could it be that you'll change
the Western Cold Palace
to the Western Warm Palace?
If you go and see her today,
I'll jump into this Taiyuan Pond.
I mean what I say.
I've sworn an oath
that you'll only love me in this life.
You can never depose me or take in consorts.
(The Queen has lost her senses.)
(It looks like I have to believe)
(that I'm absolutely charming.)
(She may have resisted in many ways before,)
(but she still fails to resist)
(such a temptation.)
(Now she's being irrational because of love.)
(How pitiful.)
Taiyuan Pond is too shallow for you to die.
Are you a fool?
I'm going to visit Yunchong.
Yunyan, watch her
and don't let her wander off.
What does this mean?
(I behaved like a shrew just now.)
(I was acting hysterically.)
(I'm sure he hates me a lot now.)
(Hurry and let me scare you away,)
(so you'll go into the arms of Baiyu.)
Your Highness, please endure.
Gently, please.
Three. Two.
Oh, my.
Your Highness,
how do you feel now?
Are you all right now?
I can't believe it.
I'm fine now.
You can leave now.
Yes, Your Highness.
Remember.
Don't let my mother know about this.
Yes, Your Highness.
I shall take my leave now.
Go.
It's all that jinx's fault.
She almost killed me.
Jinfeng is indeed rash and rude.
It's my fault.
Yunzhang,
I was talking about Liu Baiyu.
You see?
You're taking her side.
Liu Baiyu stood up for you
at the Imperial Academy today
because she wanted to get on your good side.
Of course,
Sister-in-law is behaving strangely lately.
She's becoming scarier.
Do you think I don't know all these?
But it's not their fault.
I'm the one to blame.
What does this have to do with you?
How is it not related to me?
It's my fault for being too charming
that both women lost their rationality
because of me.
I should be blamed.
Yunzhang,
is that a joke?
How is it a joke?
Didn't you see
how Jinfeng mistreated Liu Baiyu today?
Liu Baiyu may appear to be silently enduring it.
But you can see she has set her sights on me
and is prepared to seduce me at any time.
If this goes on,
how am I going to study
if a fight really breaks out between them?
Yunchong,
I have a task for you.
From tomorrow on,
you'll be responsible
for keeping an eye on Liu Baiyu
to reduce her contact with the Queen.
While I
will be responsible
for reducing Jinfeng's anger
with my charm.
This will prevent the conflict
between them from happening at the root.
Then we can create
a good learning environment.
Me?
Keep an eye on Liu Baiyu?
No way.
Are you going
to watch them torment me?
What if I get poor results in the examination?
Fine.
I'll do my best for you.
That's more like it.
Liu Baiyu,
you better watch it.
Shuan,
deliver my edict.
Say that I sympathize with the Queen
for renovating the Western Cold Palace.
From now on, Western Cold Palace
will be changed to Western Warm Palace.
It'll be Liu Baiyu's temporary residence
in the palace.
Is there a meaning to this, Your Majesty?
Isn't it obvious enough?
Liu Baiyu isn't one of my concubines.
She doesn't have the right
to stay at the Cold Palace.
If this gets out to those who don't know,
they would think she's involved with me.
I don't want such a misunderstanding.
If you change the name,
aren't you afraid Her Majesty might think
you're making advances on Miss Baiyu?
It's all right if she misunderstands.
She'll be having a sleepless night
with her heart dissipating in the air.
When she finds out about this tomorrow,
she'll be extremely happy
and wild with joy.
Go now.
What did I tell you?
Men just won't admit it.
It was during the day
he treated you indifferently yesterday.
And he changed the name of the Cold Palace
on the same night.
You need to work harder today.
You might conquer him.
Go.
Your Majesty,
thank you for changing the Western Cold Palace
to Western Warm Palace.
Liu Baiyu,
you can just sit here.
Why? This isn't my seat.
Do other seats have your name on them?
It's against the rules.
What rules?
But that's...
Don't disturb Yunzhang from studying.
♪Only second to the Emperor♪
♪Anyone who's against it should back off♪
♪I'll make a face and fear no heaven and earth♪
♪I'll let you go for now♪
♪I'm not a motherly model♪
♪Nor am I the most beautiful lady♪
♪Who says those of humble origin
can't be elegant?♪
♪Bring it on. Let's make a big bet♪
♪To be a huge winner♪
♪A couple of quarrelsome lovers♪
♪An odd coincidence became a much-told tale♪
♪Holding bad cards yet I play well still♪
♪Accept the plot twist♪
♪Cut all the romantic themes♪
♪To talk about love is childish♪
♪I shall redefine peerless elegance♪
♪Are you ready?♪
♪Tremble, my rivals♪
♪Look, the phoenix in the sky
is actually a little crow♪
♪Surprising the world with its talent♪
♪Experiencing the ups and downs♪
♪In return for a wiser life♪
♪Don't ever look down on the little crow♪
♪She wears the crown and controls the world♪
♪Striking back♪
♪To be the head of the harem♪
♪Look, the phoenix in the sky
is actually a little crow♪
♪Surprising the world with its talent♪
♪Experiencing the ups and downs♪
♪In return for a wiser life♪
♪Don't ever look down on the little crow♪
♪She wears the crown and controls the world♪
♪Striking back♪
♪To be the head of the harem♪
♪Little crow♪
♪Dear little crow♪
♪Striking back to be the head of the harem♪
♪Little crow♪
[Adapted from Jinjiang Wenxuecheng's
"Queen Liu Heipang", written by Ge Yang]