♪The golden phoenix is flying
in the colorful sky♪
♪Such a rare and perfect match♪
♪I won't be oppressed by the palace rules♪
♪Love and time are rarely aligned♪
♪But it's such a perfect match♪
♪Long live the Queen? I prefer a sweet smile♪
♪One is willing to tolerate
while the other is willing to hit♪
♪Bring it on, my rival♪
♪No might can fly up to the sky♪
♪It doesn't affect my elegance at all♪
♪Great at writing family rules♪
♪And bullying the imperial bodyguards♪
♪When I turn around and flash my smile,
tears will be shed♪
♪I'm here to annoy you♪
♪The Queen has arrived!
Nothing is a big deal to me♪
♪Shouldering the responsibility
as your virtuous and capable wife♪
♪The Queen has arrived!
She brings happiness to all♪
♪Just have fun in the world! I won't turn back♪
♪What a perfect match♪
[Adapted from Jinjiang Wenxuecheng's
"Queen Liu Heipang", written by Ge Yang]
[The Legendary Life of Queen Lau]
[Episode 21]
[This work is fictitious.
Any resemblance to reality is coincidental]
Why haven't I heard this drum rhythm before?
I feel like I've heard it somewhere.
It sounds familiar.
[East]
Stop playing it randomly.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Stop.
Grand Chancellor.
Let's speak inside the main camp.
Can someone give me an explanation?
What's going on with this?
Let me say it instead.
With a lack of equipment,
we can only replace it with defective equipment.
With a lack of soldiers,
we can only use old soldiers instead of the young.
With low morale,
we can only retreat and defend.
Grand Chancellor, you are very daring.
I was daring indeed.
But without being so,
who would speak the truth without fearing
that they might be executed?
Ask them.
Will they say it?
Since you knew about it,
why didn't you report it?
I reported it.
Your Majesty didn't approve it.
When was it?
When Your Majesty took control,
I requested Your Majesty three times
to increase taxes to be used for military funds.
But Your Majesty didn't approve it even once.
Using the people's money
to increase our military funds?
Do you want me to be scolded for centuries
and be a fatuous emperor?
Your Majesty, there's no need to be angry.
What Your Majesty saw
wasn't all true.
What do you mean?
Did the Grand Chancellor put on an act
just to make me happy?
You are correct.
Your Majesty is starting to understand me well.
The armor and weapons
on the soldiers that Your Majesty saw
were the worst out of our military equipment.
I purposely asked the soldiers
to use them for drills
to show Your Majesty.
Grand Chancellor.
You have committed
the crime of lying to the Emperor.
You seem to have misunderstood
the term "lying to the Emperor", Your Majesty.
"Lying to the Emperor"
means lying and hiding things
from Your Majesty.
What these people did
can be defined as "lying to the Emperor".
But I only used
a dramatic method
to show Your Majesty directly how scary it is
to have a lack of military equipment.
That's not considered "lying to the Emperor".
I just want Your Majesty
to feel the situation for yourself.
Simply increasing the people's taxes
only to increase our military funds?
I'm familiar
with the way of Confucius and Mencius.
I know well about governing the empire
with benevolence and righteousness.
I've never heard of such reasons.
Did Your Majesty say "only"?
Someone!
[Diligent and Committed]
Is it not pleasant to learn
with constant perseverance and application?
Having friends come from afar...
Grand Tutor Wei.
You come here today...
Let me ask you.
Why do you even study?
How would they understand a question like that?
Be direct.
I'll be direct then.
Today, someone actually
wanted His Majesty to become a sinner.
Let me ask you.
What should we do?
That's...
Grand Tutor Wei.
You may not know this.
A student becomes like this
when they have a lot of knowledge.
You need to make it easier for them to understand.
Easier?
I've already made myself very clear.
I'm telling you.
Stop studying!
All of you, come with me and do something great!
What is this?
This is the "only" Your Majesty mentioned.
Where did you get this?
Don't say it.
Her Majesty was wise.
Every word and sentence here
was written by Her Majesty
and given to me.
Why did you show this to me, Grand Chancellor?
Your Majesty might not know about this.
I've done some calculations.
In the imperial capital,
there are a total of 1,388 maidservants.
90% of them have a family member in the military.
That means
the soldiers Your Majesty saw out there
were the fathers, siblings, husbands, and uncles
of your maidservants.
I don't understand.
Of course, you don't understand, Your Majesty.
You only think
they are just Donghao Empire's soldiers,
Your Majesty.
But they might also be
a baby's father.
An old man's only son.
A noble wife's husband.
Using the word "only" when it comes to these people.
Don't you feel ashamed?
When a soldier dies on the battlefield,
a family will be destroyed
on the land of the Donghao Empire.
Every piece of tough armor
and the sharp blade you provide
isn't just giving them
the weapon to defend against the enemy.
It is also a hope for their family members
to have a happy life.
If you still don't understand,
I'm willing to bring you
to another place, Your Majesty.
(Why do I feel that Liu Xie is a kind of cool?)
Grand Chancellor is so nice.
Why did he marry the wonderful Baiyu off
to our Chong?
You are blessed.
He married Grand Chancellor's daughter.
What do you mean, Your Majesty?
Didn't Zhang
marry Grand Chancellor's daughter as well?
But I need to remind you.
The most important thing between husband and wife
is to have a harmonious relationship.
I understand.
But His Majesty and Her Majesty
weren't on good terms with each other initially.
Our queen is quite special.
Although she isn't as smart,
thoughtful, and intelligent
as Baiyu...
Enough.
Don't you feel exhausted saying so many words?
I do feel exhausted.
Don't you know?
Since my son is about to get married,
there are many things to prepare.
The date of marriage.
The location of the mansion.
The type of wedding attires.
There are many things to consider.
I'm having a headache thinking about it.
I won't be drinking tea with you today.
I have many things to prepare.
We'll go and make preparations first.
Biyun, let's go.
Yes, Your Highness.
I'm leaving, Your Majesty.
She must have done it purposely.
It's so hot.
Look how arrogant she is.
Her son is just going to marry Liu Baiyu. So what?
Xianpa Village!
I'm finally back!
Why did you bring me here?
This is Xianpa Village.
[Xianpa Village]
A few decades ago,
it didn't go by this name.
It was called Qilian Village.
Do you know
why it was called this name, Your Majesty?
I don't even know about it.
There was a Wu family here.
His ancestors gave birth to seven sons in a row.
So, the village is known as Qilian.
[* Qilian means seven in a row]
Since the old days,
this village had been full of men.
But nowadays,
the village is called Xianpa Village.
There's not even a strong man
who can work in this village.
It's because of war.
There's a story like that?
In the Battle of Eight Kings 70 years ago,
the total number of men from Qilian Village
who died in battle
was 3,143.
In the Turmoil of Jizhou 50 years ago,
the total number of men
from this village who died in battle
was 2,853.
30 years ago,
during the Rebellion of Xinan,
in which Your Majesty said your ancestors
invented the Imperial Formation,
the total number of men who died in battle
was 1,651.
To Your Majesty,
they are just numbers.
But to every family in this village,
it is a painful past.
Our village was so pitiful.
Your Majesty studied the way of Confucius
and Mencius and you want to govern the empire
with benevolence and righteousness.
I agree with that.
But I still need to teach Your Majesty a lesson.
The benevolence is not the benevolence of women.
The righteousness is not
the righteousness of the martial arts world.
Father.
Can I ask you a question?
Go ahead.
How many people from our village died?
Which war are we talking about?
The one that happened 70 years ago.
3,153.
What about the war from 30 years ago?
1,650...
You are really good at lying.
You are lying to the Emperor, Father.
Be quiet.
I made up the story.
It's not lying.
At most,
I used a very dramatic method
to tell His Majesty that he is an emperor
and not a saint.
How did you make a lie
sound like it's the truth?
That is a good question.
Do you know why
there's truth in this world?
Because someone told a lie.
Enough.
Tonight,
you'll stay here with His Majesty.
I've prepared everything.
Just think of it
as returning to visit your relatives.
What about my mother?
You've met her already.
Already?
When was it, Father?
Yunzhang.
You must be hungry.
This is our village's specialty.
Castle Full of Golden Armor.
Have some.
You knew all about this, right?
Don't listen to my father's nonsense.
I was forced.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I didn't expect him
to throw all the information out
without even telling me.
I was wrong. I apologize.
At the time, I was...
Jinfeng.
You already knew such an easy concept
of conducting yourself as the Queen.
But you didn't tell me directly
and used such a roundabout way to tell me.
I should thank you.
I used to foolishly think
you made the questionnaires
to understand me.
But I realized what you did was more meaningful.
You wanted me to know the empire,
the people,
and how to be a good emperor.
Am I right?
Yes.
Jinfeng.
I know what to do.
You said I could hit the drum
but why did I get hit by the drum instead?
It's my fault.
Why does Jinfeng
still have a bad temper after becoming the Queen?
It's my fault.
I didn't teach her well.
It's exactly your fault.
You wanted me to meet her.
But what's this nonsense that you arranged?
Okay.
I'll make a better arrangement next time.
I'm so dizzy.
Am I seriously injured?
Why do I feel so painful?
It's all my fault.
I'm wrong.
What do you mean?
Why did you keep washing my right foot?
Are you looking down on my left foot?
Let's switch it to the other foot then.
No matter where they are,
Master has ordered us
to find them even if it means
turning the capital upside down.
Move!
Both of you, go to East Gate.
Both of you, go to West Gate.
We'll enter the city
from both the east and west.
It won't do.
As the ancient saying goes,
make a feint in the east, but attack in the west.
Heading to the same place from both sides
is not right.
No.
Sun Tzu's Art of War says
the art of war
is of vital importance to the Empire.
It is a matter of life and death,
a road either to safety or to ruin.
An inquiry is of the utmost importance.
To be exact, the first is political.
The second is timing. The third is geography.
The fourth is...
No.
All of you are wrong.
According to the "Attack by Stratagem" chapter,
the best way is to win by strategy,
followed by diplomatic relations,
followed by crushing the army,
and finally, by attacking a city.
Attacking the city is not a viable method.
Enough!
What are you talking about?
Did you only learn
about military theories in class?
Take them away!
Your Majesty.
I have something to report.
Grand Chancellor, please speak.
There's a lack of military funds.
I hope Your Majesty can think about
increasing taxes to be used as military funds.
I object!
Speak.
You don't know this, Your Majesty.
Yesterday, a group of men in black
rushed into the Grand Tutor's Residence
and captured the Grand Tutor
along with a few dozen students.
Their whereabouts are still unknown until now.
What?
Who did that?
Who else could it be?
The rumors of tax increases
have been spreading all around the capital.
With the Grand Tutor
and his students being captured,
everyone in the capital is panicking.
I request Your Majesty
not to approve Grand Chancellor's request
and release Grand Tutor Wei and his students.
Everyone, please leave for now.
I have something important
to discuss with the Grand Chancellor.
Dismiss.
-We will be leaving, Your Majesty.
Grand Chancellor.
Did you really do it?
Do you even need to ask?
Am I not the one
who always does these things?
Grand Chancellor, why did you do that?
Before asking me, Your Majesty must understand
why so many students
were gathering in Grand Tutor Wei's house.
I have an idea about that.
I will also deal with Grand Tutor Wei.
Grand Chancellor, you should release them.
What if Grand Tutor Wei still can't come out?
Grand Chancellor, do you need
to put everyone on the spot?
Actually, it's easy to get Grand Tutor Wei out.
It depends on your decision, Your Majesty.
You are trying to make a deal with me?
It's obvious.
But this deal is worth it for you, Your Majesty.
Tell me about it.
Calm the grievances
of the people in the capital in three days.
If Your Majesty can do that,
I guarantee
Grand Tutor Wei and his students
will return safely.
Deal.
I'll be leaving then.
At the moment,
we only have one method.
What is it?
Jing.
How many imperial bodyguards do you still have?
Counting those who are on duty and off duty,
around 20 people.
The men under you
are fewer than the people I have
in the Imperial Kitchen.
We have blades.
What do you have?
We have cleavers.
Let's compare. Come.
Stop fighting.
Twenty people are fine.
Your Highness.
What are you trying to do?
It's obvious.
Now that there's chaos out there,
why else would I request men from you?
Well,
we only have 20 people.
There are at least 200 citizens
who are protesting.
That's...
What can we do?
You really have no clue, huh?
Can we calm down
the protesting citizens out there?
I'm requesting men from you
to save Wei in the prison.
No.
You will be beheaded for this.
Even the Emperor is going. Who dares to behead us?
That's not right.
You're right, Your Majesty.
I think so too.
Twenty people are too many.
Just a few of us are enough.
Come here. We'll do this.
I'll scout ahead.
Protect His Majesty here
and wait for my signal.
What if you get caught?
I'll tell them my identity.
I'm an imperial bodyguard after all.
What can they do to me?
You're so rash.
Who would break into the prison
by revealing their identities?
I am the Emperor, Duan Yunzhang.
Open the gate immediately.
Open the gate immediately!
Let's go.
What is His Majesty doing?
Doing one thing as a diversion.
Yunzhang must have something else planned.
The design of this place is complicated.
His Majesty must have placed many men around.
Just wait here.
I want to meet the Grand Tutor alone.
Yunzhang.
Your Majesty!
It's too dangerous, Your Majesty!
Come back.
Grand Tutor, you have suffered.
I have a bet with Grand Chancellor Liu.
If I can calm the public grievances,
they will release you.
Are you blaming me?
Grand Tutor, please say something.
Let him say it.
Young man.
What did you call me?
No. Junior.
Grand Tutor Wei has left a message.
What is it?
Grand Tutor Wei said
if his students only know
how to talk about strategies
without adapting to the situation,
he'd rather die in the prison.
What else did he say?
He also said
he is annoyed at hearing his students speak.
No one should disturb him tonight.
Thank you for your guidance, Grand Tutor.
Sir, can we leave?
Go back.
Sir.
How's your investigation?
I've cross-referenced the list
that you provided, Grand Chancellor.
I found nothing.
What should we do next?
Just leave it to me.
You may leave now.
Yes, sir.
Seems like she's the only person who can help.
The rapacious Grand Chancellor Liu.
Helper of the tyrant, Queen Lau.
Greedy Queen, Evil Emperor.
Both the Emperor and the Queen are mad.
A cruel government that's worse than a tiger.
Doesn't the person who wrote this feel afraid?
It's serious and he will be beheaded.
It is serious indeed.
Your Majesty.
Please tell His Majesty to calm down.
You should tell me to calm down first.
Your Majesty?
Look at it.
It was Liu Xie and His Majesty
who are asking them for money.
Why did they involve me?
I feel so aggrieved.
Liu Xie is so evil.
He is not only harming His Majesty but me as well.
I don't get it.
Was Mother blind
to fell in love
with such an annoying person?
Grand Chancellor.
What a coincidence.
Isn't this my dear father?
Dear Father.
Please take a look.
Look at your work of art.
Do you see it clearly?
I see it clearly.
You've ruined all of our reputations.
These characters
were badly written.
Come.
Let me show you some nice handwriting.
[Fang Yu Fu Hua Qian]
[* Incredible Beauty]
Did you come here
just to show off your handwriting?
It's part of the reasons.
Go to the point.
Help me find this in the palace.
After you find it...
After I find it,
you'll take me to see my mother, right?
I know you are using this trick again.
Let's up the ante.
You can make a wish
and I'll fulfill it.
For real?
You need to give me a hint at least.
It's related to the people here?
Not at all.
I investigated it.
What kind of hint is this?
Eliminating the wrong options
is a hint as well, right?
Do your best. I believe in you.
[Fang Yu Fu Hua Qian]
Fang Yu Fu Hua Qian?
What is it?
[Xuanchen Hall]
The whole capital is in a mess.
The butchers are putting up posters
and the vegetable sellers are pulling banners.
The prices of the Imperial Kitchen's supply
are three times higher now.
It's chaos out there.
Most importantly,
parents are causing chaos,
and kids are not going to school.
Yunzhang.
Do you know how serious it is
for children to not go to school?
Just yesterday alone,
99 cases of troublemaking by children
were reported.
Not just that.
Yesterday morning, a dozen of children
went to the South Gate's old archway
to make a mess.
They made the century-old archway
collapse.
Enough!
Isn't there any good news?
Not even one?
Your Majesty.
The old archway
was supposed to be demolished
and reconstructed at the end of the month.
We've saved the demolition fee.
I'm telling you.
If we can't calm down the public,
even Donghao Empire can't survive
let alone Grand Tutor Wei.
Think of something.
Your Majesty.
What are you thinking about?
I'm thinking about the problem Father has left me.
What problem is it?
Let me help you.
Might as well.
You've been here for a long time.
Have you heard of a place,
an incident, or a thing
that's related to Fang Yu Fu Hua Qian?
Fang Yu Fu Hua Qian?
I think I've heard about it.
Have you?
Your Majesty.
Have you thought about
the possibility
that it might not be a place or a thing?
It might be two people.
Two people?
Look.
Fang Yu. Fu Huaqian.
Doesn't it sound like two people's names?
You know them?
I remember
there was an old maid by the Late Emperor's side.
Her name was Fang Yu.
There was also an old eunuch with the surname Fu.
But I don't know where they went
after they retired.
Let's go and find the old maid.
Your Majesty.
Haven't you heard before
that we are not supposed to find
the old maids in the palace?
Who is allowed to find them then?
They are a bit...
A bit...
Your Majesty.
Imperial Physician Yu
is just their new favorite.
These old maids
have an idol who has an unshakable status.
An idol?
Who is it?
That person is wise, dignified,
a hero in his youth, and very smart.
These old maids
watched him grow up in the palace
until he achieved something great.
It's him?
Your Majesty.
If you can get a piece of his personal belonging,
and give it to Old Maid Fang Yu,
I'm sure she will give you some hints.
Are you asking me to steal from him?
There's no need to steal.
With your relationship with him,
I'm sure he will give it to you
if you ask him for it.
After all,
no daughter will fail to ask for something
from his father.
Father?
That person you mentioned was my father?
Yes.
The idol of the old maids
is Grand Chancellor.
Pretty faces. So they are all fond of pretty faces.
Pretty Face.
What's wrong with you?
Did someone beat you up?
Show me. Don't hide from me.
What's wrong with you?
Don't run. I won't laugh at you.
I need you for something.
I won't laugh anymore.
It's fine. I won't laugh at you.
Don't cry. It's fine.
I won't tell anyone else.
I have a favor to ask from you.
It's true!
What are they doing?
I don't know.
Let go. Let go!
It's so funny!
Yu Changya.
Are you done laughing?
Obviously not.
Yu Changya. You deserve it.
I'm respecting the elderly.
Those old maids have no one to depend on.
I'm accompanying them
and doing facials for them
to earn a bit of money. What's wrong with that?
You were doing a facial over here?
Besides, are you really
earning just a bit of money?
Why did you look for me anyway?
I want you to send a letter to my mother.
No.
Do you really trust me?
I didn't in the past,
but it's different now.
From what I saw,
I can already create many different stories.
I'll definitely send you the letter.
Where's the letter?
Here.
Aren't you afraid that I'll take a peek?
No.
With your intelligence,
you won't understand it.
I really don't understand.
Why are you here?
The Imperial Palace belongs to me.
I can be anywhere I want.
Why are you here?
What's yours is mine.
I can also be anywhere I want.
Where have you been? Who did you meet?
What have you done?
Just now...
Why should I tell you?
I am the Emperor.
I have the right to know
everything that happens in the palace.
Did you just...
Nonsense. I didn't.
I won't tell you if you won't admit it.
Are you...
Will you admit it?
I'm leaving if you're not.
Stand there.
I got jealous.
What?
I admitted it. Stop pretending.
Did you get jealous of Yu Changya?
I thought you wanted some juicy gossip.
Do you even want those old women?
What old women?
Don't spread it.
Otherwise,
there won't be juicy gossip like this anymore.
I got jealous for nothing.
Of course.
You are so much better than Yu.
But I didn't expect
so many interesting things
to happen in the Imperial Palace.
I wonder if Sufang
has any more gossip.
I need to ask her again later.
Why are you all interested in these things?
We are not the only ones.
Everyone in the world is interested in it.
You don't get it, right?
Let me tell you.
Do you know what the things
that people talked about most
in Xianpa Village are?
It's not whether there is a landslide
or an earthquake somewhere.
It is whether Wang's daughter
wants to marry Li's son
or Fang's son.
Also
whether the old woodcutter's son
is his biological son.
And
who was the one
who stole Granny Wang's chicken?
What?
Young man.
You are the Emperor.
Your job is to think about the Empire.
But normal citizens
only think about
household issues when they wake up.
What concerns them
are not the Empire-related issues
but household issues.
That's what a normal citizen is thinking.
Understand?
I got it!
I know that
but why are you so excited?
Now, let me share more with you.
Do you understand?
We do understand.
But why do we need to understand all these?
Exactly.
What dishes
does the Grand Chancellor's chef cook every day?
What flowers are planted in Prince De's backyard?
Which fabric shop
did Commandery Prince Wen's
womenfolk patronize?
Also.
How many times does the Ministry of War's
Official Pi visit the restaurant every month?
How many servants does
the Ministry of Rites' Official Wu have?
How are they related?
Grand Tutor Wei is right.
It's no use to think about it that way.
We need to learn to adapt.
Is this what you call adapting?
Your gamble with Scorpion Liu
is to calm the public grievances.
How are they useful?
This is just the first step.
Something greater is coming.
Madam Fu.
Why are you here?
Jinfeng asked me to give you this letter.
Do you understand it?
I understand.
Wait for me.
Madam Fu.
What's wrong with your mouth?
It's nothing.
Wait for me here.
I won't be long.
Sure.
All right.
Take these to Jinfeng.
So many?
What are they?
Oh.
When you see Jinfeng, remember to tell her
that I'm doing fine.
Ask her not to worry.
Sure.
Madam Fu.
Well...
Jinfeng is now the Queen.
Do you think these things...
Just take them to her.
Just do as I ordered.
Yes. All right.
I'll get going then, Madam Fu.
Go on.
Are they too heavy?
No. Not really.
Go on then.
All right.
I'm leaving.
Take care.
Look at how fragile he is.
Hurry up.
Arrange them nicely.
Sure.
[Liu Xie's Love Stories]
I heard that purple
is Grand Chancellor Liu's favorite color.
Something like this.
Really?
But I heard Grand Chancellor Liu
likes stargazing.
He also brought all his girlfriends
to stargaze.
There are only 1,000 books left.
Get it while you can.
Alright.
You can't get it if you're late. Hurry up!
This is yours.
That's so bad.
You promised to release it yesterday
but you released it today.
-Exactly.
All right.
Take care.
This is yours.
For you.
[The Legend of Liu Xie, Jerk of the Ages]
The last 1,000 books.
Get it now!
Take care!
Get it while it's available!
[Xuanchen Hall]
Yunzhang.
I've put all the picture books
on sale according to your order.
They'll be in trouble recently.
Especially Grand Chancellor Liu.
The students I found
all liked writing his stories.
Oh, Your Majesty.
I've already sorted out
every official's monthly expenditure
according to your order.
Good job.
Yunzhang.
There's something I still don't understand.
What you want is to divert
the people's attention away
from the tax increase.
Why do you want these as well?
That is just a temporary solution.
The main issue
lies in this.
Didn't Liu Xie give me a problem?
I will return the problem to him.
Those officials.
Their expenditures
have exceeded their wages.
If it isn't corruption,
that means they have other assets.
Whether the taxes related to these assets
have been paid or not,
that's something I do not know.
But do you think Liu Xie won't know?
-You are wise, Your Majesty!
This is called beating someone at their own game.
Gosh.
Liu Xie is evil
but he is so handsome.
Your Majesty.
It's almost done.
Why isn't he here yet?
Don't worry. He will definitely be here.
Your Majesty.
He's here.
Told you. He will surely be here.
No, Your Majesty.
Look!
♪Only second to the Emperor♪
♪Anyone who's against it should back off♪
♪I'll make a face and fear no heaven and earth♪
♪I'll let you go for now♪
♪I'm not a motherly model♪
♪Nor am I the most beautiful lady♪
♪Who says those of humble origin
can't be elegant?♪
♪Bring it on. Let's make a big bet♪
♪To be a huge winner♪
♪A couple of quarrelsome lovers♪
♪An odd coincidence became a much-told tale♪
♪Holding bad cards yet I play well still♪
♪Accept the plot twist♪
♪Cut all the romantic themes♪
♪To talk about love is childish♪
♪I shall redefine peerless elegance♪
♪Are you ready?♪
♪Tremble, my rivals♪
♪Look, the phoenix in the sky
is actually a little crow♪
♪Surprising the world with its talent♪
♪Experiencing the ups and downs♪
♪In return for a wiser life♪
♪Don't ever look down on the little crow♪
♪She wears the crown and controls the world♪
♪Striking back♪
♪To be the head of the harem♪
♪Look, the phoenix in the sky
is actually a little crow♪
♪Surprising the world with its talent♪
♪Experiencing the ups and downs♪
♪In return for a wiser life♪
♪Don't ever look down on the little crow♪
♪She wears the crown and controls the world♪
♪Striking back♪
♪To be the head of the harem♪
♪Little crow♪
♪Dear little crow♪
♪Striking back to be the head of the harem♪
♪Little crow♪
[Adapted from Jinjiang Wenxuecheng's
"Queen Liu Heipang", written by Ge Yang]