Your son shoplifted from my store.
What?
That is, if you show me your sincerity.
We shouldn't let him manipulate us
any further.
What is he demanding?
Long time no see, Junichi.
Junichi?
You appeared before him as a detective.
Sorry for making you worry.
It's okay.
The four people involved in the incident
23 years ago
reunited because Sakuma was murdered.
Let's open the time capsule.
This will be a secret between
just the four of us.
It's gone.
One of us here opened the time capsule
and took out that gun.
Give me time. I'll tell the truth.
Why can't you tell me now?
I can, but Makiko…
Ms. Makiko Iwamoto is clearly lying.
I went because you suggested it.
Why?
I don't know why.
I remember seeing someone walking around
the school grounds during my evening walk.
It was a black SUV
with a Shinagawa license plate.
Is it because they used to be married?
It's very interesting
how perfectly their alibis
line up with each other.
On January 18th, just after 9:00 a.m.,
the body of Hideyuki Sakuma, the manager
of Smile Sakuma Mitsuba Minami branch,
was discovered.
The murder weapon was a gun.
The estimated time of death is just before
10:00 p.m. the previous day, Saturday.
There are only reports of hearing gunshots
and no eyewitness accounts.
There are no clues to the culprit,
and the murder weapon, the gun,
has not been found.
WEAPON - GUN
GUN THAT BELONGED TO OFFICER KIYOHARA
The murder weapon is a gun
that belonged to Officer Kazuo Kiyohara,
who was shot and killed by the perpetrator
of the Yamato Trust Bank
armored car robbery 23 years ago.
It's the gun that has been missing
for the past 23 years.
We must find the culprit
and recover the gun as soon as possible.
As for the fact
that a police officer's gun was used
as the murder weapon,
the prefectural police's senior officials
are still carefully discussing the matter,
including whether or not
to disclose it to the media.
No conclusion has been reached yet.
Please ensure that this information
is kept confidential.
Yes, sir.
MITSUBA POLICE STATION
We have yet to determine the whereabouts
of the victim on the day of the incident.
Sir.
I talked to the employee
at the pachinko parlor
but couldn't get any useful information.
Anyone else find any leads?
Yes, sir.
Makiko Iwamoto visited Smile Sakuma
the day before the incident,
so she was questioned as a witness,
but we have since found out that
she lied in her testimony.
What?
On that day, Ms. Iwamoto
went to pick up her sixth-grade son
after he had been caught shoplifting.
In exchange for keeping
the shoplifting incident a secret…
You're saying that I have an accomplice?
That night, at 11:00 p.m.,
Ms. Makiko Iwamoto and her ex-husband,
Mr. Keisuke Kiyohara,
went to hand over the 300,000 yen.
What were their alibis
on the day of the incident?
Yes, sir. The two were at a restaurant
in the city at 8:00 p.m.
After 8:30 p.m., Ms. Makiko Iwamoto
went to Ma Saison hair salon,
and Mr. Keisuke Kiyohara went to a hotel.
They met again at the restaurant
at 10:30 p.m.
It’s been confirmed that Mr. Kiyohara
did indeed go to the hotel.
We have yet to confirm that Ms. Iwamoto
was indeed at the hair salon.
Excuse me.
Has the alibi
of the victim's younger brother,
Mr. Naoto Sakuma, been verified?
Well? Has it?
Yes, sir.
Mr. Naoto Sakuma
returned from Korea on a flight
arriving at Haneda Airport at 8:55 p.m.
He traveled home by car,
and due to heavy traffic,
he arrived home shortly before 11:00 p.m.
The 8:55 p.m. arrival time at Haneda
has been confirmed with the airline.
His mother has corroborated
that he arrived home before 11:00 p.m.
That's all.
Verify the alibis of Iwamoto and Kiyohara
and re-examine all witness accounts
from the surrounding area. Adjourned.
Yes, sir.
- You overslept?
- Sorry.
Or are you
investigating something on your own?
No.
We're buddy detectives, right?
I can't believe I said "buddy."
I'm sorry.
Yes, we're buddies.
We're buddies.
The entrance that will be built
around here
will be made with wood
from trees in Mitsuba City.
We hope to create a shopping mall
that exudes warmth,
and fosters a sense of community,
so that everyone
will want to visit every day.
Don't you think you should act
a little more like a company president?
How does a president act?
I guess they’re usually
confident and sharp.
But I’m not even the president.
You’re the managing director,
but you’re the next president.
That’s true, but…
Speaking of which, you used to get
a lot of arranged marriage proposals.
To daughters of local company owners
or the granddaughters of chairmen.
I haven't gotten any recently.
Maki told me to show her the photo
next time it happens.
We want you to find
a good person to be with.
This is no time
for such carefree conversation.
We’re doing it
because it’s not the right time.
You're right.
Oh.
What is it?
Mom has been wanting
to invite everyone over
for some hand-rolled sushi and madeleines,
just like the old days.
Hand-rolled sushi?
Junichi especially loved those.
Yeah.
Bye.
Hello?
Keisuke? Are you in Tokyo right now?
No, I’m in Mitsuba.
Then how about we have a match?
A match?
How many years has it been?
Fifteen? Sixteen?
You've got good footwork.
I guess it’s muscle memory.
You've still got it. You’ll be fine.
Although I’ll be no match for you.
It's okay. I’ll go easy on you.
Yes, please.
We haven’t had a match since that day.
When we were in sixth grade.
Red, Tobina.
Ready.
- White, Kiyohara.
- Ready.
IROHADAI
KIYOHARA
- Take position.
- Maki,
- who are you cheering on?
- Bow.
You’ll just have to cheer
for both of them, huh?
I’m going to cheer on the match.
Cheer on the match?
Let's cheer them on so that it will be
a memorable match
for everyone.
Yeah.
Good idea, Maki.
Begin.
You can do it.
Winner.
Keisuke.
Keisuke!
- You were strong too.
- Good job.
Good job.
Keisuke, you're the one who opened
the time capsule, right?
What?
On Friday night,
the day before the incident,
your car was spotted
near the abandoned school.
- Someone also saw a man walking through--
- Wait, hold on!
- Did you take out the gun?
- No, it wasn’t me.
Then why were you there?
It’s true
that I went there to open
the time capsule.
But the gun was already gone.
What?
I opened the time capsule,
but there was no gun inside.
- Are you serious?
- I’m not lying.
Why did you dig up the time capsule?
I was thinking of taking it with me for
self-defense when I went to see Sakuma.
You might not believe it,
but the gun was already gone.
I even have an alibi during the time
Sakuma was killed.
I didn't use the gun,
or take it from the time capsule.
What if the person who took the gun
and the person who used it
were two different people?
What?
Makiko's alibi has not been proven.
Are you trying to say that I took the gun,
and then Makiko used it?
There's no way I'd let Makiko do that.
- I don’t think that you would either!
- Then what is it?
Either way, the gun was gone.
I haven't told anyone that I went
to dig it up. Not even Makiko.
So?
The time capsule was opened two times.
That means someone took the gun
out of that time capsule years ago,
and kept it hidden?
That’s the only possible answer.
If you’re telling the truth,
then it would have to be either
Makiko or Naoto.
What if
it’s Naoto?
If Naoto had dug up that gun
a few years ago…
Let’s say
that he knew he couldn't possibly
beat his brother in a physical fight.
So he wanted to have a powerful weapon
and opened the time capsule.
Even if he had taken the gun
and kept it hidden all this time,
do you really think he would use it
because he hated his brother?
Of all things, it was your pops' gun.
He's not that kind of guy.
He could never kill anyone.
Makiko wouldn’t either.
Yeah.
I don’t think she’d dig up
the time capsule either.
KOTONO
I have to take this.
Don’t you have any friends
to play catch with?
No.
I see.
Maybe I'll play with you.
Oh, come on.
You don't have to look so disgusted
by that idea.
Let’s eat. Go wash your hands.
Okay.
Take it easy and rest.
Bye.
That was a call from my wife.
I remarried.
When?
A year ago.
She’s pregnant.
Does Makiko know?
No.
She doesn’t know about the marriage
or the kid.
I was going to tell her after Masaki's
exams, but then the incident happened,
so she doesn't know yet.
Please don’t tell Makiko about it.
Of course. It's not my place to say.
Yeah, you're right.
Married twice with two kids, huh?
I guess I prefer to be married.
But you got divorced.
You make no sense.
I wasn’t the right fit
as Makiko’s husband, that’s all.
Hey,
what do you think Makiko will say
when I tell her I remarried?
Makiko isn’t the only one
who'd have an opinion.
- You mean Naoto?
- Yeah.
- He’ll probably get mad.
- For sure.
I haven't told my wife about the incident.
I'm hiding things
from both her and Makiko.
It's so exhausting.
You’ve always been
tiptoeing around other people.
I don’t want anyone to not like me.
I know that.
How annoying.
Don’t you have to go?
Where are you headed now?
I’m going back to the station.
Then let’s go.
Let’s go.
Here.
Thanks.
What a hassle.
- So immature.
- Let's go.
- Hope your wife is okay.
- Thanks.
Hey.
Yeah?
What did you think when you met Makiko
for the first time in 23 years?
What?
Never mind. Let's go.
MAKIKO IWAMOTO
Please give me a call.
JUNICHI
Junichi?
Yeah.
What’s up?
Listen,
I don't know if I should be saying this
given our current situation, but…
Then
maybe you shouldn’t.
I guess so, huh?
I figured as much.
But you’ll say it anyways, right?
Yeah.
What is it?
If you have time,
I'd like you to play catch
with Masaki again.
I totally understand if you say no.
Sure.
Sure, what?
Sure, I can play catch.
Really? It's not too much for you?
No.
Yay!
Masaki will be so happy.
Oh, if you have time, stay for dinner too.
Okay.
I’ll contact you again.
Okay, bye.
Bye.
It seemed like you were enjoying
that call.
You were still here, huh?
I’m reviewing the case from 23 years ago
to make sure nothing was overlooked.
By the way,
what is your alibi, Detective Tobina?
What?
I’m just asking as a formality.
Of the people involved
with the incident 23 years ago,
I've already asked Ms. Makiko Iwamoto,
Mr. Keisuke Kiyohara,
and Mr. Naoto Sakuma about their alibis.
Detective Tobina,
where were you and what were you doing
on the night of the incident?
Where were you and what were you doing
Playing mahjong at a mahjong parlor.
I lost horribly.
I see.
Excuse me.
I'm Tobina from the Mitsuba Police.
Sorry to bother you,
but can I ask you some questions?
MITSUBA POLICE
Oh man, it's so cold.
I'm back.
Ms. Nara.
Ms. Nara, I got the monaka from Kigetsu.
And here's your change.
Sorry, there's lots of coins.
Are there any developments regarding that?
I'm still investigating.
Just to confirm,
you haven't mentioned that
to Detective Tobina, have you?
No.
But are you sure about this?
He’s your buddy, right?
Detective Tanaka,
please continue working hard.
I'm Nagai.
You bloomed so beautifully.
Chief Kosugi!
Do you like monaka?
You conducted research on me, huh?
Guilty as charged.
I love it.
Can we enjoy these in your office?
Of course. Let's go.
KIGETSU
Chief Kosugi,
since when have you worked
here at Mitsuba Police Station?
I first worked here 25 years ago,
then moved around to various places,
and returned five years ago
as the police chief.
The weapon used to murder Sakuma
was the gun of Officer Kazuo Kiyohara,
who died in the line of duty 23 years ago.
Yes.
Keisuke Kiyohara,
the son of Officer Kiyohara,
was one of the people questioned
as a witness in the Sakuma murder case.
The other people I spoke to are
Keisuke Kiyohara's ex-wife,
Makiko Iwamoto,
the victim Hideyuki Sakuma's brother,
Naoto Sakuma,
and Detective Junichi Tobina,
who was assigned here two months ago.
They were the first to discover
the body of Officer Kazuo Kiyohara
when they were all in the sixth grade
of elementary school?
Were you aware of that?
Yes.
How did you find out, Ms. Nara?
I read all the investigation materials
from that time, cover to cover.
I see.
I would like to speak again
with people who were familiar
with the situation at that time.
When that incident happened, I was working
in the administration department,
but I was called into action because
a robber and murderer was on the loose.
The four of them,
who were still kids at the time,
were taken in since they were
the first to discover the bodies,
and I was there to see all that unfold.
When Detective Tobina was assigned here
two months ago,
you knew that he was one of the boys
from back then?
Yes.
The incident from 23 years ago
and Sakuma's murder
are connected by Officer Kiyohara's gun,
and the four classmates.
I don't know how being the first
to discover the police officer's body
affected the children's lives afterward,
but in Tobina's case,
there's no doubt that he is currently
a very excellent police officer.
Even if his classmate
is involved with Hideyuki Sakuma's murder,
Tobina would never allow personal matters
to affect his investigation.
I’m glad I got to hear your input.
- I’ll be going now.
- What?
You’re not going to eat the monaka?
I'm in the mood for something spicy
rather than something sweet.
I'll be going now.
Then I’ll enjoy these myself.
Please do. Excuse me.
I’ll meet up with you later too.
- What?
- Don't sound so disappointed.
- Have fun.
- Bye.
- You forgot your ball!
- What?
You can't forget the ball.
- Catch.
- You scared me!
- Here.
- Thanks.
- Bye.
- Be careful.
- Yeah.
Let's use this.
Thank you. Goodbye.
- Sore muscles?
- Yeah.
Actually, I did kendo yesterday
as part of a work-related activity.
- You can do kendo?
- I did it from elementary to high school.
- Oh really?
- I was pretty strong.
My dad taught it in elementary school,
and our team won
a competition in sixth grade.
In the individual competition,
my teammate won first place,
and I came in second.
My dad was the teacher,
so I felt that I had to be the best.
You know,
when I was in elementary school, I was
good at sports, academics, everything.
But he always defeated me, when it came to
things that I desperately wanted to win.
Did that person
defeat you in anything aside from kendo?
Yeah…
Sounds good.
Will you guys come too?
Yeah.
But I don’t remember.
Not sure what it was now.
I'll be off now.
Bye.
Masaki, hold it like this.
Grip the ball like this.
- Like this, got it?
- Okay.
Try it.
- Like this?
- Yeah.
- Try throwing it like that.
- Okay.
That was cool.
One more time.
- Okay.
- Good.
Like this.
- Like this?
- Good.
It's a lot faster now.
Thank you so much.
- Good job.
- That was good.
I'm back.
Thanks.
Masaki, break time.
Okay.
Masaki.
My mom's here.
Hello.
This is Mr. Junichi's girlfriend.
Nice to meet you. I'm Hiromi.
I'm Masaki's mother.
Hiromi happened to have a day off today.
Sorry to make you hang out with Masaki
on your day off.
Not at all.
Junichi is having the most fun.
That's true.
Time to switch. I want to play too.
You can do it?
- I'll do it. I'm sure I can.
- Can you really?
- Really?
- Yeah.
Ready.
Wow.
- I caught it.
- Nice.
I'll throw it now.
Junichi…
That's what she calls you, huh?
Yeah. So?
You guys are really far apart, huh?
- In age?
- Yeah.
Ten years.
She's so young.
But she's mature for her age.
- Yeah, she's really calm.
- Yeah.
- What does she do for work?
- She's a nurse.
Oh, it makes sense now…
What do you mean?
You approached her at the hospital?
No, she approached me.
- Are you serious?
- Yes, I'm serious.
- The cut is pretty deep.
- Yes.
I was chasing a pick-pocket
and I almost tripped,
so I grabbed on to the guardrail.
Then this happened.
Let's stitch it up.
- It needs stitching?
- Yes.
- Clean the wound please.
Please place your hand here.
It might sting a little.
Mr. Tobina.
Yes?
Um…
Can I ask you for advice about something?
Stay away from Hiromi.
- I've done nothing.
- You're following her every night.
No I am not. Leave me alone.
Not so fast.
- Hey.
- Let me go.
Hey, hold on.
Don't get carried away.
Hey.
- Don't get cocky with me.
- Sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- What'd you say?
I'm sorry. I'll stop.
That's how it began.
How long have you guys been going out?
About three years.
I see.
Yeah.
Two months ago,
I was assigned to Mitsuba Police Station,
and Hiromi tagged along.
Tagged along?
She came to my place
and made herself at home.
You two are living together?
Yeah.
Are you going to marry her?
Junichi.
Yeah?
Let's switch.
That was fast.
I played enough.
Okay.
- You had fun?
- I did my best. It was fun.
You weren't bad.
Really? Then praise me.
- What?
- Praise me.
Nice.
I'm so glad I got to meet you.
Oh, you are?
Since Junichi never talked about
his friends before.
I haven't really seen him play catch
before either.
He'll be a great dad.
Oh sorry, don't take that to mean
that I'm rushing you guys into marriage.
No worries.
We never discuss marriage.
Well, you're still only 25, right?
Yeah…
But I don't think that's the issue.
Sorry, it's complicated.
I just don't think
this relationship will lead to marriage,
that's all.
I see.
But
it feels great to spend time outside.
It's been a long time
since we went out together like this.
I see.
After this,
we're stopping by the supermarket
to make hand-rolled sushi at home.
Is that right?
Junichi suddenly said that he wanted
to eat hand-rolled sushi.
I see.
I'm getting fired up now.
- All right.
- Let's do this.
Wash your hands.
Hello?
Hey.
I know it's sudden,
but can I see Masaki today?
What?
I have some time today.
Yeah, sure.
Maybe the three of us can go eat out.
Come eat at our place.
I already prepared dinner.
And it's more relaxing at home.
Okay. Bye.
Hand-rolled sushi?
Why are you laughing?
It's just that Naoto and I
were just talking about hand-rolled sushi.
- Is that right?
- Yeah.
It was fun back then.
Junichi was always eating
Alaskan pink shrimp.
You have such a good memory.
- Hey Masaki.
- Dad, you’re late.
- Sorry.
- I'm so hungry.
What did you do today?
I was playing catch.
- With your friend?
- No, Mr. Junichi.
What?
Yeah. Junichi played catch with him.
Since your dad bought you
a baseball glove,
- but never comes to play with you, right?
- Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I played catch
with Mr. Junichi's girlfriend too.
- Girlfriend?
- Yeah.
Junichi brought his girlfriend.
I see.
She was really cute, wasn't she?
I guess so.
You guess so?
Apparently, they're living together.
I see.
Okay, let's eat.
Thank you for the food.
Thank you.
Do you like it that much?
Yeah.
I love the taste, color, everything.
I see.
What about you?
- Me?
- Yeah.
I like dried seaweed.
Dried seaweed?
That's your favorite?
I like it the best.
Dried seaweed, huh?
I see.
Why did you decide to take me along?
I wonder why.
Do I need a reason?
I had fun. Thanks for taking me.
Was Masaki sleeping?
What?
Yeah. He's fast asleep.
You haven't opened this yet?
Yeah.
I don't drink wine by myself
when I'm at home.
You drink beer?
Yeah.
Keisuke, do you drink wine by yourself?
No, I don't drink it either.
Whoa! Oh no!
It's Naoto.
Sorry to come by so late.
What's wrong?
- Hey Keisuke.
- Come inside.
Is that all right?
Of course. Come in.
I'm not here for any particular reason.
I was passing by and saw Keisuke's car.
You feel anxious being alone, right?
Not that gathering together
will change anything.
Should we call Junichi too?
Junichi has a girlfriend he's living with.
- They're living together?
- Yeah.
- Did you know about this?
- No. I just found out.
I just found out today as well.
This happened before, didn't it?
You felt that you were left out
and started sulking.
I remember that.
- You guys didn't leave me out on purpose?
- Of course not!
You know, Naoto,
you probably forgot what you heard,
and ended up thinking no one told you.
You're so mean, Maki.
I'll message Junichi just in case.
- You don't have to.
Here.
I'm going out for a bit.
Mahjong?
- Have fun.
- Okay.
NAOTO SAKUMA
I'm at Maki's house right now.
Keisuke is here too. Want to join us?
- I'll be off.
- Bye.
- Do you come this way often?
- Yes, I do.
Were you here two weeks ago
on a Saturday night
at around 10:00 p.m.?
- I always pass by here.
- Is that right?
Do you remember if the light was on
at this hair salon?
I don't remember that.
I don't think I was paying attention.
The light was on.
You're sure?
Since I'm a hair stylist,
when I see a salon with the lights on,
I tend to wonder if they're practicing.
- So it catches my eye.
- I see.
Did you happen to see who was inside?
I did see a figure inside.
It was a woman, right?
Well, the manager of this place
is a woman, right?
Yes, that's right.
This is Nara.
This is Tobina.
What is it, Detective Tobina?
You're off duty today, right?
Regarding Ms. Makiko Iwamoto's alibi,
I got two testimonies stating that
the lights were on in the hair salon
and that there was a person inside
around 10:00 p.m. on Saturday night.
That's wonderful.
Then good day.
Um…
Isn't it best to tell your buddy Tobina
about this…?
No way, no way.
- No.
- You did it five times.
No, I didn't.
Naoto, you should drink too.
But I drove here.
I drove here too.
He can stay the night, right?
Yeah. Just sleep over there.
I got a message from Junichi.
What did he say?
He said he's coming.
Really?
Is that him?
What?
Detectives.
Good evening.
What brings you here?
Naoto.
You're all here.
We meet again, just as I promised.
Sorry for coming this late.
Yes, this is absurd.
Ms. Iwamoto has a young child too.
Would you mind accompanying me
to the police station…
Mr. Naoto Sakuma.
What?
There is something I'd like to ask you.
What's going on?
It doesn't take an hour to get
to your house from Haneda, right?
Is it true that you were caught
in a traffic jam that day?
I didn't get home until
a little before 11:00 p.m.
Our investigation
had quickly revealed that there was
no traffic congestion on either
the highway or the local roads.
So
I'd been searching for sightings
of your car that evening.
Then lo and behold,
on Saturday, the day of the murder,
you and your car were captured
on the security camera at a gas station.
It was 10:05 p.m.,
as evidenced by the gas station's records.
It is about a ten minute drive
from the crime scene, Smile Sakuma.
In other words,
it means you could have been present
at the scene of the murder.
Naoto.
Nagai.
- What's going on?
- Mr. Tobina.
What are you doing, Ms. Nara?
His alibi has fallen apart.
Mr. Naoto Sakuma will
voluntarily accompany us to the station.
IS HIS FORMER CLASSMATE
REALLY THE CULPRIT?
I killed my older brother.
I think he always had feelings for Makiko.
Please come right now, Junichi.
If one of us is lying,
who will you believe?
I thought you would never come back.
I saw it.
Subtitle translation by: Lili Morita