(This drama is purely fictional and is not associated...)
(with actual people, locations, organizations, )
(religions, or incidents.)
But are those Ro Ha remains?
We found him!
Yes, I'm sure of it. It's Ro Ha.
But we'll wait for Forensics to confirm it.
It's not like you to be this certain of something.
Well, this morning,
I ran into three mountain deities...
who pointed me in the right direction.
Captain.
We found this at the foot of his remains.
- A boy's shoe. - Right.
Captain, I brought him over.
Ro Ha... Did you find him?
Yes.
Do you perhaps recognize this?
I bought that for him when he turned eight.
Kids that age grow up so fast,
so I got them in a bigger size.
He said that his toes felt like they were swimming.
Where did you find this?
This trail...
He used to come here often for hikes with his mother.
My guess is that he came up here looking for her.
Ro Ha.
Ro Ha...
Ro Ha!
It's Dad.
I love you, Ro Ha.
(Missing: The Other Side 2)
(Episode 8)
(Closed for the day)
Did you cry again?
Who do you mean?
This detective I know.
You didn't feel anything?
What do you mean?
Ro Ha disappeared right before our eyes.
It happened to Eun Hee and Seung Jae that way too.
They were here before you arrived.
This is what this place is like.
If your body's found on the outside,
you disappear without a trace.
I still can't believe I'm dead...
and people disappear too?
What's next?
What comes after that?
I don't know. That's all I know.
What did you do to Ro Ha?
That was you, wasn't it?
Someone on the outside found his remains.
That's why he disappeared.
No, him winning the race.
Oh, that?
A mosquito bit Sang Yoon on the leg.
Ji Woo said he fell and hurt his toe.
Ha Yoon and Young Rim...
couldn't run as fast because they'd hurt their legs.
What?
Ro Ha and the other kids all did their best.
They helped him out voluntarily.
Isn't it beautiful?
It was the greatest race I ever saw.
About now,
Ro Ha will be with his mom, right?
He believed if he came first,
he could run to his mom.
I hope so.
This is such a strange place.
You realized that now?
At first, I was so scared I wanted to run away.
But now...
I want to know about this place.
Thank you.
Like you said,
it was a great race.
I could take the bus.
Goliath's still at large. It's dangerous.
Your place isn't safe either.
I was going to move anyway.
The women gossip too much.
Bo Ra was getting stressed out.
Until I find a place,
Bo Ra and I will stay with a friend.
Wouldn't it be safer to stay with Wook for now?
He seemed to think so too.
He would.
I heard you'd paid the rent I owed the landlady.
I'd kept this in my bag to pay you back when we met.
Thank you.
You could've taken your time.
No. I'll put it in here.
Do you know how to use the smartwatch?
Yes.
I'll use it if I so much as see a strange shadow.
Go see Bo Ra. I'll wait by the school.
What are you eating?
- You saw? - Did you?
Bo Ra.
Mom.
You guys go ahead.
- See you. - Bye.
Hello.
- Did you have fun? - Yes.
Are you allowed to walk out now?
Can we go home, then?
No. We'll move someplace else.
Until we find a place,
I'll stay with Aunt Ji Young.
I think you should stay where you are now.
Okay. I'd like that too.
Are they nice to you?
Yes.
Dad acts like he doesn't care,
and Jjonga's a girl's best friend.
Mr. Jang's always on my side.
- Enjoy yourself. - Thank you.
What?
Show me your stamp.
Hang on.
- Here. - Okay.
I won two.
No, you stamped this on yourself.
What are you talking about?
I want one more.
Just give her one more.
- Two baskets! - Yes!
Thank you.
Where did you get all this?
From the spring that never runs dry...
and always replenishes itself.
That's a true miracle.
Because this village itself is a miracle.
If you think of it that way, everything makes sense.
- Here. - Give me one more.
No way.
Detective Ko, take one yourself.
Yes, take something for participating.
It's weirder if you don't get anything.
Show me your stamp.
- I don't have one. - You don't?
If you don't have one,
then you just have to get one.
Let's see your other hand.
This is for Ro Ha.
It's a plaque of appreciation.
Thanks to you, Ro Ha finished the race in first place.
I didn't do anything.
- Thank you. - See?
Isn't it nice to get something?
Yes.
See you.
- Who's next? - Me.
Hey, Lee Young Rim!
I told you not to drink it!
But it tastes good.
You're so silly.
You can't have banana milk.
It's bad.
Young Rim, Ha Yoon.
Why are you fighting after a fun day?
What's it about?
That.
Stupid Young Rim was drinking banana milk.
Can't he?
Is he allergic?
That's the reason we can't go home...
or see our moms and dads.
I'm sorry. I won't drink it again.
Ha Yoon.
Gosh, what's up with them?
Did he drink this?
Yes, I gave it to him earlier.
Young Rim was drinking it and Ha Yoon told him not to.
Something about this being the reason they're here.
I should've told you about that. I forgot.
You can't give them banana milk.
Why not?
Alice is sleepy. I'll put her down to sleep,
then I'll tell you.
She must've been exhausted. She went right to sleep.
Where were we so far?
Oh, right.
Some darn woman gave the kids...
cartons of banana milk when they were in the playground.
They drank that and then fell asleep.
When Ha Yoon woke up,
Young Rim was fast asleep next to her.
The woman was watching TV. She looked at Ha Yoon,
complained that she'd woken up, and gave her more banana milk.
She cried and said she didn't want any,
but when she woke up, she was here.
I remember it...
like it was yesterday.
Where are we?
I don't know.
Don't be scared.
Are you brother and sister?
We're not.
He's stupid. He can't even read yet.
So don't bother my friend.
Are you protecting him?
Because we're friends.
I want to go home.
We live in Yonggi-dong.
Where is this place?
Lady.
Take me to my mom.
Please?
How could she do that to the sweet kids?
They don't know who she is?
No. They'd never seen her before.
It was 15 years ago already.
If Young Rim and Ha Yoon were alive,
they'd be such beautiful, bright college students.
Have you told Pan Seok about this?
Yes.
Ha Yoon and Young Rim...
went through something like that?
How can we find the person who gave them the banana milk?
Whenever he has a moment, he asks me about the villagers.
"When did they come here?"
"What happened before they died?"
Then he writes down everything I tell him.
That's what he's best at.
That's how we found Ro Ha too.
My gosh.
Both you...
and Mr. Jang worked so hard to find him.
I know because Il Yong told me.
I felt so grateful and ashamed...
that I couldn't even show that I knew.
We keep on receiving from you without doing anything.
Gosh, don't say that.
You always cook for us.
Thank you for saying that.
Speaking of which...
Why do you always cook for us?
Well...
Someone who lived here for a long time...
said this to me a while back.
"People don't become useless when they die."
"If you're useless, you're as good as dead."
I see. So the reason you always cook for us...
What are you two talking about?
You didn't even hear me coming in.
There you are, Mr. Jang.
We were talking about Young Rim and Ha Yoon.
Oh, I see.
Gosh, I'm exhausted. I helped them tidy up.
Il Yong and Detective Ko are still working there.
- I see. - Can someone...
- get me a glass of water? - Sure.
No, I'll go.
I know where all the glasses are because it's my kitchen.
Goodness.
I think Captain Kang always cooks for everyone...
because she wishes to remain useful even if she's dead.
Did she say that?
That's not exactly what she said.
But I think so.
What are you saying?
What?
Hey, what about this?
Oh, it's Mr. Jang's.
Do you take care of everyone's laundry?
No, everyone washes their own underwear.
I only take care of the ones left in the washer.
I'm in charge of laundry.
Mr. Jang is in charge of cooking, and Wook cleans the house.
The three of us take turns taking the dogs out for a walk...
There are four of us now, including you.
Anyway, Mr. Jang is very excited that you now live with us.
Well, I'm a pretty good cook.
Hey!
I'll take these upstairs.
Okay, I'll take care of the ones for the rooms downstairs.
Thank you!
Ouch.
Gosh, what is this?
(To: Kim Wook)
What?
(PO Box 90-7101 Seongju Post Office, Seongju, Gyeonggi Province)
What? They're all from the same person?
We're home!
Gosh, I'm so hungry.
Oh, you too?
Whenever I eat anything at the Industrial Complex Three,
I get hungry so quickly.
It's so odd.
- I know. - I guess even the food vanishes.
What can we do? We should just eat again.
Oh, you're back.
Hey, Jjonga. We found Ro Ha.
Really? That's amazing.
We found him thanks to you.
You told Detective Baek the exact location.
I can't believe you spelled it out for him like that. How daring.
I can't do that.
Being daring is a good thing. Jjonga is doing great for herself.
You're back.
Hi, Bo Ra.
Gosh.
What are you two wearing?
Don't tell me you went out wearing that.
We participated in the field day.
Why? Does it look weird?
I think I look pretty good in this.
Don't we look cool?
Team White versus Team Blue.
We look cool.
Oh.
Where's the key?
My goodness, this...
I'm so forgetful.
Goodness.
The 10,896th day.
Today was the field day.
(Today was the field day.)
(The 1st)
Ten years ago, when Professor Jung came to the village...
and said we should build a school...
and plan a field day...
- Go. - Go, team!
I thought, "You're going to make dead people exercise?"
"Why would you even bother going into such trouble?"
It's wider on this side, so we should make it wider.
- Oh, okay. - Goodness.
You're so bad at this.
- Go, Team Blue! - Go!
- Go, Team White! - Let's go!
- Go! - You can do it!
- Yes! - Yes, Team Blue!
(The 5th Mujigae Field Day)
(The 6th Mujigae Field Day)
- Did you tie it? - Yes, what about you?
I'm done too.
Slow down. Let's go slow.
Hey, be careful. Very careful.
- Where are you going? - Oh, we went too far.
- Careful. - Oh! Right.
Hey!
It was already the tenth field day.
It has become our biggest annual event.
If the kids were alive,
they'd be in high school or in college now.
When I see them, I feel happy and sad at the same time.
My heart breaks for them even as I'm smiling.
Those beautiful flowers...
were cut before they could even bloom.
They say there is no paradise where there are no kids.
These children shouldn't be here...
even if it means this place will end up becoming utterly miserable.
They should have never ended up here in the first place.
And...
my dear Ro Ha.
That boy came here all alone eight years ago.
He finally left today, and everyone applauded him.
He always ate two bowls of rice at a time...
because he wanted to become stronger.
And he won the race in the end.
I'm so glad that Ro Ha could leave like that.
I'm truly grateful...
to everyone who helped find Ro Ha. I can't thank them enough.
Ro Ha. Next time,
I hope you can be born into a world where only good adults live.
Do you think it'll help Ro Ha go to a better place?
Do you want to do it?
(Lee Ro Ha, Born on October 3, 2006)
No.
Just light the match then.
(Lee Ro Ha, Born on October 3, 2006)
I know how lonely and scared you've been.
You poor thing.
Gosh.
Goodbye, Ro Ha.
We've burned all his bad memories,
so let's pray for him that he can forget everything...
and rest in peace.
I'm going in.
(From 7107 PO Box 90, Seongju Post Office, )
(Seongju-Si, Gyeonggi-do)
You made him sulk again, didn't you?
I didn't.
Yes, you did.
Come in.
Why aren't you sleeping yet?
What are you doing tomorrow? It's Saturday.
Tomorrow? Why do you ask?
Now that Mom's outside,
can't we go meet her tomorrow?
Let's eat something good all together.
If you're busy, never mind.
I'll ask Detective Shin for a ride.
You mention him habitually.
Fine.
Let's go eat something delicious.
I'm going with you.
Gosh, it's already late.
Turn in, okay?
Yes!
Sweet.
Dolls.
Choi Young Bae...
Alice went missing earlier in the afternoon.
We searched the whole lakeside and found a boat.
We found her in there.
Who were you with on the boat?
Fish.
Then even at that time,
how did she come out?
I was told it'd be impossible.
Dad, come on.
Bo Ra, here.
That's one icing on the cake.
It's so pretty.
- Let's go. - Hold up.
What...
Who is this?
- Who are you? - Bo Ra.
Are the two of you going on a date?
No, three including my mom.
- What? - I see...
A date?
I thought you were off to dine out.
Hold on. Why are you so dressed up?
Isn't that from me?
We're only going to eat.
It's the same thing.
Whatever the case is, have fun.
- Go on. - Let's go.
- See you. - Bye.
- Bye. - Bye.
Come early.
Go along.
Look at you.
Are you frustrated that Wook is eating with another woman?
You and your temper really.
That's one thing.
But Lee Dong Min...
sent a letter to Wook from prison.
Once a month for ten months.
What did he write?
Gibberish.
There was nothing special, but it's still unpleasant.
Why did he send those letters?
And why didn't Wook tell us?
In case we'd worry, of course.
Wook is a talkative one, but not when it comes to himself.
What if he's trying to pull something in prison?
Tell me about it. I'm worried about that too.
Don't worry. You're prettier.
Excuse me?
You're prettier.
Are you each other's first love?
Don't ask such a thing.
We are.
Aren't we?
Well, I...
Right, he was.
I've never seen you this shy before.
Oh, right.
You know what? People call you everyone's want-to-be dad.
Bo Ra.
Why is that?
Because you're a really handsome dad.
So everyone wants a dad like you.
So I made something loud and clear.
That my beauty comes from him.
What are you talking about?
You take after me. You're my daughter.
No way. Look.
Thick double eyelids, a sharp nose, and a small face.
What on earth, you two?
The moment she saw me, she went like this.
I wonder whom she got it from. She's something.
I said I take after you.
Mom, he denied it like crazy...
that he wasn't my dad at first.
He said he was the man in the photo...
but not my dad.
No.
- What? - No, you shouldn't talk...
when your mouth is stuffed.
Let's finish this and head out for dessert.
Sure.
- Where's Bo Ra? - She's in the toilet.
She's hyper. She ate more than usual.
Why did you do that earlier?
First love?
Well, I told the truth.
You dumped me.
Not that.
Bo Ra keeps calling you Dad.
And she thinks she takes after you.
I kind of think she takes after me.
There you go again changing the subject with a joke.
You haven't changed one bit.
I clearly told her that I'm not her dad.
But she didn't believe me.
Maybe there's a reason why she believes I'm her dad.
She's just mistaken.
I'll talk her into it.
The other day, I was so confused...
with the police around that I couldn't tell her.
Do it later.
Bo Ra's going through a hard time now.
I'll find a house and take her as soon as possible.
Thank you for being nice to her.
I know you're doing this for her sake,
but if this takes long,
she may be heartbroken more.
And the same goes for me.
Bo Ra, are you okay?
You ate too much.
I don't have an upset stomach.
- Let's hurry for dessert. - Just a moment.
Captain.
- Captain. - What?
Captain, did you want to see me?
Yes, Hye Ju.
Can you watch the supermarket with Alice for a while?
I'll be right back.
Sure.
Detective Ko, are you home?
Detective Ko.
Hey.
You were home. Let's talk inside.
What is this about?
My house was robbed on the day we had our field day.
It was robbed?
Was something taken?
A doll I had.
Why did someone steal your doll?
Was the robber a child?
No, it wasn't.
I know who the robber is,
and I was hoping you'd catch the person.
Can I trust you with this since you're a detective?
I even saw that you had a gun.
Who is the culprit?
But first,
I'd like to keep this matter between us.
It will only trouble people if they find out,
and the children will be scared.
I'll tread lightly, so just tell me who the robber is.
Choi Young Bae.
He's a nasty man who targets children.
Gosh.
He's a lot taller than you...
and has a gaunt face.
His eyes are murky like those of a dead fish.
He never looks at people straight in the eyes.
If you see anyone...
who wasn't present at the field day, capture him.
A sex offender who targets minors would most likely be hiding out...
near the school or a place where kids often go.
That's why he should be apprehended immediately.
Got it.
Il Yong?
Where is he going?
(Safety First)
Are you sure you agreed to meet her here?
The theatre is that way.
We'll head over there together once she's done at the academy.
I see. Got it.
Enjoy the movie...
but don't stay out too late.
What has you smiling?
I'm happy, that's all.
I just had a meal with my mom and dad.
It was our first meal as a family.
Enjoy the movie, then. I'll see you at home.
Got it. I'll get going.
Have fun.
Excuse me.
I knew Pil Joong wouldn't show up in this neighbourhood.
What are you doing here?
Gosh, you startled me.
Mr. Jung, I could ask you the same thing.
I was out plucking weeds. What about you?
Me? I was out patrolling...
to confirm that it was safe around the school.
By the way,
have you seen anyone suspicious around here?
Someone suspicious?
Out of everyone here,
you're the one who's acting most suspiciously.
Me?
Did Captain Kang put you up to this?
Or maybe it's because the kids have grown on you...
like Ro Ha did.
It's not exactly that, but...
Keep patrolling, then.
If you see the kids,
make sure they get home safely.
I'll leave it to you and be on my way.
Sorry?
I also patrol the grounds at this time of the day.
There's no way of knowing what can happen to kids.
This right here is what I carry around for self-defence.
- Keep up the good work. - Have a good day.
You want to ask Ha Yoon directly?
That's right.
It seems as though she remembers it quite clearly.
She doesn't know who gave her the banana milk,
but we might get something to go on...
if we ask what she saw.
That idea also crossed my mind,
but I didn't say anything since it could alarm her.
We should get her in a comfortable setting...
and then ask in passing.
You and Ha Yoon are quite close.
Sure. Is there anything else you want to say?
Like what?
About your date with Bo Ra's mom...
or about someone else that's been annoying you.
It wasn't a date. All we had was a meal together.
Dressed up like that?
What do you mean? This is how I always dress.
Sure, of course. Unbelievable.
Goodness. If you nap for this long,
you'll have trouble sleeping at night.
What the...
It's me, Wook.
Why were you in there?
- Gosh. - Goodness.
I got thirsty and wanted some water.
- Gosh. - No one seemed to be around.
I thought I was being robbed.
Why were you this startled?
I thought you were robbing me.
Did you come alone?
Where's Mr. Jang?
We were on our way here, but he went to see Mr. Jung.
To get Ha Yoon and Young Rim's school records.
I see. Were you out on a date?
Seriously? All we had was a meal.
Why is everyone calling it a date?
I guess it was a date.
I'll get you some water.
Make it barley tea.
Here are ten years' worth...
of Ha Yoon and Young Rim's school records.
Eun Hee kept them neat and tidy.
Thank you.
I must've made you stay late at work.
It's not like I have a wife at home who nags me for being late.
- Shall we get going? - Sure thing.
Mr. Jung, don't you miss your family?
You never mention them.
I've heard more about my Hyun Ji than about you.
Because Hyun Ji was a bright little star.
You remind me of her,
and I miss her.
My daughter's lucky to have been loved.
Doesn't it surprise you...
that the dead make memories together...
and miss one another?
I guess it does.
Don't you want to leave? You've been here a long time.
Want to hear something funny?
The mortality rate here is at zero percent.
It's not like we can die twice.
Right.
Anyway, this is me.
Shouldn't you have taken off a few steps back?
- What? - I'll see you around.
Take care.
Look. These shoe prints are bigger than mine.
They must belong to a man.
Who's there?
I know you're there. Show yourself.
My goodness.
What are you doing here?
Oh, I was...
doing stuff.
So...
There's nothing over there.
Why are you coming from that way?
I came out for a walk and...
to do some thinking.
Hang on.
Are those handcuffs?
Did something happen back here?
What's taking him so long?
Is he filling in the forms himself?
Ms. An.
Ha Yoon, she's missing.
Ha Yoon?
Yes. She'd gone to see Young Rim,
but when I went to get her,
- they said she never came. - When did she leave?
Wait, is Ha Yoon's stuff still here?
Yes, they are.
She left before dusk so it was about 5pm.
What did you say? Who's missing?
Ha Yoon.
We must find her fast.
It's Choi Young Bae!
- Who? - Choi Young Bae.
Ha Yoon.
You're scared, aren't you?
I went to get water because you said you were thirsty,
but I couldn't get any.
I brought you a doll.
I'm pretty sure he came this way.
Where'd he go?
Il Yong and I'll go to the lake.
Detective Ko, call the villagers...
- and search every corner. - Okay.
I'll find Mr. Jung and tell him.
- Okay, let's all go. - No, wait.
- You stay with Alice. - No, I'll come too.
Hye Ju, take Alice and stay with Mr. Jung.
- There's no time to waste. - Let's go.
Ha Yoon.
You scoundrel!
Darn you.
Last time, when Alice went missing,
I got so worried about her, I forgot all about Ha Yoon.
I should've kept her close.
It's not your fault.
Did you hear that?
What are you doing?
You...
What do you think you're doing?
Oh, dear.
Die!
Are you okay?
Who are you?
Ha Yoon. My poor baby.
Look at you.
It's okay now. Were you hurt?
You must've been so scared.
Darn it.
Hurry up.
What made you think of coming here?
I followed the footprint we saw last time.
The footprint?
Still, you shouldn't have come here on your own. It's dangerous.
You really...
Were you hurt?
I'm fine. I'm more worried about the kid.
You should be beaten to death.
You scumbag.
Oh, dear.
You should take her home.
Okay. Can you get up?
Come on.
What should we do with him?
Make him disappear from this place.
I'll take care of him. Leave it to me.
Okay, you sort him out. Do you have your gun?
Tie him to a rock and throw it in the lake.
Or bury him.
So he never shows himself again.
We should've done that 15 years ago.
You won't actually do that, will you?
Why can't we?
Death is a luxury to the likes of you!
That's very right.
Did you hear that?
Let go.
Darn it.
Bring him over here.
Hold tight.
- Let go of me. - Keep still.
- Tie him up. - Let me go.
Untie me!
- Untie me! - Shut your mouth!
The Miranda rule means nothing here.
Punks like you don't deserve rights.
Why don't I?
I'm here too because I was wrongfully killed!
What?
The people here are different from trash like you.
How so?
You really don't know?
I don't want to spend time chatting with the likes of you,
so just answer my questions.
Who killed you?
What?
He came here 15 years ago?
Yes.
Where was he all this while?
I never saw him once.
He bothered Ha Yoon so much,
Comrade Jung and I left him on an island.
Do not ever think of returning to the mainland.
You brought this upon yourself,
so do not blame anyone else.
If you are lucky,
one day you will get to disappear.
You can't just leave a person here!
How dare an animal claim to be a person?
No human does what you do!
He is not worth talking to. Leave him.
He won't swim back, will he?
He cannot swim.
And look at the distance.
You're right.
It's quite deep too.
He cannot cross this while he is alive. Do not worry.
Can he if he dies, then?
Can people here die when they want?
It will not happen,
but if he finds his way back to the village,
I will find another way to exile him.
Trust me.
Okay.
Comrade Jung.
You need to paddle the other way.
We're supposed to go that way.
That's why you left the boat on land.
So what if we did?
He's back again and terrorizing the girls.
I'm so sick of this place.
However hard I try, it's all for nothing.
There's no running away or dying.
Scum like him and the kids are all grouped together.
Aren't we all...
just rats in his trap?
Captain Kang.
It must've been so tough, worrying about this on your own.
It wasn't me.
It was Ha Yoon that got hurt.
Oh, boy. I should go out and find Choi Young Bae first.
That way, the kids can put their worries to rest.
But he died 15 years ago.
Do you think you can find him?
Come on. We even found Eun Hee, who died 20 years ago.
- Right. - Well...
Wook managed to find out some things.
Well, that man...
His wife killed him.
He kept trying to escape the deserted island.
A few days ago, he fell into a deep lake.
When he regained consciousness, he came out through there.
Does that mean he went all the way to the end and came here?
It doesn't matter how he came back. Let's finish him off for good.
Find his address, and I'll tail him.
I'll see if I can gather some useful info.
Okay, sounds good.
What can I do?
You're busy.
You have to watch the store, look after Alice,
and make sure the kids get their snacks on time.
We'll take care of this. Don't worry about it.
Yes. Detective Ko will make sure he can't go anywhere.
And Mr. Jung will keep the kids safe.
Il Yong and I are here too.
Our situations may be different, but we're comrades too, you see.
Working toward the same goal makes us comrades.
He's right. I'll fill in for you this time.
So please get some rest.
Rest? I haven't even done much.
You nearly threw the plant earlier.
Wasn't it because of Choi Young Bae?
I knew it.
You sure didn't hide your anger...
when you did that.
I'm sorry.
My goodness. Thank you all so much.
What are you thanking us for?
Let's go, Wook. We should hurry.
- Okay. - See you.
Bye.
Name, Choi Young Bae. Born in 1963.
Fifteen years ago, he was forty-five.
He was never reported missing.
No criminal record either.
He has a wife, Cho Yu Sun,
and a daughter, Choi Eun Soo, who is 20 years old.
They've been living in the same apartment for 18 years.
(Mucheon)
The apartment is in Choi Young Bae's name.
They moved into the apartment before Choi Young Bae died,
and they're still living there.
Yes, I think that's what happened.
What did he do that his wife killed him?
Judging from the things he's done in the village,
he's clearly a pervert.
That's probably why she killed him.
What does his wife do?
She's just an ordinary civilian who's never paid a single fine.
She had private healthcare until three months ago through her job.
But it looks like she quit her job.
(Hogwanwon Premium Gold)
What's that? What are you drinking?
It's good for your joints. This is my occupational disease.
Oh, my knees are getting bad these days.
Stop!
I'll make a special exception and give you one because it's you.
Stay healthy and live long.
Yes, ma'am.
Where are you going?
I want to go check out Choi Young Bae's apartment.
If he goes in there, he can't get out.
Choi Young Bae is notorious.
What's up, Detective Ko?
Was Il Yong here, by any chance?
No.
Detective Ko, about Choi Young Bae...
How rude! He flat out ignored me.
Why is he looking for Il Yong in such a rush?
I wonder too.
Goodness.
Ms. Cho Yu Sun?
Who are you?
I'd like to ask you some questions about Mr. Choi Young Bae.
Oh, he passed 15 years ago.
I'm aware.
I know what kind of person he was,
and I'm aware that he passed away.
Goodness. Who keeps putting these barricades here?
(Safety First)
(Collapse Hazard, Keep Out)
Do you think she'll tell us where Choi Young Bae's body is?
She said she'd think about it, so let's wait.
Thank you.
For what?
I could only stand by and watch. Thank you for doing things...
that I couldn't do.
You're helping me too.
You're doing things that the villagers can never do.
So let's call it even.
Here, hand it over. I'll go fill it up.
No, it's okay. Wait...
My goodness.
Captain Kang, we've got a problem.
What now?
Detective Ko came to me and said...
he saw Il Yong leaving the village.
- So? - What do you mean, "So?"
Oh, Mr. Jang. You're here too.
Yes, hello. I went to the kitchen to fill this up.
Well, it's fine.
Mr. Jang knows everything.
He knows everything?
Yes, I heard everything.
So where is Detective Ko now?
He went to get Il Yong.
You should've just played dumb. Why did you let that happen?
There you are.
Detective Ko.
He came to the school and asked me about it.
Of course, I just played dumb.
But he didn't believe me.
He said he'd go there and catch him red-handed.
That's why I ran here.
If the villagers find out that Il Yong frequents the outside world,
things will get very complicated.
Wouldn't it be better to tell Detective Ko since this happened?
No, those two shouldn't meet.
- Let's hurry. - Okay.
You two.
Where were you? No.
How did you get out?
Well, Sang Chul.
- Let me explain. - You.
If you're going to lie to me again, just keep your mouth shut.
You may have managed to deceive the people in the village,
but not me.
Detective Ko, calm down.
Let's hear him out first.
Don't come close.
Drop the gun, Detective Ko. Put the gun down.
You'd better answer my question honestly.
You two.
You aren't dead, right?
Il Yong is dead.
Like you.
And...
- I'm... - Wook, wait.
I'm not dead.
(Missing: The Other Side 2)
Who made such a rule?
It's so unfair.
Captain Kang knew everything.
Please tell me.
Have you been hearing from your family all alone...
behind everyone else's back?
I guess no secrets can exist whatsoever in any kind of world.
Lee Dong Min was after Detective Shin from the start.
Who is it that he's even tracking the location?
I feel like being tested.
What are those punks scheming?
My question is, "Who is that person?"
There's someone else behind.