[Kill Lover]
[Episode 15]
There's one more thing
I have to accomplish.
Ninghai Square
carries so much of my mother's dedication.
But while she was alive,
she couldn't make it come true.
I have to fulfill her wish
and finish the construction of Ninghai Square.
[Recipient: Housing Construction Bureau] [Subject: The Design Drawing of the Ninghai Square Project Structure of Ninghai City]
♪ Love is always a blessing ♪
♪ Luck sometimes shines ♪
♪ Romance still surrounds us ♪
♪ A beautiful, happy sign ♪
♪ Sadness ♪
♪ Fades in a moment ♪
The reconstruction of Ninghai Square
will not only improve urban functions
♪ Someone like you ♪
but also inject new vitality into the city.
Please look at the big screen.
♪ When I realized I'd become ♪
♪ Someone like you ♪
♪ You're my one and only ♪
♪ Even if life resets again ♪
♪ I'm at peace as long as you’re here ♪
♪ Someone like you ♪
♪ Holding your hand, I become ♪
♪ Trading forever, by your side ♪
♪ Leaving tears in the past ♪
♪ Letting happiness stretch on forever ♪
Mom.
I'll definitely make Ninghai Square
become the pride of Ninghai.
The restart of the project
is going more smoothly than I expected.
Now
there's only one thing left to do.
Don't rush.
During this period of time,
Bu Fan and Po haven't been idle, either.
They've been investigating this purple rose tattoo
both online and offline
to find out which tattoo artist created it.
I think we'll have an answer soon.
[Po]
-Hello.
-You You.
I've found the tattoo artist.
I'll take him to see you right away.
Okay.
This rose was my proudest
work back then.
I remember that
the one who got the tattoo was also a woman.
Her name
seemed to be Rose.
Was Rose her real name or stage name?
Ma'am.
I'm not a cop.
Why would I ask so many questions?
I just did the work when the client paid me.
Well,
do you still remember what she looked like?
No, I don't.
Think harder, please.
My everyday time is very expensive.
I charge by the hour.
Actually, I'm the kind of person
who never forgets
the clients he has seen.
Back then,
this woman seemed to have told me that
she had a boyfriend
named You Zhen.
He was
the president of Xingyao Group.
He seemed to get into trouble later.
The news said he was corrupt and harmed people.
If you can find him,
I think he knows the most about it.
If you need tattoos in the future,
come to me.
Something he said
has reminded me that
to find out what happened back then,
I should ask those who were involved in it at that time.
Ms. Ruan.
It's such great news that Qi Dong has been released.
We haven't had time to get together.
Today,
we finally have time to celebrate.
Come on.
I don't know what you like to eat,
so I just cooked based on You You's taste.
I hope you don't mind.
Please eat more. Don't be shy.
Thank you.
Here you are. Be careful. It's hot.
Godmother.
Recently,
I've been so busy with the Ninghai Square project that
I haven't had time to visit you.
How about this?
I'll drink a glass of wine as punishment first.
Alright, alright.
But as far as I know,
although An Guoxuan's previous funds have been recovered,
Xingyao Group is heavily in debt
and on the verge of bankruptcy.
The collapse after the second financing meeting
has even caused many investors to withdraw their funds
and stop trusting Xingyao Group's construction capabilities.
The funding gap for this project
is really quite big.
This is
the design proposal I've made according to
Ninghai Square's current situation.
It also incorporates the current investors'
favorite commercial elements.
[Proposal for Ninghai Square]
It might attract some funding
to ease your urgent needs.
I hope that it can help you guys.
Thanks for your concern, Godmother.
However, it's not necessary anymore.
It's my fault as I didn't tell you in time.
The project's funding gap has already been filled.
It must have been tough to bring it back to life.
Actually,
Qi Dong contributed the most.
He went to the Housing Construction Bureau again and again
and convinced the officials
to trust Xingyao's construction capabilities again.
With the help of the Housing Construction Bureau,
Xingyao also talked to and persuaded many investors into
increasing funds and expanding shares.
That was how we filled the project's
funding gap thoroughly.
Actually, Ninghai Square
was already a key government project.
I just
made use of this opportunity.
The most important thing is that
the design proposal You You presented
was improved and optimized according to
Ms. Qi's design drawings
and received unanimous praise.
That was the key to restarting the project.
Qi Lan's design concepts
were indeed very advanced.
Even by today's standards,
they're still very creative.
You two should stop complimenting each other.
You both deserve credit.
You You.
In the future, if you encounter any issues,
tell me immediately.
Did you hear me?
Thank you, Godmother.
Qi Dong,
you're practically my son-in-law now.
Previously,
I tried to obstruct you and You You indeed.
But later,
I also noticed that
you treated You You so well.
So, just let bygones
be bygones.
From now on,
let's stick together as a family
and protect You You jointly.
Sure.
Godmother.
You and Qi Dong are
the two most important
people in my life.
Thank you.
Silly child,
we're a family, so there's no need for such formalities.
Just eat. It's getting cold.
Come on.
What you just heard
must stay in your belly.
Not a single word can be revealed.
Deal.
This soup is so delicious.
By the way, Godmother,
there's one more thing I want to tell you.
You You.
It turns out that
Ms. Ruan and your parents
were college classmates.
Why haven't you ever mentioned that?
You've just found out?
I thought that
Ms. Ruan and your mom were best friends,
and your dad was the third wheel between them.
Don't talk nonsense.
I'm sorry.
Actually, Qi Dong's
guess is right.
Her mother and I
were indeed best friends in high school.
We both ended up going to the same university
and choosing the same major.
We even lived in the same dorm room.
Our relationship
was certainly closer than with others.
During that time,
we also met
your father, You Zhen.
In college,
the three of us
were practically inseparable.
After graduation,
Qi Lan and You Zhen got married.
I was worried that with their own little family,
there wouldn't be a place for me anymore.
I was overthinking it.
Even after they got married,
I was still their closest friend.
Before You You was born,
I had already reserved the position of Godmother.
The first person who held you after you were born
wasn't your father,
but me.
Godmother.
Luckily, I still have you.
Silly child, what are you talking about?
Oh, right,
what did you ask me just now?
I wanted to ask you for the recipe for this chicken soup.
I want to make it for Qi Dong
after I learn it.
That's easy.
Next time, come to me earlier.
I'll teach you.
Okay.
Just now,
why didn't you let me ask Godmother
about Rose?
Because I suspect that...
she's Rose.
That's impossible.
Why?
Although back then,
at An Guoxuan's place,
I only saw him and Gao Qing,
I also discovered
a lady's brooch.
It was identical to the one
she wore in the photo.
The design of this brooch is quite common.
It's not a custom-made item.
Perhaps it's just a coincidence.
Besides,
you deliberately dropped your chopsticks just now.
Your purpose was to check the tattoo on Godmother's ankle, right?
But she doesn't have a tattoo, does she?
But we've also analyzed that
with your father's cautious personality,
unless it was betrayal by a trusted confidant,
An Guoxuan wouldn't have been able
to shift all the blame
onto him alone.
Moreover, Rose has reappeared recently.
She was able to control Gao Shanshan
right under An Guoxuan's nose
and incited him to burn the documents.
Moreover, she even managed to arrive at
the Swiss Bank one step ahead.
All these things
happened around you.
Don't you think there were too many coincidences?
However,
we don't have concrete evidence right now.
I'll investigate all these things thoroughly.
I also hope that it had nothing to do with Ms. Ruan.
Don't worry.
I will definitely give you an explanation.
I told you to
stop pestering me.
I just want to pester you.
I'm here because I have something to tell you.
I'm pregnant.
Aren't you happy?
So what are you going to do?
Of course I'm going to give birth to the baby.
Don't you love having a daughter?
I'm going to name her
You You as well.
In this way,
we will have
our own daughter.
Ruan Bi.
I'll tell you one last time.
It's over between us.
I have a family.
There's no future for us.
Moreover,
I only have one daughter,
and that's You You.
Dad, what are you doing?
I'm leaving. Let me tell you.
Don't come to me again.
You Zhen.
You Zhen!
You You.
I went to buy you some ice cream just now.
It was a pity that
the lady told me the ice cream was sold out.
I'm sorry,
but the child couldn't be saved.
[My Beloved Daughter, You You]
My dear daughter, be good.
I've almost completed all the plans.
Those who hurt you and me back then
have all paid the price by now.
You Zhen has gone mad.
Qi Lan is dead.
The rest of An Guoxuan's life is completely ruined, too.
Now it's You You's turn.
She took everything from you.
She took your life,
your name
and your father's love.
I'll make her lose everything
and die in despair.
Bu Fan,
find a way to get You You's accusation letter.
Compare it with the handwriting
on this letter.
Dong,
wasn't that accusation letter
given to You You by Ruan Bi?
Are you suspecting something?
Don't worry, Dong.
I'll find the most professional team at once
for an urgent authentication.
Within 48 hours,
I'll tell you the result.
[Qi Dong]
Dong,
we got the result of the handwriting comparison between
the accusation letter and the love letter.
They were not written by the same person.
If she was cautious enough,
during these over 10 years,
there was enough time to cover up all traces.
Maybe we're mistaken?
You're not mistaken.
Ruan Bi is Rose.
Bu Fan,
please step out for a moment.
So, you've found the evidence?
That day,
I returned to my apartment
and thought of what you had said.
Then I couldn't fall asleep.
On the next morning,
I went to my mother's grave.
I wanted to talk to her.
Hello.
Could you please tell me what's going on here?
There was a typhoon and a heavy rain last night.
The cemetery has collapsed.
We're repairing it now.
[My Beloved Daughter, You You]
[Ultrasonic Diagnostic Report of Ninghai City People's Hospital]
[Name: Ruan Bi]
The date on that ultrasound report
matches exactly with the pregnancy date
mentioned in the letter.
I've always thought that
the tombstone
was established for me by Ruan Bi.
But I never thought that
it was to commemorate her unborn child.
What's more,
the child was also named You You.
And she buried
that brooch, too.
I guess she hates my parents very much.
I gave the administrator some money
and asked him to handle it well.
So for the past couple of days,
you've been dealing with
all these emotions by yourself?
Ruan Bi clearly harmed my parents,
but she's been so nice to me.
All these years,
I've truly considered her as my only support.
But only till now do I understand that
she's been using me all this time.
And five years ago,
when you asked me to fake my death to escape,
from that moment onwards,
she already started using both of us
to reap the benefits.
Qi Dong.
It was you who woke me up
and made me see the reality clearly.
So,
whether Ruan Bi is truly sincere or not,
it doesn't matter anymore.
She harmed my mother
and conspired with An Guoxuan to frame my father.
She even killed Gao Shanshan.
These are all facts.
She has done so many terrible things.
I will definitely make her pay the price.
However,
she has hidden her tracks too well.
We have no way of finding the evidence
of her previous crimes.
So,
I have to force her to take action initiatively
and expose her weaknesses.
It looks like
you already have a plan in mind.
Why did you ask me to meet you here?
What's wrong?
Godmother,
did my parents ever mention
a name to you back then?
Rose.
I've heard of it.
I visited your father a few years ago.
He kept saying Rose.
What's wrong?
Rose was the woman whom my father had an affair with.
How can you be so sure?
Among the rose seeds my dad had hidden for 15 years,
there were letters between him and that woman.
That's impossible.
There must be a misunderstanding.
I surely understand the relationship between
You Zhen and Qi Lan, don't I?
They loved each other deeply.
This kind of thing would never happen.
If I hadn't seen those letters with my own eyes,
I wouldn't have wanted to believe it, either.
Godmother,
did my mother really never tell you anything about this?
Actually, your mother
seemed weak,
but she hated showing weakness the most.
If this matter was true,
she would definitely keep it to herself.
The older generation has its own affairs.
Don't overthink it.
Now that your mother has passed away
and your father is in this condition,
you have no way of verifying it.
Just let it go.
I can't let it go.
Even till now,
Rose hasn't even stopped.
She not only manipulated Gao Shanshan
but also wanted to take away
the money that could save Qi Dong.
Actually, I've seen her twice.
I first saw her at the Swiss Bank,
and then I saw her
right here.
However, back then,
I didn't understand what it meant.
Later,
among the letters between her and my father, I found that
she told my father she was
pregnant on that day.
But that woman
lost ultimately.
My father chose his family
and me.
So what if she was pregnant?
She still couldn't capture my father's heart.
That girl who should have been my sister
never came into this world.
I think I should have been sad.
But for some reason,
I feel incredibly lucky for her.
Because her mother
was a mistress who ruined someone else's family
and even did so many terrible things.
So even if she had been born,
being raised by such a mother,
she wouldn't have been happy, either.
Godmother,
you once said that
no matter what difficulties I encounter, I can come to you.
So...
You have to help me find her.
Don't worry.
I will do my best.
Thank you.
Godmother.
But right now,
the restart of Ninghai Square is imminent.
That's the fruit of my parents' joint efforts.
So,
I have to let this mistress know that
whether in the past
or now,
she will never
get what she wants.
[Opening Ceremony of the Ninghai Square Project]
We are about to witness
the official start of Ninghai Square's construction.
Firstly,
let's welcome the chief designer of the Ninghai Square project,
Ms. Qi Gege,
[Opening Ceremony of the Ninghai Square Project]
to come on stage and give a speech.
Hello, everyone.
Fifteen years ago,
there was a woman here
who promised her daughter that
[Opening Ceremony of the Ninghai Square Project]
she would turn this place into
a luminous
super music box that could sing
so that this place
would become a childhood memory for all the kids in Ninghai.
This woman
is the former chief designer
of the Ninghai Square project,
Qi Lan.
And I
am her daughter, You You.
Now,
the design proposal for Ninghai Square
has been finished
based on my mother's initial draft.
Of course,
I will also do my best
to fulfill her promise from back then.
[Opening Ceremony of the Ninghai Square Project]
[Architecture Constructional Drawing]
No matter what method you use,
you have to ruin You You's reputation...
and destroy the Ninghai Square project.
Okay.
Run!
[News Information: The Collapse Accident of Ninghai Square]
Recently,
the construction of the highly anticipated Ninghai Square
project has been restarted.
However, soon after the project began,
a collapse accident occurred,
which injured many workers.
As far as we know,
the true identity of
the current chief designer, Qi Gege,
is actually the daughter of the late former chief designer, Qi Lan.
And this design was also
adjusted and modified properly by Qi Gege
according to Qi Lan's design.
Compensation! Compensation! Compensation!
[Ninghai Square]
Please calm down, everyone!
Compensation! Compensation!
Everyone, please stay calm.
Compensation!
Fifteen years ago,
Ninghai Square collapsed accidentally.
Today, the tragedy has reoccurred.
Do you think the blueprint should be
mainly liable for the accident?
Hello, everyone.
I'm You You, the current
chief designer of Ninghai Square.
Regarding this accident,
please allow me to clarify something.
The blueprint of Ninghai Square
has already undergone a detailed safety assessment by
a professional building appraisal agency
to ensure safety, compliance and stability
of the architectural structure.
It fully complies with
the safety requirements for construction.
You guys have jointly used all these
tricks to deceive us.
Compensation!
Compensation! Compensation! Compensation!
Alright, alright.
Calm down.
Everyone, please calm down.
Come on, everyone. Listen to me.
Currently, the accident
is still under investigation.
Please give us three days.
I promise to figure out the truth for you all.
What truth?
My son is injured because of you guys!
How are you going to compensate him for his injuries?
Compensation!
Compensation! Compensation!
We want compensation!
Compensation!
If you have any issues, come at me.
We can't work anymore!
We need an explanation now!
Godmother.
Ms. Ruan.
I heard that you and the late chief designer,
Qi Lan, were close friends.
Do you think there are flaws
in Qi Lan's design?
Qi Lan was indeed my close friend and confidante.
I'm very sad
about her death.
But I dare to guarantee on my honor that
she was absolutely not an irresponsible designer
as you described.
You You, as her daughter,
is even more outstanding than her mother.
I have full confidence in her capabilities.
As for the true cause of the accident,
if it's our responsibility,
we will absolutely not shirk it.
On behalf of You You, I promise you all that
each victim here will
receive our highest standards of
compensation and treatment.
So please rest assured, everyone.
But as far as we know,
after this accident occurred,
many investors withdrew their funds.
The Ninghai project is actually facing bankruptcy, too.
Where will you get the money to fulfill
this so-called promise?
If you don't have money, how can you compensate us?
That's right.
Compensation!
I'll say this again.
The Ninghai Square project will not be suspended.
The funding gap
will be filled by the Bihai Group.
I will also take the lead in financing
and continue to implement the project.
As for the design issues you all
are worried and concerned about,
please rest assured.
I will make a new proposal for you.
Please trust me, everyone.
I won't let you suffer from the same problem again.
Godmother,
it must be that woman who tampered with the project.
It must be her.
Except her,
I can't think of anyone else.
Calm down.
Now we need to first figure out
what she has tampered with in our project.
Only by doing that can we catch her.
Let me handle this matter.
No.
You You is at her most vulnerable time now
and needs you the most.
Staying with her is the most important thing for you.
Don't worry.
I'll definitely figure out the truth.
Wait for my news.
The most urgent matter now
is to minimize the negative impact
on this project.
This is the fruit of your mother's efforts.
It can't be ruined again.
But now with all parties withdrawing their investments,
the funding gap exceeds 50%‌ of the total budget.
It's hard to fill the gap again.
What I said just now
was not to appease the reporters.
I will invest in this project.
What's more,
I will mobilize all the resources around me
to find new financing for this project.
I absolutely won't let this project
repeat the mistakes of the past.
Godmother.
I'm sorry.
I've made you involved in this again.
Why have I always made you worry about me?
What are you talking about?
You are my daughter.
Your business is my business.
Are you feeling better?
Much better.
But when I think of how Ruan Bi pretended
to care about me,
I feel sick.
Don't worry.
She can't keep
pretending for so long.
She proposed to invest in the Ninghai Square project today.
Wasn't she just trying to take advantage of the situation
and use this collapse accident
to become the largest shareholder of the project?
Then just let her have her way.
Let her join the project first.
With your provocation,
she has already given herself away.
The collapse accident which she created out of anger
is full of loopholes.
Bu Fan is currently monitoring her 24 hours a day.
I believe that it won't take long
before we find the person who tampered with it.
By following this clue in the investigation,
we'll surely find
the evidence of her crimes soon.
Finally,
we'll kick her out of the project.
After Ruan Bi is arrested,
this fund
will remain in the project.
It's like using her help
to complete the Ninghai Square project.
Dong, I found the person.
The surveillance camera I had installed secretly
captured the whole process.
Unexpectedly,
it was someone we know.
Who is it?
Are you satisfied?
Yes, I am.
No matter what method you use,
you have to destroy the Ninghai Square project.
Okay.
I'm very satisfied with everything you've done.
You've been a spy by An Guoxuan's side for so long.
Though he has ended up like this,
he still doesn't know you're my person.
I've always had a question.
Why didn't you let Barbie
expose You You's identity directly?
Your greatest strength
is your simplicity.
If we had exposed You You's identity so soon,
what else could I play with?
I just love watching them
fight like dogs.
Tell me.
What should I do next?
During this period of time,
you should go to Haizhou to lay low.
What about you?
The collapse accident
was just a prelude.
The climax
hasn't even begun yet.
Currently, Zhao Ke is
the key to a breakthrough of everything.
We must find him.
Got it.
You're awake.
Bu Fan
has found Zhao Ke's flight information.
He took an early flight today
to Haizhou.
He won't be able to escape.
Let's go to Haizhou now.
No.
I have to stay here.
Why?
If I leave now,
it will alert our enemy.
Ruan Bi will become suspicious.
So,
only when I stay here
can we make her relax her vigilance.
But I don't want to leave you
alone here.
I've been thinking that
Ruan Bi clearly had so many chances to kill me.
But why has she
always kept me by her side?
I think
the reason is that she hates me.
She hates me for taking everything from her daughter.
So,
she wants to destroy me bit by bit.
There are mysteries hidden in mysteries.
There are changes arising from variations.
She is so focused on destroying me that
she doesn't realize
you've already outflanked her
to solve the problem fundamentally.
But I still don't want you to take this risk.
I can't bear the cost of
losing you.
Qi Dong.
I know that
I'm very important to you.
You're also important to me.
The trip to Haizhou
is full of danger, too.
But I believe that
you can protect yourself.
So,
I also hope that
you can trust me.
It's this ship, right?
Yes.
Let's go.