[Kill Lover]
[Episode 8]
Qi Dong.
[I love my mom]
[Ninghai City People's Hospital]
[Name: Qi Xiuqin] [Department: Thyroid, Breast Cancer, and Vascular Surgery Outpatient Clinic]
Mom.
I'll be with you soon.
Can you help me, young boy?
Young boy.
How did I fall asleep?
Why is he sweating so much?
You You.
[Room 9]
What are you doing here?
I came to see you.
But I found you weren't in your hospital room.
I guessed you'd come here to Qi Dong.
This is the soup I made for you.
I simmered it on low heat for five hours.
The doctor said for your recovery,
nutrition is what you need most.
So I brought out my specialty.
[Room 9]
Try it quickly.
Po,
thank you.
But You You,
you've just recovered from your injury.
The doctor said you need to rest peacefully.
So don't come here to keep watch.
I won't feel at ease if I'm not here by the bedside.
I keep watching over him like this,
feeling that at any moment,
he might wake up.
But Qi Dong has been in a coma for so many days.
You You, how long are you going to keep this vigil?
I don't know how long it will be,
I only know
he saved my life.
As long as he doesn't wake up,
I won't leave for a moment.
Dong, you...
Shh.
What just happened?
Ms. Qi,
I just dozed off on the toilet,
and you disappeared.
Luckily, I discovered it in time.
The IV fluid is all gone.
The air has entered his bloodstream without you knowing.
But I just checked it.
Well, you're still a patient after all.
It's normal that you didn't notice.
You should go back and rest now.
Leave Dong to me.
That won't do.
Then I'll ring the bell
and have your attending physician take you back.
You You,
you should go back and rest.
Let's go.
Dong.
We're safe now.
That was a close call just now.
Luckily, I was able to think on my feet.
I'll give you credit for that.
But, Dong,
why didn't you tell You You that you're awake?
Could it be
you're enjoying You You's
care and attention?
Or do you think
this kidnapping is
Gao Shanshan and You You working together?
So you want to investigate a bit?
What do you think?
I think it's probably the latter.
Don't worry, Dong.
I'll cooperate fully.
We'll play this act well...
Ms. Qi, why are you here again?
I've recovered and been discharged from the hospital.
I'm no longer a patient,
but Qi Dong's fiancée.
Everything here,
leave it to me.
Well.
But...
But what?
You spend half of your day in the bathroom.
I don't even know
whether you're taking care of Qi Dong
or the toilet.
Okay.
If that's the case,
I'll respectfully comply.
The toilets here aren't as comfortable as the ones at home anyway.
Being this quiet is so unlike you.
Please wake up soon.
♪ When will I find my direction ♪
♪ Where is the place without pain ♪
♪ How to make our love certain ♪
♪ Who can answer and explain ♪
♪ All my question is okay you say ♪
♪ I need is a travel day ♪
♪ All troubles will be taken away ♪
♪ Nothing will be afraid ♪
♪ Now I wanna to see your soul ♪
♪ When time is enough slow ♪
♪ Walk in a beautiful path where the flowers grow ♪
Doctor!
Hurry!
What's the situation?
Did the monitoring device come loose?
It's nothing. The patient's heart rate is a bit fast.
The machine just triggered an automatic alarm.
He won't be in danger, will he?
Don't worry.
Coma causes the patient's heartbeat to slow down,
but when entering the awakening state,
the heart rate will increase again.
Then,
it will gradually return to normal.
So you're saying
he's about to wake up?
Really? That's great!
You two,
please remove all of this.
Okay.
Thank you, doctor.
However,
he has been bedridden for a long time.
He's prone to developing bedsores.
Remember to turn him over and massage him regularly.
Okay.
This will prevent prolonged pressure on his skin.
Alright, alright.
I'll follow the doctor's instructions.
Let me help you turn over first.
I'm turning you over now.
You've been awake for a while, haven't you?
Why did you stop pretending?
Let me guess,
you weren't
pretending to be sick
just to have me take care of you, were you?
Anyway,
thank you for saving me.
I only did it for the recording pen.
Saving you
was just a coincidence.
I understand.
Regardless of the reason,
I owe you a favor.
So,
until you're fully recovered,
I'll continue to take care of you.
That's not necessary.
Do you know
how worried I was about you?
I was really afraid
that you would just sleep
and never wake up again.
I'm sorry.
Gao,
you once told me
that only I could make Xingyao successful
because I was a wolf,
with a heart
that wouldn't rest until the goal was achieved.
But you forgot
that wolves also have a vengeful nature,
vengeful and merciless.
Back then,
when I gave you this fishing rod,
I told you
that if Xingyao had a share for me,
it would definitely have a share for you too.
However,
your son, well,
after I carefully nurtured him for years
and even married my daughter to him,
he ended up using your fishing rod to tangle my fishing line.
I had no choice
but to destroy him.
Otherwise,
neither fishing rod could be used anymore.
Gao,
can you understand me?
Don't worry.
Your son is currently in a coma.
I won't touch him.
But for what he did to Jingjing,
he must pay the price.
Mr. An, the hospital called.
Mr. Qi has woken up.
He's really giving us trouble, isn't he?
Mr. Qi has survived a great ordeal.
He must have good fortune coming his way.
Have you found out
about Qi Gege's identity?
Didn't you use Qi Lan's manuscript
to test her?
I think
they just happen to share the surname Qi.
Mr. An,
why are you suspicious of Qi Gege's identity
again?
Qi Gege
had a secret meeting with Gao Shanshan.
What do you think she's after?
The two of them...
The recording.
The people who want to get the recording,
besides You Zhen,
only You You is left.
Five years ago,
Qi Dong threw You You into the sea.
Five years later,
Qi Gege appears as Qi Dong's fiancée.
So, for many things happened,
once is an accident,
twice is a coincidence,
and the third time?
It's premeditated.
If you want to probe her identity,
I have a suggestion.
Five years ago, You You
worked as a drink promoter in a nightclub, right?
We could find an old acquaintance
to catch up with her.
Qi Dong secured the exhibition center project,
making a significant contribution.
It's time to prepare a banquet
to properly celebrate.
Understood.
Did you make this?
Try it.
Doctor.
How do you feel?
Much better.
You're recovering well.
You can be discharged now.
Okay, okay.
Thank you, doctor.
Congratulations on your recovery.
Thank you.
Take care, doctor.
You've been discharged.
Is there anything you'd like to eat?
Let's have...
Steak.
Sure.
-Let me do it.
-You cook steaks well.
Welcome, welcome.
A warm welcome.
How is it?
Are you surprised?
Are you amazed?
Your bonus for this month is gone.
Please don't, Dong.
I haven't been idle these past two days.
I've cleaned this room spotlessly.
Look at this floor.
I've polished it until it shines.
It's so shiny you could use it as a mirror.
And, and over there.
I specially invited a Michelin three-star chef.
All the ingredients were flown in today.
I'm giving you one minute to leave.
I'll consider this as making up for your mistakes.
Alright then.
Dong.
There's one more thing.
Mr. An is hosting a celebration dinner tomorrow night
to celebrate you securing the exhibition center.
Take good care of yourself, Dong.
We'll make a grand appearance tomorrow night.
Dong, your hair is a bit long.
Let me tidy it up for you.
♪ The future rises and falls ♪
♪ The past, no matter what ♪
♪ Was filled with storms and sunshine ♪
♪ But every scene painted happiness ♪
♪ About me ♪
♪ About you ♪
♪ About holding on ♪
♪ Love is always a blessing ♪
♪ Luck sometimes shines ♪
♪ Romance still surrounds us ♪
♪ A beautiful, happy sign ♪
♪ Sadness ♪
♪ Fades in a moment ♪
♪ Someone like you ♪
♪ When I realized I'd become ♪
♪ You're my one and only ♪
♪ Even if life resets again ♪
♪ I'm at peace as long as you’re here ♪
♪ Someone like you ♪
♪ Holding your hand, I become ♪
♪ Trading forever, by your side ♪
♪ Leaving tears in the past ♪
♪ Letting happiness stretch on forever ♪
♪ Someone like you ♪
♪ When I realized I'd become ♪
♪ Trading forever, by your side ♪
♪ Leaving tears in the past ♪
♪ Letting happiness stretch on forever ♪
You You.
I'm sorry, I...
This custom-made suit
perfectly accentuates Dong's heroic presence.
At this celebration banquet,
we'll undoubtedly be the best-dressed there.
It's just that your complexion
doesn't look quite right.
If you have something to say, say it quickly.
Dong, I think sometimes in life,
we need to take a leap of faith.
Otherwise, the girl we defended in our youth
might end up becoming someone else's bride.
You...
Speak from experience?
Don't even mention it.
Once it was "good morning" and "good night"...
Now I'm on the blacklist.
I'm just speaking as someone who's been there,
trying to give you some advice.
In matters of love,
we men need to be a bit more proactive.
We need to be straightforward.
Otherwise, the woman won't be able to feel
your affection.
Sometimes we...
Never mind, forget I said anything.
Do you have something on your mind?
No, I don't.
Did something happen between you and Qi Dong?
What are you talking about?
Are you drinking alcohol or water?
You must be drunk.
I've been learning the art of face reading lately.
One's appearance reflects one's heart.
One's looks change with one's mind.
I see that you have a rosy complexion, You You.
Your skin is glowing.
Your eyes are bright and lifted.
You must be...
Alright, alright, shut up.
What are you even talking about?
He seemed like he wanted to kiss me.
I dodged it.
It's over then.
What nonsense is this?
If I hadn't dodged it,
then I'd really be in trouble.
But You You, even though your body refused,
your heart didn't.
Before, you
were actively flirting and teasing Qi Dong in various ways.
I didn't see you having any psychological burden then.
But it's precisely because you've fallen for him
that you're now retreating as he advances.
Qi Dong and I,
we're just in a working relationship.
Who would risk their life
to save a business partner?
And who would stay at the hospital
to take care of a business partner without even changing clothes?
So,
we should return to an appropriate position.
And the most suitable position for him and me
is that of business partners.
Is it because Qi Dong is An Guoxuan's son?
You You,
the key is to be clear about your own feelings.
But whatever decision you make,
I will firmly stand by your side.
Take this to You You later.
She'll be attending the dinner with me soon.
Understood.
At this celebration banquet,
you can finally announce publicly
that you're back at Xingyao.
This is just the beginning.
An Guoxuan's real weakness
is the Ninghai Square.
Restarting the Ninghai Square project
will be my first move
after returning to Xingyao.
How's the situation with Gao Shanshan?
Well, he
survived,
but it's said that
his skull was severely impacted,
causing a tear in the dura mater
and forming a hematoma.
The police are guarding him day and night,
but they haven't found the recording pen.
I suspect
it was destroyed in the explosion.
Good.
Keep a close eye on the hospital situation.
As soon as there's any news,
inform me immediately.
Understood.
[Night Duty Room]
Ma'am, you can't visit.
I'm his fiancée.
I just want to see him for a moment.
Shanshan.
I know.
Before you fulfill the promise you made to me,
you won't die.
You're just under too much pressure from Qi Dong.
You're exhausted.
You just want to rest well.
You rest well.
Our future,
I'll work hard for it.
♪ I kiss you goodbye ♪
♪ On an empty street ♪
♪ Be careful ♪
♪ One kiss can turn the world upside down ♪
♪ One kiss can save a person ♪
Turn it off.
I... I... I'll...
I'll change this playlist
as soon as I get back.
You...
You look
good in that outfit.
Your outfit today suits you well too.
Dong,
we're almost there.
I don't want our current awkward situation
to affect our upcoming collaboration, so
we need to cooperate well later.
Also,
I have a gift for you later.
Here they come, here they come.
Mr. Qi, could you please look this way?
Mr. Qi, Mr. Qi, one more photo please.
Today,
[Xingyao Group's celebration party]
although it's an inspiring day,
I still want to pour some cold water on it.
Indeed,
winning the exhibition center project
is undoubtedly a shot in the arm
for Xingyao.
However, it doesn't solve
the fundamental problem that Xingyao Group
has been facing for years.
If we want to break through this bottleneck,
we must restart the core project,
Ninghai Square.
So today,
in front of Mr. An
and the board members,
I volunteer to take over the Ninghai Square project,
and appoint Qi Gege
as the chief designer of the project.
Ninghai Square
[Xingyao Group's celebration party]
is a project that Mr. An is holding onto.
Mr. Qi has just returned to the headquarters,
this is overstepping, isn't it?
So, the celebration was just a pretense,
and forcing a change in leadership is the real agenda.
I wonder
what Mr. An thinks about this.
Recently,
I've been thinking about
what kind of person
can lead Xingyao into the future.
Someone with ambition,
responsibility, and accountability,
and the courage to take on challenges.
I admire
your confidence.
However, every project
has its complexities.
Whether a project is complex or not
can only be known once you start working on it.
Back then,
I named the subsidiary Xingkong,
meaning that
without the twinkling of many stars,
the night sky
would lose its luster.
In fact, the relationship between a subsidiary and its parent company
follows the same principle.
We rise together,
we fall together.
Today, right here,
I make a solemn pledge.
I will invest all the assets
under my name and those of Xingkong Company
into the Ninghai Square project,
and guarantee that within two months,
I will put it on the right track.
[Xingyao Group's celebration party]
Two months,
that's quite ambitious, isn't it?
That's quite a bold move, isn't it?
Indeed.
Xingyao Group
is not my one-man show.
It's up to everyone to decide.
You need to come up with a feasible plan
to convince the board.
With Mr. An's words,
I feel reassured.
[Xingyao Group's celebration party]
This is truly
the best gift I've ever received.
Mr. Qi's future
is limitless.
Please give me more guidance in the future.
Mr. Qi, let's discuss some projects over here.
Alright.
Please.
After you.
I happen to have a project on hand.
Mr. Qi, see if you're interested.
Try this.
The bartender is here.
I'll ask her to come over
to explain it to you.