[Kill Lover]
[Episode 2]
Godmother.
When I went abroad,
I should have forced you to come with me.
If anything had happened to you,
how could I have faced your parents?
If that had happened,
I wouldn't have known the truth,
and I wouldn't have known
that it was An Guoxuan
who destroyed my family.
Do you think your impulsiveness
and immaturity
can bring down An Guoxuan?
If I remember correctly,
this music box
was a birthday gift from your mother.
If the fishing boat hadn't passed by
and those on the boat hadn't heard the music,
suspecting someone had fallen into the water,
you would have lost your life.
Revenge isn't about acting on impulse.
If you want to defeat your enemies,
you must plan for the long term
and take it step by step.
I'll give you a new identity
and send you abroad to study.
Once you're ready,
you can return to Ninghai.
From today on,
the old Youyou
is dead.
From now on,
your name is Qi Gege.
Stop right there.
Who are you?
This is my fiancée,
Qi Gege.
Mr. Qi.
Shisi.
I got evidence of your corruption back then,
and I thought An Guoxuan
had already driven you out of Ninghai.
How come
you suddenly came back?
Mr. An calmed down
and took pity on me,
so he let me come back to be the butler.
Since you've chosen to come back
and serve as a dog,
don't have any other thoughts.
Even if I'm a dog,
I should at least be a qualified watchdog.
Well then,
you'd better take good care of
my fiancée's safety.
After all,
she's also
half your master.
Understood.
Today is the anniversary of
your mother's passing.
Mr. An asked me to bring some flowers.
My mother liked many kinds of flowers,
but she particularly disliked
the smell of chamomile.
Is An Guoxuan
sending flowers to my mother
or for me to see?
I dare not speculate
Mr. An's intentions.
Ms. Qi, since you're Mr. Qi's fiancée,
I believe you'll be attending
the family dinner tonight, right?
Of course.
Mr. Qi.
Today,
you should wear a black tie.
[Kind Mother Qi Xiuqin]
Now, quickly explain to me
why you're here.
I'm here for you, of course.
Because I never fight unprepared.
Go on.
I've always been curious how
the crown prince of the mighty Xingyao Group
became a blind man of no use.
Upon investigation, I found out
that it was actually a girl
who blinded you.
And that girl named Youyou
died
shortly after that.
You didn't kill her, did you?
It seems you've done quite some investigation.
Looks like I guessed right.
So what if I did?
What?
Are you afraid of becoming the next Youyou?
No.
I'm smarter than her.
I know how to make the right choice.
It seems you're quite satisfied
with your new identity.
Of course I am.
The identity of your fiancée will
make it more convenient for me
to get closer to An Guoxuan
and help you become the future owner
of Xingyao, Mr. Qi.
I hope you cooperate well with me
at tonight's family dinner
and behave yourself.
What's wrong?
I'm wondering
what kind of people
those who live in this mansion might be.
From now on,
countless eyes will be watching you.
If you show even the slightest weakness,
they'll be like vultures,
tearing you apart and devouring you.
So,
always remember your role
and never let your guard down.
Don't worry.
I definitely won't turn tonight's family dinner
into the Last Supper.
Mr. Qi. Ms. Qi.
Please come in.
What are you doing here?
Is this how you welcome your brother?
My surname is An, while yours is Qi.
We're not even family.
Besides,
why should you come back, you blind fool?
I'm blind,
and you're lame.
Don't you think
we make the perfect siblings?
You...
Who are you?
This is Qi Gege,
my fiancée.
Call her sister-in-law.
Brother, you haven't come back
for dinner in ages,
and the moment you do,
you bring such explosive news?
You know,
I'm always very efficient in
getting things done.
Unlike you,
who didn't even attend the engagement party.
Had to go all the way to Haizhou.
In the end,
it was all for nothing.
So you met in Haizhou?
I went to the design exhibition in Haizhou
to find new designers.
As luck would have it, I ran into Brother,
and I met Sister-in-law for the first time.
Brother-in-law, you're so young, but why
does your memory seem to be failing you?
I clearly remember it was you
who personally handed your
business card to Gege.
Am I right?
That's correct.
Senior went to Haizhou
and visited me three times
just to talk to me,
hoping I would join Xingyao.
Unfortunately,
I'm not interested.
Senior?
It's such a coincidence that
Ms. Qi and I both graduated from
the Lumini School of Design and Architecture.
What's even more coincidental
is that we were fellow disciples.
Qi Dong, what are you implying?
What could I possibly imply?
I'm just trying to remind my dear sister
to keep a close eye on your fiancé.
My relationship with Shanshan
is none of your business.
You're just like your mother,
full of ulterior motives.
You'll stop at nothing to get ahead.
Jingjing!
How many times have I told you
not to be so rude?
Hello, Mr. An.
I heard from Shisi
that right after you landed,
you went to pay respects to Qi Dong's mother.
That's good.
Alright,
let's eat first.
Let's go.
I'm not going.
Ms. An says she's not in a good mood,
so she's not coming down for dinner.
She's not young anymore, yet she's
still throwing tantrums like a child.
Well then.
Prepare a portion of food for her
and take it upstairs.
Yes.
Sorry about that.
She's my only daughter. I've spoiled her.
It's all my fault.
Originally, this trip to Haizhou
was to invite Ms. Qi to join Xingyao
as the chief designer.
As a result, not only did it not work out,
but it also caused a misunderstanding with Jingjing.
However,
it brought Brother and Ms. Qi together.
By the way,
you two have only known each other
for about three days, right?
To hate someone,
it takes a lifetime.
But to fall in love with someone,
it only takes an instant.
Gege.
When did you prepare this?
Here.
From the day I met you,
from the moment you hooked your fingers
with mine,
I knew
I'm destined to with you for life.
So, to prevent you from
slipping away from me,
I had to make the first move.
Let me personally put this ring
on your finger,
to firmly bind you to me.
Ms. Qi, you're really something.
In just a few days,
you've made my son, who was
as cold as iron, blossom.
You are...
Let's sit.
The first woman he's ever brought home.
However,
Ms. Qi, why do I feel
like we've met before?
Perhaps it's because
we were destined to become family.
Well said.
Since we're family,
Ms. Qi, why don't you share
how you and my son got together?
When I was a judge in Haizhou,
there was a student
who deliberately tried to
take revenge on me.
It was Qi Dong who showed up and saved me.
From that moment on,
I knew
that the rest of my life
belonged to him.
What a heroic rescue.
But
it was too coincidental, wasn't it?
Could it be that Brother had been
following Ms. Qi all along?
That's right.
I had indeed been planning
for a long time to be with Gege.
Unlike you,
who can't get what you want.
It seems Ms. Qi's appearance
has put my son and son-in-law
at odds with each other.
But they both know very well
that what makes them most uneasy
is still the exhibition center project.
Ms. Qi.
Which one of them do you think
will win the project?
Mr. An,
what you really want to know is
between Qi Dong and Gao Shanshan,
who will inherit Xingyao, right?
In recent years, my health
has been getting worse and worse.
There have been many rumors
about Xingyao out there.
I'd like to hear
different opinions.
After all, listening to both sides
leads to clarity.
On the surface,
it's a fight for the inheritance of Xingyao.
But actually,
it's about Xingyao's operational difficulties
in recent years.
Sales have plummeted.
Xingyao urgently needs a revolution,
a drastic cure for a desperate disease.
So whoever can lead Xingyao
to break through the siege
and make a comeback from the brink of defeat
is surely going to be
the future leader of Xingyao, isn't he?
"Break through the siege and make a comeback
from the brink of defeat," well said.
Ms. Qi,
you're indeed intelligent and beautiful.
No wonder both of them
want to bring you under their wing.
Ms. Qi.
You're welcome to join
my department at any time.
You really are
persistent, aren't you?
You two are really like
sworn enemies who are bound to meet.
Why don't you channel that competitive spirit
into something more important?
How long has it been since you
played Go with me?
Shanshan,
let's play Go.
Let's eat first.
This morning at the cemetery,
you already knew who I am, didn't you?
That's right.
The reason why you didn't expose my identity
is that you wanted to see
if I had what it takes to go on.
Now it seems
I have a good eye.
You went through all that trouble to
come back to the An family
for revenge, right?
Because you harbor hatred in your heart.
You hate Qi Dong for exposing your embezzlement
of project funds,
but you hate even more the master
you served loyally for 10 years, An Guoxuan,
who drove you
out of Ninghai
like a stray dog.
Don't get smart.
I can expose your identity anytime.
Three years ago,
you fell in love with a rich girl.
and you wanted to elope with her.
However, An Guoxuan
drove you out of Ninghai,
separating you two lovebirds.
When you came back,
that girl
had died.
I didn't expect
you to be such a romantic.
What do you want?
Since we both have secrets,
and our goals align,
why don't
we join forces?
I'll consider it.
However, I must warn you.
Although Qi Dong is blind,
his mind is still sharp.
You've been lurking by his side.
Aren't you afraid that one day
he'll discover your true identity?
Someone was here.
Qi Dong.
Where have you been?
Are you worried about me?
However,
I've discovered that this house
seems to be haunted.
Are you scared of ghosts?
Sometimes,
humans are
much scarier than ghosts.
Are you scared of me then?
You seem to enjoy dancing with ghosts.
Especially with you.
This time I saw Mr. Qi,
I noticed his movements have become
increasingly agile.
It's hard to imagine what kind of effort
he's been putting in behind the scenes.
This son of mine
is indeed quite remarkable.
Also, look into
this Qi Gege.
Yes, sir.
I said I don't want to eat. Take it all away!
Fine, don't eat then.
If you lose some weight, you'll look even more beautiful
in the wedding dress in a few days.
I'm not wearing a wedding dress.
I'm not getting married.
You and that Qi Gege can both get lost!
Shanshan...
A woman like Qi Gege
is nothing but a disposable pawn.
But you
are different from her.
How am I different?
In my world,
you're the only one.
How is it?
Isn't this place exactly the same as
the apartment you lived in back in France, Youyou?
Ms. Ruan will never find out
that you've secretly returned to Ninghai.
Come on, Youyou.
Have a seat.
Actually,
Godmother has already done so much for me.
I really can't let her worry
about me anymore.
Just one word from you,
and I've run my legs off.
You've been following me around
since we were kids.
Don't you remember how many scoldings I've taken
for fighting on your behalf?
Stop, stop.
I'm sorry, Youyou.
I won't complain anymore.
Oh, by the way, Youyou,
how was the family dinner today?
Did you make a big impression?
Qi Dong proposed to me
in front of An Guoxuan.
Dong,
are you serious about the proposal?
I always felt you had special
feelings for Youyou.
That lunatic Qi Dong
actually came up with this trick.
However, I'm starting to get interested
in this fiancé of mine.
My five years of effort
haven't been in vain after all.
Tonight, I've officially entered
the An family.
So our next step is...
To team up with Gao Shanshan
and kick Qi Dong out of the picture.
["Big City, Small Love" Wedding Photography]
Ms. An.
We've been waiting for you.
We've just received a few new
wedding dresses designed by top designers.
Please have a browse.
Shanshan,
why don't you pick one for me?
Sure.
This way, please.
How about this one?
This one is too plain, isn't it?
I prefer something with more
design elements
and shinier.
I remember
there's a handcrafted designer piece
in this store.
You have an excellent eye.
That's our store's prized possession.
Let me take you to see it.
Alright.
Wait for me here.
This way.
Senior.
How do you like the wedding dress I chose?
Your taste is indeed similar to mine, Junior.
However,
I didn't expect you to
win Qi Dong over so quickly
and become my sister-in-law, Junior.
I told you,
he's just an appetizer I'm serving you.
So how do you plan to serve
this appetizer, Junior?
I'll join Xingkong
and personally handle the exhibition center project.
I'll pretend to help him secure the project,
but at the crucial moment,
I'll pull the rug out from under him.
By then,
you'll be able to reap the benefits, Senior.
You're making me impatient.
Haste
makes waste.
[Decline] [Answer]
[Jing]
How can I not be anxious?
Jingjing.
Okay.
I'll be right there.
["Big City, Small Love" Wedding Photography]
Brother.
Why are you here?
Of course I'm here to choose
a wedding dress for Qi Gege.
What?
You can get married,
but I can't get engaged?
That's not what I mean.
It's just you've come to the wrong place.
This is the changing area.
Is that so?
Oh no.
I forgot Qi Gege's
exact measurements.
Maybe I should give her a call.
Call...
Never mind.
I almost forgot that
I asked her to give me the initial design
draft for the exhibition center today.
She's probably busy.
I'll just have her come with me next time.
Take your time choosing.
Oh, right.
Remember,
don't just pick any dress randomly.
You know my sister's temper.
When she gets angry,
the consequences are very serious.
Take care, Brother.
[Xingkong]
Hello, Mr. Qi.
Have you seen Qi Gege?
I haven't noticed.
It's your first day officially on the job.
How are you adjusting?
Intimidated by your authority, Mr. Qi,
the colleagues are all very friendly to me.
Then I hope you won't
become arrogant because of this.
Where's your design?
This design features
a roof covered with a
diagonal rib structure.
The transparent space made of glass
spans the entire building,
blurring the boundaries between
indoor and outdoor.
When paired with unique lighting design,
it perfectly aligns with the
exhibition center's
main theme of a lazy and mysterious
semi-transparent style.
I wonder
if you're satisfied, Mr. Qi.
You should ask Mr. Fu, the head
of the bidding committee,
if he would be satisfied.
The quality of the design proposal
is not his concern.
To deal with Mr. Fu,
we need to tailor our approach.
I didn't expect that
you're also a seasoned
traditional Chinese medicine
practitioner, Ms. Qi.
I wouldn't say I'm a seasoned practitioner,
but to treat you,
I'm more than qualified.
Tell me,
what exactly are you up to?
The Ninghai City Amateur Fencing Competition.
You must have heard of it, right, Mr. Qi?
You want to
participate in this competition?
That's right.
Mr. Fu is one of the sponsors.
He's a die-hard fencing fan.
He's sponsored quite a few
amateur fencers to compete over the years,
but their best ranking
was only top 16.
This is also how he got the nickname
"Mr. Fu, the 16th."
I was thinking,
if we could help him redeem himself,
even if the exhibition center project
isn't a sure thing,
it would at least give us
some advantage, right?
It seems you're
quite confident
in your fencing skills, Ms. Qi.
Fencing requires speed,
accuracy, and explosive power.
I'll compete with you by locating the sound
through hearing.
If you want to win,
bring out your full potential.
Are you alright?
I don't think you're really blind.
Your eyes must have grown somewhere else.
Some things
are not meant to be seen,
but to be felt with the heart.
Oh my.
Why is this guy so harsh?
He's just a madman.
He's already holding back.
I think he was just taking the opportunity
to get back at you.
Could it be that last time at the bridal shop,
he already discovered that you were
having a secret meeting with Gao Shanshan?
If what you said is true,
then it's just as I suspected.
He's been putting on an act
with me all along.
He's been pretending to be blind.
Youyou.
You must have guessed by now.
No matter what kind of villain
I am in your eyes now,
you will eventually understand me.