GOING TO YOU AT A SPEED OF 493KM
THE PLACES, PEOPLE, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL
Nice to meet you.
EPISODE 2
Did I come at a bad time?
Should I go?
What? No.
No, I'll go. I was about to anyway.
So… are we now on the same team?
What you're saying is that
we're on the same team, right?
I'll be on the same team
as an athlete I've discovered.
That feels a bit weird.
You said you quit.
You told me it wouldn't be easy
to leave the court.
You were right.
Then I'll see you later.
We'll see each other later
since we're on the same team. Right?
Bye.
Taeyang.
Who me?
Take your bag.
Right, that's mine.
I thought it was yours.
So what I meant was…
I'm looking forward to it.
Yeah, same here.
That's right. Here's General.
Take back your racket.
I promised to give it back
when you return.
Did you just call it General?
You can have it. I'm not taking it back.
All right.
I should go.
Gosh.
Sunsoo!
Let me do it.
Do you do all the chores
as the youngest member?
Yes, I'm not the youngest, but I still do.
You can let me take the reins.
You know I'm an outcast.
I should do my fair share of work
so I can stand up for myself.
Let's do it together, then.
I'm the loser on this team.
I guess a loser outranks an outcast.
Hurry up.
I told you to take turns,
but you get them to do everything.
All right. He's one of us from now on.
You know each other already, but…
Still, it's your first day.
Introduce yourself.
I love you!
Yunis is the best! We rock!
-I'm done.
-Why don't you keep going?
That was amusing.
I'm curious what else you got.
-I'll cut it here.
-All right, then.
-Fall in.
-Yes, sir.
Wait.
We have unfinished business to settle.
You said you'd pay for all the drinks
but left without--
He paid me back.
What?
Precisely calculated
because credibility matters.
It has been handled flawlessly.
What is this? Are you two close?
-Hey…
-Tell me, are you two close?
Hey, eyes to the front!
How dare you while your coach is speaking.
Park Taeyang, Park Taejun…
Your names are alike.
Your both Parks.
Like twins. We have the Park twins.
Twins…
Now that we have the Park twins,
I want to reorganize
the mixed doubles teams.
Split up into a women's team
and men's team.
Taeyang and Taejun can--
Do you have
no consideration for our lives?
Do I need to go that far?
Seriously, I've tried…
to keep this to myself, Coach.
Then let's keep it that way.
Did she sigh twice?
All hell will break loose
if she sighs one more time.
She will go berserk.
Who would want to be
on the same team as Taeyang?
She took three years off
and isn't even close to being an athlete.
What about the effect
that will have on her partner?
You only play singles,
so this isn't any of your business.
We can sort this out within our team.
Why do you keep on sighing?
Because she is losing it.
You shouldn't force us
to make sacrifices.
Does anyone here
want to play with Taeyang?
How dare you raise your voice!
There's no one.
I'm the coach.
Mind your manners, will you?
You'd better not reorganize the teams.
I said, manners! Why you…
We have newcomers today, for God's sake.
Go easy on me.
But Coach,
does Taeyang have the skills
to join our team?
Coach? On what grounds?
I'm the issue here, so--
No, Taeyang.
You're risking your neck here.
I can handle this.
Hey, Taeyang.
Do you have something to say?
Let's talk outside… quickly!
Hey! Where do you think you're going?
Youngsim, calm down. Coach is here.
-Get off me.
-Oh, jeez.
-Youngsim, please. Calm down.
-Let me go!
-Hey! What's with you?
-Come here. Quickly.
-Please stop!
-Youngsim's gone nuts.
-Hey!
-Let go!
Somebody stop her!
-Come here, damn it!
-Hold on to her!
Does she still go berserk like that?
I guess some things don't change with age.
It's 19 million won.
What is?
My annual salary.
They insisted on shaving off a million,
because even 20 million was too much.
How did I get in?
Because I'm not worth a lot.
I'm here because I don't cost much.
That really is cheap. A total bargain.
All the national players
stay at the National Training Center.
Those who don't care
to represent the country are here.
Did you know
our dorm curfew is at 10 p.m.?
You can't get in once the doors close
and lose points if you stay out overnight.
-That means your salary gets cut.
-I hadn't heard that.
You should've looked into it.
The rules are tough.
No drinking or smoking in the dorm.
Most of all, no dating teammates.
If caught, one will be kicked out.
That I really didn't know.
Are you here to work part-time?
What made you join the team?
Even if you can't take your eyes off her,
you must keep your feelings to yourself.
Even if you have feelings for her,
you can't let it show.
You can't click with someone
and get attached to them
as you train and play together here.
You're not the type to quit
because of a girl, right?
Then why are you with her?
-Sorry?
-You can't take your eyes off her.
I see you also have feelings for her.
What? Me?
What nonsense on your first day here!
That's totally ridiculous.
You've got it all wrong.
Well, I don't care.
Do you guys also act childish
and ostracize people?
-Who…
-I noticed earlier today.
Oh, you mean Taeyang?
I understand she's not as fit
due to her long break.
Still, that sort of thing is uncommon
in professional sports teams.
I guess you have no idea
what kind of person she is.
I don't want to be the one to tell.
You'll soon find out
what the real reason is.
Continue. Good.
Hey, Taejun.
Now that you're with us,
you need to take a fitness test.
Let me introduce you to our trainer.
I'm Kim Sibong.
You can call me Mr. Sibong.
I'm Park Taejun. Nice to meet you.
Hello!
I should be training…
I can't stop
with you staring at me like that.
Gosh, I'm exhausted.
Where are you going?
I was just…
-Take it easy.
-You too.
Walk at level six for ten minutes,
run at level ten for ten,
then sprint at twelve for two minutes.
Repeat this routine on the treadmill
until you're as fit as an athlete.
Forget about holding a racket.
You have such puny arms.
-Then when will I train--
-No.
All you will do is run 7 km a day.
But what about basic training like--
No. From now on,
I know what's best for your body.
I'm in charge, not you.
Sprint at twelve for two minutes.
Yes, sir.
Three, four, five, six, seven, eight…
JINCHEON NATIONAL TRAINING CENTER
-Thank you, sir.
Hey.
Watch where you're going.
Have you picked up studying now?
Hey, Junghwan.
-What is it?
-This?
It's a list of athletes
for the world championships.
So another overseas trip? That's tiring.
Your name isn't on the list.
It's not?
That's great. I wanted a break anyway.
Really? Congratulations, then.
-I'm so jealous.
-Hey, you should just get going.
That's right. You're also not going.
-What?
-This time.
That's not true. Hey!
Gosh, he's such a jerk.
Doesn't he remind you of you
when you were young?
Sorry. It's my fault you're not going.
You should've gotten a better partner.
That's not what I meant. Hey!
Where are you going?
Why am I not playing
at the world championships?
You should take a break.
It's been decided that way for a reason.
I didn't compete
in any national matches for this,
so what do you mean--
That's why
you should do as you're told.
Is this how you tame your athletes?
What did you say?
Because of me, Hyukbong can't go either!
I'm not going to beg you. But Coach,
how are you going to cope with this?
Don't you think people will ask
why I'm not participating?
That's why I need you
to do an interview for the team.
"I wanted to give
the junior members a chance."
"I'll be here rooting for them."
Go say that
during the team press conference.
You really think I'll say that?
Don't you want to go to the Olympics?
What about Hyukbong, who counts on you
and has been training for it?
You should think about that.
There's not much
to being a coach, is there?
No.
It's true.
It's not like
any of you listen to a word I say.
You'll have to find
your own doubles partner.
When it comes to finding a partner,
the athlete's opinion matters the most.
I've got this.
Do you have someone in mind
who would be willing?
I think so.
Gosh, you're good at this.
Oh, my gosh!
Just kidding.
-Gosh, you scared me!
-That really hurt.
-It's fine.
-What else can I help with?
Why are you so adorable?
Hey, babe.
Why are you in such a good mood?
Isn't it annoying having to cook
a late-night snack for everyone?
It's not like
the seniors chipped in or anything.
Cooking is how I relieve my stress.
I just love eating.
When I was younger,
I was this big from eating too much.
So I started playing badminton
to lose weight.
Babe, I'm sure you'd be totally cute
even if you put on weight.
Chubby cheeks, check. Belly, check.
You're such a teddy bear.
You're much cuter than I am.
Nice!
"Chubby cheeks, check. Belly, check."
I could have gotten
a great shot of that too.
What is this? What were you doing there?
Going undercover?
I heard you two were cooking,
so I figured you'd be here acting mushy.
Proof secured.
Gosh, what a meaningful day it has been.
So were you hiding in there
just to take that picture?
For how long?
For an hour or two?
I thought I was going to die.
Why?
Why would you do this?
Don't you have better things to do?
Because it's fun.
You two should be nice to me.
I have a really big mouth.
Is Jiho's restaurant open for business?
I'm starving.
Gosh, look how messy this place is.
Tidy up, will you?
As if your dorm is any cleaner.
What are we having today?
Sir, please have a seat here.
You have no idea how grateful
we are to have you on our team.
You're our hope.
Can I get water with ice?
I'm thirsty from doing hard work.
Water with ice. Got it.
Hurry up.
Hurry up. Got it.
Let's dig in.
-Thanks for the food!
-Please enjoy.
-Great job.
-Thanks for the food.
-Enjoy.
I think we're missing a person, though.
Can you get Taeyang?
Sure.
Let's just eat.
Come on, don't be like that with food.
Get her to join us.
Hey.
Just eat your food. If not, then leave.
Don't make me lose my appetite.
-Captain.
-Yes?
There's zero teamwork here.
I've never seen this in my entire career.
-That bastard… Hey!
-Youngsim!
Jeez. His net play is incredible.
His reaction time is relatively fast too.
SEOUL CITY HALL PARK TAEJUN
That's pretty cool.
-Go for it!
Park Taejun.
This guy…
I hope he agrees to be my partner.
PARK TAEJUN
Oh, my gosh!
My hand has gone crazy.
It drew a heart on its own.
Taeyang, are you there?
Boys aren't allowed in here.
The girls are over at the boys' dorm now.
Let's eat together.
-Is that your room?
-Where do you think you're going?
Let me take a look.
Come on, there's nothing to… No!
Hey, wait!
Why do you get a room to yourself?
I'm jealous.
Because no one wanted to be my roommate.
Are you still jealous?
Actually, I wanted to
talk to you in person.
What are you looking at?
I was looking at you in this photo.
When did you take this?
Back in high school?
Wow, you look very determined.
Why are you looking?
All right. You said
you wanted to talk in person. Go on.
Right.
Let's be partners.
For the mixed doubles?
Yes.
As you can see,
no one even wants to share a room with me.
Who would partner up with me?
If I could play in mixed doubles
until I find a female partner,
then I could get to practice
and compete in matches.
You see, I don't have much time.
Hey, Taejun, wait up!
I'm now going to try to persuade you.
So listen with an open heart.
I'm going to share a very sad story.
I had to make an effort
to be part of a family.
When I was a kid, I thought
I'd get disowned if I was bad at sports.
So I trained like crazy.
Everyone else is born into a family,
but I didn't have a thing to me.
I had to work for everything I got.
Gosh, you can't bring that up now.
It's not fair.
I know. I'm not going to be fair.
If there's anything in my life
I can take for granted
without putting in so much effort,
I would really like to have it.
Are you saying that's me?
Yes. I want to have you easily.
To me, being an athlete is just a job.
I don't like taking a single step
without getting paid.
No one likes to work overtime.
But you were
looking forward to training with me.
Go back inside.
Hey, wait a minute.
Help me out this once.
Sorry. You're too much
of a burden for me to handle.
You're a hot potato.
-What?
-Thanks for the meal.
-The food was really good.
-It was tasty.
-I'll leave you to do the dishes.
-Thanks.
Did you enjoy it too?
Gosh, you startled me.
What's with him? He didn't even say bye.
PARK TAEJUN
What's this?
Let's see…
Coach!
Coach, did you see
Taejun's fitness test results?
His scores are
off the charts for every section.
He's a total monster.
I did see it.
Here, take a look.
Sure. What is it?
I was also shocked by his results,
so I went through his documents.
Turn the page.
See who his older sister is.
She's not that athlete
that we know of, is she?
That is precisely who she is.
He has lived his entire life
in the shadow of his great sister.
I bet he never got the spotlight.
So he just decided to throw in the towel.
Please enter your PIN.
Check your account balance
and select your desired transaction.
Sixty million won! I love you, Yunis!
Sixty million won…
Hi, Mom.
You should check your bank account.
I sent you something.
It's quite a lot.
Come on, you know how much I love you.
I have to go train now. Bye.
Do you have it?
Exquisite…
I'm sure you know
how difficult it was to find.
Things must be going well.
It's been ages since your last purchase.
Listen. I can afford even more than this,
so find me that pair.
What? Do you mean Flex Royal?
Yes. I keep seeing them in my dreams.
I don't need
the Korean flag or a gold medal.
Those sneakers are all I need
to make my life complete.
I want to be buried with them.
That I can't do.
There are only 500 pairs in the world.
In Korea,
I think there are only about five pairs.
Gosh, I would love to see them.
You're precious too.
Hey, Taejun. Wait up!
I've given it some thought,
and I think I'm your responsibility.
-What?
-I started badminton because of you!
You said so yourself
that you discovered me.
So that makes me your "perdona"?
Doesn't that sound like
a mix of "persona" and "Maradona"?
Weren't you ashamed
when that just slipped out?
Don't play innocent.
You're really not going to play with me?
You're the reason why
I'm going through this hell!
-Don't play innocent.
-No, I'm running away.
-That's irresponsible.
-I know.
You're not manning up! You know that?
Hey, Taejun.
MEN'S LOCKER ROOM
Now that you've showered,
how about taking me under your wing?
No?
I don't know what giving up means.
I'm your responsibility!
Gosh, you startled me.
Stop saying that.
What would the others think?
I don't care about the others.
All I want is you.
Please stop.
You're putting too much pressure on me.
I'm doing it on purpose.
I know.
Yes, that's what I'm doing.
Did I startle you?
-Then will you be my partner?
-Go away!
I must have frightened you.
Then I can take you under my wing.
I'm a responsible person.
Since we've run into each other,
take me under your wing.
Just this once.
Do you know the key reason
why we can't be partners?
Because you lack empathy and you're cold?
What do you think is the most meaningful
and vital thing in a mixed doubles match?
Doing a high five after scoring a point.
That's what motivates you to play.
But can you reach this high?
So my height is the issue?
Show me if you can.
I'll put up with you making me feel small
and give it a go.
I'm going to try now.
It's perfect to rest my hands on.
You're like a real senior today.
I mean, you've agreed to do an interview
paving the way for us juniors.
Gosh, you really do know
how to control your temper now.
Shut your trap.
Since the juniors also need to experience
playing in international games,
I felt it would be the right thing to do
for me to not take part this time.
I'll be cheering for them
to do their best.
Mr. Yuk.
We hear you have issues with self-care,
and that's why you weren't selected
for this competition.
Can you tell us about that?
I'm taking good care of myself.
You've been posting photos
of yourself in clubs,
driving luxury cars,
and drinking on social media.
There's a debate about
whether you're qualified to be an athlete.
What are your thoughts on this?
Why the hell does that matter?
-What are you doing?
-I'm offended and quitting.
Hey, Yuk Junghwan!
All right, make it long.
Let's try that again, starting from here.
Hey, Sunsoo.
You have to pull your chest back
and angle it down.
-Make your swing sharper.
-Okay.
Like… Gosh. Is that so hard to change?
Sorry, sir!
Sunsoo, is everything okay at home?
You seem down today.
He's always down like that.
All right, let's wrap up for today.
It's almost time to clock out.
Everyone, gather around!
-Are you sure you're okay?
-I'm fine.
What should we do today?
Jeez.
Coach, I didn't know you were here.
-That's okay. I got it.
-Want to play soccer outside?
Sports should be played indoors.
It's uncivilized
to play sports out in the sun.
We should keep our dignity.
Agreed! Wise words.
It deserves a hand.
Then how about we play four on four?
Hey, Taeyang.
Let's have a match.
The rest of you… can watch.
Let's see if you're worth
19 million won a year.
I think you might deserve less.
Shouldn't we stop them?
Let's watch and find out
how much Taeyang can still do.
Whether she has hit rock bottom or not.
You know that Youngsim is
an Asian Games gold medalist, right?
She retired from the national team
and is here to complete a Grand Slam.
Taeyang is going to get crushed.
LEE YOUNGSIM
-That was slow.
-Yes.
What is she doing?
She's completely distracted.
She hit a smash!
Not even close…
She was once famous
for her signature smash shot.
Now she's lost it.
She's doomed.
Match is over.
Let's go home.
Dismissed!
Let's go.
Look at that.
You got in just before the curfew.
Are you going outside?
Yes, to lock up the entrance.
What for? We're all adults.
I have to.
My gosh. Why are you here?
You don't belong
in a shabby place like this.
I wasn't that much of a big shot.
Flex Royal…
Who owns these?
Whose sneakers are these?
What about them?
Those are mine.
But who are you?
He recently joined our team.
You two are the same age.
How did you get…
I mean, there are
only 500 pairs in the world.
That makes me one in five hundred.
Because I'm Yuk Junghwan.
Are you wearing rubber shoes?
You should get a new pair.
Rubber shoes?
Hey, that's my room!
The thing is, he used to stay in this room
when he was here from time to time.
I see. Did you get kicked out
of the national training center?
I read about the trouble you caused.
Did you get suspended?
For a month? Forever?
For a month!
Gosh.
Hey, Rubber Shoes.
Can you leave? I'm tired.
Excuse me…
How about going to Seungwoo's room?
-Me?
No, I'll go. You two can share this room.
-Why?
-Just stay put.
It would be wrong to kick you out again
when you have nowhere to go.
You can use the bed.
The blanket is mine though.
The pillow's also yours, right?
It belongs to the dorm.
What? Are you going to Seungwoo's room?
I'm going to the bathroom.
I'll be going every ten minutes,
so curl up, Rubber Shoes.
Stop calling me like that.
Yuk Junghwan wins.
I don't see her.
Who are you looking for?
Hey, Junghwan. Come have a seat here.
I don't see Taeyang.
Right. She'll be gone the whole day.
I pulled a prank on her.
-What kind of prank?
-Curious?
Where is Taeyang?
She didn't come?
I don't know.
Maybe she's in the training room.
Taeyang!
So she's not here either?
What? She's not in the training room?
-No.
-She isn't here either.
Does anyone know where Taeyang is?
What? A Han River marathon?
So, is Taeyang there right now
running all by herself?
Come on. She'll realize it was a joke
when none of us show up and come back.
A joke?
Is it fun to put someone
through hell and call it a joke?
Don't get mad at me.
Yuri is the one who did it.
Hello? Hey, where are you?
Come quick. No one's here yet though.
You should've known it was a prank
when no one showed up.
-Why are you so clueless?
-A prank?
There's a marathon today
to Dongjak Bridge--
There's no marathon.
Catch a taxi back. Hurry.
Hello? Hey, Taejun!
Why do you all take it so far?
I just don't understand.
Are the rest of you that great?
Is it that hard
to accept her as part of the team?
This is completely ridiculous.
I guess you still don't know.
She once committed bribery.
What?
Who told you that? That's a false--
She admitted it herself.
All right. I'll run then.
I'll run as you say,
and be fooled if that's what you want.
I'll do whatever you want.
Fine.
I'm a piece of trash that bribes people.
I wish I had the money to bribe people…
I'm a rich girl? What a nice image.
Then I'll act the part.
Why did you admit
to doing something you didn't do?
For what reason?
Why do I have to be the third wheel?
I feel wretched.
The fencing team is up ahead,
15 degrees to your left.
I didn't join the national team for this.
The coast is clear…
My eyes!
If you two want to be like that,
make your relationship public.
Why do you put me…
Why me? You two can just…
Come on. Taeyang, you're adorable.
Taeyang, you're so kind.
Then, how about we all live together?
-No.
-Are you crazy?
Then… Junyoung,
you should come live with me.
No thanks.
Why not? Let's share a place.
Should we?
-That's a promise.
-All right.
I made it.
PARK TAEJUN
Taeyang isn't back yet.
Should I tell her to call you
when she gets back?
Hello, sir.
Nice to see you again.
I'm also with Yunis.
Really?
Gosh. Then it's
a good thing I didn't hire you.
Anyway, I heard it's pretty tough
to get on this team.
I'm pretty tough too.
You're going to regret not hiring me.
Okay.
Anyway, can you get Taeyang for me?
-Taeyang?
-Yes.
She's training right now.
At this hour?
Yes, it's sort of like
a special nighttime training session.
Is she getting special treatment?
-Yes.
-Well, she's not just any athlete.
Did you know
she was once called the Smash Queen?
-Of course, I do.
-That's right.
She might be sluggish for a while,
but she just has to set her mind to it.
She has never once let me down.
I'm sure she tried her very best…
not to let you down.
How could you go AWOL
when you just joined the team?
Aren't you going to tell me why?
What's the reason?
I had a moment of self-pity
at the Han River.
I was reminiscing about the past.
Are you kidding yourself?
Are you the big shot like you used to be?
No, sir.
Your heyday has come to an end.
You know that, right?
Yes, sir.
Your voice is quivering.
Why? Are you going to cry?
No, sir.
I'm aware that
I can't go back to how I used to be.
Then why can't you let go of your past?
Run a few laps around the track
before curfew starts. Okay?
Yes, sir.
Did you run by yourself at the Han River?
This can't be from running a few laps.
How did you know I ran laps?
I just happened to see you.
That's strange.
Did you tell Coach what happened today?
Why are you taking all the blame?
Is that the only thing you're good at?
I'm very tired, so I don't have--
No one told you to run.
Why do you knowingly do this to yourself?
And what's this about you offering bribes?
I know it isn't true.
What do you know?
I guess you heard the rumor.
That's all true.
I overheard you talking to yourself.
I know you didn't do it.
Does someone have something on you?
What? Did you commit murder?
Why on earth do you have to
keep your mouth shut and take the fall?
You can tell me, at least.
Who do you think you are to me?
What?
Thank you for being nice to me.
I'm grateful for everything,
but let's not overdo it.
Give that to me.
I can carry it myself.
Stop being so stubborn.
You can't even walk properly.
Hey, Taejun!
I don't want to be your partner.
Why bring that up all of a sudden?
And it's not as if I asked you to.
I know.
I won't be waiting around anymore.
I didn't ask you because I was in a hurry
and anyone would do.
I watched your matches over and over.
And I could see how talented you were.
The talent you've been looking down on.
I thought I could show you
how much better you can be.
Then it would be a win-win.
I didn't have
any reason to be that desperate.
So it was embarrassing
and I felt small, but I begged you.
But not anymore.
You find me annoying, don't you?
Well, same here.
Looks tasty.
You're late.
I got some fresh air while I was out.
You must've had fun.
Taeyang.
You brought this on yourself.
Yes, I know.
She took advantage of it to hang out.
I knew she would.
Are you not going to eat?
Why isn't she eating?
I should put on some pain relief patches.
I should also stretch before going to bed.
-Good morning!
Coach will be here later today.
I bet he had too much to drink last night.
Did you drink with him?
No, we're not… I didn't drink.
All right. Taeyang isn't feeling well,
so she won't join us today.
This morning, let's do your favorite.
Interval training.
Too slow. Move faster.
Look at you, Dongwan.
That's good.
This is really bugging me.
Hey, Park Taejun!
Taejun, where are you going?
I didn't ask you because I was in a hurry
and anyone would do.
I watched your matches over and over.
And I could see how talented you were.
The talent you've been looking down on.
I thought I could show you
how much better you can be.
Congratulations, Taejun!
-Hurray!
Look at this!
One, two, three!
THE 5TH CHUNCHEON
JUNIOR BADMINTON CHAMPIONSHIPS
CHUNCHEON SPORTING GOODS
Mom. I'm back.
Oh, you're here.
Taejun, your sister won a gold medal!
Selling badminton rackets
to raise your kid has really paid off!
What was the name of the competition?
Let me get you a banner for the store.
There's no need for that.
The World Junior Badminton Championships.
"The World."
Honey, stop.
She's a proud daughter of Chuncheon.
No, a proud daughter of Korea.
That's right!
-She's the best!
-So are we having a celebratory meal?
Of course, my treat!
Can you give me
the location of the funeral home?
Okay.
You're all sluggish today.
Don't fall behind!
OH SUNSOO
YUNIS
Good.
Dongwan, your footwork is slow.
Stay focused, there isn't much time left.
Excuse me, Coach.
I have to leave early…
Why?
My high school coach passed away.
I'm sorry.
Don't be. You should get ready and go.
Mr. Oh Sunsoo.
Yes?
You're from Jeju Island.
Do you have a suit here?
I'm at Dad's training center
to give him some side dishes.
Yes.
All right. Bye.
Isn't that Yuk Junghwan?
I keep this in my car since I often have
to attend ceremonies. You can wear it.
The person who passed away…
Is he the one that believed in you?
You told us
at the first get-together we had.
You…
remember that?
No one cares about me here.
He's only seen you in gym clothes
looking scruffy, right?
You should dress up
to see him for the last time.
What's your shoe size?
Do you have dress shoes?
That's okay.
I have a pair of black sneakers.
And…
I'm sure he'd prefer to see me
in my sneakers.
He's passed away, but that doesn't mean
his faith in you is gone.
That is now yours to keep forever.
Go and say your last goodbye to him.
How long have I been sleeping?
What? Why didn't she wake me up?
Why didn't you wake me up
when I was right there?
Do you have no sense of loyalty?
But you were only pretending.
I saw how quickly you closed your eyes.
Training hours are over.
Where are you going?
I'm going to work out a bit.
If I don't,
I'll have an even harder time tomorrow.
You should leave that
for tomorrow's you to deal with.
Let's have dinner together…
I told you not to go overboard.
Bye.
That's impressive.
Fine. I don't care whether
your body breaks down or you get injured.
Go ahead and have it your way!
Are you going to win gold
in the next Olympics or something?
Let me congratulate you in advance then!
You should go for it!
Are you crying?
How am I supposed to go for it?
There's nothing I can do.
My body aches just because I ran a bit.
And no one expects me to do well anymore.
I'm a goner who's worth 19 million won
a year, so how can I do well?
That's never going to happen!
Once an athlete is past their prime,
it never returns.
It's over for me!
I know that.
You're finally crying.
What?
You've held back long enough.
It's about time you cry.
What are you doing?
Keep on crying.
Taeyang is crying! Who wants to see?
-Didn't you want to see?
-Hey!
Over here! Taeyang's crying!
Why you little…
She's sobbing and has a runny nose!
-Come over here.
-I don't think I should.
Come here, you jerk.
You're dead meat!
What's going on? What was that she said?
Hey, what happened?
Taejun, get yourself over here!
Have you stopped crying now?
-You're such a freak!
-I can see you're full of energy.
Right. That's why I'm ready to kill you.
You're so simple-minded.
You were about to quit,
but you came back to life
with a little push.
You're seriously my type.
Come here.
Be my partner.
What?
I know now isn't
the right time to say this,
but let's be partners.
You're playing me for a fool.
No, let's play together.
If I get persuaded now,
it means I have no self-respect.
I really want what's best for you.
I thought you would be
better off with another partner.
That's why I kept saying no.
I see. That's very thoughtful of you.
Why? Do you take pity on me?
You're…
my "Perdona."
I'll be there…
for as long as you want me.
We won't get to high five though.
I'll be standing behind you.
Where are these Park twins?
I have a hunch they got into a big fight.
I'm dying of curiosity.
Why are you curious?
Let's go inside.
Here they come.
-It doesn't look good.
-Right.
-You should ask them.
-Why me?
-Ask about what happened.
-Gosh. Let go.
So, what happened between you two?
I don't know.
She hasn't given me her answer yet.
Answer to what?
Two, three, four…
Darn it.
What's going on?
Why is she going that way?
Why does she torment me?
What did he say? Spill it.
-She hasn't answered something.
-Not answer what?
-I don't know.
-I want to find out.
Taeyang, let's play together.
Come on.
You.
Yes?
You'd better make sure
to stand right behind me on the court.
And I can do it.
Do what?
Put your hand up like this.
Higher.
Raise your arm as high as you can.
Here I go.
GOING TO YOU AT A SPEED OF 493KM
It's a little late,
but you should try playing soccer.
-Sorry.
-We're on the same team.
What if they split up
shortly after becoming partners?
What am I looking at here?
"Yuk Junghwan,
national badminton tournament"?
Can you send two of our teams
to the competition?
Taejun, do you know what happens
when it rains in the desert?
Flowers bloom. Amazing ones.
You're like the desert.
It just hasn't rained yet.
GOING TO YOU AT A SPEED OF 493KM
Translated by Sae-byul Chun