Have you ever heard about that
the cliff of a snow mountain
once fascinated numerous people?
Legend has it that,
there were treasures at the peak
but also there was a bottomless chasm hidden over there.
The smart, the fool
and the kind people,
all are familiar to you.
On the mountainside, on the cliff,
on the cloud,
and in the human world,
snowflakes are drifting profusely and disorderly.
Joy of Life Season 1
Episode 18
But I'm willing to marry him.
You're deceived by
the sweet words of that brat.
He really has a glib tongue
and doesn't behave seriously sometimes,
but the expression in his eyes is really pure.
Second brother,
I don't know what has happened
between you two,
but he is definitely not a flibbertigibbet.
What kind of man he is
doesn't matter now.
Maybe he is a good man,
or maybe as you say,
he is sincere.
But he isn't supposed to come to the capital city.
Many people have been staring at him.
What do you mean?
Wan'er, our family owes you a lot.
Sometimes,
I don't really know
how I can make it up to you.
Second brother, you've always been kind to me.
I know that in my heart.
Dad seldom comes to see you
for the sake of the overall situation and our family.
I understand.
But sometimes I couldn't help wondering.
If we can't protect our family members,
what's the meaning of maintaining the glory of our family?
I don't allow you to marry him
for fear that he might get you into trouble.
I just want to protect you.
I'll leave this to you.
Don't let him see you ever again.
Brother.
Lin Gong is the one who wants to kill me.
The Second Young Master? Why?
Is he a follower of the Crown Prince,
or is it about the financial power of the Neiku?
Nobody has ever asked me!
Nobody! Never!
They just want the financial power of the Neiku, right?
I'll give it to them.
I never want it myself.
They can just ask,
but they actually chose to kill people!
Why did you
make a fuss
at the imperial residence just now?
I broke into the imperial residence
to offer him a chance to kill me.
I've noticed that his subordinates
are all martial arts masters of and above the Seventh Dan.
They are strong enough
to capture Cheng Jushu.
Later, I visited Ye Ling'er.
From her,
I confirmed that Lin Gong is the real killer.
So Lin Gong follows the Crown Prince?
Now, I have no evidence to prove that
the Crown Prince is involved.
So for now,
Lin Gong is my only revenge target.
When will you take a move?
Quick-tempered as I am, I can hardly wait.
I'll kill him tonight.
Didn't you just say that
he's surrounded by martial arts masters?
I still have to go!
Only to avenge Teng Zijing's death?
I do it for Teng Zijing,
but not only
for him.
Who else?
Ruoruo, look!
Most people in the world
are ordinary, just like them.
But there're always some theories,
some big potatoes
that regard them as insignificant.
He's dead, but he's just a guard.
I've heard that so many times.
Ruoruo, I enjoy crowds.
I think that without the ordinary people,
Nanqing won't exist.
Nor will the world.
Pick me something fat.
Look at this. And this.
I made it! I made it!
So I want to fight
with the hows and whys in the world
and tell those big potatoes that
ordinary people are important.
Brother,
you only think about them.
Why don't you think about yourself?
About what?
Lin Gong is the elder brother of Lin Wan'er,
just like us.
If someday,
Lin Wan'er kills me,
will you still marry her?
I know you want to revenge.
You refuse to accept what has happened.
I understand it all, so I won't stop you.
But you must understand that
if you kill Lin Gong yourself,
there will be no future
for Wan'er and you.
Then shall I give up
and let Teng Zijing die in vain?
I don't know, either.
But you can't have both.
I know it's hard.
But brother,
you must make the choice yourself.
Ruoruo, please go back first.
I want to be alone.
Did your second brother really
try to kill Fan Xian
this afternoon?
He hates Fan Xian so much that
he can't be persuaded.
He values you deeply.
But he saw Fan Xian sneaking into your room
without considering your reputation.
It's understandable that
he went mad.
But I just feel that
something has happened
between Fan Xian and him.
If there are
some insoluble contradictions
between your family member
and the man you love.
Who will you choose?
I...
I don't know.
As an illegitimate daughter,
I should avoid seeing my father and mother,
nor should I expect any family affection.
But in these years,
my second brother Lin Gong is
the only one who treats me nicely.
Whenever he saw
something fresh and interesting,
he would bring it to me,
for fear that I might feel bored
in the room.
He makes me feel warm.
He's really kind to me.
But as to Fan Xian,
I originally thought
I would marry someone I don't love,
and we would respect each other like guests.
But unexpectedly,
I actually met him
by fate.
In my heart,
he's the right man for me.
So emotionally,
I will take no side.
If one of them
really made a mistake...
Who will you choose?
I only hope that
there is justice in the world.
Brother,
I know you want to revenge.
You refuse to accept what has happened.
I understand it all, so I won't stop you.
But you must understand that
if you kill Lin Gong yourself,
there will be no future
for Wan'er and you.
=Wuzhu, servant of Fan Xian's late mother=
Uncle Wuzhu.
Go back.
Lin Gong planned the assassination on the Niulan Street.
Teng Zijing died a grim death because of me.
I know.
I want to kill him.
You're hesitant.
I'm not.
I'm the one that he wants to kill!
Teng Zijing died for me!
I have to kill him.
You're utterly confused!
If you go now, you'll get yourself killed.
Uncle, step aside.
Go back.
So do you also think that
Teng Zijing's death
means nothing?
Yes.
Then so be it!
You've made some progress,
but you still lack patience.
Uncle Wuzhu?
Brother, what's up?
Where's Uncle Wuzhu?
Uncle Wuzhu?
The man who helped you in Danzhou?
I haven't seen him.
Why am I home?
What's the matter?
Brother, where are you going?
To kill Lin Gong.
He's left.
This morning,
Lin Gong left the city in a hurry.
How do you know that?
Ye Ling'er from the Ye mansion came to see you.
She brought the news.
Where does Lin Gong go?
She didn't mention that.
Kill him.
No one can see my face.
What are you doing?
Wait! My sheep!
Has Lin Gong left?
Yes.
He left the city with many guards.
Do you know where he is heading for?
I don't know.
But I know that
he visited the Crown Prince before leaving.
Then he went back to the Lin mansion.
After a few minutes,
he got on a carriage and left in a hurry.
So the Crown Prince
is also involved.
How do you know it so clearly?
I visited Wan'er
and talked with her yesterday.
What did you tell her?
Don't worry.
I said nothing
about Lin Gong.
I just come around myself.
Will you inform the Investigator's Office of
his collusion with the enemies
and testify against him?
No way!
The Crown Prince is involved after all,
I can't drag my family into this.
Then there's no way out.
Si Lili's testimony alone
won't be able to prove Lin Gong guilty.
Though I can't
put my family at risk,
I won't just
watch Beiqi harm Nanqing
and do nothing.
Since you can catch Si Lili,
you must be able to
find Lin Gong.
I hope you can find him back
and figure out the whole thing.
If he really colluded with the
enemies and betrayed our country,
His Majesty will punish him.
Thanks for your information.
But he's gone already. How can we catch him?
I know a guy
who's good at hunting people.
This yard is secluded.
Let's sleep here tonight.
Tomorrow, we'll find a boat and go south.
Yes.
Second Young Master,
where are we going
exactly?
Nowhere specific.
After all, I only have to hide for now.
Second Young Master,
what do you have to hide from
in the capital city?
We must start from the Prime Minister's mansion.
The impresses of carriages are different.
Only by searching from the start
can we find a trace.
I've been thinking recently.
You might have flaws,
but capable as you are,
how come you're just a clerk?
I just seek ease and comfort.
Then you should never follow me.
In these days,
what I did
is extremely dangerous.
Your Excellency, you're generous after all.
Don't mention the money.
It's only an excuse.
We both know that
you follow me for some other reasons.
The Prime Minister's mansion is right ahead.
I won't ask if you don't want to say.
I've met you.
You're the subordinate of Chengze.
Distinguished as His Highness is,
how dare you call him like that!
I won't next time. See you.
His Highness wants to see you.
I have something urgent to deal with.
I'll ask for his forgiveness in person some other day.
His Highness is nearby.
After sitting on the carriage for so long,
it feels good to walk around.
By the way,
I'll think about our route to the south.
Since we're leaving the capital city,
we can visit some people.
Second Young Master,
a blind man at the door wants to see you.
A blind man?
Can he practice martial arts?
He doesn't have any vitality qi.
Let him in.
Everyone, watch out! Prepare to attack at any time!
Go by yourself.
Your Excellency, please go ahead.
Though I've read the Red Mansions for several times,
I'm still fond of reading it.
Have you read it?
Why are you reading here?
Cross ventilation
makes it shady and cool here.
It's really a good place for reading at noon.
The beauty of the capital city
lies not in various mansions,
but in streets and alleys.
It does have a distinctive flavor.
Your Highness, do you think I'm silly?
Why do you say so?
Your Highness, you find a place
to enjoy the cool and read the book when you're free.
And I happen to be around.
How silly am I
to believe this crap?
You're right.
I'm actually waiting for you.
Are you looking for Lin Gong?
How do you know?
This morning,
Lin Gong and the Crown Prince met at the Eastern Palace
and had a quarrel.
Your name was heard vaguely
outside the study.
Then Lin Gong left the capital in a hurry.
So I wait for you near the Prime Minister's mansion.
And you really show up.
Your Highness, how can you know
what happened in the Eastern Palace?
I sure have spies there.
Is it appropriate to tell me that?
It doesn't matter.
It's not a secret.
I've also got spies from the Crown Prince around me.
How loving and touching
you are!
No one but you
has ever talked to me like that.
Your Highness, are you waiting for me here
to tell me that?
I'm asking you,
are you looking for Lin Gong?
Yes.
I won't ask you why.
I only ask you,
will there be a fight?
Yes.
This morning, Lin Gong left
with many guards.
They are all martial arts masters.
Do you know that?
I know. They are masters of or above the Seventh Dan.
Can you defeat them?
Not really.
Xie Bi'an is known as
"Faster than Light."
He is the best swordsman
in the capital city.
Faster than light?
Fast sword.
('fast sword' is a homophone for 'express' in Chinese)
I know S.F. Express for being fast.
You actually
understand swordsmanship!
To attack fast,
besides a flexible figure,
you must borrow the power of nature.
Attacking with the wind will sure make a difference.
('with the wind' is a homophone for 'S.F. Express' in Chinese)
Unbelievable!
With Xie Bi'an by your side,
you might stand a chance.
Your Highness, why do you help me?
I appreciate your talents.
Also, if you marry Wan'er,
you'll take over the Neiku.
I'm friendly with you
for the sake of the properties.
I really appreciate
your frankness.
But this time,
no need to bother Mr. Xie.
Then be careful yourself.
Your Highness, aren't you angry?
It's perfectly justifiable to choose the Crown Prince.
It makes sense that you don't choose me.
Why should I be angry?
Compared to the Crown Prince,
I think Your Highness stand a better chance.
If you have time, we can meet more often.
We won't talk about national affairs, but romance.
Who are you?
How do you find me?
Lin Gong.
How dare you!
How can you call the Second Young Master
by his name?
Everything is related.
You want to kill Fan Xian, so I will kill you.
Kill him!
Second Young Master,
shall we ask who sent him?
After killing him,
the man behind him is sure to show up.
Bury him.
Actually, I only want to kill you.
Kill him!
I'm the son of the Prime Minster
and the follower of the Crown Prince.
Whatever you want,
I can give it to you.
A martial arts master as you are,
I can promise you a bright future.
No matter what...
Your Excellency,
the Second Prince really thinks highly of you.
Indeed.
Are you unwilling
to follow him?
I've been to that alley when I was free.
There were many street vendors
and fried cake stands on the road.
Today, they are all driven away
simply because he wants to enjoy the cool.
One day without income.
What's wrong with that?
If people are born with nobleness and lowliness,
there's nothing wrong.
Forget it.
The Lin mansion is right ahead.
Are you confident in finding Lin Gong?
They just left today, so the impressions are new.
Finding Lin Gong
is as easy as winking.
Your Excellency, come with me.
The road is actually covered with flagstones!
What's wrong with that?
Then there wouldn't be any impressions.
Your Excellency,
there's still another way.
Ling Gong left with many subordinates.
Someone must have seen them.
Let's inquire about them
along the road.
We might get some information.
There's no time.
We've wasted so much time,
I'm afraid Lin Gong
might have gone away.
=Lin Gong and his guards have been
killed at the suburb of the capital city.=
Your Excellency, where are we going?
We're leaving the city.
Find him.
He's dead.
Your Excellency, he's dead.
Here he is!
It's really Lin Gong.
How do you get the information?
It just appeared on my desk
out of nowhere.
I followed the lead
and found him there.
Have you got anything from the handwriting?
The handwriting is too neat. It's hard to find any clue.
I just don't get it.
Lin Gong was killed.
Why did the killer give us the address
to collect the body?
Judged from Lin Gong's wounds,
they might be caused by sword.
Then let's investigate
the swordsmen who have been in and out of
the capital city in recent days.
The killer is highly skilled.
Only one man is so good at sword
both in and out of the capital city.
Who is that?
Xie Bi'an,
the follower of the Second Prince.
Lin Gong is the follower of the Crown Prince.
Let's submit a secret memorial to the imperial palace,
and let His Majesty make the call.
It's the only way.
The capital city will soon descend into chaos.
Are you hungry?
I've asked the kitchen cook
to make the pastries for you.
Take it as the midnight snack.
You have something for me.
No.
Brother, don't get me wrong.
I haven't seen you
for days.
I really miss you.
You usually call me by my name.
Brother, here is the thing.
I've find a place for our shop.
We'll employ servants
from our mansion.
So we can open the shop
in just a few days.
You still remember it?
Of course, I do.
It will make a huge profit.
How can I forget?
Brother,
are you still writing the Red Mansions?
How should we
name the shop?
Why do you look at me like that?
Did I say anything wrong?
Uncle...
Right! The book.
('book' is a homophone for 'uncle' in Chinese)
Just keep writing.
Don't...
He's fine. He just passed out.
Tell me!
After knocking me out last night,
where did you go?
Do you know that
he might have ran away
during that moment?
I killed Lin Gong.
I followed him out of the city
and killed him.
If you want to kill him,
then why did you stop me last night?
Because you were hesitant.
You were utterly confused.
Who gave you the right to kill him?
Your mom did.
If you can't make the call,
I'll make it for you.
You always say so.
You were hesitant to kill him,
so I would kill him for you.
-You always say that! -Whoever wants to kill you,
I'll kill him.
You always say that!
Then where were you
when I was assassinated
on the Niulan Street?
Where were you
when someone tried to kill me?
I was not in the capital city
when the assassination took place.
I'm sorry.
It won't happen again.
Sir! Sir!
Please show mercy!
Thank you! Thank you!
You're not in the capital city recently.
Where have you been?
I went to the Jiangnan area.
Why did you go there?
Do you still have your mom's box?
I want to open the box
left by your mom,
but I can't remember the past clearly.
I only remember that the key should be in the capital city,
but I can't remember the exact place.
If the key is in the capital city,
why did you go to the Jiangnan area?
I remember vaguely that
your mom and I talked about the box
in the Jiangnan area.
So I revisited the places
to see
whether I can remember something or not.
Have you got any clue?
Yes.
Now I've confirmed that
the key to the box
might be kept in two places.
It might be kept in the palace.
The imperial palace?
Right.
We can search for it if we have time.
Uncle,
the imperial palace is filled with martial arts masters.
And you said yourself that
one of the Four Great Masters
might be there.
If we don't know
who he really is,
it might be dangerous.
If he's really in the imperial palace,
he might be that old eunuch
surnamed Hong.
Hong Sixiang?
Can we sneak into the imperial palace
without being noticed by him?
Probably not. We have to break in.
Then tell me
the other place.
The key
might be kept
where your mom once lived.
Does it have a name?
Taiping Residence.
Where is it?
Somewhere near the capital city.
What's the exact location?
I can't remember.
Help me find it.
OK.
I have to ask my father.
Don't let Fan Jian know I'm back.
OK.
That's all for now.
Find the Taiping Residence as soon as possible.
I'll stay in the capital city these days.
Where are you staying?
Uncle?
Uncle,
next time you leave,
just let me know.
Fine.
Sister.
Why did I sleep on the floor
of your room
last night?
I don't know.
Do you know
I came to see you last night?
I don't remember.
Is our mansion haunted?
Come to my study.
Who?
Me.
I also finished eating.
Mom,
since Fan Xian
came to our mansion,
Dad seldom
finds fault with me.
He has nothing to say to you.
It's not a good thing.
Mom,
this is not what we should
be worried about now.
What we should be worried about the most
is that our mansion is haunted.
Oh my God!
How come I have such a son?!
Brother.
Lin Gong is dead.
How did you do it?
I didn't.
Whatever,
just handle it cautiously.
Lin Gong is dead.
Really?
It was discovered by the Investigator's Office.
He died in a desolated yard
in the suburb yesterday.
The killer might be a sword master.
How could it happen?!
Have they found the killer?
Is Wuzhu back?
I haven't seen him for a long time.
Is Uncle Wuzhu involved?
I'm just asking.
You can leave.
Do you know Taiping Residence?
Why do you ask?
I heard that
my mom used to live there.
Yes.
I want to visit her past residence
to mourn for her.
You can't go there.
Why?
I told you that
your mom's identity
must remain a secret.
I will keep a distance.
No way.
You'll have to wait
till you inherit the Neiku.
Father.
Say no more.
Then I'll see myself out.
Brother.
Brother. Brother. Brother.
Have you thought of a name?
What name?
A name for our business.
For our bookstore?
Let's call it Danbo Bookstore.
Danbo?
There's an allusion to it.
Only by remaining indifferent to fame
and fortune can one show his high ideals.
Fine. Fine. Fine.
It doesn't matter.
Illusion or not, that's not important.
The most urgent task for you
is to write your book.
When our bookstore opens,
its future and prospect
all counts on you.
Don't engage yourself in all the social activities.
Young Master Fan Xian,
the Crown Prince has the door blocked
and orders to see you in the Eastern Palace.
The Crown Prince?
Young Master Fan Xian,
the sedan of the Prime Minister's mansion
has arrived at the door.
The Prime Minister wants to see you.
Lin Ruofu?
Can they just let him write his book?
Get lost!
Just leave us.
Yes.
It must be for Lin Gong's death.
I have nothing to do with that.
Why do they want to see me?
I'm afraid
you'll figure that out after seeing them.
Then who should I see first?
Prime Minister Lin Ruofu
and the Crown Prince are not on the same side.
Whoever you choose to see first,
you'll offend the other one.
Young Master Fan Xian,
the imperial guards are here.
His Majesty ordered to see you
through a verbal instruction.
Now you don't have to choose.
In the river of history,
time goes round and round.
Memories about the former and present lives
join each other in an endless way.
In the long drunken Milky Way,
one season follows another in a flash,
and the wild geese are flying south.
I just can't give up
to be with you for my whole life.
I have been hovering in the dreams
for hundreds and thousands of times.
I can't even say a word when I watch the flowers falling.
Year after year in the wandering,
I count the remaining years.
Even though we can't meet each other anymore,
even though we have ended up the destiny,
I never feel regretful.
In such a chaotic world,
I still miss you as ever.
I can't fall asleep under the moon.
With a gentle heart,
I cherish our remaining years.
Even though we have to go through
all the hardships along the journey,
you always stay by my side,
watching the falling flowers, speechlessly.
Year after year in the wandering,
I count the remaining years.
Even though we can't meet each other anymore,
even though we end up the destiny,
I never feel regretful.
In such a chaotic world,
I still miss you as ever.
I can't fall asleep under the moon.
With a gentle heart,
I cherish our remaining years.
Even though we have to go through
all the hardships along the journey,
you always stay by my side...