Have you ever heard about that
the cliff of a snow mountain
once fascinated numerous people?
Legend has it that,
there were treasures at the peak
but also there was a bottomless chasm hidden over there.
The smart, the fool
and the kind people,
all are familiar to you.
On the mountainside, on the cliff,
on the cloud,
and in the human world,
snowflakes are drifting profusely and disorderly.
Joy of Life Season 1
Episode 16
Who is the lady?
She checked in this afternoon as well!
She insisted on checking out
the quality of the food here
before she decided whether to eat here or not.
So I brought your food box
to her to have a look.
I did nothing else.
Why did you pick ours in particular?
Because you live close!
Just the opposite side.
He is alive again!
Your Excellency,
there is no trace left at all.
I just asked the waiter.
The lady has gone.
Is she Si Lili?
Not sure!
It is she without doubt.
What's your source of judgement?
The smell of the Chenguang.
What is that?
A type of incense
that has been used by the Joy Tsin House all the time.
Its smell is enduring
and doesn't fade easily. Have a try!
How do you know that?
It's a technique of hunting
to make judgement according to the fragrance.
That's the basic of hunting.
I mean how do you know
what type of incense the Joy Tsin House uses.
Frankly speaking,
I have also been
to the Joy Tsin House.
But only to enjoy the singing.
Nothing else.
Are you able to hold it?
It's just too expensive there.
I can't afford it,
nor do I have the guts.
Your Excellency,
it must be held back
from my wife,
or my life will be...
Fine!
Since the incense smell is confirmed,
it should be Si Lili.
Let's hunt her down tonight.
Maybe, we'll get something.
Clean your face immediately.
We're doing it now.
That lady rode her own horse
towards the Pijia Hill.
There are two ways
to the Danzhou Harbor.
One is the Pijia Hill.
Second is the Chaomeng River.
How do you know where she went?
She inquired about the way.
I persuaded her not to travel in the evening
as the Pijia Hill
is swarmed with robbers,
but she just didn't listen.
Thank you!
Let's go!
Sure!
Hold on please!
Soybean, alfalfa, and eggs.
Your Excellency,
what her horse took
was premium forage.
It is all plains and hills
in the Pijia Hill region.
That's very convenient for horses to travel.
If we are to catch up with her,
we'd better take horses as well.
What's up?
There is fresh horse waste there.
Well, Your Excellency,
this is the premium forage from the inn.
We're on the right track.
Si Lili should be ahead of us.
Wait a minute!
What's up, Your Excellency?
It makes me feel so awkward
when I saw you
eating it just now.
Your Excellency,
I didn't eat it.
Don't you think it's too smooth?
What is too smooth?
The finding of poison, the finding of Si Lili,
and the tracing of her marks.
Everything happens one after another so smoothly.
Isn't that good?
She detected us first,
right?
Yeah!
So she poisoned us.
Why did she
poison us?
She...
Because we're chasing her!
Then why would she leave in advance
before we got poisoned?
It must be her cautiousness in action.
I poisoned Si Lili
the first time I saw her.
Is that your foible?
My point is
she knew I'm proficient at pharmacology.
But the poison that she applied
is too mediocre.
Perhaps
she doesn't have any better poison.
If I were she,
I might as well sneak off than using poison.
And
she told her way of escaping
to the waiter.
Isn't that
a bit intentional?
Your Excellency mean
she did it deliberately to create confusion?
Is it possible that
she went to the Pijia Hill
while diverting us to the Chaomeng River?
No, Your Excellency!
I've checked all the forks
on the road.
There is no human trace
to the direction of the Chaomeng River.
And on our way here,
the horse footprints
have been evading from the low-lying muddy grounds.
Evidently,
the horse is manipulated by someone.
I always have the feeling that
she is waiting for our catch-up.
Your Excellency, you are thinking too much.
She is simply too panicked to select her way
which gives her away.
How long will it take before we catch up with her?
Her horse is very tired now.
Tomorrow morning!
We can catch up with her
by tomorrow morning for sure.
Let's continue!
We'll see when we catch her.
Yes, Your Excellency!
Si Lili!
There you are finally.
I've been looking forward to this moment for a long time.
You are a Beiqi agent?
Yes!
Did you try to assassin me at Niulan Street?
I like you so much.
Why would I kill you?
Let's take our time to discuss it
after we get back to the capital city.
Mr. Fan,
could you let me go?
No!
I was quite scared
to see you in the inn in town.
I was quite careful with my escape,
but you caught up with me any way.
Your technique of hunting
is really spectacular.
Thanks to Wang!
You're welcome, Your Excellency!
I've long heard that
Miss Lili is elegant and refined.
You're indeed stunning
when seeing in person.
Do you know why I led you here
with the poison?
So it is really intentional.
Because I was worried
no matter how much I ran,
I wouldn't escape.
So you allow yourself
to be seized without any resistance?
If that's the case,
I should give up in the inn.
Why would I run for one extra night?
Robbers?
What robbers?
You're indeed smart!
The robbers that hold this place
are also Beiqi agents.
We had the appointment to meet here from the start.
We found only you and Wang Qinian
in the inn.
So, we'd just make full use of the chance
to set up an ambush.
Take care!
Allow me to leave.
Your Excellency!
This is it!
It is a bit longer!
Make do with it.
They are all above Sixth Dan.
It's better for us to find a chance
and submerge into the ground.
Your Excellency,
it's too early
to kneel down for mercy now!
It's shaking!
What is shaking?
The stones.
Your Excellency, this is not the right time
to bend down and watch the stones.
Your Excellency!
Black knights!
The black knights showed up in the east?
We just got the message.
Isn't the Head back to his hometown?
How come he deployed the black knights?
Get it investigated.
Yes!
The First Division's role
is to manage the affairs in the capital city.
You don't need to
care so much about the affairs out of it.
Don't you want to know
why the black knights
were deployed suddenly?
The black knights are a very strong force
governed by the Head directly.
We have no right
to investigate their whereabouts.
But the Head has gone back to his hometown.
Why were the black knights
deployed all of a sudden?
It has nothing to do
with you or me.
Yan Ruohai,
do you know anything secret?
The strongest force
in the Investigator's Office
are the black knights
governed by the Head directly.
It's the strongest cavalry
approved by His Majesty
to protect the Head.
Isn't the Head back to his hometown?
How come the black knights are here?
The black knights' showing up
means the Head is not far either.
I can't wait to see
what kind of a person he is
who controls the terrible giant
and beast-like Investigator's Office
The Head hasn't come.
Master Shadow!
The Head knows all about what happened in the capital city.
=Shadow, Director of the Sixth Division=
=Shadow, Director of the Sixth Division
of the Nanqing Investigator's Office=
=Shadow, Director of the Sixth Division=
He has a message for you.
Me?
He wants you to act with a free hand.
Even if the sky falls down,
he will push it back.
The Head knows me?
That's all the words he wants to deliver.
When will the Head come back to the capital city?
He will be back
when you need him the most.
In spite that the Sixth Division of
the Investigator's Office takes charge of assassination,
the most terrible assassin
publicly known to everyone
is Master Shadow.
He follows the Head all the year round.
But no one ever knows
what he looks like,
neither does anyone
know his name.
That is to say,
he could be anyone
around us.
Yes!
A sweeping force of cavalries
turns all the tricks
into a joke.
That's the strong in real sense.
Who are you?
Why does Chen Pingping
send the black knights for you?
You may not believe it that
it's the first time for me to hear this name.
Chen Pingping is the name of the Head!
It's a taboo to address him by his name directly.
Which Ping is it?
The one in Fuping (duckweeds).
Sounds a bit delicate.
Didn't you say we shouldn't address him by his name?
No, don't do that!
This name used to sweep cross the world
and it is a nightmare to all Kingdoms.
Chen Pingping from the Investigator's Office
is publicly known as King of Nights
and the source of all sins.
Let's discuss it on our way back.
Your Excellency,
we must be careful
on the way back.
What do you mean?
The Niulan Street assassination
involves masters
from both Beiqi and Dongyi Town
and also the archer of the Capital Garrison.
These cannot be manipulated
by an agent.
I'm afraid
there is a big figure behind it.
So?
It's quite complicated
and we'd better stay covert
on the way.
Don't let anyone know
we have captured her.
Are you worried that she'll be killed
half way to keep her mouth shut?
Anything can happen
before we get back.
Black knights sweeping through
is a scene
which can't be hidden.
I'm afraid we'll have to
act the other way around.
The other way around?
What do you mean?
Fan Xian from Danzhou travelled a long way
to capture Si Lili, the Beiqi agent,
and escort her back to the capital city.
It seems Si Lili
has committed something serious.
It's surprising that she is an agent.
Fan Xian's got a great formation.
Seizure of the Beiqi agent
is something that can be done but cannot be disclosed.
Straightforward as he is,
he is also clever.
The more people know about it,
the safer their way of return will be.
Whoever tries to do something bad to them
reveals the guilt from the heart.
It is so according to logical thinking.
Is there any other possibility?
This is no longer a concern
if one is crazy.
Auntie, what are you laughing at?
My future son-in-law
is indeed funny.
Si Lili is a potato
too hot to hold now.
It's plausibly wise
to return on a large scale.
Shall we just kill him?
Kill him?
He will reach the capital city tomorrow
with his current speed.
If we send killers
to kill him outside of the capital city,
Wan'er doesn't need to marry him.
The power of Neiku doesn't need to be handed over either.
What a perfect chance!
Si Lili is very suspicious
to be Beiqi agent.
If we take action now,
it's very likely that we'll be convicted
of killing to keep her mouth shut.
Isn't that more interesting?
Auntie,
this is really not the right time to kill him.
Seriously?
If you do that,
I'll be in grave danger.
You see?
I'm just having a joke with him.
He takes it too seriously.
Wait!
Your Excellency!
This is the third bunch of people
in such a short while.
Let's take a guess
whose side they are from.
From the Capital Garrison.
They want to take her away as well?
Yeah!
I have turned them down
in the name of the Investigator's Office.
The Capital Garrison,
the Prefecture of Capital City,
and the Ministry of Penalty
all want you.
You are after all
a live Beiqi agent.
Once they get
any new intelligence from you,
it will be a great achievement.
You know it very well that
no matter to which side I hand you over,
what awaits you ahead
is endless excruciation.
Dying will be luxurious
by then.
Your heartbeat is faster. Are you nervous?
Who is the head of conspiracy
for the Niulan Street assassination?
Why does it have to have a head?
Why can't I be the person
to have planned it all?
You don't have the motive to kill me.
Do you really think
I'm so deeply into you,
Mr. Fan?
You're a Beiqi agent
who has been lurking in the capital city for so many years.
No one knows
how much efforts you've made
to become the courtesan in the Joy Tsin House.
The people you're in touch with
are all high officials and celebrities.
It's the prime time
to collect intelligence.
Your exposure of identity now
will ruin all your previous efforts.
It'll make sense
if it's the Crown Prince, His Majesty,
or the Prime Minister that you're trying to kill
after all these efforts.
It is otherwise
if your target is me.
What fantastic reasoning!
Is that a confirmation
that someone else is behind it?
Why don't you figure it out yourself
since you're so smart?
Who is it?
Why don't you just tell me
and I'll save your life?
As you said
just now,
every ministry wants to interrogate me.
How do you save me from that?
You'll hand me over anyway
after we arrive at the capital city tomorrow.
It makes no difference
to say it or not to say it.
You're the prisoner of the Investigator's Office.
I don't need to hand you over.
Should you be really important
in the Investigator's Office,
how come you chase me
without any retinues?
That's non-sense. I am his retinue.
Have some water please, Your Excellency!
Keeping it a secret,
I may still get rescued by that person.
If I really speak it out,
I'll end up on the chopping block.
Saving you now is too difficult.
I would kill you to keep
your mouth shut if I were that big figure.
As you said yourself,
what awaits me ahead
is endless excruciation.
Getting killed
is no less of an extrication.
How about
you telling me the name secretly
and then I set you free secretly?
Are you serious?
Right now,
the eyes of every ministry are cast on me.
You dare to set me free now?
Your Excellency,
we'd better go back to watch over her.
No need.
I'm afraid this yard
should have been encircled
by all the scouts from different ministries.
She can't escape.
If we had known that earlier,
we could have taken our time
for the return trip.
Black knights' showing up
means the Head
already knows about it.
If we don't return immediately,
it's very suspicious that we're colluding with the enemies.
That's dangerous to the family.
You're right!
But Master Shadow said
you can do whatever you think necessary
and the Head will help you
if anything goes wrong.
Chen Pingping and I are neither families nor friends.
Why would he help me?
Your Excellency still don't trust him.
Human mind is changeable.
I can't trust him
before I meet him in person.
Your Excellency,
before handing over Si Lili,
you still have another option.
Do you mean to lynch?
Yeah!
Now Si Lili is under your control.
If you lynch her,
she probably will tell the truth
after one night's of torture.
It's very easy
to torture a weak lady.
But if we have no bottom-line,
are we any different from animals?
You're right, Your Excellency!
So,
we'll have to wait
for other chances
after we get back to the capital city.
Wang Qinian!
If I chose to lynch
just now,
will you leave me?
If Your Excellency has no bottom-line,
then my monthly payment
of 150 taels of silvers
will not be guaranteed.
50 taels! 50 taels!
Don't worry, Your Excellency!
As long as you keep paying me 50 taels of silver,
I will always follow you
and serve you.
They are all
so eager!
It is a big case after all.
If you don't have the support
from the Investigator's Office,
we may not be able to hold her.
Si Lili is the prisoner of the Investigator's Office.
Your Excellencies,
please make way for us!
Mr. Fan,
we have no objection
if the Investigator's Office
really wants the prisoner.
Please show us the arrest warrant
of the Investigator's Office.
We'll make it up later on.
I'm afraid that's a breach of the rule.
Here comes the arrest warrant!
The Investigator's Office
is directly affiliated with His Majesty.
It has the right to fetch anyone for interrogation
for all matters in and out of the capital city.
Here is the arrest warrant!
If you don't have His Majesty's sacred edict,
=Yan Ruohai, Director of the Fourth Division=
=Yan Ruohai, Director of the Fourth Division
of Nanqing Investigator's Office=
I'll take her away.
Whoever disagrees can come and have a try.
Follow me!
Sister!
Fan Xian is back!
How do you know?
The whole city has seen him.
Did he make it?
Fan Xian escort Si Lili
back to the capital city.
There are a lot of people at the city gate,
seemingly to take Si Lili away.
Thanks to the showing up
of Yan Ruohai,
Director of the Fourth Division of the Investigator's Office.
He held a paper
and helped them inside.
He really seized her?
Sister,
you don't look happy about it.
It is not necessarily a good thing.
Why do you think so?
Where are you going, sister?
Why are you still following me?
Your Excellency,
Si Lili's case
is connected with the Niulan Street assassination.
Can I take charge of the trial?
Do you think I'll hand her over to you
now that I've come in person?
Your Excellency!
Agents and military organizations
are in the domain of the Fourth Division.
You're off the case.
She was captured by me.
You have all the credit to the capture.
Let that write off
Wang Qinian's stealing of the file.
The assassination is after all related to me.
Then you surely need to stay out to avoid suspicion.
Go back!
Or you want a fight with me?
Mr. Fan, aren't you gonna save me?
Where are your actions?
Your Excellency!
Your Highness!
Fan Ruoruo, the daughter of Assistant
Minister of Ministry of Revenue Fan Jian,
wants to see you.
How come she comes to me?
I asked her the reason.
She doesn't want to tell me.
What the procedures they are!
Let her in.
Yes!
Your Excellency!
She is gone!
What's the point of keeping that?
Dismantle it and get it disposed!
Don't be mad, Your Excellency!
After all, Yan Bingyun, his son,
went to Beiqi
because of you.
Naturally, he's a bit apathetic to you
which makes sense.
You're hungry, aren't you?
What did you say?
We've been rushing for so many days.
Shall I treat you with a good meal?
No, that's not needed.
I have to
go home
and let my wife know I'm back safe and sound.
And, I miss my daughter now.
Right!
Come to me after you're done!
As you're in my team,
we need to report to the mansion together.
Yes, Your Excellency!
So, you're alright?
Of course!
Remember to come to my mansion.
It's wide spread that
Fan Ruoruo is the first talented girl in the capital city.
Lady Ruoruo, have you heard it?
I'm too humble to deserve praises like this.
Why do you come here?
Your Highness, please ask the guards to leave us alone.
You can talk now.
I believe Your Highness already know
Si Lili is escorted back to the capital city.
Fan Xian is really knowledgeable.
Firstly, he shocked the crowd with a poem.
Then he killed an Eighth Dan
Martial Arts Master on the street.
Now he captured the Beiqi agent
with his own hands.
He's impressive.
Acting too wild is easy to cause trouble.
I'm willing to monitor my brother's behaviors
for Your Highness.
If he acts too exceptionally,
I'd report to you in private.
I heard that
you have a really deep tie with Fan Xian
as brother and sister.
That's why I need to protect his life.
You think I'm going to kill him?
That's not important.
My brother is arrogant and doesn't refrain himself
from all the disrespect to you.
Sooner or later,
the whole family will get involved in his convictions.
I do so
for the good of the Fan mansion.
Interesting!
My Lady!
-My Lady! -What happened?
He... He... He...
Calm down!
Isn't he the miracle-working doctor?
He is the miracle-working doctor and also Fan Xian.
I need to talk to him.
Leave us and close the door!
Leave!
Why do you come in day time?
I just got back and I want to meet you.
It's said you captured Si Lili.
Are you hurt?
Safe and sound!
I can't get hurt
with my proficiency at martial art.
Where is she?
As soon as I went through the gate,
both the Ministry of Personnel
and the Ministry of Penalty came to take her over.
She was eventually taken away by the Investigator's Office.
Alright! Let's not talk about these.
Is that edible?
I feel hungry now.
That's my leftover.
I don't mind!
You won't give up like this.
You can't let go of Teng Zijing's death.
Don't talk!
I just want to sit beside you quietly
like this for a while.
I always wondered
if I hadn't gone to the Qing Temple that day,
I would not have met you
holding a drumstick.
Time flows like a river. Lives are like fishes in it.
They meet in undercurrent and rapid torrent.
We're destined to meet.
Even if we hadn't met on that day,
we'd meet elsewhere.
We're destined to meet?
Perhaps!
I feel so much settled
after hearing your words.
You can turn to Ye Ling'er!
Ye Ling'er? What do I turn to her for?
She's been to the Joy Tsin House.
Why would she go there?
When she knew
you are Fan Xian on that day,
she insisted in visiting the Joy Tsin House
to check out if there is anything
between you and Si Lili.
After that,
the news became wide spread
that she fell into the water and got saved.
She never came to meet me
ever since then.
I think
she could have seen something on that day.
What a coincidence, Mr. Lin.
I'm diagnosing for her.
Brother!
Why are you mad?
You, a bastard from Danzhou!
How dare you step into my sister's room?
How do you know I'm Fan Xian?
I must kill you with my sword today.
Take out your sword then.
Brother, we didn't do anything shameful.
If anyone knows about this,
your reputation will be ruined.
But we have marriage contract.
You can't marry this guy.
Why do you hate Fan Xian
so much?
It is treacherous of him
to disguise himself as doctor to meet you.
If he really cares about you,
he should think
for your reputation.
How could he do something like this?
He's such a villain and not good at all.
He is not that type of person.
It's just that
his idea
differs from what people usually think.
You're too naive.
I'm a man as well.
You may be cheated by him, but I won't.
From today on,
I'll send the guards here.
If Fan Xian dares to come again,
I'll kill him without mercy.
That's going too far.
Aren't you gonna ask me?
Ask you what?
Who wanted to kill Fan Xian.
I'm not the interrogator.
Who is it then?
Chen Pingping is not here.
Is it Zhu Ge from the First Division?
I'm waiting.
For what?
For the interrogator to come.
Can I help you?
I'm Fan Xian.
I want to meet Your Lady, Ye Ling'er!
One moment please.
What can I do for you?
I heard that
you fell into the Liujing River the other day.
Why do you ask that?
Wan'er told me
you visited the Joy Tsin House
to investigate Si Lili.
How could it be him?
Why did you fell into the river?
What did you witness
on the boat on that day?
I didn't see anything.
You're lying!
You know that guy!
No!
No?
That means you did see someone.
Stop asking!
You're daughter of the Chief Guard of the capital city,
but you still dare not
to say who it is.
It must be someone
with enormous power.
In the river of history,
time goes round and round.
Memories about the former and present lives
join each other in an endless way.
In the long drunken Milky Way,
one season follows another in a flash,
and the wild geese are flying south.
I just can't give up
to be with you for my whole life.
I have been hovering in the dreams
for hundreds and thousands of times.
I can't even say a word when I watch the flowers falling.
Year after year in the wandering,
I count the remaining years.
Even though we can't meet each other anymore,
even though we have ended up the destiny,
I never feel regretful.
In such a chaotic world,
I still miss you as ever.
I can't fall asleep under the moon.
With a gentle heart,
I cherish our remaining years.
Even though we have to go through
all the hardships along the journey,
you always stay by my side,
watching the falling flowers, speechlessly.
Year after year in the wandering,
I count the remaining years.
Even though we can't meet each other anymore,
even though we end up the destiny,
I never feel regretful.
In such a chaotic world,
I still miss you as ever.
I can't fall asleep under the moon.
With a gentle heart,
I cherish our remaining years.
Even though we have to go through
all the hardships along the journey,
you always stay by my side...