[English subtitles are available]
It hurts.
What are you yelling for?
Look at all the dead skin I scrubbed off.
Why do you always torture me?
Tell me, who are you?
I'm just a kind person passing by.
Miss, do you want to scrub your back?
No.
Scrub my back for me then.
Come on, scrub harder.
♫My Altay♫
♫My homeland filled with life♫
♫The everlasting sun♫
♫Golden Altay♫
♫The spirit of the land♫
♫Grass green like jade♫
♫Golden Altay♫
♫The spirit of the land♫
♫Grass green like jade♫
♫Golden Altay♫
♫The spirit of the land♫
♫Grass green like jade♫
♫Golden Altay♫
♫The spirit of the land♫
♫Grass green like jade♫
[Episode 3]
[To the Wonder]
The three of us smell so good.
There's no smell of cow dung at all.
Let's go.
Hello?
Is that a phone? A cellphone?
That's a telephone.
Call me tonight.
Call me at night.
This is a public phone.
I brought it out. It's mobile.
It's much better than that satellite phone.
You can call without a signal.
Just apply for one at the
telecommunication office.
Okay, I got it.
I'll ask Tokan to call you tonight.
Okay. I'll tell her Chaoge is looking for her.
Zhang Fengxia.
Do you have black soap?
What is black soap?
It's a Kazakh black soap made of herbs.
It looks like a black egg.
Here, take a look.
This one?
This kind of natural handmade soap
is very popular in the city.
Many people want this.
If you can get me some,
I'll buy them at 5 yuan each.
5 yuan each?
Yes.
Wow, this is so valuable.
Okay, I'll keep an eye out for it.
Okay.
550, right?
Okay, thank you.
Okay, bye.
Bye.
How's the business?
Zhang Fengxia.
What brings you here?
How have you been? Is everything going well?
Yes. How is your kid?
He's fine.
How much is this flashlight?
5 yuan.
5 yuan? Any discounts?
Do you have cough syrup?
Cough syrup.
Sell it to me at the wholesale price. 20 yuan.
Fine, I'll give you 20 yuan.
- I'll sell it to you at the wholesale price.
-20 yuan.
Okay.
How much is this?
20 yuan per kg.
20 yuan per kg?
Is the watermelon sweet?
Yes. Lady Zhang, buy one.
It's too heavy. I'll buy it next time.
You rest here.
I'll find an ox cart.
Are you sure you won't stay here?
Lady Zhang, what do you mean?
You want to leave me here?
Didn't you whine about wanting to write here?
I'm going to the summer ranch.
I've told Grandma.
That's right.
Grandma, have a seat.
[Internet cafe: Please go to the third floor.]
Granddaughter, you haven't finished your homework yet?
Grandma, I'm 19 years old.
I don't have homework anymore.
The silly lies you make
just to avoid doing homework.
[But even if I can't make money, I'm still willing to stay in that city.]
[I barely make any money working in Ürümqi.]
You can't just write your essays.
You've been bad at math since youth.
But all you do is write essays.
Can you make a living out of writing?
Even if I can't make a living out of it,
I still like it.
Grandma,
don't you like watching martial arts films?
Yes.
I was collecting garbage in Shenyang.
At night,
I slept under the bridge.
I was so tired that I wanted to cry.
So I imagined that
I was in a martial arts film
and I was wandering the martial arts world instead.
As I thought of it, I didn't feel that bad anymore.
See? It's the same for me.
It's the same for me and writing.
Every time I pick up the pen,
I feel very capable.
I'm just like those martial artists.
They can go wherever they want.
I can write whatever I want.
I feel very free.
[Liu Haibo]
[Liu Haibo email]
Uncle.
I need to use the bathroom.
Please keep an eye on the things for me.
Okay.
And my grandma, she's asleep.
Thank you.
Zhang Fengxia.
Semahul, I was going to look for you.
Here's the rent for this year.
No need.
The old house would be empty otherwise.
No one else lives there.
No, no need.
I even prepared it.
How are you doing?
How is life in the county seat?
It's good,
but I have no place to walk my horse.
Look how fat it is.
My son wants to join a horse race in the summer.
So, I'm walking it now.
By the way,
since you don't want the rent,
have this instead.
I made it myself.
Good for you, Zhang Fengxia.
You are more and more like a local.
You even know how to make milk curds now.
This is nothing.
I'm going to the summer ranch.
Going to Naren?
The 5th Husbandry Brigade came yesterday
and bought everything in my shop.
I'll restock some goods
before I go back and depart
for the summer ranch with our chief.
By the way, Zhang Fengxia.
Tell me about the village.
I heard that
Tokan is discussing her remarriage with Murat's family.
You guys
It's the spirit of Hatong;
we communicate and look out for each other.
Greetings, Mr. Liu.
Not long ago,
I attended your lecture in Ürümqi.
I learned a lot.
According to your suggestion,
which is to record my daily life,
I tried writing some essays.
After thinking about it,
[Gaoyuan Publishing House]
I picked the two best entries
and sent them to you.
I hope to receive your feedback.
[Recycling]
I look forward to your reply.
Here. Your wastepaper sold for 5 yuan.
Don't call it wastepaper.
That was all the newspaper pages
I've published over the years.
There were 7 headlines.
How could you call them wastepaper?
One yuan per kg.
I sold 4.8 kg.
He gave me 20 cents more.
5 yuan in total.
Look at you.
Don't get carried away.
Our weekly magazine did worse.
Coated paper only sells for 30 cents per kg.
I'm sorry.
I promised to start over after I quit.
I'll reflect on myself.
I'm still extremely bothered.
I know.
I'm insignificant.
I'm worthless.
I've wasted my life in this world.
I'm nothing.
But I feel awful.
I have to frame this five-yuan note.
This is proof of my years of experience.
What are you looking at, Liu?
A young lady
attended my lecture.
She sent me some essays she wrote.
How is it?
I'll send it to you.
Uncle, where's my grandma?
She was here just now. Where did she go?
How do I get to Shenyang?
I want to go to Shenyang.
Grandma.
Have you seen an old lady?
I want to go back to Shenyang.
I want to go home.
Grandma.
Mom!
Grandma is missing.
She was sitting here just now.
I went to the internet cafe, and she disappeared when I came back.
How long has she been missing?
Around 20 to 30 minutes.
Let me sober up first.
What should I do?
Your grandma is so old. She can't go far.
Find her now.
Grandma.
Comrade,
How do I get to Shenyang?
Grandma!
Who are you?
Stay away from me!
-Who are you?
-I'm Wenxiu.
I'm your granddaughter.
Stay away from me!
Let go of me!
Don't...
Give it to me.
Mom.
Mom!
I'll hit you.
We're leaving for Shenyang.
The car is leaving for Shenyang.
Is anyone boarding the car?
Anyone going to Shenyang?
Comrade,
are you going to Shenyang?
Yes, to Shenyang. Are you going?
Is the ticket expensive?
The ticket is usually quite expensive.
But it's free for the elderly.
Are you 70?
I'm not 70.
I'm only 35.
You're only 35?
I'll apply for half price for you. Are you coming?
Yes, yes.
Let's go. Get in.
Okay.
Hurry up. We're leaving soon.
Thank you.
We're heading to Shenyang.
We'll depart soon. Let's go.
I don't need your help.
I'm going back to Shenyang.
The writing is simple,
and she's naturally good at wording and phrasing.
She's a genius.
I want to find this person
and meet her.
Let's reply to the email first.
There's a contact number here.
Let me make a call.
Shenyang, my hometown.
Comrade, how much is the half-price ticket?
50 yuan.
Here.
I should have asked for more.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
I didn't take good care of Grandma.
No need to apologize for that.
I always lose her somewhere.
It's fine as long as we find her again.
What were you doing at the internet cafe?
I went to submit my work.
Did your work get selected?
The result is not that fast.
They'll call me if my work gets selected.
Is this usable at the summer ranch?
It needs to be charged regularly.
The summer ranch has no electricity. How can we use it there?
Zhang Fengxia.
Moving to another ranch, Bater?
I heard Tokan is going to remarry.
Is that true?
Don't ask me. I don't know.
Where's your spirit of Hatong?
We communicate and look out for each other.
Tell me, did he die in your shop?
Who said that?
But she is demanding a remarriage.
You're quite sober now.
Murat should have inherited the family business,
but he passed away.
He left his wife and two children.
There is also Batay, Sulitan's younger son.
I called you all here today
because there are things we need to discuss
after the death anniversary.
I said before that I didn't want the ranch.
My stance hasn't changed.
I'm just here to help for the summer.
I'll go back to the stable after summer.
In-law.
What's the matter? Tell me.
Let's talk about it later.
No, tell me now.
Shall we go?
Yes.
Then...
If you won't say it, I'll say it.
Tokan has two children.
Life is hard for her.
According to tradition,
I want Batay to marry Tokan.
No.
This can't be done.
Why not?
Aren't Yerdana and Nadyra
this family's children?
This is different from marriage.
Would you rather Tokan take the kids
and go to someone else's house?
Can't you take care of them?
If you keep talking about this, I'll go back to the stable tonight.
In-law,
this depends on the two kids.
If Batay doesn't want to,
you can't force him.
Besides, we need to ask what Tokan thinks.
Couldn't you have talked about it later?
Last time, you told me to wait until the death anniversary was over.
But it's over now.
Any later,
I might never get to remarry.
Don't say it out loud. It's so embarrassing.
Sister, look at her. Look at her.
No one in our family has ever remarried.
You're embarrassing us.
It's so embarrassing.
This is more embarrassing
than having a beggar in the family.
No, I want to remarry.
It's embarrassing for others to hear it.
I want to take my kids with me and remarry.
Murat had long agreed to divorce me.
I've been waiting for a long time.
What's wrong with you?
You can ask Zhang Fengxia if you don't believe me.
She can remarry,
but the kids have to stay.
The kids belong to this family.
What a disgrace.
Talk to her.
She won't listen to us.
Sister-in-law.
What is it?
No one in this family can convince me to leave my kids behind.
Got it?
How about this?
If my brother really said that,
our family would keep his word.
Is it up to you?
Father-in-law has the final say.
As long as my brother had said it,
I'll convince my dad for you.
Go if you want.
Men can go wherever they want.
We women need to cook, wash clothes,
and take care of the kids.
I don't even have time to go out.
Mom, Mom, don't cry.
I told your brother many times,
to go to the provision store
and buy me a washboard.
He never brought it back up till he died.
Get out. I'm going to cook.
Take these away.
Hello?
[Take things yourself. Put the money here.]
Batay! Batay!
My horse is having a hard time giving birth. Help!
Push harder. It's stuck.
Harder.
Hold its head in place.
Okay, okay. Harder.
That's it.
You're finally out, baby.
Great!
Batay.
Let's go inside and have some tea.
Okay.
Uncle Bek.
Didn't the auntie at the provision store leave early in the morning?
Why isn't she back yet?
You want to ask Zhang Fengxia about your brother?
Yes.
Are people from the south always so slow when they shop?
Maybe it has nothing to do with that,
and more to do with the fact that they are women.
Oh, uncle.
[Slow down]
It's my turn.
Bomb!
Anymore?
Come on.
Young lady, please pay up.
1 yuan.
Hurry.
My money!
There are cards here.
Sister Ma, how are you?
Bater!
Didn't you move to the other ranch already?
I'll go after a bowl of laghman.
Who is that?
Sulitan's younger son, Batay.
How much?
20 yuan in total.
Here, 20.
Okay.
Mom.
Can we buy a hamster?
Don't we have enough rats at home? You want to buy more?
How about this one?
How long will this take to grow up?
This is a dwarf rabbit.
It won't grow up, so it's always this cute.
That means it won't be enough for a dish even after 1 year.
Mom, this is a pet.
It's for being cute.
Our camel is cute too.
Let's go.
Gao Yong, is that a cigarette behind your ear?
At least I didn't light it.
What else are you planning to do?
I'll tell your mom. She'll punish you for sure.
Who is Gao Yong?
Listen.
I'm Gao Yong Bek from now on.
These are my Kazakh brothers.
If anyone bullies me,
I'll ask my brothers to teach him a lesson.
He became so arrogant after two days in school.
Look at him.
Walk on your writing-hand side.
Walk on your eating-hand side.
Sir, are you left-handed?
How much are instant noodles?
1 yuan.
80 cents.
I'll tell your mom later.
Take it.
Get out of the way.
Grandma, here.
How much is the lighter?
80 cents.
Say it again.
Take your grandma inside.
Okay.
80 cents. 80 cents.
Lady Bai wine.
Bill, please. 120 right?
How much is the lighter?
Lady Bai wine.
Are you buying?
Auntie, what's this?
Lady Bai wine.
What food did you bring?
Aren't you the young man with the bow last time?
Take whatever you need.
Which young man?
Why are you looking at him?
Is he edible?
Why don't you cook something?
It's been a day. I'm starving.
Stop looking.
Mom, where is the salt?
The salt is in the sugar jar and the sugar is in the soda ash jar.
Don't touch the salt jar.
There's laundry powder inside.
What is this?
Don't touch this one.
It's not food.
What's inside?
Baking soda.
Ahbozat.
Who?
This is a horse skull, not a human skull.
Of course it's not human.
It was the horse I rode when I was a kid.
It's already like this.
How did you recognize it?
It was a Mongolian horse.
I can tell from its forehead.
It should be hanging on a tree. Why is it at your house instead?
Because I was under the tree that day with a lot of sheep.
It fell into my arms on its own.
I thought it was a human skull.
I was so scared.
What's so scary about it?
Because it's like witchcraft.
What is witchcraft?
Witchcraft is a kind of sorcery.
Do you have any iron wires?
Iron wires...
Yes.
Get the pliers too.
Thank you.
Your pliers.
Don't scare her.
It's okay. I'm not scared.
I mean, don't scare my horse.
Do you want to come up?
Can I come up?
Why not?
Come on.
Here.
Hush.
Keep your voice down.
You'll really scare my horse this way.
This horse is unrideable and cowardly.
How strange.
To the Kazakhs, horses are our best friends.
If a horse dies,
we will miss it.
So we cut its head off
and hang it somewhere we pass by every day.
Some villages put the skulls
in the cracks of rocks.
There are no mountains in our village.
So we hang it here
on the largest tree around.
We can see it when we miss it.
There's no witchcraft,
only nostalgia.
Be careful.
Look, a rainbow.
That's the direction of the river.
There's water vapor in the air.
By the way,
our village is called Saykhan Bulake.
You know that, right?
I know, Rainbow Bulake.
Saykhan Bulake.
Rainbow?
Saykhan.
Oh, it's not rainbow?
They sound similar, but Saykhan is Mongolian.
It means splendid.
It's not "rainbow" in Mandarin.
What about Bulake?
Bulake means spring water.
I thought
this was a village
where one could always see rainbows.
We do always see rainbows here.
Rainbow
has a nice ring to it.
It's a beautiful misunderstanding.
Well,
what does Ahbozat mean?
Ahbozat
was a white horse.
It was
white like the moon.
What about it?
It's called Snowshoe.
What does it mean?
Look, all four of its hoofs are white.
It's like it just walked out of the snow.
So Snowshoe means exactly that.
Yes.
But
Snowshoe got injured during the previous race.
It wasn't just an injury to its hind leg.
Psychologically, it cannot
handle another shock anymore.
It also hates being ridden.
I hope that by the time summer ends,
it can get better
and return to the arena.
Let's go.
It's so high.
It's okay. Get down.
What's your name?
I'm Bakhetbek.
Call me Batay if you think it's long.
Batay.
What about you?
I'm Li Wenxiu.
They all call me "the girl from the provision store."
I know.
You do?
Yes.
You're famous now.
Aren't you the girl
who lost her grandma?
Is this the spirit of Hatong again?
Yes.
A young man called Bater
ate a bowl of laghman at Ma Chunhan's house.
He told Ma Chunhan about it.
Ma Chunhan told the whole village.
Now everyone in the village knows
that a Han girl
lost her grandma
in the county seat today.
Can't you guys spread some good words instead?
This is our Kazakh tradition.
If Tursenhan wants to remarry,
the kids must stay with the father's family.
But if my brother promised her,
we have to keep our promise.
I'll try to convince my father.
No.
I've never heard such a thing.
Tokan is lying.
What's going on?
Mom.
Murat and Tokan must have spoken in Kazakh.
Maybe they did mention it,
but you didn't understand.
That's right.
Don't you know your brother?
Would he agree to such a thing?
He wouldn't even buy a washboard for your sister-in-law.
Got it.
I'll go back and talk to Tursenhan.
Why is there only one?
Come on, fold the blanket with me.
Well,
will Tokan be separated from her kids?
If she doesn't remarry, she won't be separated.
A widow can take care of her kids too.
She's so pitiful. Her kids are so young.
Besides, don't kids always follow their mothers?
They are different.
They have their own way of living
and getting along with the world.
You don't have to agree with them,
but you can't be arrogant
and try to change them.
Aren't you staying here to go to the summer ranch?
If you want to stay here,
don't think you're smarter
just because you're from the city.
So...
I'm really sorry.
After attending your lecture,
I only wrote those essays
on a whim.
My husband found out when I went home.
He was very upset.
Because I promised him
to take care of our family.
We have three children.
My daily life is very busy
and I don't have time for myself.
So, I don't want to affect my children's lives
because of these things.
So...
I stopped writing.
Please reconsider.
You're really talented.
And I know you don't live on writing...
I understand.
Madam.
Virginia Woolf once said,
"A woman must have
a room of her own."
It's time.
I should pick up my kids from school.
You...
Thank you.
Why would someone
not cherish their talent?
Forget it.
Don't force it.
She has made her choice.
Who will pay the bill?
Me.
In the past glory of the headlines I basked.
Not knowing it was now worth 5 yuan when asked.
Liu.
Although I can't write well,
I feel terrible seeing someone
who writes so well
but doesn't cherish it.
Don't be upset.
We're just getting started.
In the future,
there will be more emails
and letters coming our way.
I believe
there must be someone who writes well among them.
Liu.
Cheers!
Okay!
I'm only lending it to you. Remember to return it to me.
Okay.
Here.
Mom.
How's the packing going?