[English subtitles are available]
[A Lonely Hero's Journey]
[Episode 23]
You…
just relax.
Since you're here,
you can go out for a walk.
There are many good places in Suzhou.
You can visit anywhere.
In that case,
let's go visit the Willow Garden.
Sure.
Two years ago,
I tried to copy the Painting of the Tiger Hill,
but I just couldn't present
the garden part very well.
Mr. Jiang.
Do you have the Painting of the Tiger Hill by Qian Gu of the Ming Dynasty
in your hands?
That is a rare treasure.
Did you bring it?
I want to see it, too.
No problem.
You said tomorrow yourself.
Do you hear that?
I'm going on a trip tomorrow.
Stop making excuses.
Mr. Jiang, don't be angry.
Mr. Li has ordered us
to only listen to Mr. Zhou
when it comes to matters in Suzhou.
I've no objection.
Then...
that's it.
Okay.
I'll send some to you later.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
See you.
Okay, Mrs. Jiang.
Take care.
Goodbye.
Okay.
Tell me if you need anything.
I will.
Go back.
Have you made a deal with Jiang?
I gave him a chance to escape.
Whether he lives or dies
depends on his own fate.
It's coming, Zhou!
There are not only ten gold bars
but also a bracelet.
You just like these worthless things.
Do you know what's his most valuable possession?
The Painting of the Tiger Hill from the Ming Dynasty
is in his hands.
That is priceless.
Go back now.
Get it.
Go back to No. 90.
Sir!
How many times have I told you?
You're always in a flurry.
Sir.
Gu Yizhong is here.
Didn't he run away?
He came to work as usual in the morning.
Warden Lu is not here?
Lu ran away.
Why did he run away?
It's all because of that hole.
The Japanese put pressure on him.
Lu is not stupid.
He can't stay here as a scapegoat, right?
That's interesting.
Cell 8 was exposed.
And he saved Xiao Junxia.
Logically, in the communist party,
he should be able to prove his innocence.
But he still came back.
Interesting.
He is Mr. Si's spy.
No doubt about that.
If so,
what can you do?
He has Mr. Si as his backer and is undercover.
Kondo is also protecting him.
What can we do?
Yes.
About Lu,
is everything arranged for him?
Yes.
I let the warden escape overnight.
I guess he's already out of Jiangsu now.
There's another news.
You need to spread it for me.
Surely, he couldn't quit a job
that earns 80 a month!
Money isn't as important as life.
But Lu prefers the money.
Everyone, assemble!
Mr. Kondo is going to give us all a speech.
Let's go!
Yizhong.
Did something happen again?
Yesterday afternoon, Iwai went out
with four or five people,
and he didn't come back until midnight.
Clang…
Clang, clack… They kept at it almost all night.
I wonder who's in trouble this time.
Attention!
The news that the dungeon was blown up
has been spread to Nanjing.
Everyone in the advisory body and the military police
is laughing at me.
Someone has to
pay the price for this matter!
Bring him over.
For the last time,
where is Jiang?
I really don't...
This is the result of deceiving and betraying the imperial army.
The person in the photo is Jiang Boxian.
He's hiding somewhere in Suzhou.
Whoever finds him
will be awarded 10,000 yuan.
If you know something
but not report it,
you will end up
like Lu.
Understand?
Yes!
Director,
I think the dungeon incident
must have something to do
with someone inside our agent station.
Who do you think
he could be?
Could it be…
Gu Yizhong?
Or…
Vice Director Huang.
Just get to the point.
Don't beat around the bush.
Okay.
According to the landlord in Pishi Street,
that house
was only rented out seven or eight days
before the incident.
They needed to dig a tunnel from that house
to our agent station.
Meanwhile, the person was also aware of the existence of the secret canal.
If it was not someone who was a professional architect
and knew the underground structure well,
it was impossible to make it.
Gu Yizhong's major is architecture.
That's one of the reasons.
Secondly,
the tunnel goes straight to the cell,
which means they knew
the exact location of the cell.
I checked the records of access to the prison.
Before the incident,
Gu Yizhong had been to the prison.
What's the third point?
Thirdly,
Xiao Junxia was Gu Yizhong's former leader.
Logically speaking,
they must have had a strong emotional connection.
There's the motive.
So, about the dungeon incident,
Gu Yizhong is the most suspicious.
Vice Director Huang,
what do you mean by telling me this?
Director.
This is an important matter.
I dare not neglect it.
Don't worry, Director.
Whether it's a friend or family,
as long as it affects the great cause of the Empire's
peace movement,
I can sacrifice them all!
Amazing.
You're such a talent.
So mean.
Director.
But you've always taught us not to do anything
that will only hurt others but bring no benefits to ourselves.
Look.
You only remember the useless things that I said.
Director,
do you have something
on Gu Yizhong?
Why did you start to accuse me, too?
No, well...
You have a blood feud with him.
Think about
Gu Yizhong's father's death
and his sister's death,
right?
And Director,
why didn't you tell Mr. Kondo
but let Lu take the blame?
Xinzhai.
Why didn't you tell the Japanese
what you just said to me,
but instead, you came to me?
After all, these are just speculations.
We can't arrest him without evidence.
That's right!
After all this time,
it's the first time we've been on the same page.
Listen.
Now, in Suzhou Station,
there are both CBIS
and NBIS members.
And now, there's even a Mr. Si.
It's so lively now.
Right?
Director,
don't listen to their nonsense.
What NBIS?
I'm always at your command.
Thank you.
Director,
don't let Xie Wenchao investigate me anymore.
I have nothing to do with Chongqing.
Really?
Really!
I promise
I won't tattle on you
to the Japanese.
Have you done that before?
No, of course not!
Really?
Really, really.
They were all just regular work reports.
Xinzhai.
Thank you
for being so honest with me.
Tonight,
I'll borrow your kitchen.
Right!
Let's have a drink
to relax a little.
No, no.
You misunderstood.
Xinzhai.
I'm going to treat someone to dinner
at the dorm tonight.
But we don't have a kitchen in our place.
So, I want my wife
to cook some dishes in your kitchen.
Is that okay?
Sure.
How about
you come too and have a drink tonight?
No.
I happen to have something to do tonight.
Okay. That's too bad, then.
I'll tell your wife.
Yizhong.
You're here.
Come in and sit down.
Come in.
Make yourself at home.
My wife
learned that I was going to treat you to dinner,
so she made you some dishes
from our hometown, Yixing.
Braised bamboo shoots with salted pork.
Matsutake mushroom.
Try them.
Here's a toast to you.
You…
You're just like an old agent.
Look.
It's Wu Sibao's fault.
He was locked in No. 90
and was poisoned to death.
From then on,
the agents
could no longer trust each other.
Director, you called me here.
Just say it directly.
In this Braised bamboo shoots with salted pork,
the bamboo shoots
are a big deal.
They were brought here
by Mr. Li's friend from North Fujian
at the beginning of the year.
They're different from ours.
We use spring bamboo shoots.
They use winter bamboo shoots.
My wife and I
have been reluctant to eat them.
We have stored them in the fridge.
Knowing you were coming for dinner,
I especially went back to the Mansion to get them here.
Yizhong,
your sister's death
really had nothing to do with me.
Believe it or not,
it hurts me, too.
After all,
she died in the hands of her beloved one.
She loved the wrong person.
Maybe.
Your brother-in-law,
I mean Hu Zhiping,
was shot to death by me.
I kind of took revenge for your sister,
right?
This is to your sister.
Why did you come back to No. 90?
I have unfinished things to do, of course.
Are you targeting me?
I'm not like you.
You only care about personal grudges.
Do you know why?
That's because I know
matters of national interest
are beyond the capabilities
of small potatoes like us.
Cell 8 has been exposed.
You saved Xiao Junxia, too.
Listen to me.
Let go when you should.
Why don't you brush off your robes and leave, when matters are settled?
Is No. 90 a place that one can leave so easily?
Director,
I remember you told us
when giving us classes,
that our work as agents,
in the end,
is political work.
We should be loyal to the party,
to the country,
and to our leader.
You're in it for one day,
and you'll be in it for the rest of your life.
Yizhong.
Well said!
You're indeed my best student.
I almost believed it.
Director.
In this world,
everyone has shortcomings.
No need to die for the Japanese, right?
Everyone has seen
the end of Lu Yaoting today.
That is also what I wanted to say.
Yizhong,
we have no grudge against each other,
right?
Your father's death has nothing to do with me.
Your sister's death has nothing to do with me, either.
We have no grudge.
Even if there is,
it's your grudge against the Japanese.
Right?
Of course.
So,
I won't stand in your way.
And you…
give me an out, too.
Okay?
You're right, Director.
That's why I always think
you're the most promising one
at No. 90.
Mr. Li will come to Suzhou
in a while.
I'll introduce you to him by then.
You haven't answered me
why you came back to No. 90, have you?
For Jiang Boxian, right?
The reward of 10,000 yuan
is not easy to get.
Mr. Gu,
would you value 10,000 yuan?
You.
Go tell your friends,
Jiang Boxian is a wanted criminal by Mr. Li.
No one can take him away.
The one who wants Jiang Boxian most now
is Kondo, right?
No, it's me.
Everyone thinks
Jiang Boxian was under my control.
As time goes on,
try to imagine
my suffering.
Director,
thank you for inviting me.
See you.
Are you leaving already?
The dishes are not all served yet.
Yizhong.
Vice Director Huang?
What happened?
The chopsticks were not even used.
They've cooked the bamboo shoots saved for
the Spring Festival.
How is it possible that Zhou Zhifei didn't get great benefits?
Yizhong.
Don't believe him.
That old man never tells the truth.
Not necessarily.
See?
You're poisoned.
You're already poisoned, Yizhong.
Do you want to make contributions with me?
Tell me.
I found traces of Jiang Boxian.
The two agents
from No. 76 got drunk.
They said Jiang Boxian would go to Willow Garden tomorrow.
Vice Director Huang.
It seems that you'll earn
10,000 yuan soon.
It's not about money.
Yizhong,
I need help now.
If you work with me,
I won't mistreat.
Think about it.
Consider it.
Hello?
Yizhong.
I got it.
You didn't call the extension number?
Oh, I listened to you. I dialed directly.
Target:
Tomorrow afternoon, Willow Garden.
Got it.
You're here, sir.
Have a seat upstairs.
Take care, sir.
Please come back again.
You're here.
Sir, please come in.
Hongbo.
Xinzhai.
Why did you pick such a place to meet?
The lowly brothels are the second best place
for a temporary meeting
of agents.
Only the NBIS teaches things like that.
If Mr. Xu knows
we come to such a place to talk business,
he'll scold us.
That's why
Mr. Xu couldn't climb as high as Mr. Dai.
You looked for me so urgently.
Have you found him?
We have the time and place of Jiang Boxian's whereabouts.
Really?
Tell me.
The pass,
issued by the district office of Wu County.
Not fake.
Business travel permits,
travel expenses, and tickets for a detour through Shanghai.
[Suzhou to Shanghai]
Yours and your wife's.
A part of the gold bars.
[Pass]
Jiang Boxian.
Hongbo.
You didn't lie to me
about my mother, did you?
Xinzhai,
that's too much to talk like that.
Back in Chongqing,
I took better care of your mother
than my own mother.
And didn't I show you
the photos before?
Why are you suspicious now?
No, no, no.
If it weren't for my old mother,
I wouldn't do such a risky thing.
Zhou Zhifei was assassinated.
He has already suspected
that I leaked his home address.
Jiang Boxian.
Give me four men,
six guns, 100 bullets,
and a car.
Tomorrow afternoon,
wait at the back door of the Willow Garden.
Say it.
Tomorrow afternoon, Jiang Boxian will go to the Willow Garden.
How many people will there be? How many guns?
I don't know the exact number.
The security of Jiang Boxian
is handled by the agents
from No. 76.
He has two bodyguards.
The number of security guards outside is unknown.
Okay, I got it.
You can leave.
Cousin-in-law,
I'm somewhat suspicious of this piece of intelligence.
Jiang Boxian's whereabouts have always been mysterious.
No one from No. 90 knew about anything about it
except Zhou Zhifei.
But last night,
there suddenly was news.
You think the information is unreliable because it comes from a single source?
On the contrary,
there are two sources
confirming this information.
It is just too coincidental.
I suspect
someone leaked the news on purpose.
Zhou Zhifei.
Maybe.
I see.
Go.
Where is Haimo?
I've sent you the news.
You should release her now.
Don't worry.
We'll keep our promise.
Haimo has nothing
to do with our walk of life.
Don't lead her into this business.
[Rongguang Photo Studio]
Sir,
we're closed.
How much is the rush service?
What size would you like?
A set for two inches and five inches each.
Please go upstairs.
Jiang Boxian has been
a member of the Central Committee of Kuomintang for a long time.
He's somewhat related to Chiang, too.
I'm worried that he came to Shanghai this time
on behalf of Chiang
to talk with the Japanese secretly,
which will affect the Anti-Japanese National United Front.
How can they negotiate with the Japanese
when the two sides are already locked in an all-out war?
Chongqing has always been a bit hesitant.
They've been watching the situation
while secretly preparing an escape route
for themselves.
But the Wang Regime in Nanjing
doesn't want the Chongqing government
to establish contact with the Japanese.
Otherwise,
as a puppet,
they will become a useless pawn.
So, Zhou Zhifei, Kondo,
Huang Xinzhai,
and the CBIS in Chongqing
all want Jiang Boxian.
There may be more.
There will be a big show in Willow Garden tomorrow.
Maybe this is a trap
Zhou Zhifei set.
Maybe.
Zhou Zhifei wanted to use Jiang Boxian
to make all the parties kill each other.
Then,
he can benefit from it.
Sir,
in that case,
what do you think we should do?
Once the Japanese
establish contact with Chiang,
it will be more difficult for the counter-Japanese war to proceed.
Saving Jiang Boxian
is the best option.
[Famous Porcelain from Jiangxi Transported by Ding's Store]
Are you still mad at me?
Yesterday, I shouldn't
have slapped you.
I apologize.
How about
you hit me once?
Let me tell you.
Men are unreliable even if they're your bosom friends for ten years,
let alone a man you just met.
He's a good person.
A good person?
For his own benefit, he abandoned his girlfriend
and forced his father and sister to die.
How could such an unfilial and unloyal person
be a good person?
He has his own difficulties.
All men's difficulties
are excuses
used to trick women.
I don't want to hear that.
[Willow Garden]
Please get off.
Nice.
Great.
I haven't seen this for a long time.
Are you two also here
to visit the garden today?
Who is this gentleman?
Mr. Li's guest.
Let me tell you.
I just found some very suspicious people
at the back door.
Who are you?
Chongqing sent me here
save you.
Back door. Hurry up!
Where are you taking me?
Go!
This...
Slow down.
I can't run fast.
Vice Director Huang, what a coincidence.
You didn't go to a brothel today
but came to a garden instead?
[Lotus-admiring Pavilion]
Kill him!
Go to the front door. Someone's there to pick you up.
Who are you?
Just go!
[Lotus-admiring Pavilion]
Mr. Kondo.
I found Jiang Boxian.
He is now in the Willow Garden.
Okay.
[Clear Sky And Crisp Air]
Let's go.
[Willow Garden]
This is killing me.
Mr. Jiang.
Mr. Jiang, come with me.
Who are you?
Go!
Xinping!
Don't go in.
Don't go inside.
Let go.
No one going in Willow Garden today
can come out alive.
We have arranged for the top assassins
of the Peace Army to be inside.
Listen to me.
I must take Jiang Boxian back to Chongqing.
Why do you care about him?
It's more important that you live.
Let go!
We can't change the current situation.
Listen to me. Go back.
Move!
Don't go in.
I told you to move!
Stop following me,
or I'll kill you, too.
Go!
Xinping.
Get down!
Go.
[Willow Garden]
Who are you?
-Go.
Where are we going?
Go!
[Willow Garden]
Hurry.
Go back.
Go! Go!
Hurry! Go!
Take Mr. Jiang away.
Ms. Ou.
Let's meet at the next liaison point.
Go!
Yes.
Let's go.
Go!
Give up resistance.
Take her away.
Bad news!
Director Zhou, bad news!
Many people died over there.
Xie Wenchao is crazy!
He wanted to shoot me to death.
Director Zhou.
Xie Wenchao must be crazy.
He wanted to shoot me to death.
He wanted to shoot…
How many gold bars
did you get with my home address?
[Clear Sky And Crisp Air]
[Beauty of Flowers]
Keep it down! Junsheng just fell asleep.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Did they give you a hard time?
No.
That day,
besides slapping me once,
my cousin-in-law never hurt me again.
What about you?
Did you help them?
Jiang Boxian has escaped.
What about my cousin-in-law?
Something happened to her?
They took you hostage,
and you still care about her?
Actually, though my cousin-in-law
is a bit mean,
she's not a bad person.
She didn't mean to hurt me.
Otherwise, she wouldn't have let me go.
She just used me
to make you help them.
You've been frightened these days.
Let Mrs. Wang
take care of Junsheng.
Have a good rest.
You know where she is, right?
She was arrested
and locked up in the prison of No. 90.
Will she live?
Kondo wants to persuade her to surrender.
So, unless she surrenders to the Japanese…
My cousin-in-law won't do that.
She hates the Japanese the most.
She once told me
she'd have either one of these ends:
Either she'd kill the Japanese
or be killed by them.
Many men
are not as good as women.
Can you think of a way to save her,
Mr. Gu?
[Receipt of Shanghai Branch, Bank of China]
[Receiver: Huang Xinzhai]
How could Huang Xinzhai be an undercover for Chongqing?
We found that
during the past year, Huang Xinzhai
had frequently dealt with
the higher-ups of the NBIS in Chongqing.
Other than exchanging information,
they also secretly sold military supplies
to make money like crazy.
Ding Jiansheng's case
had something to do with him.
These gold bars
were found
in Huang Xinzhai's house.
So, you've been investigating him for a long time.
Why didn't you report it earlier?
Didn't you ask us
to unite and make a good job of the peace movement?
I wouldn't dare to tell on him.
I was afraid you'd say I undermined the unity.
Besides, I didn't have enough evidence.
Now, it's different.
By the way,
look.
There's a photo here.
It's the photo taken when he was meeting
with the Chongqing agents.
We took it on the spot.
And the previous Willow Garden operation.
Huang Xinzhai
listened to the order of the Chongqing regime
and saved Jiang Boxian.
Luckily,
you saw through their plot in time.
Jiang Boxian has escaped?
Don't worry.
The entire city has been locked down.
We can catch him sooner or later.
Where is Ou Xinping?
I'll follow your instructions.
Is the rumor about your relationship with Ou Xinping true?