[English subtitles are available]
[A Lonely Hero's Journey]
[Episode 20]
Lin,
your wife brought you delicious food again.
Eggs？
What is this?
I don't eat eggs.
Why give me eggs?
That bitch!
Jiang,
why don't you
give these eggs to me?
Eat up.
There are plenty here.
The two parties are cooperating.
[This is a prison]
[Knock on the wall for positioning]
What does it say?
How is it?
Do you hear something?
There's nothing.
Why don't you take a rest upstairs?
Eat something first.
Okay.
Wait.
Did you hear that?
I think I heard it wrong.
Let's go.
Yizhong.
Captain Zhang.
What are you doing?
Hanging those stubborn things.
The director said
it's too troublesome to go to the Stump.
To avenge Section Chief Lian,
hanging
is the most satisfying way.
Isn't it tomorrow?
It changed to today?
Today is a good day.
[Captain for the country]
Are they really coming to rescue us?
You communists are digging a tunnel?
We're saved.
Director.
I told Gu Yizhong
we're taking action today,
but he didn't react at all.
He went into the Investigation office
and hasn't come out.
Will he
really let them die?
Miss Xiao. Miss Xiao.
Here.
I've brought the stuff. Hurry.
Okay.
Hurry.
Let me do it.
Is Pishi Street near the fake mountain?
Yes.
Captain Zhang,
lead a team immediately
over there.
There's a house
with a long blue shirt hanging out the 2nd-floor window.
Keep an eye on that one.
Xie Wenchao.
Sir.
Bring Gu Yizhong here.
Okay.
What are you doing here?
Hurry up.
They are digging the tunnel.
Amazing.
It’s unbelievable.
Gu Yizhong.
Hurry up!
Yizhong,
I heard you majored in architecture.
Right?
Yes.
I have a professional question for you.
If you dig
a tunnel
from there on Pishi Street
and keep digging
until you get under No. 90,
do you think it's plausible?
Director Zhou,
in Pennsylvania, I studied architecture
on the ground.
I really don't know
about the underground.
What a pity.
It's okay.
You're invited to watch a good show.
Go back.
Miss Xiao, calm down.
Transfer me to the warden.
Hello?
Yaoting,
bring those two people in the dungeon
to me.
Yes.
Right away.
Okay, right away.
Give him a chair.
Jiang, wake up.
It's time to go. Wake up.
[Sino-Japanese Relations]
It's lit.
No, no.
That one.
The one with a long shirt over there.
Go!
Is it an earthquake?
Take it. Hurry.
Come here.
Junxia.
Ruotong.
Sir.
Junxia, let's go.
Leave him. It's too late.
Junxia.
Junxia, be careful.
There's a grenade.
No.
Come back.
What did the Director say?
He asked us to keep an eye on this house.
Keep watching.
Go!
Hurry.
Sir.
Xiao Junxia ran away. That…
That person is still here.
Gu Yizhong,
you colluded with the people outside
to dig a tunnel from the Pishi Street
to under No. 90.
This move is really amazing.
Smart
and brave.
Director Zhou,
what do you mean?
You don't know?
You probably didn't expect
that our men
would catch you from the back, right?
Captain Zhang is taking his men
to Pishi Street
to block your people there.
The house with the long shirt on the 2nd floor
is your place, right?
Put this on.
Take this money,
and leave this place.
Just pretend that we never met.
Understand?
Yes.
Sha,
we have to go now.
Put it there.
Wait.
There are spies outside.
Seven or eight of them.
We're surrounded!
Go!
Director Zhou,
I work from 9 to 5 every day
and only go from Gu's Garden to No. 90 and back.
I dare not slack off at work.
Why do you suspect me?
Besides,
I'm a wanted man
by the Communist Party.
If you want to frame me,
why beat around the bush?
You've improved.
I'm staring at you at such a close distance
and it's hard to find your flaw.
You are really good at being an agent.
Let’s wait and see.
Ruotong!
Hurry up and come out!
It's Li!
Come out!
Hurry up!
Hurry!
Let's go.
Go!
Go after them!
Get down!
Go.
This...
[Deda Oil Shop]
They got away?
On the way,
a bunch of Mr. Si attacked.
Their firepower was too strong.
Iwai and the military police
couldn't reinforce in time.
[Xinsheng Water Shop]
Junxia, we're here.
Junxia.
Let's go.
Hurry!
Be careful.
I'm fine.
Director Zhou,
if there's nothing else,
I'll go back to work.
I haven't finished finalizing the summary
of Ding Jiansheng's case.
Mr. Kondo
is still waiting for my report.
Okay.
Your job is very important.
Go now.
In the future,
I'll need to ask you some more
about architecture.
As far as I know,
the aboveground and underground
are actually connected.
My pleasure, any time.
Okay.
Sir.
You just let him go?
Yes.
Send him to the interrogation room.
I bet we can
get something out of him with a beating.
Yes.
It's too dangerous to have him
staying undercover here.
He must have colluded with Mr. Si.
So what?
The Mr. Si by Taihu Lake
has over 10,000 guns.
Can you defeat them?
Besides,
Xiao Junxia ran away.
Don't blame yourself.
Mr. Li arranged all of this.
In this way,
we can test Gu Yizhong's true nature.
Understand?
But from now on,
Mr. Jiang must be safe.
Yes, sir.
As you ordered,
he has been moved to the safe house.
The guards outside and inside
are all comrades from No. 76 in Shanghai.
Good.
Mr. Jiang's location
must not be leaked,
especially to Huang Xinzhai and the Japanese.
Understand?
-Yes.
Go ahead.
[Hongxiang Tea House]
Li, get me some clean towels.
Sure thing.
Junxia, here.
Let me take off your clothes
and clean your wound.
Let me do it, Junxia.
Ruotong,
I'll take off my clothes.
Junxia.
Why are you crying?
I'm fine.
No.
I'll get the doctor.
Don't.
I can handle it.
The people from No. 90
must be searching for us all over Suzhou.
They beat you so hard.
I'm lucky
to have come out alive.
Towel.
Here's the towel.
Give it to me.
Do you have alcohol?
No.
I can find a way to buy some.
Then please do that.
Okay.
Buy one with high concentration.
Got it.
Let me see.
There's no rush.
I have something to tell you.
Close the door.
Sit down.
What happened
after I was arrested?
Why is Gu Yizhong
working as an agent in No. 90?
Was he assigned by the organization
or is there another reason?
This window
has a bamboo stick.
with a shirt hanging from it.
A blue shirt hanging from the window
means everything is going as planned.
The plan is over now.
The blue shirt
has been removed, right?
Yizhong,
you have to give me a way out.
I just want to know who Cell 8 is.
If I told you,
would you be able to leave No. 90?
I won't make a deal.
That middle-aged man
should be your butler,
Fu Gui.
The young lady
was Xiao Ruotong, who brought you
the Waterman pen, right?
And her brother, Xiao Junxia.
With my ability,
do you think
they could leave Suzhou
if I wanted to catch them?
Get to the point.
Yizhong,
in this world,
there are no permanent enemies,
nor permanent friends.
What do you think?
Can you
tell your organization
that I, Zhou Zhifei,
am willing to establish contact with them?
Why do you only draw scenes but not people?
Try to draw us in.
How harmonious.
Yizhong is definitely not Cell 8.
I don't believe it either.
Things were so difficult
during your absence.
Who do you think
Cell 8 is?
I think
I know who it is now.
Do you remember this photo?
Isn't this the Nakanishi Tarou
that we were going to rescue in the Garden of Pleasance operation?
The person in the photo
is not Nakanishi Tarou at all.
After I was arrested,
I was locked in No. 90's dungeon.
About a week later,
the Japanese Police
came to bring food to a death row prisoner.
That was where they usually
never went to.
When the death-row inmate tidied up his clothes,
he suddenly started singing The Internationale.
Stand up,
slaves who are hungry and cold.
Stand up, people who suffer all over the world.
Comrade.
Are you a Communist Party member?
I am.
I'm from the Japanese Communist Party.
You're Nakanishi Tarou?
How do you know my name?
Do you know me?
Comrade,
don't give up.
Soon,
Japan will be defeated.
-Nakanishi Tarou.
-By then,
all of you
will walk out from here
without restraint.
Comrade!
Down with Japanese imperialism!
The Japanese Communist Party member
named Nakanishi Tarou that we were going to save
was not the person in the photo.
Something is wrong with this photo.
After we were ambushed during that night's oepration,
I suspected
we had an internal traitor.
I reviewed all the details
and filtered all the participants.
But I overlooked the photo.
It was only after I met Nakanishi Tarou
that I realized
the entire operation
was a trap all along.
Whoever gave this photo
is Cell 8.
Who gave you this photo?
Zhou Zhenwu.
[Temple Donation Box]
Xiao Junxia was kidnapped by the Communist Party.
Who?
Xiao Junxia is not dead.
I thought
everyone died that day, except Gu Yizhong.
Why did you keep him around?
His family is rich, right?
I wanted to keep him in exchange for some money.
You're still thinking about money?
Gu Yizhong joined forces with your people outside
to take him away
from No. 90's dungeon.
It was a two-sided collaboration.
Xiao Junxia was saved.
He will suspect me
once he meets up with Eagle.
You mean
Hu Zhiping gave you this photo?
Yes.
This was the photo.
I remember it very clearly.
I'm going to retreat from them.
Before that,
you have to tell me the liaison point
of the New Fourth Army.
I won't.
You want your wife to know
that you're Cell 8?
Give me some time.
I don't have time.
The traitor is Hu Zhiping.
We must cut off
all contact with him immediately.
The leaders of Jiangsu Provincial Committee
crossed Suzhou's borders recently.
All activities were arranged
by Hu Zhiping.
If Hu Zhiping is Cell 8,
Zhou Zhifei will inform him soon
that I have been saved.
He'll grow desperate and panic.
The leaders will be in danger.
We have no clue about
when they came,
where they live,
and where they'll enter and exit.
We can't contact the leaders of the provincial committee either.
We must find him immediately
and stop him.
I'll contact the liaison immediately.
Huizhong.
Come in.
Director.
The special agent is here.
Mr. Ji.
It's been six months.
How have you been?
Have a seat.
I flew from Chongqing to Guilin,
then Guilin to Hong Kong,
and then took a British ship to Shanghai.
It took more than half a month.
After doing office work for so long,
my back can barely hold up anymore.
Director, you guys talk.
I'll arrange lunch for the special agent.
Deputy Director Shen, stay here
to listen to Mr. Xu's verbal message.
This was specifically instructed
by Mr. Xu before I left.
To Xinping and Yifei,
you two have gone to Suzhou with your men for three months.
I listened hard but did not hear of any news.
Why?
Mr. Jiang Boxian
is a party pioneer.
He has been captured for days.
Three risky rescues have been ordered,
but there's still no trace of him.
Traitor Zhou Zhifei
was an exemplary party member
but decided to follow the traitorous Wang.
You guarantee that he sides with goodness.
The letters I wrote
have also received no responses.
If it's confirmed that he can't be used by the party,
we must sanction him severely.
Xinping
has always been braver than men.
Why are you so timid
after entering Suzhou?
Sincerely, Enzeng.
Xinping, sit down.
Sit down.
I failed Mr. Kejun.
I don't deserve to sit.
You exaggerate.
Have a seat.
Director Ou,
you've always been admired by our comrades.
But I heard that, a few days ago,
five more men died in the military hospital.
Since you ask,
I don't dare to hide anything.
No. 90 guards heavily.
Jiangsu District will create another plan
to save Mr. Jiang.
Xinping.
Saving people and killing
are two things.
If you can't accomplish one,
I'm afraid it'll be difficult
to explain to Mr. Kejun.
Do you have any new plans
about sanctioning Zhou Zhifei?
We're working on a strategy.
Director Ou, you had a good chance
but you has lost it.
Why do you say that?
Rumor has it that
Director Ou has been hiding in Zhou's Mansion.
Is it true?
Yes.
Deputy Director Shen didn't report this to me.
I
arrived in Suzhou two days ago.
I asked some old friends and found out about it.
Zhou Zhifei has always been cunning.
His residence is not known to outsiders.
Regarding the specific location of Zhou's Mansion,
I think you
must still remember, right?
Director Ou,
please write down the specific location of Zhou's Mansion
and have the operations team
carry out the mission.
No. 2, Minsheng Lane, Shantang Street.
[No. 2, Minsheng Lane, Shantang Street.]
It's the same.
You already had the address?
I was afraid the intelligence from the NBIS
might have mistakes,
so I asked you to confirm it.
I appreciate it.
Deputy Director Shen,
please
give orders to our operations team.
Han, No. 2, Minsheng Lane, Shantang Street.
Action.
Zhou Zhifei's car is bulletproof, right?
Both teams have armor-piercing shells.
They specialize in hitting bulletproof cars.
The three of us will wait here
for the good news.
Sir!
Do you need a car?
Ruotong said Junxia wants to see you.
It's urgent.
Sir, here.
Who is it?
It's me.
[After drinking the jade nectar, walking through bamboo forest]
I found where the special agent is staying.
Why don't you have Li go with you?
It's too late.
I’ll check it myself.
Ruotong,
the tea house is not safe now.
Be careful.
Got it.
Sir, we're here.
Turn left and go upstairs.
Stay outside and observe.
Got it.
Thank you, sir.
Who is it?
It’s me,
Ruotong.
Yizhong.
Where is Junxia?
Follow me.
Junxia.
Yizhong.
Don't get up.
A world-class architect like you
is now in this state?
Give it to me.
Don't laugh at me.
You look good.
You're a professional Kuomintang employee.
How is it?
Can you handle it?
It's alright.
By the way,
I've prepared some sulfanilamide for you.
It's the most effective antibiotic.
Hurry and give it to Junxia.
Be careful.
Yizhong,
you've had it difficult
these days.
Any hardship
is worth it for this moment.
I'm still here.
Don't get too romantic.
Junxia.
I thought you'd died.
I didn't expect
to see you again.
How is that possible?
I haven't attended
your wedding with Ruotong yet.
I haven't heard you call me Brother-in-law yet.
Alright.
Junxia, sit down.
You're still injured.
Yes.
Zhou, why are you here?
You're just going to make me stand outside?
Can't I come in?
I wanted to see you urgently
to confirm who the Cell 8 is.
Hu Zhiping.