[English subtitles are available]
[A Lonely Hero's Journey]
[Episode 8]
Gao Hu, step forward.
Gu Yizhong, step forward.
Combat training.
Gao Hu, you go first.
Go.
Harder.
I said harder.
Gao Hu, did you forget to eat or something?
[Brave and Decisive] [Obey and Comply]
Get up. Get up. Get up.
[Strong and Resilient]
Gu Yizhong, get up.
Look over there.
Who told you to look?
What are you guys doing?
Get up!
Get up! All of you!
Uncle Gu.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
My leg injury has deteriorated.
I felt something was off
when I woke up this morning.
Usually, around this time of year,
Zhaohe would come to check on me.
I'll go get Dr. Lu.
Don't go.
I'm too ashamed to see him now.
With Yizhong gone,
our virtues of filial piety, brotherly love, loyalty, integrity,
propriety, righteousness, probity, and a sense of shame are lost.
Uncle Gu,
what happened to Young Master
might not be that simple.
What do you think?
It's hard to say.
Sit down.
As soon as Yizhong arrived there,
he would be seen as a traitor.
Hong Chengchou was an important official
under the Ming Dynasty.
Once he surrendered to the Qing Dynasty,
he was regarded as a traitor of the Ming Dynasty
for the rest of his life,
and listed as one of the traitor officials
in history.
Since the Japanese occupied Suzhou,
they repeatedly threatened and bribed me.
But I would rather die than comply. Why
is that?
I know history.
I know that I cannot
carry the burden of being a traitor.
Uncle Gu.
Maybe Young Master has his own reason.
Miss Haimo,
I know you're kind.
But...
my son's action cannot be tolerated.
From now on, no matter what happens,
do not talk to him.
This is my request.
I owe you and your father too much.
My 60th birthday is coming next month.
I want to formally adopt you as my daughter
at the birthday banquet.
I wonder if I have this chance.
This is my humble request.
Don't rush to answer.
Take your time to think about it.
Discuss it with your cousin-in-law.
I didn't expect Master Gu
to like you so much.
You are really a genius at what you do.
Cousin-in-law,
I recently was thinking we shouldn't lie to
him.
Others are begging for this chance.
Gu's Garden will be our home from now on.
He wants to adopt the real Haimo,
not me.
What real or fake Haimo?
That girl died long time ago.
Now you are the real Haimo.
Nobody in the world remembers that part.
I can't do this anymore.
I don't want to stay in Gu's Garden anymore.
Where are you going to go?
Master Gu is very ill right now.
His daughter is missing.
His son became a traitor.
What's he going to do if you leave him?
With his health condition, is he
able to survive this winter?
Shouldn't you pretend to
have a conscience?
Did Master arrange
Gu Yizhong to join No. 90?
If we could act this out,
they could too.
I wish it could be like this.
Slow down.
I can handle.
Director.
Close the door.
Don't worry. It's just some scratches.
You'll be okay soon.
Apply hot water when you got the time.
You'll recover very soon.
It's a minor issue.
Our training used to be even
more rigorous than yours.
Let me give you some private lessons.
Please do, Director Zhou.
Blending in is the most difficult skill for
a secret agent.
It's not about how smart the that person is.
It's about how stupid the opponent is.
Do you know my background?
During the 1927 Revolution,
I became a member of the Communist Party.
My superior was called Gu Shunzhang.
Back then, a group of young fellows
at your age followed him.
We devoted ourselves to the cause,
and were committed unconditionally,
hoping that one day we could make changes.
Then I got arrested.
I was tortured for seven days and nights,
and almost died.
Someone came in to persuade me to surrender.
Do you know who that person was?
It was Gu Shunzhang, that bastard.
He betrayed us.
I never thought
that he would betray us.
From that day on,
my heart died and I lost hope.
Then you joined
CBIS in 1932.
Who told you that?
Among the four departments of No. 90,
the intelligence department is the most
unreliable.
Those idiots.
Come on, tell me.
Tell me everything you know about me.
You made your success under Xu Enzeng
in CBIS.
In 1939,
No. 76 agent headquarters was established.
The first big case solved by Mr. Li
is to arrest
all the CBIS personnel in Shanghai-Suzhou
area.
There were over 40 people.
The only one who escaped was the District
Chief, Xu Zhaolin.
A man who was arrested at the same time
was also the deputy District Chief
named Zhou Youren.
Director Zhou,
that must be your alias.
You really are someone who studied abroad.
Go on.
It was a big headline
in Shanghai News.
You can find it
in the photo resource room at the station.
Director, I want to ask you.
Are you
working against
or working for them in No. 90?
You really are a talent.
You are wasting your talent in No. 90.
You should really be in No. 76.
Go work for Mr. Li.
You haven't answered my question.
Director.
How should I put it?
Today in No. 90,
or the entire Wang government,
which one of them is sincere?
Including Zhou Fohai, Chen Gongbo,
Minister Ding and Mr. Li,
in my opinion,
they are all there to please the Japanese
and Chairman Wang.
Then do you know
why everyone is so focused?
It's simple.
Money, power.
Mr. Li once said
if we can catch big fish by the river,
why should we go inside the river
to catch the small fish and shrimp?
Yizhong, it's good that you're here.
We will catch big fish together.
I'm not interested in money.
You're too young.
Still too young.
If you didn't accuse me
of being Cell 8,
I wouldn't have ended up like this.
Yizhong.
You know that I didn't mean to do it.
Let me put it this way.
I thought you were a student.
You'd surrender in less than a few rounds.
You're good.
Not only did you not give up,
but also you made it to No. 90.
I'm quite impressed.
Yizhong, come here.
Have a seat.
Let me tell you something.
Something from the bottom of my heart
that could put me in danger.
No. 90
is just a place
where we met by chance.
The Japanese will eventually get kicked
out of Suzhou.
By then, this place will still be ours.
I don't care whether the future government
belongs to Jiang or Wang.
I don't care who you'll listen to in the future.
I want to be your friend.
I mean it.
Really?
Yes.
Can you tell me
who is Cell 8?
In the end,
you're still working for the Communist Party,
aren't you?
I'm working for myself!
Cell 8 has almost killed me!
I need to get rid of him quickly!
I really underestimated you!
You are more stubborn than your father.
Don't blame me for not convincing you.
Get out of No. 90 as soon as possible.
Or else,
you'll die in No. 90.
Director.
What?
Can I stop monitoring Gu?
He knows
every move I make.
I can't do this anymore.
I can't do it.
Don't you have a gun?
Kill him.
If you kill me,
will he kill you too?
[Director of No. 76 Agent Headquarter and
Pacification Operation Committee Secretary General Mr. Li]
Mr. Li.
Kondo, how are you?
Not good.
Sir Kondo has been concerned about
the magistrate of Wu County.
Guo Jingji has been dead for so long.
You still can't find a candidate.
Chairman Gao of Jiangsu Province
specifically called me,
saying that if you don't make a decision,
he will.
I came to Suzhou
just for this matter.
Got it.
I still recommend
Wang Zemin, who I mentioned to Sir Kondo.
First, it's because this man
is widely known in Suzhou.
The people admire him.
He can't do it.
He's greedy and corrupted.
Those
are just slanders.
Wang Zemin is very rich.
His family is loaded.
How could he use the magistrate position
to make more money?
If you hire him,
I will get rid of him.
Alright.
How about this?
No. 90
won't make any proposals.
Mr. Li,
tell the Civil Affairs Bureau
to propose a candidate.
Zhifei.
Although "pacification" operation bureau
of Kunshan, Changshou and Taicang
report directly to the Pacification Operation
Committee,
the work of "pacification" operation
needs a lot of local support.
That's why
all local agent stations
should participate in the selection
of local officials.
It's also something that the highest leader
has endorsed.
We ought to follow.
Got it.
Mr. Kondo.
Gu Xixing.
If Gu Xixing is willing to,
he'll be the most ideal candidate.
But the problem is
No. 90 has been trying to persuade him
for six months,
he rejected us for six months.
What could we do?
We can't keep the position of the magistrate
of Wu County
vacant while waiting for him.
How about this?
I think
we can let...
Wang Zemin.
Wang Zemin
will take over the acting magistrate for
a while.
Is that okay?
Gu Xixing's son
is now working for No. 90.
I think this means Gu Xixing
is softening his stance.
You Chinese all care about your reputation.
You want face.
Since Gu Yizhong is willing to enter No. 90,
Gu Xixing could be the magistrate of Wu
County.
That's not necessarily true.
The Yamato people always rise above the
difficulties.
Many examples can prove that.
For example, building a peace government
along the riverside.
Besides, you guys,
Chen Gongbo, Zhou Fohai, Ding,
and you, Mr. Li,
didn't you all get in the water?
That's too much!
Major Kondo.
I won't allow you to slander Mr. Li.
Mr. Li is devoted to the peace movement.
He has always been considerate of Japan.
I hope you can apologize.
Zhifei.
In that case,
I'll leave the candidate of the magistrate
of Wu County
to be decided by Major Kondo.
I have something else to do.
I won't ask Mr. Kondo to stay for dinner.
His name is Cui Yaomin.
He came from Shanghai to meet us.
He claimed that he could buy quinine with
his connections.
You got it?
He's not our man.
He is a middleman.
He's a student of the famous Du Yuesheng
from Shanghai.
After Du Yuesheng fled to Hong Kong,
he was appointed to take care of
everything at Shanghai Pier.
It is said that he has many connections.
Chongqing and Nanjing
both respect him a bit.
Is this two-faced person reliable?
With money, you can ask him to do anything.
It works on him.
I found him
through a connection in Shanghai.
The old scalpers were either arrested or
fled away.
Only he has some connections
who are willing to deal with us.
When will he arrive?
Tomorrow.
Two in the afternoon.
Caizhi Pavilion Tea House.
Okay.
I'll meet him
by then.
Bring a copy of Jiangsu Daily.
He will have a copy of Shanghai News
in front of him.
He wants money.
No matter what price he offers,
say yes first and we'll discuss it later.
Our priority is to buy quinine.
Yes.
Mr. Li, did you see that?
I said I wanted to stay with you,
but you sent me to No. 90 in Suzhou.
How did he treat me?
The Japanese.
He looks down on us.
Zhifei.
You've never
worked at No. 76.
Not to mention a Japanese Major,
even an ordinary soldier
can piss Ding and me off.
Peace National Movement.
We must be firm.
What should we do with Wang Zemin?
We'll make things work out sooner or later.
Let's put it aside
for now.
A few days ago,
I asked Jinhai to send some gifts to your
residence.
They're from Wang Zemin.
I received the gifts.
Ask him to stop sending them.
It's okay.
If wealthy people like them are willing to
contribute,
just let them do so.
It doesn't matter.
I think Kondo
is the most troublesome.
He just wouldn't listen.
I told him Gu Xixing
is stubborn.
He wouldn't listen.
Gu Xixing.
He doesn't consider the face of Chairman
Wang.
He's just a Japanese Major.
What can he do with it?
If he wants to try,
Just let him do it.
He'll come back to you
once he reaches a dead end.
By then,
he will understand
that this is China.
If he leaves us on our land,
the Japanese won't able to
do anything without us.
Right.
Let these Japanese understand
that nothing can be done
without our support.
What are you doing?
You got the wrong person.
Xinzhai.
Why are you in such a hurry to see Sir?
Mr. Kondo went out early in the morning.
Did the big fish confess?
Why are you running?
Why are you being so distant?
Mr. Li is here.
He came to Suzhou for work inspection.
Director and Mr. Kondo
all went to Li Mansion.
That's strange.
Didn't they invite you?
Section Chief Lian, you're joking.
They...
The man's name is Cui Yaomin.
He's from Shanghai.
I heard that he's meeting someone
from CPC tomorrow afternoon.
What else did he confess?
That's all I heard.
Huang Xinzhai asked me to leave.
Yizhong, get changed quickly.
We got operation.
Where is my gun?
You weren't given a gun.
Where are we going?
What is the operation?
It's a secret.
[Sino-Japanese Relations]
Gu Yizhong.
Where are you taking the prisoner?
A secret operation.
What secret operation?
Cui got a lot of intelligence to offer.
[Sino-Japanese Relations]
Take him back.
Vice Director Huang.
It was Director Zhou who wanted to interrogate
Cui.
Mr. Kondo is waiting for me
to interrogate Cui.
Take him back.
Let the Japanese wait then.
Let's go!
I'm not going.
Go!
Sir,
Cui Yaomin confessed
that he made a deal with the New Fourth Army
to trade quinine.
Quinine?
Quinine.
If we investigate him,
maybe we can find
an information network of intelligence.
Even Lian Jinhai takes credit for it.
Sir, I felt very wronged.
Zhou told me that Cui Yaomin
was going to meet someone from CPC.
It might be a big fish, Sir.
Zhou said this is
a good opportunity to test if Gu Yizhong
is still colluding with the Communist Party.
I agree.
Gu Yizhong doesn't look like an accomplice.
That's not important.
Right.
What matters is whether
Gu Xixing takes part in the peace movement.
Now Gu Yizhong is a bait.
It doesn't matter if he works for the
Communist Party.
It doesn't matter if he saves people
from Communist Party.
As long as he's exposed,
we can use him
to threaten Gu Xixing.
Yes.
Li, come with me.
OK.
Gentlemen,
please enjoy.
Sit down.
Where are you going?
I want to pee.
You'll have to pee later.
Do you know the guy
who was beaten up like a pig?
Cui Yaomin.
Today we're catching
the communist who is planning to meet him.
I don't know if it's a real operation
or a test.
Gao Hu, let's switch seats.
Why?
Let me see that pig head.
What did you tell
Huang Xinzhai last night?
Nothing.
I don't know about anything.
I'm just here to pass a message.
You'd better not know anything.
If you dare to lie,
I'll cut off your tongue.
Sir, who are you looking for?
Is it him?
Mr. Hao has booked a room.
Mr. Hao, it's on the second floor.
The second floor?
Yes.
Allow me.
This way.
Here.
[Caizhi Pavilion]
Wait for me there.
See you next time.
Thank you.
A copy of Jiangsu Daily.
Okay.
[Newspaper Pavilion]
Waiter.
I want some water.
OK.
Here's your tea.
Are you blind?
I'm sorry.
It's so hot.
Are you blind?
Who are you yelling at?
You can't even get this right.
[Newspaper Pavilion]
Are you blind?
Can't you stop?
[Caizhi Pavilion]
We're here for an operation.
Are you blind?
Who are you scolding?
What's the big deal of being an agent?
Enough.
Are you done?
I'll tear your mouth off!
Stop it!
Do you know who we are?
Who are you scolding?
So what?
I'll tear your mouth off!
Come on, do it.
Do you know who we are?
Get that woman!
Cui Yaomin is running away.
[Caizhi Pavilion]
Where's Cui Yaomin?
Where's Cui Yaomin.
Go.
It's a misunderstanding.
Just a misunderstanding.
Section Chief Lian, Cui Yaomin wasn't able
to run away.
It's a misunderstanding, Section Chief Lian.
I just wanted to pee.
I didn't want to run away.
Close the door.
Everyone, back to your seat!
I didn't flee.
Trust me.
Gao Hu, stand up.
What operation?
What was that all about?
It's none of my business.
The waiter poured hot water on me.
Waiter, come here.
Come here.
I didn't mean it.
I got tripped.
Get lost.
Sit down.
Gu Yizhong.
You're profound.
Don't assume that I don't know
what you're up to.
I'll get you sooner or later, Gu Yizhong.
Back to No. 90. Now.
Take Cui Yaomin away.
He,
how was it?
How was the meeting?
Is Xiao Ruotong back?
Xiao Ruotong?
She's been upstairs the whole time.
Take care.
Xiao Ruotong, what's wrong with you?
Who asked you to go to the tea house?
Do you know
I was on a mission today?
Following me?
You lack organization and discipline.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have followed you today.
I violated the rules.
I accept all punishment from the
organization.
You know you violated the rules.
You'll be punished.
But I also want to thank you.
If you didn't go today,
I might not have a chance to come back.
I saw Gu Yizhong today.
He was with No. 90.
Based on your relationship with Gu Yizhong,
it's understandable
that you don't believe he's a traitor.
Ruotong,
I hope you to be rational
in this matter.
Eagle went to meet Cui Yaomin today,
and almost got arrested.
Gu Yizhong was
among the agents in the operation.
Are you sure?
I knew that Gu Yizhong
didn't die a few days ago.
Eagle has informers too.
He saw him going back
to Gu's Garden with people from No. 90.
I couldn't prove it at the time,
so I didn't tell you.
He's not dead.
Then why did my dad
hold a funeral for him?
Father, you knew
that Gu Yizhong was still alive.
Yes.
He went to No. 90 to be a traitor.
You knew that too.
Yes.
Dad, I don't understand
How could you let him do that?
What is a traitor?
That's a lackey of the Japanese.
You told us about the four social values
and eight virtues since we were young.
To be filial piety, brotherly love, loyalty, integrity,
propriety, righteousness, probity, and a sense of shame!
He became a disgrace to the Gu family.
Take a look at this.
This was from when we were kids.
You still kept it?
Do you remember this?
[Practice makes you famous, reasonably reassured]
These are Yizhong's shoes when he was young.
You bought them for him
when he was nine.
Your mother told me
you saved up pocket money for a year
in order to buy these shoes.
He wore these shoes
and ran around the street,
yelling
"My sister bought this pair for me."
Since young,
you've been protecting and helping him.
You were afraid he'd get hurt.
You even helped him in a fight.
I don't understand
now that you've grown up,
how did things end up like this?
Father.
I have my belief,
and my responsibility.
Right.
You have your belief.
I won't stop you
from your anti-Japanese work.
But if
you still think me as your father,
promise me one thing.
What is it?
You have to promise me.
Huizhong,
you are a mother now.
You should know
parents and siblings are connected by blood.
No matter how great the belief is,
we can't live without family.
We cannot abandon family.
Keep these shoes.
Remember,
no matter when,
no matter what,
Yizhong will always be your brother.
You are his sister.
[Who is number eight? 90.]
[If you don't get in touch with me within a
week, I'll make it public]
We might lose the clue of Cell 8.
Don't we have
his dark secret contact?
I contacted him twice,
but no reply.
Could it be that he hasn't returned to
Suzhou?
No.
He is in Suzhou.