才会见面, mais segur地 tratar你。
I am your wife,
Liu Zhao Yin.
Hey.
Su Heng,
how long are you going to keep me in the dark?
You're drunk.
I found him.
Si Wen?
Where is he?
He said
you were married,
so he disappeared.
Impossible.
He won't disobey me.
He gave it to you.
Liu Zhao Di,
thank you for your brief contact.
But now you have a family,
you should start a new life.
I wish you happiness,
and a long life.
Si Wen is dead.
Tell me where he is.
I'm going to find him.
You can't escape.
I can't make the decision.
Let me go.
I'm going to find him.
You've been married for half a month.
I treated you like this.
Why did you humiliate me?
I didn't mean it.
You bastard.
What did you say?
Let me go.
Say it again.
I said you're a bastard.
How dare you insult my finger?
You're narrower than me.
How bold you are!
Prudence can kill you.
But a heart is selfish.
What do you think?
Help me!
We can't go any further!
Master!
Go!
Help me!
Master Su...
Go and get your child out.
What are you doing?
Try it.
Master, what should I do?
Hua Er, call your father.
Hua Er, call him!
Hua Er...
Father!
Father! I'm Hua Er!
Father, come back!
Father!
I'm Hua Er! Come back!
Go on.
Father!
I'm Hua Er! Come back!
It's fake!
Come back!
Master Su...
He has a wife and a son like this.
Master Su, what about that lunatic?
Take him to the Zhou Manor.
What did you see when you were unconscious?
I...
It was all me.
I couldn't see anything.
No...
There seems to be a monster.
No, it's a ghost.
It must be a ghost!
Liu Qingsong died in this way.
Do you remember who I am?
You gave me this scar.
Scar...
Siwen?
Master, I was wrong.
Please forgive me.
I'm here to solve cases.
I'm not here to search for the city.
Sit down.
I just need to know
what happened to Liu Zhaodi.
After we got married,
Liu Zhaodi has been very protective of me.
I...
I hit him several times.
I also beat him several times.
Then he ran away.
He ran away overnight.
He rushed back to the old house of Shan Yixian.
He ran away.
At that time,
his mother had gone to the Beishan Temple to get married.
His father also married a concubine.
That concubine gave birth to a son for the Liu family.
The Liu family finally has a son!
Let's call him Xuan'er.
At that moment,
he realized that the Wu family was precious.
When Wu Lu died,
he was taken in by a monk.
Miss.
Miss, wake up.
I'm sorry, Master.
I'll leave now.
Miss, are you hungry?
Come.
Eat.
Thank you, Master.
Eat slowly.
Master,
whose children are they?
At that time,
it seemed peaceful.
But there were many people
who couldn't afford to raise children.
I picked them up.
There are not many good people like you.
They are lucky.
Some parents
will send their unborn children
to the Eagle Mountain Tower.
There is no chance of survival there.
Have you been there?
I have been there a few times.
There are many accidents.
Some children have very small feet.
Most of them are female.
If there is really a Buddha in this world,
I hope he can help these children.
You have a new friend.
Master,
you have a new friend.
this is...
This is Lv Yi.
She often comes here to see children
and bring them food.
Just call me Lv Yi.
Lv Yi, I am Liu Zhaodi.
It seems that Lv Yi and Master
are all admired.
You are called Zhaodi,
but you are a man.
Different thoughts.
Let's try it together.
Children, come and eat.
Come on.
Zhaodi has been hiding
in Shangshan Temple for several months.
I found him.
Children, I brought you some delicious food.
You are here.
Master,
I am here.