Zhaodi, I saw your letter.
I'm sorry.
I didn't leave with you half a year ago.
Are you still mad at me?
You're right.
If we had really run away,
we might have been in jail.
They said you went to Yuezhou.
Your general must have been worried about you.
You're going to the general's house soon.
That's good.
I'm happy for you.
I heard that you and your daughter...
You two are very close.
I don't know about the others.
If I say I'll take you away now,
will you be willing to?
If you tell me now that you're taking me away,
how nice would that be?
I'm happy for you.
It's really snowing.
Zhaodi, I wish you a happy and prosperous year.
Today's winter snow is also a good start.
What did you say?
I said I wish Siwen a happy and prosperous year.
You're right.
I'm happy for you.
I wish you a happy and prosperous year.
After we met for the last time,
I left the Red-Eye.
Yin Zhao Tianning made me leave the Sword Realm.
Then no one wanted to find me.
I understand.
Xu Tian, Xiao Shen Po, Yu Wen Xian,
are those three children.
Those three children.
Then why did you kill Xian?
Later, I moved into the west of the city.
I was a secretive citizen.
I did a lot of illegal business.
Life became very beautiful.
But until a year ago...
You...
Are you buying cloth?
Xian.
Zhao Di.
I'm sorry.
You're useless.
You kicked me out.
This is some money I saved.
Take it and start a new life.
I'm still a prostitute.
What else can I do?
I've figured out a reason.
As a woman,
you always rely on men.
Some people rely on children.
But in fact, the one who should be the most dependent
is yourself.
From the perspective of a prostitute,
anyone can reason with me.
Anyone can scold me.
Right?
Xian.
Brother, you're here.
I told you before.
We don't kill people.
I didn't ask you to kill people.
Just cut his hands off.
You're so cruel.
Why?
He took all my hopes in Yihong Restaurant.
Now he can live on his own hands.
It's not fair.
Miss,
it's not enough.
I'll pay you.
Is it enough?
Enough.
Now they can exchange.
Let's go.
Miss, you'll pay us.
I'll find out what Xian did in the end.
What are you doing?
From that moment on,
I can't play the flute
or walk in the sand.
No!
But my brother is dead.
And Uncle Yu.
No!
The End