[tvN x TVING original drama]
[Cha Joo-young and Lee Hyun-wook]
[This drama contains product placement and virtual advertising]
[Director Kim Sang-ho, screenwriter Lee Young-mi]
["Yuan Jing"]
[This drama is a secondary creation of historical figures and events and is purely fictional
Strict production guidelines were also adhered to when filming child actors and animals.]
The Higan Temple is the one that died in the year of Wuyin.
The place where the two princes and their husbands prayed for blessings
[Previous Situation]
This is a country of sexology.
He invited His Majesty to personally attend the temple renovation ceremony
Don't you think there's something fishy?
I will first strengthen the vigilance
[Previous Situation]
[Higanji Temple]
Block any armed persons at the entrance
[Previous Situation]
I will guard it strictly and not let any mouse get in.
Emperor Yao once said
[Previous Situation]
[King Lee Seong-gye (father of Lee Bang-won)]
God appoints a king
I don't love the monarch alone.
But for millions of people
What does your Highness mean?
What should we do for these millions of people?
I'm just thinking about this question for a while.
I am so grateful to be able to summon you to such a significant occasion.
I am very grateful to my father.
What is it?
That's what's in there
Not Qinduo
Must stop
Absolutely not
Your Highness...Your Highness
Empress of the Middle Temple
-The Empress of the Middle Temple
-Your Highness
Catch quickly
[Catch and arrest]
Is this God's will?
stop
I order you to stop.
All retreat
What is the purpose of killing the son and father?
You go back now
Father, do you really want to take your life?
I order you to go back.
But please, father, continue to preside over the Qinduo Offering Ceremony
What
Father, please look at the common people.
How can people be willing to follow
A monarch that his father wanted to kill.
You have the nerve to call yourself a commoner
Just you
God appoints a king
For all the people
Then I will continue this offering ceremony
Waiting for the grand offering ceremony to be completed
Then he captured the Supreme King
[Episode 3]
Madam, why don't you try to turn your shoulders?
I will ask the pharmacy to ask the queen to take the medicine well.
It will get better soon.
Understood
Is it really okay?
The royal doctor said it.
Just a scratch.
My father's hammer flew towards me with precision.
In front of all the civil and military officials
Taking advantage of the moment when I show my filial piety
How did the Middle Temple know?
The qinduo box contains a hammer.
My father wants to kill me.
How did the Middle Temple know?
this…
I also learned about this by chance.
Please don't worry, Your Highness.
[Kaegyeong Shouchang Palace]
Who is helping?
I really can't bear to use foot amputation
[The punishment of cutting off feet]
So I hope you can tell the truth
Who is helping?
Hurry up
Little one doesn't know
Your Highness
You see clearly
It's your turn next.
Straighten his face so he can see clearly.
Without help, this would never happen.
Who is
Little one doesn't know
Tell the truth
Home... Don't copy
Didn't you just say don't copy it?
[The family copied the most elite private soldiers in the palace of King Taejo Lee Seong-gye]
Um... yes
good
There are also people who copy other families in the Three Military Offices
[The Three Armies are composed of the Central, Left and Right Armies
Early Korean Central Army Organization]
So
After killing the widow
If you don't rob the house, you will take over the palace.
Northeast side
The other families are also gathering around Zhao Siyi's men.
[Relatives of Queen Sindeok, the second wife of Lee Seong-gye, Cho Sa-eui]
Is this what the Supreme King intended?
yes
Why
His Highness ordered to gather all the troops
They will march southwards to attack Kaifeng
Father
Fangyuan is here
As a monarch, you are even willing to stain your dragon robe with blood.
I'm afraid my father can't go anywhere now.
Your father shouldn't have given birth to you.
yes
Why did my father give birth to me?
Why raise me?
Why do you want to teach me to read and write?
Why should I be so proud when I passed the imperial examination?
Asshole
It was my father who made me like this.
Father's hand always points to the highest position
I always thought that was what it meant to go all out.
This is how I climbed to this position.
Why should I criticize my father's painstaking guidance?
Why are you denying it now?
Yes, I will deny you.
You can't do it now
It won't work in the future.
You'll never make it.
Father
I will definitely
I'm gonna kill you
Let everything that is distorted return to its original state
From now on, father can only live in this palace
You can't even take a step out of the palace.
My father wants to be in this palace
Look at how outstanding this son who was not chosen by his father is.
Father, please watch
My father will understand the person who killed Fang Fan Fang Shuo
Not my son Fangyuan
The father himself
Father will definitely understand.
Asshole
Your Highness
My Lord asked me how I knew about the existence of the hammer.
How did the lady answer?
This palace said it was a coincidence
The Lord did not ask any more questions.
[Lijiang Jun Min Wujiu, the younger brother of Queen Wonkyung]
Why not take this opportunity
How about handing over our Min family's spy organization to the master?
No
[Licheng Jun Min Wuji, the younger brother of Queen Wonkyung]
Once it is submitted, it becomes a public organization.
By then, it will be difficult to grasp the movements of those meritorious officials and clan members.
Pan Zhu's organization is spread all over the country
To distinguish between friend and foe
You need to know who is dealing with whom
The spy organization and the financial resources to support it
This is the strength of our Min family
Perhaps it would be better to keep it a secret from the Master for now.
good
Now doesn't seem to be the time
It seems to me that the Queen Mother
Let His Majesty be so lonely
I will comfort Your Highness.
yes
You are the only one left to me
I will guard your Highness.
You all should back off.
It's the queen
Now there's no one outside.
Your Highness, you can release yourself and I will guard you.
Although there have been many disturbances recently
But when the King offered the qin-dak to the Hyeam Temple
[Father of King Lee Seong-gye and Lee Bang-won]
I have already prayed for the future of this dynasty
yes
Sentence
[Official position in charge of criminal prosecution and prison]
Minister in
I heard rumors that something shameful happened at Higanji Temple.
I order you to find the mastermind of the rumor and punish him severely.
It's your highness.
Know about
[The secretary who conveyed the imperial edict]
Minister in
The Middle Temple believed in bizarre rumors
Not only did it bother the father who was trying to offer the zither to the Buddha,
It also ruined the rare chance for reconciliation between me and my father.
This is obviously disrespectful.
Therefore
I order you to take charge of the proposed process of deposing the concubine.
[Deposed Queen]
Your Highness
The Empress's Servant Xu Shanggong
The maid came in
The slaves are terrified
I heard that His Majesty summoned the Lord to
Order him to discuss the process of deposing a concubine
Empress of the Middle Temple
His Highness is just worried that the incident at Higan Temple earlier would make the Empress angry.
This is why we are preparing to deliberately denigrate
No need to make a fuss
Empress of the Middle Temple
Lijiang Jun and Licheng Jun ask for an audience
Xu Shanggong
What is going on?
How could His Highness depose the concubine?
[Chengen Shanggong Ringtone]
That is to say
Someone is coming to the palace
Yeah
They are the younger brothers of the empress.
Then I'll stay here.
Wait until you see the queen before you leave
If the Lord is not crazy
Why would you mention the deposed concubine?
Licheng Jun, be careful with your words
Be careful with your words
Your Majesty, how should I be careful with my words?
If it weren't for the Queen
The master died under that hammer a long time ago.
But he wants to depose his concubine
That's the father killing his son.
Your Highness does this
Isn't it just to prevent the news from spreading?
How can this be stopped?
Besides, the only way to stop it is to depose the concubine.
The Central Palace
If it goes against the wishes of His Highness and his father, you must abandon it.
Your Highness wants to show your filial piety, right?
It's like killing two birds with one stone.
Your Highness needs a title to succeed the throne.
Isn't it ridiculous?
Don't even think about how we treated him.
Why don't you shut up?
My brothers are terrified
It's strange
Suppose that day was tragic.
The Lord really died tragically under the hammer of the Supreme King
The heir to the throne should be the eldest prince's son.
But
How could the Supreme King want to let my son Ti'er succeed to the throne?
And wield the hammer
That being said…
The lady means someone is helping
There must be a powerful force in the palace to help
I heard that there are also people in the Three Military Offices who have their own family
The lady is referring to them.
A person who can use these home copies
So
king
The king is brave and good at fighting
I fought on the battlefield with my father.
[King Yi Banggo (Jungjong, the second brother of Yi Bangwon)]
Among the family copies of the Three Military Office
Aren't there still many soldiers following His Majesty the King?
So
The King was also involved in the incident at Higan Temple
Shhh
Madam, this is what you mean
This palace is just guessing
only
If the Queen can already guess this
Wouldn't the Lord know?
My Lord, you don't want to think so.
After all, this means that we will have to raise the knife against our own brothers again.
Empress of the Middle Temple
So
My brother remembered something.
I heard someone
Meeting with Jia Biechao in the Three Military Offices alone
This person has burn marks on his face.
It should be Yuan Fan
[Yi Seong-gye's confidant]
Go find him in secret and don't let the news leak out.
Find out who he's been in contact with.
Empress of the Middle Temple
Cheng En Shang Gong asked for an audience
The Queen's Servant Ringtone
I came here because I was worried.
I will never leave this palace
You don't have to worry about it.
yes
When the servant reported the matter of the deposed concubine
The queen was not moved at all
But what can I say
This servant has also served the Empress Dowager.
You should always do your duty
Your Highness, please don't be in such a hurry to leave.
May I ask you to report this to your Highness?
I am only going to pray for the souls of my brothers.
No need to report
The Grand King is also waiting for His Royal Highness
Your Highness goes out like this...
Nothing
Don't come out.
I will serve you again in the future.
It's not my own idea.
Has this happened to me?
Blame you
Although the queen said...
But he never got close to his servants.
Please allow me to serve you as closely as before.
Empress of the Middle Temple
You have already received the favor
No longer my personal maid Cai Ling
Niangniang
The slave is just a ringtone
The ringing bell that had served the queen for many years in the residence of Chudong
[Chuldong Qianseong, the residence of Yi Bang-won before he ascended the throne]
Even if I dedicate my body to the Lord
My heart still belongs to the queen.
The servant has not changed
you…
It's changed
Now, His Majesty wants to discuss the matter of deposing the concubine.
There is also a lot of discussion among the people
[The filial palace lady Yeong-sil]
Everyone says that His Highness is filial.
Abandoning the Wife of the Poor
Abandoning the Wife
This will never happen.
I know your Highness well.
Unpredictable
Who would have thought that the Queen would rest here today?
I want to erase the central palace from the master's heart
But I don't know what to do
My lady, don't worry, just wait quietly.
The past Jing'an Jun period
[Title of the prince during the reign of Prince Jeongan Lee Bang-won]
Why did His Highness want the Queen?
Naturally because of freedom
Men will eventually abandon those women who can't resist
As long as this is good for our little prince
How's the safflower rouge you mentioned last time?
You can buy it soon
Oh, my lady, she is so beautiful even without dressing up
If I put on that expensive rouge
She must be like Yang Guifei reincarnated.
I want to give birth to a prince
What
I must give birth to a prince
I have to give birth to a prince while I am still young and beautiful.
I have to keep on giving birth
Would you like to help me?
Cheng En Shang Gong needs to endure
good
I will endure it
In this way, the Yang energy will gather in the lower abdomen.
Wait until the Yang Qi gathers in the lower abdomen
When His Majesty's Yuan Yang entered the body of Consort Cheng'en
You can stay for a long time
This makes it very likely that you will get pregnant.
It's Jin Shanggong
Why is Your Highness here?
The Supreme King has been looking for me
I know in my heart that I am waiting for the Supreme King
What will the Supreme King order?
[Southern Expedition to Li Fangguo's Confidants]
Just left the palace for a while
Those who died for me on the battlefield in the past
The tablet is here
His Highness the King
I have thought about
If I come to Hades Palace again for the same thing
[The Palace of Hades, a place to pray for blessings in the afterlife]
How should
Your Highness, don't you feel wronged?
The throne was taken away by Fangyuan
Your subordinates will definitely find it back for Your Highness.
The subordinates want to regain the throne
Just waiting for your Highness' orders
All subordinates will prepare
The most important thing is that this is also the intention of the Supreme King
[Father of the Taesang King Lee Seong-gye, Lee Bang-won and Lee Bang-gwa]
I don't want to see any of you die again.
Why does Your Highness only think about sacrifice?
His Highness the King
The glare of the sun
If the sun is scorching
I have to hide in the shade temporarily
I am just worried whether the shade of the tree will last forever.
Are you worried that I will be deposed?
Why would the Queen say this?
Don't worry too much
anyway
I will take good care of all the princes.
[Yi Ti Ryung Grand Prince]
[Prince Lee Boo Hyo-nyeong]
[Prince Yi Seok-chungnyeong]
[Li Bo Jingningjun (son of the filial palace master)]
It didn't take long for the child to be enlightened
Quite a lot of progress
The father promised his son
After finishing a book, you will receive a reward.
Yeah
My father also praised me and gave me food.
I also gradually find reading interesting.
So
well done
The Queen Mother praised me for doing a good job.
Yeah, well done.
Did your father really reward you with food?
yes
The Queen Mother of the Central Palace has arrived
You don't have to follow me anymore. Just stay here.
Earlier, when the incident at Higanji Temple occurred
I once asked the middle temple how he knew there was a hammer in the box.
At that time, the middle temple replied that it was a coincidence.
In the past, when the private soldiers were reformed
I clearly told you not to keep spies privately.
But the Queen Mother has been hiding the fact that she has been raising spies.
So, is this the reason why His Highness mentioned the deposed concubine?
I have only been on the throne for a short time and my regime is still unstable
The Central Palace and the Min family of the Central Palace disobeyed the imperial decree
How can I tolerate such discussions in the court?
It is because of this that we can help our master escape from trouble.
Please stop now, Central Palace.
From now on, I will face it myself
Solve it yourself
Can Your Highness be so sure of distinguishing between friend and foe in the court?
The bloody storm still remains everywhere
Your Highness, since you have experienced it, you will naturally know
Who were loyal to the previous dynasty?
Who are loyal to His Majesty the King?
Who are loyal to His Majesty?
Do you have confidence?
Can quietly identify all these people
What does the palace want to say?
Your Highness, please think about it.
If that day was tragic
His Highness really died tragically under the hammer of the Supreme King
nave
How could my father act like this without any preparation?
Wouldn't Father make plans for his afterlife?
nave
His Majesty the King
Your Highness had already guessed it.
But deliberately avoid
So the middle hall is to call me
Do you regard your father and second brother as enemies?
I want Your Highness to calm down and see the reality clearly.
Wait until His Highness is sober and calm enough
It won't be too late for me to clear out the spies.
Does the Central Palace want to completely ignore me?
I said I would face it myself.
I said I would solve it myself.
I am the ruler of a country.
I said I would handle it myself
Your Highness
If the Queen really thinks I am the ruler of a country
So I stopped there
If you dare to mention His Majesty the King again
I will never let you off easily.
Hearing that His Highness is on a hunger strike, His Highness is very worried.
I want you to call the king.
Call the king
[Yi Seong-gye's confidant]
Yuan Fan came here on the orders of His Majesty the Grand King
The Northeast will raise troops as planned
[Southern Expedition to Li Fangguo's Confidants]
Isn't the King under house arrest in the palace right now?
Your Highness had already expected this.
Your Highness has his own plans
So
All the families in the three military headquarters must be gathered together.
to this end
The king needs to give a signal
His Majesty the King...
Undecided
I don't know what to be afraid of
Let's do this then
Present our signed secret letter to His Majesty
[Signature with palm print]
How to send it
Since the last incident at Higan Temple
The palace was heavily guarded
There is a way
Tell me about it
Secret summons from Nanzheng Mansion
There were many ministers who were once members of the Imperial Court.
What
Oh, our Palace Master is becoming more and more favored.
I have the opportunity to live in a house like this
Ouch
welcome
I've been waiting for you.
That's safflower seed rouge
These days, it's priceless.
Oh, is that so?
Then this one
this
Oh ok
Let me see
It suits you too.
Yeah
And this
Oh, you
In addition to this
ah
for you
I found this after searching all over Baocheng.
If you use it to clean your private parts
That's a must.
Ah, scared me
Who is it?
You asked me to deliver this item to the Upper King's Palace to the Mishan Palace
[From the palace of the king to the palace of the secret palace, the palace lady who serves Li Fangguo (the king) personally]
good
What is this
You don't need to know this...
The King has sent messages many times to find His Highness.
World Trouble
His Majesty is at peace.
The king is worried
You don't know yet
The matter that troubles this king has not yet been exposed.
What is this
The servant is worried
So I cooked some porridge and brought it to
Porridge
I remember the time in the Chudong Cave.
The Queen Mother relies on black sesame porridge to regulate her spleen and stomach
Improves appetite
Oh, Chengen Shanggong is really sensible
Empress of the Middle Temple
Cheng En Shang Gong brought some black sesame porridge
Want to announce?
Xuan
This servant belongs to the Empress Central Palace.
in this way
Would you like to hear the Lord's thoughts?
Tell me
Would you like
So, can this servant serve the Queen closely?
good
The slave is willing
His Highness will be here tonight
The reason why His Highness came to see Lady Chengen is because...
I know
His Majesty has arrived
No need
Has Lichengjun visited the Central Palace recently?
yes
Lijiang Jun Licheng Jun
Both of you have been there
What did they talk about?
It seems that they talked about His Majesty the King.
How to say
I didn't hear it clearly.
After all, their voices were very low when they talked in private.
About the King
You need to tell me everything.
yes
That's it.
If you are as careless and impatient as before
I'm afraid it will ruin things.
What to do on the bed
Just hand it over to His Majesty.
I heard that the Lord stayed at Cheng'en Shanggong's place tonight.
Where is the Lord staying?
As the Queen Mother, I must know this.
The Queen taught me
It's late at night
Madam, why don't you take a rest first...
I know.
Go down
yes
don't want
Asshole
You'll never make it.
I'm going to kill you.
Let everything that is distorted return to its original state
Your Highness
Your Highness, please relax and lie down comfortably.
Aren't you sleeping?
Slave...
Rather than falling asleep facing His Majesty's back
Why not use the dim moonlight?
Sit here
Staring at His Majesty's face all night
You were a servant in the palace.
Later she entered the palace and became a personal maid
yes
Later, Cheng Le En became Cheng En Shang Gong
You are so ridiculous that you ask me to come to your place twice a month
So you get a lot of things, right?
This servant has not yet won the favor of His Highness.
You can't have one foot in the nave.
One foot is here.
Your Highness
You can't make your own decisions
Just send the messages you want to send
It is absolutely forbidden to know without reporting
Everything needs to be reported to me for decision.
Do you understand?
Why not answer?
If the slave agrees
Your Highness, would you like to believe
Everyone still thought that I was still a member of the imperial palace.
I believe
The Widow
Willing to believe
If the slave does this
What will His Highness promise me?
I will give myself to you
Put yourself...
Deliver to you
All right
My Lord, you are serving me well.
yes
My Lord, have you ever been unhappy?
There was no sign of
The Lord sleeps peacefully.
Quite capable
You actually filled the vacancy in this palace.
I dare not
The slaves are just following orders.
You go down
It seems that the opportunity has come for the Queen Mother
The second brother is referring to the Ming envoy
yes
It turns out that the queen knows all
If the Ming envoys come to look for the Supreme King
It would be difficult to discuss the matter of deposing the concubine.
-yes
Go to the Lord and make up your mind.
yes
only
Being too aggressive is probably not a good idea.
The Queen Mother
Just don't know
Can the King be released from the palace?
The movement in the northeast is unusual.
Ask Panzhu to listen carefully to the news
The Queen Mother
this...
Should I hand it over to His Majesty the King?
good
besides
this...
What is this
A small gift
No need
To Mishan Palace
His Majesty has arrived
Your Highness
I heard that the Ming envoys were about to arrive in Kaifeng.
How are the preparations for hosting the Ming envoys going?
The palace conventions have always been prepared by the Empress
But now they are still discussing the matter of deposing the concubine.
It is to welcome the governor to say that preparations are complete.
[A temporary organization established by the Welcoming Supervisor to entertain Ming envoys]
I am also worried that something might go wrong.
The Ming envoy expressed his wish to personally meet the Supreme King
Understand the situation clearly
They said they wanted to see the Supreme King to find out the situation.
Its real purpose is to pay tribute.
At present, Zhu Yunwen and Zhu Di are fighting fiercely.
The most needed thing is a war horse
[Zhu Di (Emperor Yongle) was defeated by his nephew Zhu Yunwen (Emperor Jianwen) during the Jingnan Campaign
The war for the Ming throne]
But if we pay tribute to Zhu Yunwen directly,
Zhu Di will hold the power one day.
I must make plans early
I think we should delay time to see the war situation clearly.
Only His Majesty the Supreme King can do this.
Hearing that the envoys came
When His Majesty the Supreme King was in the northeast
He has a close relationship with His Royal Highness the Supreme King.
But
Is His Royal Highness willing to come forward?
Your Highness, why don't you order the Highness to come forward?
Long before His Highness ascended the throne
The Queen has been mediating between His Highness and the Supreme King.
Your Highness wants me to go and see my father in person.
Convince your father?
What does the Central Palace want?
I am willing to go
only
I grant you the title of the middle palace
Mr. Supervisor
The matter of abolishing the concubine was stopped
We have to set a date for the bedtime
The Queen's menstruation has stopped for eleven days.
[Monthly period refers to menstruation]
But tomorrow is the day of Si
It is not good on Si day, nor on Yin day.
The first and the thirty-fifth day of the lunar month are all unacceptable
So when can we
Why not wait until next month...
Can't wait till then
This official observes the celestial phenomena
Worried about thunderstorms in the near future
snort
How about today?
Today?
Si and Yin days are not good.
The first thirty ten...
Not fifteen either.
No thunderstorm either.
Why did Zheng Shanggong suddenly
There is still a little mist...
That's it.
Let's set it today
How can there be such a rule?
Rules are based on needs
You stay here
I heard that the chief envoy of this mission is my father's close friend.
Many years of friendship
Reuniting with a Lost Friend
I think it can also relieve the fatigue in my heart...
Nonsense
The envoy will ask us to pay tribute of 10,000 fine horses.
But it takes some time to prepare properly.
Please give me some advice, my father.
You plan to observe the situation of the Jingnan Campaign
While dealing with the Ming Dynasty's request for tribute
So I want to ask you to buy some time
If this is the case, why doesn't the Lord come forward?
And it was the central palace again.
After all, the incident at Higan Temple came first.
The Lord may feel a little embarrassed to meet his father
besides
My Lord, I feel that since I was in the palace
He had a close relationship with his father.
That was the royal palace period.
Now he is on the throne
There are things a king should do
There are things that the nave should do
how
Are you going to use the guise of Dawn People again?
Teach me a lesson
No Father...
Didn't you secretly think
The world of North Korea belongs to your Min family.
Why did the father say this?
It was your Min family who pushed today's master to the throne.
Father
The master originally listened to you in everything.
Only in the future
Will there be no more blood?
Why did my father say this to make me feel so frightened?
The King's Affairs
Father
I called him here.
What does the father want his son to do?
Die
Father
[Preview of the next episode]
The Shang Gong on duty will give a signal every hour.
According to the signal...
The central hall just needs to do as it says.
Just follow and obey unconditionally?
My intention is to ask the middle palace to learn to be smarter.
It seems that they will eventually rebel.
The grief of having to kill his son
It is the righteousness of the widower
Second Brother
Spare her life.
Only the nave.
Your Highness, please kneel before me.
Please spare her life.