The
the
The beauty is in the wind and frost, where is the peace?
The
beauty is in the wind and frost, where is the peace?
The beauty is in the wind and frost, where is the peace?
Since foundation Radiant
Dou sorrows
Let the Earth wait for an opportunity.
I am sick
區諾大人
After we arrived in Angelaít justice
you okay withoque
亞國人談判
Xiao Zhi Yi Lie Dong Zhi Yi 10
will puts time on everything his family is willing to do.
Aren't you the Imperial Guards?
Why are you here as the wedding dresser?
Who are you watching?
I was originally...
just a white dog.
I was lucky enough to follow you.
The fire five years ago,
I was going to die too.
Fortunately, there was a doctor to help me.
I only had a piece of my butt.
The book is right here.
Don't talk.
Listen to me.
Who is it?
Sorry to disturb you.
You guys continue.
Continue.
You are indeed a rich and rich lady.
Tong Guang,
when did you start to worry?
I was just a servant.
Who told you to promote me?
I was really happy.
Listen to me.
I'm not the one.
Do you really like her?
Then why don't you kill her?
She's alive.
For the two of us, she's a shadow.
Say something.
A while ago,
there was an hour of time
that I wrote a poem about.
I really liked it.
I remember the green gourd tree
in the garden.
It looked like you when it cried.
Suddenly,
I couldn't stop myself.
Stop lying to me.
I'm a living person.
I'm standing in front of you.
You don't even touch me.
He Dong Wang said
he saw you and him get away from each other.
You treated me
like a monster from start to finish, right?
You're just like me, right?
I hate the blood
on my own back.
Do you want me to say it?
Yes.
I can't rely on you too much.
Because I have inferiority complex.
I just did a great thing.
I want to be the prime minister.
You're the most brilliant and famous
in Sha Xi Bu.
The most noble woman in the palace.
And I...
I'm a son.
If it weren't because you're too lonely,
what right do I have to stand by your side?
I'm sorry.
I really can't do it.
Father.
I'm sorry.
I won't do it again.
I won't force you again.
Just this shoulder.
Just sometimes
let me lean on it.
That's enough.
The master is back.
I don't know the morning and the night.
The family is the most rare.
I'd rather die in the hands of a beauty.
I'm not even crazy about being a ghost.
Why so many years?
This is...
Cousin?
Oh, it's cousin.
No wonder there are so many nails.
No wonder the nails let us
go to save people.
What's your cousin's name?
Cousin Guixin?
Her name is Ren Ruyi.
She went to the country with us.
She's also responsible for the teaching of the prince.
This is Qian Zhao.
She knows a little bit of everything.
This is...
This is not important.
I'm too important.
My name is Yu Shisan.
I know more than Qian Zhao.
Cousin, why do you look so pale?
Are you not feeling well?
Yes, she's badly injured.
Let her see.
How did the wound
get into the blood of the doctor?
She's a bad person from Chu.
She's a bit of a stranger to the doctor.
Drink it.
Cousin is a good sister.
I admire her.
But why isn't cousin talking?
Is she...
Is her throat injured?
She just doesn't want to talk to you.
Don't be afraid.
I'm very interesting.
Okay, let's go.
Okay.
If you can do it,
I'll ask Yu Lang to buy you
three bags of Zhangji Yi Gou Song.
Really?
Really.
Okay.
Ruyi,
what's wrong?
This is very delicious.
Nothing.
It reminds me of an old friend.
Thank you.
Why
don't they suspect my identity?
Because you brought it with you.
And Brother Qian showed you the medicine.
That means they think you're one of them.
You believe him that much?
He asked us to die.
I won't blink.
He's that good?
Of course.
We think of our family name.
Mother is a great teacher.
I heard she was a woman in the palace.
In terms of literature,
she can get into the imperial exam.
In terms of martial arts, she's the best.
She's a good fighter.
She's the first one
who became the vice-president at the age of twenty.
How can that be bad?
Even if she's married,
there must be hundreds of women
in our six halls.
Really?
There's a saying
you must remember.
Never fall in love with a man
in your life.
But you must have
a child of your own.
You're finally talking.
I'm worried.
I didn't expect
you to be so good.
Don't call me that.
Don't be so cruel.
Today is a beautiful day.
It's the first day
you and I are going together.
The Saeless
is waiting.
The Flute is serious.
Following the Sa fabulously,
the Flutist sits down."
See you there, SaButi.
Hmph That'smarked.
Beware of yourή
Ohh
Romilot
He's coming.
OK, Immortal.
Here.
about the
Go.
Toer.
Toer, why do you think they started fighting like that?
A bridegroom has to be a master even if he is brought in by a wolf.
Otherwise, it will be a mess.
I understand.
Toer, you are the first wolf, and Ru Yi is the second wolf.
Brother Qian is old, so he is the old wolf.
I am young, so I am the young wolf.
What about Brother 13?
The second wolf.
I am not the second wolf.
I want to be a wild wolf with a manly charm.
Your Highness, this is Ren Ru Yi.
I hired a bridegroom for you.
He knows everything about Angu.
From today, he will teach you.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Qingshan.
Lord Ning, why don't you discuss it with us and change the person?
Because you are incompetent.
I can't teach him well.
How dare you!
I am the empress's own child.
I was born with Princess Xunyang.
Send the bridegroom back to the capital.
Yes.
What are you doing?
Let go of me.
Lord Ning, what's going on?
You have no choice.
This is not a discussion.
This is a notice.
Yes.
I... No, I...
I asked him to teach me.
This is my order.
You...
I...
What are you writing?
Which great figures are there in Angu?
You will memorize them later.
Why aren't you afraid of me?
You were so timid before.
You were so hesitant.
Why did you ask me to stay?
Tell me.
Because you can control the maidservant.
The maidservant is very strict.
She hit you?
Let me look.
I didn't know that people are like this.
Why didn't you tell me?
I was afraid you would find it difficult.
The maidservant was trying to remind me to listen.
Yuan Lu.
Send a message to the person you sent back.
Before you go back to the capital,
the six pagoda's vows,
you must not miss a single day.
Yes.
Why are you crying?
Lu Yi.
I already told you.
Thank you.
And these years, I haven't seen Ying for a long time.
I was careless.
You don't know the tricks of women in the palace.
It's normal.
I happen to tell you.
In addition to the business team,
there are many brothers in the delegation responsible for protecting her.
After that, in the delegation...
You don't ask me how to teach her.
You don't need to ask.
Since I chose to let you teach her,
I will not doubt her.
Moreover,
who can understand Anguo better than the human race?
I have been leaving Anguo for five years.
But you have been doing Baique for five years.
Isn't that enough?
I didn't finish just now.
In order to avoid trouble,
in front of the delegation,
I said you were the female member of the six pagoda.
But in front of the thirteen pagodas,
I said you were a bad person of Chu.
Why don't you tell them directly
that I am Baique of Zhu Yiwei?
Because I guess that
in this world,
there is no woman who wants to be
sold out by others.
You are the same.
If I have to go to the five pagoda,
I don't want to become
Baique who is sold out by others.
By the way,
especially Qian Zhao,
she hates Zhu Yiwei very much.
She must not reveal her identity.
Lord Ning,
you are really thoughtful.
The King of Chu
Tell me, how many tribes do you have in Anguo?
I know this one.
There are three tribes in Anguo.
There are Sha Xi, Sha Dong, and Sha Zhong.
Which tribe is the one
that is saved by the second prince?
It is...
Sha...
Xi...
The one who was taken by Anran
in the Tianmen Pass war,
how many cities does he have?
From tomorrow,
I will tell you
an extra hour after dinner.
If you go out again,
I will give you 100 times more.
You are so kind.
You are a little girl.
A little girl.
Little prince.
Isn't Ruyi and the prince in good conditions?
Why is the prince crying?
The one who is a teacher will be in danger.
Although Ruyi punished the prince.
It doesn't mean that he will be happy with the prince.
Let's go.
Your Highness.
Please.
Please drink this cup.
Wrong.
A man should drink like this.
Continue eating.
I...
I...I have a bad appetite.
I can't eat.
Then go to the backyard.
Turn around for an hour.
Okay.
Do you think I'm too cruel to him?
No.
You are cruel to him now.
It's better than being cruel to the people of Angu after you arrive in Angu.
Besides...
Forget it.
Make it clear.
Besides, I believe that you must have suffered more than him.
You must have suffered more.
But time is short.
He is still a child.
If he can learn one tenth of you.
I will be satisfied.
You are so nice to me.
I'm not used to it.
It was before.
Now we are in the same boat.
Of course it's different.
Really?
Anyway, there is no one else now.
Why don't we sit down and drink together?
Let's talk about
how to make a toast.
I have an alcohol problem.
I can't drink cold wine.
Then I will help you to
heat it up.
I will help you to heat it up.
I will help you heat it.
I will help you to heat it.
Let's take a break and continue.
Okay.
Why are you so obedient?
Because when I first saw you,
I liked you.
I will definitely listen to you.
No.
As a princess,
you are so bad at dating.
You should listen to her.
This can only mean
that you have been used to
following others.
You don't dare to resist them.
My mother and
the female officers taught me that.
They said that a woman should
be treated with respect and kindness.
I am a princess, I should be treated like that.
Otherwise, I will never be able to get married.
Who said that a woman
should marry?
You are a princess.
You can be alone and be free forever.
But
if I don't get married,
who will take care of me?
Who will play jokes with me?
How can I have a baby?
What's so good about marrying?
You can't be someone else's wife.
You have to suffer for a hundred years.
If you don't get married,
women can also have their own children.
But
people say that
I need to find a good husband.
This is the most important thing in my life.
They are lying to you.
No.
I know.
But my sister-in-law will never lie to me.
She also told me that.
Really?
Then do you know
that Empress Xiao
wanted to send you to the netherworld?
Don't say that.
She treats me so well.
She treats you well?
She knew that you are a princess
but she asked you to dress up as a man
and go to Angu.
Are you really blind to those officials?
I can't even tell that you don't have a husband.
You only have a
good-looking wife
and a bad-tempered woman.
I...I am
a woman who is too hasty to die.
When you see Prince Yan,
you can tell him.
Let me tell you the truth.
Prince Dan Yang
doesn't want your brother to come back safely.
He wants to see
your brother's body.
Then he can be
in a good mood.
The Empress doesn't want to save your brother.
She just wants to hold him for a few more months.
When the child is born,
she can respect your brother as the crown prince.
No.
She called herself Empress Dowager.
As for you and your brother,
it's best to be locked
in the dark prison of Angu.
After a few years,
they will die together.
That's why it's called being happy.
You lied to me!
You don't believe me? You can ask him.
Brother Yan Zhou.
You shouldn't have told him that.
I just want him to wake up earlier.
At least he won't be a fool in the future.
Yang Ying,
listen carefully.
If you don't change your
temperament right away,
you will really die.
Use all your strength to eat
and get fit.
Try to learn.
That's your only way to survive.
Brother Yan Zhou,
is what he said true?
呀
young
winter
The first is the first in the East, the second is the first in the West, and the third is Li Cheng Yuan.
He's making progress fast.
It's true that Xia Meng is also going to be the first.
Hurry up. The wind is blowing.
Hold it well. Be careful.
How's the food?
Don't worry, sir. It's ready. This way, please.
I'm so hungry, Brother 13. How long do we have to wait to get to the border?
We have to get to Lingzhou first, then Jiangcheng, and then many other provinces.
Let's just take it as a free meal.
What are you looking at?
A beautiful woman's car is shining.
What are you talking about?
I'm hungry.
Let's eat when you're done.
Sit.
What's wrong, Your Highness?
I'm in the infirmary.
Where is the infirmary?
Your Highness, this way.
Sister Ruyi, what should we do?
I think I suddenly...
That one.
The person who serves you has never prepared anything for you.
This time, I came out in a hurry.
I think it's been a while.
Can you help me find something useful?
Please. They are all men.
Thank you, Sister Ruyi.
Give me a horse.
Sure.
Your Highness, this way.
I'll go by myself. You don't have to serve me.
Yes.
Your Highness.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Go get some water. I need to wash my hands.
Please wait.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, what's wrong?
I'm sorry.
I'm not feeling well.
You can go ahead.
Sir, I'll go check on her.
Who is it?
It's me.
Hello.
Are you all right, Ying?
Brother Yuanzhou,
I have a stomachache.
Wait for me. I'll get Qianzhou.
No need.
I...
I'm not sick.
Sister Ruyi went out to find something for me.
You can help me get the hot water from the other side.
Brother Yuanzhou,
please help me taste it.
See if it's hot.
This hot water...
Is it supposed to be this sweet?
It is.
Here, drink some.
It's still hot.
Put it on the table for a while.
I want to drink it after I wake up.
If you feel uncomfortable,
call us anytime.
Okay.
I'll go.
I...
You're awake.
I'm addicted to the medicine.
Not me.
Otherwise, you wouldn't be able to wake up.
It's the princess.
It's an accident.
I didn't expect that she would be so bold.
Qianzhou just blamed me.
She gave you the medicine.
She even added a soft gold to you.
Maybe I scared her with my words that day.
She didn't want to.
She just wanted to run back to the capital
and ask the queen and the king about it.
She's really a busy old master.
She's really embarrassed now.
Please help me call Yaorou and the others.
They're all confused now.
I'm the only one who can move now.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Do you want to know what kind of person I am?
I'm not actually from Angu.
I was sold to Zhu Yiwei when I was very young.
I'm not worth anything.
I just use the land to make a living.
I got the heart.
I grew up thinking that
I wouldn't be so bad without a good family.
That's why I added a human heart.
It's not easy.
My benefactor said the same thing.
He's the old friend I asked you to investigate
who killed his murderer.
The queen of Angu.
The queen?
Didn't you get punished because you killed her?
Zhu Yiwei's life is like a day in the dark.
She's the one who treats me the best.
In my heart, she's like a mother.
How could I harm her?
I went to the Apothecary House that day
to save her.
You're a silly child.
You don't know anything except being an assassin.
There's something you must remember.
Don't fall in love with a man in your life.
But you must have a child of your own.
Go!
She just told me
to leave Zhu Yiwei
and live a happy life.
She also said
not to fall in love with a man in your life.
But to have a child of your own.
So you changed to be a man.
I pretended to be dead
and escaped to Shengzhou.
I was in a house where my daughter's mother was killed.
A few years later,
Zhu Yiwei went to Shengzhou to pick a white dog.
The people there didn't recognize me.
They caught me.
I wanted to take the opportunity to investigate
who killed her.
I was so angry that I went back to Zhu Yiwei.
It's a good thing.
But don't worry.
As long as you call His Highness,
I'll do my best to help you investigate
who killed the Empress.
Thank you.
But I will definitely fulfill
Her Highness's wish.
So,
what about my child in the future?
Good memory and good listening.
Ren Xiaochuan's name is cute.
But don't you think it's a bit like my name?
And this is your business.
You don't have to tell me this.
Although the child is mine,
you also have a name.
Just take it as a souvenir.
What do you mean I'm also a man?
No, did I just...
No, it was just a moment.
I won't force you to do something you don't like.
Are you serious?
Calm down.
I'm not you.
Don't worry. I'm very calm.
Actually, I've decided it's you.
You have good martial arts and a high head.
The child will not be like you or me in the future.
You don't have a family.
Give me a child.
It won't hurt other women.
If you go to Angu,
if you die halfway,
I can leave you some incense.
Such a beautiful thing.
How good.
What do you mean?
I wanted to seduce you little by little.
But I didn't expect you to be so kind.
Since it's like this,
I'd rather not see you again.
No, calm down.
Listen to me.
I won't give you a child.
I just want to be with the one I like.
I want to be with the one I like.
How dare you say that you don't love me at all?
Don't lie.
The most popular thing in Baique
is to touch the heart of men.
I know
why you've been so gentle to me recently.
You're kind.
First, you deliberately neglected me.
Then you find a chance to mention my past.
Care about me, pity me.
In this way, I will be more careful to you.
Lord Ning,
you're really thoughtful.
I...
And your body
is also warm.
What warm?
You're right, Ren Ruyi.
I'm too thoughtful.
If you give me a child, you'll suffer.
How could it be?
It's good to have a child like you.
Don't worry.
The mother lion on the grassland
has always been hunting and raising children by herself.
As long as the male lion cooperates,
as long as you cooperate well later,
as long as it succeeds,
I won't investigate you again.
I'm not a lion.
And let me tell you,
I'm a fool.
My family is gone.
The child thinks I'm not delicious at all.
The child is...
What a coincidence. I am too.
Just accept it.
At most, I'm at home.
This...
After I'm at home,
I'll protect the princess.
Is that okay?
I don't need it.
Ren Ruyi.
You're robbing the man.
You shout.
Guards.
Ren Ruyi is crazy.
They're all confused.
They can't help you.
It's no use if you don't shout.
Listen to me.
Calm down. Listen to me.
I'm poisoned.
I'm really...
Listen to me.
How could Zhang Song let me take the princess and the gold
and leave the capital so easily?
Before I left, he made me take the jade and the gold.
I had to take the medicine from him every time.
Now is the seventh day I set out.
The most poisonous hand.
You can see it yourself.
See it yourself.
It's okay.
I have the poison of ten thousand poisons.
It can cure the poison of the world.
With him, I can't hurt the child.
But I'm not in a good mood right now.
Even if I succeed once,
the child may not be enough.
How about this?
I promise you.
But give me two more days.
When I take the first dose of the antidote,
I'll make sure you succeed.
I promise you.
Heart-shaped butterfly.
I'll believe you when you use it.
Okay.
I'll take it.
Now, can you help me take the antidote?
The antidote is in the water.
There's not that much.
Come on.
Ren Ruoyi!
Okay, I won't bother you now.
The mountain is closed, the sword is drawn.
Between the rivers and lakes,
life and death are different.
Who is the next one?
The king and the army are alone, there is no regret.
Once, the soldiers were with the moon,
high in the spring wind.
Once, the soldiers were with the moon, high in the spring wind.
High in the spring wind.
Who drinks a cup of snow, the blood turns into ashes.
Who sighs for a moment, the sky is scattered like water.
Looking back, the future is so beautiful.
The world is so beautiful.
Who will stay with me for the rest of my life?
Who is the one who worries about the future?
Who hopes that dreams will come true,
only for the coming of the wind and the coming of the wind.
Who is the one who cares about the future?