=Fate's Crossing Nan & Ke=
=Episode 11=
It can't be him.
What's wrong, Ke?
Nothing.
I haven't devoured
such an easy dream in a long time.
Shen Nan did well
by showing Luo Xinyao the truth.
Otherwise, it would have taken me
some effort to solve her problem
with "A Dream of Millet".
Why?
"A Dream of Millet"
is made with one's lifeblood
and fueled by the soul.
Naturally, it would require some effort
to devour the dream it creates.
Ke.
I see my lantern there.
It must be tough for you.
Don't say that.
It's my duty.
Have you ever thought about leaving?
I've promised
to stay here forever for someone.
I won't go back on my word.
Is that person very important to you?
I would assume.
I can't remember.
Why?
On the day I became
the guardian of Wangchuan,
my memories were taken away.
I've been cultivating diligently,
hoping that one day
I can mend my own dream.
It's just a pity
that after hundreds of years,
I can only recall some vague images.
Perhaps I haven't tried hard enough.
Ke, don't be sad.
Rest early.
We're meeting with Mr. Mo tomorrow.
I've sent someone to turn him down.
We have rules here.
If someone needs help,
they should visit in person.
They expect me to go to them?
You just said
you weren't trying hard enough.
How come you're putting on airs
to a guest now?
People come in person to seek help.
I never make house calls.
Ke, where are you going?
Just taking a walk. Don't worry.
It is said getting drunk
dispels a thousand worries.
But why does the wine
taste more and more bitter?
What's wrong?
You wished for immortality as a kid.
Your wish has come true.
Are you happy?
Suffer centuries of loneliness
for someone I'll never meet again.
Ridiculous.
It's really ridiculous.
- Did you have fun?
- Yeah.
- Let's come again.
- Nice booze.
- So pretty.
- Go take a look.
Miss, are you alone?
Join us for some fun.
Let's have fun.
Get lost.
She's got a temper.
Interesting.
I like it.
What are you looking at?
She's a tough one.
Knock it off.
Come on.
Shen Nan.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm here.
I'll take you home.
♪Years go by and wind back again♪
♪I take up the pen,
illustrating you in my memories♪
♪Unfulfilled emotions
in this unfinished song♪
♪Have two cups of wine
to fulfill the heart's desires♪
♪Flowers by the Wangchuan River
haven't withered♪
♪In my heart, they remain♪
♪The fate of past and present
is like clouds, like smoke♪
♪Blown by the wind, yet it stretches on♪
Are you okay?
Sorry.
I'm losing power
as the full moon approaches.
I can't lead you into dreams these days.
It's okay.
Just be careful and stay safe.
If I hadn't gotten there...
It won't happen again.
I was careless today.
I caused you trouble.
I'm so sorry.
I got you injured.
Name it if you want any compensation.
♪Wait for the flowers to bloom again♪
It's you. I knew it was you.
Shen Nan.
You can't just hug me.
That's very rude.
What's so funny?
I've finally found you.
It's the same knot from 15 years ago.
So stop denying it.
♪Despite the vicissitudes of life♪
Fine.
I am that woman.
I am the one who saved you 15 years ago.
I am the monster that never ages.
Are you happy now?
Any more questions?
If not, you can leave.
I'm going to rest.
I'm injured.
You did it.
You...
When did you become such a scoundrel?
After I met you.
♪Yet hard to complete like the moon♪
I'll stop teasing you.
I'll leave after you fall asleep.
I'm not a child
who needs a lullaby.
♪Wait for the flowers to bloom again♪
I've worked on some cases.
The assaulted girls
have stress responses at night.
You may have it, too.
♪Deep affection never fades♪
I'll wait outside.
Go to sleep.
♪One more drink in the mortal world♪
♪Just like we just met♪
♪It's the attachment I can't wear down♪
♪Despite the vicissitudes of life♪
♪It will not change♪
♪Wait for the dew
to tint the cooking smoke♪
♪We meet again by the pavilion♪
♪There's always
a longing that never ends♪
♪The unfinished oath♪
♪Fearless of parting♪
♪To be with you in the next life♪
♪One more drink in the mortal world♪
♪Just like we just met♪
♪It's the attachment I can't wear down♪
♪Despite the vicissitudes of life♪
♪It will not change♪
♪The fulfillment yet to come♪
♪Is the undying destiny♪
♪Years go by and wind back again♪
When did he leave?
I didn't hear him at all.
I've finally found you.
It's you. I knew it was you.
No way.
I can't let him hold onto this anymore.
Ke.
Check on that tree in the backyard.
This tree
has come alive?
♪Years go by and wind back again♪
♪I take up the pen,
illustrating you in my memories♪
♪Unfulfilled emotions
in this unfinished song♪
♪Have two cups of wine
to fulfill the heart's desires♪
♪Flowers by the Wangchuan River
haven't withered♪
♪In my heart, they remain♪
♪The fate of past and present
is like clouds, like smoke♪
♪Blown by the wind, yet it stretches on♪
♪I only wish to be with you♪
♪My life goes without regrets♪
♪Wait for the flowers to bloom again♪
♪I'll hold your hand♪
♪It is the longing that never ends♪
♪Through joys and sorrows♪
♪Deep affection never fades♪
♪No longer fearing the future lives♪
♪One more drink in the mortal world♪
♪Just like we just met♪
♪It's the attachment I can't wear down♪
♪Despite the vicissitudes of life♪
♪It will not change♪
♪The fulfillment yet to come♪
♪Is the undying destiny♪