auch
Do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do
Ooh, Nia
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Nia
Come on, guys, get ready
Feel the music
Breathe in and out, feel the floor
Two, three, four
Five, six, seven, eight
One, two, three, four
Go, two, two, left
Two, one, down
Seven, three, two, three
Four, turn
Six, seven, eight
Go, one, two, three, four
Five, six, seven, eight
Two, two, three, four
Five, six, seven, stop
Music
Hello, Kai Qi
Why isn't Luo Man here?
Did she say she would come?
I saw her asking you where you were going to class yesterday
I thought she would come
She was just saying
She's so early, how could she come?
Try this, it's really popular lately
I saw a lot of celebrities and celebrities sitting around
Thank you
How are things between you and Zhong Zun?
Did he contact you?
There are too many people today, I can't take care of them
I'll treat you to a meal next time
I love you
The play is already like this, who doesn't understand who's thinking?
And now you're sending this kind of message
It's so funny to have a piece of cake early in the morning
Okay
I didn't contact her
Maybe I'm not her type
I think she likes Luo Man more
How could you be everyone's type?
Boss Zhou is in good terms
Her ex-wife is in good terms too
Although Luo Man is my best friend, you know that
I'm not her type
We all say that we shouldn't use women's age and appearance to measure their values
But who doesn't have a sense of sense?
Luo Man is already very good to ordinary men
But I think she can't get rid of Zhou Mosheng
Even Luo Man can't get rid of her, I can't either
I'm not much younger than Luo Man
I'm still a little bit young
You're 25 years old, you're in your prime
If you're too young, men won't think about you
Where's Mrs. Chen? She hasn't come out yet?
What's wrong?
Someone called Mrs. Chen, I thought they were calling me
Your husband's name is Chen too?
Yes, my husband's name is Chen Mian
Do you know him?
I'm sorry, I don't know the company
It's okay, it's a small company, you don't know them well
Do you want to go up and play?
No, I can only make instant noodles
Instant noodles?
I don't remember what instant noodles taste like
Every day I think about how many cards I have to play
I can't stand it, let's see what I can do
No, these two are too demanding
You're too stingy
No
This is the first time I've seen someone make double cups at home
So amazing
I like to make these
I've always thought that the happiest flavor in the world is the taste of home cooked food
Your husband is really lucky, he's so nice
He doesn't think so
He always complains to me, he says you have to help me do this and keep my figure
What do you want?
I think he's stressed
I've never seen a perfect woman like you
She's beautiful, generous, gentle, she can cook, she can cook
How amazing is that?
You're good at talking
It smells good
Are you Mr. Zhou?
I just said he was interested in you
My roommate
He forgot to bring the key, he wants me to open the door for him
I'll ask the driver to send you there
No need, I'll just take a taxi
Thank you, Sister Kaixi
You're welcome
Then we'll meet again later
I'll open the door for him
Okay, see you
See you
I'm leaving, bye bye
Why are you here?
I'm so bored
This is my roommate
He's generous and generous
He's like Zhou Musun
He's so particular
He's not delicate, he's willing to spend money on himself
He's so generous
I'm so familiar with this kind of man
Chengcheng
Be good
I'll bring you something to eat
I'm afraid it's this kind of man
That night, my father followed a woman
He didn't come back
Mom
Do you remember what I said?
Women
Have to rely on themselves
Hello, new friends
Hello
What do you want to perform?
Perform...
What can I perform here?
How about I tell you a joke?
Okay?
I'll think of something funny
I have an idea
I used to be a good singer
I used to have a hard-working Zhu Guoli
He called himself Zhu Guoli Bang
Every time he encouraged himself
He would say Zhu Guoli Bang Bang Bang
It's not funny, right?
I'm sorry
I'll think of another one
What's this?
So many
Thank you, brother
Brother hasn't stopped
Thank him
Thank you, brother
What's your name?
Wind chaser
Thank you, wind chaser
I'll see you
Thank you
I want to see you now
Wind chaser
Sit down
Hello
You scared me
You chose a good place
I passed by the bun shop
I bought three buns
Do you want some?
No, thanks
You are...
Wind chaser
Yes
What's this?
Beef and scallion
If it's with chives, it's better
It's my taste
Xia
Sorry
We don't serve outside
We have everything you want
I'll go to the place you chose
How far is it?
Upstairs
I don't believe it
Show me your phone
Is it connected to your wifi?
Then...
Have some water
With ice
I can eat buns
Brother, how about you order an hour?
That's okay
Do you want anything?
No
Brother
Brother, come
I don't want to waste food
I'll order a bun with rice and a bun with fries
But you can tell the chef not to cook
I'll eat my buns
Is that okay?
Yes
I think it's good
That's it
Thank you
And
Don't call me brother anymore
Thank you
Okay
No, brother
I'll order it right away
You're not kidding
What do you do?
Wait
It's nothing
Well
My roommate and I
We started our own business
We used a social media app
We were lucky
And we got the promotion
We got it right
But then
I became the manager
In my daily life
I listen to other people's reports
And I fool others
I was so bored
I thought you guys
Would eat fish and salad
With black coffee
Rich people are not fools
Yes
I'll answer the phone
Please
Go ahead
Okay
Okay, I got it
There's a media interview tomorrow
I confirmed some details
Actually
I hate this kind of thing
You have an interview every day
No
It's arranged by PR
But I think
It's stupid
I'm not a celebrity
Why do you interview me?
My users don't buy my products
Because they like me
And
Those companies that like to show off
Usually have problems in the present
I think
The most comfortable thing in the world is
To avoid those fools
And make money without thinking
And then spend it
That's great, right?
Yes
I think
The whole process is boring
But there's one thing
I think it's interesting
This reporter came from abroad
I asked my assistant to book him a hotel
A five-star hotel
You know
It's not worth much
After he finished
He can play for a few days
Have a nice weekend
I think this is interesting
Yes
Don't talk about me
You do it
Me?
I'm just a ten-line actress
It's hard, right?
Okay
Why not?
I'm talking about you
The director is looking for you
Sorry
You're waiting for him, right?
Hurry up
Sorry
Sit down
Sorry, I'm sorry
I'm sorry
Hurry up
Camera
Yes
Camera, one, two, three, four
Camera
Hold on
Hurry up, the patient is getting faster
Camera
Hold on
One, two, three, four
Just like you watched my live show
My friend was too poor to watch it
So she was lazy to watch it for me
But I don't plan to do that for a long time
You're so boring every day
Yes, I'm boring
What do you think is interesting?
You want to hear this?
You guys shouldn't be interested in these things
Because you're pretty
Hurry up
Okay
I majored in acting
But you don't have to check my acting
You won't find me if you do
Our industry is too particular about resources, connections and luck
But I don't have any of these
Many actors and actresses are now live-streaming
They come fast and easily
Yes
So I don't understand them
I like acting
When I turn on the camera, the camera is facing me
I feel like I can become that character
And you know, every time I have an interview opportunity
I can't sleep at night
I feel like I'm usually lost
But as soon as I start acting, I come back to life
I become a living person
Go on
People say that coming to the big city is for dreams
But I feel that many people are now mixed
And they become living for their lives
I don't think so
But sometimes when I take the subway
I also doubted
What's the point of living like this?
But it's different when I go to the subway station
There will always be a number of suns in front of me
It's like the stage light
The kind that is especially for me
I feel like I'm in the right city
There must be something waiting for me
Don't you think I'm a little unrealistic?
For your dream
I'm going to the bathroom
Okay, I'll take you up
Am I the first person who didn't go to your room to drink water and play cards?
Don't get me wrong
In three and a half years, I have to watch the play of AC Milan
If I go to your room to watch TV
Does it seem that I have no interest?
Okay, let's go
What?
I think you have no time
People live on an impulse
I came to see you today also on this impulse
But I didn't expect it to be the happiest day of my year
Where are you? I'm in the bamboo forest
I'm almost there
Where are you?
I had a video conference this afternoon
It's too boring
I'm sleepy
I'm going to sleep
Come on
Okay
I'm going to sleep
Hello
How are you now? I'm in the car
Don't worry
The more it is, the more you have to hold on
I know
Tell me if you need anything
Tell me right away
Maybe a little bit later
Sorry
I'm writing a script
Tell me when you leave
There are still many highlights in this project
The problem now is that the valuation is too high
The last part is over
No hurry
You do your work
What do you want to eat tonight?
Okay
I'm going to sleep
Are you sure you want to come?
What?
Hello
Did you come down?
No
What is it? I'm so worried
I... I... I...
I want to say
Is this situation really going to go up?
Did you think about it before...
You mean
I'm not going first
I'm not going to sleep
No, no
How about this
You come over quickly
I'll wait for you in the lobby
Okay
Hello
The number you have dialed is not available
How long will it take?
Almost there
There are still a few lights
I'm going to sleep
I'm coming
You're here
Come in
Your sofa looks comfortable
Why are you nervous?
I'll knock you down on the bed in a second
What would you like to drink?
Coke
I'll have sugar free
We all drink coke
What's the difference between sugar free and sugar free?
This sugar free coke
Sounds like a man's mouth
I love you
You talk like a little fart in our hometown
I've been like this since I was a kid
I can't change it
I can't wear a big one either
Why do you want to live in a hotel?
Convenient
It's okay to go anywhere
I mean, why don't you just buy a house or rent a house?
Chen Xiaoting
I think this reason is stupid
When I was a kid
I saw a social news
How Jiang Yi's brother was so popular
How did it shine?
It was particularly impressive to me
The reporter said
This big brother has been living in five-star hotels for four seasons
I thought in my heart at that time
This is the life of my dream
Later, the conditions were allowed
I went to live in a hotel
Of course there is another more important reason
Look
Just over there
Did you see the long-term store?
That is the most delicious bun shop in the city
Bun again
Good for you
Why did you call me here?
Aren't you sleepy?
Jincheng
I want to talk to you
You say
Let's be good
Is it like this?
I never lack a woman who comes upstairs
There must be a man who wants to take you back to the room
We both understand
I asked you to come at four o'clock in the afternoon
Why are we here?
Life is short
I don't want to be rash anymore
I am not entangled
Is it love me or love my money?
What kind of stupid cat am I?
I think money is my home and my home
Which part do you love me?
You love me
Am I right?
How long have they been up?
At most fifteen minutes
I am sorry
Why are you here?
Zhou Muxen asked me out for dinner
It doesn't matter
Have you made up your mind?
If you go up, there is no way back
Don't worry
I didn't want to go up and make trouble
I just want to knock on the mountain and the tiger
Make a joke
Think about it
I don't want to make a fool of myself before the end
I am not stupid
If we get along, I will do my best to help you
No matter in economy or business
And you don't have to be stressed
It's just a man's ability to do what he likes
Especially when I have a family
I can't live without it
You are married?
I am thirty-six years old
I am a year older than you
I didn't see you bring your wedding ring
You mean this?
I went out to play
I kept taking it off
But I really lost it
Qingcheng
I am not a shameless person
You can still declare that you are single outside
I will never interfere with your choice
If one day you meet your true love
I will never stop you
But if you never see it
And you are willing to stay with me
I will make you feel that everything you do is too late
Is it that hard to decide?
Hello, the phone is ringing
The phone
You don't answer the phone
Hello
Hello, where are you?
I am at the office
Hello
Hello, where are you?
I helped you get your suit
I am in a meeting
Can you not call me during work hours?
You are too busy
There is no time to work
Don't bring it back
Give it to Tiao Tiao
Luo Man said he saw you talking to someone in the lobby
I am in the lobby
I didn't see you
Okay
Wait a minute
I will come down
Hello
Did you call the car?
Is it that hard to decide?
Hello, the phone is ringing
The phone
Why are you laughing?
You answer the phone first
It's not good not to answer the phone, right?
What you said was too sudden
Give me some time
I need to think about it
I am leaving
Let me send you down
No, no
It's not good to meet someone in case
Can we meet again?
There is a call
I am in a meeting
Can you not call me during work hours?
You are too busy
Give me some time
I will come down
Hello