Brother.
What are you doing?
The shower in my room is broken,
so I came to use yours.
As for Miss Yao,
I have no idea.
Huainan, I came to see you.
I wanted to see your room
to get to know my fiancé better.
Oh, my.
Isn't this Miss Yao?
Why are you with Qingzhou?
Well...
Soon,
the new mistress of the Song family will be moving in.
Don't act like you used to.
You must learn the rules of this house.
Understood.
Mistress.
Make way.
Miss Yao, you haven't married into the family yet.
They are guests here, after all.
This isn't proper etiquette.
Then what kind of hospitality
is the Song family showing?
Huainan, you trust me, don't you?
You're my future wife.
Of course I trust you.
Huainan.
Enough, Stepmother.
Let's drop this.
You may leave.
How long are you going to hold onto me?
Yao Shengsheng, this is a military building.
You can't just come here whenever you want.
I'm here to see my fiancé
to bond with him.
Do I need your permission?
I'm sorry, Miss Yao.
Entering this building
does indeed require my approval.
Besides,
there is a dress code.
No high heels.
You can't wear your hair down.
And you're not wearing formal attire.
I'm sorry, Miss Yao.
You don't pass.
Come on.
Look.
Make an exception.
Qingzhou.
Brother.
I received a request from Uncle Yao this morning.
He said you want to be my secretary
to get to know me better.
Since you didn't refuse,
I'll take that as a yes.
What makes you think
you can handle this job?
What makes you think I can't?
This isn't playing house.
If you want to be my secretary,
then prove it to me.
And you.
Messing around in the military academy.
Miss Yao has been very forward lately.
Now she wants to come to our academy
to be your personal secretary.
Could this be a setup by the Yao family?
A smokescreen?
Do you want me to investigate?
No need.
She is just a wealthy young lady.
She will leave once she has had her fun.
You are dismissed.
Yes, sir.
Brother.
Go ahead.
How do you plan to test me?
Strip.
Strip searches are usually for men.
Isn't it a bit inappropriate for a woman?
To be my secretary,
loyalty is the primary condition.
I need absolute obedience,
regardless of gender.
Strip.
That's enough.
Didn't I just say that's enough?
Men and women are equal.
I don't need special treatment.
How was it? Did I pass?
To work here,
you still need some fitness
and competitive training.
No.
Why can't I?
Whatever Song Qingzhou and the others do,
I can do it too.
I hope you can hold on.
He isn't trying to test you.
He wants you to back off.
Song Huainan takes this road every day.
Hey, gorgeous.
It's getting late.
Why are you out here all alone?
Do you want me
to walk you home?
Boss,
are you all right?
Who are you?
Meddling in our business?
Let's go, Boss. Forget it.
Let's go.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Thank you for saving me.
Why are you out here
alone so late?
I sprained my ankle.