Miss, please bear with it.
Doctor, how is my wife?
Commander, rest assured.
Luckily, the bullet hit her left shoulder
and missed vital organs.
Once we remove the bullet,
she will recover in time.
Good.
My sister has always been pampered.
How can she stand such a severe injury?
Is your sister afraid of pain?
Since childhood, if she even scraped her skin,
she would cry for half a day.
Let alone a gunshot wound.
You are quite tough, not making a sound.
I've suffered worse injuries.
Huainan.
I'm here.
It's okay. It's okay.
Commander, I will take my leave.
You may go.
Doctor.
How is it going in there?
How is my sister?
The patient is temporarily out of danger,
but her body is still very weak.
Can we go inside and see her?
Yes, you may.
Thank you.
Shengsheng.
How are you? Does the wound still hurt?
The bullet is out.
I'm fine, Brother.
You're so pale, yet you say you're fine.
You've really suffered.
I apologize.
We failed to protect your sister.
It is the Song family's negligence.
Rest assured.
I will do my best to heal her.
Brother, I'm really fine.
Father must have been worried sick.
Go and comfort him.
Huainan is taking care of me. Don't worry.
Brother, let me get
a military doctor for Sister-in-law.
For these knife and gunshot wounds,
military medicine is much better than the hospital's.
Okay, go ahead.
Now that you've seen her,
you should all leave.
Shengsheng needs to rest.
Shengsheng, why are you so silly?
Why did a frail woman like you take a bullet for me?
I only had one thought in my mind then.
I couldn't let anyone hurt my husband.
I'm sorry. I doubted you before.
I didn't realize
that I meant so much to you.
If you doubt me again,
I'll have to punish you.
Get some rest.
I'll check if the medicine is ready.
Come back soon.
Okay.
Two days from now, at the Song house,
send a hitman to shoot Song Huainan.
Dead or alive.
Here is the deposit.
Shengsheng, are you okay?
Shengsheng.
What's wrong? It's Huainan.
Huainan.
I... I just had a nightmare.
It must be the trauma from yesterday.
It's okay. Everything will be fine.
Yao Shengsheng, why are you
resisting me so much?
Yesterday, you risked your life to save me.
But look at you now.
Yao Shengsheng,
I really can't figure you out anymore.
I...
Guards!
Young Master.
Guard the Madam's door.
Without my permission,
no one is allowed to see her.
Yes, sir.
Brother,
why did you lock Yao Shengsheng up?
I locked your sister-in-law up
so she can reflect on herself.
It's also a chance for her to heal.
What's wrong?
Heal?
If during this time,
something happens to her, what will you do?
Don't forget.
Yao Shengsheng took a bullet for you.
You didn't take good care of her,
and even restricted her freedom.
What does that have to do with you?
Song Qingzhou, I've told you many times.
She is your sister-in-law and my wife.
It is not your place to interfere.
You'd better stay away from her.
How dare you...
Shut up.
One more word and I'll lock you up too.
Lock me up, then.
Do you think I won't?
Of course you will.
You wouldn't just lock me up.
You'd even dare to kill me.
Bullshit.
My dear brother.
The day I was chasing deserters,
the one who shot me in the back
was your man, wasn't it?
What did you say?
Adjutant Li has followed you for years,
risked his life for you,
and handles your dirty work.
Who else could make him shoot me
but you?
Brother, do you want me dead that badly?
What the hell are you saying?
If anyone else touched a hair on your head,
I'd have their head.
Yet you think I want to kill you?
That's right. It was Adjutant Li who hurt you that day.
But it was an accident.
I sent him to investigate something else.
Besides, I've already shot him.
Investigate something else?
What was it?
You don't need to know.
Song Qingzhou, let me tell you.
Anyone else can blame me,
but not you.
Everything I've done
is for the sake of our Song family.
If I hear such rebellious words again,
get out.
Marshal,
the adjutant reported that Ambassador Johnson
has matters to discuss with you.
I'll deal with you when I get back.
Second Young Master.
Move aside.
But...
the Eldest Young Master ordered that no one
disturb the Eldest Young Mistress's rest.
Since you call me Young Master,
you should know who the master is.
Get lost.
Yes.
Yao Shengsheng.
So this is your plan?
Hiring someone to assassinate my brother, and then taking a bullet for him?
Aren't you afraid of dying?
You figured it out.
What if something went wrong
and you lost your life there?
You schemed to marry into the Song family.
How far will you go
before you stop?
Until the Song family
pays back everything
they owe me.
If you keep taking risks like this,
do you really think you'll live to see that day?
Zhu Luoli.