Who are you?
Why are you in my room?
I'm just curious.
Why did you leave early?
What I do in my own home
is none of your business.
You're my future sister-in-law.
How is it none of my business?
In that case,
you should learn some respect.
A younger brother looking after what belongs to his older brother,
isn't that only right?
What do you think,
Sister-in-law?
Everyone,
I, Mr. Yao,
have two things
to announce today.
The first thing is,
that the Yao family and the Song family
have reached an agreement
to jointly invest in and run a medicated soap factory.
And the second thing,
is a happy occasion.
This is also something Brother Song and I
decided together.
That is,
I will betroth my beloved daughter, Yao Shengsheng,
to the Song family's eldest son, Song Huainan.
The wedding ceremony is scheduled for next month.
Luoli.
I, Song Huainan, promise here,
that I will make you willing to marry me.
Marriage is a serious matter.
It concerns my lifelong happiness.
How could you decide without discussing it with me?
I'm not ready.
Nonsense.
Is this a business deal?
Shengsheng.
I, Song Huainan, promise here,
that I will make you willing to marry me.
Song Huainan.
This time,
I will turn your promises
into a dagger of vengeance
and thrust it deep into your heart.
I won't let anyone or anything
stand in the way of my plans.
Back then,
if I hadn't happened to pass by,
you would have met your end.
This wine tastes good.
How are things going on your side?
Open the door!
Open up! Yao Shengsheng!
W-What's going on?
Is he looking for you?
Open the door!
Is that person settled?
Of course.
Detective Lin, I'm sorry.
What is it?
Yao Shengsheng!
I have to inconvenience you today.
Wait, that's a huge inconvenience.
You don't expect me to go down from here? It's the third floor!
The man outside has a gun.
I'm afraid he'll misunderstand and the gun might go off.
Yao Shengsheng!
Open the door! Yao Shengsheng!
Master Song.
Is something wrong?
Where is the person who was in your room?
There's no one else in my room.
It's just me.
You are the Song family's daughter-in-law,
my future sister-in-law.
Don't let me catch you having an affair.
Or else I will...
You will what?
I won't let you off.
I'm curious.
Are you jealous?
Qingzhou.
You'd better behave yourself.
Don't play with fire.
Shengsheng.
Brother, look at him.
He accused me of meeting another man in secret,
and tried to ruin my reputation.
I'm warning you.
Stay away from my sister.
And,
don't slander her.
Let's go.
What game is she playing?
Does that punk
have feelings for you?
Brother, I'm tired today.
I don't want to talk about it.
Okay?
All right.
Whatever you say.
Go back to your room and rest.
Okay.
It seems
the Song brothers really like this face.
Next,
I will make the Song family
taste the bitterness of brothers turning against each other
and a household in chaos.
You must be Huainan's fiancée, Yao Shengsheng.
You certainly have the elegance of a well-bred lady.
It's a pity,
you came at a bad time.
Huainan had business early this morning,
so he went out.
When will he be back?
I can wait for him.
That's hard to say.
Sometimes when Huainan goes out,
he doesn't return for days.
It doesn't matter.
I must see him today.
Then suit yourself.
Do you mind if I look around?
It's my first time at the Song residence.
You...
Madam...
The Young Master is taking a shower in the Eldest Young Master's room.