The contract is in the study.
I hid it under the desk.
Got it.
Go back now.
My dear brother,
you really have some nerve.
Why are you back this time?
Don't tell me you missed me,
your big brother?
My dear brother,
I came back...
To avenge my mother, of course.
Still unrepentant?
Song Huainan,
you're the one who deserves to die.
Seize her.
No need to chase.
Did you find her?
Marshal, we found her.
Good.
Luo Li.
Be gentle with my ex-wife.
Zhu Luoli.
Sometimes I have to admire you.
You played us all for fools.
You're quite something.
I really didn't expect this.
No wonder we couldn't find your body.
It's just a pity
about that memorial tablet we set up for you.
Since you already know,
do with me as you please.
It's just a pity
that in the end, I couldn't avenge my father
and kill a demon like you.
Demon?
No, no, no.
I'm no demon.
Zhu Luoli.
This dagger...
I'm not the owner of this dagger,
but you should be very familiar with its owner.
What do you mean?
Why don't you ask him yourself?
Luoli.
Here he comes.
Hurry.
Song Huainan, what do you want?
Let her go.
Don't you want to avenge your family?
Here is your chance.
Come on.
Hold it.
Do you have feelings for your sister-in-law?
Yes.
As long as you divorce her,
I can marry her.
Qingzhou.
Is this yours?
Luoli.
Is this your knife?
So this is what they call
love.
Alright.
Song Qingzhou.
Right now,
you look just like a clown.
Get the hell out.
No need.
A stray dog
is nothing to fear.
Good.
Revenge is served.
Come, let's celebrate.
Zhu Luoli.
This is a celebration ceremony
I carefully prepared for you.
Humor me.
Come.
I'm actually quite curious.
Tell me,
what's it like to kill the one you love with your own hands?
How does it feel?
The person I should kill the most
is you.
Do you think you still have a chance?
You've already destroyed the Yao family.
Your father's murderer,
you killed him too.
Why not just be Yao Shengsheng
and be the wife of Song Huainan?
I can make it up to you.
Make it up to me?
With what?
You killed so many people.
Song Huainan,
you'll die a horrible death.
Fine.
It doesn't matter.
We have plenty of time.
In the coming days,
you can think it over.
Maybe
you'll change your mind, right?
Guards!
Yes, sir.
Take the Young Mistress
away.
Yes, Marshal.
It's just a shame about the steak.
If you use a knife,
the abdomen isn't protected by ribs,
so one strike can be fatal.
But as long as vital organs are avoided,
the wound won't be fatal.
Tang Mengjia
Dai Gaozheng
Lin Yadong
Wang Huiyi
Li Yunshen
Lei Xiaoyu
Li Xiaopeng
Yin Jian
Zhang Xiaolei
Aikeremu Aikebaier
Zhang Minmin
Pan Yating
Pan Liangliang, Song Jingwei
Xu Shilin
Wang Kangqi
Liu Wenjie
Ji Zhilin
Lu Kaizhan
Zeng Shuanghong, Sun Jiantao
Liu Qingquan
Kong Jinyun, Zheng Wenjun
Zhao Han
Li Xintong
Huang Fengming, Ou Yuanjie, Zhang Yulong
Cheng Wenbo
Huang Lele
Zhang Yuehua
Co-Producers: Tian Zitian, Geng Lei
Jin Xueyu, Liu Mengjunyu, Liu Hongfei
Jin Kaizhou, Zhou Yating
Miao Rongxu
Deng Yining
Fei Yufei
Xia Zhi
Finance: Sun Wenbin, Luo Qian, Ma Qiang
Li Na
Zhou Yating
He Xinrong
Zhang Minmin
Liu Zhe, Hao Shiyang
Jin Panpan, Jin Huangyanmin
Jin Ke
Liang Jingyu
Wu Liting, Ding Binbin
Liang Jingyao
Chen Jianwei
Yu Dalong, Fan Shixin, Liang Yibiao
Liang Yiheng, Zhou Xianchong, Wu Zhenliang
Zhou Taotao
Long Gongping, Yang Yicheng
Lighting Assistants: Long Yi, Li Zhengzuo, Wang Libo
Tian Jun, Huang Liwei, Long Tao
Ding Lei
Liu Xiaolin
Du Biao
Wang Qiangqiang
Xi Changchun
Han Yanan
Fan Nannan
Wu Lidan
Mao Qiang, Li Menghao, Zhao Bao
Han Jinkui, Liu Ju
Su Weigang
Zhang Kun, Yu Tiantian
Zhang Xinyi
Hu Xiaoqing, Xie Yawen, Yuan Yuan
Chen Jianxin
Gao Yang, Chen Panpan, Song Kangkang
Niu Lude
Zuo Yuxin, Lu Ziyi, Liu Zhongliang
Zhu Qiang, Liu Yanyan
Liu Ju
Zhu Lei, Zhang Mengfei
Liu Wei, Wu Yujian
Yang Zheng
Zhou Xing
Assistant Casting Directors: Jin Yutong, Yang Tuo
Still Photographers: Zhou Tao, Wu Dechao
Xue Yuan, Fu Xiao
Gong Jichao
Song Chaochao
Chang Xinhua
Wang Kaiqiang
Song Chaochao, Han Jingtao, Chen An
Song Chaochao
Bi Lei
Ding Tengyu
Su Fubo, Shi Jinrui
Sound Effects Designers: Bi Lei, Guo Yizeng
Dialogue Editors: Bi Lei, Jia Yuxiang, Wu Yuge
Bi Lei
Liu Yadong
Zhou Kai
Zhang Yu, Wang Ziqi
Lü Xiaolong
VFX Artists: Liu Lei, Jin Yunlong, Zhou Weijia
Wang Qiming, Liu Bingxuan, Wu Huijie
Zhao Yongsheng
Chen Peng
Fu Jiayu, Liu Tonghe, Guo Yuxing
Yang Yihe
Chang Xiaokang, Wei Zhen, Liu Yaofang
Feng Xuemin, Shi Tongrui, Wang Zhiming
Wang Zipeng, Yu Haiqi, Ren Zhichao
Ling Wen, Li Yucong, Su Zena
Xu Yunshuai
Ding Doudou, Zheng Ji, Song Yu
Jiang Cunxiao
Ma Tao, Fu Yu, Huang Hao
Ma Tao
Singers: Tang Mengjia, Li Huan
Chen Chen
Ma Tao
Chen Meiyi
Li Xiang
Weibo
Sina, Sina TV