[English subtitles are available]
[Ordinary Greatness]
[Episode 28]
[If by life you were deceived]
Well, you and Cui...
Chen.
You're back, Chen.
Call me if anything happens.
Okay.
Bro, you're back.
Chief Gao.
By the way,
your sister-in-law
bought me some good tea.
Don't always drink your kind of tea.
It's okay.
I'll send it to you later.
Xia Jie.
Officer Chen.
Liu Xiaoli caused trouble again.
We brought her back.
She said she wanted to see you.
What happened?
She accompanied guests in drinking at the bar
and got into a fight with another lady.
That lady called the police,
so we brought the two back.
All right, let's go and have a look.
It's you again.
Tell me, what's going on?
Mr. Chen.
Don't call me Mr. Chen.
Tell me, why did you make trouble?
Xia Jie.
Come.
Master,
you don't have to see her.
Look at her hair. It's dyed green.
Just like a ghost.
Enough.
Xia Jie.
What?
I'm going to
ask the instructor to come over.
Please ask her for me later.
According to the police responding record,
the bar she went
is very far from her home.
Ask her why she went to this one
and why she caused trouble.
The more carefully she says, the better.
See if there's anything new.
Master, I think
she can't live without such place
and such job.
The thing she said last time is probably fake.
She's hopeless.
OK.
That's it, Xia Jie.
Xia Jie.
What's up?
What is it?
You seem preoccupied.
Why are you looking at me
instead of working hard?
Hello, Instructor.
Instructor.
Chen.
Did you talk to her?
Yes.
You're right.
She came here for a reason.
In a sense,
she
came here specially for you.
What do you mean?
She told me
in this world,
you're the only one
who listened to her carefully
and trusted her.
So she came here.
It can be said that
she caused trouble and fought at the bar
to attract the police's attention.
In this way,
she can come here
again
to get your attention.
So she told me that
she thought
you're the only one who could help her.
This child...
It's a general dispute
for two girls fighting and pulling their hair.
We can just educate them and release them.
She said she wanted to see you before she left.
Let's go.
Dawei, stop following me.
Keep looking.
See if there are any new clues.
Okay.
-Wait for the call.
-OK.
Alright.
Stop crying.
Tell me what happened.
Then I can help you.
Mr. Chen.
Since that thing happened last time,
I couldn't stay at home anymore.
No one believed me.
They said I was lying
and I found someone to rape me.
My stepmother doesn't allow me to go home now,
and my dad doesn't care about me.
I really have nowhere to live.
I can only dawdle outside.
Mr. Chen,
why is life so hard?
Only your life isn't easy?
Everyone else lives easier than you, right?
When something happens to you,
you only blame others, your family and your stepmother.
Your life is yours.
Why do you always blame others?
Liu Xiaoli,
you're not a kid anymore, you know?
You're an adult.
Does it matter that much how others treat you?
Look at you.
Look at you now.
You look like a ghost.
You give up on yourself.
Who can you blame if your future is ruined?
You can only blame yourself.
But...
But my stepmother won't let me in.
She doesn't let you in?
Is it up to her or the law?
Your household register is there, you know?
She can't stop you from going home.
Master, the number you asked for is here.
Liu Xiaoli.
Alright, you can go back now.
I'll go there myself.
Don't worry.
I'll help you till the end.
Remember what I told you last time.
You must learn to love yourself, you know?
Alright, Xia Jie, Dawei,
send her out.
Be careful.
Your master seemed so angry just now.
What happened to him?
He said Liu Xiaoli was a disappointment.
My master
must think of Liu Xiaoli as Jiajia.
Every family has a sad story.
Xia Jie, what's wrong?
Don't bottle it up inside.
I'm not.
Do you think I can't tell it?
You sighed
and was distracted.
And you just thought about life.
Is it because of your mom again?
I accidentally saw your phone.
You want a loan?
You once wanted to
do ride-hailing business
and then wanted to refund the rent.
I know you have financial difficulties.
But your mom
has been back from Dali, right?
Then why you...
Li Dawei,
why are you so nosy?
Don't provoke me.
The more you provoke me,
I'm telling you, the more I will care.
Tell me.
Since you have spent money,
and your mom has gone to Dali,
she can make you so unhappy
after she came back?
Why should I tell you?
It's said that
find the police if you have any problem. I...
I'm also a cop.
I can find myself.
No, more people...
More people, more power, you know?
You can't deal with
the problem alone.
Tell me and you can have another person to share the burden.
Mind your own business.
What do you mean?
Fine, I just can't stay idle.
Tell me.
Maybe I can help you.
Xia Jie.
Dawei.
Come with me.
Something has happened.
Get changed quickly.
I'll wait for you in the car.
OK.
Liu Xiaoli didn't lie.
That night,
she must have been raped.
Although we don't have enough evidence,
I'm sure
what she said is true.
But we have no evidence now.
What should we do?
Solving the case is of secondary importance now.
Let's find a place
to let her stay.
We can't let her get hurt anymore.
But she's not in our jurisdiction.
But she is our client.
We have to help her.
Your home?
-You actually know this is your home?
-Let me in.
No way!
Look at you.
You're a disgrace to your dad.
Where are your wild men?
They dumped you?
Go find them.
You're the one who's having affairs.
I date with the wild men?
You're the one who do that.
-What are you talking about?
-You think...
What are you talking about?
I don't know what you did behind my dad's back?
Who do you think you are in this family?
This house,
the hostel and the hair salon
were earned by my mom when she was alive
together with my dad.
I can share them but you cannot.
Right?
Fine.
Ask your dad to kick me out.
Listen.
I'll make it clear today.
There's only one of us can stay in this house.
Look who your dad will choose.
Fine.
What are you looking at? Go away.
Try it.
Let me in! Let me in!
What happened?
-Liu Xiaoli.
-Mr. Chen, it's her.
She didn't let me in
and threw my things out.
Hello. Hello.
Are you Liu Xiaoli's stepmother?
I don't deserve it.
Who are you?
We're police officers from Balihe Police Station.
Hello, madam.
Although you're Liu Xiaoli's stepmother,
you're a family after all.
And her family register is here.
You can't stop her
from living here.
This is our family business.
It's none of your business.
Balihe, right?
Balihe Police Station
has nothing to do with us.
Yes, yes.
But you can't say that.
Liu Xiaoli.
Is your father here?
He drinks outside every day.
Who knows when he will come back?
Don't mention that man.
He drinks every day.
My money is not enough for him to drink.
He even brought such a kid with him
who only
seduces wild men outside all day long.
I really don't know that
you're quite capable.
You've seduced two police officers.
How could you...
How could you say that?
I'm warning you.
If you insult the police,
you shall bear legal liability.
Mom.
Sister, you're back?
Your class is over?
Go do your homework.
Go in.
This woman...
Liu Xiaoli, how about this?
You go to the community office first
and wait for us.
Dawei.
I'll take that for you.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Chen.
Chief Song.
What brings you here?
Come, have a seat.
OK. OK.
Come on.
OK. Come on.
Have a seat.
Where is Chief Wang?
He is in the police station...
He lost the tug-of-war of our two police stations
several days ago.
He also said that our stations
can find a time to have another contest.
What happened?
He doesn't talk about it now.
Is he afraid of losing?
Don't you know Chief Wang?
He's old enough to brag anything.
But Chief Song,
I'm here today to trouble you
for another thing.
What is it?
There's a girl named Liu Xiaoli in our jurisdiction.
You know her, right?
Yes, yes.
She
is one of our biggest problems.
keeps making small troubles.
Yes.
What?
Did she commit a crime in your jurisdiction?
If you take her over,
it'll save me a lot of trouble.
No.
I met her
because of a case.
But as far as I know,
I think this kid
is not bad, right?
It's mainly because her mother passed away early
and she has an irresponsible father,
who doesn't care about anything.
Many kids turn bad
little by little because of that.
Chen,
you've cared about many things.
But how can you deal with the father-daughter relationship?
Not even good officials can settle family troubles.
Besides,
we...
we all understand this truth.
But we police
can't take such a big responsibility.
That's right.
Even so,
we've run into this.
How can you ignore it?
We are the police, after all.
Right, Chief Song?
Moreover, she is very likely
a witness of a major case.
So we have to protect her, right?
Can you find a place for her to stay
in your jurisdiction
and then find her a job?
Finding a job is easy.
There are not top jobs but there are ordinary ones.
But for the place to stay...
You're challenging me.
Yes.
But I've been to her house.
Legally speaking,
her stepmother has no right to stop her
from staying at home.
But you know her family situation, right?
Even if we police
send her back,
it's hard to guarantee that
her stepmother won't kick her out again, right?
Besides, even if she stays here,
she'll feel like she has to depend on others.
You have to help her.
How about this?
I
get her a qualification of low-rent housing
and arrange a job for her.
Her salary can support her.
How about this?
That's great, Chief Song.
Well, I owe you a favor.
What?
You're working in our jurisdiction.
I owe you a favor.
This young man is your new apprentice?
Hello, Chief.
You look energetic.
Better than you.
He's a silly boy.
Okay, we're leaving.
OK. OK.
Take care. Thank you, Chief Song.
OK. OK. Please stay.
Okay, let's go.
Thank you, manager.
Thank you.
Please stay.
Thank you. Thank you.
How is it?
Yes. You look energetic.
Good.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
Xiaoli.
Although you'll be a cashier in the supermarket,
it's hard to find a job like this.
You can do this for Chief Song's sake,
so you must cherish it.
Also,
the cashier
has to deal with money.
You must be careful.
Be scrupulous about it.
By the way,
how is the house
rented for you?
Have you checked it out?
Yes, it's good.
It's just behind the police station.
It will be safe this time.
Safety is good.
Safety is more important than anything.
Xiaoli,
you must work hard from now on
and live a good life.
You're still young, right?
As long as you work hard,
the happy days lie ahead of you, right?
Chief Song has told your situation
to your manager.
In the future,
if you have any ideas or requirements,
just tell him.
Don't be afraid, right?
Also,
we're still investigating your case.
But I promise you
as long as that case once happened,
the criminal will definitely be brought to justice.
Even if he runs to the end of the world,
we will get him back.
Mr. Chen,
do you still suspect the truth of that case?
I believe you.
But I am a police officer.
I have to find evidence to support all crimes.
But we will find the evidence.
Alright, I'll stop nagging here.
Work hard.
I'm leaving.
Okay.
By the way,
I'm afraid you won't have time to drink water when you're busy.
Drink more water, okay?
I bought you a small kettle.
It's convenient to drink.
Drink more water and work hard.
Okay.
Okay, I'm leaving.
Mr. Chen.
Mr. Chen,
thank you.
Okay, thank you.
Come, Jiajia.
Here. Okay.
Here's ice cream.
And chicken wings.
Eat more.
It's all yours.
Dad, her stepmother doesn't want her?
Yes.
Outsiders
know her just wandering around
and ruining herself.
But they don't know
the misfortune behind her.
At first,
I didn't like this child either.
I think
she's an adult now, right?
She should be responsible for herself.
Why can't she live a good life
like a decent kid, right?
She always dyes her hair
yellow or green,
makes her face look like a ghost,
and goes to nightclubs, bars
and other places.
That's what I used to think of her.
But when I found out
her family background and experience,
I understood her.
Besides,
I really take pity on her.
Actually, she is also a girl who lacks love.
Jiajia.
You are different from her.
You have me.
Yes.
In fact, for you, I...
I just don't know how to express it.
Do you know that?
All these years, without you by my side,
I felt upset.
I couldn't pull myself together no matter what I did.
After you came back,
I felt much better.
I'm full of energy when facing everything.
I'm too stupid.
I don't know
how to express my feelings to you.
Dad, I know.
I know you love me.
Me too.
I also don't know how to say.
Jiajia,
tell me if you need anything.
I will try my best to do.
Dad, actually I know everything.
I just feel that your life is too hard.
I want to care about you.
But I don't know why
the more I care about you,
the more I want to get mad at you.
Dad, I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
Silly girl.
You don't need to say
sorry or forgiveness to me.
You and I...
You actually take after me.
You also keep everything to yourself.
You don't want to and won't say anything.
By the way,
Jiajia,
I have something
to discuss with you.
Do you plan
to continue staying with
Xia Jie?
I mean
Xia Jie
goes to work and deals with cases every day.
She's so busy and tired.
Is it a liitle inconvenient?
If you don't want to live with me,
it's okay.
Then I will rent a house
next to our home for you.
What do you think?
Dad.
I'll go home with you.
That's great.
Here.
I'll drink this.
Chen, you're here.
Morning.
-Chen.
-Good morning.
Morning, Officer Chen.
Morning, Xia Jie.
Morning, Chen.
-Are you busy?
-Morning, Chen.
Zhigang.
Master.
Dawei, good morning.
I've been thinking
if Yue Wei
is really a habitual offender
as you think,
then Liu Xiaoli is absolutely not
the first victim.
Did we have
unsolved rape cases before?
Is there any DNA
left in these cases?
If the DNA
can match Yue Wei's,
we can prove that he did those cases.
So,
I was searching on the Internet just now.
Did you find anything?
Hey, there's really something.
Look.
In 2014, a girl
reported to the police station in Xianqian Street,
saying she was taken to Yue Wei's house
and was raped by him.
But just like this time,
the police at that time couldn't figure out
whether it was rape or voluntary,
so they closed the case.
That's why we didn't find out before.
I found it in the record of the case closing.
You're good.
You've improved.
Not only that.
Let me show you.
I have a picture of this girl.
Look, who does she look like?
Liu Xiaoli.
Do you have her contact information?
Yes.
Here. I've written it down.
ID number and address.
Okay, take it. Let's go.
Hello.
Is Lin Cuicui here?
Looking for our manager? Please wait a moment.
Manager Lin, someone's here for you.
Thank you.
Hello, this way please.
Hello.
We're from Balihe Police Station.
This is Officer Chen.
Hello, I'm Li Dawei.
We've talked on the phone before.
I told you on the phone
not to come to me.
I know nothing.
Besides, you come to my unit.
It will affect my work.
We're doing this for work.
Sorry, Manager Lin.
We'll leave right away.
If you have anything to report
or remember anything,
you can call this number.
Sorry for bothering you.
Bye.
Master, we just let go of this clue?
Lin Cuicui.
Hello?
Lin Cuicui,
we've found your report record that year.
Yes.
You've been trying to forget that hurt.
We understand.
However,
if the criminal can't be punished,
your injury will never heal up.
What we need to do now
is to prevent him from being at large forever.
According to our speculation,
he has been committing crimes all these years.
We want to bring him to justice,
so we need your help.
He knows me.
Once
we met on the way.
He even made a gesture to wipe my neck.
So,
only by catching him as soon as possible
can you be truly safe.
Fine, I'll tell you.
Back then,
I was 18 years old.
I just came to the city
and worked as a foot therapist at a foot massage shop.
But...
But if I tell you now,
don't punish me.
Don't worry.
It's all in the past.
I really needed money back then.
My boss also wanted us to do that,
so that he could get commission.
If the customer gave us a lot of money,
we could go out too.
So Yue Wei showed up at this time?
But he didn't follow the normal procedure.
He just waited for me at the gate
after he washed his feet in our shop.
He asked me to go with him
and gave me 500 yuan.
He said there's no need to tell the boss.
500 yuan
was not a small amount to me.
In a moment of madness,
I left with him.
And then?
Then,
after I went to his house,
I found something was wrong.
I wanted to leave,
but he...
he tied me to the bed
and tortured me for two or three hours.
He didn't let me go after that.
He was drinking alone
as he told me that
I shouldn't trust men easily,
and I shouldn't leave.
Here, have some water.
Take your time.
I was terrified.
I saw him holding
a cleaver.
I thought the next second,
he would stab me with that cleaver.
I felt like I'm going to die.
How did you escape then?
Maybe I was really lucky.
When I thought I was dying,
he answered a phone call.
Soon after,
he started crying.
After that, he untied me.
He even yelled at me
and asked me to get out before he changed his mind.
Did he give you money?
In that situation,
how could I ask him for money?
It's lucky enough that I could survive.
After I left his house,
I was so scared.
I don't know
whether I was lucky to survive,
or I just met
a perverted customer.
After I came home, the more I thought about it, the more scared I was.
So I went to the police station in Xianqian Street.
But Yue Wei insisted that
it's consensual, right?
Not only that,
he threatened
to report our shop for prostitution.
I was afraid,
so I couldn't insist on any longer.
Is this photo what you looked like back then?
Yes.
August 21, 2014.
This should have happened before.
But it won't be too far.
Maybe one or two days,
at most three or four days.
Okay.
If you have any news,
inform us immediately.
Okay, thank you.
Master.
Yue Wei has left home for many years.
The local police
can't recognize him anymore.
They need to check
to see if something happened
in Yue Wei's house those days.
Dawei,
I really have a feeling that
Lin Cuicui and Liu Xiaoli
may be the luckiest two.
Other girls
might never come out alive
after they went into his rental house.
You should quickly check
if there are any missing persons in the past two years.
The check point is the girls in the nightclubs,
foot massage shops
and
bars.
Do you suspect
he's a serial killer who killed fallen women?
It's hard to conclude that now.
But look,
there are many similar points in the two cases.
And there are many points
being very suspicious.
Then give these materials to Captain Luo.
We gave them the clues last time,
but they dealt with it as prostitution and whoring.
Then give these new clues to Captain Luo.
Our police station is to maintain security.
Solving big cases
is the business of the criminal police group.
We can't replace their role.
Okay, Chief.
We'll do it.
Okay.
There was once before.
Then why didn't we find out at that time?
Captain Luo, here's the thing.
Just like this time,
they couldn't tell
whether it's rape or prostitution and whoring.
So the case was closed.
You mean
investigating whether there are any missing women?
Yes.
The point is
women who used to work in the brothel
at least ten years ago.
Okay, we'll investigate it right away.
If there is any new progress,
we'll inform you in time.
Please.
Captain Luo,
do you believe in intuition?
I do.
But
I believe the evidence more.
Master, they are definitely not as dedicated as us.
Why should we hand it over to them?
This is internal work of the police.
But
Captain Luo is an experienced criminal policeman.
I'm not worried about that.
I'm just worried
he has too many cases now.
He might not have much energy
to our case.
That's why we should deal with it.
Just give it to them.
We just need to keep an eye on it.
Hello, Chief.
There's a fighting.
It's a fighting with weapons.
Okay, we'll reinforce them right away.
Jinbao Street, right?
Come on.
Dawei, give me little rice.
OK.
Zhijie, is anyone here?
Sit down.
The rice is too hard recently.
Jinbao Street.
It's one we went to
deal with the fighting with weapons...
Stop that.
Hello.
What did you find?
What did you say?
Are you sure?
Thank you.
This news is very important to us.
Thank you so much.
Okay. Okay.
There are clues from Linchang Police Station.
Master.
On the night of August 20, 2014,
Yue Wei's mother died.
To be specific,
she died at night
at around 12 o'clock.
In other words,
not long after his mother passed away,
his family called Yue Wei
to inform him about his mother's death.
Master, it's very likely that
Yue Wei was trying to kill Lin Cuicui.
After he answered this call
and knew about his mother's death,
his plan was ruined by this accident.
That's why Lin Cuicui
survived.
Master, you're right.
Yue Wei is a perverted killer.
We're not sure.
It's just
our reasoning.
Strictly speaking,
that's not reasoning.
It's just a possibility.
How about this?
Let's report to the chief first.
In a city like ours,
it's not realistic that there are no missing persons.
But most of them only
lost contact with their families temporarily.
Most likely, they could be contacted soon.
But for this girl,
since she went missing,
there's no news about her till now.
How long has she been missing?
What did she do before she went missing?
The case was reported nine years ago.
Before she went missing,
she was to accompany guests in drinking in a nightclub.
She disappeared without any signs.
As you all know,
people in this kind of place get moved around a lot.
If it weren't this girl
still had three months of salary to be paid,
and
her friend paid attention to her,
the nightclub wouldn't have reported this case.
She is
in the jurisdiction of
the criminal police group in the city.
When the group received this report,
after some investigation,
they found even the girl's ID card was fake.
They didn't find any more suspicious clues,
so they put the case aside as the case of disappearance.
In our investigation,
we have found a few clues.
There was no Skynet project nine years ago.
But
there were surveillance cameras in this nightclub.
The criminal police group at that time
retrieved their internal surveillance videos.
We brought them here.
Look.
You two take a look.
It's him. It's Yue Wei when he was young.
But it's too vague.
We're just suspecting it.
We're not sure it's him.
If this person is Yue Wei,
he might be
related to this girl's disappearance.
But the girl's ID card is fake.
We can't get more information about her,
and we can't locate her.
We can only increase suspicion of Yue Wei.
It can't solve any problem.
One more thing.
If Yue Wei is a perverted killer,
according to behavior psychology,
he won't stop committing crimes.
He will only commit crimes more frequently.
If we take Liu Xiaoli's case
as his last case,
he has been quiet since then
and been driving his unofficial car without making troubles.
This doesn't meet
the characteristics of a serial killer.
Captain Luo, it's only been a while.
You...
So,
we had no other choice last time.
We can only strengthen our secret investigation on him.
Luo,
our station
has also discussed
this case.
I think Chen and Dawei's
direction of judgment is very accurate.
Of course, solving cases
is the task of your criminal police group.
If you need Balihe Police Station
to cooperate with you,
just say out.
We have added two surveillance cameras
where Yue Wei will pass in and out.
But we don't have
enough manpower.
I think...
Can I hand over the task
of surveillance videos to our station?
No problem.
Chief, leave it to us.
Okay.
Okay, it’s settled.
Thank you, Captain Luo.
Thank you. Thank you.
Brat, I've set up a trap for you.
Let's see if you can escape.
Are you playing games?
You're so obsessed.
What are you talking about?
How could I play games during working hours?
I'm investigating the cases.
You changed your mind?
Are you going to tell me?
The problem is
I don't think anyone can help me.
Don't think like that.
Tell me first.
Maybe the bystander knows it.
Something is actually wrong with my mom.