[English subtitles are available]
[Ordinary Greatness]
[Episode 36]
[Things always change.]
I knew my master would get released today,
so I'm here to welcome him.
Only you remember him.
No, madam.
Our chief specially called to remind me of it.
He wanted to come too.
But he's too busy in the police station,
and is unable to come here.
I understand.
Didn't Yaya come?
I didn't let her come.
Jianjun won't want Yaya
to see him walking out of such a place.
Madam,
today's society
is with more inclusion.
My master
was just punished for drunk driving,
so it won't affect much
of the rest of his life.
Since it has passed,
you don't have to
mention it anymore
in front of Master and Yaya.
Thank you. I'll keep it in mind.
He's out.
[Detention Center, Pingling City]
Look at you.
It's only been half a year's imprisonment,
but you now look like two or three years older than before.
Master, you're out.
Chief asked me to welcome you on behalf of everyone.
Thank you, Yang Shu.
And thank Chief.
Let's go home.
Yang Shu, come to our home with us.
Let's together celebrate your master's being released.
Madam, your family finally can get together now.
I won't go bother you.
Master.
Chief asked me to tell you
if you have any difficulties
in job-hunting or in life,
just call me.
All comrades in our station
will do their best to help you.
Thank Chief and everyone.
Hui.
Wait for me in the car.
I have something to say to Yang Shu.
Okay.
It's okay.
Yang Shu, thank you.
Master, take an umbrella.
Is everyone okay?
They should be fine.
Should be?
What do you mean?
Master, I haven't told you yet.
I'm now transferred to the Municipal Bureau
to do research.
When did that happen?
Was it because of me?
No, master.
From now on,
don't call me master anymore.
I don't deserve to be your master.
It's for your own good.
Don't say that, master.
You'll always be my master.
What you taught me
will be beneficial to me for my whole life.
As an negative example, right?
No, Master.
Don't think like that.
What has everyone in the station been busy with recently?
Master,
Chief also asked me to tell you
that you're no longer a police officer.
You don't have to
care about the matters in the station.
Just live your own life.
Thank you for picking me up.
Thank you.
Jianjun.
You know... for a man who was once a policeman...
You're alone in the bureau.
Remember to visit the station often.
I will.
I also miss the station, and everyone there.
I miss the group.
Get in the car
Yang Shu, bye.
Bye, madam.
Bye, master.
Come in.
Chief.
Chief Cheng, what's up?
Come here.
What's wrong?
Should we let him come here?
Jianjun.
You're here.
Chief.
How are you?
Are you doing well?
Yes.
You're doing well too, right?
I'm fine.
That's good.
Zhou Hui told me
thanks to the station...
I just want to come
to express my gratitude to the station.
Not really.
Jianjun.
Zhou Hui has been spoiled since young,
and it was really not easy for her
to survive the six months.
You should cherish her.
You should cherish Zhou Hui, your child,
and your family,
and live well.
Do you hear me?
Yes.
Thank you, Chief.
Since it's busy in the station,
I shall not take you upstairs.
Go home first.
Help Zhou Hui more in housework
and share her burdens.
Chief, I'm leaving.
Bro...
You go first.
Chief.
See,
Jianjun
is almost 40,
and has gotten criminal punishment,
I don't think it's easy for him to find a job.
Should we figure out a way
to help him?
He's been a policeman for half of his life
and has no other skills.
What else can he do?
How about this?
Go to other precincts to ask
if there's any position
like a security captain.
Maybe he can
do this.
Why other precincts?
Can't we just find him a position in our precinct?
We all know Jianjun.
If he's in our precinct,
we can take care of him.
We can't keep him in our precinct.
We should help him let go.
Chief Cheng,
call Chief Qi
of the police station on the Miaoqian Street.
There are
many newly-opened malls there.
They must be in need of an experienced security guard.
Remember,
be sure to find a position
as a security captain.
Otherwise, if he earns too little,
it's not enough for him to live.
Alright, that's it.
Those were your life savings with my mom.
Officer,
I've called the police several times.
Can you
help us first?
We've been disturbed by the ones upstairs every day.
You spent your whole life in saving them...
Behave yourself.
How could you just transfer the money to them?
Besides,
could you understand what was said on the website page?
It was all in English.
It's understandable for you to do so if you knew English.
But since you don't know English,
how could you just transfer the money to them, dad?
What if we can't get the money back?
How should my mom and I face others in the future,
dad?
Be good.
What do you think?
The police will get the money back for us.
Nothing's found yet?
Nothing unusual.
He drove around every day
and sometimes went to a foot massage store.
He hasn't brought any girl home lately.
This is the record of where he went?
How could you be so imprudent, dad?
-The child is lost! What should we do? -You and my mom have spent your whole life in saving them!
If your son comes back and asks for it,
-how will you explain it to your son? -Let's go explain it to the police.
-What's wrong with you, old man? -Listen to me, go explain it to the police.
Damn...
If you don't explain it to the police,
we can't get the money back.
Master.
Mr. Cao!
Jianjun?
Why are you here?
Cheng, Dawei.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
I just want to have a look...
To have a look...
I want...
Can I go in and have a look?
Jianjun, what are you talking about?
This is your home.
I'll go open the door.
Jianjun.
Just go on with your work.
Don't let me keep you.
Doesn't matter.
I can do it myself.
Cheng, just go on with your work.
Dawei, sorry for bothering you.
I can open it myself.
Mr. Cao.
The password has been changed.
Come in.
Comrade Cao Jianjun
has firm faith and is loyal to his duty.
[Award Ceremony for Meritorious Service]
He's firmly kept in mind the principles and devoted himself to the people.
He is brave and responsible.
He's made great contributions
to the social stability of the precinct.
This photo is still hanging here?
Yes.
This is the honor of the station,
as well as yours.
Chen,
I'm leaving.
Jianjun.
Take care.
Live well
for your family.
Morning, Dawei.
Morning.
It must be the traffic jam during the morning peak.
Sir, how long will it take?
You just came off the night shift, right?
Get some sleep in the car.
It's you!
I had recognized you
before you got in the car.
What a small world!
Weren't you a bus driver?
Why do you become a driver for online car-hailing service?
For earning some extra money.
My dad was in debt because of the medical treatment
and has passed away.
Didn't you donate...
I originally was to get my liver transplanted to him.
But the examination showed that I'm not a match.
But the surgery was done.
How was it done?
There happened to be a matching liver.
It was originally for someone else.
But that person's condition worsened
and he just passed away.
And it didn't match those in front of my dad.
Then my dad just got it.
Wasn't that good?
Well,
it may be the fate.
We got the liver match.
But there was rejection just a few days after the operation.
It got worse
and took his life.
I'm so sorry to hear about it.
It's not that bad.
It's not bad for me
to be a driver for the online car-hailing service.
I can meet different people every day,
listen to various issues,
and talk about different things.
It can make me be in a good mood.
When people are in a good mood,
everything will be fine.
Being in debt
is not a big deal.
I've already paid off many of the debts.
Do you think
it's good or bad?
Do you still drive the bus?
Yes.
That's my job.
This is just a part-time job.
Where is it?
Lanming Building.
It's newly built on the Liyuan Street.
You may not know.
There are all internet companies inside.
It even requires facial recognition to enter the building.
It's definitely dignified to work there.
What's the position?
The position you told me to find for him.
Security captain.
But it's just a deputy.
Why is it just a deputy?
Chief, you don't know.
A security team
only needs one captain.
There's no deputy captain at all.
I forced Qi
to beg for leniency.
And they set up such a position specially for Jianjun.
How much can he earn a month?
Not much, over 5,000 yuan.
Tell Jianjun
to work hard
to get promoted as soon as possible
so that he can earn more money.
Actually, Zhou Hui is quite happy.
She said after Jianjun came back,
he seldom went out of home,
just staying in the house every day.
She said if he could get a job,
even if he couldn't earn much,
she still would be happy about it.
Jianjun really has a good wife.
Chief.
Qiancheng.
Chief Gao.
Chief, you're here.
Instructor.
I have important good news
to tell you.
Chief Gao, tell them.
Yesterday, through Interpol,
the prime culprit of the fraudulent group we cracked
was arrested abroad.
Bravo!
According to reliable information,
in this campaign
against the telecom fraud,
the fraudulent group we cracked
is the biggest one.
The money involved is also the most.
Its fraud has covered
many countries in Southeast Asia.
The money involved has reached tens of millions.
Although we only recovered a few million,
we anyhow recovered it.
Chief Gao just now
got highly praised by the bureau.
Now,
I'd like to let you know it.
You'll also be commended for your work.
Chief, shouldn't we celebrate?
Right, Chief.
Xia Jie, someone is making trouble in the household registration center.
Go and have a look.
Sir, can we talk?
I'm not going.
I'll talk here.
Can we talk inside?
Don't disturb others' work here.
My poor daughter.
You died with a grievance.
The police are disregarding human lives now.
Sir, stop arguing here.
Let's talk inside, okay?
Who will redress the grievance for her?
Sir, don't cry.
What happened to your daughter?
Tell me.
There was a grievance in my daughter's death.
If you mean your daughter died of homicide,
then you should go to the service center.
This is the household registration center.
They are two different centers.
You guys here are exactly the ones who I came for.
Calm down.
Tell me what happened.
What happened?
You did it yourselves.
Now are you asking me about it?
My poor daughter.
I was going to give her an autopsy,
but your police station just
let that bastard get my daughter cremated.
I'm the one holding her household register.
How could that bastard be allowed
to cancel her household registration?
Tell me,
how did you cooperate with him?
How did you collude?
You burnt my daughter's corpse to destroy the evidence.
You know?
Then that can be very serious if you say so.
What you said can be a criminal case.
If you have evidence,
I can take you
to the service center to report the case now.
I'm not going. I don't trust you.
You colluded with each other.
I don't trust them.
What happened?
It was during the last few days before Ms. Wang gave birth.
You were still absent at that time.
Ms. Wang handled the procedures and I implemented it.
I remember the date clearly.
Around 9 a.m. on the 16th,
a man named Xu Jianshi
said that
his wife had died of disease for three days,
and he had to cancel her household registration to cremate her.
Ms. Wang and I saw that he had all the materials required,
and he also had a death certificate from the hospital.
What about the household register?
He said his wife's household register
had been in his father-in-law's house
and was not held by him.
But he had the property card, ID card,
and their marriage certificate.
He said his father-in-law went on a trip
and wouldn't be back soon.
He wanted his wife
to rest in peace as soon as possible,
thus hoping to finish all the procedures.
Without the household register,
how could you cancel his wife's household registration?
There were similar cases before.
The procedures were complete,
and other certificates could be handed in later.
And he said
once his father-in-law came back,
he would hand in the household register immediately.
He didn't look like a bad guy,
so Ms. Wang agreed to handle it for him.
Xia Jie.
That old man suddenly left.
He left?
Yes.
I saw him sitting there alone,
and I was afraid that he might disturb others.
But for an instant
he just disappeared.
Get back to work.
Don't be affected.
I'll tell it to Instructor.
Okay.
Officer Xia, will I be fired?
Then I'll be doomed.
Don't worry. It's also my responsibility.
Go.
Are you looking for me?
No.
Hao,
can you get me
the surveillance video of the household registration center?
I need to see what happened there after 9 a.m. on the 16th.
Okay.
Thank you.
What happened?
You'll see.
Most importantly, that man looked
like a loyal husband.
When I was handling the procedures
for canceling his wife's household registration,
he cried terribly
when seeing his wife's photo.
The video shows nothing abnormal on that day.
Xia Jie, why are you here?
I was looking for you.
Instructor,
I was about to report to you.
No need to report to me.
The "12345" hot-line of the bureau
reached me directly just now.
We were complained to have colluded with someone
and canceled the household registration of that person's daughter.
What happened?
This is what I wanted to report to you.
Here's the thing.
The man on the screen is Xu Jianshi.
He came to cancel his wife's household registration in the morning on the 16th.
His wife passed away three days before that day.
He was in a hurry to cremate her.
But just now,
the father of his wife came,
saying her daughter's death was unknown
and his son-in-law urgently canceled her household registration
for destroying the evidence.
That would be a criminal case.
Has the household register been canceled?
Let me finish.
I think it was not necessarily for destroying the evidence.
But there must be a story.
The key to solving the problem
is to find Xu Jianshi first.
Secondly,
we did have our problems
over the procedures of canceling the household registration.
What problem?
Xu Jianshi didn't show
her wife's household register at that time.
But we just agreed to his demand
out of sympathy.
Who did it?
It doesn't matter.
I'm responsible for what happened.
-Xia Jie. -Instructor, please give me some time.
I will give you a satisfactory answer.
Okay, as soon as possible.
Xia Jie.
It's okay.
By the way, Dawei,
if I don't have enough time,
I may need your help.
Go ahead.
I may need you to go to the hospital
to verify the death certificate of his wife.
No problem.
Thank you.
Hello.
-Officer. -Did you call the police?
-Yes, I did. -Where did it happen?
On the third floor.
Officer, sorry
for making you come here.
But it has actually been solved.
Why?
Here's the thing.
We have
an experienced security guard here.
Before I finished reporting the case,
he had just solved it.
Where is he?
H-H-He's over there!
He's giving the two sides...
Besides, what if you had made each other seriously injured...
Ask him to sign it.
Okay.
You would be detained even if it's a minor injury,
A minor injury
can also make you be sentenced to three years at most in prison.
Then what effects will it have on your future life?
Have you thought about it?
Is it worth it?
There can always be conflicts between people.
Have you thought about it?
Officer...
Just face it and solve it.
He's back?
Yes.
He worked there for less than a week
and resigned without getting the salary.
He came back to a mall in our precinct
and became an ordinary security guard.
I heard from Director Gao that
the salary is less than 4,000 yuan per month.
Try to move.
I think we should just let Jianjun do as he wishes.
After all, he's worked in our station for over a decade.
He can't bear to leave us.
And if he works
in our precinct,
it can be convenient for us to care for him, right?
After all, we've been bros for years.
Jianjun.
Chief.
Have some water.
Chief,
don't get me wrong.
I'm not here for anything else.
It's just for being closer to home.
I won't trouble the station.
Jianjun,
I've been having a backache
again in recent days.
I had to go to the hospital every day.
I tried therapies like acupuncture and Tuina every day.
To think it over,
I'm already 55 years old now.
I'm leaving the Balihe police station by the end of the year
to be an investigator in the bureau,
retiring from the leading post.
Chief, you've worked hard all your life.
You should get some rest.
Maybe I'm really old.
I'm getting homesick.
I used to be addicted to working overtime.
But now I always try my best to avoid working overtime.
When I go home,
I always ask your sister-in-law to make me some porridge
and some side dishes.
Then I can have some porridge
while listening to her chattering
about various things,
like our son is disobedient,
and she doesn't like her daughter-in-law and so on.
Such moments really make me feel at ease,
which is beyond words.
So, Jianjun,
for everyone's whole life,
whether you're successful or not,
what you have in the end
will only be your own home,
your wife and your children.
You're lucky
to have such a good wife like Zhou Hui.
You are really...
When you were in trouble,
she not only took care of the family,
but also stuck up for you.
When you worked in the police station,
you totally devoted yourself to the work.
You worked overtime every day.
You're really lucky
to have such a good wife like Zhou Hui.
Jianjun,
listen to me,
just forget about being a police officer.
It'll never happen again.
Just find a job with high salary,
live a good life,
and support your family.
Do you hear me?
Chief.
How can I forget?
Can I?
You have to.
Sister Xia Jie.
Sister Xia.
Who are you calling sister?
I call you sister to show your status.
Get away!
Zhao Jiwei, you didn't see
Xia's glorious image
when she was solving the problem.
She did it in a really outright and decisive manner.
Fine, stop touting me.
Jiwei, look at him.
He's come back to life, right?
When something happens,
it can immediately arouse his sense of justice,
and make him become so vigorous.
You too.
Have some meat to get more energy.
Thank you.
Can you two stop touting each other?
Can you not treat me like air?
Who treated you as air?
Aren't we talking to you?
Yeah.
Look at you two.
If I'm not air, what am I?
Xia Jie, let me tell you.
When you were shouldering the responsibility for others' mistakes
in front of the instructor,
I really wanted to stop you.
That was not it.
Though I indeed did so
for preventing Cui from being expelled,
I really thought
it was also my fault.
It was our fault for agreeing to cancel the household registration.
But when I saw Xu Jianshi in person later,
I felt more relieved,
seeing him loving his wife so much.
Besides,
that old man came to the police station again.
He even brought a woman like that.
From his words, I could tell that
he didn't care about her daughter's life at all.
What he cared about was just the house property.
Then I suddenly knew what to do.
Not bad, Xia Jie.
You've grown up.
Be careful, I'll report you to Chief.
Anyway,
I should thank you.
for the death certificate
and everything you got from the hospital.
And...
That old man has never
gone to the hospital to see his daughter.
That's the key point.
It made the old man silenced right away.
What's wrong?
Don't allow us to eat?
Didn't you have a good chat?
Keep chatting!
Continue to take me as air!
Sir,
are you jealous?
Stop it.
Get him!
Louis!
Good friends...