[English subtitles are available]
[Ordinary Greatness]
[Episode 5]
[Goodness]
I got an old man, a child
and a woman.
The same with you.
I also got an old man, a child,
a woman and her husband.
You win. The situation is more complicated than mine.
Don't stop me.
Honey!
-Don't stop me. -Honey.
Don't stop me!
I'm going to get even with that old man.
Don't stop me.
Is there no law here?
Sir, calm down.
He is a rascal.
What's the use of looking for him?
Who else can I look for?
Calm down.
OK, officer.
You are the police.
Please help me!
That old man
He scared my child.
What should we do about it?
Do you police still care about it?
Do you care?
Listen to me first.
Please calm down and listen to me.
The old man who had a fight
with your wife
is in the hospital too.
What?
He hit my wife and kid.
He even pretended to be the victim and went to the hospital.
Where is he?
Sir, calm down.
Don't be impulsive.
The child is still lying in the hospital, right?
Let's go check on the child first, OK?
Ms. Zhou, please help me persuade him.
I just want to reason with him.
-This is the hospital.  -Yes.
-What are you doing? -Don't affect others.
For the sake of the child,
I have to talk to him.
-Right. Right. -Right?
Should I talk to him?
Yes.
How could he do that?
OK, we'll talk later.
Ms. Zhou, please talk to him.
Li Dawei,
You should...
You go and check
what's going on with the old man.
Contact his family as soon as possible.
-Ok. -Go.
Master, have some water.
OK. Go now.
Yang Shu, we're even now.
What does he mean?
I don't know what he said.
Water.
Dawei bought it.
Excuse me.
What happened to him?
He was fine just now. Why did he lie down?
The patient fell asleep.
How is he?
We won't know until we do further examination.
But the patient can't be stimulated.
Listen to me.
He can't walk now.
He's not sick.
He's really not sick.
Officer,
please come here.
If he's not sick,
how can he be lying in bed.
Don't disturb other patients.
Be quiet.
Don't go any further.
Did you receive any benefits from them?
You still take their side?
Yes.
What are you talking about?
The doctors have never seen that family.
How could they be biased?
What are you doing?
Besides,
why don't you take care of the elderly?
Why are you arguing with the doctors?
What is the point of taking care of him?
He's already unconscious.
Behave yourself.
We have no other request.
Where are they?
You are only responsible for calling them out.
They should pay the bill.
They should pay for us, right?
Yes, that's right.
OK. OK.
Listen to me.
In this case,
your old man was indeed wrong.
We all saw that.
That he suddenly fell to the ground has nothing to do with the other side.
What do you mean by saying it has nothing to do with them?
Right.
I think you guys must have conspired with them
and hit him down like this.
You guys must have conspired with them
and irritated the old man.
Ms.,
we have video records
in the whole process.
We're also recording it now.
It can be proved that
your old man did faint by himself.
And he didn't have a dog license.
He didn't leash the dog.
He broke the law first.
Who are you?
How dare you cut in
while we are talking?
Go away.
-Can you watch your mouth? -He is on purpose.
Be quiet!
-Shut up. -Be quiet.
What bullshit are you talking about?
Stop yelling.
This is a hospital, you know?
Your old man is not sick at all.
If you keep arguing here,
you will make the situation worse.
This will be identified as violence against doctors.
I'm warning you.
If you keep messing around, I'll take forced measures.
What are you looking at?
Security.
Clear the place.
Don't touch me.
Let's see who dares to stay.
Let's go, bro.
It's OK now, everybody.
It's OK now. Sorry to disturb you.
Don't touch me. Don't move.
I went out to buy some vegetables
but I didn't take the key.
If I remember correctly,
your home should be on the 18th floor.
Yes.
Look at the top floor.
The one next to the deck.
That one.
Officer Zhang, you have a good memory.
Please take a cigarette.
No, thanks.
Officer Zhang, you told me last time
to install a security door.
But it was too safe.
It can't be opened without the key.
Where is your wife?
She didn't take her key either?
My wife is on a business trip.
She'll be back in a few days.
I can't sleep in the corridor these days, right?
You mean...
Officer Zhang,
take out the key for me.
Take it out?
How do we take it out?
Look.
The deck next door is not closed.
You can just step over the wall
and go into my home, right?
I didn't close the window.
Have you watched too many American movies?
Do you think we police
are all like Spiderman?
Officer Cheung,
Who is this young comrade?
What are you talking about?
-We taxpayers pay the money. -Enough. Enough.
We just want you to serve the people.
Calm down.
He is Zhao, a new officer in our station.
How could he talk like that?
He was just kidding.
No, Officer Zhang.
Just tell me
will you help me or not?
It is really dangerous
to climb onto he 18th floor.
If we go up
and fall off,
you will remember this scene
for the rest of your life, right?
How about this?
You can hire a locksmith.
It will cost only one or two hundred yuan.
You think it is a small number?
It's not easy to make money now.
How about this?
I'll pay for you, OK?
I don't think it's appropriate.
Sure it's appropriate.
I'll spend 200 yuan
to buy our lives.
That's perfect.
Stop hesitating and call a locksmith.
I'll call then.
Li Dawei,
Didn't I ask you to contact his family?
Why are you playing with your phone?
Master.
Can you stop being so prejudiced against me?
Do I need prejudice?
Master, here's the thing.
The old man
didn't bring his ID.
We only know a name,
Wang Jianguo.
So what?
Do you know how many people
named Wang Jianguo are there registered in our system across the country?
Don't you know how to screen a list?
Do you know
how many people over 70 named Wang Jianguo
are there?
Why are you talking so much nonsense?
Get to the point.
Alright, get to the point.
After my calculation and screening,
I’ve locked 16 police stations.
I respectively sent them
a photo of Wang Jianguo.
Tunhe Zhuang Police Station just called back.
Go on.
They said he looked similar.
But they couldn't confirm it.
On the one hand,
the registered photo of him is too small.
On the other hand,
this Wang Jianguo's eyes are closed
in the photo.
Can't you take a picture with his eyes open?
I have to open his eyes first.
He's not awake yet?
Master! Master!
Say it.
The station said
the photo of this Wang Jianguo
doesn't match the one over there.
That Wang Jianguo over there
was abandoned by his family and no one cared about him.
The police station has been mediated several times.
That old man is living alone.
Master, you win.
The doctor said he has liver hardening at a terminal stage.
He was lively when he was cursing.
Sir, you're finally awake.
Don't let her run away.
I need her to pay for my treatment.
Sir.,
your illness has nothing to do
with Ms. Zhou.
Why?
She hit me and I got this illness.
The doctor said
you have had cirrhosis
for several years.
Mrs. Zhou scratched your face
instead of your liver.
Dawei.
I don't care.
If she hadn't hit me,
I wouldn't have ended up here.
Sir, calm down.
It's bad for your health.
We're here
to ask you
how to contact your family.
I don't have any family.
Mr. Wang,
you live in Tunhe Village, right?
According to your household register,
you have a wife
and a son.
What did I do in my previous life?
I am terminally ill when I am old.
I was driven out by them.
Why are people like this nowadays?
I deserve it.
I really deserve it.
Don't think that I'm willing to scam people.
I really have no choice.
I have no choice.
What's the point of living like me?
I'd rather die.
Sir.
It's not necessary.
Calm down.
Come on.
That old man broke the law.
And he was obviously pretending to be sick.
How could we just let him go?
I think it makes no sense.
I knew you would say that.
This old man is old.
He pretended to be sick this time.
What if he is really sick next time?
What should we do?
Look at Li Dawei.
I don't know how long it will take them to stay in the hospital.
How many cases can we solve if they have that time?
But if we just let him be like this,
will people like him
be more rampant
and more disrespectful for the laws?
Shu,
reality is reality.
Theory is theory.
Our reality is to solve the problem.
It's not about who's right or wrong.
We only need to ease the conflict
and calm things down.
That's true.
But we are police.
We are law enforcement personnel.
Right and wrong.
If we don't know, who will know?
If we don't correct it, who will?
It shouldn't be ignored
with a word of reality.
If we hadn't ignored them
and kept trying to reason with them,
would they have left?
If it continues, will there be any peace in the hospital
and will the patients get treated as usual?
You need to know
what is more important?
Am I right, Ding?
Master.
Shouldn't we focus on
the guy with a scare on his face we saw at Datun Village?
Jiwei,
shouldn't you find a place to stay?
It's not good
to in the station.
I have a place to stay, Master.
I have a relative in the city.
Besides, I just arrived at the station.
I just want to get familiar with the colleges.
I'm too busy handling
all these cases.
And renting a room
is a waste of money, Master.
Let's go.
I heard you ran away from home.
Who did my mom call this time?
She's familiar with most people in the station.
If that's the case,
I won't go back.
I have rented a house anyway.
It's not easy for both of you.
It's not easy for her either.
I think you should talk to her.
Even if you want to move out,
it shouldn't be the reason that you are angry.
It should indeed be for the convenience of work.
If you talk to to her,
she should understand.
I want to do something
to make her change.
I'll drive you home.
Take a seat.
We are in trouble.
I just had a phone call with Officer Tong
from Tunhou Village.
Tong said...
What is the guy's name again?
Wang Jianguo.
Yes, Wang Jianguo.
He said Wang Jianguo hasn't paid
health insurance for over two years.
And Tong agreed to offer us help.
He has informed the relevant personnel
and done everything he can.
As long as he pays the health insurance,
he will be able to claim the medical expenses.
Nonsense.
He's in their jurisdiction now.
If it's so easy, why haven't they helped him pay the insurance?
With the medical insurance, we don't need to worry.
You can't talk like that.
After all,
he broke the law in our place.
Can we shift the responsibility to them?
No.
Chief, here is the situation.
Even if the insurance is paid,
he can't claim 100 percent expenses, right?
Wang Jianguo has cirrhosis now.
When will this end?
It's truly a big problem.
And
when we came back from the hospital,
the hospital informed us that
if he doesn't pay the hospital fee tomorrow,
Wang Jianguo will be sent to our station.
That's impossible.
Impossible?
Then let's send the check to the hospital.
Do you think our station is printing checks?
You just wait for them to carry him here.
Haven't I told you that
our priority is to find his family.
I've been looking for his family.
But you called me
to come back to report it
and have a discussion, right?
Yes, I did.
I wanted to discuss it with you.
Forget it. It's late now.
Go back and have a rest.
Go to find his family tomorrow morning.
What about the hospital fee?
I don't understand.
Why do we have to do this.
-You shut up. -You shut up.
All right, go back.
I'll figure it out.
Do you figure out
where Wang Jianguo's son lives?
Maybe.
What do you mean maybe?
Can we enforce the laws with vague information?
I'll make it accurate.
I'm here at the station to make it more accurate.
Hurry up.
I'll wait for you in the car.
Are we looking for him today?
Do you think we can wait till tomorrow?
No.
Then what are you talking about?
Is Zhao Jiwei sleeping inside?
No.
Don't be nervous.
-I heard you rent a house nearby. -Yes.
For the convenience of work.
Can't you let Zhao live together with you?
I told him about it
immediately.
He said he had a relative in the city.
He didn't need to rent a house.
Dawei,
I don't know
how you young people communicate.
But I think
living with relatives
even with siblings
will be inconvenient after a long time.
Yes.
Besides,
the income of you cadets
is not enough
after you rent a house
and give some money to parents. Right?
Yes.
Of course, you are an exception.
You have parents to support you.
It's hard for me too.
How old do you think I am to depend on my parents?
That was why
I wanted to rent an apartment with Yang Shu and Xia Jie.
Them what was the reason why
Zhao refused to rent with you?
He thought it was too expensive?
That's one of the reasons.
I understand. Instructor.
I see.
I will deal with it.
My Master is waiting for me outside.
I have to go.
Do you really understand?
Does he really understand?
Instructor,
there is a fight in Jinbao Street.
There are many participants. It's an emergency.
Two of you stay in the station.
The rest ones.
You guys, follow me and respond to the call immediately.
Du.
Get everything ready.
Get geared up.
Instructor,
there is a fight on the Second Road. Some guys are using knifes.
What is wrong with tonight?
Wang, Lin.
Take two people to Second Road.
OK.
Be careful with the knifes.
Wang, let's go.
Instructor, it's a fight with weapons in Jinbao Street.
I think we need more people there.
Instructor, take me with you.
All right.
You come with us.
OK.
Hurry up. Keep an eye on it.
I'll be right down.
Hurry up.
Get in.
Hurry up!
Speed up!
Keep up! Hurry!
Get in the car.
Get in.
Hurry up.
Anyone else?
Yes.
♫The clouds float in the light♫
It's full. Comrade.
♫The story behind the scenes♫
Master.
♫intertwine♫
Is everyone here?
Yes.
♫Joy, anger, sorrow♫
Instructor, I…
Go.
Keep up.
♫We chase the alleys along the street♫
Let's go.
♫The light is as bright as daytime♫
♫In the dark night♫
♫flowers bloom♫
♫I'm used to running♫
♫Pursue right and wrong♫
♫How many times♫
♫similar moments♫
Zhijie, when did you get in?
♫Step by step♫
I never got off.
♫The missing sunlight♫
You don't have a night shift tonight.
♫How many times does the time record♫
My disciple is here.
Of course I'm here.
♫different outlines♫
♫Little by little♫
Zhao Jiwei!
I have something to discuss with you.
Go ahead.
I'm on a mission with Instructor
♫Unconsciously♫
to Jinbao Street.
Good for you. #行啊(Good for you./Sure.)
Is this your first mission?
♫My conviction and intuition are sinking♫
Let's talk about it after that.
It's OK. Tell me now.
I'm still on my way.
♫Different summaries♫
I told you about our rent.
The living room rent is 800 yuan. It's indeed a bit expensive.
♫and give me♫
I've changed the rent to 400 yuan.
Stop!
Police! Freeze!
Drop the weapon.
Please evacuate.
Drop the weapon. Don't move.
Drop the weapon!
Drop the weapon.
Three hundred yuan will also be fine.
Now that the living room is empty.
You shouldn't always stay with your relatives.
It's not convenient.
We should help
each other.
Sure.
Let me help you.
I will pay 400 yuan then.
I can clean
and cook.
Sure.
Then I make it 200 yuan.
Do you think I'm a cheap worker?
♫Follow the track of your heart♫
Four hundred then.
♫The growth witness♫
♫through the gap of time♫
♫are accumulated little by little♫
♫of happiness.♫
♫I believe that time♫
♫fill the meaning of jigsaw puzzle♫
♫It's meaningful♫
Four hundred then.
OK, as long as you think it's appropriate.
What?
Nothing.
Zhao... Zhao Jiwei.
Turn it off.
Get to work.
Coming.
Hello.
We're from Bali River Police Station.
Are you
Wang Jianguo's son, Wang Gang?
No, you got the wrong person.
Did you get it wrong again?
That's impossible. That's right.
Stop it.
What's wrong with you guys?
I said I'm not the one you are looking for.
I have old people and children at home.
You're disturbing us, you know?
Are you Mr. Wang Gang?
No.
Can I see your ID?
Did I do anything wrong?
Why should I show you my ID?
Every citizen is obligated
to cooperate with the police, understood?
This is the law.
Let's talk downstairs, OK?
OK. Wait me for a second.
OK. Let's talk here.
My name is Qi Gang.
I don't know Wang Jianguo.
What about showing your ID card?
I don't know him.
Why do you need my ID card?
Here's the thing.
Mr Qi,
we have checked your information.
No matter what your name is now,
your name was Wang Gang.
You used to live in Tunhe Village.
You moved here
because of family disputes.
Well, Mr. Wang,
or Mr Qi.
Here's the thing.
No matter where you moved to and
no matter what your last name is,
you are
Wang Jianguo's son.
It can't be changed.
Look.
I broke off the father-son relationship with Wang Jianguo.
We've signed on it.
Mr. Wang, you need to have a conscience.
You can't ignore your father
because he got an incurable disease.
What did you say?
-How interesting. -Right. Right.
Do you believe the old man?
Then I have no conscience.
Mr. Wang.
We shouldn't
judge who is right or wrong in your family.
Actually, no one is right or wrong
in a family.
These are all just trivial matters.
Right?
But.
Speaking of which,
he is your father after all.
Right?
The old man is now in hospital because of liver cirrhosis.
As his son,
you are obligated to take care of him.
It's written in black and white.
He cut ties with me.
My mother's divorce paper is still in the court.
He didn't sign it. He didn't pick it up.
That's his business.
And let me tell you.
I don't want to hear about him and I don't want to care.
He can say whatever he wants about me.
I'm okay with it If he says I don't support him
and I have no conscience.
It doesn't matter.
He can say whatever he wants.
I don't care.
Let me put it this way.
I should be heartless to that old man.
It's too much.
It's all out of anger, Mr. Wang.
Even though he is an unforgivable man,
you are his son after all.
Enough. Don't reason with me.
It won't work.
Did you mention that I'm not fulfilling my duty to support him?
Fine. I admit it.
What can you do about me?
You want to arrest me?
No.
In fact, the problems between your father and you
can be solved
through negotiation, right?
The current situation is...
He is still in the hospital.
All right, you can leave now.
You're not leaving? Fine. I'll go back.
Don't knock on my door again.
I have a family.
If you knock again, I'll complain about your disturbance.
Mr. Wang.
Master.
I think
He didn't something wrong and we leave him to die?
Who didn't ever do something wrong?
You didn't.
You don't care if you have a problem?
What has every father done wrong in the world?
Fine. Master.
Just take me as a vent.
Gosh.
Mom, what are you doing?
I'd better go to Qingdao.
I won't be annoy you anymore.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
I was rude yesterday.
I've thought it over.
Your aunt was right.
All these years,
I have thought blindly by myself
and got myself into trouble.
You've grown up.
You have your own plans.
I've always
controlled you in my way.
If you follow my order,
you will be unhappy.
If you don't listen to me,
I will be unhappy.
Nothing can be solved.
So,
I'll go to the beach to have some peace.
Do you really think so?
What else can I think?
But you suddenly want to go there.
I don't have time to book a place for you to live.
I've talked to your aunt.
I'm still staying with your aunt.
Don't worry.
It's not my first time living in your aunt's house.
OK. Let me help you pack thing up.
Mom, I've prepared everything for you.
I've prepared some plasters for you.
If your back hurts again, remember to put it on.
This is mosquito repellent.
Aunt lives by the beach after all.
There might be mosquitoes.
And cold medicine.
You must take care of yourself there.
By the way, mom,
I'll transfer the money to you.
I have your aunt in Qingdao.
I won't spend much money.
Yes. You are right.
But you shouldn't bother her.
Aunt has been taking care of
us for so many years.
All right.
You just came to work.
Where did you get so much money?
I got my salary.
I don't have much to spend money on.
It's free to eat in the office.
The police uniform is distributed by the station.
You should take enough money when you have a journey.
Just take it.
Just remember.
Don't let aunt spend money on you.
If your dad were still alive...
Enough, Mum.
There you go again.
Aren't we good now?
You have me.
Because of you,
I always think about
whether being a police officer
is safe or not.
It's not a big deal whether the work is tiring.
You always make me worried.
You became a police officer
and fulfilled your father's last wish.
I can't stop you.
Neither can I.
But we can make a request to the bureau.
You can change to another office
where your work is easier and you don't have to work overtime.
All right, mom.
Let's not talk about this.
Go to bed early after packing up.
You have to catch the train tomorrow.
Actually, I feel contradicted.
I haven't worked for years.
If you hadn't become a police officer,
we would have lost contact with the bureau.
So I am not saying you can't be a policewoman.
You can change a post.
All right, mom.
Go to sleep, OK?
Let me help you pack things up.
When you get up tomorrow,
you can just carry your luggage and leave.
You can go to sleep.
They say good deeds lead to good results.
How can I throw a rock at my foot?
Zhao Jiwei. Earthquake!
Wake up!
Zhao Jiwei.
Yang Shu.
You are awake too?
He is snoring so loud.
My bed is trembling in my room.
How can I go to sleep?
What kind of martial art is he practicing?
How can he snore like this?
Zhao Jiwei, wake up!
Zhao Jiwei!
Zhao Jiwei! Zhao!
Wake him up!
Zhao Jiwei!
Pinch his nose! Pinch his nose!
Zhao Jiwei. Wake up. Zhao Jiwei.
He opened his eyes.
I beg you.
Can you stop snoring?
Darn it.
Wake up.
He's still asleep.
Jiwei.
Zhao Jiwei!
Wake up, OK?
Amazing.
Dawei, you brought him in.
You must be responsible.
How?
Just get him into your room.
Close the door and window.
You sleep here.
Why should I?
Look at him.
How long has it been since he slept well last time?
That's why he snores like this.
Just let him stay in your room
for a few days.
It will be fine.
Yang Shu.
Yang Shu, you have to help me.
I'm going to bed.
He is still not awake?
I deserve it.
It's really annoying that the electric bikes are missing.
The police are here.
Let's take a look.
Let's have a look.
Who called the police?
I called the police.
Do you have your ID card?
-Qiu Chenli. -Qiu Chenli.
Register her.
OK.
Tell me about it.
Officer,
seven or eight electric bikes are missing
in our neighborhood.
Tell me.
What job are you police doing?
Exactly.
You only ask us to register.
We know our electric bikes are missing
even though we don't register.
You have to solve it as soon as possible.
We are waiting to ride the electric bikes to work.
Yes. My bike is a new one.
It's not easy for us.
We need it every day.
All right, don't worry.
Calm down.
It's useless
to get agitated.
We're here.
The police are for the people, right?
So don't worry.
We set up a special team
for the electric electric bike theft case.
I'm in charge of the details.
Please give us some time.
I'm saying
we're waiting to go to work.
Yes, I understand.
But we still have to follow the rules.
We have to register first.
Otherwise, we can't do our work, right?
Yes, we will cooperate with you.
Let's start with the ladies.
OK.
Get out of the way. None of your business.
We must hand over Liu today.
Master, what happened?
-Stop arguing. -Calm down.
Stop arguing. Calm down.
Get up.
Make way.
You have grievances.
We can solve it, right?
Slow down.
Screaming won't solve any problem.
Why is it here?
As a daughter, why did you leave him here?
If your father is sick,
go to see a doctor.
This is not a hospital, OK?
Stop wasting time.
Hurry up.
Take him to the hospital.
Come on.
Go.
Wait, wait.
Dad, say something.
You go inside
and tell the police about the problem.
OK.
Leave me here.
I'll wait for you here.
OK.
Chief, we can't let him stay here.
We have to carry him in.
He's over 70 years old.
What if something happens?
Zhi Jie.
Zhi Jie, go to the community hospital.
Get a doctor and a nurse.
Just in case.
-OK, go. -OK.
Listen, calm down.
-This room. -Hurry.
This room. This way.
Come on.
The door is too narrow.
Put me down!
Put me down.
Put it here.
Just lie on the table.
The door panel.
We need the door panel.
Lying here is comfortable.
Come on.
Dad, be careful.
OK.
Here.
Are you OK? Here.
Slowly.
Lie down.
Be careful.
Where is the doctor?
Coming.
Doctor, hurry up.
Get a doctor!
Sir, what's wrong?
I'm not feeling well anywhere.
Did you see that?
This is the video
we got from the surveillance
on the road.
The couple were walking on the road with their child.
Suddenly, your dog rushed out.
Look.
He ran after the kid
and she
fell and got hurt.
Look here.
Our police officers
accompanied the child's father
to proactively
settle with you.
Your father...
Your father was irritated
and fell down.
Besides,
you have
no dog license.
This is illegal.
Besides, it was against the urban management regulation
that he did not leash the dog.
So in this matter,
the other side did nothing wrong.
It was your father's fault.
Chief Wang. You can't say that.
Right.
How do you know
they came back to reconcile with my father?
My father fell down
because they came back to provoke him.
Chief Gao.
Show the video from the law enforcement recorder to him.
That one.
Pay us for wasting our time.
Let's be reasonable.
And then I will pay you. OK?
You haven't grown up yet. I'll compensate you my ass.
Sir, don't fight.
Don't fight, Sir.
Don't fight.
Calm down. Don't fight.
What are you talking about?
He's unreasonable.
-Why do you have to reason with him? -You live in vain at such an old age.
Say it again if you dare.
Stop it.
What do you think?
That man said my dad lived in vain
at such an old age.
Chief, listen to it.
Didn't he say so on purpose
to piss my father off?
Your father
was wrong.
He went out to walk the dog without a leash.
The dog scared the kid.
It's understandable for the child's father
to be angry.
As for the responsibility
he needs to take
for causing your father's illness,
the law will judge it.
It seems that your father collapsed
because of his poor health.
Chief Wang,
Why do you always defend the other side?
Right.
Did you get any benefits from them?
Say it again.
♫Like a seed♫
♫kissing the season♫
♫and getting ripe withering away♫
♫I'm warming your hands♫
♫The shadow of wind♫
♫chases green leaves♫
♫I choose to compromise♫
♫and embrace love♫
♫Love♫
♫from the smallest♫
♫love♫
♫to the greatest♫
♫Dream in the sunset♫
♫To name the eye of the night♫
♫Listen to the flower in the cloud♫
♫I am not afraid to become dirt♫
♫I am running to you♫
♫Flowers♫
♫becoming dirt♫
♫I'm not afraid♫
♫to run to you♫
Why do I have to take the blame?
Who else do you think should the blame?
On this early morning,
a group of people came here angrily.
Have you ever thought about this?
Paint.
What are you doing?
How dare you paint here?
Don't run. Calm down.
Come on.
Calm down. Put the knife down.
Don't run. Put the knife down.
Officer.
No. Did you see it?
You didn't see it.
How could you say that
we poured ink in their house?
Who said it?
Do you have any evidence?
Right. Do you have any evidence?