[English subtitles are available]
[Ordinary Greatness]
[Episode 27]
[To be or not to be]
Chief.
you have to speak for Jianjun.
Chief,
Jianjun just made a mistake.
We need to help him.
Chief, even if he gets demoted for three grades,
we just can't watch him get sent to prison!
Chief, he just solved a case
and caught a criminal.
His contributions are far more than his mistakes.
Come in.
Chief.
I heard...
What are you trying to say?
Though I don't like Cao Jianjun,
for he always seeks to prevail against others,
and always put his own interests first,
I think we should
try to save him anyhow.
Chief,
Jianjun has joined the force for 16 years.
He's always been in danger and gotten injured many times.
Just because of some of his problems,
we sometimes even didn't give him
the honor and commendation
that he deserved to get.
But look at how he's been working.
We've all seen it.
I know it's serious.
But considering its root cause,
I think it's understandable.
All the police in the station
are watching.
If we don't save him,
everyone will be disappointed.
Then who will work like Jianjun in the future?
Think about it, Chief.
How about you
asking the director
to let the traffic police be lenient
and just give him a disciplinary punishment?
If you think it's inappropriate for you to do it,
we can write a report in the name of our police station.
Later if there's any responsibility for it,
we can...
Have a rest.
Chief,
for all these years, Jianjun has been working hard,
and has solved many problems for the people.
You can give him punishments,
but if you get him expelled...
Isn't that too cruel?
Yes.
Everyone may make mistakes.
Exactly.
Even the criminals can get a way out.
The police are humans too.
What do you take the police for?
The ones with a privilege?
You said the police are also humans.
But the police are the ones
who hold the right to enforce the law.
If a law enforcer breaking the law
can get away with punishment,
then who will still be law-abiding in the future?
Today,
let me remind you again.
Regarding Cao Jianjun,
no one is allowed to plead for him from now on.
As for how he will be punished, it depends on the law.
It's not what we can decide.
For the things I just told you,
get them completed as soon as possible.
We can't delay the work for the fourth quarter.
Don't make everyone
look bad.
Meeting adjourned.
Chief.
He should be punished, but we still should help.
Jianjun is our comrade.
Hui.
Why are you here?
We certainly should come.
Let's go inside.
Change your shoes.
Officially
indicted?
Today,
it has officially informed us of it.
Can't his police station or the bureau
plead for him?
What he did can't be pleaded for at all.
How many years is he gonna get? Have you asked about it?
Chief Wang said
at least
a few months' detention.
A few months isn't long.
After he gets released upon completion of a sentence,
what should he do in the future?
You've always been saying
he's a policeman,
he's a policeman.
Now he gets into trouble,
why didn't his identity as a police officer help him out?
Hui, look at you, married to such a man,
and got nothing good.
The whole family has to be taken care of by you alone.
And he even got himself sent to prison just by drinking.
You should have married a man
either wealthy
or powerful.
But look at him!
He's even more awful than your brother-in-law.
By the way, Hui,
your brother-in-law is no longer on the blacklist.
It needs three million.
He just signed and paid it off.
Mom, we're here to comfort Hui.
Why do you mention him?
I'm telling your sister
to reflect on her marriage.
Hui, look at you.
Look at what your sister eats and wears,
and what you eat and wear.
And now,
your husband will later become an ex-convict.
Mom!
What are you gonna do?
What are you gonna do in the future? Have you thought about it?
Y-Y-You still insist on choosing him?
Look at your brother-in-law.
Stop it.
Mom, what are you doing here today?
I came to see you.
Then why do you keep mentioning my brother-in-law?
If my brother-in-law is so capable,
and can pay off three million easily,
then how could he get blacklisted?
Why did he pull a pitiful face?
I'm willing to live with Cao Jianjun.
No matter how bad Jianjun is,
he's loyal to me.
He is a good husband.
He is a good father.
How about my sister?
My brother-in-law is rich, that's true.
But he went whoring and cheated on his wife.
The creditors even came to his home to collect debts.
What good did my sister get?
Sis, you do live a rich life by marrying such a man,
but are you happy?
Don't mention him.
I have to say it.
Mom, I know you always look down on Cao Jianjun?
Now,
he's even to be sent to prison,
you must be very satisfied, right?
But you misjudged your daughter.
I like Cao Jianjun.
Let me make this clear.
No matter how long he will be detained
or how hard our future life will be,
I've acknowledged him as my husband,
I like him,
and I'll follow him for my whole life.
Mom, it's okay if you don't like him.
I don't care.
But please don't come to my home again
in the future.
I won't go to your home either.
Let's just ignore each other.
It's time for me to pick up my child.
You can leave now.
Cong.
She even wouldn't let me talk.
I'm all thinking
for your own good!
I don't care.
Sister, take her away.
Let's go, mom.
You're really something, huh!
You are capable, okay?
I'm telling you, if you're so capable,
then don't ever ask for help from the Zhou family.
Get out of my way. I'm leaving.
I'll leave.
Chief Wang.
Director said our morning meeting on Monday
might last for a long time.
He asked you to go back first.
He knows what you mean.
Lv,
our morning meeting ended early.
I don't have other things to deal with.
I can just wait here.
Fine. Have a seat.
Have a seat.
Here you are.
Okay, thank you.
Chief Wang, don't be like this.
We heard about what happened to Cao Jianjun.
Director is also upset.
Jianjun shouldn't have failed us.
Anyway, thanks for your understanding.
Sorry for the trouble.
Don't mention it.
Have a seat.
As for the document this time,
I think you must have known about it.
We must carry out
all-round fights against crimes.
For relatively remote places,
we must intensify
the law education among the public.
Don't miss any blind spot.
He insists on waiting for you.
and won't leave.
He's still there.
Director Song.
Don't call me Director Song.
You are my master.
Since I joined the force,
you've been the one teaching me how to be a policeman.
About Jianjun,
except what you said at my home
last night,
are there any new ideas?
Are there?
Let me know if there are. I'm in a meeting.
What else can I say?
My subordinate committed such a serious crime
and I still shamelessly came to see you...
What else can I say?
I understand the principles.
But I must come.
I must try to
get the last bit of hope for Jianjun.
Song.
Jianjun is your junior.
You know him well.
Can we think of a way
to not let him get sent to prison?
Song.
Master.
I can't assure you that.
It depends on the law.
But in terms of the discipline,
anyone found drunk driving
shall get no pardon.
It has been stipulated long ago.
I don't know
whether he will go to jail,
but he definitely
can't be a policeman anymore.
Master,
it's useless for you to be like this now.
You should have disciplined him more strictly earlier?
That's all
I can say about this.
Master...
I know
you all have your own opinions
over the criminal punishment
that Cao Jianjun got.
It's true that
Cao Jianjun ever made a second-class merit.
I even personally awarded him
the medal for his merit.
So what?
Everyone is equal in front of the law.
Merits won't spare you from punishment when you make mistakes.
If there is any difference for the police,
then it's that the punishment will be harder
for the law-enforcer to break the law.
Cao Jianjun broke the law.
Both our bureau
and your station
should be blamed for failing in educating
and disciplining him.
The bureau has decided
to take Cao Jianjun as a negative example,
and conduct thorough education throughout the bureau
to strengthen the bureau's self-discipline.
[Balihe Police Station]
You're here.
Morning.
Yang Shu.
What are you looking at?
It's time to go on duty!
Mr. Chen, it's time to go on duty.
Dawei, let's go.
Jie.
Come to my office.
Jiwei.
Dashu.
I've been waiting for you. Where have you been?
Let's go.
Come with me.
There are quite a few neighborhoods we need to go today.
There's water leaking in Madam Ding's house.
She's nagging
and has complained about it for many times.
Okay.
Dashu.
I'm fine, so are you.
I'll talk to you later.
Qizi.
Ask Xu and others to go to the meeting room.
Xu.
Meeting in the conference room.
Coming.
What smells so good?
Let me guess with my eyes closed.
Cold pot skewers, right?
Why do I feel
this scene happened once before?
Where's Yang Shu? Being alone in his room?
I shall talk to him.
Dawei,
why can't you just
leave him some private space?
You know nothing.
Just listen to Jiajia.
Leave him alone.
Okay, thank you.
How is it? Is it good?
It's delicious.
I didn't expect
you would take me to eat pig face.
You really didn't eat your words.
I must keep my words!
You have to do it when you think of it.
Why are you looking at me?
You really don't want some?
I'll drink tea.
It's not the work time. Still be strict with yourself?
One of our capable colleagues
destroyed himself with the alcohol.
Drunk driving!
It not only got his police uniform stripped off,
but also got him sent to prison.
It wasn't totally drunk driving.
He...
It was that
all the troubles
came to him at once, you know?
Things are unpredictable.
Yes, things are unpredictable.
It's more often seen in the hospital.
There are so many people falling ill and passing away every day.
So, just take it easy.
I just think
he is really a good policeman.
He just made contributions.
How come...
Just...
Maybe this is his fate.
It's not about the fate.
It's about his personality.
Yes, that's right.
Let me tell you.
I once told Cao Jianjun,
that policeman who's now in prison...
I've been telling him,
Cao Jianjun,
you need to change your personality,
you have to change it,
if you don't,
you'll be in great trouble one day.
See? As expected.
It's been over ten years, but he hasn't changed at all.
If one's personality can be changed,
then so can the fate.
But if the fate can be changed,
then there's no such thing as fate at all.
Old buddy,
I just like talking to you.
It's penetrating.
Enough.
It's not easy for us to have a meal.
Don't be so depressed.
Say something happy.
I really have nothing happy to say,
nor could I find someone else to talk with.
Then just say as your wish.
Go ahead. I'm listening.
You listen, and I say.
I told you before that
four young people
came to our police station, right?
There's a top student from Peking University.
He was the disciple of Cao Jianjun,
that policeman who's now in prison.
After what happened to his master,
the bureau suddenly
had an important investigation,
which needed someone good at writing.
The bureau wanted him
and asked me if I agreed with it.
Then did you agree?
How can I...
For the bureau,
it's seemingly being nice,
but I know what it means.
It's just worrying that this treasure
may also get into trouble
if he keeps staying in our station.
You're a little anxious?
You think too much.
I'm just anxious.
Buddy, give me some advice.
Do you think I should agree
or disobey the order?
Can you disobey the order?
I certainly dare not disobey the order.
But
the director was my apprentice before.
I can ask him to seek some wiggle room.
Old buddy,
for what happened in the bureau and in your station,
you seldom talked a lot about it.
And I dare not to give you casual advice.
I can only tell you how I feel.
We just mentioned that everyone can get old, fall ill and finally dies.
Things are unpredictable.
You'll understand it after reading enough of it.
The thing is that
when you are capable of it,
then just try your best,
but when you're not,
then just let it be.
Capable of it...
Not capable of it...
Chief, what’s the matter?
Chief.
Instructor, Chief, are we gonna have a meeting?
What’s the subject for today?
Have a seat.
Sit.
Excuse me, Chief.
Chief Gao, Chief Cheng, Instructor.
Yang Shu is here.
Yang Shu.
I have
a very good thing.
The Municipal Bureau
will conduct
a special research.
And it will select a talent
from each police station.
The talent should be recommended by each police station.
For our station,
the Municipal Bureau directly selected Yang Shu,
saying that Yang Shu has an education background in law,
is good at writing,
and during the internship,
he had good performance.
Well...
The Municipal Bureau also
asked for our opinions,
saying that if we agree to get Yang Shu transferred...
I thought,
it would be a good thing.
This is a good thing, right?
Firstly, it proves
Yang Shu is a capable person,
a talent that's wanted by all.
Secondly,
the Balihe police station
must think for the greater good,
right?
Yang Shu, just do this.
Go through the handover procedure
and report to the Municipal Bureau.
It’s a good thing.
Well, Instructor, Director Cheng,
you two help Yang Shu
complete the handover procedure
and send a car
to take him to the Municipal Bureau.
Meeting adjourned.
Have you heard it?
Dr. Yang Shu will be transferred to the bureau.
At this time...
Cao Jianjun just went to jail,
I guess...
The bureau may not trust our station.
Well,
I've grown quite fond of that guy.
He's quite simple.
He is a good guy.
Yes.
Come out and talk.
You want to talk about Yang Shu, right?
You heard about it too?
I not only heard about it,
I also confirmed it with my master.
What are they doing?
It's said that the bureau asked to get him transferred.
What about Dashu?
I didn't see him when I came back.
I haven't seen him since I heard the news.
I asked where Yang Shu was
in WeChat group this afternoon,
but none of you replied.
How would I know what you are doing?
I guess Dawei thought so too.
He and his master have been on duty.
I supposed he missed the message.
What should we do?
What else can we do?
It's not a bad thing.
After we go back tonight,
let's happily hold a farewell party for Yang Shu.
Then tell Dawei in the WeChat group.
Let him come back early after he's done with the work.
Okay.
Let's go.
So suddenly...
Dawei,
why did you buy so many things?
I was ordered by Xia Jie and Zhao Jiwei
to buy some vegetables for tonight's hot pot
to bid farewell to Yang Shu.
Bid farewell to Yang Shu?
He has already left!
He left?
He came back in the afternoon and cleaned up his room for a while.
Then he pulled the luggage and told me
he was to work in the bureau for a while,
and it could be inconvenient to come here.
I thought you all knew.
Xia Jie, Dawei, Jiwei.
I'm going to the bureau.
I want to get used to the new environment in advance.
I shall not get together with you today.
I'll come back often.
Yang Shu
left without saying goodbye.
Fine, good for him.
No wonder that he kept being silent in the WeChat group.
He left so quietly.
Maybe it was for avoiding us.
Mom, did you eat on the plane?
I ate a piece of bread.
Is Dali fun?
No.
Don't you always think it's good?
When did I say that?
Fine.
You're back. Let's stop here.
It's meaningless to come back.
You are so busy at work every day.
You don't have time to accompany me.
Mom!
Why didn't the bureau
send a car to pick me up?
We have our own car.
Why must we bother the bureau?
The car is in the parking lot.
Let's go.
Mom.
Are you asleep?
I shall take a nap.
Hello, auntie.
My mom wasn't in a good mood when she came back.
Did something happen to her over there?
Jie.
It's because of Mr. Liang.
I think they two are very likely to break up.
Why?
Mr. Liang seems to have someone else.
I see.
It's not his fault.
At first, I could see he was quite passionate.
But your mother was always so proud.
Then Mr. Liang went to find someone else,
He also finished his work here in advance and went back.
Okay.
Thank you, auntie. I got it.
Jie.
Mr. Liang.
Jie, why are you here?
Come, let's talk in the shade.
It's hot here.
I just brought my mom back
from Dali yesterday.
Thank you
for taking care of my mom in Dali.
I'm here to express my gratitude.
Your mom is back?
Didn't she say she would spend the winter there?
She had this plan.
But I don't know why
she suddenly wanted to come back.
I only found out that you had also come back
after my mom came back.
Mr. Liang,
how is your relationship
with the new lady you found?
She was introduced by someone else.
I haven't decided it yet.
To be selfish,
my mom can't find someone better than you
in this world.
If you two miss each other,
it will not be your regret,
but hers.
I know.
Although your mother rejected me,
she actually relies on me in love.
I also don't want to let her go.
At first,
I was just hoping to repay your father's kindness to me.
Later, I felt pity for your mother.
Thanks for your endeavor, Jie.
If your mom is willing to be with me,
it will certainly be fine.
But...
I understand.
Mr. Liang, I'll ask my mom to reply you as soon as possible.
Okay.
Mom, you just came back. Have some fruit.
Our place is not as good as Dali, huh?
There's even no good show to watch.
Then let's not watch it.
What are you doing?
Mom, you've been away for so long.
I miss you too.
Let's not watch TV today
Let's have a chat.
Are you going to talk about that guy surnamed Liang again?
Mom, Mr. Liang is nice.
Why do you call him like this?
He is nice?
Jie.
Do you really dislike your mom so much?
Are you so eager to get your mother married?
Not at all!
I've been thinking for you
and protecting you.
I sacrificed everything for you.
But in the end,
you either moved
or wanted me to marry that guy surnamed Liang.
Tell me,
are you really so eager to get rid of me?
What are you thinking?
We've been living together for so many years.
How could I want to get rid of you?
Mom, I'm afraid you'll be lonely.
But I've been alone for so many years.
Besides, I still have you.
Mom,
I'll only get busier and busier at work.
And I'm already 22 years old.
Fine, a grown girl can't be kept!
I know you're 22.
Are you trying to say
you want to get married
and you need to date,
right?
I just want to say
I also want my own life.
What do you mean?
To be with mom
has prevented you from living your own life?
Why is my life so miserable?
Your dad left me alone.
Now even you're trying to get rid of me...
What's the point of my living in this world?