[tense music playing]
[Shimura groans]
This is a warning.
Shimura?
Shimura!
Aki.
Are you okay?
[groans]
I wasn't much of a fighter.
At least you're okay.
We've other issues now.
A warning?
But why Shimura?
Someone's jealous because we're popular,
so they attack Shimura?
Maybe.
You reek of alcohol.
Oh, no.
You're imagining things. [chuckles]
I'm underage, you know?
I tell you what…
if something like this happens again,
then next time I'm gonna--
It's very fishy.
Do I smell that bad?
These events are too coincidental.
- I agree.
- [sniffing]
It's likely that the hacker
and your attackers are the same guys.
Oh, now I get it.
But how did they do it?
Our username and passwords
are very secure.
It beats me too.
Unless somehow,
they got their hands on our password.
But how?
- Kanegon.
- Hmm?
You didn't fall for some phishing scheme
on a porn site, did you?
Oh, come on.
I'm not a pervert or anything.
Hey, Kanegon. Show us how you edit.
You really wanna know?
- Yes!
- No. Wait, really?
Okay. [laughs]
- Oh, this is so great.
- [phone beeps]
- [Toru] Let me see, V-I-R-A-L.
- [girl 1] Viral.
- [Toru] H-I-and-T
- [girl 2] Ah!
[girl 1] Don't forget the password.
[Toru] K-K-D…
[whimpers] Oh.
Hmm? What's wrong?
[Toru] Oh no.
It's nothing
HIGH SCHOOL
- Oh, hi. I had a great time last night--
- I'm sure you did.
- If you want the girls' info--
- [Toru] The password!
You stole it.
What? I don't know.
- You're making things up.
- Don't play dumb with me.
You got our account suspended
and you had those guys ambush Shimura.
What do you mean?
What are you accusing me of?
I don't have time for this.
[gasps]
Recently, I joined an agency. So I'm busy.
- Have a good day.
- Hey! Wait, you…
God dammit!
What am I going to do?
[pop music playing over speakers]
- Good work today.
- [Kaho] You too.
- What happened to you?
- Huh?
Your head.
Oh, this.
Did you fight again?
Uh, no, I didn't. I got ambushed.
It was two against one.
I didn't stand a chance.
Who did this to you?
I don't know. But, don't worry.
Next time, they don't stand a chance.
[chuckles]
Oh, here.
I forgot to return this. Thank you.
Oh, thank you.
[gate slams]
- [pop music continues]
- Uh, can I…
Huh?
Oh, yeah.
I was wondering about our café date.
Ah! [giggles]
I'll let you know, yeah?
- Well, better get back to it.
- Yeah, I'll be right there.
[phone buzzing]
I KNOW WHO DID IT
Kanegon?
[Rumi] Hey, so I heard
that Viral Hit's account got hacked.
Really?
Mr. Kimishima, was that you?
[laughs] And why would I do that?
Anyway, this is good.
Now you don't have them to worry about.
Hmm.
But… I really want more followers.
[chuckles] Oh, I know.
I told you.
I'll do anything for you, Rumi. Hmm?
[chuckles] Mm-hmm.
[Shimura] Influencer agency?
Yeah. Rumi recently joined an agency.
That's it there.
CANDY CROWN
CREATOR
- There she is.
- Not the point. Keep scrolling down.
Hey! These are the guys who attacked me.
Yeah, I thought so.
Now all the dots are connected.
We need to solve this quickly
so I can redeem myself to Aki.
Redeem yourself? Why?
- What's Aki got to do with…
- Come on! You know I have a crush on her.
- No.
- Hey, you haven't figured that out yet?
Uh, no.
[Toru] Jeez. We need
an emergency meeting now.
At Aki's!
Come on!
[Shimura] How long has this been going on?
PINGURI
They've got 600 subscribers who post
videos doing obnoxious shit in public.
And you think it was Rumi
who had them attack me, right?
She denied it, but there's
no doubt they're connected.
They got hold of my password
after she stole it.
Mmm.  Let's go to police.
There's no doubt that this is a crime.
[Toru] I know where you're coming from,
but if we do that, our channel,
it could get taken down.
Young people are flocking
to the streaming app
that we've been using.
But since it's so new,
there's no oversight.
That's how we do what we do.
If they find out
we're making money by using violence,
they'll ban our account immediately.
So, what are you saying?
We should forget it?
- [tense music playing]
- We've just found our next opponent.
They trapped you, they think,
but you allowed it. Didn't you?
Hang on a sec.
There are two of them, yeah?
I was off my guard when they attacked.
We'll be bringing down streamers
who attack members of the public.
Good content, it'll make money.
HOW TO BEAT A THUG IN A FIGHT
Can I really win by listening to you?
[groaning]
How am I supposed to fight
two guys at once?
[phone chimes]
NEW VIDEO ALERT
HOW TO WIN AGAINST MULTIPLE OPPONENTS
- Yes!
- [rhythmic electronic music playing]
[TOU-KEI] What happens when a person
with zero training in martial arts
attempts to fight
multiple opponents at once?
He will never win.
Yeah. But you're gonna show me
some new moves now, aren't you?
If you are serious about winning,
you must master
at least ten of my techniques.
Ten? Wow.
That's kind of a lot…
[inhales through teeth]
[TOU-KEI] That's right. In other words,
there's no chance
for a beginner like you to win.
You cannot win against multiple opponents.
So give up.
What? You serious?
I… oh… come on! There's nothing?
[TOU-KEI] However,
even if you can't win the fight,
you can still win the game.
URABE GENERAL HOSPITAL
I'm glad to hear
your son is enjoying school.
I think he's made some good friends.
He's been so lively lately.
Your son is busy enjoying his age!
He's already in high school.
- What if he starts dating someone?
- [laughs]
[woman] Now, we have a meeting
at 10:00 today.
Yes, I'm aware.
Great work today.
- Good morning.
- Hello, Director. Good morning.
Oh, look, are you feeling better today?
I have good and bad days.
Don't worry. With us working together,
we'll beat this thing.
- Thank you.
- Mm.
[nurse] The director's
such a wonderful man.
[tense music playing]
KABUKICHO
Hello!
- I'm Pink! Yeah!
- Green! Yeah!
Tonight we're hitting the nightlife
to prank some people!
Whoo!
Which unsuspecting victim
will give us the best reaction?
- It's showtime!
- Woo-hoo!
- Hey, hey. What about that girl? Woo-hoo!
- Yo!
- He went for it!
- [woman 1] So cute.
- [woman 2] Yeah, he's gorgeous.
- [Pink] Miss!
- There's a snake on you.
- [both scream]
Whoa! Oh my God!
[Green and Pink] Just run!
- [Pink] Come on, run!
- [Green] Just run!
[Pink] Run some more!
[Shimura] You bastards.
That's quite enough of your bullshit.
[militant music playing]
[Aki] Time to go live.
DID HE GET TALLER?
IT'S A GROWTH SPURT LOL
You're the guy from Viral Hit?
[Green] Why the hell are you here?
GET 'EM, SHIMURA! LOL
TOO FUNNY LOL
We're starting now.
The Viral Hit live stream.
[TOU-KEI] How to win
against multiple opponents.
The answer lies in your nature.
It's bluff and intimidation.
The bluff of a mantis,
fending off an attacker for survival!
The intimidation of a gorilla defending
his rank in the hierarchy.
Now, show them
that you can take them all on,
even though you're alone.
Last time you caught me off guard.
I can take you both on. Not an issue.
[grunts] Heh!
[TOU-KEI] The bluff of a mantis!
Give me the new password
and get the hell out of here…
[gruffly] …or I'll kill both of you!
[TOU-KEI] Intimidation of a gorilla!
Whoa, wait a minute.
We're already live, so…
[Green] That's right.
[both chuckle]
[TOU-KEI] However,
you must never forget this one point.
Don't ever let your opponent catch on…
[groans]
…to your bluff and intimidation.
- You idiot. What are you doing?
- I just…
[Pink] Hey, wait a minute. Look at this.
His shoes are full of all these insoles.
[both laughing]
Dipshit.
Do you think
we're dumb or something? Huh?
- [Shimura] Hey! Hey!
- [Green] Don't mess with us.
[laughs]
[Shimura] Damn it. I can't hear
the master's voice anymore.
What should I do?
- What's this? What's this!
- Stop it. I said stop!
- Come on! Show me!
- [Shimura groans]
- We're gone.
- [Green] Show me!
- [laughing]
- Look at his shoulder!
- [Green] It's all padded. It's fake!
- [laughing]
SHOULDER PADS ARE SO 80S
THIS IS HILARIOUS
[Pink] He's such a loser!
[rhythmic drum music playing]
[both laughing]
I can't stand your type of person.
It's time.
Beatdown time!
- [grunts]
- [groans] Ah!
[Pink] Don't mess with us.
- Take…
- [growls]
- [both straining, grunting]
- [suspenseful music playing]
[Pink] Damn it! That hurt, you bastard!
[all grunting]
[Shimura] I don't know.
Something's wrong with me.
[Pink] Ah! Take it!
- This is bad.
- Just wait.
- [Green] Yes!
- [grunting]
- [Shimura gasping, grunting]
- [Pink and Green grunting]
- [Shimura] What's happening to me?
- [Pink] Wait! Hey!
[Toru] Come on!
[Pink] Hey! Wait!
[Green] Hey!
[Pink] You're going nowhere! Hey!
- [Green] Wait!
- [Shimura] I'm scared to death.
- But at the same time, kinda pumped.
- [Pink and Green yelling]
VIRAL HIT
[motors revving]
- [Shimura panting]
- [Pink] Wait up!
Damn it!
Bastard! Stop running away! Hey!
[Shimura continues panting] Ah! Ah!
[Pink growls]
Catch him! Hey! Hey!
Get over here, bastard.
[motors revving]
- [Pink] Hey, stop!
- [Shimura grunting]
- [Pink] Hey!
- [man] Look out!
- [both grunting]
- [tires screeching]
[both yelping]
[boys yelping]
- Calf kick! Calf kick!
- [Green and Pink howl]
[grunting]
[Pink] Wait! Hey, you! Come back!
[Shimura grunting]
- [tires screeching]
- [Shimura yelping]
[Pink] You have to let it go!
- Calf kick! [grunts]
- [Pink yowls]
- [Pink wails] Ow!
- [Shimura grunting, panting]
[Green] Ugh! That really hurt.
[Pink] You bastard.
I won't forgive you!
- [Pink and Green gasping]
- [Aki] That's enough!
The match is over, can't you see?
Huh? Who the hell are you?
You know much better than anyone
how exhausted you must be.
[Green] Don't mess with us.
- We're not leaving until this is finished.
- All right then, go ahead.
That is, if you don't care
that you look like a couple of asses.
MISSED THE BEST BIT LOL
KEEP UP, CAMERAMAN!
[panting]
Hand over the password, then go home.
- Shit!
- [both thud]
[Green groans] Shit!
PASSWORD CHANGE COMPLETE
[Ai] Everything's back to normal.
I've changed the password again.
Yeah! I didn't expect you
to put up a fight like this.
When they started at you,
I thought you were done! [chuckles]
Yes, that's right.
Well… have I just gone nuts?
I don't fully understand it either.
At some point,
I was afraid, but also fearless.
Like… like I was pumped, you know?
That's so great.
Main thing is you're okay.
Maybe I'm not okay at all. [laughs]
[driving electronic music playing]
Hello there. I apologize
to all of you about the recent suspension.
- CONGRATS ON YOUR COMEBACK
- YOU WENT THROUGH HELL
Our main channel was hijacked
by some nasty trolls.
My recent fight you saw on the subchannel,
you can now see on my main channel.
Oh, and please, keep up the donations!
- [device beeps]
- Okay!
Aki, how are the donations?
- [Aki] Fantastic donations pouring in.
- [Shimura] All right!
You see, you can't do without me, can you?
You've got a nerve, haven't you?
You're the one
who got us into this trouble.
[Toru] Yeah, sorry about that.
Kanegon.
What's next for us then?
[video game sounds bleeping]
[game characters grunting]
[man 1] Hey, when are you gonna quit?
[man 2] Move, damn it!
[game voice] K.O.
I died.
Your turn's over. Over!  Now move it!
Go!
[man 2] What, punk? Wanna go?
What are you, Viral Hit 2.0?
[tense music playing]
Give me 100.
[man 1] What?
[men groaning]
VIRAL HIT
#3 RECOMMENDED VIDEO
[students screaming on video]
[HAMAKEN on video]You little rat!
VIRAL HIT
#1 TOP PICK VIDEO
Viral Hit.
[music fades]
I'll put your fresh clothes here.
Thank you.
- Say, have you heard of streamers?
- What?
Kids these days want to be streamers
when they grow up. It says it, just look.
Is that right?
#1 DREAM JOB FOR BOYS:
STREAMER
Oh, but I'm not into that. [chuckles]
Of course not.  Why would people want
to watch streaming of you?
[Shimura] Ah, you're right.
Oh, maybe I should give it a try.
And who's gonna watch that?
Oh, I think I'd be pretty good at it.
Like a mother fighting off
a disease. [laughs]
[chuckles]
Just curious.
What do you think now
that you've read about them?
Why do you ask?
Oh. Like I said, just curious.
I don't see anything wrong with it.
But… I'd be worried as a parent.
I'd rather my child work
a normal job like you do now.
I see.
Oh.  It's time for me to get going.
- So busy! Working again?
- No.
There's just something I need to do.
You seeing a girl?
Oh, of course not. No, you're wrong!
Aw. That's too bad.
[both laugh]
VIRAL HIT
[Toru] Viral Hit is looking for fighters.
Refer yourself or others.
All right, it's uploaded.
Oh, look!
It's already got views.
Where's Shimura today?
Who knows?
He said he was busy or something.
Is he working?
Don't think so.
- Oh.
- He's seeing Asamiya.
He was all serious,
saying he had to see her today.
I think it might be a date.
And, you know, it's…
just the two of us here now. Isn't it?
[chuckles] Aren't you nervous, you know?
- [poignant music playing]
- Uh…
- So, Aki… do you have a boyfriend?
- [door slams open loudly]
Don't you dare
lay a finger on my daughter.
KYOTO VEGETABLE MIBUNA
BUBUZUKE
- Oh, I would never.
- [jaunty music playing]
Well, I don't think I trust you.
Oh, that's silly.
What are you talking about, Dad?
Dad?
Aki.
I'm glad that you made friends,
but why do you only bring men around here?
[Aki] Oh, shut up and get back to work.
- Deh!
- [splutters]
Hey!
[slides door closed loudly]
Sorry.
[laughs] It's okay.
I guess you guys are, um, used to
joking around with each other, yeah?
Uh… he was deadly serious.
Oh, I see.
Where did you live when you were overseas?
We were in the US.
Yeah? That's really great.
Dad's work took us there for 12 years.
It… was tough.
- [buoyant electronic music playing]
- [birdsong]
[no in-scene audio]
Thank you for paying. Hope it was okay.
It was my way
to thank you for the other day.
That's nice!
Parfait was great!
Mm. You wanted to talk?
Something on your mind?
Oh, right. Uh, yes.
[Shimura] Now I can't make myself ask it.
Asamiya-san…
- Your house, it's fancy.
- Huh?
[Shimura] What the hell am I saying?
Actually, the other day,
I followed you
to return your handkerchief.
Uh, I…I wasn't trying to stalk you.
Mm, I understand.
It just… felt like you and I…
are kind of different.
Your dad must be a very important person.
That's not true. He's fairly normal.
I wondered why you worked part-time.
What's so weird about that?
I guess nothing. [laughs]
So that was it?
Oh.
No. Not entirely.
[music fades].
Another time, I think.
Mm. Okay, then.
[laughs softly]
Guys! [laughs]
I found your next opponent.
Really, who is it?
Shinjo Reo.
He's a Tae kwon do champion.
Tae kwon do?
The thought of you facing off with him
is sending the viewers crazy!
He's a high school dropout
and notorious troublemaker.
They say that he smashes
his wristwatch every fight.
It's a hot matchup.
The buzz will be huge
and think of the donations.
- Wait a minute, I--
- [Aki] It's too dangerous.
It's reckless
taking on a skilled guy like that.
I agree.
Sorry, but that's how it is.
The reason the viewers are so hyped…
is 'cause he volunteered himself!
@REOSHINJO FIGHT ME
IT'S HIM!
SHINJO FOUND YOU!
GAME OVER LOL
No way.
- [woman] Asamiya?
- Yeah?
['60s pop music playing over speakers]
Did you see this?
VIRAL HIT'S HOT GIRLFRIEND!
Oh, that's us.
[man] Someone managed to figure it out
from the video of you
on Hamaken TV and Viral Hit.
FOUND TRUE BEAUTY!
WIFE MATERIAL
[woman] You should be careful.
Let me know if any weirdos come in.
I'll tell the manager.
Yeah.
Don't let
these test results bring you down.
- Your numbers will improve again.
- [sighs]
- [boy 1] Whoa!! Awesome!
- [boy 2] He won again!
[mother] Sh! Boys!
Keep it down. We're in hospital.
It's okay.
Oh, that looks fun. What are you watching?
Viral Hit.
He's super popular.
[doctor] So, this is
what kids are into these days?
[boy 2] I'm gonna be a streamer
when I grow up.
[chuckles] Very good. I hope you will. Mm.
- Thank you so much. Thank you.
- Oh! Awesome punching!
ASAMIYA: THAT WAS FUN
SEE YOU AT WORK
[phone chiming]
Hi there.
Shimura, where are you?
I'm heading off to work. Why?
Aki, she's in trouble!
[ominous music playing]
[Shimura panting]
Don't make me repeat myself.
Shimura will not fight you.
I wasn't asking you.
Aki, that's enough. Let's go.
Let me go!
You volunteered yourself
and now the viewers are egging us on.
Withdraw your challenge.
Don't tell me what to do.
- Please, Aki, let's go home. Come on!
- Aki. Are you okay?
Did you call him?
- I'm sorry.
- You should be ashamed.
Let's go home, Aki.
[Reo] Wait a second.
Will you fight me?
[ominous music continues]
I'm sorry, but I won't.
You're far too strong.
Then…
hand over your channel.
Huh?
[grunts] Ah! Ah!
- [Shimura] Kanegon!
- I know you're making bank.
[Toru coughing]
- Give it to me.
- [Toru hacking]
- What are you saying? [grunts, groans]
- [Shimura] Stop this!
[yelping] Ah! Ugh!
Ugh! Ugh! Ugh!
- [kicks thudding]
- [Toru grunting]
I said stop it!
[music fades]
[tense music playing]
[Reo] Hand it over.
Stop it! You're gonna kill him!
[screaming]
Let go of me!
[solemn choral music playing]
[yelping]
[shudders]
[Aki choking]
Okay! Okay, then.
You can have it.
Our channel, it's yours.
Just stop. Stop doing this.
[gasps]
Announce it in a video.
Tell everyone.
[music fades]
I hear that streamers are all the craze
amongst the younger generation.
Um, yeah, they are.
They're even recognized by society now.
It's a cop-out for losers
who can't land a real job.
RUMI
72,000 FOLLOWERS
[footsteps approach]
Here.
My follower account
has stopped growing lately.
You'll have times like that.
What should I do?
Hmm.
Well, it costs money to get exposure
and to promote you, you see.
[eerie music playing]
If you took on more jobs,
the cost can be offset.
Well, that's what I'll do.
I'll take on more jobs.
Will you? Really?
Ah, that would help out a lot.
Our sponsors are important.
I'll do it. What is it?
The job is simple.
That was a disaster, wasn't it?
Things are just getting too dangerous.
We're
just not cut out for this, I think.
I'm not buying it.
Huh?
I didn't want to hand it over.
That's our channel. It belongs to us.
[poignant music playing]
When you took on Hamaken,
I,
truthfully, was very moved.
If we're weak and even made fun of,
that it's okay to be brave.
Miracles can happen.
So how can you…
say that you'll give up
the channel so easily?
[labored breathing]
Is that…
how little you care for Viral Hit
and all we've done?
Yeah, it is.
There's no point
taking on a guy like that for real.
I'm not an idiot.
[Aki] Are you okay?
What's wrong?
[poignant music continues]
Go away.
What are you saying?
- Aki came all this way--
- Just go!
Get outta here.
Come on, let's go.
[grunting] Ah! Ah!
[echoes] Stop it! You're gonna kill him!
[groans, yelps]
[whimpering]
[choking, straining]
[crying]
[tender music playing]
I am such an idiot.
When Shinjo sets his sights on a target,
he attacks their friends
rather than the target themselves.
In front of the target.
He's a real psychopath who gets a rush
from leaving his opponents
totally helpless and also humiliated.
And they…
They say…
he murdered
a fellow delinquent a few years ago.
He was released
due to lack of evidence,
but no one has been charged
with the killing.
That's how dangerous he is.
Someone like that…
I won't fight.
That's our channel. It belongs to us.
Is that
how little you care
for Viral Hit and all we've done?
[groaning]
- [games whirring, chattering]
- [muffled dance music playing over PA]
[Reo] Uploaded the video yet?
Not yet.
As I promised,
you can have that channel to yourself.
But… I have one condition.
You must defeat me
in a fight one month from now.
Just say time and place
when you actually decide.
So that's how it is.
[Aki] Huh?
What the hell are you thinking?
I told you not to do this.
- I know, but I have.
- Take it back! Immediately!
It's too late. We've already agreed on it.
I knew it.
You are an idiot.
You keep quiet.
Well, I'll be off.
I gotta start my training, yeah.
Hey. Wait, Shimura.
This time, you might not
just walk away with injuries.
So, why… are you doing this?
For money. Why else would I?
[footsteps depart]
You must be kidding!
You just took an entire month off.
Yes, I'm sorry.
So, how long do you want
to take off this time?
- [jaunty music playing]
- About the same.
[scoffs] Shimura!
Are you secretly studying abroad
or something like that?
- Who takes leave from a part-time job?
- I'm very sorry.
What… now you're gonna run?
- [entry bell jangles]
- Shimura! Huh!
Asamiya!
I talked to the manager about your shift.
I'm sorry for causing you trouble.
Mm.
Is this another fight?
Oh, don't worry though.
I've got someone I can count on.
- I see.
- Mm.
Tell me, would you still…
do it if your friend… wasn't there?
[chuckles] Why are you asking me that?
[chuckles] Well, you keep challenging
tougher opponents. I'm worried.
Oh, that's nice.
I was wondering…
whether we could go out again
when my next fight is over?
I want to tell you what I couldn't
the last time we met.
Of course!
It's a date, okay?
Mm. Okay, deal!
Mm. [giggles]
Tae kwon do?
I need to learn so I can win this thing.
Well… if you can stop him
from using his legs,
you might have a chance at winning.
Stop him using his legs.
But…  that's not something
a novice can accomplish in a month.
Yeah, I figured that.
- [man] Hey, Tatsuya. Time for a spa.
- Okay.
- Oh, sorry, I interrupted.
- No worries. Happy to help you.
Thanks.
- Here you go.
- Let's do it.
[door opens, closes]
[Shimura] Oh, nothing.
[man 1] He's here, Sir.
- [man 2 groans]
- This way.
[tense music playing]
[echoing] That's BAD FELLOWS.
Who are they?
You don't know?
It's a super popular show that pits
amateur fighters against each other.
- Are you Shimura from Viral Hit?
- Uh, yes.
I'm the representative of BAD FELLOWS,
I'm Kuwata.
Oh, yes. I've heard of you.
That makes things easier.
What do you say?
Would you star in our show?
Hey?
You could become
even more famous than you are now.
Oh
Uh, wow.
Sorry, I'm not interested
in that kind of thing.
Hmm?
I guess it's just… I mean, I'm not looking
to become a professional fighter.
And I'm not interested in becoming famous.
Okay.
Well… if you ever do need money,
please come to me anytime.
I'd be glad to help you.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[Kuwata] Hmm.
- And there you are.
- Thank you.
There's your change.
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you so much.
- Thanks, have a nice day.
- [woman] That was delicious.
- [door opens]
- [bell jangles]
- [door closes]
- Okay, who's next?
- ['60s pop music playing over PA]
Dad.
VIRAL HIT'S HOT GIRLFRIEND!
[Hamaken on video] You're so annoying,
you piece of trash!
[Shimura] I'm not a loser,
but you're a loser for sure!
[Hamaken groans]
[sighs]
[phone chimes]
[man] Any more would be dangerous.
LOGAN
[pensive music playing]
[grunting]
[phone chimes]
NEW VIDEO FROM HOW_TO_FIGHT
HOW A NOVICE CAN BEAT
A TAE KWON DO FIGHTER
[music fades]
ONE MONTH LATER
[dramatic rock music playing]
Let's go.
[Aki] They say
he murdered
a fellow delinquent a few years ago.
[Toru] What? Shimura, where are you going?
He's fast.
[tense music playingj]
[Shimura] Fighting mindset,
rule number one.
Make your opponent lose his cool.
You little…
What are you doing?
[Toru] You stay here.
We'll use this to talk.
But why can't I come?
I want to handle this alone.
I don't want you to see me…
when I'm frightened.
IT'S ALREADY STARTED!
GO! SHIMURA!
IS HE SPRAYING WATER?
I NEED YOU TO WIN, SHIMURA
I'M SWEATING LOLOL
IT'S HAPPENING!!!
[drops hose]
[exhales]
[whooshing]
Keep your eyes shut, and you're dead.
How to beat a tae kwon do fighter,
rule one.
Take control of the space
so they can't use their feet.
[Shimura grunting]
[groans]
[grunting]
Dumbass.
You thought you could win
by splashing water?
[straining]
[gasping]
What made you think I'd only kick?
[Shimura groaning]
This is… a fight, right?
[Shimura grunting]
You're right.
This is a fight.
[squeaks]
WHY ISN'T SHIMURA SLIPPING?
HE'S WEARING WATER SHOES!
THAT'S SNEAKY LOL
[Shimura grunting]
[Shimura] It's not over yet.
We've barely begun.
[grunting continues]
[TOU-KEI] Nothing in the world frustrates
a kicker a more
than a tackle.
The key to a successful tackle is
to grab the back of the knees.
Grab and pull
at the back of your opponent's knees.
You can take down even a large opponent.
This is the double leg tackle!
Yeah!
[music intensifies]
[TOU-KEI] If the takedown is successful,
your odds jump past 50%.
But you must never swing
your fist from above.
You only get one chance
against a martial opponent.
You must finish them off in one blow.
Put your hand behind your opponent's neck,
grab their collar and pull them close.
[grunting]
[both straining]
[TOU-KEI] Even if your opponent resists,
don't let go!
This is a technique
that compresses the carotid artery.
The cross choke!
It takes ten seconds
for your opponent to pass out.
So, count it out in your head.
[Shimura] One…
Two…
- Yeah!
- Three…
Four…
Five…
- [students murmur]
- [Shimura] Six…
Seven…
Eight…
Nine…
HUH?
SHINJO DOESN'T LOOK WORRIED
YOU'RE RIGHT LOLOL
[Shimura straining]
- That's bad, the choke came off.
- [Shimura groans]
Idiot.
- You didn't land it right.
- [gasps]
[Shimura grunting]
Shimura!
ALMOST HAD IT!
YOU WERE SO CLOSE!
Oh no.
Shinjo allowed the hold deliberately.
Huh?
[Reo] You really thought
I'd fall for that move?
[breathing heavily, sniffs]
This is what I wanted.8
[shoe plops]
[TOU-KEI] Remember, the only way
for an amateur to beat
a tae kwon do fighter
is to steal their kicks.
Now I can use the legs.
[TOU-KEI] And if you fail to do that,
there's only one thing left to do.
- Run for your life!
- [alarm blaring]
[gasps]
- [kick thuds]
- [Shimura groans]
[Toru] Shimura!
It's too dangerous. Run!
[Shimura] I'm such an idiot.
Especially after all of that practice.
[Shimura groaning, grunting]
Oh shit.
This guy, he's gonna kill Shimura.
[solemn choral music playing]
[approaching sirens wailing]
[gasping]
[Japanese rock music playing]
VIRAL HIT
[Japanese rock music continues]
[music ends]