I'm sure you're aware Japan's ratio
of determining the cause of death
is much lower than in other countries?
Yes.
To improve that,
we're going to experimentally introduce
the American medical examiner system.
Medical examiner?
The biggest difference from Japan's system
is that medical examiners,
or forensic pathologists,
have investigative authority.
What?
Does that mean doctors
can investigate cases like the police?
No, not in exactly the same way,
but they can conduct investigations
to determine the cause of death.
They also have the authority
to determine the need for an autopsy.
I see…
So,
we're bringing in Dr. Masumi Mizusawa,
who has worked as a medical examiner
in the US for 15 years.
And Ms. Kiryu,
you'll be the director
of Medical Examiner Japan.
Okay.
What?
Why am I being demoted?
I mean, there's no way a policy change
is going to increase the rate
of determining the cause of death.
And you know,
I became a bureaucrat
because I wanted to create systems
that let everyone in this country
live their lives smiling.
This topic is not even my specialty.
I don't have the knowledge.
And I'm supposed to be in charge on-site?
There's no way I can do it.
CENTER DIRECTOR
MAHO KIRYU
Oh! Dr. Mizusawa?
I'm Masumi Mizusawa.
Call me Masumi.
I'm Kiryu.
- Pleasure to meet you.
- Same here.
Huh?
- Did you just come from the airport?
- Yes.
Are you okay with your jet lag?
Well… I don't know.
You know, jet lag is like rigor mortis.
Jet lag is like rigor mortis?
What do you mean?
Well…
Jet lag doesn't happen
just because of time.
It depends on light exposure
and the amount of sleep.
Rigor mortis isn't determined
by time alone either.
It changes based on temperature,
humidity, and posture.
In other words, both depend
not just on time, but on conditions.
Oh, okay.
Right…
Good.
It finally starts tomorrow,
the medical examiner system.
Ms. Dojima, should we call them?
Call who?
You know, the new system starting today,
where we have to report
all abnormal deaths
to that, uh, medical examiner.
Oh, that ridiculous system.
No need to call them.
Yes, ma'am!
At this hour, no one would even
answer the phone, right?
Call them then.
It will prove
that we tried to contact them.
Yes, ma'am! I will call them!
They answered!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It's fine.
Decomposition doesn't progress much
at this hour.
What?
Hello.
Who are you? What are you--
Hey, stop!
- He's the medical examiner.
- Huh?
What's that? I wasn't told about it.
I'm the supervisor, Kiryu.
With the new system, any unusual deaths
must first be examined by
a forensic pathologist.
The medical examiner will--
Um…
The deceased's mother
was the first to discover the body.
His clothes are wet.
Keitaro Aikawa, 17 years old.
He didn't come home by dawn,
so his mother got worried, searched
the neighborhood, and found him here.
She called 119 and performed CPR.
They determined he was clearly
already dead, so he wasn't transported.
Found a smartphone.
The pond is about 40 centimeters deep.
- This is murder.
- Yes.
There's no way someone drowns
in a pond this shallow.
I'm sorry to bother you at a tough time.
May I ask about the situation
when you found your son--
Hey, don't… I'm sorry, Ma'am.
Back off.
Doctor.
Could you stop interfering
in the investigation?
I'm not interfering.
What?
You just did.
This is a legitimate investigation
based on the authority
granted to a medical examiner.
Supervisor.
Care to explain what's going on?
In order to determine the cause of death,
medical examiners
are granted investigative rights.
Are you playing detective?
Also, under this system,
all abnormal deaths must be evaluated,
and the medical examiner
decides if an autopsy is needed.
It's clearly a murder.
It is, it is a murder!
We still don't know
whether it's a homicide.
You're in my way.
Why is a bureaucrat the director here?
What?
Do you even have a medical license?
Do you?
No, I don't, but this is not only
a medical institution, it's also part of
the country's policy
in determining the cause of death.
There's a document from the Ministry
about autopsy regulations, right?
Yes.
Created by the department
overseeing the medical system.
That document
is completely useless in the field.
You don't say.
Really?
Of course, it is.
It was made by bureaucrats
who don't understand the field.
Let's begin.
Are you okay?
I'm totally fine.
The cause of death is drowning.
In a 40-centimeter-deep pond?
- Yes.
- How could he have drowned there?
So he drowned somewhere else
and was moved there?
No, that doesn't add up.
The plankton in the pond water
matches what was in his lungs.
That means he was alive
when he entered the water.
So he was assaulted, lost consciousness,
and then thrown into the pond?
There were small abrasions on his palms.
Possibly defensive injuries
from when he fell.
That suggests he was conscious,
trying to defend himself.
It doesn't add up.
So then, he was pushed
into the pond while conscious?
The pond is 40 centimeters deep.
He should have been able to stand up.
It doesn't add up.
Then maybe someone held his face down
while he tried to get up.
That would leave marks on the head,
neck, and shoulders.
It doesn't add up.
So then how did he drown
in a 40-centimeter-deep pond?
Who knows?
I wonder.
It's a mystery.
Well, whatever.
Then,
what about signs of assault?
There are injuries to the head and chest
caused by external force.
First, on the head, the marks
are concentrated in two places.
Likely left by a great external force,
such as from a weapon.
As for the chest fractures,
there are three patterns.
One was caused by CPR.
There was no bleeding or vital reaction.
In regard to this area,
it shows a significant loss of blood,
and was very likely caused by assault.
And the last one
is one that can't be explained
by either of the other two.
It does not show a strong vital reaction,
but there was something.
This mark shows the slightest
amount of vital reaction.
Is that the clue to
determining it was homicide?
I don't know if it will or not.
But it might be a piece of the puzzle
to solve the mystery.
Anyway, solve it quickly.
- Supervisor.
- Yes?
Do your job and supervise.
What's that?
The content of the notebook by the pond.
The phone next to it
was the one that belonged to
Keitaro Aikawa.
Then the phone in the pond…
Still being verified.
Does anyone know what this means?
For now, it's a mystery.
We identified the owner of the phone.
- What?
- Ryoya Sakagami, 17 years old.
One arrest for marijuana dealing.
He's a member of a group
based out of Club Heads
that engages in fraud and drug dealing.
Why are you running away?
Hey!
Police! Nobody move!
When was the last time
you saw Ryoya Sakagami?
You were having him sell marijuana,
were you not?
Don't know him.
Cut the crap! Don't cover for a murderer!
Murderer?
Ryoya?
Who did he kill?
- Aikawa--
- A 17-year-old boy.
You don't mean…
Keitaro?
How do you know that?
Was he one of your group too?
Any marijuana show up?
Initially not,
but when we retested
using liquid chromatography,
marijuana was detected
in Keitaro Aikawa's blood and urine.
I knew it.
Huh? What does that mean?
Keitaro Aikawa
was part of a marijuana trafficking group.
He and one of the members, Ryoya Sakagami,
ran off with the marijuana.
Then, they may have had
a falling out, and he was killed.
We're currently tracking Ryoya Sakagami
as a key person of interest.
I'm going to Keitaro Aikawa's home.
- What's that?
- Some questions need answers.
The numbers and arrows in the notebook,
the weak vital signs
of the chest fracture,
and why he drowned
in a 40-centimeter-deep pond.
There may be pieces there
that solve these mysteries.
Hey, Supervisor!
Medical examiners are granted
investigative rights to gather info--
- Hold on!
- Wait!
SONGWRITING NOTES VOL 3
DID THE SOUND GET WORSE??
IT'S NOT FAIR
GOD SAVE ME
WHY?
I'M SCARED… REALLY SCARED
IT'S OVER
I'M SO, SO SCARED
SHIT SHIT SHIT
Ms. Dojima.
No marijuana was found.
Let's go.
Okay.
Did Keitaro like music?
If you're done, leave already.
Man, I'm exhausted.
Today felt insanely long. Way too long.
Being demoted was humiliating enough,
but going out into the field
made it even worse.
I really can't do anything.
I'm just there. Just watching.
But I'm the one in charge.
I want to go back to my old job.
There's no way
I'm stuck in the field forever, right?
This is Medical Examiner Japan.
He really liked music.
It sounds silly, but…
he used to say he wanted to be a musician…
Even though
becoming one
is harder than winning the lottery.
But
then…
his hearing went bad.
He said
he was giving up on music.
He had worked so hard at it,
so I think
it was a massive shock to him.
Around that time,
Ryoya…
a delinquent he knew
from middle school, invited him.
Because of him…
Keitaro joined a bad crowd.
Marijuana, huh?
Maybe he…
Maybe he was a good-for-nothing kid,
but to me,
he was my precious child.
I want to know why this happened.
I want to know what happened.
The whole truth.
Please.
Find out the truth.
If he was murdered…
I will never forgive them.
I have no future left, anyway.
I'll live my life just to hate the killer.
What are you doing?
What? Sudoku?
Hey, where are you going?
- The pond.
- What?
There might be a piece
I haven't found yet.
What are you doing here?
Investigating.
Investigating, huh?
Did the police find out anything?
It wasn't on the day of the crime.
He was seen with a man
thought to be Ryoya Sakagami.
Standing opposite each other
across the pond.
They were shouting, clapping,
and throwing stones into the water.
Most likely, they were just high
and acting out.
Oh, it's Ms. Dojima. Excuse me.
Don't answer.
- No, but--
- I said don't answer it.
What?
The pieces
might be…
coming together.
Hey!
Damn it!
Let me go!
Now what?
- I would like you to check something.
- What?
About the apps on Keitaro Aikawa's phone.
Look, forget it.
They caught Ryoya Sakagami,
and the interrogation is about to start.
I'll be right there!
- You're even coming to the interrogation?
- Yes.
Based on the legitimate authority
granted to a medical examiner--
Enough!
Fine, I get it.
You went to the pond on April 6th, right?
What happened there?
What did you do?
I didn't go to the pond.
Then why was your phone found in the pond?
Excuse me.
May I ask a question?
Go ahead.
Do you know
what this is?
You know
what this means, don't you?
Yes.
And,
there were three types of fractures
on Keitaro Aikawa's chest.
The first
was from being assaulted.
The second
was from his mother performing CPR.
The third one…
was from you, right?
What happened?
I'm sorry.
I will now explain
the cause of Keitaro's death.
Please.
We determined
that the cause of death was drowning.
First, around 5:00 p.m. the prior evening,
he was struck in the head,
causing a hematoma,
essentially a lump.
Left alone, it was an injury
that would have healed naturally.
After that, Keitaro came to this pond.
This pond has a bridge spanning it,
and the surrounding slopes
form a bowl shape,
creating an environment
where sound echoes easily.
MASUMI MIZUSAWA
The sound bounces back
from various directions,
making you lose sense
of where it's actually coming from.
For Keitaro, who was hard of hearing
in his left ear,
it was particularly confusing.
Then, at around 10:00 p.m. that night,
while Keitaro was standing
at the edge of the pond,
a motorcycle horn honked.
A horn is designed to resonate loudly
in a specific direction ahead.
Keitaro got startled by it,
feeling as though the sound source
was close to him.
He instinctively tried to avoid
the loud noise from an unknown direction,
and it is likely that he slipped.
He fell into the pond
and hit his head on the water's surface.
At that moment,
a second impact was delivered
to a brain that had already been damaged.
This is known as Second Impact Syndrome.
If the brain receives a second blow
before it has recovered from the first,
even a minor force can amplify the damage
and lead to a fatal outcome.
In Keitaro's case,
he suffered a severe concussion
and lost consciousness.
As a result,
he drowned in a pond
only 40 centimeters deep.
What?
In other words,
it was a tragic accident resulting
from a series of coincidences.
An accident?
If he hadn't been hit in the head,
he wouldn't have died, right?
If that horn hadn't been honked,
he wouldn't have died.
He died because someone did those things,
didn't he?
And yet, you call it an accident.
I won't accept that.
I can't let it be.
Keitaro was murdered.
Wasn't it Ryoya who honked the horn?
I know he rides a bike.
That boy killed Keitaro, right?
Arrest him. Aren't you the police?
I understand how you feel.
But based on the objective facts,
the police are treating this case
as an accident.
We have released the person of interest
after questioning.
That's not right.
Keitaro is dead,
so why does he get to live a normal life?
I understand how you feel,
but these are the facts
derived from a forensic perspective.
I told you
I can't accept that.
Shouldn't we tell her about it?
That thing?
Yes.
My job is to convey the results
of the cause-of-death investigation.
Anything else is not for me to say.
However…
you are the supervisor, Ms. Kiryu.
If there is something else
you want to convey,
please use your own judgment.
But to me,
he was my precious child.
I want to know what happened.
The whole truth.
The one who honked the horn
was Ryoya Sakagami.
Hey.
What are you doing?
It's the decision of the supervisor.
Do what you want.
The police won't take responsibility.
Ms. Aikawa…
Keitaro hadn't given up on his dream.
How could you know that?
It's the arrows and numbers
written in the notebook.
Because Keitaro
could only hear out of one ear,
the direction sound was coming from
differed from the actual source.
He was using this pond
to confirm that deviation,
and was trying to correct it himself.
Close! You're almost there.
The arrows are the direction of the sound,
and the numbers represent
the angle of the shift.
You're amazing, Keitaro.
You're making progress.
I shouldn't have invited you
into the gang.
I'm really sorry.
Do you think I can still be a musician?
You will.
If anyone can, it's you.
So you have to get out of the gang.
Right.
But,
my mom used to say all the time
that becoming a musician
is harder than winning the lottery.
And then, on that day, Keitaro was…
I…
want out.
I don't want…
to sell marijuana anymore.
Come here!
The trace amount of marijuana
detected in Keitaro
was most likely from secondhand smoke.
Can't you just let Keitaro go?
I'll sell his share too.
Just please
let Keitaro out.
Please!
Hey.
Hey!
Stand up, asshole.
Don't fuck with us!
Please…
Please!
- You little shit…
- Please…
Take that!
Bastard!
Please.
You little shit…
In exchange,
you bring in three million yen
in one week.
Thank you!
Lame.
He honked his horn
because he wanted to tell Keitaro
the good news.
He was just happy and honked it.
Hey!
Quit messing around.
Keitaro!
Hey! Keitaro? Hey!
Hey!
Keitaro!
Keitaro…
I thought he might have died
because of the CPR I gave him.
I got scared and ran away.
I'm sorry.
If Ryoya had called an ambulance,
would he have lived?
No.
Even if he had called one,
the result would have been the same.
There was a fracture
on Keitaro's chest that showed
a very slight vital reaction.
That was
from the CPR performed
by Ryoya Sakagami.
The fact that the vital reaction
was so minimal
proves that the CPR
was performed immediately after death.
In other words, it means that Keitaro
had already passed away.
Ms. Aikawa.
CPR…
was performed twice.
The two sets of marks
on Keitaro's chest were both
left by people
who desperately wanted him to live.
Keitaro…
Keitaro!
Please!
Stay with me, Keitaro!
Keitaro!
Please!
So…
you're telling me to forgive him?
Don't make it sound so simple.
Dying like that…
is harder than winning
the lottery, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry…
Regarding the pickup
of Keitaro Aikawa's body,
the funeral director should be here
in about 20 minutes.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you for today.
But,
I think my decision today
was one step away
from rubbing the bereaved mother
the wrong way.
In America,
they call the deceased a "Loved One."
Loved One?
Does that mean someone…
who was important
to someone else?
The term…
is hard to translate.
What?
It's a word only used at the scene,
and also a word only for oneself.
A word only for oneself?
Yes.
Only you can decide
what it means.
Your decision today
was your own way
of facing a Loved One, wasn't it?
The death was caused by a fall.
Is it fun?
Talking about someone's death like that?
If I had known it would be
the last time, I--
It's not over yet.
You're a forensic pathologist.
There may still be a piece
we haven't found yet.
Subtitle translation by: Maslin F.