BASED ON THE WEBTOON SERIES
THE TRAUMA CODE: HEROES ON CALL
DEPARTMENT OF TRAUMA SURGERY
DUTY DOCTOR ROOM
Are you a zombie or what?
Are you dead?
Are you finished?
All right, you're still alive.
Anus, keep it down.
- Not again!
- What is it?
The audit team sent a warning email.
FW: BUDGET CUTS WARNING FOR TRAUMA CENTER
Dr. Baek's sure gone all out.
I know you can't just ignore the red ink,
but this is a hospital after all.
Hello, Trauma Team.
Yang Jae-won of trauma surgery.
Dr. Yang, there's been a pile-up.
Get here fast!
I'm on my way.
Dr. Baek, you need to wake up.
Patients?
Yes, the ambulance is on its way.
Start running.
- Sorry!
- Dr. Baek!
At this rate, I might drop dead first.
- Should I make that happen?
- No, sir!
What a great runner.
Let's start prepping.
- Dr. Baek will be here any minute.
- Okay!
Are you okay?
- Yes.
- I'm sorry.
- Thank you.
Hey, Gangster.
So what happened?
- Don't call me that.
- Shut up and fill me in.
A dump truck crashed into a car.
They suspect driver fatigue.
It happened inside a tunnel on a wet road,
so the car's front seats
took most of the damage.
The patients are being transported here.
REGIONAL EMERGENCY MEDICAL CENTER
Let's see.
Dr. Yang, his stomach…
It's hemoperitoneum. It's too severe.
- Hey!
- Yes?
- To the resuscitation room. Now!
- Yes.
How long has he been out?
Around 15 minutes.
Thanks.
Insert an A-line and take him to the OR.
- I'll get the A-line.
- Dr. Baek, we have another patient.
All right, make way.
- Over here.
- All right.
- Right.
- Okay.
- Scissors.
- Here.
Dr. Baek, we're taking him to surgery.
- Tell Anus I'll be right there!
- Yes, sir!
Please administer anesthesia.
All right.
- Dr. Hwang.
- Yes?
Could you please speed up a bit?
Look, Dr. Yang.
I already feel incredibly uncomfortable
performing anesthesia without any tests.
And rushing me like this is going too far.
All I'm saying is,
since the patient is in critical--
Okay, fine.
Leave it to me.
Just stay out of the way.
Excuse me, Doc.
Can't you see the state he's in?
He's on his 12th unit of blood.
Will you take the blame
if the patient dies?
Wait.
- What is that thing even saying?
- "That thing"?
- Yeah.
Some of us are going flat out
trying to save a life.
- And you insult me, you lazy ass?
- What?
"Lazy ass"?
- Did you hear that?
- Calm down.
What did you say?
I want to save lives too!
This calls for more than words!
- Cut it out!
- Dr. Hwang!
All right, I'll get right on it
and complete the anesthesia.
In return,
give me her name.
I'll be filing a formal complaint.
- Stop it.
- I'll make her pay.
She's glaring! What's your name?
- What?
- Give me your name!
Hey, Anesthetics.
What's the problem?
What's your name?
Sir?
Don't ask questions you can't answer.
Prep properly if you don't want
to get into trouble. Understood?
Yes, sir. I'll get started right away!
I'll go scrub in.
- Hey, Gangster.
- Yes?
Don't you know what matters
in front of a patient?
I'm sorry.
Don't pick fights with just anyone.
Leave the fighting
to me.
Yes, sir.
What do you think of Dr. Baek Kang-hyuk?
I don't know him well enough
to make a judgment.
I just want your honest opinion.
As an anesthesiology resident,
you encounter all sorts of surgeons,
don't you?
Dr. Baek is…
He is a monster.
He performed an intercranial decompression
and partial lung resection
in under two hours.
Well, need I say more?
I see.
His skills are indeed remarkable.
Unfortunately, though,
that kind of individual genius
can sometimes be harmful
to the organization.
And on that note,
if you help me out a little here,
Dr. Park,
I'll have plenty to repay you for later.
Are you asking me to be a mole?
Oh my, the moon is so bright, isn't it?
SURGERY IN PROGRESS
NAME: LEE GI-YEONG, GENDER: MALE
HEMOPERITONEUM
Irrigation.
BP is dropping, moron!
- Inotropics! Quick!
- Yes, sir!
- Warm saline, please.
- Okay.
- Anus, suction. Focus!
- Yes, sir.
- Inotropics in.
- Get 30 more units of blood.
- Speed up the transfusion.
- On it.
Dr. Baek, we're losing too much blood.
We must find the source quickly.
BP is still dropping. It's 60 over 40.
Dr. Baek?
Dr. Baek, what do we do next?
Dr. Baek!
We'll lose the patient at this rate!
This much bleeding means it's an artery.
Dr. Baek!
Where is it?
Where?
Where are you?
I've found it.
Suture. Quickly! It's slippery.
How did you find that?
I didn't see anything.
Suction. Stay focused!
I'm not flying solo here!
Yes, Doctor.
The superior mesenteric artery
was damaged.
Anus, place the omni retractor
and cauterize all bleeding.
Yes, sir.
But what do we do about the liver?
I can't cauterize all of this.
The damage seems worse than expected.
We'll need to resect 80% of it
to control the bleeding.
A liver rupture…
Damn, he's even had liver cirrhosis.
It's at least a Class B.
That means his liver function
is next to zero.
If we control the bleeding,
will he survive?
The chances are slim. Gauze.
Then…
don't you think
we should just close him up now?
Medicine is all about probability.
Death is never a certainty.
We'll only buy him a few more hours.
You know that.
Nobody will give us credit anyway.
Could we try something else?
What the heck does she know?
What, is she a doctor now?
Could you please watch your mouth?
Sorry?
That's Nurse Cheon Jang-mi.
She's a fifth-year senior
who has been here since Dr. Kwon's time.
She's probably seen
more trauma cases than anyone.
She's more experienced than either of us.
Please show her some respect.
Having fun, are we?
Are you done?
- Sorry, Doctor.
- I'm sorry.
Gangster.
What do you suggest we do?
What if he got a donor liver?
Whose liver would that be?
Yours? Mine? His?
Dr. Baek, earlier today,
I ran into an organ donor coordinator.
I'm sorry.
ORGAN AND TISSUE DONOR CONSENT FORM
If they're here at this hour,
it means a registered donor
is declared brain-dead, so--
What are you waiting for? Call them.
Yes, Doctor.
This is Kang Chang-su.
We urgently need a liver transplant.
Is there any possibility?
There's a brain-dead donor, right?
Has the surgery already begun?
Well,
everything has been put on hold.
We've lost contact with their next of kin.
We're just waiting for them to call.
You know the drill.
We need their consent to proceed.
Give me the address.
Pardon?
Who was that?
We'll send someone to get their consent.
- Give me the address.
- I can't.
It's illegal.
Forget the law.
Saving a life comes first, doesn't it?
Dr. Baek, why don't we check
their blood type first?
Unless the donor is type O,
the consent will come to nothing.
Mr. Lee Gi-yeong is type O, so…
Hang on.
What did you say their name was?
Oh, the patient?
The patient's name is Lee Gi-yeong.
NEXT OF KIN INFORMATION: LEE GI-YEONG, SON
LEE HYE-YEONG, DAUGHTER
The donor's son's name on our file
is the same as your patient's.
Just a moment.
Is the date of birth July 12, 1988?
That's correct.
You don't think…
He's the donor's family?
Hold on.
Could that woman be…
There was someone in the passenger seat.
Do you know who it is?
It's probably
the daughter, Lee Hye-yeong.
So the two siblings were on their way here
to see their father, the brain-dead donor,
when they got into an accident.
Good.
Can you confirm that the donor is type O?
Yes, that's correct, but…
Then it'll be a transplant
between family members.
Pardon?
- But it's illegal without consent--
- Hey!
The next of kin are unconscious,
so who do you expect to give consent?!
Mr. Lee Gi-yeong will die
without that liver!
We'll add him to the wait list and--
Are you kidding me?!
Do you want us to do the transplant
on a dead patient?!
We'll go ahead with the liver transplant.
If any issues arise from this,
I will take full responsibility.
I understand.
I'll put a rush on it.
One more thing.
I need a favor.
We'll proceed
with the patient's organ donation today.
They'll transplant the liver now.
Contact the recipients
of the other organs.
- Yes, sir.
- One more thing.
Dr. Baek Kang-hyuk made a request.
It's our lucky day.
We came so close to losing this patient,
but now he has a donor liver.
Even so, how could you say such a…
Can you save a brain-dead man?
Sir?
Answer me.
No, I can't.
I can save Mr. Lee Gi-yeong.
Then what do you think
is the right choice?
I'm sorry, sir.
I'm going to save him, no matter what,
to make sure that the donor
can pass away in peace.
You may begin.
Let's have a moment of silence.
Okay.
Dr. Baek, that was barely a second.
He will understand.
He'd care more about saving his child
than our silent prayer.
Scalpel.
NAME: LEE JI-YEONG, GENDER: MALE
ORGAN DONATION
One more.
All set.
Why are you running?
We have another patient, Lee Hye-yeong.
Dr. Baek! Wait a second!
What is it?
Damn it.
I need to tell him about the warning email
from the audit team.
Oh dear.
That female patient from earlier,
which OR is she in?
She's in OR 27 in the main building.
- Okay, 27.
- Yes.
- Dr. Jung Jun-su is treating her!
- Sorry?
Dr. Baek, wait a second.
She's been moved to orthopedics,
so she's not with us now.
What? She's a major trauma patient. Move.
- Well, the thing is…
- What now?
Dr. Jung Jun-su,
the one in the surgery, is a little…
He is one of your kind.
What?
- Is he a genius?
- Yes.
What?
No, that's not…
What I mean is,
he's a little
intense.
Fine, no fighting.
I'll just check one thing. Move.
Hold it properly, damn it!
- What the heck?
- Wrong name.
I'm Baek Kang-hyuk of trauma surgery.
I just need to check something.
That Dr. Baek.
I've heard a lot about you from Dr. Han.
How dare he steal my protégé?!
Chewing him up wouldn't even be enough!
DIE, BAEK KANG-HYUK
My teacup!
Baek Kang-hyuk!
I heard you triaged her.
Are you here to follow up?
Couldn't you have done a better job
to begin with?
Just look at this. It's a complete mess.
This is a difficult case.
Are there ever any easy ones?
It's up to you to do a good job.
What the hell, kid?
If I were your kid,
I'd be a son of a bitch.
Why, this little bastard…
Dr. Jung, please contain yourself.
Another act of violence,
and the board won't let you off.
Damn it.
Open it wider, asshole.
Her creatine has really spiked.
Nurse? What's the patient's I/O like?
Fluids and blood transfusions
total around 2,000 cc,
but there hasn't been any urine output.
There's no kidney function at all.
Yes. She's already getting hydronephrosis.
Lab results show
that uremia has set in too.
Is she going to the nephrology ward?
Yes. Dr. Shin Jeong-u of nephrology
is on his way here.
Shin Jeong-u here.
Baek Kang-hyuk of trauma surgery.
- Oh.
- Lee Hye-yeong is your patient, right?
- Lee Hye-yeong?
- Yes. What is your care plan?
I'll put her on dialysis
and monitor her lab results.
That is a death sentence,
especially for a trauma patient
with acute renal failure.
I know, but I'm at a dead end.
I can't exactly find a kidney somewhere.
As for that,
I've already secured one.
One more thing. I need a favor.
Along with that liver,
please save a kidney for me.
I have the feeling
that Lee Hye-yeong
has acute renal failure.
I'll get to the transplant right away.
Could you begin dialysis in the OR?
The kidney is here.
I've heard all about that kidney.
The donor is Lee Hye-yeong's father.
I'll leave the dialysis in your hands.
I'll begin now.
- Anus.
- Yes?
The patient is in a very bad state.
Let's give ourselves 30 minutes.
Yes, Dr. Baek.
A kidney transplant in 30 minutes?
You're one big bluffer.
Scalpel.
NAME: LEE HYE-YEONG, GENDER: FEMALE
KIDNEY TRANSPLANT
3-0.
Now cut.
Okay. Done.
That took exactly 24 minutes.
I know, I'm amazing.
Tell me something new. Let's go.
After you.
Hey.
How can you yawn in this situation?
But we're all done now.
I thought you were a well-mannered kid.
I guess I was wrong.
Come with me. We have somewhere to be.
- Where?
- Just come.
Let's have a moment of silence.
Didn't we do that earlier?
That was a short version.
This time it's formal.
We should do it properly.
How thoughtless of me.
Organ donation is a noble sacrifice.
Let us pay
proper respect.
Thank you.
Rest in peace.
I'm tired.
- Wake up!
- Yes, Dr. Baek!
Oh my.
You'll have to try harder
to crack your skull.
Sorry, Doctor.
Are you leaving?
Yes, outpatient appointments.
- Let's do the ICU rounds after lunch.
- Sure.
Did I sleep?
Hey, Anus!
He called him "Anus."
You
are just pure evil.
Why? I got it right, didn't I?
Isn't that your official title?
I've been in trauma surgery all this time,
and he still calls me Anus!
Hey.
I guess it's not all that bad.
It's been a month already.
What do you think?
Guess what I hear all the time nowadays.
Number one, "Hey, Anus."
Number two, "Start running."
Number three, "What do you think?
That was so easy, right?"
It's easy to remove a liver
and then transplant it.
It's easy to sew up a shredded artery.
Even cardiotomy is easy for him.
Is any of that
easy?
Dr. Baek must be the type
to toot his own horn.
If that were the case,
I would keep my mouth closed.
The truth is,
he truly finds these things easy.
Is there something wrong with me?
Not at all.
Everything is completely normal.
The same goes for your liver.
Everything looks clean.
Come back in six months.
If all is well then,
you won't need to see my face again.
Thank you so much.
I never got to thank you properly.
I was so out of it in the helicopter.
If you want to show your gratitude,
why don't you do me a favor?
A favor?
One, two, three!
You're the first doctor
to ask me for a picture.
It's both to document and to commemorate.
Thank you for everything.
I might as well put them on display.
If not, no one would ever notice.
I should let them know.
Dr. Baek!
That brat! He is not with his outpatients.
Where on earth is he?
Damn it.
Hey, Anus.
Yes?
Is this your first time
seeing a liver transplant patient?
Yes, sir.
And you, Gangster?
Yes, same here.
So you will be handling
post-transplant care for the first time?
Yes.
What am I gonna do?
How am I ever gonna teach this lot
to start pulling their own weight?
By the way, Dr. Baek,
I tried to tell you earlier…
What? Why?
Am I in the dark here?
The thing is…
Budget cuts?
Budget cuts, my ass.
Since you joined us,
the audit team has sent
over ten warning emails.
Wait, so,
what is the review service's excuse
for these budget cuts?
They have a baseline, not an excuse.
Go over it and your budget gets cut.
If not, it's payday. You know that.
I'm saying that the baseline is all wrong.
I sent them a whole compilation
of theses and case reports.
I understand where you're coming from.
But I am the epitome of this Trauma Team.
A senior nurse
with a mere five years' experience.
I wouldn't be a senior anywhere else.
This is just a hollow shell
that was made to barely function.
So,
how do you think we've managed
to stay afloat despite everything?
We would bow down
to the director's office,
grovel to the board of directors,
and plead with the review board.
That's how we stuck it out.
That's how we survived.
Well done. Good job.
Are you fishing for compliments?
If you keep this up,
this team will fall apart.
I want to protect our team.
Gangster.
What do you mean "protect"? We just--
Dr. Baek!
There you are!
How are you doing?
What's the occasion?
Come with me.
Where to?
You'll find out when we get there!
I'd like to know before I go.
Seriously. Damn it.
My apologies.
You all took time
out of your busy schedules to be here,
but today's meeting…
It was canceled because of you!
Do you realize that?
As far as I know,
those meetings aren't mandatory.
Hey!
Come on, Dr. Han.
Listen, Dr. Baek.
I sent out text messages and emails
asking all attendings to make time
for this week's meeting.
Yes, I saw them.
Then I forgot.
I guess that can happen.
That I understand.
But this?
The trauma surgery department's deficit
has exceeded 300 million won.
This I can't just let go.
Can't we cover around 300 million won
with the government subsidies?
I can't believe this guy.
That money
goes toward the center's maintenance
and equipment purchases.
It is not intended
to cover deficits like this.
I don't think that's the intended purpose.
You should use it correctly.
While we're at it,
let's talk about the Trauma Center ICU.
It's been a stopgap
for the main ICU's overflow.
At the moment,
in a room with only three beds,
there is one trauma patient
and two from internal medicine.
All patients are treated equally.
Stop splitting hairs!
I don't think so.
Using money meant for trauma patients
on something else,
isn't that basically fraud?
Watch it.
If we get flagged by the review service
and face a special audit,
forget 300 million won,
we could be out tens of billions of won.
If that worries you,
stop the overtreatment.
The attendings are so money-hungry!
Dr. Baek!
That pie hole of yours
doesn't have a filter, does it?
My apologies!
In any case,
don't hassle me about the deficit again.
Excuse me.
I need to get back to saving lives.
I dare you to leave!
Don't you dare open that door!
Hey! Stop!
What? You're leaving?! Really?!
I saw that look you gave me!
You little brat, get back here!
That bastard…
Yu-rim.
Yes, Doc.
That bastard is good for nothing.
He's a pit bull.
I know.
We can't just let him be.
He'll get us into deep trouble.
The board of directors
will not stand for this deficit.
My chance of being the next director
would be gone.
As would your chance of being
the chief of planning and coordination.
That just cannot be.
Doc.
Leave it to me, Doc.
Let me handle this, okay?
Everyone has skeletons
in the closet, right?
Trust me with this, Doc.
Hi, Dr. Yoon.
I heard you were back in Korea.
We should catch up over dinner.
You spent a long time
with the International Medical Association
for Peace.
Could you look into something for me?
All right.
INTENSIVE CARE UNIT
NAME: LEE HYE-YEONG
By the way,
do you think it'll be okay?
The swelling is slow to go down.
She'll be fine, I'm sure.
We'll have to wait.
No, not that.
The chief of planning and coordination
summoned you.
What do you care?
You're being presumptuous.
I know I am, but it worries me, Dr. Baek.
Hey, Anus.
Doctors are never in the wrong
for saving lives.
That's just a given.
All that stuff
about our deficit or whatever,
just ignore it.
Yes, sir.
This won't do.
My treat tonight. Let's eat out.
- Out?
- Yes.
- Outside the hospital?
- And…
Yes?
Make sure to pass my message on
to Gangster.
What message?
Excuse me?
He wants you to come out
looking half-decent.
Fine, got it.
I can't believe this.
I just don't bother to doll up,
but when I do…
As long as I'm not naked, it's fine.
What should I wear?
TV shows are so unrealistic.
No real-life doctor is that good-looking.
Dr. Baek!
Oh my God!
I'm sorry I'm late.
Wow, Anus.
You look like a whole new person.
I'm known for being relatively stylish
at the hospital.
Is it your empty stomach talking?
Joke much?
Actually, someone bought me
the whole outfit.
Who? Your girlfriend?
Don't tell me it was your mom.
Whatever. Let's just go.
We could get an urgent call at any moment,
so let's cram in every extra bite.
What are we having anyway?
Beef? Raw fish?
Sushi?
Good grief.
TRADITIONAL CHINESE CUISINE
Nurse Cheon, dig in.
Maybe I should've dressed better.
Living nearby, I just threw something on.
Who cares? We are here to eat.
It's good to be comfortable.
You say that, but… Prada!
You look good.
Isn't this a bit much, Dr. Baek?
This place is really expensive.
I'm loaded.
Silver spoon?
Or do your parents own a building?
Not at all.
I'm the rich one.
I lost my parents young.
Sorry, I didn't mean to bring it up.
It's fine. I don't mind talking about it.
Oh, of course.
Compassion.
This is not the best time to mention it,
but since we're on the subject,
my mother passed away when I was little,
so I have no memories of her.
My father was a street cleaner.
One day, during an early morning shift,
he got into a car accident.
His injuries were so severe
that no hospital would admit him.
In the end,
he died at the last hospital
he was taken to.
That's why I became a doctor.
You said to lean on a sob story.
But what I meant was--
Anyway, if you don't eat,
I'll finish it all.
Wait. We're on it too.
Dr. Yang, eat up.
Sure.
Oh, right.
Dr. Baek, I'm curious about something too.
Your arm tattoo.
This is just…
It is believed to ward off all bullets.
Excuse me?
I've run through countless battlefields,
and I never once got hit.
Syria, huh?
Were you off on an IMAFP mission?
Well, something like that.
Is that when you learned
to fly a helicopter?
Do doctors in Syria fly the helicopters--
Time for the major announcement.
Hey, Anus.
This is about you.
Now that you're part of trauma surgery,
it feels wrong to still call you "Anus."
I agree. It's wrong.
So I thought
I might…
untag you from the "Anus" label.
I've given it careful consideration.
How about "No. 1"?
- "No.  1"?
- Yes.
Like Protégé No. 1?
Pass me a napkin.
Sure.
No, not protégé.
Slave No. 1.
No way! Please don't.
I want a different…
Just call me by my name.
No. 1, what are you doing?
Answer the phone.
EMERGENCY ROOM, HNUH
Yang Jae-won of trauma surgery.
What?
It's a pedestrian accident, sir.
Prep an OR. We'll be there in ten.
We'll be right there.
I'll come with you.
Nope, you're off duty.
He's right.
I'm off duty.
I meant to tell you this.
I'm busy, so I'll keep it short.
Gangster, you're seriously mistaken
about something.
You fight to win, okay?
To hell with protecting the team.
I'm going to win.
Finish it all and follow us.
What is he saying?
How can I eat all this?
Taxi!
- Hey, No. 1!
- Sir?
Let's keep it under five.
Hey, let me borrow that.
CHINESE DELIVERY
Dr. Baek.
We started CPR 34 minutes ago.
Clear!
Shock.
Stop.
Get down.
Call their next of kin.
Take him to the morgue.
It's not your fault, Dr. Baek.
His cervical vertebra is fractured.
And his skull is crushed.
Still, if I had been here…
It would have been the same.
Even you can't save every patient.
Fall victim incoming!
Make way.
Prep an OR. Hurry!
We had to keep running.
Even agonizing over a patient's death
was a luxury to us.
Twenty-four hours a day, 365 days a year.
It felt as though if we stopped,
even for a moment,
someone's heart would stop too.
So we
had to keep running.
New patient!
To keep our patients' hearts beating,
we must
keep running.
SURGERY IN PROGRESS
Subtitle translation by: Helen Cho