♪In a corner alone, feeling blue♪
♪At parties, I feel out of the loop♪
♪Friends ask who I'm waiting for♪
♪I respond with silence and a smile♪
♪Years have passed without love or hate♪
♪Ignoring rumors and endless debate♪
♪Sometimes,
I gaze at the stars late at night♪
♪Thinking of us who can't go back♪
♪From a small town to a big city♪
♪Years of youth traded
for dozens of traveling tickets♪
♪Chasing dreams
and seeking a peaceful life♪
♪All for living life in a good way♪
♪From a small town to a big city♪
♪Maybe only one trip home a year♪
♪Parents' wrinkles grow
and I've lost innocence♪
♪Time spares no one♪
=You Are My Whole World=
=Episode 20=
(Meeting Parents)
Father. Mother.
A Cha, my precious daughter.
You're finally back.
Is my daughter back?
You're acting
as if you could never see
each other again.
So what?
Liu, you're back too.
Your parents and I
often talked about you.
We said when you come back,
we'll finalize
your wedding arrangements.
They are...
(He's a young master
and she's a princess.)
(My mother will freak out if she knows.)
They are my friends in the palace.
Your friends.
Uncle. Auntie.
This girl is really sensible.
Hello.
Introverted.
Don't just stand here.
Sit.
I'm going to get you something to eat.
Come. This way please.
Wait. Let me use the kitchen first.
What do you need the kitchen for?
It's a secret.
- Well.
- What's she up to?
A waxberry?
Shrimp.
Crispy outside, soft inside.
And there's filling.
Sourness and sweetness are just right.
So delicious.
So the recipe...
A promise is a promise.
I'm going to get it for you now.
So tasty.
Great.
(Revelry Tavern)
Dive in.
Everyone, help yourselves.
Liu, you too.
Why are you so reserved?
I should thank you
for taking care of A Cha in the palace.
Not at all.
I often went to A Cha to ask for food.
So you often had dates in the palace?
Why aren't you eating?
They don't suit your taste?
Eat more. This is tasty.
Try this.
This is also tasty.
A prawn.
Here.
My father made this. Eat.
He's an adult.
Doesn't he have hands?
Why are you picking food for him?
That's right.
Alright, what are you doing?
How did you know A Cha?
This is easy to explain.
I was outside the palace.
I met some people and fought with them.
A Cha saved me.
Young man, you look decent.
It's not good to get into trouble.
You are right.
I was just about to ask.
What do you do?
I'm currently unemployed.
Young man.
You should work hard while you can.
Yes.
You can't live your life
in a muddle.
Yes. You're right.
Liu is young
and already an imperial physician.
He works for the government.
It's a well-paid job, understand?
Absolutely.
Enough.
I heard
girls in the palace
have a new list of dream boys.
Mr. Liu ranks first on that list.
Me?
- Him?
Mr. Liu is honest, mature, and composed.
He's reliable and gentle.
He is very meticulous
when taking care of patients.
Especially his well-paid job.
That's a job for life.
Eat.
Eat, everyone.
Come on.
Have some dishes.
Don't just sit here.
You've never seen so many dishes, right?
Indeed, I haven't.
Father, you eat too.
I'm coming in.
Come in.
Sorry for what happened today,
Grand General.
Have a piece of sweet bunny cake
and you'll have a good mood.
Actually, you said this to me before.
So sour!
Why do you believe everything?
Wait.
You're that little crybaby?
You've changed a lot.
A Cha.
We can't let my mother
find out I'm here.
I'm off now.
See you tomorrow, little crybaby.
(Revelry Tavern)
A Cha.
Take good care of yourself
in the palace.
Mind your step.
Okay.
Got it, Mother.
Liu.
Take good care of A Cha.
Take good care of yourself too.
Rest assured, Auntie.
You must eat on time.
Mubai.
Thank you.
You can't stay up late.
A Cha
likes you a lot.
But you should win credit for yourself.
Take this.
Go make a better living,
so that after A Cha leaves the palace,
you'll have the confidence
to marry her, right?
Okay.
Make way.
Seventh Young Master, Princess Gongsun,
please return to the palace.
Keep a low profile outside the palace.
Get up.
Princess? Young Master?
Auntie.
- Mother.
- Auntie.
Are you okay?
She's fine. She just got startled.
Are you okay, Mother?
Give it back.
Seventh Young Master,
it's my private savings
I've kept for many years.
Auntie, are you okay?
Go away.
How dare you keep private savings!
Where is the money?
Many people are watching.
How much more do you have?
Give it to me.
This is all of it.
How dare you run away!
I'd like to see where you can go.
♪After the wind, lingering desires stay♪
♪Clouds drift and shape, momentary play♪
♪Emotions reach, stirring in the heart♪
♪Tears in solitude,
how often they start♪
♪The wind's whispering,
and rain's sobbing♪
♪Years pass
with flowers' bloom and grace♪
♪In dreams we met, can we meet again♪
♪Your voice fades and becomes distant♪
♪If farewell is not for meeting's sake♪
♪Leave no yearning for you♪
♪When spring ends,
peach blossoms spread wide♪
♪For you, I'd be the last pedal♪
♪Spring knows not my love's face♪
♪April showers and falls with grace♪
♪The flower of love withers♪
♪Love's whispers appear in gaze♪
♪I hold my love in spring with cheer♪
♪Scent of yesteryear now reappears♪
♪In longing, the wind whispers not♪
♪Hearts pine softly, in thoughts begot♪
♪Spring knows not my love's face♪
♪April showers and falls with grace♪
♪The flower of love withers♪
♪Love's whispers appear in gaze♪
♪I hold my love in spring with cheer♪
♪Scent of yesteryear now reappears♪
♪In longing, the wind whispers not♪
♪Hearts pine softly, in thoughts begot♪