♪In a corner alone, feeling blue♪
♪At parties, I feel out of the loop♪
♪Friends ask who I'm waiting for♪
♪I respond with silence and a smile♪
♪Years have passed without love or hate♪
♪Ignoring rumors and endless debate♪
♪Sometimes,
I gaze at the stars late at night♪
♪Thinking of us who can't go back♪
♪From a small town to a big city♪
♪Years of youth traded
for dozens of traveling tickets♪
♪Chasing dreams
and seeking a peaceful life♪
♪All for living life in a good way♪
♪From a small town to a big city♪
♪Maybe only one trip home a year♪
♪Parents' wrinkles grow
and I've lost innocence♪
♪Time spares no one♪
=You Are My Whole World=
=Episode 8=
(A Pipe Dream)
Young Master, Mr. Cao has already been
settled properly.
I've assigned people to guard him.
He's absolutely safe.
Mr. Cao is in a state of madness.
It's hard to talk to him.
Investigate the others
as soon as possible.
I have started already.
These people will soon be found.
Besides,
Young Master,
the girl nicknamed Doubao,
you asked me to look into,
I have found her.
Who is she?
I carefully went through the registry
of the maids in the palace.
What are you laughing at? Just say it.
Guess who she is?
Speak!
A Cha.
Try this, black plum sauce.
With the sweet bunny cakes,
it's super delicious.
So sour!
Why do you believe everything I say?
Young Master.
But now A Cha is in trouble.
What trouble?
Isn't it because of you?
Me?
But indeed, it is because of you.
You're dilly-dallying. What's going on?
There're bad comments about A Cha
in Royal Kitchen now.
It's the gossip
between Seventh Young Master and her.
Haven't you done talking?
No one's talking about you.
Don't flatter yourself.
But, your affair with
the Seventh Young Master,
is it true or not?
What are you talking about?
Me and him, how could that be possible?
He is the Seventh Young Master,
and I am just a kitchen aid.
What relationship could we have?
So, you're dating Mr. Liu?
Liu Mubai and I are like sisters.
Would you get engaged with your bestie?
Seventh Young Master is here.
Come to be my private chef.
Be my private chef,
and you can make these people know
I simply admire your cooking skills.
What do you say?
Seventh Young Master, could you
give me some time?
I'll reply to you tonight.
Say no, or yes, no, or yes.
In front of so many people,
he said that I was just a cook.
Who cares to have anything to do
with him?
Say yes, or no.
But he's the noble Seventh Young Master.
If I say no, would it be too snubbing
for him?
Seventh Young Master, A Cha said
this was her response.
What does it mean? She agreed?
This is fish head with green
and red chopped chilies,
symbolizing you being red and her green.
The fish head is split in two,
having a head but no tail,
meaning have a beginning but no end.
This smashed cucumber
clearly signifies a sudden separation.
This isn't just a bowl of ordinary rice.
This is millet steamed with sorghum.
I guess A Cha is trying to say,
the thing between you two,
is but a pipe dream.
Alright, stop talking.
I have spoken out of turn.
About the news that A Cha refused to be
my private chef,
spread it out.
Young Master, this...
I see, Young Master.
You want to protect A Cha.
If she agrees to be your private chef,
then naturally,
who would dare to bully her?
If you spread the news
of her rejecting you,
that's to restore her reputation.
Isn't it, Young Master?
After all, she has saved my life
and cooked for me.
Now she's fallen into needless trouble
because of me.
It's only right that I help her
out of it.
If push comes to shove,
we'll just be strangers.
So wise of you, Young Master.
Annoying.
(My great vengeance is unrequited.)
(Involving her in it is meaningless.)
I'm planning to retire
and return to my hometown this year.
I have petitioned to City Lord
to hold a palace gourmet competition.
Only the first place winner
can succeed my position.
Only Royal Chefs may enter
the competition.
Alright, everyone, get to work.
As I see,
do you also wish to become
the Head Royal Chef?
If life were without dreams,
what difference would it make
from the salted fish?
Even if the salted fish turns over,
isn't it still a salted fish?
Sir, I heard that Seventh Young Master
made a special trip to Royal Kitchen,
to sever ties with A Cha.
Don't be like those maids and eunuchs,
always prying into the master's affairs.
Sir, you are the hub of the palace.
If not you, then whom should I ask?
That is true.
I don't see any future between
A Cha and Seventh Young Master.
You haven't messed up again
like last time, have you?
Absolutely not.
I've heard
that you and A Cha were
childhood sweethearts.
That's true.
And I've heard that you two
were betrothed when young.
Young Master, the imperial meal
has been reheated three times.
At least have something.
Take it out.
Young Master, even if you know A Cha
was betrothed to Mr. Liu,
there's no need for you to fast.
Dayuan,
go order some dishes from Royal Kitchen.
Yes.
♪After the wind, lingering desires stay♪
♪Clouds drift and shape, momentary play♪
♪Emotions reach, stirring in the heart♪
♪Tears in solitude,
how often they start♪
♪The wind's whispering,
and rain's sobbing♪
♪Years pass
with flowers' bloom and grace♪
♪In dreams we met, can we meet again♪
♪Your voice fades and becomes distant♪
♪If farewell is not for meeting's sake♪
♪Leave no yearning for you♪
♪When spring ends,
peach blossoms spread wide♪
♪For you, I'd be the last pedal♪
♪Spring knows not my love's face♪
♪April showers and falls with grace♪
♪The flower of love withers♪
♪Love's whispers appear in gaze♪
♪I hold my love in spring with cheer♪
♪Scent of yesteryear now reappears♪
♪In longing, the wind whispers not♪
♪Hearts pine softly, in thoughts begot♪
♪Spring knows not my love's face♪
♪April showers and falls with grace♪
♪The flower of love withers♪
♪Love's whispers appear in gaze♪
♪I hold my love in spring with cheer♪
♪Scent of yesteryear now reappears♪
♪In longing, the wind whispers not♪
♪Hearts pine softly, in thoughts begot♪