♪In a corner alone, feeling blue♪
♪At parties, I feel out of the loop♪
♪Friends ask who I'm waiting for♪
♪I respond with silence and a smile♪
♪Years have passed without love or hate♪
♪Ignoring rumors and endless debate♪
♪Sometimes,
I gaze at the stars late at night♪
♪Thinking of us who can't go back♪
♪From a small town to a big city♪
♪Years of youth traded
for dozens of traveling tickets♪
♪Chasing dreams
and seeking a peaceful life♪
♪All for living life in a good way♪
♪From a small town to a big city♪
♪Maybe only one trip home a year♪
♪Parents' wrinkles grow
and I've lost innocence♪
♪Time spares no one♪
=You Are My Whole World=
=Episode 14=
(Twelve Dishes)
It's gone.
Mr. Cao, slow down.
- It's gone.
- Mr. Cao, slow down.
Mr. Cao, slow down.
Why exactly are you looking for
this mad eunuch?
And you are even
keeping a close watch on him.
Back at my birthday banquet,
my mother died of poisoning.
He is the only one
who knows the truth now.
I want to know the truth.
I have to find clues from him.
So you want me to help you?
He likes the dishes you make.
Perhaps you can get him to talk.
(His long-time worry
is the birthday poisoning case.)
(If I can help him find the truth,)
(perhaps I can help him resolve
his emotional distress.)
A Cha,
I really didn't want to
get you involved,
but I have no other choice.
So I thought...
Say no more.
You've helped me so many times already.
Let me help you this time.
It's gone.
Mr. Cao, this is my specialty dish.
What do you like? I'll make it tomorrow.
This one.
The white wine braised trotters.
Okay, no problem.
By the way.
Do you know
what day it is today?
What day?
Today is the wedding day of the master
and the Queen of the Women's Kingdom.
Wedding day. Wedding day.
Yes.
Queen of the Women's Kingdom?
He always calls me that.
There's food and drinks.
Come on, drink up.
Us?
Of course.
It's your wedding day.
You have to drink eighty-one cups
of cross-cupped wine.
Otherwise, I won't eat
the dishes you make.
Cao Rui, don't go too far.
Hold on, Seventh Young Master.
Don't you remember what I told you?
Drink up. Let's drink.
Great.
Eighty-one cups of cross-cupped wine.
You will love each other forever.
Great. Come on.
How many cups have we already drunk?
I'm not quite sure.
Slow down.
My butt.
Your eyelashes are pretty long, huh?
Your nose bridge
is also quite high.
You look quite handsome.
You're drunk.
Answer me.
If my dish and I
fell into the water at the same time,
who would you save first?
I would of course save...
Of course, I would save you first.
Come on.
Mr. Cao
will love the dish I make this time.
I didn't expect you to be so proactive.
Proactive? What?
Don't you remember what happened
last night?
Last night?
I had a sound sleep last night.
I don't even remember how I got back.
Drink. I want to drink more.
Stop it.
Come on. Lie down.
I still want to drink.
No more drinks. You're drunk now.
I still want more.
I can drink another thousand cups.
You're drunk.
A Cha.
Why are you still here?
Don't tell me.
A Cha.
Let's see if you can run again.
Go to sleep now.
Drink, drink.
What are you laughing at?
I am laughing at Mr. Cao.
Is it good?
The trotters are tender.
The aroma of wine is wonderful.
It's so good.
Master,
you and the Queen
of the Women's Kingdom...
We are already married.
That's true.
One can't get married twice, right?
Ten years ago,
what happened at the banquet
of Seventh Young Master?
Do you still remember?
I'll let you eat if you can answer me.
No, I want to eat meat first.
I want to eat meat first.
This eunuch is crazy.
Even if he speaks,
he wouldn't be clear about
what happened then.
Do you want to eat something else?
I still want to eat
imperial pumpkin, eight-treasure tofu,
snowy soup, crab-stuffed oranges,
wheat-scented chicken,
yingyang yam, hundred birds' nest,
crystal stew, crab roe pastry,
Buddha Jumps Over the Wall Soup,
Tele-Rhino, lotus steamed fish...
You remember
what happened back then, right?
Those were the twelve dishes
at the banquet.
You remember all of them, huh?
Stop playing the fool and speak up.
♪After the wind, lingering desires stay♪
♪Clouds drift and shape, momentary play♪
♪Emotions reach, stirring in the heart♪
♪Tears in solitude,
how often they start♪
♪The wind's whispering,
and rain's sobbing♪
♪Years pass
with flowers' bloom and grace♪
♪In dreams we met, can we meet again♪
♪Your voice fades and becomes distant♪
♪If farewell is not for meeting's sake♪
♪Leave no yearning for you♪
♪When spring ends,
peach blossoms spread wide♪
♪For you, I'd be the last pedal♪
♪Spring knows not my love's face♪
♪April showers and falls with grace♪
♪The flower of love withers♪
♪Love's whispers appear in gaze♪
♪I hold my love in spring with cheer♪
♪Scent of yesteryear now reappears♪
♪In longing, the wind whispers not♪
♪Hearts pine softly, in thoughts begot♪
♪Spring knows not my love's face♪
♪April showers and falls with grace♪
♪The flower of love withers♪
♪Love's whispers appear in gaze♪
♪I hold my love in spring with cheer♪
♪Scent of yesteryear now reappears♪
♪In longing, the wind whispers not♪
♪Hearts pine softly, in thoughts begot♪