♪Don't cry for me in sorrow♪
♪My silence is only a disguise
for my defiance♪
♪I stand alone in a forsaken place,
drenched in mud♪
♪My name and my love♪
♪Have turned into strength
and part of my memories♪
=Madam=
=Episode 1=
Little girl,
I can make any of your wishes come true.
Any wish at all?
Liar!
Don't believe him.
Zhenxuan!
Zhenxuan.
(The dragon pearl
recognizes only its master.)
(Anyone who defies its orders
shall be punished.)
Madam.
Madam,
it's time to go to the banquet.
(Shan Yunshu, Madam)
It's said Chairman Hu is seriously ill.
No wonder Shan Yunshu
is throwing a banquet today.
She's probably going to take over
Dongsheng Trading Company.
I heard she hasn't gotten married
into the Hu family yet.
Really?
It's because Young Master Hu
died young.
I also heard
that Master Hu's concubine
is fighting her over the inheritance.
Honored elders,
officials,
ladies,
and gentlemen,
welcome to
the Dongsheng Trading banquet.
I wouldn't become
the chairwoman of Dongsheng Trading
without your support.
Dongsheng will work together
with you all
for the good of the people of Mo City.
Thank you.
Cheers.
- Cheers.
Madam, Master is sinking fast.
(Hu Zeyuan, Chairman of Dongsheng)
Yunshu,
there's something I need to tell you.
I acknowledged you
as part of the Hu family,
but I never gave you
what you rightfully deserved.
(Zeng Baozhu, Hu Zeyuan's concubine)
Mr. Hu,
Zhenxuan and I
were betrothed since infancy.
Back then, he risked his life to save me.
I may not have officially
married into the Hu family,
but I've long been your daughter-in-law.
Yunshu.
I really
miss Zhenxuan.
Bury me
close to him.
Master!
- Master!
(Tomb of Late Father-in-law, Hu Zeyuan)
Kneel and bow.
Before the tomb, dutiful children kneel
to honor virtue and propriety.
Ritual completed.
(Father,)
(Mother,)
(twenty years ago,)
(our family was slaughtered.)
(So Mr. Hu raised me as his child.)
(Now,)
(I've become the chairwoman
of Dongsheng Trading.)
(Rest assured.)
(I'll definitely find my sister)
(and the murderer who killed our family)
(to avenge you.)
(Hen, assassin)
(Dragon King Temple)
Who sent you?
Who sent you to kill me?
Ask the Grim Reaper later.
Go now!
(Aojue, Dragon Prince)
(Chongming, Jiao Dragon)
You?
Didn't I already die?
The Dragon Pearl
saved you.
The pact seal summons us
to protect you.
It's been years.
I didn't know the pact seal still held.
♪All will become my strength♪
Don't worry.
I won't let you die.
Kill them.
Why should I listen to you?
I'm the master of the dragon pearl.
Then you need to pay the price.
Fine.
♪I stand alone in a forsaken place,
drenched in mud♪
♪My name and my love♪
♪Have turned into strength
and part of my memories♪
♪I guard myself endlessly
with no end in sight♪
Aojue,
let's see who's faster.
Chongming,
Confidence isn't the same as arrogance.
That scar-faced woman
is holding the key evidence I need.
Would you please
chase her?
- No.
Then move aside.
I'll go myself.
You're still as brainless as ever.
What do you mean?
Our powers are restricted
by the pact seal.
We can't act against her will.
Then how do we break the pact seal?
The dragon pearl has fused with her.
If the pact-bearer grows old
and dies naturally
or willingly bleeds out
their last drop of blood,
the pact seal will be lifted.
But we can't kill her.
How do we make her bleed out?
She's a mere human.
She'll need our help.
If we can manipulate human greed,
it's only a matter of time.
Stay here and keep thinking.
I'm off for some stretching.
Oh.
Looks like I'm not the only one
who's brainless today.
(Darned pact seal.)
(My power is blocked.)
♪Despite the downpour or mist,
I never forget♪
♪Exhaustion and pain
are left far behind♪
♪Dressed in splendor,
I reminisce amidst the noise♪
♪My footsteps and my shoulders♪
♪All will become my strength♪
♪Never leaving, always with me♪
♪Don't cry for me in sorrow♪
♪My silence is only a disguise
for my defiance♪
♪I stand alone in a forsaken place,
drenched in mud♪
♪My name and my love♪
♪Have turned into strength
and part of my memories♪
♪I guard myself endlessly
with no end in sight♪