♪Don't cry for me in sorrow♪
♪My silence is only a disguise
for my defiance♪
♪I stand alone in a forsaken place,
drenched in mud♪
♪My name and my love♪
♪Have turned into strength
and part of my memories♪
=Madam=
=Episode 20=
Mingkai!
Yunshu,
I'd finally done something for you.
Don't talk.
I can definitely save you.
In my next life...
In my next life,
please
go on
a date with me.
Mingkai?
Mingkai!
It's all my fault.
I encountered Black-robed Man
when I was pursuing Mo Shenhai's men.
That's why I'm late.
It depends on him
whether or not he can survive.
One more mark has faded away.
Seems like the pact is getting weaker.
Mingkai,
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have doubted you.
You have to wake up.
Show yourself.
Aofeng.
I knew you were here.
How does it feel to lose
two of your loved ones?
You owe me two lives now.
You better be a good girl.
If not, you'll lose even more.
I'll make you
pay for them.
Aren't you overestimating yourself here?
The Dragon Pact only has one mark left.
What gives you the confidence
to think that you can deal with
both Aojue and Chongming at once?
How dare you provoke me?
Provoke you?
This is just the interest
of the pain you've brought upon me.
You better think carefully.
Try to go against my will,
and your brother and Chongming
will be summoned here immediately.
Now, may we talk?
What are you up to?
I wish to negotiate a deal with you.
With the Dragon Pearl?
Yes.
For what?
Mingkai's life.
Is his life
more important than yours?
I've owed him too much.
What if Aojue and
Zhang Mingkai died at the same time
while I could only rescue one of them?
Whom do you
wish for me to rescue?
Seems like you're concerned
about our relationship.
If he dies,
you'll remember him forever.
Isn't that pretty good?
If he survives,
I'll never forget him as well.
Do you know what
the Dragon Pearl mean to you?
Of course I know.
Aren't you afraid that I might
go against my promise?
That's why
I wish to form a pact with you.
You can have the Dragon Pearl
as long as you promise me three things.
Oh.
What three things?
Firstly,
save Mingkai.
Secondly,
do not harm the people I love.
Thirdly,
leave Mo City and never come back
after obtaining the Dragon Pearl.
You're sacrificing yourself
to protect the people you love, huh?
Are you that naive?
I'm not being naive here.
You should be more pragmatic.
Once the pact vanishes,
you'll have no chance
to obtain the Dragon Pearl.
Ha ha.
If only I could witness
Aojue's pain and suffering
upon knowing that you're sacrificing
yourself for another man's sake.
They'll return soon.
Come with me.
Madam's bed is untouched.
I suppose she left last night.
Mo Shenhai's body is missing as well.
That girl,
she always thought
that she was the world's savior.
I have to teach her a lesson
for her self-assertion in the future.
Are you sure Aofeng didn't abduct her?
If Madam was abducted,
there should be signs of a struggle.
And, the Dragon Pact is still intact.
It's impossible.
According to Yuzi's letter,
she's going to seek
the truth behind the Dragon Pact.
What does that mean?
She did say that she saw the things
that I, Chongming, and Black-robed Man
had done behind her back
in the Dragon Pact.
Zhang Mingkai wasn't supposed
to appear in the pact.
Logically speaking,
only those who form the pact
should be recorded.
Are you saying
Yuzi had already found out
that Zhang Mingkai is Black-robed Man?
I...
Both Aojue
and Aofeng
have a pact with the Dragon Pearl.
And,
the Dragon Pact will record
all of our actions
until the pact is dissolved.
If Madam intentionally sent us away,
that means she must've found out
some sort of secrets.
I'm afraid it isn't that simple.
That girl is trying
to do something silly again.
To dissolve the pact,
one must activate the great formation
with dragon's blood.
Last night, I fed Zhang Mingkai
my blood to save him.
Madam is in danger.
Let's split up and act.
Okay.
Let's go.
Why aren't they out yet?
It's crowded.
Yeah.
Why are they taking pictures?
Judging from this, I suppose we can't enter
from the main entrance.
What are you doing?
I don't have any powers now.
I cannot teleport.
I know this.
Just watch and learn.
Shu!
Is this a hidden tunnel?
That's right.
When I was an assassin,
it was inconvenient
for me to use the main entrance.
I could only use this tunnel.
You're looking for me
not just for Zhang Mingkai's sake, right?
Who exactly are you?
What's with that question?
I once entered
the Dragon Pact's illusory realm.
I saw something
that I'd never seen before.
Oh?
What have you seen, then?
How did you control
Zhang Mingkai to spy on me?
You found out, huh?
Was his death
part of your plan?
No.
That was his own will.
Mo Shenhai betrayed me.
Seems like Zhang Mingkai
truly cared about you.
You poisoned me
and the masses
just to get rid of Aojue.
Do you hate him that much?
Why should I?
As his younger brother,
I have no complaints.
What I hate is
the Dragon Clan behind him.
I wish to eradicate the Dragon Clan.
However, as long as Aojue is around,
the Dragon Clan will never fall.
It's just like how you hate
Wanlong Chamber of Commerce.
As long as Mo Shenhai is still around,
Wanlong Chamber of Commerce
will never fall.
So,
I'm sure you understand my feelings.
I'm different from you.
Mo Shenhai killed my parents.
Wanlong Chamber of Commerce is his base.
I wish to destroy
Wanlong Chamber of Commerce.
However, I won't harm the innocent.
Your father murdered
Mo Shenhai's father.
Mo Shenhai avenged his father
by murdering your father.
Now,
you've murdered Mo Shenhai.
Mo Shenhai has children.
In the future, Mo Shenhai's children
will try to take your life.
Will you offer
your life generously, then?
If I slaughter the entire Dragon Clan
and leave Aojue alive,
it'll only make us sworn enemies.
I would rather kill him
than let him live
as an avatar of vengeance like me.
You're truly a despicable scum.
You're making up an excuse
for your unpardonable crimes.
How did you think I was able to survive
the past century of torment?
How did you think you were able
to survive the past two decades?
My vengeance is ten times
as much as yours.
This secret tunnel is well-developed.
Mo Shenhai had run
this place for many years.
Even I couldn't fully comprehend
the complexity of this place.
You didn't dare to look at me
in broad daylight.
What's wrong?
Are you getting bolder
just because it's dark in here?
Are you an owl now?
Regarding what happened that night,
why don't we talk about it?
I said it already.
I don't need you
to bear responsibility for it.
You're carefree and straightforward.
You're different from Yunshu
when it comes to that.
You see,
she's only devoted to one man.
What's wrong?
Can you stop comparing me to my sister?
Are you jealous of your sister?
You can court my sister
if you like her.
Stop being long-winded.
I couldn't even court you,
let alone your sister.
You're a few hundred
years old, you know?
I'm sure you've seen
all kinds of women before.
I think
you shouldn't have become an assassin.
You should've become a writer.
Humans have a short lifespan.
You guys are only concerned with
reproduction and survival.
Unlike us non-humans.
We have a long lifespan.
We're different from
what you imagine us to be.
Am I worthy?
I suppose.
I guess I'm your boyfriend now.
There's one more question.
What is it?
I'm a human.
I have a short lifespan.
I'll grow old.
I'll die.
If so, I'll find you again
once you've reincarnated.
I'll make you fall for me again.
Don't get ahead of yourself here.
I haven't fallen for you
in this lifetime yet.
Now, you're talking about my next life?
Do you love Zhang Mingkai?
The kind of love between sexes.
I love him, but it's not the kind
of love between sexes.
Mingkai had a rough upbringing.
I promised him
that I would be his kin
as long as I'm alive.
Someone was living here indeed.
Judging from my understanding
of Mo Shenhai,
I don't think he was living here.
Madam?
Look over there.
That's the Soul Possession Spell
that blurs the line
between real and false.
(Aofeng.)
(Zhang Mingkai.)
(He visited Shan Yunshu before)
(when I was still inside the pact.)
Aofeng,
what are you up to?
Hurry and rescue Mingkai.
Yunshu,
Aofeng is Zhang Mingkai.
Zhang Mingkai is Aofeng.
As long as you like it,
I can be Zhang Mingkai forever.
So,
you didn't control Zhang Mingkai.
You were just lying to me all along.
All of that no longer matters.
Most importantly, I fancy you.
I've fallen for you.
You lied to me.
You said you would forgive me.
I didn't lie to you.
That was for Zhenxuan.
If you survive this,
we'll be even.
Yunshu,
I knew you loved me.
Can you please give me one more chance?
Dumb Aofeng.
♪Because our meeting was meant to happen
a thousand years later♪
♪Loving you
is more than I ever hoped for♪
♪I run to be in your arms♪
♪I don't want our moment to end♪
♪Because our meeting was meant to happen
a thousand years later♪
♪I can't express my sadness
with words♪
♪So I whisper the overwhelming love♪
♪I won't let this moment end♪
♪Because our meeting was meant to happen
a thousand years later♪
♪Loving you
is more than I ever hoped for♪
♪I run to be in your arms♪
♪I don't want our moment to end♪
♪Because our meeting was meant to happen
a thousand years later♪
♪I can't express my sadness
with words♪
♪So I whisper the overwhelming love♪
♪I won't let this moment end♪