"Fuyao" by Karen Mok
♫ I start to dance nimbly and gracefully ♫
♫ For what my beautiful face is frowned? ♫
♫ Without him, I'll drift with the current ♫
♫ Why is the tune of the zither a farewell song? ♫
♫ Without me, he'll be lonely in this universe ♫
♫ My heart silently waits at the cliff of Firmament ♫
♫ The heaven, the earth, the sun and the moon are all in my bosom ♫
♫ How can I own the top freedom in this world? ♫
♫ There is no fear from my heart ♫
♫ Deep love won't hide ♫
♫ True love won't run short ♫
♫ Dreams give hopes through all the ages ♫
♫ Why go through storms and stress to be bright and beautiful? ♫
♫ There is no struggle from my heart ♫
♫ Swaying along with the wind ♫
♫ I can do anything freely ♫
♫ I enter my dreams easily and unrestrainedly ♫
♫ What a beautiful dance ♫
[Legend of Fuyao]
~ Episode 19 ~
I heard that the abducted Elegant Miss is from the Prime Minister's Manor.
She's even your newly named goddaughter.
Prime Minister, you have a soft heart.
When she was sent and had arrived at the palace gates,
did you suddenly feel regretful and came up with this idea?
Of course not.
Not mentioning a goddaughter,
people in the whole Deep Water are Your Majesty’s people.
I did indeed oversee the supervision.
But I don't intend to shield myself.
Your Majesty, please give me a few days.
I'll surely catch the culprit to calm your fury.
Then thank you for your hard work, Prime Minister.
There’re also assassins who entered the Prime Minister’s Manor.
And your manor even caught fire.
You’re also looking for the culprit throughout the whole town.
I’m afraid that you might be too busy.
The nation’s matter is a big matter. Your manor’s matter is a small matter.
And Prime Minister is usually busy with court responsibilities.
Just let Zhang Henian investigate the case today.
As Your Majesty wishes.
Right. If Zhang Henian wants to investigate, he'll need people.
If he wants to catch the culprit, he'll need soldiers.
And naturally, he needs funds.
Since he has asked for money on his memorial, just give it to him.
Your Majesty, catching the culprit and asking for military expenditure are two different matters.
Prime Minister.
Prime Minister,
who’s the king of Deep Water?
Is it you or me?
Do you think that
it was you, Qi Zhen, who pushed me up to the throne,
so Deep Water will have to listen to you from now on?
Don’t forget.
You’re not the only official in the imperial court.
Besides, you're not the only one with military power.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Prime Minister, you’re tired.
Quickly go back and rest.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Report!
They found Elegant Miss Yuwen Zi outside the palace.
She’s being carried into the palace now.
Waiting for Your Majesty's orders.
Where is she now?
Answering Your Majesty. Elegant Miss is waiting outside the palace.
It's just that she is unconscious.
Her personal maid is taking care of her.
- Summon her in quickly.
- Yes.
Summon her!
What happened?
Answer Your Majesty. After Miss Yuwen was abducted,
the guards and I had chased them a long time until reaching the lakeside.
It seemed like the culprit had recognized her by mistake.
He threw Miss into the lake. That’s why we were able to save her.
But, our pitiful Miss...
Was it real?
Why would this happen? Quick!
Someone please come.
Quickly call the imperial doctor to check.
Your Majesty, you take good care.
- Prime Minister, isn’t Medical Sage Zong Yue staying in your manor?
- Yes.
Why don’t you call him here?
I guess Prime Minister would rather use your own man, right?
I will use. I will use.
Mister, your acting was beautiful just now.
Look at Qi Zhen. He couldn’t even talk because he was shocked by you.
Can't you tell whether I'm angry for real or not?
Someone touched my person, but I didn’t know.
He honestly did get angry.
Back then, if it wasn't for me who assisted him, could he have today?
Go down.
He had the nerve to reprimand me in front of the imperial court.
He used Zhang Henian to pressure me!
Who does he think he is?
Godfather, please calm down.
He’s just a puppet I supported onto the throne.
Yun Hen has no right to say this.
But this place is Deep Water.
No matter how useless the puppet is,
the king is still the king.
Are you reminding me that his surname is Xuanyuan?
I don’t dare to.
You’re right.
His surname is Xuanyuan.
Only by tolerating and holding in your anger can you retain the capability to solve any problems.
But today's incident is not simple.
Godfather, are you suspecting that the abduction was arranged by Xuanyuan Min?
You’re right.
Then, he could push all the blame on me this way.
Agreeing to give Zhang Henian military expenditure
will be achieved without effort then.
He’s actually this treacherous.
Not only treacherous, but also out of control.
If this continues, I’m afraid that it would be even harder and harder to control him.
Then our spies in the palace?
Even though we have Cao Cheng to spy and bring us news,
he is still one layer away.
We still have to think of another way to keep a close eye on him.
Yes.
Fifth Older Brother! Fifth Older Brother!
Prince Zhan!
I heard the Elegant Miss sent by the Prime Minister's manor was abducted by a powerfully impressive expert.
I'm guessing, it's you Fifth Older Brother who saved Fuyao. Right?
I also think so, Prince Zhan. Where is Older Sis Fuyao right now?
Fuyao has her own arrangements.
She doesn't plan on leaving Prime Minister's Manor .
She plans to enter into the palace.
Why?
The palace is so dangerous.
Will Fuyao be fine by herself?
The palace isn't a place that you or I could easily enter and leave.
Fuyao has always been smart.
She can handle it on her own.
Also, you helped to change her appearance, so she should be all right.
What are you doing?
I still have things to take care of.
I originally planned to save Fuyao to repay my gratitude and leave the Deep Water for some time.
Now, Fuyao doesn't need me to get involved.
I plan on immediately setting out.
You guys take these gold leaves.
You will have a use for them in the future.
Thank you, Fifth Older Brother.
Great. We will go with you wherever you go.
So you have someone to take care of you on the road.
No.
Why?
Official Yun.
Is Mr. Zong available?
He is taking an afternoon nap. No one can disturb—
No problem.
Why did Mr. Yun come to see me today?
The Prime Minister's goddaughter Miss Yuwen got abducted by an abductor this morning.
Is this the same Miss Yuwen who didn't die from the night of the big fire?
Yes, it is she.
Fortunately, she was rescued and only suffered some shock.
Sorry to trouble you to help and take a look at her.
Since Mr. Yun has asked personally,
then naturally Zong Yue shall respect your request and sincerely obey.
Qing Feng, deliver my medical box over.
Yes.
- Just see me off here.
- But—
I don't like repeating myself.
Fifth Older Brother, this trip is so long and full of danger.
I'm not at ease letting you go alone.
It's exactly because it is too dangerous, that I'd be too preoccupied to take care of you.
- Bringing you along would just be a burden.
- But—
That place isn't a place you should be going to.
I know you're concerned for my safety.
All day long, you wear a harsh strict facial expression.
Eyes glaring wide intently like those of a bull's.
Can't you be a little nicer to me?
About my departure this time, you must not let Deep Water nor Heaven Fiend find out.
If they catch wind of it,
you will never be able to see me again.
Don't worry, Fifth Older Brother. I definitely won't tell a single soul.
The situation of Deep Water's capital is hard to tell right now.
It's a problematic place.
When I'm not here, there will no longer be anyone who cares whether you are alive or dead.
If you feel unsafe, just go back to Qiongye first.
No need to wait for me.
These last six years, I accompanied you, ran through the entire Five Regions.
How could there be something that I can't take care?
I'm going.
About the big fire in the manor that night, I wonder if there is any news of the culprit?
The culprit and his associates were all caught the next day.
Really? What kind of criminal would dare to be so audacious?
They're just some infamous pirates.
Who knows what muddled their minds for them to get the idea to aim at the Prime Minister's Manor.
But the Prime Minister has ordered for them to all be killed.
They're all dead?
Yes. Once the culprits are dead,
unexpected troubles can't spring up.
Mr. Yun's execution is sharp.
It's Prime Minister's blessing.
It’s so late. Does Mr. Yuan have something to see me about?
Can I come in to talk?
We flipped the place inside out today trying to find the assassin.
The assassin has a wound on his body, so he should be easier to identify.
I don’t know if Mister would be willing to let me take a look at your arm.
You guessed correctly.
I’m the person you’re looking for.
Then I must ask you to please come with me to see the Prime Minister.
Don't you want to ask me why I readily just confessed?
Mister can personally report the hidden reasons to Prime Minister.
If I'm not wrong, your real birthday is the fourth day of the sixth month.
You're 19 years old this year.
What does that mean?
You were five years old when you entered the manor.
The old housekeeper personally told Qi Zhen, that you were his biological nephew.
But before he died,
why did he tell you your real birthday and tell you not to tell anyone,
especially your godfather, Qi Zhen?
You dare to say another word.
Have you found anything from investigating your real identity for so many years?
How did you find out?
I coincidentally know of an old story
that may be related to your identity.
I wonder if Mister has time for about seven minutes?
Has Mister heard of the late Heir Apparent Wenyi?
That year, Heir Apparent Wenyi established a brilliant military success.
But he had a disloyal heart and
coveted the throne of Deep Water.
As he was such a disloyal and unfilial man, his whole household was exterminated.
Naturally, everyone in Deep Water knows about this incident.
What if I told you, that the truth of this incident isn't such?
When Heir Apparent Wenyi was famous all over the world,
King Renzong was at his peak.
Heir Apparent was brave, capable and benevolent.
The citizens of Deep Water only know about Heir Apparent not Renzong.
There were malicious people in the palace who spread slander about him.
Renzong became more and more suspicious.
In the end, an evil person set up a plot to frame Heir Apparent.
King Renzong couldn't tolerate this Heir Apparent who stood out more than him.
The person who set him up...
was the former Heir Apparent's best friend,
now the most powerful Prime Minister, Qi Zhen!
About the execution of the Heir Apparent's whole family,
everyone thought it was the extermination of his lineage.
But I know he still has two descendants.
The two of them are living ignoble lives.
Both of them have an aquatic dragon tattoo on their shoulder!
Could it possibly be that Mister's shoulder coincidentally has the same tattoo as mine?
Impossible!
I was abandoned when I was young.
Prime Minister gave me the chance to start over!
You've become so familiar with living a life with the foe as your father,
that you've forgotten what's flowing in your blood.
♫ A solitary sailboat is drifting everywhere with no boundary ♫
It's fine, too.
If you think what I've just said is just nonsense,
then arrest and take me to Qi Zhen now.
♫ My heart isn't an isolated island ♫
♫ Changing mind and fluctuating only takes one second ♫
♫ The world is the embrace ♫
Mister Qiu is making sugar art in the south of the city.
You can ask him to confirm.
Mr. Zong is here.
Miss Yuwen, Mr. Zong is here to attend to your illness. Please open the door.
Come in.
This way, please.
I didn't expect that we'd meet again inside the palace.
Are you able to recognize me?
Look at your fierce-look.
Who else could it be but Fuyao?
You should have said earlier.
Back to the point. My head has been hurting a lot.
It feels like my head is about to split from moving slightly.
I think you must've been kicked by a donkey.
You'll be fine after a few acupuncture needles.
No need. Thank you, thank you.
What are you up to today?
Why have you summoned me into the palace?
I'm just worried about you.
I wanted to see if you were dead or alive.
If you keep hassling me, I'll really be a dead soon.
You're a medical sage.
Even dead people can be brought back to life by you.
If you die one day, I definitely won't ask the king of hell to give you back.
Come on, you. I've at least delivered the item for you, didn't I?
Even if I don't get credit for it, I still used effort to do it.
Why don't you ask me about my situation?
You're already in his harem.
What other situation do I need to ask about?
Maybe he has convinced you to be his internal agent in the palace.
About the item I've given you, as long as it lands in his hands,
you don't need to worry about anything else.
I really am worried about your safety.
I really feel uneasy because you took the arrow in my place that day.
Think about it. Danger is hiding behind every corner in the Prime Minister's Manor.
Even if we're not friends, we did live through hardships together.
Shouldn't you at least give me some condolences?
All right. If you're really feeling unwell, I'll give you a diagnosis.
What's wrong?
Am I going to die soon?
Yes.
You're not going to live for long.
Fortunately, there's these effective medicines.
You'll be fine after you take it.
Black one is for saving lives.
White is for killing people.
For the vermilion one, ask me before you use it.
Then what is the vermilion one for?
Her pulse is like that of a living person, but also a dying one.
Why is it so strange?
Mister was burning with anxiety when Miss Fuyao was abducted that day.
But now, Miss Fuyao is already in the palace.
Is Mister going to visit Miss Fuyao?
Do you like me?
Find her!
Or else the Five Regions will once again be doomed eternally because of her.
There's no rush.
There is plenty of time.
[Prince Fierce is very ill.]
[He has gone to the mountains for resting quietly to recuperate.]
Fifth Older Brother, Fifth Older Brother.
Your mind is only filled with your Fifth Older Brother the whole day.
You don't even know where he is now.
How are you going to find him by yourself on a horse?
Leave Deep Water. Head North and it's Heaven Fiend.
I can absolutely find him.
But-- But didn't you promise to wait here for his return?
Why are you going to find him?
I did promise him.
But I've gotten used to running after him over the years.
For me to stay here alone to just sit and wait, I can't take it.
But the road is dangerous.
For a lady on her own,
what will you do if someone bullies you?
Who will dare to bully me?
I'm the one who bullies others.
How about it? Do you want to come along with me?
Heaven Fiend is covered with ice and snow.
They also have mountain foods Deep Water doesn't have.
It's quite fun.
Really?
Why would I lie to you?
It's winter all four seasons there.
You can ski or ice skate.
There are mountain stags to eat wherever you go.
They also have sugared fruits made with liquid sugar.
I guarantee you, you wouldn't have eaten anything as delicious.
Then... all right, then. I—
No. I can't go with you.
Why not?
I have to go find Fuyao.
I left Mt. Mystic Soul with her at the start,
but now she's stuck in the palace.
There are unknown dangers,
so I can't leave her on her own.
A loyal friend!
Fuyao didn't dote on you wastefully.
But the palace is now heavily fortified.
Fuyao has become an Elegant Miss.
How would you find her so easily?
That doesn't matter. I have a solution.
But I can't tell you yet.
All right.
Anyway, when I come back with Fifth Older Brother,
I must see a living and kicking Fuyao.
If she gets hurt, I'll blame it on you!
Don't worry.
Then, I'll wait for you to bring back sugared fruits for me.
Deal! I'm leaving then.
Take good care of yourself!
You take good care of yourself, too.
I really look forward to this eagerly.
Don't you look forward to this?
Master is the one in the spotlight.
I am fine as an onlooker.
You're getting better at acting.
Summon the Elegant Misses!
Welcome, Your Majesty!
Today is the day I'm choosing a consort.
I've purposefully summoned you all here to help me come up with an idea.
Your Majesty, choosing consorts is a serious matter.
How do we dare take precedence?
It is because it's a serious matter,
that I especially summoned you all to help me make a final decision.
Summon the Elegant Misses into the palace hall!
Respectful greetings, Your Majesty.
These are all excellent beauties.
Next time, when I act in a play,
I wouldn't have to be worried about not having someone to act with.
You.
Come to the front.
What is your name?
My name is Tang Zhirong.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
She is the daughter of General Border Security Tang Bonian, Tang Zhirong.
She is seventeen years old.
General Border Security.
Your Majesty, General Border Security, Tang Bonian, has guarded the borders for many years.
He is a subject who has contributed greatly to Deep Water Nation.
Is that so?
Then, I will choose the one whom Prime Minister thinks is best.
For serious matters like choosing consorts, Your Majesty should decide yourself.
Then, you're picked.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Who is the next one?
Greetings, Your Majesty. My name is Chen Xiangxie.
- Go back.
- Yes.
- My name is Yuwen–
- Why is there still so many people?!
Your Majesty.
- This Elegant Miss is Yuwen from the North–
- All right, all right, all right.
Jiang Feng, hand the jade tablets to Prime Minister.
I'll just choose whoever Prime Minister thinks is good.
Yes.
Your Majesty, don't make a joke such as this with me.
Prime Minister, please.
Your Majesty, I am not deserving of this good fortune.
Prime Minister, why are you being so polite?
Although choosing consorts is a matter of the harem,
it is also related to the frontal palace.
As Prime Minister works in the best interests of the country, for you to choose consorts for me,
naturally you shouldn't refuse to accept the responsibility.
- I don't dare.
- You–!
Since that is the case, the ones I've chosen before are void!
Today, I'll set a precedent,
spinning the jade spinner.
- Don't be impatient, don't be impatient.
- I want this one.
- Okay, okay.
- This one looks good.
Don't be impatient. Don't be impatient.
- Does it look good?
- Yes!
This one for you two to eat.
You two eat this one. Take it. Take it.
- Thank you, Grandpa.
- Thank you.
Take it.
This one is for you two to eat.
Older Brother, wait for me!
Hurry! Mr. Qiu is blowing sugar art again!
Okay.
- Which one do you want today?
- Mister Qiu.
This one is for you.
Take it. Okay, okay.
Little Mister, do you want to buy a sugar art?
Little Mister is still the same as the past, only looking at it.
You couldn't bring yourself to eat it even when it melted.
Mister Qiu.
Every miss, lessen your impatience!
Your Majesty has said, whoever the jade spinner lands on,
she will be chosen into the harem.
You all just wait for the summons.
Hey! How could there be such logic?
In all of Deep Water's history and former generations,
nothing as ridiculous as this has ever happened before!
All history and former generations are in the past.
Today, His Majesty has spoken.
So we, who are under his command, should follow.
- Let's go.
- Preposterous!
Three queens were from our Prefect Xiping's Manor.
I've never heard of them being chosen by spinning a jade spinner.
What are you smiling about?
I think someone who is like a baldhead worries that she has no hair so she put flowers on her head.
You-You're insulting me?
Enough, enough, enough! Enough.
We still have to get by as sisters in the palace. Don't break the harmonious atmosphere.
- Who do you think you are?
- Me?
You were born from a concubine!
Don't think that just because His Majesty chose you before, you're qualified for calling me "sister."
Yeah.
Say, if even those borne from a legal wife aren't picked,
how could she be fit to be our sister?
You wild brat! I'm going to tear your mouth!
You–!
Look at your face that has been kicked by a donkey.
If I were you, I wouldn't dare to come out to scare people.
- Older Sister.
- What?
Your mouth.
What's wrong with my mouth?
- You–!
- Today is really a good day.
The wish that Miss Gao has just made has come true.
Older Sister, your face is so pretty.
Choosing consorts is an important matter.
It's not quite appropriate to treat it like a game, right?
I asked Prime Minister to choose, but Prime Minister wouldn't.
I-I can only ask the gods to choose.
Whoever this lands on will be picked.
Summon! Tang Zhirong, Jian Xue, Yuwen Zi,
Fu Jiayi, Na Lanjing, Chen Xiangxie,
Zhang Wanting, Liu Jueqi, into the palace hall!
I'm not included? How could I not be included?!
I'm not included?
Miss Gao, how unfortunate.
Even if Zhirong wants to use you to get higher in status and be sisters,
- I'm afraid there's no chance now.
- You–!
Mister, please have a seat.
Look, you—
Zong Yue said you were the one who betrayed your master for selfish gains.
What First Mister said about the past is right.
Why?
Second Mister,
do you know what was written on the imperial decree fifteen years ago?
"In the Heir Apparent's manor, no matter if they're male, female, old, young,
high or low in status, are to be killed with legal authority."
What is this?
This is to cut that final tie Heir Apparent Wenyi had with Deep Water!
It was to exterminate his lineage!
Killed with legal authority.
But you're still alive!
I am alive.
I am still alive.
All the people criticize behind my back and call me a traitor.
Saying that I betrayed my master for selfish gains.
But who can understand?
If I didn't get Qi Zhen's trust at that time,
how could I have protected the two misters' lives?
That year, when I acted to have betrayed my master for my gains,
that was... that was the last thing Heir Apparent entrusted to me!
I... Even if I have to go down in history infamously,
I still could never fail him!
I've seen so many ladies today.
In terms of appearance and demeanor,
I think...
you are the best.
Thank you for your compliment, Your Majesty.
What should I reward you with?
You will be conferred Lady Precious.
- Thank you, Your Majesty.
- Get up.
Your Majesty! The rules of the Deep Water has always been to
name the 4 ladies, Precious, Virtue, Virtuous and Fair among Elegant Misses at the same time.
Then decide on the Queen from among them.
There is no previous antecedent event, where titles were given one at a time.
You–
You.
You. Say your names.
My name is Jian Xue.
My father is Jian Shen, an Imperial Secretary from Hanlin Imperial Academy.
My name is Yuwen Zi.
My father is Yuwen Jian, the Deputy of South Island County in the north area.
Miss Yuwen is Prime Minister's goddaughter.
What?
All right, then. Both of you look pleasing to the eye.
How about this, you'll be conferred Lady Virtue.
You'll be Lady Fair.
All the others will be Vibrant Miss!
Thank you, Your Majesty!
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Congratulations, Your Majesty.
Three of the four main lady consorts have been chosen.
There is only one Lady Virtuous missing. There's–
This– Let's end here today, all right?
Let's discuss all others another day. Okay?
Your Majesty.
I didn't expect choosing consorts to be this tiring.
Jiang Feng, accompany me back.
Yes.
Selecting consorts is an important and serious issue!
All right, all right!
If there's anything else, let's discuss after I wake up. Okay?
Second Mister.
Mister Qiu!
Second Mister, I dragged out an ignoble existence till now
just to let Mister know who your enemy is.
You can never be softhearted and light-handed;
more so, you can't name the villain as your father!
"Hard-to-Get Love" by Lala Hsu
♫ What do you know? ♫
♫ What are good about the three realms? ♫
♫ If there're no three poisons, if there're no worries ♫
♫ How can it make me reluctant to leave? ♫
♫ Worry for love, beg for hate ♫
♫ And even discard my soul for affection ♫
♫ The one, who asks me to love him, loves me ♫
♫ I only want him to love me ♫
♫ What do you use to exchange for this hard-to-get love? ♫
♫ If there's no sickness or weakness, if there's never oldness ♫
♫ How can it make a spark to chase after stars alone? ♫
♫ Slim down for him, stay for my heart ♫
♫ And even chase away all luck for dreams ♫
♫ It wants me to be so pretty that I seize his soul ♫
♫ And continue dazzling in his heart ♫
♫ There is a saying that what a person asks for the lifetime ♫
♫ Is no more than staying together with one's lover by any means ♫
♫ If one can't obtain what one asks for ♫
♫ One is filled with anxiety and with knitted brows ♫
♫ There is a saying that if a person asks for the next lifetime ♫
♫ One should only ask to know everything about warfare ♫
♫ Dreams beg heart to grant me love ♫
♫ And have someone's company for the rest of my life ♫
♫ Have someone's company♫
♫ There is a saying that what a person asks for the lifetime ♫
♫ Is no more than staying together with one's lover by any means ♫
♫ If one can't obtain what one asks for ♫
♫ One is filled with anxiety and with knitted brows ♫
♫ There is a saying that if a person asks for the next lifetime ♫
♫ One should only ask to know everything about warfare ♫
♫ Dreams beg heart to grant me love ♫
♫ And have someone's company for the rest of my life ♫