"Fuyao" by Karen Mok
♫ I start to dance nimbly and gracefully ♫
♫ For what my beautiful face is frowned? ♫
♫ Without him, I'll drift with the current ♫
♫ Why is the tune of the zither a farewell song? ♫
♫ Without me, he'll be lonely in this universe ♫
♫ My heart silently waits at the cliff of Firmament ♫
♫ The heaven, the earth, the sun and the moon are all in my bosom ♫
♫ How can I own the top freedom in this world? ♫
♫ There is no fear from my heart ♫
♫ Deep love won't hide ♫
♫ True love won't run short ♫
♫ Dreams give hopes through all the ages ♫
♫ Why go through storms and stress to be bright and beautiful? ♫
♫ There is no struggle from my heart ♫
♫ Swaying along with the wind ♫
♫ I can do anything freely ♫
♫ I enter my dreams easily and unrestrainedly ♫
♫ What a beautiful dance ♫
[Legend of Fuyao]
~ Episode 16 ~
Long time no see.
Senior Sister, it really has been a long time.
The grudge between you and I has nothing to do with other people.
Please let Xiaoqi go.
I am the one who sets the rules.
You don't get a say!
Both of you must die!
Xiaoqi!
Why is it you? Where is Xiaoqi?
You are about to die but still think of other people.
Today, you are doomed to die.
Who is it?
Come out!
Why is it you again?
I should ask you the same question.
I've been nice and saved the beauty heroically.
You should at least thank me.
Sure.
A beautiful prefecture princess is now lying on the ground.
- Take her. Don't be shy!
- Naughty!
Let me ask you. Have you waited here for a long time?
You just waited for this moment so that I could thank you.
I want a whole lot more than just a simple "thank you."
I don't have time to chat with you.
I'm in a hurry to save someone.
If I help you find that person, can I ask you a favor?
- Xiaoqi! How's Xiaoqi?
- He's fine!
Once I cut the rope later, your side will drop.
I'll catch you.
Okay.
Don't touch me!
Your tiny body is actually quite heavy.
- Xiaoqi, Xiaoqi!
- Older Sis Fuyao.
- I'm here.
- I knew you would come save me.
It's all because of this thing. I'll remove it for you.
- Wait!
- Why?
His life is now interlocked with the Earth Absorbing Bell.
If you take it away, he'll die.
Then what should we do?
Godfather.
Who told you to do this?
I just thought we should not keep Zhan Beiya alive.
After he escaped from the fire at the Official Post,
he remains a latent threat.
I worry that he may disclose your great plan.
It will hurt you and—
I've told you before,
this person can't be killed.
Not only can you not kill him right now,
but you also have to support him and provide all he needs.
The Earth Absorbing Bell is useless now.
If you kill him,
what else can I use to negotiate with Zhan Nancheng?
Therefore, what does Godfather mean?
About the mess in Heaven Fiend, I don't want to get involved.
I don't want to offend either of these two brothers.
If you killed him right here,
we would have trouble in explaining what happened to the Earth Absorbing Bell.
Now I understand.
Palace Leader has come.
I hope Xuanyuan Min can't get away this time.
What is this?
Take Xiaoqi and leave first. Leave the business here to me.
- What about you?
- Go!
- Don't die!
- Don't worry! I won't die so easily.
Let's go!
Xiaoqi, Xiaoiqi, Xiaoqi! Xiaoqi!
Fuyao!
Zhan Beiye!
How to remove the Earth Absorbing Bell?
- How is he?
- Fortunately, you have transmitted him your energy.
His life is saved.
Energy?
Help me guard us. I’ll remove the Earth Absorbing Bell.
All right.
Done.
Xiaoqi! Xiaoqi!
Xiaoqi!
Older Sis Fuyao.
- Thank you.
- He’s injured because of the coldness of Earth Absorbing Bell.
I need to gather energies to heal him in order to speed up his recovery.
Please take care of Xiaoqi for a while.
Okay, be careful.
I’ll come back in a minute.
I thought there was nothing you can’t do.
It looks like you still need my help.
Yes, I really can’t do this without you.
I ask you. Why did you let me stab you in the slavefighting ring that day?
If I didn’t do that, would you have stopped?
Your doing that makes me inhumane and unjust.
But people only remember your chivalrousness.
These leaves have become demons.
We can’t just fight over them like this.
These things have no blood, flesh or fixed composition.
Normal techniques can’t hurt them.
We've succeeded.
It’s difficult to fight against it this time.
Run! Quick!
Quick!
It's you?
If it weren't for her,
today would be your death day.
What happened?
Are you so worried about me?
I just wished you wouldn't die in the hands of someone else.
Your Majesty!
These people were not here when I was in danger and only rushed here now.
Since they’re here, I've found Xiaoqi and the Earth Absorbing Bell.
I’ll let you take care of the rest.
I’m leaving now.
If we act, we have to finish the drama.
If you leave now, who will act with me?
What’s happening?
His Majesty disappeared.
Why is His Majesty so slow?
Godfather, it seems that there is no sound and movement.
His Majesty cannot be... Can he?
Hurry up!
Hurry up! Send this lady away.
Your Majesty, what happened in the forest just now?
What happened?
Prime Minister, are you very unhappy with me being the king?
That’s why you ordered people to assassinate me in the forest.
Your Majesty, why did you say such a word?
Everyone can see that I’m loyal to Your Majesty.
Then, tell me. Why are there monsters in the forest?
If it was not for that girl who got injured on behalf of me, I would be the one dying.
Your Majesty,
the ones you met in the forest aren’t monsters or assassins.
They may be the Heaven’s Rule.
What do you mean?
I remember this is written in an old book.
When a new king takes over the throne of Deep Water,
he has to experience a test from the Heavens.
That test is called the Heaven’s Rule.
If you successfully passed the Heaven’s Rule,
the country will definitely be prosperous.
This is a very good fortune sign.
A good fortune sign.
Your Majesty is mighty.
Prime Minister, is what you said real?
Very real.
Good, it looks like the heavens are helping me with my position.
I don’t have to worry that people will covet my place anymore.
Of course. Of course.
Your Majesty, look. You came out without any injury, didn't you?
Oh, yeah. Prime Minister, the girl today did a great job.
Choose one day and send her to my palace, okay?
I’ll definitely fulfill your request.
But I don’t know where the girl is from, I—
Prime Minister, she’s from your manor.
Why are you asking me?
My manor?
Godfather, what’s the matter?
When the manor in Changning sent the girl here,
they said her birth date was extraordinarily good.
I thought that was some nonsense and didn’t believe them fully.
After today’s happening, you know?
This is an overlord’s star.
Godfather, you planned to...
Today, we didn’t get to kill Xuanyuan Min.
Indeed, he’s not as simple as what we see from outside.
I think we have to slowly plan for our big plan.
Since Xuanyuan Min thinks Yuwen Zi saved him,
then this girl
is the best chess piece to be put beside him.
God’s will.
Fifth Older Brother.
- Has he become better?
- Yes.
His life is safe now.
Pitiful boy, being bullied in such a way.
He’s okay.
Now, the one who got in trouble is Fuyao.
Miss got everyone’s attention yesterday.
The Prime Minister will come and visit you personally later.
Miss, why don’t you prepare yourself?
What did you say? Qi-Qi Zhen is coming here personally?
Yes.
The veil isn’t that important.
It will be bad if you forget about your birthmark.
- How do you—
- I know Miss is generous.
Master has reminded me to take care of you on everything.
Who’s your master?
Is it Zhan Beiye?
Although everyone knows Prince Fierce is mighty,
comparing him to our master, I think he’s way more weaker.
Don’t tell me it's that liar?
Miss, stop asking. I won’t tell you anything.
Prime Minister is here.
Greetings, Prime Minister.
What’s the matter? Are you afraid of me?
Since I entered Prime Minister’s Manor,
this is my first time seeing Prime Minister.
Everyone says Prime Minister is a well-known important person.
I’m afraid that I’m not well-mannered enough and would surprise Prime Minister.
I see. What did they say about me?
Tell me.
They also said Prime Minister is a big hero of Deep Water.
If there was no Prime Minister, there would be no Deep Water today.
They even said,
I have a chance to enter Prime Minister’s Manor, is my fortune that I cultivated for years.
What’s the matter?
Doctor Zong from the manor said
I got an epidemic disease from the Hunting Field.
Once we get in contact, the disease will be passed to you.
I’m afraid that Prime Minister...
and my face is ugly with a birthmark on my face.
I’m afraid that it will shock you.
Even if a person has a beauty which can shut down the moon and put the flowers to shame,
she won't look pretty if she’s not talented nor kind.
I see you’re calm and well-mannered.
This isn’t a personality which we can find easily.
These are so much more important things than your beauty.
Prime Minister, thanks for your praises.
But, how brave are you?
You actually collaborated with culprits.
Collaborated?
Qi Zhen has discussed with his loyal officials that they want to select concubines for Mister.
Just that I didn’t expect that Mister would predict this and step in a step ahead.
I was planning to let him bully me,
and I just need to observe.
But after the incident in the Hunting Field yesterday,
I actually have a new plan which not only can mess Qi Zhen’s plans up,
but also keep the person I want.
I’m-I’m just a lowly girl
and staying in the manor everyday.
How do I dare to collaborate with anyone else?
Tell me. How did you save the King in the Hunting Field yesterday?
In the hunting ground yesterday,
I was just curious and wanted to have a look at the King’s face.
That’s why I entered the hunting ground.
Suddenly, strong wind blew and the leaves became the shape of a human.
- Really?
- What I said is the truth.
Those leaves which formed a human rushed towards me.
I was shocked and ran away quickly
and so happened to meet the King.
Then?
The human-like leaves rushed towards me and the King.
I was very shocked.
That time, who knows that His Majesty... His Majesty...
actually...
Actually what?
His Majesty actually hid behind me.
But I was too scared and didn’t know where to hide,
so I could only hug the King and wait to be killed.
Suddenly, I’m not sure how,
there shot a fire arrow and all the leaves were burned.
Did you see clearly who shot the arrow?
Because I just arrived at Deep Water not long ago,
I don’t know anyone.
But because I was shocked yesterday, so I fainted.
When I woke up, I was already here.
Is what you said real?
Everything is the truth.
It looks like there’s someone protecting His Majesty secretly.
This is Deep Water Nation’s luck.
It’s also your fortune.
His Majesty thinks you saved him.
He asked me to send you into the palace and become his concubine.
What virtue or capability do I have that—
Just remember, you have an overlord’s star’s fate.
You have to deal with big things in the future.
If both of us can collaborate,
that will be the great luck of Deep Water.
Do you understand?
His Majesty?
Prime Minister... Prime Minister, are you really thinking highly of me?
Yes, after you enter the palace,
I’ll make sure that you will become the queen of Deep Water.
But you have to understand that as I recommended you to the palace,
rewards and punishments all depend on me.
It’s my fortune to be able to share Prime Minister’s burdens.
After you enter the palace, I’ll take care of your family on behalf of you.
You don’t have to be worry.
Since now, you’ll be my goddaughter.
Yuwen Zi thanks Prime Minister on behalf of my family.
Since now, everything will...
everything will go just as Godfather’s plan.
I’ll order people to teach you about the manners in the palace these few days.
Kid, don’t disappoint me.
I won't.
Stand up.
The Earth Absorbing Bell is back to its rightful owner.
I've also found Xiaoqi.
Why do I need to stay here?
Miss, if you want to run away, I won’t be able to stop you.
I just hope that Miss will have some pity.
I would like to ask for your understanding.
Of course, I can’t leave.
If I leave, everyone who served me in this Prime Minister’s Manor
and the ones in Changning Yuwen’s Manor
will not be able to escape from this.
But—
But I can’t stay here just like this either,
and wait for Qi Zhen to send me into the palace.
I assume Miss already has a solution.
It’s okay, you can eat first.
Don't need to wait any more. Fifth Older Brother—
Eat slowly. I-I’ll give you the rice.
Eat slowly. Eat slowly.
There’re enough food here.
Thank you.
You really suffered.
Unexpectedly, you have suffered because of the Earth Absorbing Bell.
Look at you, so skinny.
I was afraid that you wouldn’t endure it.
- I’m okay. The problem is—
- All right. All right.
The problem is Older Sis Fuyao is stuck in Prime Minister’s Manor in order to save me.
So, I need to eat more.
After I’m full, I’ll have energy to save her.
Have you found a way to save her?
Although I was dizzy that time,
I remember the route to the Prime Minister’s Manor clearly.
I’m not talented, but my memory is good.
Don’t worry.
So, do you plan to enter the Prime Minister’s Manor and save her?
I wanted to do that, too.
Let’s do it together! Together! Together! Together!
What were you saying?
What can we say? Right?
Fifth Brother, you’re back? You must be hungry.
I’ll fill your bowl with rice.
I’m warning both of you.
Don’t go and create troubles.
Godfather.
How was it?
Prefecture Princess Pei Yuan said that she actually didn’t take anyone away from the water prison.
I wanted to ask her a few more questions,
but Prefecture Princess was very angry.
- I can only—
- Absurd.
What does she think my Prime Minister’s Manor is?
Spread the word, without my permission, no one is allowed to let Pei Yuan out of my manor.
Whoever disobeys, kill!
Yes.
I've ordered people to investigate as well.
Prefecture Princess Pei Yuan brought the kid from the water prison to the hunting ground at that time.
But not sure why, she was injured when she returned.
And there’s no news about the kid later.
Godfather, do you think that Zhan Beiye has taken the Earth Absorbing Bell back?
I guess the same thing, too.
Zhan Beiye's appearance that day was strange.
He spoke everything against me in front of Xuanyuan Min.
I fear that he has known the whereabouts of the Earth Absorbing Bell for a long time.
Never mind. Let’s observe how things will go.
Yes.
Now that you mention it,
there’s news from the palace.
They said Zhang Henian entered the palace by himself early this morning.
His Majesty summoned him.
- What?
- We are still not sure what they said.
But according to the spy from Marquis Zhang’s Manor who reported to us,
it had something to do with the pay and provisions of the soldiers in the eight garrisons.
Pay and provisions? Did they hear any details?
That... When Zhang Henian entered the palace,
His Majesty had all the servants sent away.
There is no confirmed news from the palace, either.
But, Godfather, don’t be worried, everyone beside His Majesty is our people.
You can just rest assured.
Rest assured?
I have been in the office for thirty-seven years and I've never had a restful day.
What your people saw was everything from the surface.
And what Xuanyuan Min is really thinking. I’m afraid that—
we can’t delay His Majesty's marriage anymore.
Godfather, are you really going to use Miss Yuwen as your bet?
Stars have ten thousand phenomena, humans have thousands of faces.
How would it be enough if we only have one path?
All right.
We’re choosing concubines for the king.
It’s not a chance for you to earn money.
Every contestant’s person, background, age,
birth date, personalities,
every single thing is important.
We can’t be careless.
Look at this. Who is this?
Daughter of Jundong County Deputy.
Even such a lowly girl can take part in this?
Go down.
The time is here.
Put them in the storage.
These are the documents of all the selected Elegant Misses.
Among them, there is the candidate for the future queen of Deep Water.
Remember, you must make no mistake.
Yes.
So much kerosene. Where did you get it?
Tonight, there will be a fire here.
I’ll pretend to be a servant and leave.
There will be a burned corpse.
Then there will be a burned corpse in a room at North Park.
Since then, there will be no more Yuwen Zi in this world.
Indeed, Miss is thoughtful.
Even if I’m thoughtful, I still need your help.
Has Miss ever thought of visiting the palace?
Maybe it may be interesting there.
Let me go.
Godfather, these are the selected Elegant Misses.
The inner court made selections in advance of today.
The final selected Elegant Misses were recorded.
They are all here.
Qi Zhen is so impatient.
He employed people from the inner court so quickly.
All right.
Then, let’s have a look at the beauties who the Prime Minister has prepared.
State Depuy Lee’s daughter, General Ji’s niece.
You wanted to ask me if it’ll be problematic because of her background?
Godfather, you’re smart.
This girl has a good background.
She looks like a good choice,
but putting her onto the name list is only to fawn over her uncle.
That's all.
Once she enters the Harem,
don’t forget that her grandfather was Heir Apparent Wenyi’s important subordinate.
Heir Apparent Wenyi?
Gao Puruo, Prefect Xiping’s daughter.
Pretty and elegant, just like the Lilium Concolor.
Looks like the dawn snow without even applying powders.
Prefect Xiping, this old man,
has some age;
still thinking of multiplying his fief.
He would definitely not keep quiet when it comes to choosing concubines.
Jian Xue, Hanwen Institution’s Jian Sheng’s youngest daughter.
Clear and bright eyes, slim and tiny.
The waist is as...
Was this Jian Sheng Zhang Henian’s student in the past?
Then, Jian Xue is recommended by Marquis Zhang?
Yes, and also no.
Everyone knows Jian Sheng is promoted all the way up by Zhang Henian,
and is thought highly by him.
His daughter is selected as an Elegant Miss now.
Everyone would think she’s a chess piece of Zhang Henian.
Then, why does Godfather let her pass?
Of course, you don’t know.
Jian Sheng has become a chess piece in my hand.
Openly, I need to have my trusted subordinates.
Secretly, I need to have my people as well,
so that I can make sure that nothing will go wrong.
Godfather, you’re smart.
Then, Godfather, who do you want to be the Queen?
This is really a hard decision.
Whether Xuanyuan Min is really ridiculous or faking to be silly,
we must not be careless.
Mister, look at it.
Yes?
General, Prefecture Prince, Marquis, Prime Minister,
the background of these Elegant Misses are better one after another.
I’m afraid that there may be countless connections behind them.
The harem is another battlefield for power to start with.
Don’t ever look down on these women's minds that hide under their silk dresses and hairpins.
Sometimes, they will be the sharpest knife.
Mister, the knife you mean is?
I know in my heart which one.
It's just that I can control Deep Water,
but I may not be able to control her.
Mister, you mean is?
I've spoken too much.
East wind is blowing quietly.
There will be a big incident tonight.
Today’s weather is good.
I’ll present a big incident for the Prime Minister’s Manor.
The wind is strong tonight. Once the fire lights up, you just run away during the chaos.
Thank you, girl and your master.
- Hurry up and leave.
- Let's go!
On the fifteenth, the full moon is in the first heavenly stem position.
When I wear the Imperial Dragon Scales robe, bloody moonlight will fill the sky up. (T/N: bloody moonlight = rebellion)
What time is it now?
Fiftenn minutes left before midnight.
I’ve checked on the route to Imperial Qilin Stage.
Everything is fine. Mister can depart anytime.
Help! Someone please help! There’s a fire!
Someone. Someone please come quickly! There’s a fire!
Someone please come quickly! There’s a fire!
Someone please come quickly. Put out the fire.
Quickly put out the fire!
There is still such a mysterious and sophisticated thing in this world.
Heaven treated people well.
This Dragon Scale Armor is one of the four wonders of Five Regions.
There’s a rumor that says that after a battle in the heavens a long time ago, God surrendered four mythical beasts.
Then, in order to protect these hard-earned halcyon days,
he left four utterly precious wonders.
But, Mister, what exactly is this Dragon Scale Armor?
To many people, the Dragon Scale Armor is their everything.
Everyone wants to be strong and be free of all kinds of diseases and ailments.
These can all be done by Dragon Scale Armor.
No wonder people could do anything to get this Dragon Scale Armor for the past thousands years
and are willing to lose their lives.
Even the mighty Heir Apparent Wenyi couldn’t be spared.
I remember that a folk rumor in Deep Water that Heir Apparent Wenyi privately hid the Dragon Scale Armor
and was greedy over the throne; that’s why he was killed.
He, himself. even carried eternal infamy.
But there were also people saying that Heir Apparent Wenyi's high merits scared His Majesty.
It caused King Xuanyuan at that time to be jealous and suspicious,
so he made up a reason to frame him and kill him.
There are always a lot of sayings about this royal family’s secret.
Fifteen years has passed.
Who knows which is the truth?
Beside those who experienced it that time, no one else cared about it.
But... even people have forgotten about it,
the truth is always the truth.
There’s an assassin!
Quickly catch the assassin!
Hurry up and catch him!
Hurry up!
Separate ourselves and search!
Few of you, go there!
Search carefully!
- It's me!
-  Hurry up!
This way!
Go and check there!
Search carefully!
Follow me!
Don’t let the assassin escape!
Hurry up!
- Where are we going?
- We can't delay. Leave quickly.
Okay.
Over there!
Fuyao!
"Hard-to-Get Love" by Lala Hsu
♫ What do you know? ♫
♫ What are good about the three realms? ♫
♫ If there're no three poisons, if there're no worries ♫
♫ How can it make me reluctant to leave? ♫
♫ Worry for love, beg for hate ♫
♫ And even discard my soul for affection
♫ The one, who asks me to love him, loves me ♫
♫ I only want him to love me ♫
♫ What do you use to exchange for this hard-to-get love? ♫
♫ If there's no sickness or weakness, if there's never oldness ♫
♫ How can it make a spark to chase after stars alone? ♫
♫ Slim down for him, stay for my heart ♫
♫ And even chase away all luck for dreams ♫
♫ It wants me to be so pretty that I seize his soul ♫
♫ And continue dazzling in his heart ♫
♫ There is a saying that what a person asks for the lifetime ♫
♫ Is no more than staying together with one's lover by any means ♫
♫ If one can't obtain what one asks for ♫
♫ One is filled with anxiety and with knitted brows ♫
♫ There is a saying that if a person asks for the next lifetime ♫
♫ One should only ask to know everything about warfare ♫
♫ Dreams beg heart to grant me love ♫
♫ And have someone's company for the rest of my life ♫
♫ Have someone's company♫
♫ There is a saying that what a person asks for the lifetime ♫
♫ Is no more than staying together with one's lover by any means ♫
♫ If one can't obtain what one asks for ♫
♫ One is filled with anxiety and with knitted brows ♫
♫ There is a saying that if a person asks for the next lifetime ♫
♫ One should only ask to know everything about warfare ♫
♫ Dreams beg heart to grant me love ♫
♫ And have someone's company for the rest of my life ♫