"Fuyao" by Karen Mok
♫ I start to dance nimbly and gracefully ♫
♫ For what my beautiful face is frowned? ♫
♫ Without him, I'll drift with the current ♫
♫ Why is the tune of the zither a farewell song? ♫
♫ Without me, he'll be lonely in this universe ♫
♫ My heart silently waits at the cliff of Firmament ♫
♫ The heaven, the earth, the sun and the moon are all in my bosom ♫
♫ How can I own the top freedom in this world? ♫
♫ There is no fear from my heart ♫
♫ Deep love won't hide ♫
♫ True love won't run short ♫
♫ Dreams give hopes through all the ages ♫
♫ Why go through storms and stress to be bright and beautiful? ♫
♫ There is no struggle from my heart ♫
♫ Swaying along with the wind ♫
♫ I can do anything freely ♫
♫ I enter my dreams easily and unrestrainedly ♫
♫ What a beautiful dance ♫
[Legend of Fuyao]
~ Episode 31 ~
To tell you the truth,
a good friend of mine is falsely accused.
I needed to take this man to the Megrez Imperial City to see the Emperor
so that he can clear the charges for my friend. Who knows—
Forget it.
I'll go to the Megrez Imperial City and have an audience with the emperor first.
Are you saying that you want to go to Megrez Imperial City
and even want to enter the palace to have an audience with the emperor?
Is there anything wrong about that?
It's easy to enter the Imperial city, but hard to enter the Imperial palace.
Don't even talk about having an audience with the Lord Emperor.
Megrez commands the Five Regions and has tight security to begin with.
Now that Crown Prince has returned from his training, the whole city is rejoicing.
The more it will be hard for an outsider to go in.
Who really is that Crown Prince Wuji?
Recently, I keep hearing you all talk about him.
I only know that at the age of ten,
he already produced world renowned literary works and his arrows can travel thousands of li.
At age 12, he charged into the south border by himself alone,
fixed the conflict between the northern and southern tribes,
and resolved a great calamity that almost exterminated the Qiongye Tribe.
By age 15, the heavens sent down an auspicious sign that preserved the harvest of the whole Five Regions.
There is even such a person?
Even the story tellers won't dare write things like that.
Wuji isn't human.
What?
He's a god.
Sorry...
Then, can we stop talking about your god?
Can you... tell me how to enter the city?
I just happen to be going to Megrez Imperial City in a few days.
- Really?
- One is that the leaves of Winged Tree in Mt. Herding Spirit
can stop the epidemic.
Second, I have an important matter to do, too.
Seeing how you're of the same age as me,
and that we're fated to meet,
why don't you stay for a few more days?
After I finish the matters at hand,
I'll take you with me when I seek an audience in the palace.
- Really?
- Yes.
Wuji, you're finally back.
Older Sister Fuyao, my Miss has fallen ill.
This way.
Miss! Miss!
- Miss...
- Let me pass.
Older Sister.
Fuyao.
I'm here.
You all just go back to your work.
Miss Fuyao and I will just privately say a few words.
No matter how well one can predict, they can't really predict their own life.
I really feel embarrassed for asking you to come here today,
but I have a very important matter that I must ask you to do.
Sister, just give the instructions.
To tell you honestly,
my going to the Imperial city this time is originally for the official matters of the Five Regions.
But now, I fear that I won't be able to rush there anymore.
- Miss, don't say such things.
- I won't be able to rush there.
Miss.
Do you still remember the Crown Prince Wuji that I told you before?
I remember.
He is my fiancé.
Miss is the second princess of Plough Nation.
Since she was little, she was already engaged to Crown Prince Wuji.
My purpose for going to the Imperial city this time is both for state affairs
and to discuss my marriage matters with him.
Although he and I are thousand of miles apart,
we would exchange letters through swan geese these past years.
This yearning has never lessened all these years.
I also have decided to not marry anyone except him in this lifetime.
He also said that he will never marry anyone except me.
Since he's such a faithful man,
you will surely get better
and then get reunited with him.
I treated so many people.
I know this illness very well. I fear that...
Miss, you will surely get better!
Even if I'm able to survive it,
we mustn't cause any delay on the official matters.
Qiaoling, go get my badge.
Miss.
Hurry up.
This—
This is the Purple Phoenix Badge that can represent my status.
I beg you to go to Megrez Imperial City using my name.
Go see Crown Prince Wuji and Lord Emperor for me.
- You... want me to disguise as you?
- Right.
This... We mustn't do this.
I can't disguise as you.
- I beg you.
- Miss...
Older Sis Fuyao, I really can't understand it.
Why did that Older Sister Folian want you to disguise as her?
She said that the Megrez Imperial City is currently facing a huge crisis.
She is also a representative of Plough Nation.
The Megrez Imperial City called for envoys from different nations to discuss this matter.
If she didn't go there on time, the Megrez Imperial City will surely blame Plough for it.
Her engagement with Crown Prince Wuji might also get canceled.
But is it really right to do this?
What's wrong about it?
We are not going there to harm anyone.
We just need to explain it clearly once we see the emperor.
Maybe, we can even clear Zhan Beiye's name in passing.
Isn't that good?
Hope so.
- Let's go.
- Let's go!
Let's go.
Older Sis Fuyao. Older Sis Fuyao, I can't believe that I'm inside the Imperial City!
After we left Mt. Mystic Soul, we went to Deep Water.
And now, we're actually in Megrez!
If you don't go out to travel the world, you really won't realize how huge it is!
Indeed.
Maybe, this will be lead to another adventure!
Megrez Imperial Palace...
It's really... so imposing.
It's really better to see it than just hearing of it.
Look. There are so many people over there. Let's go there.
I beg you...
- I beg you...
- Thanks...
- So pitiful.
- I just want to cure my younger brother's illness.
- This uncle, what's happening here?
- Please spare me.
- I won't do it again.
- It's all because of the noxious illness.
This miss and her younger brother rely on each other for survival.
Who would have known that when her younger brother went out to find work a few days ago,
he was found to be sick with the epidemic disease upon returning.
This miss heard that the leaves of the winged tree in Mt. Herding Spirit can cure this illness,
so she secretly went there to pick some.
But the winged tree is the symbol of the royal family.
It's not something that a commoner can casually pick.
Who did that?
Several men bullying one woman, don't you find that embarrassing?
Who are you?
Don't bother asking who I am. I can't stand men like you.
Move aside! Move aside!
Oh, it's a heroine.
Attack.
Kill her!
Stop!
Greetings, Prince Virtue.
Greetings, Royal Uncle.
First Royal Son, pick up your belt first.
Don't embarrass yourself in front of the saintess of the Five Regions.
You must be careful of a very important item like that.
Royal Uncle, you're saying that she's... ?
If she's not from the royal family of Plough,
who would have a Purple Phoenix Badge like this?
I was disrespectful...
So, you're the First Royal Son.
Sorry for offending you earlier.
But can I ask First Royal Son to let this miss go?
She went to pick the leaves for her family.
Since Megrez is the Imperial City of the Five Regions,
the more you should empathize with the citizens.
Saintess must have misunderstood things.
First Royal Son was also just worried that the epidemic might spread to the citizens here.
Hence, he's making intensive investigations.
As for these leaves of the winged tree,
the palace has planned to distribute them to the citizens and refugees.
I happen to have brought some today.
First Royal Son...
His Highness Crown Prince will be back in the city soon.
Lord Emperor also hopes that his citizens will be healthy.
Immediately practice good deeds for His Majesty.
Thank you, First Royal Son! Thank you, First Royal Son!
Good! Good!
- Thank you, saviors.
- You're welcome.
Quickly take these leaves home.
- Thank you, saviors.
- Go back now.
Saintess indeed has a heart of Bodhisattva.
You are so benevolent.
I thank you two on behalf of the citizens.
I already knew that the Princess of Plough would be coming to Megrez.
I've made the preparations. Why don't we—
No need to make such troubles.
I'll take my leave.
Where are we going?
I don't know.
[Wuba City Gather]
Isn't that the peculiar shop in Deep Water?
- That's right. This is also—
- Indeed.
Our Wuba City Gather is distributed all over Five Regions.
Our branches can be found everywhere.
We especially provide convenience for the citizens of different areas.
Good timing. We've just arrived in Megrez Imperial City today.
We happen to be looking for an inn to settle down.
Do you have any suggestion?
Wait a minute. Let me check.
[A miss carrying a Purple Phoenix Badge is a special guest from the royal family of Plough...]
Miss, are you a special guest from Plough?
Do you also know that?
I already knew that Miss would come.
A few days ago, someone came here and reserved the most unique courtyard in Megrez.
He said that it's for an important guest from Plough.
He even reserved a carriage.
- Who made the reservations?
- Who else?
You are First Royal Son's important guest.
Of course, it was he who made the reservations.
No need...
No... this...
This First Royal Son is something.
He really knows to set the helm according to the wind.
One who is unaccountably solicitous is hiding evil intentions.
- We mustn't accept such favors.
- Right.
But what should we do now?
He already bribed the whole street. How are we going to continue?
We will find a way.
Hateful doctor?
What? You lost them?!
She didn't stay in the hotels or inns that we'd arranged beforehand.
Useless. You are all useless!
Your Highness, what should we do now?
What did I tell you before?
I must be informed immediately once the Saintess Folian enters the city.
She's the second princess of Plough Nation.
The silver and gold mountains are all in their Plough.
If I'm able to get the support of Plough,
will I still fear not getting the Crown Prince position?
Look at these great things that you all have done.
She is already inside the city, but you all didn't even know.
Good!
I completely offended her now.
Useless! You all are useless!
Your Highness, I know now.
I'll go ask around for her whereabouts now, so it will be convenient for you to approach her.
Quickly go!
That chicken was not bad.
- Hateful doctor.
- Medical Sage Zong.
- Had enough wine and food?
- Yes.
Let's discuss the bill then.
12 jars of Single Joy wine, 40 liang each jar, at a total of 480 liang.
Four orders of deer ears in soy sauce and green jade cakes from Flower Filled Restaurant, a total of 120 liang.
No...
Also, 8 little plates of precious fruits with immortal dew—
Medical Sage Zong,
are you some unscrupulous businessman?
- Didn't we just eat some food?
- That's right.
- Don't we have a friendly relationship?
- Good friends.
That wasn't a normal kind of eating.
You—
Tell us how we should settle this then.
Anyway, we don't have any money, but we have our lives.
Let's do this then.
Sign a contract of selling yourself to me.
What? What are you trying to do?
What are you planning?
I'm just lacking some subordinates here in Megrez and will reluctantly take you two in.
You're telling me to become an underling?
If Medical Sage Zong is willing to take us in, we'll have a place to stay in.
- Let me think about it.
- Right.
Hey! I'm done thinking!
Isn't being an underling just doing labor?
It's fine.
We at least get to have free lodging and food, right?
There is meat for three meals, right?
- A room with a huge bed.
- Work for one day and rest for five days.
- That works.
- Passable, right?
- No problem.
Go and get these medicines.
The last two medicines can only be found in Upper Yang Palace at the city's southern side.
(T/N: Yang- a positive force against yin.)
Remember, not one less.
Okay.
This... There are so many people guarding. How are we going to get in?
[Upper Yang Palace]
It looks like we can't enter this Upper Yang Palace through the main entrance.
How are we going to enter it then?
Just follow this prescription and gather the other medicines.
Leave this place to me.
No... I can't leave you to do this alone.
No way.
- No, it's too dangerous for you to go alone.
- I can do it. Just go.
Fine. Be careful. Don't get caught. Okay?
Be careful.
This tune... sounds so familiar.
Your Highness, Saintess Folian has entered the Imperial City.
It's just that presently, no one knows where she settled in.
Got it.
Don't let anyone disturb me.
Yes.
You liar!
You finally came to find me.
Have you been well?
Give me back my item.
Let go of me!
Let go!
How did you know that I've been thinking about you day and night?
I never stopped.
You are a liar.
Anything you say is a lie anyway.
I still don't know who you truly are.
I don't want to talk anymore.
Just give me back my item.
- You—
- Where's my mystic spirit leaf?
Wait.
I haven't seen you for so long.
Do you have anything you want to say to me?
What do I have to say to you?
You speak no truth anyway.
I'm sure you also have no good intentions in being here, right?
I didn't tell you this, but I am the Crown Prince of Megrez.
You are the Crown Prince? You—
His aide. I'm Yuan Zhaoxu.
- You are the Crown Prince's aide?
- Yes.
You must be lying, right?
If it's true, then take me to see the Crown Prince.
Why?
In coming here to Megrez Imperial City, there were a lot of people on the way that're saying
the Crown Prince Wuji of Megrez excels in wisdom, is highly intelligent, and is matchless in the world.
How can there be such a person who really exists in this world?
There is.
What I did in Deep Water before was an order from the Crown Prince.
It shows that Crown Prince isn't some good person, either.
Let me tell you. Do not talk badly about the Crown Prince in Megrez
or you will have bad luck.
Okay already. Stop being angry with me.
As apology, I'll take you to a fun place.
Why don't you take me to the Royal Palace?
Why do you want to go there?
I can't tell you that.
Then be good and listen to me first.
Selling steaming bun.
What bad scheme are you brewing?
How did you feel when you saw me again?
If not because I can't beat you, I would have attacked you long time ago.
Fine then.
I surely won't fight back this time.
Liar, nothing you say is ever true.
I will never believe you again.
Why did you bring me here?
It must be because you're a frequent guest in this brothel.
Are you jealous?
You wish.
I've drunk a lot.
Am I also drinking?
Why did you steal my five-colored stone?
Isn't it to let you find me?
You're a great liar!
I won't talk to you anymore. Great liar...
- Liar.
- Hey...
Let me tell you. You are not allowed to...
leave again next time without saying anything.
Do you hear me?
I promise you.
- You liar!
- I—
Enough.
Prince.
Royal Uncle.
Enough.
Leave.
Yes.
Royal Uncle, Crown Prince left for so many years.
Emperor Father's health is also weak.
For most of the court affairs,
it's you and me who has handled them.
Now, we're being asked to just hand them to that guy.
Royal Uncle, are you able to put them down?
First Royal Son has achieved numerous military merits and has such illustrious prestige in the imperial court.
Not being happy with suddenly handing over your power is expected.
Am I not asking about your feelings, Royal Uncle?
I didn't catch what you said.
Okay.
I won't beat around the bush then.
Because a person suddenly appeared,
I'm now being asked to hand over the affairs that I've been managing for so many years.
Royal Uncle, I really couldn't accept it.
If there comes a day that this matter won't be ending well,
I hope that Royal Uncle will stand on my side.
I surely will not treat you unfairly.
You shouldn't tell me about your complaints.
I don't meddle with state affairs anymore.
Even if you tell me, I will just treat it as if I never heard anything.
Royal Uncle, could it be that you've forgotten that matter in the hunting grounds back then?
Royal Uncle, forgive me for wearing my heart on my sleeve.
But you do know that Wuji has always disliked you.
If he became the emperor, do you think he'll be able to accommodate you?
Look. I didn't know that you were coming.
This... I didn't prepare any good tea.
It's really such poor service.
How about I return to my manor and get some good tea?
I can't let Prince Assist suffer, right?
Jeez, Royal Uncle, I won't trouble you now.
I'm done talking.
I'll take my leave.
The person who is unable to tolerate my existence isn't Wuji.
It's him.
Since His Highness Crown Prince didn't return to court as scheduled,
I fear that we must still let Prince Assist approve the matters for today.
I fear this... is inappropriate.
Everyone knows that when His Highness Prince Assist led his army to South Wilderness,
he already promised the whole army
that he would reward them based on their merits when they victoriously returned.
Now, the army has returned to the city for several days.
The military inspection officer has also submitted a request to rush it twice.
We kept delaying it until the Crown Prince returned, so he can personally make the appropriations.
We mustn't delay this matter anymore.
Be that as it may,
but the commanding officer for this expedition was His Highness Zhangsun Pingrong.
If we allow His Highness to personally sign the rewards,
won't that easily invite suspicion?
Defeating the enemy is a meritorious contribution and should be rewarded.
This is just proper and right.
How could that invite suspicions?
But if this matter continued to be delayed,
the more we won't be able to control other people's suspicious mouths.
My army bathed in blood on the battlefield.
They used their lives to exchange for a temporary halt from South Wilderness.
They deserve to have these rewards.
If Crown Prince is against it, let him talk to Lord Emperor.
- You've heard all of it?
- Yes.
The whole city is looking for you,
while you are instead with a beautiful woman.
You didn't delay being romantic at all.
Emperor Father, so you have known everything.
I instead want to listen more to your explanation.
Emperor Father, you are wise.
You clearly knew that today was the day that the inner court would approve the funding for Pingrong's army;
a good day to win people's hearts.
But you instead deliberately moved away and let PIngrong be this good man.
Why?
♪ We played together when we were young
♪ We talked merrily as much as we liked
♪ You made a pledge seriously
♪ I don't know why you broke your pledge to me
Is the song Prince Virtue is singing "Water Yu Tune?"
I didn't know that Empress was here.
I was disrespectful.
"Water Yu Tune" sings about a man gone to visit his childhood sweetheart in their declining years
and they reminisce about the days they were together in their childhood.
Singing an old tune like that by yourself,
it does make it gloomier.
Wuji is back.
I know.
Pingrong is a petty person.
I fear that he can't accept others to steal the limelight from him.
But Wuji is after all my biological son.
If Prince Virtue cares, then try to teach him more.
Crown Prince is an especially gifted leader.
Him inheriting the throne is what everyone wishes.
I'm not that great.
I'm willing to render him my services.
I thank you on behalf of Wuji.
I still have things to do in my manor.
I'll take my leave now.
Prince Virtue, you're not in your declining years yet.
It's better to sing less of "Water Yu Tune."
Oldest brother made a meritorious deed by leading his army.
It's most suitable for him to be the one to reward the army.
Is it because you don't want to steal this job from him
or you're unwilling to get involved in this muddled water?
Or that you felt this army as being trusted aides that Pingrong trained himself,
so you're unwilling to use them in the future?
All are correct.
It's good that you have your own stand.
Tell me about the incidents in Deep Water.
Emperor Father asked me to weaken Deep Water with the least cost and the most covert method.
I'm sure that Emperor Father already knows that I used some tricks to become the King of Deep Water.
Now that a big war in Deep Water has just ended, their threatening strength has diminished,
they surely must rest for some time.
Good.
Very good.
You trained in the Firmament for ten years.
Now, without spending one soldier, you were able to weaken a vassal nation.
It's time to share the burden of governing the world with me.
Yes.
Your Majesty, Her Highness Empress especially set up a family dinner.
She's inviting Your Majesty and Crown Prince to go there.
Emperor Father, you think—
Crown Prince will soon be there.
I'm already old and my strength is diminishing.
I let the important ministers handle the important state affairs.
Among all, Pingrong and Prince Virtue also shared a few of the burdens.
Although you're the crown prince,
you don't have much foundation within the Imperial court.
Do you know that... regardless of which nation or empire...
the fight for royal power has always been a life-or-death struggle?
Child,
you are still young. Always be vigilant.
Emperor Father, take care of your health.
Just let me do the rest.
Go now.
Yes.
Doctor,
you're saying that this Yuan Zhaoxu has been with Crown Prince Wuji since he was little, right?
Yes.
- Then he... is 25 to 26 years old?
- Yes.
- Doctor.
Will you die if you talk more?
Do you want to hear about Crown Prince Wuji or Yuan Zhaoxu?
Your Highness Crown Prince.
"Hard-to-Get Love" by Lala Hsu
♫ What do you know? ♫
♫ What are good about the three realms? ♫
♫ If there're no three poisons, if there're no worries ♫
♫ How can it make me reluctant to leave? ♫
♫ Worry for love, beg for hate ♫
♫ And even discard my soul for affection ♫
♫ The one, who asks me to love him, loves me ♫
♫ I only want him to love me ♫
♫ What do you use to exchange for this hard-to-get love? ♫
♫ If there's no sickness or weakness, if there's never oldness ♫
♫ How can it make a spark to chase after stars alone? ♫
♫ Slim down for him, stay for my heart ♫
♫ And even chase away all luck for dreams ♫
♫ It wants me to be so pretty that I seize his soul ♫
♫ And continue dazzling in his heart ♫
♫ There is a saying that what a person asks for the lifetime ♫
♫ Is no more than staying together with one's lover by any means ♫
♫ If one can't obtain what one asks for ♫
♫ One is filled with anxiety and with knitted brows ♫
♫ There is a saying that if a person asks for the next lifetime ♫
♫ One should only ask to know everything about warfare ♫
♫ Dreams beg heart to grant me love ♫
♫ And have someone's company for the rest of my life ♫
♫ Have someone's company♫
♫ There is a saying that what a person asks for the lifetime ♫
♫ Is no more than staying together with one's lover by any means ♫
♫ If one can't obtain what one asks for ♫
♫ One is filled with anxiety and with knitted brows ♫
♫ There is a saying that if a person asks for the next lifetime ♫
♫ One should only ask to know everything about warfare ♫
♫ Dreams beg heart to grant me love ♫
♫ And have someone's company for the rest of my life ♫