"Fuyao" by Karen Mok
♫ I start to dance nimbly and gracefully ♫
♫ For what my beautiful face is frowned? ♫
♫ Without him, I'll drift with the current ♫
♫ Why is the tune of the zither a farewell song? ♫
♫ Without me, he'll be lonely in this universe ♫
♫ My heart silently waits at the cliff of Firmament ♫
♫ The heaven, the earth, the sun and the moon are all in my bosom ♫
♫ How can I own the top freedom in this world? ♫
♫ There is no fear from my heart ♫
♫ Deep love won't hide ♫
♫ True love won't run short ♫
♫ Dreams give hopes through all the ages ♫
♫ Why go through storms and stress to be bright and beautiful? ♫
♫ There is no struggle from my heart ♫
♫ Swaying along with the wind ♫
♫ I can do anything freely ♫
♫ I enter my dreams easily and unrestrainedly ♫
♫ What a beautiful dance ♫
[Legend of Fuyao]
~ Episode 60 ~
With the dignity of being the Empress, I beg you.
Empress, you must not!
Promise me, okay?
After all... After all, this will be Wuji's choice.
I can't hinder him making his choice.
Even if his choice is wrong?
Even if his choice is wrong!
I think that Wuji knows more than you and I that
there are a lot of things in this world that you can't judge based on right or wrong,
but only via pros and cons.
Hence, I can't interfere with his decision.
Sorry.
But do you know that there are some things that are destined to be wrong once you do it?
For this matter, he can't do wrong.
Empress, what's right or wrong has always been decided by you people.
You've been making the decisions for him.
Molding him according to the direction that you want.
Never asking him if he felt any pain, if he was willing.
Wuji is the most clear-headed and most responsible person that I know.
Every decision that he makes must be based on his own reasons.
Hence... Hence, I won't interfere with his decision.
But do you know that only on this matter,
he really can't commit a mistake?
What really is the reason?
Because...
Empress,
even if Wuji will indeed commit a mistake, I will bear the consequences with him.
What he needs isn't a strategist but a companion.
Hence... sorry.
Fuyao!
When did you come?
Enough for me to hear all of it.
Thank you for understanding me.
Go and see your Empress Mother.
- I'll wait for you here.
- Yes.
Empress Mother.
Ji'er...
You've gotten thinner.
No.
You're the one who has gotten thinner.
Emperor Father said that you've been praying in the temple for me these past days.
I've let Empress Mother worry.
I am unfilial.
Quickly rise, my child.
It's just right for a mother to worry about her son.
Have you been well in this journey?
I'm very well.
When they said... that you'd died in the desert,
I didn't believe it.
In this life, in this deep palace,
only you are my only worry.
If you're gone,
what's still the meaning of the long years I've endured here in this palace?
For letting Empress Mother worry,
I deserve to be punished with death.
Ji'er,
you will probably be staying a bit longer in the palace this time, right?
There is a lot that has happened in the imperial court.
I temporarily can't fulfill my filial duties by your side.
Is this about Prince Virtue inciting a rebellion?
- Your Emperor Father wants—
- All these are court matters.
Empress Mother shouldn't get overly worried about it.
What if I beg you? I beg you don't—
Empress Mother!
There are some things that shouldn't and need not be mentioned.
I know how to properly handle it.
May Empress Mother understand.
- But—
- No buts.
I always keep in mind my position as the crown prince and place the nation first.
May Empress Mother not worry.
No one can waver my determination of punishing the rebels.
It's already late.
May Empress Mother rest early.
I'll take my leave.
No. Wuji!
If I tell you...
that he is...
- your—
- Greetings, Your Ladyship Empress!
His Majesty said that Your Ladyship will surely be very happy in reuniting with Crown Prince after a long time.
However, this kind of emotional fluctuation might harm your health.
He especially ordered me to deliver a calming soup.
Empress Mother, take care of your body.
I'll take my leave.
No!
Bodhisattva!
Is it because I committed too many sins?
I beg you, Bodhisattva.
Don't let my Ji'er go to war.
No.
I've let Prince Assist wait for too long.
Come, drink some tea to cool down.
Just for this tea, I've painstakingly waited for two hours.
I've been in my tent discussing some important military matters.
Those are all grand matters that concern life and death.
I can't disregard it.
I risked my life and brought 80,000 elite men to reinforce Royal Uncle,
but you instead deliberately neglected me
and embarrassed me in front the whole army.
By doing that,
aren't you afraid that I'll withdraw my army and put you in a difficult spot?
Don't forget.
You now have no retreat path.
Prince Assist, you've said it too seriously.
At present, there are so many people without a retreat path.
I fear that you are one of them.
You!
It's not my intention to belittle the people that you've brought.
It's just that we haven't started the war yet,
but only 60,000 men are left from your 80,000 army.
The change in number is really too great.
Since that's the case, why don't you just tie me up?
Use me to force the Imperial City to withdraw their army.
That is indeed a good strategy if we've reached the end of the rope.
You!
It's just that you've also lost the value of being a hostage now.
You devised many means to kill Wuji
and even harmed the person he wanted to protect.
Do you think that Wuji will withdraw his army just to save you?
As for that emperor of ours, I fear that what he cares about is only himself.
Do you think that the person Wuji hates is only me?
I fear that the person he hates the most is you.
Don't think that you're able to hide your affair with the mistress of Pure Mist Palace Hall so perfectly.
Let me tell you too that in the palace, there isn't a wall where gossip couldn't pass through.
I'm just reminding Royal Uncle...
to not be fainthearted and hesitate.
Since I've decided to rebel, there then won't be any room to be fainthearted.
Yes.
I indeed rebel because of that person in Pure Mist Palace Hall.
But if one day, I really have to face Crown Prince in the battlefield,
I will surely not be lenient, either.
You make it sound so pleasant.
But if you really kill her son,
aren't you afraid that she'll hate you forever?
Let her hate me then.
As long as she's by my side,
she'll eventually forget it.
In this world, it's impossible to have everything both ways.
In between you dying and I living,
there has always been just one choice.
Okay!
If Royal Uncle can really do what you said,
I'm willing to be at your beck and call.
Sure.
It's good that Prince Assist can be a sensible person.
Then regarding our initial arrangement in the palace,
it's time for them to make their move.
Your Majesty, your medicine is here.
Did they go there already?
Your Majesty, everything has been prepared.
Okay.
Your Ladyship Empress, please come with us.
Was it he who told you people to fetch me?
How dare you!
You were not sent by him.
Capture the assassins!
Let's go.
Stop!
Let them leave.
I find this matter strange.
Are you talking about Prince Virtue's rebellion?
These past years, Prince Virtue has been careful and cautious.
He was able to handle internal and external affairs appropriately without any notable lapses.
For a person like that, if he doesn't have full confidence that he'll win, how could he suddenly rebel?
Why then, at this time, did he set up camp on the north bank of the river and isn't making any move?
Your Highness, I heard that assassins have appeared in the palace.
I just don't know the exact situation yet.
- Go and investigate it.
- Yes.
Your Highness! Your Highness!
- Your Highness!
-Talk.
Empress is missing.
- What?
- For these past days,
Empress Kindness has always been in front of Buddha's statue praying to the ancestors to bless the Five Regions.
But just earlier, some assassins trespassed into the palace and then she went missing.
Could it be that the assassins abducted the Empress?
I'll go look.
Grand Teacher... please...
give me...
some...
some more time.
Time? There's no more time.
You are not wearing down my patience,
but are wearing down the fate of the whole world!
Megrez is currently in a crisis.
I can't hide in here.
If you keep hesitating and delaying it like this,
you will become the traitor who brought disaster to the Five Regions.
Just for one's selfish reasons, you messed up world order and treated human lives as mere trifle.
What's your difference with the Zhangsun Jia of Megrez?
Grand Teacher...
I beg you to give me some more time.
After placating the situation in Megrez,
I...
will return to accept my punishment.
Mister—
What's going on exactly?
I've never seen Mister this weak.
- How about I go to Plough now to invite Mr. Zong over?
- Don't panic first.
I've used my internal energy to treat him.
I just couldn't tell if it's an injury or poison.
We encountered this once while in Plough, but he wouldn't say a thing.
Then... what about Mr. Zong?
He was in Plough at that time, too.
He indeed knows more than I do, but he couldn't do anything.
What about Empress Yuan?
How many assassins were there?
They said that there were two groups.
- They probably acted separately but in sync with each other to cause a distraction.
- Two groups of men...
Well-trained and knowledgeable of the topography.
They were able to abduct Empress Yuan with accurate timing.
It means that they are from this palace.
Who could it be?
This... I also dare not make rash conclusions.
But—
Prince Virtue.
That is also what I think.
I got news from outside that the assassins went northward after leaving the palace and left the city very quickly.
They probably are heading to the rebel army garrison on the north bank of the river.
I fear that they will be using Empress as a hostage and blackmail Crown Prince to surrender without fighting.
- Mister, you must not!
- Get out of the way.
Mister! Mister! You must not.
If you leave the Imperial City, that's falling into their trap.
You clearly know that Prince Virtue's main target is you.
Why must you go along with his plan?
Are you really trying to be my enemy?
I've served the Upper Yang Palace for more than twenty years.
I always remember the words you told me.
One can do things that are deemed impossible,
but one mustn't do things rashly, disregarding the general situation, Mister!
You going into their trap alone is a thing that mustn't be done!
- I have to stop you!
- You!
Moreover, Prince Virtue's... Prince Virtue's target is you only!
He wouldn't really harm Empress Yuan and Miss Fuyao, Mister.
Your Highness Crown Prince.
Your Highness Crown Prince, His Majesty urgently asks to see you.
Emperor Father.
You're here.
Wuji,
I expected that Zhangsun Jia would rebel.
I also expected Pingrong would sail with the wind.
But I never expected that they would do something to your Empress Mother.
Wuji, has the army you mobilized arrived?
Probably by tonight or tomorrow morning.
Do you have any confidence that you'll win?
I've really now become alone.
Each one betraying and leaving me.
In the whole Five Regions, you're the only one left that I can trust.
Good thing, you're here.
Even if I... leave this world now,
I, at least, have a son that will send me off.
Emperor Father.
I can only trust you.
That year, at the hunting grounds,
Zhangsun Jia almost killed you with his arrow.
Only now do I understand that it might be destined
that only one can live between the two of you.
Life and death are fated,
but Emperor Father, don't worry.
My life will not end here.
I am old.
I can't even hold a sword.
Hold it well.
Set out for battle.
Kill Zhangsun Jia on my behalf.
Emperor Father, rebels and traitors should be executed.
I will not refuse such a duty.
It's just that—
What you're worrying about is your Empress Mother, am I right?
Sit down.
Wuji, so many years have passed.
There are indeed some matters
that there is no harm to let you know.
The Prince Virtue then and your Empress Mother were indeed a perfect couple that everyone envied.
That time, even though I loved your Empress Mother, too,
the two of them had mutual affection for each other.
I can't steal somebody's lover.
But if Empress Mother loves him,
why then did she?
That's right.
I also asked myself that back then.
Why then did she enter the palace?
I think it must be because... the status of being the Empress,
its reputation and might,
that is indeed being a mother figure of the world, being above everyone.
Who doesn't want to have it?
Just like that, she entered the palace.
She received a lot.
When a man obtains what he desires, he tends to desire more.
That time, I had to attend to state affairs day and night.
Maybe your Empress Mother feels that I've neglected her.
She bore discontentment.
Hence, she remembered the romantic times she had with Prince Virtue.
And the Prince Virtue at this time,
took advantage of your Empress Mother's little trust in him,
used her to secretly poison me.
Emperor Father.
Good thing.
I was fortunately saved.
But my health can't endure any more exhaustion.
And every day,
I can't attend the court and just stay here in this meditation chamber to cultivate inner energy pills
to resist the poisons that they've given me that are still inside my body.
Days then went by one by one just like that.
You then...
were in Firmament training and hadn't returned.
Pingrong, on the other hand, wasn't fit to bear any important responsibility.
Who then could I tell it to?
Thus, I could only pretend that I know nothing.
After telling you all this,
don't get mad at your Empress Mother.
She is after all a woman I loved.
After all, she gave birth and raised you.
You should also forgive the mistakes she committed.
But your Royal Uncle, Zhangsun Jia, I can't tolerate him.
You know what to do, right?
Emperor Father, don't worry.
I understand what I should do.
Remember my words.
This Zhangsun Jia is more adept in tactics than you can imagine.
You must be very careful when you meet him in battle.
But I don't care what price you have to pay, what means you must use, or how many casualties you may incur,
I only want you... to personally kill him.
You must promise me...
that you will personally kill him,
or else, I will not die in peace.
I... will obey your command.
Go now.
Emperor Father, take care.
Yi'er, you have suffered.
A'rong?
- Get out!
- Yes!
How come it's you, A'rong?
You still know that my name is A'rong?
Do you still remember... that I'm your wife?
My nickname...
only you can call it.
But now, you're not qualified to!
It's been so many years.
Have you been well?
I didn't die.
Tell me. Is that good or not?
I know that you hate me,
but the person I clearly rescued was—
You clearly rescued that bitch, am I right?
Are you very disappointed now?
A'Rong, you shouldn't be here.
- Yi'er, she—
- Don't mention her in front of me!
I won't tell you where she is
even if you kill me.
How could I kill you?
You are, after all, my wife.
Wife?
Have you really treated me as your wife?
No.
You never did.
From the start,
you were just faking your affection.
In your heart,
there was never a position for me!
From the start, I shouldn't have believed your lies.
I shouldn't have married you.
In your heart,
I'm just a replacement, a cover, a stupid woman that you can use anytime!
When I married you then,
I indeed had intentions to win over the support of Deep Water.
But even so, I never treated you unfairly.
The status and glory you deserved.
I... gave them all to you.
It was you who requested to leave.
I requested to leave?
Did you think that I took Lian'er with me and left
all just because I learned about your affair with that woman?
You don't know.
You don't really know what happened!
You don't know what happened to Lian'er!
You don't know how I survived that time!
What happened?
What really happened?
What's still the point of saying all these?
Yes, I forgot.
You once were the top fighter of Megrez.
Even if I spend so much effort these past years and learn as much magic as I can,
I will never be able to defeat you.
Yes, I'm an assassin.
I failed.
You decide on my punishment.
Fine.
Now is not the time to reminisce.
Just rest here.
Do you have any news about them?
I've meticulously asked around. There is indeed no news about Ms. Fuyao,
but the rebel army indeed abducted a woman.
Prince Virtue ordered that she be treated well.
They will never dare to neglect her. Maybe, it's Empress Kindness.
What's going on? I heard that you abducted the wrong person.
How could you commit such a huge blunder?
Leave now.
Xu Lai, you leave, too.
I have to ask you then.
All the palace spies were arranged by you.
Only you and I know about the whole plan.
How could they have abducted the wrong person?
Are you then suspecting me of covertly informing Emperor Father of our plans?
Isn't that it?
I've staked all my possessions and my life on you.
You're actually doubting me?
A smart gambler will never stake everything on one person.
What do you mean?
If you don't believe me, why then did you make an alliance with me?
What are you trying to do?
I really didn't leak any information!
At this point, it's already not important who leaked the news.
Now that we failed, we won't have another chance to enter the palace.
We can only attack.
If we win, I will still have a chance to save her.
If we lose, then don't bother discussing anything anymore.
Attack?
The 80,000 army of the Liu Family in Changhe are still on their way here.
We haven't finished stocking up our military provisions.
If you attack now, isn't that suicide?
I don't need to explain things to you.
Even if I don't attack, the army of Megrez is already on their way.
I won't force you to stay.
Just do as you please.
If I knew that you would commit suicide, why did I side with you?
Get out!
What do we do now?
I was so wrong about him.
He is a total lunatic!
He will surely lose this battle. We mustn't get involved in this mess.
What you mean then, is...?
Pack up our things and leave.
What is this place?
It's no use.
Don't waste your energy.
Empress. This?
This is the most important secret chamber of Megrez.
The ones binding our body
are also the Imprisonment Chains that are the hardest chains to be broken here in Megrez for hundreds of years.
Since he wanted to lock us in here,
he then was sure that we wouldn't be able to escape.
In here, even if you hurt your throat from shouting, no one will hear you.
Whether we live or die,
it's all according to his whim.
As long as he doesn't say it, then no one will ever know that we're here.
Prince Virtue looked like a person with high morals,
yet he actually is this despicable!
He even treated you like this.
Do you really not know who abducted you?
Do you not understand who is the true mastermind behind all this?
Prince Virtue.
Prince Virtue isn't his competition.
"Hard-to-Get Love" by Lala Hsu
♫ What do you know? ♫
♫ What are good about the three realms? ♫
♫ If there're no three poisons, if there're no worries ♫
♫ How can it make me reluctant to leave? ♫
♫ Worry for love, beg for hate ♫
♫ And even discard my soul for affection ♫
♫ The one, who asks me to love him, loves me ♫
♫ I only want him to love me ♫
♫ What do you use to exchange for this hard-to-get love? ♫
♫ If there's no sickness or weakness, if there's never oldness ♫
♫ How can it make a spark to chase after stars alone? ♫
♫ Slim down for him, stay for my heart ♫
♫ And even chase away all luck for dreams ♫
♫ It wants me to be so pretty that I seize his soul ♫
♫ And continue dazzling in his heart ♫
♫ There is a saying that what a person asks for the lifetime ♫
♫ Is no more than staying together with one's lover by any means ♫
♫ If one can't obtain what one asks for ♫
♫ One is filled with anxiety and with knitted brows ♫
♫ There is a saying that if a person asks for the next lifetime ♫
♫ One should only ask to know everything about warfare ♫
♫ Dreams beg heart to grant me love ♫
♫ And have someone's company for the rest of my life ♫
♫ Have someone's company♫
♫ There is a saying that what a person asks for the lifetime ♫
♫ Is no more than staying together with one's lover by any means ♫
♫ If one can't obtain what one asks for ♫
♫ One is filled with anxiety and with knitted brows ♫
♫ There is a saying that if a person asks for the next lifetime ♫
♫ One should only ask to know everything about warfare ♫
♫ Dreams beg heart to grant me love ♫
♫ And have someone's company for the rest of my life ♫