THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION.
ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES,
ORGANIZATIONS, RELIGIONS, AND INCIDENTS
IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
PROMOTION AND RECOGNITION CEREMONY
You all had to overcome
the fierce competition to be here.
We welcome you
to the Seoul Metropolitan Police Agency.
Please do your best to fully carry out
your responsibilities and duties
as civil servants
to ensure safety and happiness
of the people of Seoul.
Once again, I'd like to emphasize
the importance of being faithful
to your duty in your own positions.
"Award of Excellence, Officer Jeon Ho-gyu.
This award recognizes
that you completed the program
with the highest grades.
On March 12, 2016.
Park Yeong-jin, the Commissioner-General
of the Seoul Metropolitan Police Agency."
About face.
Present arms.
FRAMED
Tell us if there was anything notable.
Detective Jeon was already dead
when we got here.
-Over here.
-And Jo Tae-sik...
-Yes.
-He was right beside him.
So we were going to arrest Jo Tae-sik,
but he hit us and ran.
-Captain.
-Which way?
Captain.
-Yes.
-It's over here.
-Search this area.
-Yes, sir.
-What about over there?
-There was nothing.
-What about the gun?
-We haven't found it yet, sir.
-Where is Detective Kim?
-He's over there.
-How about the area behind the site?
-Not yet.
-Search that area too.
-Yes, sir.
We'll check over there.
Why are you both going there?
One's enough.
I'll go.
-Go check.
-Yes, sir.
-Hey, let's go together.
-Sure!
Please check over here.
I don't think we'll find anything here.
I'll look again, just in case.
Search thoroughly.
There has to be something. Focus, guys.
Yes, sir.
-Hey, Detective Seo!
-Yes, sir!
Yes, sir.
Isn't that one of ours?
-Check the serial number.
-Yes, sir.
Hey, KCSI!
Check the serial number.
Next news.
Detective Jo of
Seoul Metropolitan Police Agency's
Regional Investigation Unit who was
in charge of Jeong Sang-hun's case
shot and killed his colleague
nearby his residence
earlier this evening and fled.
-The police
-That can't be.
suspect that he committed such an offense
as a retaliation
for being suspended from work
due to forging an official document.
This is regarding
the murder of Corporal Jeon Ho-gyu
which took place around 10 p.m. yesterday.
For now, the most likely suspect
is Lieutenant Jo Tae-Sik
of the Regional Investigation Unit.
According to Internal Affairs,
Corporal Jeon was already dead
when they arrived at the scene.
Based on the gun found at the scene
and the text message Corporal Jeon sent
right before the murder took place--
A text message? What did it say?
He wrote that he was being threatened
by Detective Jo
and asked them to come to where he was.
So? Do we know Jo Tae-sik's whereabouts?
It seems like he fled
in the direction of the main street
through the woods behind the scene.
We're currently trying to find out
where he went from there.
I'd like you and RIU 3 to be in charge
of the investigation team.
And all other teams should support them
as much as they can.
Arrest him quickly,
or we'll be humiliated.
Arrest him as soon as possible.
Understood?
-Yes, sir.
You're dismissed.
Will you be all right?
You and Jo Tae-sik were close.
We were, but I'll be all right.
We should arrest him quickly
for his own sake.
All right.
I got all the security footage
from the cameras around the main street.
What else, sir?
Monitor everyone around Tae-sik
as well as their phones.
Yes, sir.
NAME: JO TAE-SIK
DATE OF BIRTH: AUGUST 20, 1984
Where's his car?
This is nuts. I can't find it anywhere.
Do you know of any place
where Detective Jo might be now?
What on earth happened?
Jeon Ho-gyu.
Ho-gyu.
What are you doing here?
Hey.
What the heck are you doing here?
Get up, okay?
Ho-gyu.
Hey.
Jeon Ho-gyu...
Why the hell are you here?
Ho-gyu.
Did you ask for me, sir?
POLICE PUT OUT APB FOR DETECTIVE
WHO SHOT AND KILLED A COLLEAGUE
Was this your doing?
You stopped him at the right time.
That detective, Jo Tae-sik, doesn't know
how scary this world can be.
He doesn't know how scary people are.
It's been ages
since I last saw the likes of him.
And I must say,
it's quite amusing to watch him.
I'm intrigued to find out
how far he'll go.
But the thing is,
there's a right time for everything.
Right now,
I'm not in the mood to play with him.
That's what matters.
This will teach him
that he should stop snooping around.
But we never know,
so you need to take care of him perfectly.
I don't want to see him
making trouble around Seo-hui
ever again.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
Hong Min-guk is meeting
the leader of the opposition party
at a Japanese restaurant at 7 p.m.
You should call him before they meet.
I heard Mr. In had a one-on-one meeting
with Chairman Jeong.
Who could it be?
I don't think Detective Jo Tae-sik did it.
Do you think he's being framed?
Please find out more
about this case.
So what's going on with that girl?
Come on. Why are you even asking?
It's obvious.
Goodness.
Tae-sik, where are you?
Why aren't you picking up?
Are your fingers broken or what?
Tae-sik.
You're alive, right?
Hey, Jo Tae-sik.
Are you all right?
Say something, please.
-Shall I ask her?
-Yes, ask her.
-For real?
-Yes, do it.
Hey, Sergeant Kang.
Is it really true?
The murder case on the news.
Is it really about your previous team?
I guess it is true.
How could he do such a thing?
I can't believe he killed his teammate...
Captain.
Yes, what's up?
May I go on patrol?
Sure, go ahead.
All right, be safe. See you later.
Hey, Jin-gyeong!
Captain.
You haven't heard anything
from Tae-sik, have you?
No.
What about you?
Up until a week ago,
I thought that we were doing well
and that things
were going great.
Even after the team's disbandment
and Tae-sik getting suspended,
I kept thinking,
"It's okay. Things happen.
It's all right."
I kept telling myself that.
But now...
I mean, why...
I just can't believe it.
You know him better
than anybody else does.
Why on earth would Tae-sik kill Ho-gyu?
Something's gone awfully wrong.
He has no reason to kill Ho-gyu.
Ho-gyu
wrote a statement
during the internal investigation.
He wrote that Tae-sik forced him to do it.
That's what I heard.
Ho-gyu wrote that?
People are saying
that's probably why Tae-sik killed Ho-gyu.
But as you know,
Tae-sik is not that kind of guy.
So,
if you hear from him,
tell him to come out and clear his name
as soon as he can.
And before that,
make sure you call me first.
Sir, if we make concessions
to all of the three conditions,
we'll end up losing
tens of billions of won.
Why did you make such a decision?
Are we running a charity here or what?
How could you make such a compromise
without consulting any of us?
You should've at least gotten approval
from JQ Foundation
and the subsidiaries
that are investing in the business.
Excuse me.
It is my company.
Must I obtain your approval
prior to making every single decision?
Sir, you're not the sole owner of JQ.
But you and I both know
that it's not your company.
You're just the head of the foundation,
and I think I'm being more than generous
by letting you attend our board meeting.
You'd better not cross the line.
I think I've made myself clear
to all of you.
Do you have anything else to say?
Directors, when we launch the business
after the bill passes,
we'll get money from the government
and quickly recover from the loss.
I'll readjust the profit-sharing ratios
so that you're not affected by
the loss at all.
-Hello?
-It's me.
Detective Jo.
I can't talk long.
Would you
be able to come to where I am?
Yes, I'll meet you there. Hold on.
Tell me where you are.
Yes.
And...
I have to ask you a favor.
THE NATIONAL ASSEMBLY
OF THE REPUBLIC OF KOREA
You should just call it a day.
-Pardon?
-Mr. Kang
wants to speak with me about the bill.
I have to go and meet him now.
Now?
I think he's overwhelmed because
the Judiciary Committee
is around the corner.
-Where are you headed, ma'am?
-It's okay. It's getting late.
Don't worry. You should just go home.
But still...
PRECINCT STATION
Assemblywoman Kim, what brings you here?
Why don't you get in?
I'll give you a ride home.
No, it's okay. I can just take the bus.
Get in, quick.
Assemblywoman Kim, where are we now?
Detective Jo, are you there?
We're here.
I came with Detective Kang.
What the hell?
Where have you been?
You don't care about those
who have been worried about you.
How could you ditch me
and leave me all alone like that?
With both you and Ho-gyu gone,
do you know how scared I've been?
Tae-sik.
Ho-gyu...
I'm sorry.
Ho-gyu is...
Take care.
That arrogant prick.
He has no right.
He doesn't even do anything,
yet he's so greedy.
Please don't mind them, sir.
The directors are reacting like that
because they don't know
why JQ has to purchase the national land.
From now on, I'll handle
the board members' complaints
and just keep you updated, sir.
Dealing with the police
is keeping you busy enough
at the moment.
It's all because of those morons.
Both you and Mr. In have
so much work to do because of them.
No, sir.
It's my job.
Please don't worry.
All they have to do is
just sit back and keep quiet.
Now, tell us.
What the hell is happening?
I have no idea either.
When I got there, Ho-gyu was already...
Ho-gyu!
Hey.
Who is it? Who did this to you?
Who is it? Who?
Hey. Hey!
Hey! Ho-gyu!
Hey, Ho-gyu.
Ho-gyu.
Ho-gyu. Get yourself together!
Detective Jo Tae-sik!
-Here--
-Hands up.
And get up slowly.
-What are you guys doing?
-I'll repeat.
Put your hands up and get up slowly.
-What the hell are you doing?
-It's an order!
Hands up, and get up at once.
-This is--
-Hands up!
You got the wrong idea.
Someone called Internal Affairs
to the scene right at that time.
That way, they can get me arrested
without a hitch.
What about your gun?
Why didn't you return it on time?
Things got out of hand
because of that gun.
What do you mean? What gun?
I returned mine
after the disciplinary hearing...
What?
Then,
Are you saying that someone deliberately
placed your gun at the scene?
Someone tampered with the scene?
At the moment,
that is the only plausible explanation.
Everything was set up from the start.
But why?
Why would anyone go to such lengths?
To stop us.
Ho-gyu called me that day.
He had found something
and had to see me urgently.
What did he find?
What was it?
I don't know.
Ho-gyu
must've found something
on your laptop.
I took
your broken laptop
to his place
and asked him to fix it,
saying we should do something
to help Tae-sik
return to work.
I said that to him.
Had I not gone to his place that day,
he wouldn't have...
It's my fault
that Ho-gyu ended up like that.
Hey.
He died because of me.
Why is it your fault?
What do I do now?
It might be uncomfortable to stay here.
I'm not in a position to be picky.
I'm fine.
Please just comfort her on your way back.
Okay. I should leave now.
I'm sorry.
That you're going through all this.
Are you the criminal?
What?
It's the criminal
who should be sorry, not you.
I once felt the same way.
I was really upset and frustrated.
I feel really bad for Ho-gyu.
But if I quit just like this
and just give up without solving anything,
it will make Ho-gyu's death
come to nothing.
I'll take this to the end.
Now, this has
become my business.
SEOUL POLICE AGENCY
ARMORY, RESTRICTED AREA
Come here.
You really came here.
I told you not to step foot in here
for the time being.
Hey, you, of all people,
can't be in here now.
Because of your team,
the Seoul Police Agency
is in utter chaos now.
I just don't understand the whole thing.
What's so hard to understand?
Tae-sik...
Detective Jo Tae-sik
handed in all his guns.
The day he was suspended,
he came right here
and returned all his guns.
That's what he said.
Did you meet him?
Are you crazy?
How would I meet him?
I heard it before it happened.
You're so naive.
Do you trust him?
Who handed in what?
Jo Tae-sik didn't return his guns.
You sounded so convinced
that I just checked it again.
There's no record
in the management ledger.
It only says that he took them out.
Hey, are you serious?
Yes, I am. Are you done now?
You should go now.
-What if someone sees--
-What about the security cameras?
There are security cameras in there.
If he returned them, it must've been
recorded on the cameras.
If he didn't,
he wouldn't be in the footage.
Let me just check it.
If he's not in the footage,
I will never ask you
a favor like this again.
Hey.
About the security cameras...
This is why I told you not to come.
Actually that's why
things are so tense in here.
What do you mean?
All the security camera footage is gone.
There's no footage recorded
around that day.
I guess he tussled with someone a lot
before he died.
He got beaten up all over his body.
Darn it.
Whoever killed him shouldn't have at least
beaten him up.
Why would they hit him so hard
when they were going to kill him?
-I heard Detective Jo is a suspect.
-He can't be.
He's falsely accused.
You know him.
He's not the sort of person
who'd kill someone.
Detective Kang, I'm an autopsy doctor.
An autopsy doctor
only judges evidence from a body.
And I can't find anything from the body.
Not even the DNA of a suspect.
So I can't be sure
that Detective Jo isn't a suspect.
My gosh.
Doctor, is there anything else
you found out?
Is there any evidence
to prove that Tae-sik isn't the suspect?
-What is this?
-It's from the victim's nails.
-I don't see anything.
-It's a piece of fiber.
I'm not sure
if it's from clothes or shoes.
But this is all I could find
about the suspect.
Doctor, does that mean
we can catch the criminal with this?
Not a chance.
There's no sample to compare.
-A sample to compare?
-Yes.
About the accident. The hit-and-run
accident of Assemblywoman Kim.
The security cameras in the vicinity
were off at the moment of the accident.
Right at the moment of the accident.
-It's very strange.
-What if
someone deliberately deleted the footage?
Someone inside the police.
Right after it happened,
the investigation team came down
to check the management ledger
and the footage.
But the footage was all gone.
It has never happened before.
It is a little strange.
There's someone
inside the police?
I'm going to have dinner.
Make sure this place is well guarded.
-You can go to eat dinner in 30 minutes.
-Yes, sir.
What brings you all the way here?
I know you've been working hard.
But I didn't come to see you even once.
And I didn't even thank you properly.
Here. I opened an account in your name.
Once the bill is approved
and the project goes ahead,
you will have a lot more work to do.
Use it at your own discretion.
In a situation like now,
you even have the time
to take care of things like this.
I just don't understand it, Father.
What?
I've always thought
we were feeling the same way
about Sang-hun.
But now, you don't seem
to care about Sang-hun at all.
Seo-hui, how could you
say such a thing?
I thought about
when you started to change like this.
That's when Sang-hun's eye was
delivered to Bareun News.
I will ask you outright.
Stopping the investigation of Choe's case
and changing the investigation team.
Was that your doing?
Why did you do that?
What is it Choe Su-hyeon tried to do?
Why are you doing all this?
He said he'd be back in 30 minutes.
Are you right here?
Wait there.
I've run a business for a long time.
I can't say I've led
a flawless life the whole time.
But I at least didn't do
anything to be ashamed of.
I just needed
an investigation team who can focus
on Sang-hun's case.
There's no other reason.
Choe Su-hyeon clearly
had something to do with Sang-hun.
That's what I believe.
Apparently, you've been
influenced by Detective Jo.
So do you trust the cop
who killed his colleague
even more than me?
Detective Jo didn't do it.
Then why do you think he ran away?
They have definite evidence.
You can't tell what he's like
just by looking at him.
It's a good thing
that you trust people easily.
But you also need to be careful
with the people around you.
Then do you
really trust
Mr. In and Yeong-min?
Keeping someone close
because you need them
and keeping someone close because
you trust them are different things.
You're the only person I've ever trusted.
That's why I'm worried about you.
What on earth did he see?
THERE IS NO PAPER FOR PRINTING
Where did he go?
Damn it. He just took off
without changing the shifts?
That stupid jerk.
Damn it.
Hey.
I heard others often benefit
from their colleagues' help.
But what's wrong with my colleague?
She just drags me down.
Did you bring it?
Hey, let go of it.
Hands off.
Are you kidding me now?
Why did you bring something I can't see?
I didn't bring this to show you.
I just took it for my sake.
Let me make it clear, okay?
-All right.
-So you're saying
there's someone else
who shot your colleague that day.
-Not Detective Jo.
-Right.
So he switched the guns,
deleted the security camera footage,
and put the whole blame on your senior?
My gosh.
And it has to be one of the cops
who had a gun on the day of the murder.
Hey. Seriously, you'll be in big trouble
if you keep doing this.
You can't suspect an innocent person
-only with suspicion--
-Can't I suspect an innocent person?
Another innocent person just died.
It's not like I'm doing this
with great expectations.
If I don't do this,
I feel like I'll just go insane.
Just do me a favor.
So when was it again?
The 8th.
Gosh.
Gosh, don't be silly.
Say it.
Kim Pil-hun.
He checked out a gun on April 27.
He hasn't returned it yet.
Park Jin-su.
He checked it out on April 15.
Oh, no. He returned it already.
So it's not him.
And...
There's Yu Dae-yong.
He checked out a gun when he went to
Songju and hasn't returned it yet.
Hey.
Gosh.
YU DAE-YONG
JO TAE-SIK
What?
Do you belatedly have
a guilty conscience or what?
Are you crazy?
Now even Tae-sik?
You already finished one.
Getting rid of one more
won't make much difference.
How much...
How much more do you want me to do?
You already did this to Ho-gyu.
Isn't that enough for you?
How long are you going to drag me around?
Mr. Yu.
You seem to believe
that your life is stuck
in a mire because of me.
But think about it.
We met in the mire
in the first place.
It's been ten years already, right?
You threw yourself
into the mire.
And that's why I chose you.
Now you're whining that you can't do this,
but I know
you will do it when the time comes.
Since you started it,
you must end it yourself.
Before the whole world finds out
what kind of person you really are.
Jo Tae-sik is the last one.
I promise.
After that,
you and I will never
see each other again.
This means
Ho-gyu also got his hands on the list.
Who the heck are these people?
Captain.
How did you find me here?
Hey, Ho-gyu.
Tae-sik called me.
He said he would be late
and asked me to come here instead.
Do you have
the flash drive from Ms. Kim's laptop?
Give me that. I'll give it to him.
You will?
Ho-gyu.
When our team got disbanded like that,
I didn't feel good about it.
When I saw how you guys
didn't give up and kept trying,
I felt even worse.
I am here
to help you guys.
So just hand me over the flash drive.
I'll give it to him.
Wait.
How did you know
that I had the flash drive?
I didn't tell Detective Jo
that I had the flash drive.
Captain.
You're not here
because Detective Jo called you, right?
Was it you?
Were you the one
who hacked Ms. Kim's laptop
and deleted the security footage?
You were behind all that?
Hey, Ho-gyu.
It was you.
It was odd the security cameras
didn't work only around that time.
I doubt the hit-and-run driver had
enough time to destroy the evidence
before vanishing.
"The security camera footage
in the vicinity has been checked,
but nothing was recorded
due to the mechanical defect."
It was Captain Yu who closed this case?
You covered up Choe Su-hyeon's case
a long time ago just like this.
Hey, you're mistaken about that.
Then, tell me.
Didn't you delete the footage
and cover up Choe Su-hyeon's case
as a suicide?
Why did you do it?
Captain.
I thought we were a team.
Why did you do it? Why?
Hey, Ho-gyu.
In life,
some things happen
regardless of your intentions.
Now is one of those moments.
Just give me the flash drive quietly.
I'll explain everything later.
No. This isn't right.
Captain, I'm sorry.
Hey.
Let go.
-Wait.
-Hey. Let go.
Let go!
Ho-gyu! Damn it.
DETECTIVE JO TAE-SIK
Damn it.
You bastard.
You bastard!
Damn it.
Jerk. You jerk.
Jerk.
How could...
How...
Captain.
I'm really scared.
Please don't leave me.
Damn it.
Ho-gyu!
Hey.
Who did this to you?
Why...
Why!
Since you started it,
you must end it yourself.
Before the whole world finds out
what kind of person you really are.
Why...
It is as you expected, sir.
The two of them plotted it
and framed Detective Jo Tae-sik
for the crime.
Will you not take any action?
It seems to me
they did a nice job
of cleaning up the mess.
By any chance, if Detective Jo Tae-sik
does end up
taking the fall for the murder...
What would you do
if you were in his shoes?
I'm not sure.
I wouldn't want to just sit by
and be framed for something I didn't do.
I think I would hire an expensive lawyer.
Judging from his personality, I doubt
he would hire an expensive lawyer
to clear his name.
And I'm certain
that he would never stay quietly
in hiding and be on the run.
Keep a close eye on Seo-hui.
I can assure you
that those two will meet pretty soon.
GO YEON-U, GU JIN-JU
LEE SEO-YEON, LEE HA-EUN
Yes, this is the file I saw.
The file was
in Choe Su-hyeon's flash drive.
The list is longer than I expected.
There are more than 100 names.
Then, is this the list
-the late detective saw?
-Probably.
It makes me wonder what this list means.
Whatever it is, they were willing
to kill people to keep it hidden.
They caused a car accident
to take it away from you.
And seeing how they killed people
to keep this a secret,
I thought there must be
something hidden in this list.
Perhaps, this could mean...
What is it? Do you have a hunch?
Something is just bothering me.
Remember the families
we visited the other day?
They were on the list.
-Go Yeon-u and Gu Jin-ju.
-Yes.
Go Yeon-u had lung cancer.
And that girl, Gu Jin-ju,
has a hematologic malignancy.
-Yes.
-And when we visited this town,
there were a lot of shamanic rituals.
Remember?
-Yes.
-That's bothering me.
GO YEON-U, GU JIN-JU,
GI HAN-YEONG, KIM YUN-JU
I wonder if everyone on the list...
They all might be ill.
Is that what you're saying?
There were three people
who could have fired the gun that day.
KIM PIL-HUN
Kim Pil-hun was in Gangnam
at 9:14 p.m.
He's not the one.
At 9:34 p.m., Choe Hyeon-u
was at the Police Agency.
He stayed there throughout the night.
YU DAE-YONG
At 9:24 p.m., he was
in Bakmo-dong, Jongno-gu.
345-12, BAKMO-DONG, JONGNO-GU, SEOUL
Captain was really at the scene.
GO YEON-U, GU JIN-JU,
GI HAN-YEONG, KIM YUN-JU
SONGJU, HUI-DONG
YEONGIL-MYEON, BUHEUNG-MYEON
Here's my guess.
I think it's because of the land.
Are you talking about the land
for the new business?
There's no way
he would make such a demand
unless that's what he was going after.
What kind of demand did he make?
He said that he would comply
with all of our demands
under one condition.
Article 15.
He asked to protect the article
on the purchase of national land.
He doesn't want the other party
to go after the article
on the purchase of national land.
"Purchase of national land."
"National land..."
BUHEUNG-MYEON, HAGYE-MYEON,
YEONGIL-MYEON
All of them reside in...
ASSEMBLYWOMAN, KIM SEO-HUI
...Yeongil-myeon,
Buheung-myeon,
and Hagye-myeon.
So let's say that everyone
on this list is ill.
What do they have to do
with the new business?
She asked how long we'd been living here
and when my son had become ill.
Location.
Are the locations
of the patients relevant
to the new business?
Damn it. Why did you come here
at such a late hour?
Tae-sik.
Dae-yong.
He stood in our way
of reinvestigating Choe Su-hyeon's case.
-Who is it?
-And he killed Ho-gyu.
Who did this to you?
No. He forced me to take
Kim Seung-cheol's case
because I was going to leave soon.
That was why.
He didn't want me to find out anything.
It was Captain.
I checked that he made a call
around the scene that night
and that a gun was in his possession.
I checked everything.
It was our Captain
who killed Ho-gyu in cold blood.
YEONGIL-MYEON, BUHEUNG-MYEON
HAGYE-MYEON
SONGJU
It really is true.
YEONGIL-MYEON, SONGJU RMC
These sick people
are really living
on the land
where the new business will be set up.
LAND RESERVED
FOR NEW RENEWABLE ENERGY BUSINESS
2ND RESERVED LOT: HUI-DONG
1ST RESERVED LOT: BUHEUNG-MYEON
Soon,
it will be mine.
It will happen soon enough.
Dae-yong.
Why did you do it?
Ho-gyu.
Why did you kill him?
We have a problem.
Then, we only have one option.
We must make a suspect
who will be framed for your act.
Put Jo Tae-sik's gun at the scene.
What?
Switch my gun with Tae-sik's?
Shut up, and just do what I say
unless you want to be arrested for murder.
I'll clean this up.
Just do what I say.
ARMORY, RESTRICTED AREA
UNLOCKED
RECORD OF WEAPON AND AMMUNITION
LOGGED IN AND OUT
GUN, JO TAE-SIK, 3.8 PISTOL
3.8 PISTOL
Hey, Detective Seo!
Yes, sir!
Yes, sir.
Isn't that one of ours?
Check the serial number.
Yes, sir.
Hey, KCSI!
I know you were at the scene
when Ho-gyu died.
I also know that the record
of my gun is gone.
Was it you
who killed Ho-gyu
and framed me for the murder?
Me?
You didn't do it?
Tae-sik.
I understand that people make mistakes.
I understand that you acted
in the heat of the moment.
But,
you've gone too far.
Now, you can't undo this.
Turn yourself in.
What on earth are you talking about?
Dae-yong.
The secret is in this land.
SONGJU DAILY
The secret JQ is desperately
trying to hide.
If Dae-yong has been working
for JQ all this time,
there should be
some kind of a call record.
Find out whom he was talking to
on the phone
when Ho-gyo died.
These people are getting financial support
from here. Please tell me why.
I need the medical records
of the patients on this list.
The patient conspired with a hospital.
If this hospital doesn't cooperate,
it may look suspicious.
I worked so hard to get this.
I even broke the law.
It was because he found out
the real agenda of the new business.
They were trying to tell the public.
I dispatched my officers to find him.
Just be patient.
Let's hurry.
I clearly told you
that I will put an end to everything
if you just handle Jo Tae-sik.
Who's giving you orders?
Who the hell is behind you?
Why are you going this far?
You don't know
how frightening they can be.