[This is a work of fiction. Characters, places, agencies, events, groups, and settings are all fictional.]
Seahorses are quite romantic.
They're known for being monogamous until they die.
What's monogamous?
It's loving only one person your entire life.
Seon Ho, do you like the seahorse?
Just leave the documents on my desk, and you can go home.
Okay.
It's been a while.
- Yeah.
- Who is he?
An attorney...
I used to work with.
- Hello.
- Yes.
We'll look around. Take your time.
Seon Ho!
You shouldn't walk around alone like this.
Seon Ho, hurry up, lets go.
We'll be late for the dolphin show.
Dad, buy me a dolphin.
He asked for a dolphin.
We can't buy you one.
Dad.
Dad, are you also monogamous?
Huh?
Will you only love one person for the rest of your life like a seahorse?
Seon Ho, you remember everything you learned at the aquarium? Huh?
Who do you take after that you're this smart?
Yes. Sure.
Are babies monogamous, too?
Huh?
Will you love only one baby for the rest of your life, too?
Of course.
He'll only love our Seon Ho for the rest of his life.
That's enough, seriously!
I'll never break up with you!
I won't take another step until you forgive me.
This is humiliating! Why are you doing this?
I don't want to!
Just forgive me this once.
She should just accept him, gosh.
[Messages from Chae Yeon, Oh Yoon Ah, Park Joo Yeon, Park Moon Jin]
Half of the world is women.
Why's he going that far?
You're too much, Jin Seon Ho. He was just dumped.
He's like a beggar.
Begging for a love that's not possible.
[Cheer Up - Episode 8]
Why?
What is it?
Break time is over.
We need to practice.
I'll be right there.
Stop looking at him.
Can't you look at me instead?
What?
I keep stumbling, so
take a look at my routine.
Oh, I thought
you were confessing.
As if.
If I do and it goes wrong, then it's the end.
Hyung!
What is this?
Is this really you?
All the incidents that occurred within the past year,
[TheiaTV]
I couldn't just sit back and watch them turn into accidents,
so I requested a police investigation.
I also plan to provide this item as evidence.
Why do you keep stirring things up, Hyung?
Let's talk later.
What's more urgent than this?
Because of you, I–
Never mind.
Good job.
I mean, what–
Mom, why am I so immature?
Hey, either eat or speak. Can't you just stick to one?
Why am I so immature?
What are you suddenly going on about?
This isn't the time for me to worry about this.
I don't have time, I don't have money,
but I try to do everything everyone else does.
Immature. You're immature, Do Hae Yi.
Hey!
People who have a lot of money and have all sorts of things...
You have one thing they don't.
What? I don't have anything like that.
You're young!
It's game over if you just have that.
If someone paid me for that, I'd sell it without hesitation!
I want to grow up and have money and live in stability.
Stop saying nonsense, and just eat.
Here, open up.
I thought
you were confessing.
As if.
If I do and it goes wrong, then it's over.
So freaking pathetic, seriously.
What the? What's wrong with him?
You're here?
What's up?
[Cheers]
Welcome–
I don't like it when you look after Yoo Min unni.
What are you doing...
I'm... going to work here part-time starting today.
Oh, I s-see.
You're here?
Welcome–
How are you feeling?
We're going to do this next.
[Cheers]
Will it be okay to arrange the seats like this?
Yes.
Should we stop here today?
Oh, yes. Sure.
Hae Yi!
Yes.
Do you need anything?
I need someone to help me with the ticket numbering.
What?
Can you help me after you're done with work?
It won't take long.
Okay.
You said you have something to do.
- You can go.
- Oh!
Okay.
Apparently, you and I are similar.
Don't you think so?
What?
People say you and I are similar.
I wondered if that's really true.
I'm not sure.
Do you like Jung Woo?
What?
Why?
Just. It seems like it.
What about you?
Do you like Captain?
I do.
Jung Woo's a good kid.
I like him, too.
Captain's a good person.
That's enough.
It'll only get complicated if you go any further.
I'll take care of it.
Drink this.
[Park Jung Woo]
[Just wait. I'll reveal everything.]
It is you.
[Unknown User: Kick Do Hae Yi out.]
Why did you do it?
I didn't like Do Hae Yi.
Problems keep occurring because of Do Hae Yi.
Is that why you sent something like this?
Because you don't like Hae Yi?
Not anymore.
Why did you change your mind?
Just.
[Repeat]
What about the photos?
What photos?
I don't know what more there is, but it's not me.
I can't help it if you don't believe me.
I'll believe you.
However, I won't allow this from now on.
If there's something you want to say from now on, don't use this kind of method.
Say it in person.
Okay.
But, you should be careful, too.
Of what?
So that special treatment rumors don't arise.
We have...
so many memories. Here and there.
[Year 2002]
God, I almost became f***ed.
Is he someone you know?
What? No. I think he's just someone who needs help.
Goodness.
Gosh, why does he keep concerning me?
[2019 Yonhee Festival, Glorious]
Darn!
Isn't this enough for us to report to the Labor Department?
I'm going to the restroom.
Hurry back!
You... You shouldn't press that hard.
I know.
Give it to me.
Like this.
[2019 Yonhee Festival, Glorious]
He didn't get anything done.
♫ Like the spring breeze, ♫
♫ the soft music ♫
Captain, I...
♫ Words of confession that I practiced for many days ♫
♫ You and I are here together ♫
I...
What I tried to tell you yesterday...
So that special treatment rumors don't arise.
It's better off not saying anything.
♫ I'm just smiling ♫
Oh, I just... thought you were too absorbed by your first love.
So I just wanted to tell you to
differentiate your personal and professional life and focus on us, newbies.
Sure. I'll pay more attention.
Yeah, sure.
Good luck, then.
♫ If I call you tonight ♫
[Saturday, May 5th, 2019 at Yonhee Amphitheater, $13]
♫ We won't be able to go back ♫
♫ This song plays tonight ♫
Is something wrong?
Nope. I just hurt my finger.
♫ Now I'm just smiling ♫
[Captain Park Jung Woo]
[Newspaper clippings]
[Yonhee pamphlet]
[The Yonhee Blue]
Was it you?
I had a feeling an outsider was trespassing recently, so I dropped by,
but I'm not sure if I should call you an outsider, or an insider?
Yes, I trespassed. But I didn't do anything else.
We were wrong before, but now we're right?
I just wanted... to make more money.
The Media Department really set their hearts on ripping us apart, so I thought they'd air it if I made a report.
Honestly, it's not a crime to leave this inside a locker!
If it's not a crime, then why did you try to get rid of the evidence?
I didn't want to be misunderstood.
Because I didn't want to undergo another police investigation.
Did you even make a report? Huh?
Did you just threaten me?
Man, no wonder!
The police wouldn't be involved in something like–
How can we trust that you weren't behind everything else?
Whether you trust me or not, do whatever you want. In the end, it's not me.
You can report this stolen if you want.
You like reporting things. God.
I did well.
I didn't.
If you ask the flower, will it inform you if Soo Il is the culprit or not?
That's not what I asked.
Then? Then what did you ask?
Did you ask about your feelings or something?
I asked about something! Why do you keep asking?
Gosh, how much can we trust Soo Il?
Is he really overreacting because we reported him to the police?
It could be... all done by different people.
Whatever.
We gave Soo Il a scare, so he'll be quiet from now on.
Right, I hope so.
When we had the after-party last time... The day Hae Yi left first.
Where was Min Jae at that time?
Min Jae?
He was at Cheers. Why?
Nevermind.
[March 28th: Hae Yi received the first message.]
[March 29th: Hae Yi received a second message.]
[A member of the Cheer Squad will die.]
[It's going to happen to you, too.]
[April 10th: Hae Yi's third message during pep rally]
[REPEAT]
[April 13th: Media Department's video]
[April 14th: Min Jae's message - Kick out Do Hae Yi.]
[Min Jae]
[19145633, Kim Min Jae]
So it was you.
[Unknown User: Kick out Do Hae Yi.]
- Why did you do it?
- Because I don't like Do Hae Yi.
Min Jae? He was at Cheers.
[Soo Il]
Yes, I trespassed. But I didn't do anything else.
[The Yonhee Blue]
[It's going to happen to you, too.]
[REPEAT]
Someone who knows what happened two years ago.
[Address book of 2017 Theia Members]
But...
Why Hae Yi?
[Do Hae Yi]
About Ji Yoon, is she really sick?
- Huh?
Why? Ji Yoon's sick?
I mean, we were good until the day before yesterday.
We messaged each other, too.
But she said she was sick yesterday and I haven't been able to contact her since.
I wondered if she was sick to the point she couldn't hold her phone.
Should I buy her medicine?
No. Ji Yoon doesn't really take medicine.
- Then should I buy her porridge?
- No.
Ji Yoon doesn't like porridge.
- Then what can I...
- Just don't do anything.
So, just wait until she contacts you.
Right?
It could be hard for her to contact me if she's sick.
Yes, yes!
One, two, three, four.
Gosh, Jin Seon Ho, you have no rhythm.
One, two, three, four, five!
It's this, but you keep going, one, two, three–
Let's stop here.
What do you mean? We haven't even done a third of it.
- I need to go.
- Hey.
You're the one who's the most behind.
You're actually worse than he is.
Don't you think you should try harder?
Why don't you do it yourself if you want to do it that badly?
- Hello.
- Sure.
Everyone has different paces, so you shouldn't rush them.
Then when will he improve?
If he doesn't step up, we're all going to be disqualified.
I want to stand on stage, too.
Why are you scolding me when I'm doing my best?
Shouldn't you be scolding Jin Seon Ho?
[You don't recognize youth when you're young.]
♫ You don't recognize youth when you're young ♫
[You don't recognize love when you're in love.]
♪ And you don't recognize love when you're in love ♪
Sang Eun unni is really great.
(T/N: A singer from the '80s.)
How did she compose this song at 23 years old?
Exams are over, so let's drink!
That's right.
"You don't recognize youth when you're young."
That's why someone once said,
"Youth is wasted on the young."
Customer, it's bothersome if you keep mumbling to yourself like that.
Are you still upset at me?
I'm not upset with you.
I'm just expressing my opinion.
And you're totally ignoring my opinion.
Fine, then go ahead.
What?
I said, let's do it.
Let's officially start seeing each other.
What do you mean by officially seeing each other?
Let's date.
Let's be an official boyfriend and girlfriend or something.
Then will we have certain
pet names...
Right? That's going too far. That's too much.
How's baby?
Baby?
I mean, who else will call us baby at our age?
My... baby?
Yes! Baby's right here.
Wah.
I'm right here.
Drink up.
[Youth has no age.]
Baby's going to get drunk.
[Finals on all subjects]
Brother-in-law!
You know... Her vulnerability...
Besides weakness, is there anything else?
I'm just someone who lacks weaknesses.
- Why do you like my sister?
- Huh?
I can tell that you have nothing to lose and you look really popular.
There's no need for you to be hung up on my sister.
I'm amazed.
Sam Da lives really diligently.
That amazes me.
That's why I like her.
I've never been that desperate in my life.
I'm going. I need to go to the library.
Are you not going to tell me another vulnerability?
I don't know my sister that well either.
But, rather than asking me,
wouldn't it be better to ask her personally?
You're right.
Anyway,
thank you for helping me settle the case.
Oh, right. Hyung!
Did you know?
That you're kind of a prick?
Is that why my sister doesn't like you?
[We're having a party. Join us.]
What?
You got dumped in such a short time?
I mean, technically speaking, I wasn't dumped.
You liked him in a blink and got dumped in a blink.
You're quick to fall in love, but your progress speed is almost 5G.
No 7G.
- I wasn't dumped directly!
- Then what happened?
I got dumped second handedly.
Good for you!
It's better to get dumped sooner than later.
And do you think Captain would date you while breaking the rules?
You think so?
Is it because CCs are prohibited?
But then again, if you look at Yoo Min,
that doesn't seem to be the case, right?
I guess.
You're right. He just doesn't like me.
It looks like your mood swing switch in an instant.
Whatever!
I don't like someone who doesn't like me, either.
Just wait and see.
I'll treat him nonchalantly as if nothing happened.
- You were here, Captain!
- Theia.
Yeah, why?
Huh? Nothing!
Just thankful. You're sitting here?
You were sitting here.
Please go on.
[Don't beg for love.]
Don't beg for love.
- I am okay.
I am okay.
Our existence alone
- is overflowing with love itself.
- Overflowing.
- I am okay.
She's my daughter, but there's not a second I'm bored. She's a handful.
It's fun just watching her.
Cheer up. Hang in there.
Hey, Son, you're here? What about food?
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Give this to Seong Chul.
Tell him to give it to his mom.
She saved your life, so you should at least thank her.
Forget it.
Hey!
I bought this expensive cream with a big heart.
I bought this cream that I'll never even get to use with shaking hands.
- Bring it with you!
- I said, forget it!
Hey!
Hey, you almost broke it!
Do you know how pricey this is?
Fine, forget it.
It's not like I don't know her. I'll just go.
Please just stop it now!
Hey.
Do you know what that bastard said?
He said you'll just come back with your tail wagging if he gives you some money.
That bastard said that because you're always talking about money.
It's because you always act so crudely that–
Apologize!
Yeah?
Apologize to your sister this instant, you punk!
Apologize.
I said, apologize.
Hey, where are you going?
He'll come back when he has nowhere to go.
And you use that.
That wench isn't the only one with a face.
You can use good products and do whatever you want!
Stop living such a cheap life of embarrassment!
Start.
One, two, three, four!
- One, two, three, four!
- Again.
One, two, three, four!
- One, two, three–
- Do Hae Yi.
Get it together.
I'm sorry.
We'll take five, so get it together in the meantime.
Okay.
What's up? You even made a mistake.
I'm not in a good mood.
Rather than ask me,
wouldn't it be better to ask my sister personally?
Sam Da, what do you like?
Why are you suddenly asking?
Right.
It was a sudden and inappropriate question, huh?
- About me...
- Huh? What about you?
Do I look that bad to you, too?
Am I that materialistic
and shallow?
What are you saying now?
I do run around a lot.
Yeah, you do run around a bit.
Right? That's right.
Well, you know...
I'm not saying you are,
but I think you're incredible.
Are you being sarcastic?
You remember what you said to me?
The thing is, I'm f***ing poor.
It's something that could be embarrassing.
But I was amazed you could say it so frankly.
I don't think I could.
I just said I'm poor since I'm poor. What else can I say?
Well, you know,
I can't say anything embarrassing.
Because it could disappoint.
But you just say it,
and also live diligently.
I really think you're incredible.
That honestly takes a lot of courage.
You would do the same in my shoes.
No,
I don't think I could.
All right!
I'm quite incredible.
I've got it together, so shall I show them?
Whoa, how unique!
How in the world do you do it like that? Huh?
I don't think I could move my body like that.
You have quite the unique body movement.
Now, let's try it one more time.
One, two, three, four!
Two, that's right!
Hey!
Why would you trip there?
Hey, you've got dirt on your face.
Are you sure you've wanted to do this since high school?
Yeah.
Hey, are you okay?
What the heck?
Why is he handsome?
[Dance evaluation for the new song]
[Battle]
We will now begin the 2019 Theia dance evaluation for the new song.
The team that wins will perform on the main stage.
Everyone, fighting!
♫ At times, if you don't collide head-on with all your might ♫
♫ You won't be able to tell where it ends ♫
♫ And if you don't make it out of the herd ♫
♫ You won't be able to see the world ♫
♫ Shine, your smile, your eyes, your song ♫
♫ Even your tears ♫
♫ Shine, your failures, your fumbling firsts ♫
♫ Give it all you've got ♫
[Yonhee University Cheering Squad]
Both teams have done a great job.
The team that will stand on the main stage is...
- Team Captain is Cool!
- Yay!
Captain, Theia!
Hey, fist bump.
You, too.
Gosh. I see you practiced a lot.
I don't like inconveniencing others.
Look at you acting cool over nothing.
Good job.
- You did a good job, too.
- You, too.
Good job.
I'm sorry. You guys went through so much.
My choreography was lacking.
It wasn't!
You worked really hard.
Good job.
I told you to put this in there. It looks nice.
Noona!
Noona, why are you crying?
I just put you guys through a lot of trouble.
I really wanted to put you guys on stage.
It's fine.
We can go on next time.
You saw Park Jung Woo bragging earlier, right?
In my eyes, our team did a lot better.
Noona, you're really cute.
You...
Don't ever tell the kids I cried.
If you do, I'll kill you!
Okay.
Don't smile.
I said, don't smile.
What can I do when senior Ji Wan decided everything already?
I'm sorry, man.
Hyungnim, come on.
You're still doing that?
Wasting a lot of energy in...
making needless noise.
Probably because you're too scared to fight face-to-face.
What gives you the right to be back and f*** around like that?
Why?
Is there a reason why I can't be back?
You're the one who's still about that life.
Just stay still.
Don't go around making a mess like back then.
You might get hurt again.
Wonsilim!
(T/N: Primitive forest designated as a national treasure.)
♫ Throw your body into the raging rain and winds ♫
♫ Face your fate like a big, dignified whale ♫
♫ A world where you can't run away or get lost anyway ♫
♫ Yes, the long-awaited time has come ♫
[Yonhee 2019, Glorious]
♫ When the lightning strikes, open your eyes ♫
♫ Come on, sing out loud, dance with all your might ♫
♫ Keep your head up even if you crouch down ♫
♫ Now it's time to leave ♫
♫ Rough wind and rain ♫
♫ will swallow everything ♫
♫ Now open your eyes and spread your wings ♫
♫ through the eye of the typhoon ♫
Gosh! Do you not have any common sense?
Look at it before you fix it.
[Youth is now! Everyone wear jeans for the youth.]
I quit.
Wait! Where the heck are they going?
Fighting!
♫ The dazzling brilliance ♫
♫ said there was a ray of light ♫
♫ I remember his song ♫
♫ through the eye of the typhoon ♫
Good work!
[D-2]
[D-1]
The festival is finally tomorrow.
We're all going to sleep at the motel across from the main entrance.
We're going to take turns standing guard because of the stage equipment.
Each person should check their time with So Yoon.
Okay!
I know you're all tired, but let's do our best until the end.
- Fighting.
- Fighting!
All right, the tickets.
They're precious tickets, so keep them safe.
These are really hard to get.
[Yonhee 2019, Glorious]
[Do Hae Yi, Jin Seon Ho]
That's right.
Did you guys hear?
If you're with your crush below the half-moon spot on the day before the festival,
your love apparently gets requited or something.
Seriously?
Where is the half-moon spot?
I don't know. No one knows the spot.
Why are there so many legends in this school?
Half-moon spot.
Vice Captain!
Do you have some time later?
Time? Why?
Well, Woon Chan said to do the final sound check with you.
Really?
I thought So Yoon was going to do it.
Then... What about around 8:00 p.m.?
Okay. I'll see you at 8:00 p.m. then.
Okay.
[2019 Yonhee, Glorious]
Mom!
What?
The glass cuts through the silence!
Well... Here.
What is it?
They're tickets to my school festival.
Why are you putting them there?
Well, you can come watch if you're bored.
- Me?
- Yes.
You can also tell Do Jae Yi to come if he's bored
or you can just throw them out.
All right. I'll think about it.
See you.
Take care.
I'm not coming home tonight!
Hey, are you crazy? I'll break your legs–
Yes.
My hair... My hair.
Wait, what am I going to wear?
Hey, wait...
J-Jae Yi, Jae Yi! Got to call him.
[2019 Yonhee, Glorious]
I didn't break it.
I wasn't the one who b-broke it.
It broke by itself.
Gosh, I can't be caught.
It's dangerous.
Look who I have here.
It's my Seon Ho!
My son...
My treasure!
The reason for my life.
- Did you drink?
- Hush!
Just a little.
Mommy... drank just a little.
Have you ever seen Dad celebrate an anniversary?
He doesn't, so I need to celebrate it, at least.
Please stop it now!
Why do you always wait for Dad, who never comes?
It'd be better for you to give up.
Oh, no.
You're here, Dear?
Did you drink?
A little... I drank just a little.
Today's your anniversary.
Mom drank while waiting for you, who never comes.
Even strangers aren't this bad.
Seon Ho, don't be like that.
[2019 Yonhee, Glorious]
Hello.
Could you help me?
Finally, tomorrow is the festival.
Are you excited?
Yes.
I was really excited the day before my first festival.
Were you offended because I told you not
to like Jung Woo?
W-Well, I mean...
You see, I don't want what happened to me to repeat.
I don't know what happened, but
you and I are different people, Senior.
I'm a veteran who's experienced the land, the sea, and the air.
So not many things can make me blink.
It's okay. You don't need to worry.
That's true.
You and I are different.
This is the room.
Thank you for giving me a hand.
Sure.
- I'll be going then.
- Okay, see you.
[Unknown User: REPEAT]
[Unknown User]
[werther@zmail.com]
[Unknown]
[You're the one from two years ago, aren't you?]
[Go back.]
[Message read]
If I do this, then this becomes the half-moon spot.
Which movie should we watch?
You can decide.
- Thanks Oppa.
- Go on.
- I'll call you.
- I'll be off.
Who is he?
My boyfriend.
What?
Oh, when...
Not too long ago. Shall we?
W-Wait.
Well...
Never mind.
- Huh?
- Oh, well. So Yoon said she checked the sound system.
What? Then you should've called me sooner.
I just found out, too.
Okay.
Half-moon spot, my foot.
[Motel Lumiere Group Reservation List]
[Yonhee University Cheer Squad, 7 & 8 FL, Rooms 7001 - 8009]
[Room 7007]
Sam Da! Get up. It's your turn, now.
Huh? I wasn't sleeping. I'm totally fine.
Three americanos, please.
Okay.
It's 13,500 won.
It's the sleepiest time. It's not odd to buy her some coffee.
I'll give one to Hae Yi, one to Seon Ho, and one for me.
We're all drinking it together. It's not odd at all.
Are we on guard until 2:00 a.m.?
Yeah.
You don't look too well today. Is something wrong?
No. My head just hurts a bit.
Should I buy you some painkillers?
No. It'll ease up.
Sure.
Gosh, what will we do for three hours?
Oh, my gosh!
What the? Why did that suddenly turn on? It's scary.
Well, the light even turned on.
Should we dance?
Okay. Let's just sit here. We'll just sit still.
That time...
You asked me what I find difficult.
You are still hung up on that?
Then I do know what your hardship is.
The assumption that people don't think you have any hardships. Right?
Sorry. I'm slacking on reading the atmosphere today.
I don't like my dad.
Hating my dad is hard.
I'm joking. I thought you were bored.
Look at you.
Sure.
But you know...
Don't you think it's hard because you like him and not because you hate him?
I was like that, too.
Sometimes, I hate that I was born into my family.
But I really like it, too.
But those hateful feelings gave me a hard time.
Well, not that I really know.
Hey. Why are you crying?
Hey, I'm sorry. Oh, I don't know jack. Just ignore me, okay?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Why isn't it me?
Why do the people I like, look at other people?
♫ It's quite ♫
Can't you just look at me?
♫ A beautiful thing ♫
♫ That you and I met ♫
♫ And shared that moment together ♫
I'm sorry.
♫ It's unforgettable ♫
♫ The me, who wasn't worth anything ♫
It's okay.
♫ You hugged me warmly ♫
♫ The tears will dry ♫
♫ The wounds will heal ♫
♫ Our memories will fade ♫
♫ Just like the moonlight dispersing far away ♫
[Cheer Up]
♫ It's quite heartbreaking ♫
♫ Much time will pass ♫
I know how the Captain feels, so I cleared everything up today.
I hope today will be a special moment.
You have too many thoughts, so you're slow to act. You're going to regret it.
- I already do.
The ones sending threatening messages are probably all from the Cheer Squad.
They'll probably be watching today, too.
Where's Hae Yi?
Will now start part 3 of the festival!
♫ will heal ♫