(13 vs. 13 Team Death Match officially begins)
Let's go.
Fighting.
- Fighting.
Yes, let's move forward.
Don't forget the choreography.
Try again.
- Let's go.
- Again.
Are you okay?
- It's dangerous.
- It's okay.
Ah, okay.
- Fighting.
- That's the spirit! Feels good, huh?
(Round 2 Performance, D-DAY)
(MOON JAEIL, JUNMYEONG, HARUTO,
HWANG HEEWOO, YANG HYEONBIN...)
(HYO, I love you)
(JUNHYEOK, SECHAN)
MC DEX: Who is your boy? B:MY BOYZ.
MC DEX: Hello, I'm MC DEX
from B:MY BOYZ.
(Round 2 TOP IDOL MONSTA X)
MONSTA X: Hoo! MONSTA X! Hello? This is MONSTA X.
MC DEX: B:MY BOYZ Round 2
13 vs. 13 Death Match.
MC DEX: The team chosen by the TOP IDOL
MC DEX: survives as a whole,
and the teams not selected
MC DEX: all become
elimination candidates.
(MY MONSTAZ,
a backstage full of tension)
The moment we finish this,
make eye contact.
HYO: We practiced a lot, so I think
we can win, we have to win,
HYO: and I really want to win.
(Round 1 ranking 26, KIM JEONGHOON)KIM J
EONGHOON: Losing means elimination,
EONGHOON: so we must try hard.
KIM BOHYEON: This time, I really
want us all to survive and win.
HARUTO: Since we have
practiced a lot so far...
AI: I think we're better.
AI: MY MONSTAZ team, we're going to win!
(Master's Room)
So this time,
(Team Death Match, the masters joined each team)
I was a bit closer to them, you know.
- Ah, that's right.
- Since the teams were divided.
YUJEONG: If they lose, it's like
they might be eliminated there.
- LIA KIM: YUJEONG, are you going to cry today?
- YUJEONG: No, no.
(Already teary eyes)
MC DEX: B:MY BOYZ
Round 2 will start now.
MC DEX: Who is your boy?
- B:MY BOYZ.
MONSTA X KIHYUN: I'm getting nervous.
MONSTA X HYUNGWON: Curious
about the stage.
(Which team will get
MONSTA X's TOP PICK?)
(Round 2 title song match, Love Killa vs. Shoot Out)
MC DEX: B:MY BOYZ 13 vs. 13.
(Team Death Match first title song match)
MC DEX: First title song match.
MC DEX: Let's meet the two teams.
(MY MONSTAZ, Love Killa Team)
(MONSTA B, Shoot Out Team)
(BOHYEON)
BOHYEON.
(Welcome)
(MONSTA B vs. MY MONSTAZ)
(MY MONSTAZ "Spring Day" Team
MONSTA B "You Were Beautiful" Team) Yay, let's go.
SEO JUNHYEOK: Give it your all.
(MONSTA B, let's go)
Let's go.
(Masters are also nervous)
- They are doing it. - No hesitation, huh?
(Do your best, B:GINNERs)
- It's starting right away. -Yes, good.
(1st title song match)
Five, six, seven, eight.
(Coolness overload)
(Cool) (SECHAN)
- Hello.
LEE YEONTAE: We are...
- Love Killa Team!
- Hello.
- It's Shoot Out Team!
MC DEX: Yes, please give
a warm round of applause.
(Anticipation) (Welcome)
(The nail-biting showdown
team's title song match)
(Love Killa Team)
MONSTA X KIHYUN: Good physical.
MONSTA X KIHYUN: B:GINNER
BAN DANIEL kinda looks like you.
(Looks like HYUNGWON,
MONSTA baby BAN DANIEL)
I heard that he is only 14 years old.
HUI: Oh, look DANIEL.
YUJEONG: He looks handsome
when he puts his hair up.
DANIEL showed a somewhat cute
(Gentle baby BAN DANIEL)
and innocent side.
(Coolness overload, Baby BAN DANIEL)
MC DEX: MONSTA X, if you
have any questions, please ask.
MONSTA X HYUNGWON: By any chance... which
one of the three of us do you like the most?
(Quite puzzled)
MC DEX: Ah, that's a very difficult question.
KIM JEONGHOON: BAN DANIEL
should answer this.
(Hesitant)
- You're not seriously going to choose, right?
- Just say they're all good.
(Feeling uneasy)
- No, no. - Just say you like them all.
- Don't fall into a trap, kids.
- Our DANIEL.
BAN DANIEL: Personally, I like
senior SHOWNU the most.
(Screaming masters)
- No. - BAN DANIEL.
(Mixed emotions)
- Oh. - Ah, it's really...
MONSTA X SHOWNU: BAN DANIEL!
MONSTA X SHOWNU: Thank you.
(Full of affection)
MONSTA X SHOWNU: I'll watch with gratitude, yes.
Ah, I'm jealous.
(Shoot Out Team) MC DEX: I want to ask
what you think about this title song match.
YANG HYEONBIN: Very nervous.
I'm very nervous.
(Staring)
MC DEX: You're very nervous?
MC DEX: If you smile at me
like that lovingly, I...
(So cute)
MC DEX: My heart's beating like this.
How about everyone watching out there?
(Heart-throb HYEONBIN)
MC DEX: MONSTA X,
MC DEX: are there any B:GINNERs
that you are looking forward to?
First of all, HARUTO.
(MONSTA B, HARUTO)
MONSTA X SHOWNU:
You have a very cute image,
MONSTA X SHOWNU: but your unexpected
charm is highly anticipated. And next to him...
(Eye-catching deltoid muscles) MONSTA X SHOWNU:
The outfitreally highlights those deltoid muscles.
(Shy)
(So cute) MONSTA X SHOWNU: I'll keep a close watch
on the deltoids muscles.
(MONSTA X Original Beast Idol, SHOWNU)
MC DEX: But still, compared to you,
MC DEX: his physique seems a bit lacking.
MONSTA X SHOWNU: He's still young, yes.
(I want that too) MC DEX: SHOWNU,
I really envy those awesome shoulders of yours.
(Love Killa Team)
What key points would you like us
and the B:IN US to focus on
when watching
the Love Killa performance?
LEE YUNSUNG: I think the intro part
of Love Killa is the most important.
(The intro part of Love Killa
that captivates from the beginning)
(Indeed) (Love Killa Team struggled picking the OST intro)
We kept debating who fit best, so it took a while.
- HUI: Ah, the intro was no joke, seriously.
- That's right
(It changed a few times)
- This one? - Yes, this one.
The intro part.
- YUJEONG: It changed three times.
- Really?
(Three times?)
What's the reason?
(Love Killa, what on earth happened
to the MY MONSTAZ Team?)
(Shoot Out Team)
Did you focus on any key points while preparing?
MOON JAEIL: The song 'Shoot Out' is
the most famous and mainstream song.
(First terrestrial #1, loved Shoot Out )
♪shoot-out, shoot-out, shoot-out fiercely♪
MOON JAEIL: With the idea of capturing
the unique vibe of 'Shoot Out'...
(Expectation)
(1st title song match)
(How was the practice process for
the two signature song match teams?)
(Round 2 Contest D-17, MY MONSTAZ Practice Room)
- Let's gather. - Love Killa.
Shall we check it out?
(MY MONSTAZ checking
the choreography for 'Love Killa')
Wow, that's cool!
(Intro part that catches
the eye with a strong impact)
So good.
KIM JEONGHOON: Honestly, this
song's intro carries half the impact,
KIM JEONGHOON: so we really
struggled with how to arrange the parts.
HYO: Shall we start by deciding
who will be the center?
HYO: You know this.
LEE YEONTAE: Right, the intro part
has to be sealed with this move.
LEE YUNSUNG: Can I try it out?
WILLIAM: I really want
to do the intro part.
WILLIAM: Honestly, the biggest highlight
of the song 'Love Killa' is the intro,
WILLIAM: and I was more confident
than anyone else in nailing it.
(Intro part candidates: WILLIAM, LEE YUNSUNG)
For now, WILLIAM and YUNSUNG.
HYO: We should discuss
who will do it as well.
(Emergency meeting to decide the intro part)
This song has to be decided right here.
BAN DANIEL: Overall,
I think WILLIAM is better...
LEE YEONTAE: When it comes
to stability, it's probably WILLIAM.
(WILLIAM handled the intro of the Round 1 'Kick It' well)
♪Let me introduce you to some new thangs♪
KIM JEONGHOON: I can see
WILLIAM making expressions,
- but it comes off a bit excessive.
- Right.
KIM JEONGHOON: That powerful energy
doesn't quite match this song.
KIM JEONGHOON: It's more about
subtle sexiness, and I think...
(LEE YEONTAE) (HYO)
- YUNSUNG? - Yes.
(Who will be the owner of the intro part
decided after the meeting?)
(WILLIAM/LEE YUNSUNG)
HYO: Wouldn't it be better for YUNSUNG to take this?
(LEE YUNSUNG became the intro center)
I will try harder.
It's really the beginning for us.
It was also the part I wanted to
do the most, so I have to work hard.
LEE YUNSUNG: I feel both pressure
and nervousness with this part.
(With the parts decided, it's time for serious practice)
Five, six, seven, eight.
One, okay.
It's done, done.
(Wow, it's cool. It's already cool.)
Do you really dislike it? Here?
We look so small...
(Tiptoeing)
HYO: At first glance, his physique is great
and my eyes keep going to YUNSUNG,
HYO: so I think he's
perfect for the center.
KIM JEONGHOON: YUNSUNG, your
timing is on point when you dance,
KIM JEONGHOON: but you should...
(JEONGHOON helping center YUNSUNG)
You really have to put strength into your body.
You can't dance it lightly.
LEE YUNSUNG: I had many
weaknesses in dancing,
LEE YUNSUNG: so JEONGHOON taught me
a lot and was very dependable.
BAN DANIEL: He did great with both rapping
and singing on the 'Fact Check' stage...
(Fact Check's all-rounder,
B:GINNER KIM JEONGHOON)
HUI: I was really surprised
when I saw JEONGHOON.
LIA KIM: JEONGHOON's
doing well. He's good.
(Masters also recognize KIM JEONGHOON)
LIA KIM: He has great balance.
(J Entertainment 1 year)
I trained for about 1 year at JYP
(C Entertainment 2.5 years)
and about 2.5 years at Cube.
(Solid skills built through a major agency)
Whether it's expression or vocals,
I'm confident in showing
powerful energy broadly.
(JEONGHOON became the leader of the title song match)
First, what we need to check is,
KIM JEONGHOON: if there's
any confusing part, unclear timing,
KIM JEONGHOON: or you're not sure
what to do, please speak up right away.
I'll make sure you remember it clearly.
(I trust you)
- Yes. - Great.
LEE YEONTAE: He has leadership, and
when the dance progresses, he counts well too.
(A leader that team members can trust and follow)
One, two, three, four. That's right.
You've got to sweep it like this
to really bring out the feeling.
Yes, just touch it, as much as possible.
- Yes, yes.
- Okay!
KIM JEONGHOON: I'm doing it
with the attitude of doing my best to win.
(Love Killa Team Leader)
KIM JEONGHOON: As the leader,
KIM JEONGHOON: I want us to win,
no matter what.
KIM JEONGHOON: No matter
what it takes, I'll give it my all.
(MY MONSTAZ led by JEONGHOON, practicing for a long time)
- Focus, let's try it live. - Yes.
(Round 2 Contest D-17, MONSTA B's Practice Room)
- Alright, shall we take a look? - Let's do it.
(Oh no)
♪Shoot Out♪
(MONSTA X's signature masculine charm
and powerful energy in the choreography)
AI: I'm lacking in dancing
with enough power...
YANG HYEONBIN: Feels like
my body's about to give out.
HWANG HEEWOO: I think
I was a little worried.
(While everyone feels lost)
It was a good choice, 'Shoot Out'.
MOON JAEIL: Because it's a
more impactful song than 'Love Killa',
MOON JAEIL: and I'm confident
in our performance and dance,
MOON JAEIL: I believe we can win by
a big difference against Love Killa Team.
(B:MY BOYZ official dancer, MOON JAEIL)
MOON JAEIL has that real music show performance vibe.
(How will 'Shoot Out',
led by MOON JAEIL, perform?)
- MOON JAEIL: Okay, we can do this. Yeah, we can.
- Yes.
('Shoot Out' MONSTA B's
choreography leader, MOON JAEIL)
Use your shoulders a bit.
(Dancing hard) (HARUTO)
(God JAEIL, in charge of choreography copying and training)
- Like this, half circle, okay? - Like this?
Okay, one more time. One...
(Dancing hard)
YANG HYEONBIN: I think JAEIL
is our team's secret weapon.
YANG HYEONBIN: JAEIL's choreography
skills are really impressive.
HWANG HEEWOO: JAEIL was the fastest learner,
so everyone relied on him a lot.
(MONSTA B's official secret weapon)
One and bam.
Like that, one more time.
Good, you're doing well.
MOON JAEIL: Actually, I feel like everyone's been
keeping up really well, so I'm truly grateful.
AI: But somehow, no one spoke up to JAEIL...
Even though he never scolded us,
AI: he's kind of scary.
Oh, stop, stop.
MOON JAEIL: SUTHASCHAI, please
sync up the timing a little better.
(Like this?)
Here...
- MOON JAEIL: Like that, and a little more to the side.
- Ah, got it.
- Focus.
- Yes.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
(Wobble)
MOON JAEIL: SUTHASCHAI! Focus!!
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
(SUTHASCHAI struggling to keep
up compared to other beginners)
(SUTHASCHAI)
SUTHASCHAI, please focus again.
MOON JAEIL: I think
SUTHASCHAI is a bit lacking
MOON JAEIL: in performance and
dance compared to the other members.
(Continuous choreography mistakes)
- Let's do it again. -Yes.
MOON JAEIL: SUTHASCHAI, you're
making mistakes here repeatedly.
SUTHASCHAI: I was just focused here.
MOON JAEIL: Stop messing up the choreo.
How many times have we gone over it?
MOON JAEIL: I have to do it too,
and I don't want to just sit here.
MOON JAEIL: If you keep slipping like this, people will
think you're not putting in the effort.
MOON JAEIL: Details, sure, I understand
you might not get them instantly,
MOON JAEIL: but choreography?
MOON JAEIL: We have the videos
for that, remember?
- MOON JAEIL: Let's get it right in one go, one time.
- SUTHASCHAI: Yes.
AI: Even BOHYEON, the oldest,
listens when JAEIL, says something...
(Attention)
KIM BOHYEON: I got scolded a lot
by JAEIL even though I'm older.
(A tense atmosphere)
MOON JAEIL: Since we have to survive,
MOON JAEIL: maybe we should
be tougher, like a strict teacher.
(Two team leaders with contrasting practice styles)
KIM JEONGHOON: I'll make sure
KIM JEONGHOON: you remember it well.
(How's the mid-check for the B:GINNERs-led title song match?)
Shall we start with MY MONSTAZ first?
- Yes.
Let's go.
YUJU: Don't forget the choreography!
- Yes.
With focus.
(MY MONSTAZ' Master / MONSTA B's Master)
Focus. Seriously.
Right now, you're
basically like parents.
Ah, we're watching this with
the heart of a parent right now.
But that's just how it ends up.
(Fierce energy from both masters?)
You two are gonna do this when MONSTA B comes out, right?
(MY MONSTAZ)
I can't see them very well right now.
(Our master is the best)
I'm just keep looking here.
(MY MONSTAZ/MONSTA B) For someone stuck
in the middle, this is really entertaining.
(Do your best, guys)
I'm so happy, and anyway...
HUI: First, we have to watch
the title song match performance.
HUI: I heard there was a lot of
talk about the center position.
That's right.
HUI: So who was decided on now?
(What happened to the intro center?)
I became the center.
(New intro center, B:GINNER CHOI YOHAN)
Okay guys, shall we start the class?
(Round 2 Competition D-15, Dance class
by Master YUJEONG, in charge of MY MONSTAZ)
YUJEONG: YUNSUNG is starting?
LEE YUNSUNG: Yes.
YUJEONG: It's good when
you're standing at the start.
YUJEONG: But from the moment
you start walking out...
(A simple-looking but
impactful move is needed)
YUJEONG: Even a little sloppiness can
make everything after that really risky.
LEE YUNSUNG: Yes.
YUJEONG: Either change
members to be more visible,
YUJEONG: or show it
clearly by matching it.
YUJEONG: JEONGHOON, you
definitely need to clarify it.
(Criticism of the carefully chosen intro center)
KIM JEONGHOON: Yes.
KIM JEONGHOON: I think my confidence
got shaken a bit.
KIM JEONGHOON: I seemed to have
been very worried about what to do.
(The intro center was eventually switched from YUNSUNG to YOHAN)
Among ourselves, we decided on YOHAN.
(With the sudden center change, will
MY MONSTAZ receive positive feedback?)
♪I'm sorry, did I make you anxious♪
♪Beautiful love killa, love killa♪
(Stuttering)
♪Love killa, love killa♪
♪As you know, we never♪
♪Can't let go of each other♪
♪We throw everything in♪
(Even B:GINNER KIM JEONGHOON goes off-key)
♪See it through, see it through♪
♪Now take a shot♪
♪Take a shot♪
♪Take a shot, no hard feelings♪
♪I'm sorry, did I make you anxious♪
(Sharp glance)
(A stage with many mistakes overall)
HUI: Did you know today
was the mid-check?
(Tension)
LIA KIM: I guess you guys
didn't practice seriously.
(Colliding while moving on stage) LIA KIM: Collisions
happened due to poor stage movement coordination.
JINHO: And the intro lacked charisma.
JINHO: You should capture
everything in the intro.
(Even the replaced intro part is getting harsh criticism)
JINHO: The moves and energy in the intro feel off.
JINHO: The overall
tension is just too low.
CHOI YOHAN: I was worried
and ended up regretting not dancing harder.
HARUTO: Still showing a lack
of confidence in the dance,
HARUTO: singing, and movements...
MOON JAEIL: There were
many small mistakes,
MOON JAEIL: and the stage
movements had quite a few flaws.
I think you all should
start feeling the urgency.
This is a big deal.
KIM JEONGHOON: As the one
leading the choreography,
KIM JEONGHOON: I was disappointed
and felt the pressure
KIM JEONGHOON: seeing we only delivered
KIM JEONGHOON: this much quality
at the mid-check.
(MY MONSTAZ in crisis)
I kept thinking, "This is serious trouble."
(Continued mid-check for MONSTA B)
Let's watch MONSTA B's performance right away.
- Yes.
(Starting with B:GINNER
MOON JAEIL at the center)
(Wow)
(That's right)
(MONSTA B starting with Shoot Out's distinct intense energy)
♪Walker, walker, walker, growling♪
♪Walker, walker, walker♪
(Despite concerns, SUTHASCHAI finds stability in the center)
♪Shoot-out, shoot-out, shoot-out for me♪
♪Shoot-out, shoot-out, shoot-out♪
(Continuing with HIROTO's Rap part)
♪Blakk blakk blakk. Can't block block block.♪
♪You're blah blah blah stop ta, talking♪
♪The feelings that left, burst out
without hesitation, pop pop pop♪
WILLIAM: The dance is well synchronized.
PARK SECHAN: They are doing great.
YUJEONG: Still, it seems like
you guys practiced a lot overall.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
(Well done)
Good, well done.
YUJEONG: I really want to praise JAEIL.
YUJEONG: The energy JAEIL
gives when he starts
YUJEONG: seems to carry the mood a lot.
YUJEONG: That's why
I want to praise him.
YUJU: Since the opening
energy was amazing,
YUJU: the overall stage
felt more impressive
YUJU: than that of MY MONSTAZ.
(You all worked hard)
YUJU: You worked hard.
- Thank you.
KIM BOHYEON: It feels like
a ray of hope is breaking through.
AI: I gained confidence
that I can do well.
SUTHASCHAI: There's still some
worry about whether I can do well,
SUTHASCHAI: but for now, I'm having fun
and will try even harder next time.
MOON JAEIL: Thanks to the team members
keeping up well, I believe we finished it successfully.
(Suddenly)
The disappointing parts...
LEE YUJEONG: The disappointing parts are
LEE YUJEONG: that each part's center
should really own the moment,
LEE YUJEONG: but every time the centers
appear, they actually come off too weak.
LEE YUJEONG: Actually, those weaknesses
were especially noticeable with HIROTO.
(Relatively weak as a center, B:GINNER HIROTO)
♪The feelings that left burst out without hesitation, pop pop pop♪
LEE YUJEONG: Those parts
definitely need to be strengthened.
HIROTO: Yeah, I know... I'm still
lacking, and I do feel a little apologetic.
(After mid-check, MONSTA B's dance class)
LIA KIM: Master YUJEONG said earlier
LIA KIM: that when you're
center, you have to fully commit
LIA KIM: with your
expressions and gestures.
LIA KIM: HIROTO, you get it?
HIROTO: Yes.
LIA KIM: Try it alone that part once.
LIA KIM: Start.
(B:GINNER HIROTO looking quite lacking in confidence)
♪Blakk blakk blakk. Can't block block block♪
♪You're blah blah blah stop ta, talking♪
♪The feelings that left burst out♪
LIA KIM: Stop.
(Embarrassed)
(The vibe naturally changes to HIROTO's personal class)
LIA KIM: You need to have this body when doing this.
LIA KIM: Move like this.
LIA KIM: Doo-doong, like this, start!
LIA KIM: Doo-doong.
LIA KIM: Practice a lot. Watch yourself
in the mirror and really put in the work.
HIROTO: Yes.
LIA KIM: It's not just about the moves,
you've got to train the vibe too.
HIROTO: Yes.
HIROTO: This round's been a bit tough... I'm
trying a lot of things for the first time, like rapping,
HIROTO: and I've been feeling nervous,
like, "Can I really pull this off?"
(When everyone is asleep, B:GINNER HIROTO
comes out to the living room alone)
(Pronunciation practice focusing
on parts lacking compared to others)
(Yawn)
(Cue the tough-love mentor)
(Scouting the scene)
Okay, HIROTO fighting.
HIROTO: Thank you.
(Practicing hard)
(Next morning)
(B:GINNER HIROTO, the first
to arrive at the practice room)
HIROTO: I know I'm lacking in skill
and trying a lot of things for the first time,
HIROTO: but I see it as a great
opportunity for growth.
(HIROTO, who always pushed himself
one step further than the others)
- Okay.
- Ah, yes.
HIROTO: It's taking me a long time,
so I feel really sorry to my teammates.
HIROTO: I'm going to work even harder. Let's
all do our best, so we can make it together.
(After the mid-check, MY MONSTAZ gather)
JEONGHOON, you really worked so hard too.
We're almost there now,
just a little bit more.
LIM JIHWAN: Is everything
going alright, JEONGHOON?
KIM JEONGHOON: Hmm...
right now, I feel like I'm a bit...
KIM JEONGHOON: Ah, don't say that.
- Good job.
- You're doing well.
(Sudden burst of tears)
- You're doing well. - You're doing well.
(Sorry)
KIM JEONGHOON: Actually, I was
the one leading the choreography,
KIM JEONGHOON: so as the leader, I should
have been the best at expressing it.
KIM JEONGHOON: But I felt lacking,
KIM JEONGHOON: and I started to question
KIM JEONGHOON: whether
I'm really fit to keep leading.
(KIM JEONGHOON, feeling sorry and
responsible for the team, bursts into tears)
KIM JEONGHOON: Since losing
basically means I'm out
KIM JEONGHOON: unless
the rankings shift dramatically,
KIM JEONGHOON: I really need
to lead the team to success,
(B:GINNER KIM JEONGHOON, who wanted
to lead the team better than anyone else)
KIM JEONGHOON: but
it's not going smoothly.
LIM JIHWAN: It's okay, you're doing
well, so don't feel too pressured.
(Since the team knows JEONGHOON's heart)
LIM JIHWAN: You lead, but communicate well with the team.
LEE YUNSUNG: JEONGHOON worked hard,
LEE YUNSUNG: so we need
to show our best for his effort.
WILLIAM: We just need to trust JEONGHOON
a bit more and follow along well.
Okay.
- It's okay.
- Okay.
(MY MONSTAZ, gradually aligning
their goals and determination) It's okay.
It's okay.
Okay.
KIM JEONGHOON: Let's
start from 'five, six, and.'
(Thus, starting over from the beginning to synchronize)
KIM JEONGHOON: Five, six, and seven, and eight.
(And KIM JEONGHOON gets up again to lead the team)
KIM JEONGHOON: Instead of pushing it out like this,
KIM JEONGHOON: you need
to bend it like this, like this.
KIM JEONGHOON: Yes a bit more.
IKUTO: JEONGHOON is giving dance
feedback to each member one by one.
Come over here and try it like this.
Yes.
YANG CHENGXI: From the very
first day, he kept saying
YANG CHENGXI: he truly believes in me
and thinks I can do well on stage.
KIM JEONGHOON: Seven and eight and one.
KIM JEONGHOON: Yes, make sure
the moves are spot on.
LEE YUNSUNG: As the youngest,
JEONGHOON probably felt it hard
LEE YUNSUNG: to reach out
to the older members,
LEE YUNSUNG: yet he motivated us
and helped with the dance moves a lot.
HYO: I think overall confidence increased
and the team atmosphere improved.
(And the unresolved task of the intro center)
At first...
KIM JEONGHOON: I think YEONTAE
should be the intro center.
(As the new intro center, LEE YEONTAE)
You'll need to put in plenty of effort and preparation.
KIM JEONGHOON: I thought it would
be good for YEONTAE to do it
KIM JEONGHOON: because he
brings this part to life so well.
LEE YEONTAE: I'll work harder,
and if we all put in more effort together,
LEE YEONTAE: we'll definitely win.
HIROTO: If we practice diligently
and do well, I think we can definitely win.
MOON JAEIL: We haven't slacked off
since the mid-check.
MOON JAEIL: Because we've
practiced even harder,
MOON JAEIL: I assure you that we will show
you that much of a great stage.
KIM BOHYEON: MY MONSTAZ! Those
who need to leave, go home safely,
KIM BOHYEON: and for the rest, fight your
way back up on your own!
(The passion of the two teams
burning until the end)
(Which team will be smiling at the end?)
(The two teams on stage)
(Love Killa Team)
MONSTA X KIHYUN: I have a tip before starting the stage.
(Concentration) MONSTA X KIHYUN: I hope
you don't put in 100% effort.
(Heartfelt advice from a senior)
MONSTA X KIHYUN: It might get too stiff,
MONSTA X KIHYUN: so just keep that in mind.
- Yes.
- Yes, I got it.
(Shoot Out Team) MONSTA X KIHYUN:
Earlier, I told the others not to overdo it,
MONSTA X KIHYUN:
but "Shoot Out" is different.
MONSTA X KIHYUN: For "Shoot Out",
you should make it tear up the stage.
("Shoot Out" requires powerful performance)
MONSTA X KIHYUN: Fight like your life depends on it.
MONSTA X KIHYUN: Fighting!
- Thank you.
(1 set title song match) MC DEX:
Let's check out the stage of Love Killa.
(MY MONSTAZ Team's first attack,
"Love Killa")
Fighting, fighting.
Fighting.
Give it a try!
MOON JAEIL: If the opposing team
kept pushing after the mid-check,
MOON JAEIL: it could be a match
where no one knows who will win.
(Love Killa Team, together to the last)
Let's go.
LEE YUNSUNG: It's been a rough ride,
but let's make this stage perfect.
LEE YUNSUNG: Let's all 13
of us go up together!
KIM JEONGHOON: Let's give it everything
we've got, just like the lyrics say.
KIM JEONGHOON: Don't hold back. If we
stay focused on our stage, we'll win.
(The Love Killa Team that went
through many ups and downs)
(Will they be able to
show unity on stage?)
Oh, cool.
Cool, cool.
Cool.
("Love Killa" original song by MONSTA X)
♪LEE YEONTAE: Got room for one more♪
(Surprised)
(LEE YEONTAE's intro part
that captivates attention!)
♪HYO: Oh I'm sorry,
did I make you anxious♪
♪HYO: Move subtly like swish♪
♪HYO: Silently like hunting prey♪
♪HYO: In the repeated battle
of wills we soar♪
♪HYO: Even the red siren
turns off now it's you and me♪
HYO is a leopard, a leopard!
♪LEE YUNSUNG: Anyway
you and I are love or hate♪
♪LEE YUNSUNG: Want and hate like crazy♪
♪WILLIAM: I'ma slay,
I'ma chill, I'ma kill♪
♪YANG CHENGXI: From now on,
it's a twist♪
♪KIM JEONGHOON:
Pull the trigger, ya pull pull♪
♪BAN DANIEL: We are all
psycho halfway I go crazy♪
♪IKUTO: Throw everything ya♪
♪HYO, LEE YEONTAE, WILLIAM:
See the end, see the end♪
(Great)
♪IKUTO: Now take a shot ♪
♪IKUTO: Take a shot,
there's no hard feelings♪
Vocal is good.
♪IKUTO: Now take a shot♪
♪LEE YUNSUNG: Enough, enough♪
♪LEE YEONTAE: Cruel and beautiful
love killa, love killa♪
♪CHOI YOHAN: Love killa♪
♪LEE YEONTAE: Beautiful
love killa, love killa♪
Oh, LEE YEONTAE.
♪BAN DANIEL: That's right,
you look at my eyes♪
♪BAN DANIEL: Straight into
my eyes and just say♪
(Well done)
(BAN DANIEL!)
Wow, he does something like this.
♪CHOI YOHAN: I want you
eat me like a main dish♪
♪CHOI YOHAN: Hot like it burns, hottish♪
♪CHOI YOHAN: It ain't
clićhe cliched ending pass it♪
♪CHOI YOHAN: I want
something more stimulating hot♪
♪HYO: Sharpen it more sharply♪
♪HYO: I'm a sava savage,
your love is rare♪
♪LEE YEONTAE: Doesn't even satisfy
you like that year wasn't even close♪
♪LEE YEONTAE: I'ma slay,
I'ma chill, I'ma kill♪
♪YANG CHENGXI: From now on,
it's a twist♪
♪WILLIAM: Pull the trigger,
ya pull pull♪
♪LEE YUNSUNG: We are
all psycho fantasy fighters♪
♪KIM JEONGHOON: Throw
all the appearance away♪
♪HYO, LEE YEONTAE, WILLIAM:
See the end, see the end♪
♪KIM JEONGHOON: Now
take a shot, take a shot♪
♪KIM JEONGHOON: No hard feelings♪
(Satisfied)
He's good at singing.
♪BAN DANIEL: Enough, enough♪
♪HYO: Cruel and beautiful
love killa, love killa♪
♪IKUTO: Love killa♪
♪HYO: Beautiful love killa, love killa♪
♪IKUTO: The moment
we aimed at each other♪
IKUTO!
♪YANG CHENGXI: As you know
we can never let each other go♪
(Great, YANG CHENGXI)
♪WILLIAM: This kind of love,
this kind of situation♪
♪WILLIAM: A person who can handle it♪
♪IKUTO: You know that♪
♪WILLIAM: You always♪
♪HYO, LEE YEONTAE, CHOI YOHAN:
Look at the end, look at the end♪
♪WILLIAM: I don't think that's bad♪
♪WILLIAM: No hard feelings♪
♪HYO, LEE YEONTAE, CHOI YOHAN:
Check 'em out, check 'em out♪
♪WILLIAM: Next we have to run♪
♪KIM JEONGHOON, IKUTO: Cruel and beautiful,
(baby, no) love killa, love killa♪
♪KIM JEONGHOON: Beautiful
love killa, love killa♪
♪KIM JEONGHOON, IKUTO: Beautiful,
(no, no, no, Killa, no) love killa, love killa♪
♪IKUTO: The moment
we aimed at each other♪
♪LEE YEONTAE: Cruel and beautiful
love killa, love killa♪
♪WILLIAM: I'm falling in♪
♪CHOI YOHAN: Hush, hush♪
♪CHOI YOHAN: I'ma take you down♪
♪HYO: Oh I'm sorry,
did I make you anxious♪
(Well done, IKUTO)
(Satisfied)
KAI: They are completely different
from what I saw at the mid-check.
KAI: We were thinking
that we would definitely win.
KAI: It's a big deal.
KAI: I thought we
really need to do well.
(Well done, MY MONSTAZ!)
Well done.
It's ending with HYO's abs!
(Surprised)
Oh, right. His abs are really defined.
Did he contour his abs?
(MY MONSTAZ, HYO)
(MY MONSTAZ, CHOI YOHAN)
(MY MONSTAZ, LEE YEONTAE)
(MY MONSTAZ, IKUTO)
(MY MONSTAZ, WILLIAM)
(MY MONSTAZ, LEE YUNSUNG)
(MY MONSTAZ, BAN DANIEL)
(MY MONSTAZ, YANG CHENGXI)
(MY MONSTAZ, KIM JEONGHOON)
You just watched MY MONSTAZ Team's
"Love Killa" performance.
MONSTA X HYUNGWON: With a performance like that,
MONSTA X HYUNGWON: it's impossible not
to use all strengths.
MONSTA X KIHYUN: No choice. We were like that too.
MONSTA X KIHYUN: Even just looking at the comeback stage.
MONSTA X HYUNGWON: You almost tried to break the floor.
MONSTA X KIHYUN: SHOWNU really broke it, right?
B:MY BOYZ Round 2.
13 vs13 Team Death Match.
Let's check out the "Shoot Out".
Prepared by the MONSTA B team.
(MONSTA B, fighting)
Fighting.
I think it will be cool.
It will be cool.
Ah, this intro is really...
(Full of anticipation)
It's amazing.
Fighting.
KAI: We'll bring the heat and erase
the memory of the last "Love Killa".
YANG HYEONBIN: We will win this time.
WILLIAM: MOON JAEIL is scary.
(MONSTA B's No.1 threat: MOON JAEIL)
MOON JAEIL is so scary.
KIM JEONGHOON: MOON JAEIL alone is
enough to stress us out. I'm so anxious.
MONSTA X HYUNGWON: Wouldn't
"Shoot Out" have been harder?
MONSTA X KIHYUN: Honestly,
it's okay if we don't do live vocals.
MONSTA X KIHYUN: Remember?
Whenever we practiced,
MONSTA X KIHYUN: I almost passed out.
("Shoot Out", even hard for MONSTA X)
MONSTA X KIHYUN: My head feels oxygen-starved.
(Can MONSTA B Team do well?)
("Shoot Out" original song: MONSTA X)
Oh, wow.
♪ALL: Walker, walker, walker, growling♪
(So cool)
Oh.
♪ALL: Walker, walker, walker♪
(As expected, MOON JAEIL)
Oh.
♪ALL: Walker, walker, walker♪
♪ALL: Walker, walker, walker, growling♪
♪HWANG HEEWOO: Excuse
me, I'm walkin' like zombie uh♪
(Wow, what is it?!)
♪HWANG HEEWOO: Half dead, going
crazy, jumping up jumpin' uh♪
♪HWANG HEEWOO: Remember it forever,
hand shapes like guns, blokka blokka♪
♪HWANG HEEWOO: I've become an obstacle
in front of you choppa choppa♪
♪HIROTO: Blakk blakk blakk.
Can't block block block♪
♪HIROTO: You're blah
blah blah stop ta, talking♪
♪HIROTO: Burst the feelings
that have left♪
♪HIROTO: Without hesitation
pop pop pop it all♪
Right.
Good.
♪HIROTO: Burst
the emotions that have left♪
♪HIROTO: Without
hesitation pop pop pop it all♪
♪KIM BOHYEON: Never gonna stop this♪
♪KIM BOHYEON: You go without hesitation♪
♪KIM BOHYEON: I'll now let go
of the string I was holding drop♪
Oh, so cool.
♪MOON JAEIL: Half out of my mind♪
♪MOON JAEIL: Dragging
heavy legs as I walk♪
♪SUTHASCHAI, AI: I'm
lost, what should I do? (Ah)♪
♪HARUTO: In the twilight
without you, until dawn♪
♪HARUTO: This grip
on my ankle, it's farewell♪
Good, good.
JINHO: He even winked during that.
(Charm emission)
(Target hit completed)
♪HWANG HEEWOO: Wobbling
precariously in the darkness♪
Let's go, MOON JAEIL!
♪MOON JAEIL: Shoot out
shoot out shoot out for me♪
♪MOON JAEIL: Fiercely shoot
out shoot out shoot out♪
♪KAI: If it's all over anyway,
if your heart has already left♪
♪KAI: Throwing away all
hope, leaving none behind♪
♪SUTHASCHAI: Shoot out
shoot out shoot out for me♪
♪SUTHASCHAI: In one shot,
shoot out shoot out shoot out♪
That's right!
♪YANG HYEONBIN: They
say it will come someday♪
♪YANG HYEONBIN: But
it sounds even more cruel♪
♪HWANG HEEWOO: Hurry, make it colder♪
♪ALL: Growling! Walker, walker, walker♪
♪ALL: Walker, walker, walker♪
♪YANG HYEONBIN: In the twilight
without you, until dawn♪
♪YANG HYEONBIN: This grip
on my ankle, it's farewell♪
♪SUTHASCHAI: Wobbling
precariously in the darkness♪
Main singer puppy.
♪AI: Shoot out shoot out
shoot out for me♪
♪AI: Fiercely shoot
out shoot out shoot out♪
♪HARUTO: If it's all over anyway,
if your heart has already left♪
♪HARUTO: Throwing away all
hope, leaving none behind♪
♪SUTHASCHAI: Shoot out
shoot out shoot out for me♪
♪SUTHASCHAI: In one shot,
shoot out shoot out shoot out♪
YUJU: It's okay.
(Worried)
♪AI: But it sounds even more cruel♪
♪HIROTO: Hurry, make it colder♪
♪KAI, HIROTO: Fire♪
♪KAI, HIROTO: Right now with your mouth♪
♪KAI, HIROTO: Shoot the word
"end" into my heart♪
(Heart attack)
♪YANG HYEONBIN, HARUTO: Fire♪
♪YANG HYEONBIN, HARUTO:
End this hell-like hope♪
♪MOON JAEIL: Shoot out
shoot out shoot out for me♪
(Surprised) ♪MOON JAEIL: In one shot,
shoot out shoot out shoot out♪
♪YANG HYEONBIN: If it's all over
anyway, if your heart has already left♪
♪YANG HYEONBIN: Throwing away
all hope, leaving none behind♪
♪HARUTO: Shoot out
shoot out shoot out for me♪
♪HARUTO: Fiercely shoot
out shoot out shoot out♪
♪MOON JAEIL: They
say it will come someday♪
♪MOON JAEIL: But it
sounds even more cruel♪
(True to MOON JAEIL,
he flaunted his charm!)
JINHO: Look at the gaze.
♪MOON JAEIL: It sounds even more cruel♪
♪KIM BOHYEON: Hurry, make it colder♪
Guilty, guilty.
(Perfect)
(MOON JAEIL is praised by Master LEE YUJEONG)
MOON JAEIL really nailed the details.
YUJU: MOON JAEIL's vocals
are really solid.
(Approved by the masters,
B:MY BOYZ's all-rounder, MOON JAEIL)
(The performance of MONSTA B Team,
poured out without any regrets)
(MONSTA B, YANG HYEONBIN)
(MONSTA B, AI)
AI: I think I could have done more.
There are some regrets.
MOON JAEIL: Not the best,
but I think we did a good job.
MOON JAEIL: Still I feel relieved
thinking that we did as usual.
MC DEX: You just watched MONSTA B
team's Shoot Out performance.
MC DEX: Seeing the B:GINNERs' faces after the stage,
it looks like they're going through a whirlwind of emotions.
(MONSTA B, MY MONSTAZ)
I'm so curious about what MONSTA X members
thought of the performance just now.
(A stage of Love Killa where sexy vibes are essential)
This song really emphasizes the sexy vibe,
and you all created
MONSTA X HYUNGWON: such a great atmosphere
that I completely forgot about the age difference.
The only downside was
(Tension)
MONSTA X HYUNGWON: that the performance
seemed a bit too forceful at times,
MONSTA X HYUNGWON: but if you
just consider that as a minor detail,
(The Love Killa team, who seemed a bit tense on stage)
MONSTA X HYUNGWON: I think it would be perfect.
MONSTA X KIHYUN:
Actually, when I saw on the profile that
B:GINNER BAN DANIEL is 14 years old,
MONSTA X KIHYUN: I wondered
if he could handle a song like Love Killa.
MONSTA X KIHYUN: I was really worried,
but he did it so well.
(Stage manners that make
it hard to believe his age)
MONSTA X KIHYUN: In that short part,
his sudden focus really impressed me,
(The highest praise)
and I realized I was worrying for nothing.
(BAN DANIEL blushing like
the unmistakable 14-year-old)
(So proud of him)
LIA KIM: It wasn't even a highlight part,
just a transition, but he brought it to life.
BAN DANIEL: I was so happy to meet
the seniors I look up to, and I felt even better
BAN DANIEL: when KIHYUN gave me
a compliment. Thank you so much.
MONSTA X KIHYUN: B:GINNER LEE YEONTAE
really drew attention
MONSTA X KIHYUN: throughout
the entire performance.
(B:GINNER LEE YEONTAE stole
the spotlight from the center)
MONSTA X KIHYUN: I was
listening through the in-ears,
MONSTA X KIHYUN: and you really
kept your vocal tone in sync.
(Happy) LEE YEONTAE: I didn't
expect my name to be called.
LEE YEONTAE: It felt like
my hard work had paid off.
Alright then now...
(Feedback on MONSTA B team's stage for Shoot Out?)
we'd like to hear your evaluation
of Monsta B team's Shoot Out performance.
MONSTA X SHOWNU: First of all, the intro is
a very important part of the song.
(The intense impact
of the Shoot Out intro)
MONSTA X KIHYUN: As soon as it started,
I thought, 'This is a winning stage!'
(A performance that captivated MONSTA X from the start)
♪What?♪
(Satisfied)
I felt it right away.
MONSTA X KIHYUN: It was a stage
I really wanted to praise,
MONSTA X KIHYUN: but since
it's such a tough song,
MONSTA X KIHYUN:
there was a sense that the vocals
MONSTA X KIHYUN: and dance started
to fall apart toward the end.
(Vocals that weakened in the latter half)
♪Shoot out, Shoot out♪
MONSTA X KIHYUN: Despite some
off-notes, I have to say I really admired
(KIHYUN giving constructive feedback and support)
how confidently and powerfully they sang.
SUTHASCHAI: I felt a bit sad. If
I had done my part a little better,
SUTHASCHAI: I think the team could
have received a better evaluation.
MONSTA X KIHYUN: And
B:GINNER MOON JAEIL,
you did a great job on stage.
Thank you.
When doing your part,
MONSTA X KIHYUN: it felt like you
truly made the song your own.
♪Shoot out, shoot out, shoot out♪
(MOON JAEIL delivered a highly
immersive stage for MONBEBE)
MONSTA X KIHYUN: I think you did
an amazing job on stage,
MONSTA X KIHYUN: so I really
enjoyed your performance.
MOON JAEIL: Getting a compliment from senior
KIHYUN made me feel like I owned the world.
I felt so good.
PENTAGON HUI: While MY MONSTAZ team has
B:GINNER YEONTAE, MONSTA B team has JAEIL.
PENTAGON HUI: That shows how well both teams'
center members pulled off their parts.
LIA KIM: What's great about JAEIL is when
I give a direction, he does it right away.
(Oh)
(More growth expected in the future)
He change it right away.
(B:GINNER MOON JAEIL)
But that isn't easy.
MONSTA X HYUNGWON:
B:GINNER YANG HYEONBIN.
(Bouncing)
MONSTA X HYUNGWON:Your deltoids stood out,
MONSTA X HYUNGWON: but I especially liked
the intensity in your eyes during your part.
♪To the end of the world♪
(YANG HYEONBIN had a
strong presence despite a short part)
MONSTA X HYUNGWON:
When performing in a group,
MONSTA X HYUNGWON: it's crucial to
highlight your own charm in a brief part,
MONSTA X HYUNGWON: and I feel
that was especially noticeable here.
YANG HYEONBIN: I felt incredibly happy.
YANG HYEONBIN: Honestly,
I have no regrets even if I were to die tomorrow.
(13 VS 13 Team Death Match,
title song stage over)
(Great job)
You really nailed it.
Thank you for your hard work.
MONSTA X KIHYUN:
It must really be tough.
(Around the end of verse 2, haha)
It gets really tough near the end.
(The original singer confirmed, Shoot Out
is indeed quite hard to perform) This is so hard.
Hard, hard, seriously hard.
YANG HYEONBIN: It was a bit disappointing,
but honestly, it was better than I expected.
(Time to leave the stage
putting regrets aside)
(Time to leave the stage putting regrets aside)
Thank you.
(Good job, B:GINNERs)
LEE YEONTAE: The center position changed the most,
and a lot of the parts were changed as well.
LEE YUNSUNG: I feel a bit regretful, but I feel
satisfied because I showed us doing our best.
HIROTO: There are a lot of regrets, but
I have no regrets because I worked hard.
KIM BOHYEON: I would be truly grateful if you
could look upon us with kind and supportive eyes.
KIM JEONGHOON: We passed the first round
with some anxiety, and even now,
KIM JEONGHOON: while struggling
and sometimes shedding tears,
KIM JEONGHOON: we've led the team without
giving up and pushed ourselves to 150% together.
KIM JEONGHOON: So, I'm quite
satisfied with our effort.
MOON JAEIL: MONSTA B, you worked very hard,
MOON JAEIL: and I'm really thankful
for keeping up although it wasn't easy.
MONSTA B, fighting.
KAI: Well done, everyone. Great job.
(A title song battle
fueled by sweat and passion)
(Round 2: 13 vs 13, Team Death Match)
B:MY BOYZ 13 vs 13 Team Death Match.
(First title song match of the three matches completed)
The first title song match has ended.
(Second round of the 13 vs 13 Team Death Match)
Let's move on to the second battle.
(Vocal match)
We're starting the vocal match now.
(Vocal match,
MY MONSTAZ VS MONSTA B)
SEO JUNHYEOK: Since this team
mission is crucial for all of us,
SEO JUNHYEOK: my mindset is
to outperform the MONSTA B team!
LIM JIHWAN: We can't just go home
like this. We have to grit our teeth.
and definitely beat MONSTA B!
KANG JUNSEONG: Since we've
been practicing nonstop until now,
KANG JUNSEONG: I think we have a good
chance of winning the live vocal match.
We can do better than MY MONSTAZ!
The B:GINNER representing
MY MONSTAZ will open the vocal battle.
Please come up on stage.
(The team that wins the Team Death Match survived all)
This is really a matter of
(The team that lost the Team Death Match)
win or lose, huh?
(The team that lost the Team Death Match
is all elimination candidates)
(I absolutely refuse to lose!)
I hated the idea of losing, no matter what.
JANG WON: Since our team's stronger,
(MY MONSTAZ)
we're going to come out on top!
(The second vocal match is just as intense as ever)
We'll begin with team introductions.
We'll greet you now, two, three.
- Hello.
- We are
- your spring days.
(Spring has come!)
Oh.
MONSTA X KIHYUN: Just hearing
their voice already gets me excited.
MC DEX: You really
came dressed like spring.
LIA KIM: Wow, pink outfit is so pretty.
SECHAN suits very well.
(Cute)
SECHAN kind of sings like the Little Prince,
(Pink prince)
with a delicate and tender heart...
PENTAGON HUI: When SECHAN sings,
- PENTAGON HUI: he has that unique boyish charm, you know?
- YUJU: That's right!
- PENTAGON HUI: That part suddenly hits me right in the feels.
(Sympathy)
This is my first time seeing him sing.
Oh, really?
(First? Shocking firm statement)
Oh.
(In unanimous agreement, SECHAN sang during the mid-check)
- He sang back then. - During the mid-chcek.
(Frontal lobe loading)
(Did I... see it?)
Don't you remember?
(Hiding the embarrassing memory with my hand)
Excuse me, sir.
(An embarrassing memory he covers with his hands)
- He sang. - You should watch first and...
(Round 2 competition D-11 Mid-check)
♪From the place where I said this?♪
(A gaze so fierce, I could barely look away)
♪I want to see you♪
(On top of that, the highest praise...)
It's so good, you were born with it.
(Omega-3 bulk purchase vibes)
If you don't remember...
I'm sorry.
MONSTA X KIHYUN: All four
of you have amazing voices.
(Moved, moved)
Already...
MONSTA X KIHYUN: I heard you reinterpreted
Spring Day instead of doing it exactly like the original.
(Q. How was Spring Day reinterpreted?)
How did you approach it?
SEO JUNHYEOK: When we looked
at the lyrics of the song,
SEO JUNHYEOK: we felt like it was about
singing for the people or things we miss.
(Smiling) All the members
thought about the people they miss,
and we decided to sing it that way.
So, we arranged the song
in a more ballad-like style and prepared it.
MC DEX: I think it might be a serenade
towards the "fans in front of us here"?
(What does Spring Day
mean to MY MONSTAZ?)
(Round 2 competition, 0-17,
MY MONSTAZ's practice room)
LEE JUNMYEONG: We have to arrange this.
LIM JIHWAN: Yeah, we have to
make it 3 minutes and 30 seconds.
(Ah!)
LIM JIHWAN: The vocal team
has to arrange the original song,
LIM JIHWAN: and we're in charge of things
like concept, direction, and arrangement.
LIM JIHWAN: That way, we can
create the stage we want to perform.
LIM JIHWAN: I felt that doing this would make
it easier to express the kind of stage I want to do.
First of all, I...
(Original song: Spring Day by BTS)
(A message to youth: Life may
be hard, but never lose hope)
(A lyrical and wistful original song)
(Focusing)
SEO JUNHYEOK: The keywords are
infinite love, unconditional love.
SEO JUNHYEOK: And what I mean is,
I've actually felt that kind of love.
SEO JUNHYEOK: Our fans love us without
conditions, and seeing how they continue to
SEO JUNHYEOK: support us even now... it
really made me realize how deep that love is.
LEE JUNMYEONG: Nice.
Kind of like a fan song.
(Agree)
Oh, it's a fan song.
PARK SECHAN: The intro begins with a soft
piano version of our climax melody...
SEO JUNHYEOK: We begin
with a rich orchestral sound,
SEO JUNHYEOK: and then it eases into
a softer orchestral section.
PARK SECHAN: We went
through a lot of reference videos,
PARK SECHAN: and personally, I was
really drawn to the orchestral ones.
PARK SECHAN: That led us to transform a K-pop
song into a ballad-style piece,
PARK SECHAN: a fan song, made with love.
LEE JUNMYEONG: I really
like the orchestra part,
LEE JUNMYEONG: but I hope
the chorus has more impact.
What if we layered the harmonies there?
(And the Spring Day team's
musical ideas just keep flowing)Good, I love it.
(Arranged as a song dedicated entirely to our fans)
A back-and-forth would work great.
(Arrangement direction is getting clearer)
When one person sings powerfully, and someone
(Passion) follows with "Looks like the
cherry blossoms are blooming".
- That sounds really cool.
- Yeah, that's right.
(Serious)
LEE JUNMYEONG: Would it be good?
(Our team is so awesome)
LIM JIHWAN: Since chances
like this are rare, I felt thrilled.
SEO JUNHYEOK: I thought
if we went with this vibe,
SEO JUNHYEOK: we could
create a truly legendary stage.
(Mid-check)
Hello. We are 'Spring Day' team.
Go for it.
(What kind of evaluation will the Spring Day team receive?)
Shall we listen?
This is making me nervous.
(Even the masters in charge are nervous)
I am really all nervous...
(Sweet piano intro, Spring Day
arranged by B:GINNERs)
KIM BOHYEON: They really
nailed the arrangement here.
♪I miss you♪
(B:GINNER PARK SECHAN calmly starts)
♪Saying this makes me miss you even more♪
(Oh)
♪Such a cruel time♪
(SEO JUNHYEOK gathers emotions thinking of the fans)
♪I feel like seeing each other♪
♪Has become difficult♪
(LEE JUNMYEONG's continuing emotional rap)
♪It's all winter here, even in June, winter comes♪
(Good emotion)
♪My heart runs through time♪
(Nods)
♪The Snowpiercer left all alone♪
(At last, Spring Day moving toward the climax)
♪Beyond the cold winter's end♪
(Layering harmonies carefully)
♪Until spring comes again♪
♪Until the flowers bloom♪
♪Stay there a little longer♪
♪Stay♪
Oh, they practiced a lot.
Good.
Thank you.
PENTAGON JINHO: I don't think the team
has any major issues with the vocals.
(Received praise)
(Spring Day team, though... the concept)
But the concept feels a bit off...
(Feeling anxious)
I think the concept is off.
But I think the fan song concept is...
Yes.
PENTAGON JINHO: If you guys
wanted to really express thanks
PENTAGON JINHO: to the fans
through the arrangement,
PENTAGON JINHO: the movements
on stage needed to match that feeling.
PENTAGON JINHO: But as it is, I don't get
PENTAGON JINHO: why you
used that first formation,
stayed still in the middle,
PENTAGON JINHO: and then suddenly moved
and linked arms at the end...
It just looked like a friendship song.
It doesn't feel like a fan song at all!
PENTAGON JINHO: If you chose that
arrangement direction, you should stick to it.
Yes.
PARK SECHAN: Our initial goal was a fan song,
PARK SECHAN: but because it was starting
to feel more like a friendship song,
PARK SECHAN: the atmosphere seems to have
shifted to a more serious tone after the mid-check.
(After mid-check vocal class)
Guys, you worked hard.
- Hello.
So,
about our song lyrics.
Yes.
YUJU: What's the line
that keeps repeating?
"I miss you."
(Lyrics repeated "I miss you")
"I miss you", right?
- Yes.
YUJU: Out of all
the "I miss you" lyrics,
none of them really touched my heart.
(PARK SECHAN is calm but lacks feelings)
♪I miss you, saying this makes me miss you even more♪
(Self-blame)
YUJU: I think that's more serious
than being off-pitch or off-beat.
PARK SECHAN: Vocally, I found it difficult
because I'm younger than the others,
PARK SECHAN: expressing feelings
in the song was a bit challenging.
YUJU: Shall SECHAN try
singing it again first?
-♪How...♪
♪How long must I wait♪
♪How many more nights must I stay awake♪
♪How long♪
It doesn't feel like
forcing the singing.
(YUJU sings to help understanding)
♪How long must I wait♪
(Oh, cool)
Just look here.
Try it.
(Looking afar)
Like taking a deep breath.
♪How, how long♪
(Right)
Lower your arms and relax.
Shall we just relax
and try walking a bit while we do it?
(Why is she laughing?)
I think we need to prohibit
SECHAN from answering.
It seems like you're
freezing up while answering.
(Answering "Yes" silently)
Just say it like 'uh' and give it a try.
♪How, how♪
Shall we walk a bit? Sing while walking.
♪How long must I wait♪
(Sorry, SECHAN)
(Our SECHAN)
You are a trainee now.
YUJU: SECHAN, you have a really
good voice but the problem is,
if this happens
while filming the music video,
(Unintentional lip-sync)
wouldn't it mess things up?
Try imagining you're
filming a music video.
(Mini Spring Day MV)
(Main actor, PARK SECHAN)
(Supporting actor, LEE JUNMYEONG)
♪How long♪
♪Must I wait♪
♪How many more nights♪
♪Must I stay awake♪
♪How many more nights must I stay awake♪
♪Until I can see you♪
But you did well, SECHAN,
I'm sorry I laughed.
YUJU: From the start,
it was really good.
PARK SECHAN: After taking YUJU's class,
I know all details, and I'm thankful.
(Lacking emotions, PARK SECHAN
further devotes to practice)
(Got help from the older
members on the tricky parts)
PARK SECHAN: JUNHYEOK, JUNMYEONG, and JIHWAN,
who lead our vocal team, have helped me.
PARK SECHAN: Even when I'm struggling,
they encourage me, which warms my heart,
PARK SECHAN: and motivates
me to work harder.
PARK SECHAN: We're working hard
to create a stage where we all shine.
LIM JIHWAN: I trust our team. We will
definitely win the Round 2 mission,
and with passionate hearts chasing dream
together, these are precious moments.
LEE JUNMYEONG: I really hope
we win with strong friendship.
Here's Spring Day performance
reinterpreted by MY MONSTAZ.
SEO JUNHYEOK: It is really for the fans,
especially for the B:IN US fans,
SEO JUNHYEOK: and I wanted to
express my gratitude through this song.
SEO JUNHYEOK: Let's do this.
LIM JIHWAN: We can do it.
PARK SECHAN: Please,
let's debut for real.
PARK SECHAN: Don't be nervous,
just do what we always do,
PARK SECHAN: and keep
the emotions in check until the end.
(Worry)
Oh, please do well.
LIA KIM: I'm more
nervous about the vocals.
YUJU: If the voice wavers even a little,
it'll be immediately noticeable.
(Spring Day, Original Song by BTS)
♪PARK SECHAN: I miss you♪
♪PARK SECHAN: Saying it like
this makes me miss you more♪
♪PARK SECHAN: I miss you♪
♪PARK SECHAN: Even when
I'm looking at your photos♪
♪PARK SECHAN: I miss you♪
♪SEO JUNHYEOK: Such a heartless time♪
♪SEO JUNHYEOK: Even just
seeing your face once♪
♪SEO JUNHYEOK: Now it's hard for us♪
♪LEE JUNMYEONG: It's all winter here♪
♪LEE JUNMYEONG: Winter
comes even in August♪
♪LEE JUNMYEONG: My
heart races through time♪
♪LEE JUNMYEONG:
The snowpiercer left alone♪
♪LIM JIHWAN: Holding your hand,
I travel to the other side of the Earth♪
♪LIM JIHWAN: I want to end this winter♪
♪LIM JIHWAN: How much
longing must fall like snow♪
♪LIM JIHWAN: For that
spring day to come, friend♪
♪LEE JUNMYEONG: Like the small dust♪
♪LEE JUNMYEONG: floating in the air♪
♪LIM JIHWAN: If I were
the snow blowing in the wind♪
♪LIM JIHWAN: just a little faster♪
♪LIM JIHWAN: I could reach you♪
♪SEO JUNHYEOK: Snowflakes are falling♪
They are doing really great.
♪SEO JUNHYEOK: I miss you♪
♪PARK SECHAN, LEE JUNMYEONG,
LIM JIHWAN: I miss you♪
♪SEO JUNHYEOK: I miss you♪
♪PARK SECHAN, LEE JUNMYEONG,
LIM JIHWAN: I miss you♪
♪PARK SECHAN: How long must I wait♪
♪PARK SECHAN: How many
more nights must I stay awake♪
♪PARK SECHAN: Until I can see you♪
♪SEO JUNHYEOK, LIM JIHWAN,
LEE JUNMYEONG: Can I see you♪
♪PARK SECHAN: Will I meet you♪
♪SEO JUNHYEOK, LIM JIHWAN,
LEE JUNMYEONG: Will I meet you♪
JANG WON: They are performing
better than in rehearsal.
♪ALL: Beyond the end of the cold winter♪
♪ALL: Until spring days come again♪
♪ALL: Until the flowers bloom♪
♪SEO JUNHYEOK: Stay
there a little longer♪
♪SEO JUNHYEOK: Please stay♪
♪PARK SECHAN: You know it all♪
♪LIM JIHWAN: You know it all♪
♪LEE JUNMYEONG: You're my best friend♪
♪SEO JUNHYEOK: You're my best friend♪
♪LIM JIHWAN: The morning
will come again♪
♪PARK SECHAN: No darkness♪
♪SEO JUNHYEOK: Can last forever♪
(Awesome)
(Surprised)
JUNHYEOK is almost...
JUNMYEONG, let's go!
♪LEE JUNMYEONG, SEO JUNHYEOK: Looks like
the cherry blossoms are blooming♪
♪LEE JUNMYEONG: This winter will end♪
♪PARK SECHAN, LIM JIHWAN: I miss you♪
♪PARK SECHAN, SEO JUNHYEOK: I miss you♪
LEE YUNSUNG: Why am I feeling
so emotional? I feel like crying.
♪PARK SECHAN, SEO JUNHYEOK: I miss you♪
♪LIM JIHWAN, LEE JUNMYEONG:
Just wait a little longer, just wait♪
♪LIM JIHWAN: If I stay
up just a few more nights♪
♪LIM JIHWAN: I'll come to meet you♪
♪PARK SECHAN, LEE JUNMYEONG:
I'll come to meet you♪
♪LIM JIHWAN: I'll pick you up♪
♪PARK SECHAN, LEE JUNMYEONG:
I'll pick you up♪
♪ALL: Passing through the cold winter♪
♪ALL: Until the day spring comes again♪
♪ALL: Until the flowers bloom♪
♪LEE JUNMYEONG, LIM JIHWAN:
Stay there a little longer♪
♪LEE JUNMYEONG, LIM JIHWAN: Please stay♪
(PARK SECHAN)
(LIM JIHWAN)
(LEE JUNMYEONG)
(SEO JUNHYEOK)
I watched it without breathing.
(A stage that took her breath away in a different way)
- Well done. - Well done.
JINHO: JUNHYEOK has such
a stable and comforting voice.
(A vocal stage recognized by masters)
JUNHYEOK certainly sings very well.
(What is TOP IDOL
MONSTA X's evaluation?)
Yes, well, that sounded
really good. And now,
MONSTA X KIHYUN: our
B:GINNER LIM JIHWAN.
MONSTA X KIHYUN: Were you
very nervous at first?
(Surprised)MONSTA X KIHYUN: Were you
LIM JIHWAN: Yes, I was very nervous.
(The voice was trembling from beginning)
♪How much more must it snow like this♪
LIM JIHWAN: It was a mistake...
I could tell while singing.
LIM JIHWAN: I started wondering
if it showed too much.
MONSTA X KIHYUN:
I could feel the tension,
MONSTA X KIHYUN: but you seemed to relax
a bit towards the end, right?
LIM JIHWAN: Yes, I got really immersed.
(LIM JIHWAN was singing so well)
You were singing so amazingly.
MONSTA X KIHYUN: So don't be nervous,
MONSTA X KIHYUN: and I'd like you to trust
yourself more and be more confident.
(Awesome)
Wow.
KANG JUNSEONG: The main
vocal praised the singing.
(I'm jealous)
MONSTA X KIHYUN: Our
B:GINNER LEE JUNMYEONG
(Praise them again)
was singing so well.
Thank you.
MONSTA X KIHYUN: The way you changed
your tone to match the song was amazing.
(A voice that changes together)
♪Here it's all winter♪
(With the song atmosphere)
(Exceeded praise limits)
You really sounded like a professional singer.
Thank you.
Oh, professional singer.
(Awesome)
Wow.
- That's really high praise.
- They must be so happy.
MONSTA X KIHYUN: B:GINNER
SEO JUNHYEOK nailed the high notes.
♪I miss you♪
MONSTA X KIHYUN: but,
MONSTA X KIHYUN: about
the falsetto part,
I was really surprised
by how well he handled it.
(Soft falsetto like cotton candy)
♪I miss you♪
MONSTA X KIHYUN:
It's that kind of refined sound
MONSTA X KIHYUN: that usually takes
several takes in the recording studio,
MONSTA X KIHYUN: but I haven't seen it
in a live performance for a long time.
(A flood of overwhelming praise)
The falsetto was just amazing.
(Totally agree)
SEO JUNHYEOK: He said,
"The singing is so refined and good,
SEO JUNHYEOK: it could
come out of a recording studio."
SEO JUNHYEOK: That made me think
SEO JUNHYEOK: I can be a bit
more confident in my vocals.
MONSTA X KIHYUN: And our
B:GINNER PARK SECHAN.
(The final praise, your voice is art!)
Your voice is pure art.
(Moved by artistic praise)
Thank you.
MONSTA X HYUNGWON:
I really love pop music,
(I want to collaborate with you)
and I think you have
(Seeking for collaborating together)
such an amazing voice
MONSTA X HYUNGWON: that
I'd love to work with you next time.
Wow! Really?
KANG JUNSEONG: That's an honor.
MONSTA X HYUNGWON: I really
hope to meet you next time.
Thank you.
PARK SECHAN: Though my
trainee period was short,
PARK SECHAN: today will be
the most memorable moment.
(Today's TOP PICK)
It was amazing.
He'd love to collaborate with him.
Wow, truly high praise.
YUJU: SECHAN won't be able to sleep
today because he's so happy.
PENTAGON HUI: If SECHAN keeps training,
he'll really become an amazing singer.
PENTAGON HUI: His tone is just great.
Why aren't you happy?
No, I'm happy.
No, that's not it.
(I was kind of... Smiling though, why?)
(That's quite an awkward excuse)
You went, 'Oh,' and then...
(MONSTA B, his side's stage)
(MY MONSTAZ, the other side's stage)
Ah...
(It naturally happens like that)
Oh really? Okay.
(I'm just joking)
(At that time, the MONSTA B
vocal team lost their smile)
Wow, such high praise...
Ah, we...
I'm really scared.
KANG JUNSEONG: I think today, out
of all the rehearsals and check-ins,
KANG JUNSEONG: Spring Day
team did the best.
(MY MONSTAZ completed
the stage successfully)
MONSTA X KIHYUN: Earlier, the Love Killa team
and the Spring Day team are the same team, right?
MONSTA X KIHYUN: Ah, this is hard.
(Spring Day team is good?)
That's what I'm saying.
It's over.
PARK SECHAN: Our team
received a lot of praise,
PARK SECHAN: so I think
it means we did better.
PARK SECHAN: For the vocal match,
I believe our team has the upper hand.
(The two teams meet backstage)
You did great on the broadcast.
Well done.
(The two teams meet backstage)
LI ZHIWEI: The Spring Day team has unique
voices, and each one is really great.
LI ZHIWEI: They all did an amazing job.
KANG JUNSEONG: I felt like the Spring Day
team next to us was doing so well too.
KANG JUNSEONG: Maybe that's
why my confidence dropped a bit,
KANG JUNSEONG: and this time,
I ended up getting really nervous.
(13VS13 Team Death Match)
Yes then, MONSTA B, please take the stage.
JANG WON: I felt a bit anxious
because the Spring Day team's
JANG WON: individual vocal skills
seemed relatively better,
JANG WON: but still, I thought
our team could do well too,
so it was worth a shot.
MONSTA X KIHYUN: I'm really
curious about this team.
(Second vocal match) KANG JUNSEONG: Anyway,
we have to show everything in one moment,
KANG JUNSEONG: so I thought we
needed to stay calm and focused.
KANG JUNSEONG: I made up my
mind to strengthen my mindset.
(The fiercely prepared
'You Were Beautiful' team)
He was really good.
I was confident
we'd win in vocals, but...
(The Spring Day team is getting anxious)
They're kind of making us nervous.
(The vocal battle is getting fiercer)
It's actually not easy to perform this well.
(And)
(The final match of Round 2)
The last showdown of the team death match.
(Masters and B:GINNERs in deep thought)
How about you work on the concept a bit?
Is there a way for us to shine together?
(Mega performance, what's MY MONSTAZ’s killer move?)
Oh, that's nice.
You guys did well.
Is there a way to make
it more technical?
(MONSTA B, going stronger
unlike their opponents)
(KAI just can't help being playful)
Extremely heavy.
(Those who smile through
hardship are a top team)
(One song, two styles,
mega performance showdown)
(Break into MONSTA X's heart without permission)
Wow, why are they so good?
Wow, they did well.
This is...
(Losers face total elimination, who will win Round 2?)
Wow, they stole my heart.