(Round 3 starts now!)
(Who is the MC that appeared
with dazzling lights?)
(Two people today?)
(Finally seeing the two-shot,
unable to close their mouth)
MC MIYEON: The mega global audition
for the next-generation K-POP group.
MC MIYEON: Who is your boy?
MC MIYEON: B:MY BOYZ.
MC MIYEON: Hello,
I'm B:MY BOYZ MC MIYEON.
(Princess MIYEON)
(Nice to meet you)
MC DEX: Hello, I'm MC DEX.
(Finally meeting the two MCs both on the stage)
MC DEX: Ah, finally meeting you.
MC MIYEON: Yes, exactly.
MC MIYEON: Seeing you
on stage like this feels new.
(Round 3 we want to see as much as the 2 MCs)
MC DEX: Then, let me introduce the 3rd round
MC DEX: in which the B:GINNERs
will be evaluated today.
(B:MY BOYZ Round 3)
MC MIYEON: In B:MY BOYZ Round 3,
(Who is the TOP IDOL?)
MC MIYEON: the TOP IDOL is...
(Who is it?)
MC MIYEON: It's WANNA ONE.
(B:MY BOYZ Round 3 TOP IDOL WANNA ONE,
from selection to debut, an unprecedented impact)
(With visuals that turned
the entire nation into producers,)
(a perfect hexagon idol group
with no weaknesses in vocals or dance)
(The wannabe of boy group auditions)
(TOP IDOL WANNA ONE)
Our legendary idols, WANNA ONE.
(WANNA ONE HA SUNGWOON)
WANNA ONE HA SUNGWOON: Ah, hello. I'm HA SUNGWOON. Nice to meet you.
(WANNA ONE LEE DAEHWI)
WANNA ONE LEE DAEHWI: Hello, I'm LEE DAEHWI. Nice to meet you.
(WANNA ONE PARK WOOJIN)
WANNA ONE PARK WOOJIN: Yes, hello. I'm PARK WOOJIN. Nice to meet you.
(WANNA ONE BAE JINYOUNG)
WANNA ONE BAE JINYOUNG: Hello, I'm BAE JINYOUNG. Nice to meet you.
(WANNA ONE reunited after a long time)
(Didn't expect to see this scene again)
(Excited WANNA ONE's fans)
MC MIYEON: It feels like it's been a while since
seeing all the WANNA ONE members together like this.
(Undoubtedly an iconic presence in audition world)
MC MIYEON: WANNA ONE,
MC MIYEON: you guys are iconic figures
in idol survival shows, right?
MC MIYEON: This time, you've come not as
a participant but as a judge. How do you feel?
WANNA ONE PARK WOOJIN: It feels like
WANNA ONE PARK WOOJIN: quite a bit of time
has passed, but I still remember how we were back then.
WANNA ONE PARK WOOJIN: For the B:GINNERs,
this is just as important a moment as it was for us,
WANNA ONE PARK WOOJIN: so I plan to
evaluate them with careful consideration.
(What is the theme of Round 3)
MC DEX: Well, the theme for today's Round 3,
(with WANNA ONE present today?)
MC DEX: in which the B:GINNERs will be evaluated,
(B:GINNER'S PICK Match)
MC DEX: is the B:GINNER'S PICK Match.
(Princess MIYEON, Princess MIYEON)
(What's this one about?)
(Curious, anticipated)
(The identity of this
unpredictable round is?)
(After the signal song surprise mission)
MC DEX: Through the surprise mission,
MC DEX: all your rankings have been determined.
MC DEX: Round 3, B:GINNER's PICK Match, will proceed
with everything determined by the B:GINNERs' choices,
(Another round decided by B:GINNERs' choices)
MC DEX: just like a surprise mission.
MC DEX: First, among WANNA ONE's
four representative songs,
(Song choice and team selection that will change B:GINNERs' fate)
MC DEX: You'll choose the desired song and form a team.
(WANNA ONE's representative song 1,
Start of excitement: Energetic)
(WANNA ONE's representative song 2,
A novel-like emotion: Beautiful)
(ROUND 3: B:GINNER'S PICK Match
WANNA ONE 'Energetic' VS. WANNA ONE 'Beautiful')
(WANNA ONE's representative song 3,
Intense beat: Boomerang)
(WANNA ONE's representative song 4,
Blazing passion: Burn It Up)
(WANNA ONE 'Boomerang'
VS. WANNA ONE 'Burn It Up')
MC DEX: The team thus formed must sing
the second verse of the song they selected.
MC DEX: And you have to sing the first verse
of the opponent team's song as well.
SEO JUNHYEOK: It was a unique competition style
where two teams perform the same song on each stage.
MC DEX: From now on, song selection
will proceed in reverse order,
MC DEX: starting with
the lowest-ranked B:GINNER team.
(B:GINNER'S PICK Match song selection method)
MC DEX: After selecting the song you prefer,
(However, each WANNA ONE song has a lineup of 6 members)
MC DEX: please move and take your seats.
MC DEX: But, not everyone
can get the song they prefer.
(Huh? Did I hear wrong?)
(What?)
MC DEX: I mentioned that the top-ranking
members have a benefit, right?
(Benefit given to the first place
in the signal song surprise mission)
MC DEX: The benefit
of the surprise mission is
MC DEX: Pushing out team members.
- How can this be...
- It doesn't make sense!
MOON JAEIL: I thought there wouldn't be
much worry for the song selection.
MOON JAEIL: I just pick the song I want.
(Begin song selection for B:GINNER'S PICK Match)
MC DEX: Now, let's begin the song selection
MC DEX: for Round 3
B:GINNER's PICK Match.
(Signal song surprise mission 1st place,
B:GINNERs LEE YUNSUNG and HIROTO)
(B:GINNERs LEE YUNSUNG and HIROTO
select the songs they want without hesitation)
(Signal song surprise mission 10th place,
B:GINNERs LIM JIHWAN and JANG WON)
(Signal song surprise mission 9th place,
B:GINNERs IKUTO and BAN DANIEL)
(Signal song surprise mission 8th place,
B:GINNERs CHOI YOHAN and HARUTO)
(Signal song surprise mission 7th place,
B:GINNERs AI and HYO)
(Energetic 1 person/ Beautiful 6 people (full)
Boomerang 1 person/ Burn It Up 2 people)
(From now on, a push-out is possible)
(Signal song surprise mission 6th place,
B:GINNERs LI ZHIWEI and KIM BOHYEON)
(BOHYEON! It's that way!
You just need to find 'Burn It Up'.)
(Mulling)
Because it suits you so well.
(While BOHYEON hesitates,
LI ZHIWEI chooses 'Energetic')
Oh, this drives me crazy.
(BOHYEON torn between 'Energetic' and 'Beautiful')
Should I go with Energetic? Ah...
(Yes! I decided!)
I'm sorry.
(BOHYEON chooses 'Beautiful', and pushes out HIROTO)
I've decided.
(Signal song surprise mission 4th place
KANG JUNSEONG also chooses 'Beautiful')
- Well, everyone.
- Ah, no way...
(No way)
One, two.
Three.
(JUNSEONG chooses 'Beautiful',
and pushes out BOHYEON who pushed out HIROTO)
(BOHYEON filled with regret)
Ah, I really wanted 'Beautiful'.
(Signal song surprise mission 3rd place
SEO JUNHYEOK chooses 'Beautiful')
(SEO JUNHYEOK chooses Beautiful,
and pushes out IKUTO)
(Energetic 3 people/ Beautiful 6 people (full)
Boomerang 2 people)
(Signal song surprise mission 1st place,
B:GINNERs LEE JUNMYEONG and MOON JAEIL)
(MOON JAEIL goes straight for Burn It Up)
No, no, no.
(Guarding at all costs)
I can't be pushed out.
- JAEIL, we are Baggy Jeans family.
- I know, DANIEL.
(BAN DANIEL actively appeals to keep his spot)
All four Baggy Jeans members are here.
I know, DANIEL.
- What if you come here? Baggy Jeans...
- I know, DANIEL.
I'll go with whatever JAEIL decides.
- Are the two of you going together?
- What? Are you both going together?
(Is JAEIL going with JUNMYEONG?) (That's big trouble)
Ah, really?
No, no.
No, no,
(Don't do this to me)
No, huh?
- I'm sorry.
- No, no.
- No.
- Sorry.
(MOON JAEIL and LEE JUNMYEONG chooses 'Burn It Up',
and pushes out BAN DANIEL and JANG WON)
MOON JAEIL: Because members like SECHAN, JEONGHOON,
YEONTAE and HYEONBIN are kind of stable skill-wise.
(Round 3 24 Participants by Teams)
(Verse 1 vs Verse 2) (Verse 2 vs Verse 1)
Same song, so the comparison's even clearer, right?
(TEAM SWITCH, Round 3: Competing with the same song)
We're gonna win,
so go ahead and give it your best shot.
(Who will claim the true victory?)
- Their moves are super sharp. - They've got great energy.
(All fired up, losing isn't an option)
He's got that killer instinct.
(A single stage, but distinct chemistry in each verse)
Wow, they are doing great.
(Which team will take the TOP PICK at the end?)
I'm going to own this stage.
(The grand Round 3 with WANNA ONE)
MC DEX: Then, B:MY BOYZ Round 3.
(Starting now)
MC MIYEON: Let's start now.
MC MIYEON / MC DEX: Who is your boy?
B:MY BOYZ.
Let's go, let's go.
Hey, let's go.
It'll be fun. I can't wait to see it.
(Finally, B:GINNER'S PICK Match starts)
MC MIYEON: B:MY BOYZ B:GINNER'S PICK Match.
MC MIYEON: Let the first match begin.
- They must be really nervous right?
- Feels like watching a stage. It must be really nerve-wracking.
MC MIYEON: What's the first battle song
for B:GINNER'S PICK Match?
('Energetic' VS. 'Beautiful')
('Energetic'/'Beautiful')
MC MIYEON: It's 'Energetic' and 'Beautiful'.
(Fundamental masterpiece)
Come on.
My favorite song!
('Energetic'/'Beautiful')
(Powerful debut song, 'Energetic')
MC DEX: 'Energetic', the debut song
(Debut song MV reaches 100 million views)
MC DEX: by a male idol group to reach 100 million views.
('Energetic'/'Beautiful')
('Beautiful' with an emotional melody)
MC DEX: And 'Beautiful' swept 1st place
in various music charts.
MC DEX: What do the two songs
mean to our WANNA ONE?
WANNA ONE LEE DAEHWI: 'Energetic' is
WANNA ONE LEE DAEHWI: the song that first
introduced us WANNA ONE to the public.
WANNA ONE LEE DAEHWI: So,
it's a really thankful song to us.
WANNA ONE LEE DAEHWI: Since
it's a song that HUI gave us as a gift,
WANNA ONE LEE DAEHWI: it
feels even more meaningful now.
(Masterpiece maker)
I made it, but...
(Relaxed smile)
WANNA ONE PARK WOOJIN: 'Beautiful' was
a song that received more love even overseas.
WANNA ONE PARK WOOJIN: It is also
one of the few lyrical songs of WANNA ONE.
WANNA ONE PARK WOOJIN: Both songs
are very precious to us.
LEE YUJEONG: If they hear this,
they'll be very nervous.
I think it would be a burden.
(Beauty+Zetic Team,
tension-filled backstage)
HIROTO: I think it's
the most famous song
HIROTO: among WANNA ONE's songs,
HIROTO: so there was a sense
of responsibility, I guess?
(Meanwhile, the Energy+Full Team shouting 'Fighting!')
1, 2, 3, fighting.
HYO: Let's do it with confidence,
I often say that too.
HYO: We just want to show
that we are having fun.
HYO: I only thought
'let's sing and rap for fun'.
(Chapter 7 Moment of Choice B:GINNER'S PICK Match)
MC MIYEON: Round 3 B:GINNER'S PICK Match.
MC MIYEON: The two teams for the first
battle, please come onto the stage.
Come on, come on.
(Bursting tension)
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
(Beauty+Zetic Team)
(Energy+Full Team)
(Beauty+Zetic Team, Energy+Full Team)
(Beauty+Zetic) (Let's go)
(Energy+Full, fighting)
'Energetic' and 'Beautiful' have different vibes,
yet they have to do both.
MC MIYEON: I heard today, the two teams will split one song
into the 1st and 2nd verses for the competition.
MC MIYEON: I'm curious about which
part of which song each team prepared.
HIROTO: Our team prepared the energetic
second verse of 'Energetic' and
HIROTO: the sweet
first verse of 'Beautiful'.
He seems a bit nervous.
(Tension) (Adam's apple)
Tension is visible in the Adam's apple.
HYO: Our team prepared the first verse of
'Energetic' and the second verse of 'Beautiful'.
(Round 3 B:GINNER'S PICK Match,
Energetic/Beautiful)
What is your team's strength,
and the biggest aspect
you'd like us to focus on?
HIROTO: Our team's strength is vocals.
(WANNA ONE main vocalist)
Vocals, vocals.
We'll show powerful
vocals full of energy.
HIROTO: B:GINNER LI ZHIWEI
is a technically skilled singer.
(Not only a powerful vocalist,
but also capable of)
(handling high notes
with deep resonance)
LI ZHIWEI: The song's high notes are
very high and require explosiveness.
LI ZHIWEI: I want to show
my explosiveness.
WANNA ONE LEE DAEHWI: Then, everyone has
difficulties preparing their stages, right?
WANNA ONE LEE DAEHWI: I heard that, due to KIM BOHYEON
and WILLIAM's lateness from the first day,
WANNA ONE LEE DAEHWI: you guys started
practice a bit later than the other teams.
(Beauty+Zetic Team frozen
by the cold, sharp critique)
(Frozen too)
(What happened to Beauty+Zetic Team?)
(Round 3 competition D-13, Beauty+Zetic practice room)
No, no, that won't do.
No, no.
(Beauty+Zetic's first practice, WILLIAM's tardiness)
- Latecomers from the first day... - From the first day...
There are not just one, but two.
Didn't you say 10 minutes, WILLIAM?
(HIROTO: WILLIAM, please come quickly/ WILLIAM: I couldn't
catch a taxi, I might be about 10 minutes late, sorry)
(Failed to hold in laughter)
Because of traffic...
No way.
HIROTO: WILLIAM was late
due to traffic problems.
HIROTO: Another member
is probably still dreaming...
(For Episode 3, B:MY BOYZ's representative sleepyhead, BOHYEON)
BOHYEON.
Please wake up, wake up.
(A practice room filled with groans instead of singing)
What a shame.
You should be scolded.
(Surprised) (Sorry)
Sorry.
- Is it okay for you to be late like this?
- Sorry.
CHOI YOHAN: You can guess
when BOHYEON will come.
BOHYEON hasn't come yet?!
WILLIAM: I thought I was the only one
who was late as soon as I arrived,
WILLIAM: but there were only four.
(Finally, Beauty+Zetic Team
encounters the lyrics)
Whose is this one?
(BOHYEON, hurry up and come)
BOHYEON.
(I'll go quickly)
Alright, alright.
(Meanwhile, the Energy+Full Team with perfect attendance)
Let's take a look.
- Yes.
- Let's start with 'Energetic'.
(Focused)
(The intro of 'Energetic', with the piano
choreography as the highlight)
(Powerful song and choreography
are the key points)
SEO JUNHYEOK: I think 'Energetic' is a song
where group dance is more important.
(Energetic lyricist and composer, Master HUI)
SEO JUNHYEOK: Since it's a song made by Master HUI,
SEO JUNHYEOK: I wanted to
show a better performance,
(Full of enthusiasm)
SEO JUNHYEOK: so I got a bit greedy.
(TEAM SWITCH / Energetic 1st verse ending with the SWITCH section)
Oh, it's a switch, the switch happens here.
We won!
(Energy+Full Team full of confidence)
(Confident)
Our team actually has a lot of confidence,
thinking that our overall
skills are quite high.
LIM JIHWAN: The atmosphere
is really good,
LIM JIHWAN: and I thought, 'If it stays
like this, there shouldn't be any problems."
(There's going to be a lot of problems here?)
Should we just write it down for now?
- Yes.
- A little bit...
It's confirmed.
Does WILLIAM do this part?
For now, for now...
IKUTO: Practice just started, but I already
felt a bit anxious about the future.
WILLIAM: I felt really anxious.
Well, that team is already fully gathered, but...
- I'll just check the video once.
- Let's see.
(Some members are stretching
and learning, but a few are dancing.)
What is it?
I don't know this part.
(JUNHYEOK, AI, HYO already can dance it)
- JUNHYEOK too? - No, HYO already has it down.
HYO: But, don't we all
know this already?
Why do you know?
We'll pick up the 'Energetic'
choreography quickly, right?
(Confused)
Why does everyone know it?
KANG JUNSEONG: Why does
everyone know it?
KANG JUNSEONG: Am I the only
one who doesn't know it?
HYO: The first song I learned
to dance to was 'Energetic'.
SEO JUNHYEOK: Actually,
'Energetic' is a song
SEO JUNHYEOK: that every Korean
male idol trainee has to practice.
(Energy+Full Team, with 3 members
knowing the choreography, improves swiftly)
(Focused)
(Their teamwork is fitting perfectly)
(Beauty+Zetic Team is more curious
about KIM BOHYEON than choreography)
(Surprised) - The team feels a bit
different from before... - Boom?
(Finally, the late-sleeping prince
KIM BOHYEON appears) You're late.
- Really sorry.
- First, among ourselves...
Ah, I'm really sorry.
(B:GINNERs are in a cold atmosphere)
(Beauty+Zetic, delayed in practice due to
KIM BOHYEON's tardiness) The opposing team is practicing.
Yeah, but we couldn't.
KIM BOHYEON: I'm really sorry.
I apologize.
KIM BOHYEON: First,
I felt really sorry. Really sorry.
KIM BOHYEON: I started to think
maybe I messed up the start.
(Finally, Beauty+Zetic Team
is checking the choreography video)
(Energy+Full Team suddenly appears) (Surprised)
We need to show more of the wave here.
(Flustered)
Why?
What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- Monitoring.
(Full of swagger)
We've got it all covered.
LIM JIHWAN: We were practicing. Since we
couldn't hear the music, we came to check.
That is also a strategy.
(This is competition)
SEO JUNHYEOK: Many people left
our team and joined your team, right?
(HIROTO, IKUTO, and KIM BOHYEON,
who wanted 'Beautiful' but got pushed out)
I wanted to do 'Beautiful'!
(The two teams standing
at the opposite ends of fate)
- I think it turned out well.
- So do we.
(Tense standoff) - I think it's good because
you can do the first verse well. - You are...
(KIM BOHYEON is thrown off by the taunt)
Did you come here just to mess with us?
(Just kidding)
They came here just to mess with us.
AI, go up.
(What's this?)
Two tall people. Try picking him up.
Two, three.
(AI's cute provocation)
First, we...
(What is that)
We'll talk about it...
(Waggle)
Just try your best. Try hard.
Try your best.
What?
(In Japanese)
Do your best!
(AI, you did well)
(Can't lose)
Maybe, first...
(This is a clear victory in the height battle)
Make your decision, okay?
(Where are you, HYO?)
- But, really like this?
- Really?
(Really tall)
WILLIAM: Though we're competitors, since we're
on the same song on the same stage, let's do our best
WILLIAM: and create a great stage.
- Fighting.
(Round 3 competition, D-7 mid-check)
Starting with the Energy+Full Team. Okay.
LEE YUJEONG: This feels new.
The 1st and 2nd verses are different.
JINHO: You watch the opponent team's
stage for the first time, right?
- Yes.
(Dopamine overload)
JINHO: This is fun.
HIROTO: The opponent has
many talented members,
HIROTO: so it seems like they'll
deliver a high-level performance.
IKUTO: I felt a sense of crisis because
the opponent team looked too relaxed.
KANG JUNSEONG: What could be the worry?
KANG JUNSEONG: I'm confident,
so I'll do well.
(B:GINNER KANG JUNSEONG in charge of the intro)
♪Your lips and my lips♪
♪I can feel it more and more♪
(Nice)
(Precisely synchronized group performance)
♪Make me feel so high, I'm going crazy♪
(Nervous)
♪Can't stop me♪
(Stable choreography and vocals of
the Energy+Full Team) ♪Feel so high, I'm so crazy♪
♪Leave worries underground♪
♪Whatever you do
the modifier 'one' will linger♪
(Ending with an explosive performance)
♪In our ears♪
Oh.
(1st verse: Energy+Full, TEAM SWITCH,
2nd verse: Beauty+Zetic team)
KIM BOHYEON: First,
when we hear that we're doing well...
KIM BOHYEON: Maybe
it was just blind confidence,
KIM BOHYEON: but after seeing
the first verse, I thought, "We can pull that off."
LI ZHIWEI: I think we need to
perfectly show ourselves.
LI ZHIWEI: I think we can do
better than the opposing team.
♪Let's go♪
(What's in store for Beauty+Zetic Team, given their late start?)
♪Make me feel so high, I'm going crazy♪
(Vocal is good)
♪Can't stop me♪
(Sensing)
(The only one who moves differently)
♪You make me feel so high♪
(Huh?)
♪I'm so crazy♪
♪Just drawn more♪
(High notes explosion LI ZHIWEI)
- ♪Pull me Baby♪ - ♪Whoa, yeah♪
(Wow, they are doing well)
♪I'm feelin' so energetic♪
(The 'Energetic' of two teams showing different feels)
AI: I thought the vocals were good.
LIA KIM: The dance is difficult
and the song is difficult too.
- How did you make it?
- Sorry.
(It's okay) - That was too much.
Apologize them.
KANG JUNSEONG: Master HUI,
the original producer of 'Energetic',
KANG JUNSEONG: was there,
so that made me a bit worried.
WILLIAM: It was an honor,
but it was also terrifying.
(What is HUI's evaluation, the original
producer of 'Energetic'?) HUI: Personally...
HUI: The harmony in Energy+Full Team's
vocals wasn't bad.
HYO: It's a song made
by Master HUI, right?
HYO: It was thankful. I felt so good.
HUI: You showed stable performance
HUI: and vocals to a certain extent.
(Even dance Master LIA KIM couldn't resist the performance)
LIA KIM: Your performance is neat and complete.
LIA KIM: "Wow, they knew exactly
what I wanted."
(Right) LIA KIM: "And they really practiced it."
I was impressed, but still felt like something was off.
LIA KIM: I was impressed, but still felt like something was off.
HUI: It feels like the Beauty+Zetic Team
practiced parts individually.
HIROTO: It's a bit of a big problem.
HIROTO: As expected, the start...
HIROTO: We started
with a bad atmosphere.
(Beauty+Zetic Team, kicking off a bit late)
The beginning was slow. I think
we wasted a lot of time
(Only spent time on individual practice without a break)
- matching the performance. - Without communicating with each other.
I think we just practiced.
LIA KIM: Honestly, it's too obvious
which team will win.
WILLIAM: Total meltdown...
It was a mega meltdown.
LIA KIM: Doing the same moves
makes it more comparable.
♪Make me feel so high♪
LIA KIM: Energy+Full Team could keep
my attention while moving positions.
♪Make me feel so high♪
LIA KIM: While, for the Beauty+Zetic Team,
you always looked down, so I couldn't focus.
LIA KIM: It's obvious
that Energy+Full Team will win,
LIA KIM: I can clearly see it. So,
you really need to step up your game.
CHOI YOHAN: When I heard the result
was obvious, I felt really disappointed.
WILLIAM: I think my pride got hurt.
WILLIAM: I'm disappointed
in myself and also angry.
(Beauty+Zetic Team's dance class after mid-check)
LEE YUJEONG: How is it after the mid-check?
It's scary.
I thought I should work harder.
LEE YUJEONG: Why does
this feel bittersweet?
(Somehow, it's a bit emotional)
LEE YUJEONG: Why does this feel bittersweet?
LEE YUJEONG: Looking at it one way,
the Energy+Full Team might be complacent.
LEE YUJEONG: They do
seem a little bit excited.
LEE YUJEONG: I'm here to help, but you have
to stay focused on practice and class. Clear?
(Morale boost)
Yes, thank you.
♪Let's go♪
(Dance class starting energetically)
(Very serious) LEE YUJEONG: Raise it
powerfully, increase the tension!
(CHOI YOHAN's shoe left
from group dance)
(CHOI YOHAN performing
the choreography stoically)
(Disarmament)
LEE YUJEONG: Why are you doing this?
(Stage manager dealing with
the intruding audience member)
(Thanks to this, center IKUTO
equipped with a smile)
(Achieved with barefoot passion)
(The most energetic practice?)
(Sorry)
I'm sorry.
Shoes...
(Energetic regained thanks to CHOI YOHAN's shoes)
LEE YUJEONG: Why are you doing this?
Right.
LEE YUJEONG: You're tall,
which is great.
LEE YUJEONG: If you nail those moves
cleanly, it'll ramp up the tension.
Thank you.
I'll work even harder.
- LEE YUJEONG: Smile a lot. You should do it.
- Okay.
LEE YUJEONG: Put some life in the practice.
It'll shine through in the song.
LEE YUJEONG: Got it?
Yes.
LEE YUJEONG: Seems possible.
Let's practice.
CHOI YOHAN: To boost our teamwork
a bit more, we need to smile more.
- Okay.
- A little more.
(The Beauty+Zetic Team is back with smiles,
in sync as a team, not just individuals)
HIROTO: We lost in the mid-check,
but our team will win.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Let's smile. Energy power.
(Round 3 competition, D-1 rehearsal)
Let's try 'Energetic' first.
(Energy+Full Team's 1st verse rehearsal)
♪Your lips and my lips, I can feel it more and more♪
(Focused)
♪The hot air in this place♪
(AI in charge of high pitch part)
♪Why this moment now♪
(Focus)
♪Can't stop♪
♪No feeling, No No No No♪
- Nice.
- ♪Make me feel♪
♪The modifier will linger in our ears♪
(Energy+Full Team gets numerous praises)
LIA KIM: They are great. Don't have much to say.
(Beauty+Zetic Team's 2nd verse rehearsal)
♪Make me feel so high♪
- That's it.
- ♪I'm going crazy♪
LIA KIM: LI ZHIWEI's intro is so cool.
JINHO: Now, he's truly
become a vocalist.
♪I'm feelin' so energetic♪
Dancing is improved.
Improved a lot.
(Beauty+Zetic Team
improved after mid-check)
(Both teams nailed their stages)
Both teams have improved a lot, so...
JINHO: That's how you make a sound.
(Beauty+Zetic Team showed good vocal skills)
JINHO: You did the ad-libs in the 3rd verse perfectly.
(Two teams showing close skills)
Their abilities are even.
KIM BOHYEON: I thought if we did this well,
we really had a chance of winning.
SEO JUNHYEOK: I thought
it might be a little risky.
HYO: I think we made the stage safe
through choreography and singing.
HYO: I think we need the courage
to break everything we did until yesterday.
HIROTO: I don't know
which side will win yet, but...
HIROTO: we'll win!
(An unknown contest became a battle)
B:MY BOYZ Round 3.
B:GINNER'S PICK Match.
(Round 3 first stage 'Energetic')
Let's watch their performance
covering WANNA ONE's 'Energetic'.
(Come on)
Come on.
Fighting.
(Let's enjoy)
(Backstage, Beauty+Zetic Team
is comforting each other)
We've really worked hard so far, right?
Because it's the last...
Let's smile, be energetic,
be confident, and have fun.
Let's smile! Let's smile! Energy power.
KIM BOHYEON: If we show
our chemistry and just have fun,
KIM BOHYEON: we might
be able to win by sheer momentum.
(The Energy+Full Team is shouting
"fighting" to the end) Fighting.
- Okay, deep breath.
- Energy.
HYO: We'll win by a big margin
in terms of perfection and energy.
HARUTO, fighting!
('Energetic' by WANNA ONE. 1st verse: Energy+Full: KANG JUNSEONG,
SEO JUNHYEOK, AI, LIM JIHWAN, HARUTO, HYO)
(B:GINNER KANG JUNSEONG's clean gaze handling)
- Oh, good gaze. - That's right.
- What's wrong with him?
- Yay!
Yeah! Do it like this! Why should he
play the piano by looking only forward?
♪KANG JUNSEONG:
Your lips and my lips are getting close♪
(Surprised)
♪KANG JUNSEONG: More and more
The hot air in this place♪
(Cool)
♪SEO JUNHYEOK: Shivers
travel all over my body♪
♪HARUTO: Now, we're
gonna start our story♪
- Wow.
- Yoo hoo.
♪SEO JUNHYEOK: I don't
know without knowing♪
♪LIM JIHWAN: I'm falling for you♪
♪HYO: Breathtakingly, baby♪
♪AI: I don't know why,
this moment right now♪
(Watching)
♪AI: I can't stop this
feeling, no, no, no, no♪
- That's right!
- Oh, good.
♪AI: I can't stop this
feeling, no, no, no, no♪
♪SEO JUNHYEOK: Make me feel so high,
I'm going crazy, can't stop me♪
Doing well.
So good.
♪KANG JUNSEONG: You make me feel so high,
I'm so crazy, the moment you look at me♪
His expression is good!
(Original singer satisfied)
They are all doing well.
♪HARUTO: I'm so attracted, pull me
more, baby, I'm feelin' so energetic♪
♪LIM JIHWAN: Tonight, just us two,
out of control, Yeah, I'm feelin' so energetic♪
(Come on)
♪KANG JUNSEONG: Until the moment my heart
stops, I'll protect you, I won't go away♪
- That's right.
- Yay.
(B:GINNER KANG JUNSEONG already on point after
yesterday's feedback) I told him to do that strongly yesterday.
♪KANG JUNSEONG: Until the moment my heart
stops, I'll protect you, I won't go away♪
♪LIM JIHWAN: This isn't
just a momentary promise♪
♪HARUTO, SEO JUNHYEOK: Now,
tell me baby, you tell me how to feel♪
♪HYO: Uh, one, two, three, four
Don't like those other guys next to you♪
♪HYO: Who am I? A killer who only
protects you, just like that, I kill it, yeah♪
♪AI, HYO: Uh, I'll hold you in my arms and be
on alert, but throw your worries to the basement♪
♪AI, HYO: Whatever we do, we are one now.
That word will linger around our ears♪
(Good vibe)
They are doing well.
(Good, good)
Ah, this is good, verse 1 is good.
(What remains is the second verse of the Beauty+Zetic team)
Can this second verse win?
The second verse needs to dance more.
(TEAM SWITCH, team change)
(TEAM SWITCH)
(Finally, coming out!)
(Anticipating)
(Already)
Looks cool?
('Energetic', original song: WANNA ONE, Verse 2 Beauty+Zetic:
KIM BOHYEON, LI ZHIWEI, WILLIAM, IKUTO, CHOI YOHAN, HIROTO)
(Nervous)
Let's go!
♪Let's go♪
♪LI ZHIWEI: Make me feel so high,
I'm going crazy, can't stop me♪
Wow, LI ZHIWEI uses
his expression so well.
♪LI ZHIWEI: Make me feel so high,
I'm going crazy, can't stop me♪
Oh my, look at those
relaxed expressions.
♪WILLIAM: You make me feel so high,
I'm so crazy, the moment you look at me♪
♪IKUTO: I'm so attracted, pull me
more, baby, I'm feelin' so energetic♪
(Good job)
Wow, that was good?
♪IKUTO: I'm feelin' so energetic♪
♪LI ZHIWEI: Tonight, just us two,
out of control, Yeah, I'm feelin' so energetic♪
Why are they doing it so comfortably?
♪LI ZHIWEI: I'm feelin' so energetic♪
(Gulp)
♪KIM BOHYEON: I'm
feelin' good, I wanna touch♪
♪KIM BOHYEON: This unstoppable
feeling is like freedom♪
Good.
♪IKUTO: I'm feelin' good,
I wanna touch baby♪
♪LI ZHIWEI: Come to me tonight, yeah♪
♪Yeah♪
(Cool!)
Wow, what?
Oh!
♪LI ZHIWEI: Come to me tonight, yeah♪
♪KIM BOHYEON: Alright♪
♪KIM BOHYEON: Oh oh work your body,
it's time to come closer and enjoy let's dance♪
♪CHOI YOHAN: Even if your nice shoes
get dirty, move it, quickly, hurry up♪
♪HIROTO: Ask questions later
so other guys can't look at you♪
♪CHOI YOHAN/HIROTO: So anyone can see that
we make it so cool, let's start now, you know I mean♪
- Oh!
- ♪I'm so attracted♪
♪WILLIAM/LI ZHIWEI: Pull me more, baby.
I'm feelin' so energetic (energetic baby)♪
- Well done.
- ♪I'm feelin' so energetic♪
(Yeah)
♪IKUTO/WILLIAM: Tonight, just us two, (Ay)
out of control. Yeah, I'm feelin' so energetic♪
(Did so well)
(Beauty+Zetic HIROTO)
(Beauty+Zetic IKUTO)
(Beauty+Zetic WILLIAM)
(Beauty+Zetic CHOI YOHAN)
(Beauty+Zetic KIM BOHYEON)
(Beauty+Zetic LI ZHIWEI)
(TOP IDOL is satisfied too)
- Good job. - It was great, well done.
(The result that became more mysterious after the stage ended)
- Did well. I don't know really. - Really cool.
HYO: Really, LI ZHIWEI was
really good at high notes.
So, I really don't know
the result for sure.
(What will be the result of the first stage 'Energetic'?)
So, I'm curious how WANNA ONE saw this stage.
Please give us your comments.
WANNA ONE HA SUNGWOON: Personally,
I want to applaud the Energy+Full team.
(Impressed)
WANNA ONE HA SUNGWOON: Overall,
the group dance and vocals were well balanced.
WANNA ONE HA SUNGWOON: Rather than saying
someone did poorly or someone did well,
WANNA ONE HA SUNGWOON:
I think overall you all did well.
WANNA ONE LEE DAEHWI: Especially,
B:GINNER KANG JUNSEONG...
(Me?)
'Your lips and my lips'.
When you start here...
(What is this beautiful voice?)
I'm pretty good, right?
(Of course)
(Failed to hold laughter)
- You suddenly boast.
- I'm sorry.
(Sorry)
Just this verse is...
WANNA ONE LEE DAEHWI: It's the start of
this song, and I think it's very important.
(B:GINNER KANG JUNSEONG who digested
the opening that sets the atmosphere well)
♪Your lips and my lips♪
WANNA ONE LEE DAEHWI: In this part,
you gave us complete goosebumps.
(Dimples full of joy launch)
Thank you.
WANNA ONE LEE DAEHWI: B:GINNER
SEO JUNHYEOK who took the first chorus also...
WANNA ONE LEE DAEHWI: your
voice was really good and stable.
(B:GINNER SEO JUNHYEOK who showed
a honey voice and stability in the first chorus)
SEO JUNHYEOK: I'm glad that he said
I showed a good performance in the chorus.
That part was the most rewarding.
WANNA ONE PARK WOOJIN: In
the case of the foreign B:GINNERS,
WANNA ONE PARK WOOJIN: rapping
in Korean is not an easy task, but...
WANNA ONE PARK WOOJIN: In the case of B:GINNER HYO,
the lyrics were really clear.
(B:GINNER HYO's rap was strong enough
to break the barrier of pronunciation)
Thank you.
HYO: I'm incredibly happy, and
HYO: I thought I want to work
harder to show a better side.
I was very happy.
WANNA ONE HA SUNGWOON: For the Beauty+Zetic
team member, I want to compliment LI ZHIWEI.
Thank you.
WANNA ONE HA SUNGWOON: The song must have
been really difficult alone,
WANNA ONE HA SUNGWOON: but I think
it's amazing that he handled everything.
(B:GINNER LI ZHIWEI's high notes
comfortably soaring without limit)
(Genuine excitement explosion)
Wow, what?
LI ZHIWEI: I was really happy because
it was an extremely high evaluation for me.
WANNA ONE HA SUNGWOON: When B:GINNER
KIM BOHYEON came out the energy was really good.
Thank you.
When B:GINNER BOHYEON
came out, I think...
(B:GINNER KIM BOHYEON who captured WANNA ONE's attention)
I think it definitely drew attention.
(B:GINNER KIM BOHYEON
who captured WANNA ONE's attention)
(A stage that showed definite energy
and mood shift in the bridge part)
Good.
HUI: BOHYEON could become
the TOP PICK here, right?
KIM BOHYEON: I felt
like, 'I can do this,'
KIM BOHYEON: and I'm happy that
I was able to show the effort I put in.
And the Beauty+Zetic team chose this song
because you all wanted to, right?
(Beauty+Zetic team frozen by the sharp question)
- Right? - Yes, that's correct.
WANNA ONE LEE DAEHWI: I actually
feel like Energy+Full team did well...
I wonder if it was a lack of practice?
WANNA ONE HA SUNGWOON: When I felt it,
the overall group choreography seemed a bit messy.
(Beauty+Zetic team's group dance overall was out of sync)
♪Make me feel so high, so other guys can't look at you♪
(A lot of bows/less bows)
But, the angle is not right.
That gaze angle is not right.
The ending is disappointing.
So, it was a bit disappointing...
(There was an individual who was praised,
but the overall team was lacking)
It made me think like that.
Wow, but the feedback
is a bit intense today.
Because...
LEE YUJEONG: The Beauty+Zetic team chose
the song themselves, but saying 'Did you pick it?'
LEE YUJEONG: and that Energy+Full
team did better is really heartbreaking.
(Oh, right...)
That's right.
Opinions are...
If opinions are divided like this...
In the Beautiful stage...
That's right.
(In Beautiful stage, they can only try harder)
They might just pump each other up and get more energized.
(Right)
WILLIAM: Ah, we absolutely have to
win this. We can't lose, seriously.
HIROTO: We just have
to do 'Beautiful' well.
HIROTO: It's not saying our team
ended with 'Energetic'.
First! We'll focus on 'Beautiful'.
HYO: 'Beautiful' is where
the other team does the first verse.
HYO: So, our team's impact
might be weakened, right?
Want to focus and show a better stage.
(The B:GINNERs finished the first stage,
what will the next stage bring?)
MC DEX: Following 'Energetic', the two teams
are about to perform 'Beautiful'.
This song, unlike the others,
(Must express emotions in 'Beautiful')
requires emotional expression.
(Q: How did you interpret 'Beautiful'?)
I wonder how you interpreted this song.
The story we came up with is about
KIM BOHYEON: being close friends
who can no longer meet,
(A story about longing for an estranged friend)
and now feeling the longing for a distant friend.
WANNA ONE LEE DAEHWI: They
even created a story?
(Admirable)
They created a story.
Yes, our team reinterpreted
the song 'Beautiful'
(A story longing for memories with friends we were with)
as a story about missing the memories.
(Both teams came up with a story through friendship)
It's about friends, both teams, huh?
Friendship.
(How will the friendship story
created by both teams turn out?)
(Round 3 competition D-15,
Beauty+Zetic team practice room)
(Beauty+Zetic team)
('Beautiful' first verse, point is the intro)
The point is the first intro.
(Agree! Intro)
Intro.
(Let's finish at the first verse!)
Feeling like we finished it.
(From now on 'Beautiful' only exists in the first verse)
Really cool.
'Ah, this team is the best',
this kind of feeling?
HIROTO: The way to win is to think, 'We
have to satisfy them with the first verse.'
KIM BOHYEON: Because 'Beautiful'
was a song I wanted to do,
KIM BOHYEON: doing
well in the given part...
(Just... want to beat the Energy+Full team!)
Ah, just want to beat that team.
(Unforgettable painful memory)
(Energy+Full team)
Personally...
(Personally, our opposing team...)
Our opposing team...
(I think Beauty+Zetic team will do well)
I think they'll do well.
(Somehow, BOHYEON...)
Anyway, BOHYEON?
'Beautiful'.
(Candidate for caution No. 1, B:GINNER KIM BOHYEON)
I think we can do well.
(Beautiful appearance and voice fits perfectly with the song)
♪The song full of regrets like a fool♪
(Candidate for caution No. 2, B:GINNER IKUTO)
Because IKUTO also has a nice vocal...
(B:GINNER IKUTO, owner of a honey voice that even makes bees cry)
♪so beautiful, beautiful♪
(Candidate for caution No. 0, B:GINNER LI ZHIWEI)
I think LI ZHIWEI...
(LI ZHIWEI has high notes cooler than a water bomb)
♪Why am I crying like this♪
KANG JUNSEONG: LI ZHIWEI
is a bit concerning.
KANG JUNSEONG: First of all,
he sings really well,
KANG JUNSEONG: and I thought they
could bring out something good in 'Beautiful'.
(Energy+Full team preparing for choreo
practice putting worries aside)
But, there's something about
hearing it just once, you know?
AI: Yesterday, I made all
of Beautiful's choreography.
(Awesome, wow)
Wow.
That's awesome.
(Did you get the choreography in advance?)
Got it?
HYO: AI made the choreography last night
comparing it with the original song for 'Beautiful'.
(Studied choreography in advance for team members)
I thought it would be good
if they could memorize the choreography quickly.
('Beautiful' choreography director, AI's class begins)
Okay, please tell us the position.
(JUNSEONG, please stand here)
Okay, YUNSUNG's part, please stand here.
E.
(Learn the movement in advance and proceed quickly)
- E. - Alright.
A.
Here.
Yes.
D.
HYO: While others roughly memorize
and teach the choreography, many do that.
HYO: But, AI even takes into account
hand shapes timing and rhythm and so on...
HYO: It feels like we can make
something meticulous, which is good.
(Choreography practice
became easier thanks to AI)
(But there's one thing AI is lacking)
At first, looking down at something...
(Mumbling)
(Hehehe)
Huh?
(What do you call #$%?)
(Laughing)
(AI is also feeling the reality check)
(AI's Korean skill compromised with reality)
Reality check.
(So cute)
With a reality check feeling...
SEO JUNHYEOK: The way AI speaks,
and even his tone and actions,
(It's so cute)
is just so cute.
One, two, three.
(Ddu dudu ddu du)
(Funny)
(Giving up Korean for fast progress)
(Like Morse code,
exchanging back and forth)
HYO: Honestly, with the choreography,
you can just see it, right?
HYO: You don't need to
explain it all with words.
(Mid-check)
What should we start with?
From the 'Energetic' team.
- Yes.
(Beauty+Zetic team looking tense)
Make the space a bit wider...
(Energy+Full team looking relaxed)
Do you remember our story?
Oh, scary.
YUJU: Will they be able to express
the emotions of the song well?
♪Like a fool, with regrets, I hope
this song touches the sky♪
(As expected, BOHYEON is good)
♪The prayer I stayed up
all night with in tears♪
♪I miss you so much♪
(The group choreography part is also on point)
♪Only now feeling our space♪
(Oh...)
♪I miss you so much♪
(LI ZHIWEI also hits the high note part without mistakes)
♪Even as I cry like this, why didn't I♪
♪Even know it♪
♪Beautiful♪
♪I hate realizing only now♪
KANG JUNSEONG: I thought, 'Huh? Maybe they
only practiced 'Beautiful' and not 'Energetic','
KANG JUNSEONG: because they
were really in sync at the start.
(1st verse Beauty+Zetic team, TEAM SWITCH,
2nd verse Energy+Full team)
KANG JUNSEONG: But, actually I was so confident
in 'Beautiful', so there was no worry.
(Sharp angles)
♪Memory is like a vast ocean warehouse♪
(Oh)
(Surprised)
♪Even if I wander inside all day♪
♪So beautiful, beautiful♪
(Vocals progressing stably)
♪Because you're more beautiful than anyone♪
(Concern)
♪Don't be sick don't cry♪
(The chorus part is also in sync)
♪If you hear the song for you, come back again♪
(Oh the harmony is good)
♪Beautiful, beautiful♪
♪Standing alone in the mirror♪
LI ZHIWEI: I thought, "Wow, as
expected, they're a strong team."
LI ZHIWEI: I felt they
were a bit ahead of us.
(What are the masters' mid-check evaluations?)
At first glance...
PENTAGON JINHO: I wished the tenderness longing, and
everything were expressed a bit morem, but actually...
(Neither team really
showed that kind of thing)
(The two teams lacking
emotional expression)
YUJEONG: Of course, Beautiful is a song
where the vocals play a huge role,
but in HYO's team, it seems like you
lowered the focus on the dance a bit.
The differences in details
from the previous stage are too obvious.
(Unlike 'Energetic', which focused on details)
♪Make me feel so high♪
♪Only now feeling our space♪
(Beautiful lacks details
like gaze direction)
(Beautiful lacks details like gaze direction, hand position)
♪Your last words♪
SEO JUNHYEOK:
Ah, I felt a bit disappointed.
Our title song is Beautiful, but...
Team A, that
"Oh I miss you, I miss you" part.
Suddenly, the lyrical song
becomes too vigorous.
(Choir that severed the song's mood)
♪If you hear it, come back again♪
♪Oh I miss you, I miss you♪
There's no harmony.
(Surprised)
HIROTO: I didn't know well, but matching
the pitch details seemed difficult.
(Beautiful is more
difficult than expected...)
(The day after the mid-check...)
(The victory in Beautiful is determined by immersion)
I think it's a battle of who immerses more.
(And conveying emotion is important)
Think of something that can draw out longing.
So, I think it would be great
if you guys come up with a story.
PENTAGON HUI: I think it would be better
if you guys have your own story.
(Our own story...)
LIM JIHWAN: We have practiced together
and have experience having good stages together.
And when you have
that feeling, something...
LIM JIHWAN: When we imagine
our memories, the emotions we feel
(Time spent together taken for granted)
aren't just sadness, right?
(Those memories are soon our story)
It's about our story, huh?
SEO JUNHYEOK: I really like
the members I'm with now.
SEO JUNHYEOK: So later, when we look back,
this time together will become a memory.
(Expressing memories with friends as longing)
Trying to capture the longing in this song...
HIROTO: There was probably
a friend for each of us
HIROTO: who we were close with in the past,
but then something happened and we drifted apart.
When you start to drift apart
from a really close friend, to the point
KIM BOHYEON: where it becomes uncontrollable...
there are times when it's painful to lose someone
KIM BOHYEON: who will now only remain
as a memory. It's like losing someone precious.
(The reason farewells are sad is because there was love)
But, in a way, that's also a form of love, right?
(BOHYEON turns on the camera during break time)
Please take good care of us.
Yes, please take care of us.
♪Still receiving love♪
Because they seem to find Korean
pronunciation quite difficult, so...
(BOHYEON's small consideration for foreign B:GINNERs)
I wanted to help a little in that part.
♪Love, love♪
♪Love♪
(Pretty attack)
(Collapse)
♪Love♪
(B:GINNER LI ZHIWEI)
♪Why am I crying?♪
(Team members work harder knowing BOHYEON's efforts)
Try this pronunciation, 'Geu, neu, deu'.
Geu, neu, deu.
Neu.
LI ZHIWEI: BOHYEON is
really caring about me.
LI ZHIWEI: He's a really good
Korean pronunciation teacher.
WILLIAM: Ultimately, what we
have to show on stage is teamwork.
WILLIAM: If the team's opinions, harmonies, and mindsets
are all different, we can't be one team in the end, right?
KIM BOHYEON: What I can confidently say
is that we've become much closer.
KIM BOHYEON: It's just amazing. It seems truly
amazing to change like that in such a short time.
WILLIAM: I feel like I've made good use of all the time
I spent practicing, shedding blood, sweat, and tears.
(A time that could be overcome
because they were together)
SEO JUNHYEOK: Although it's a short time, I think
we managed to create a truly family-like atmosphere.
SEO JUNHYEOK: I think
being able to feel that way
(Feelings only possible because they're friends)
is also one of the strengths of our members.
Fighting, fighting.
JANG WON: Do well. Fighting.
WANNA ONE PARK WOOJIN: But this time,
I think the Beauty+Zetic team might be better.
The tables can turn.
WANNA ONE PARK WOOJIN: For some
reason, I'm more looking forward to this team.
Let's do well, let's do well.
Focus, focus.
Focus.
(Beautiful, original song: WANNA ONE KIM BOHYEON,
LI ZHIWEI, WILLIAM, IKUTO, CHOI YOHAN, HIROTO)
(Opening filled with
the emotions of longing)
(Good feeling)
The introduction is important.
♪KIM BOHYEON:
Like a fool, with regrets♪
I hope this song touches the sky♪
♪KIM BOHYEON: The prayer
I stayed up all night with in tears♪
♪KIM BOHYEON: May it reach your heart♪
(Well done! Our BOHYEON)
Ah, our BOHYEON.
BOHYEON is doing well.
PENTAGON HUI:
BOHYEON already looks so sad.
♪WILLIAM: I was young, I didn't
know it'd turn out like this♪
♪WILLIAM:
I thought it was obvious at that time♪
♪CHOI YOHAN:
The smile left to me by you♪
♪CHOI YOHAN: still remains in my heart♪
♪IKUTO: Honestly, I♪
♪IKUTO:
It seems I still need to receive love♪
♪IKUTO: The time I remained alone♪
♪HIROTO:
The longer it becomes, the more I'm afraid♪
♪HIROTO: I miss those times♪
♪HIROTO: I miss you so much like this♪
♪WILLIAM: I miss you so much♪
♪WILLAM/KIM BOHYEON:
Now, I feel our space uh uh♪
♪LI ZHIWEI: I miss you so much♪
♪LI ZHIWEI: I'm crying like this, but♪
♪HIROTO: why didn't I know?♪
(What's with the gaze?)
♪ALL: So beautiful, beautiful♪
♪KIM BOHYEON: Because you will
be more beautiful than anyone♪
♪WILLIAM/LI ZHIWEI:
Don't get, hurt don't cry♪
The song towards you♪
♪IKUTO: If you hear it, come back again♪
♪ALL: Oh I miss you, I miss you♪
♪LI ZHIWEI: The figure standing
alone in the mirror♪
♪CHOI YOHAN/KIM BOHYEON:
It's unfamiliar, it's scary♪
♪CHOI YOHAN: I need you♪
♪LI ZHIWEI:
I hate myself for feeling it only now♪
♪KIM BOHYEON: Come back again♪
(Nailed it)
What's with the gaze?
That's right.
(What's with the emotion?)
Did they break up yesterday?
(TEAM SWITCH)
LIM JIHWAN: Believe in ourselves
and trust in our teammates...
HARUTO: Let's create
a stage without regrets.
(Let's trust in our practice)
Let's believe in what we practiced, and...
(and immerse ourselves passionately in this stage)
Let's give our all on this stage.
Wow, it's like a movie.
So cool.
(Beautiful, original song: WANNA ONE
KANG JUNSEONG, SEO JUNHYEOK, AI, LIM JIHWAN, HARUTO, HYO)
♪LIM JIHWAN: Memory is
a vast warehouse like the sea♪
(Seal applause)
(JIHWAN, nailed it)
Doing well, he already nailed it.
♪LIM JIHWAN: Memory is
a vast warehouse like the sea♪
♪LIM JIHWAN: Even if
I wander inside it all day♪
♪HYO: Even this loneliness felt alone♪
♪HYO: Is your only trace♪
♪HYO: With eyes forcibly closed♪
♪HYO: Enduring again today♪
(Doing well)
♪I miss you so much♪
♪AI: I miss you so much♪
♪AI/KANG JUNSEONG: Now,
I feel our space uh uh♪
Wow... the emotion
♪SEO JUNHYEOK: I miss you so much♪
♪SEO JUNHYEOK:
I'm crying like this, but♪
♪HARUTO: Why didn't I Know?♪
(I saw it, he wiped away the tears!)
He wiped away the tears!
♪HARUTO: Why didn't I Know?♪
♪ALL: So beautiful, beautiful♪
♪SEO JUNHYEOK Because you are
more beautiful than anyone else♪
♪AI/HARUTO: Don't get hurt♪
♪AI/HARUTO: A song for you♪
♪KANG JUNSEONG:
If you hear it, come back again♪
♪ALL: I miss you, I miss you♪
♪SEO JUNHYEOK: The figure
standing alone in the mirror♪
(The 100th time clapping like a seal)
♪HYO/AI: It's unfamiliar, it's scary♪
♪HYO: I need you♪
♪HARUTO: I hate myself
for feeling it only now♪
(Nod)
♪HYO: Yeah, holding a pretty flower like you♪
♪HYO: I want to stand
in front of you again♪
(Doing well, huh?)
KIM JEONGHOON: Slightly gives me chills?
♪KANG JUNSEONG: I want to
appear in front of you, yeah♪
♪HYO: Draw the familiar
times with fingertips♪
♪HYO: Cry like a clock
that doesn't turn in place♪
♪LIM JIHWAN: Shining you♪
♪AI: Angel-like you♪
♪KANG JUNSEONG: Beautiful you♪
♪KANG JUNSEONG:
I want to hug you freely♪
(Hugged, they hugged!!)
(What's with the emotion?)
Hugged.
Ah, good job, JUNSEONG.
♪KANG JUNSEONG: Want to hug you freely♪
♪HYO: I really want to see you again♪
♪AI: So beautiful, beautiful♪
♪AI: Maybe crying somewhere♪
WANNA ONE HA SUNGWOON: I'm about to cry.
♪HARUTO/SEO JUNHYEOK:
Any words are fine (uh)♪
♪KANG JUNSEONG/AI/LIM JIHWAN/HYO:
Oh I miss you, I miss you (I miss you)♪
♪LIM JIHWAN/SEO JUNHYEOK:
Your last words drifting away (I miss you)♪
♪KANG JUNSEONG/LIM JIHWAN:
It's unfamiliar, I'm afraid♪
♪AI: I need you♪
♪HARUTO: I hate myself
for feeling it only now♪
(Choking up)
LIA KIM: Wow, look at
the emotional expression.
♪LIM JIHWAN: I hope
this song touches the sky♪
♪LIM JIHWAN: The prayer
I stayed up all night with in tears♪
♪LIM JIHWAN: May it reach your heart♪
(HYO, SEO JUNHYEOK, KANG JUNSEONG, LIM JIHWAN)
Ah, each word, each line of the song was sung with such care,
(AI, HARUTO)
and I really feel like we sang with all our heart.
It was a performance with no regrets,
and I think it was a really good stage.
(Beautiful that also
touched the seniors' hearts)
WANNA ONE LEE DAE HWI:
I think they can debut like this.
(The masters were also moved)
I really almost cried.
(Full of aftertaste)
(Song that resonated with the B:GINNERs' hearts)
Oh, something really hits.
(Emotions not calming
even after the stage ends)
Don't cry
(Knowing that feeling, the Energy+Full team cries together)
- Why are you crying? - JIHWAN.
Crying? Crying? Are you crying?
WANNA ONE LEE DAE HWI: Why are you crying?
You did so well, but why are you crying?
- Oh, did they cry? Did they cry?
- What?
PENTAGON JINHO:
They really thought of a story.
- PENTAGON JINHO: So, those things are noticeable even on stage.
- Are they really crying? While singing?
LIM JIHWAN: I thought this might
be the last stage with these friends,
LIM JIHWAN: so I prepared
with a sense of urgency.
LIM JIHWAN: Because we were in sync emotionally,
I feel like we were able to create a sense of unity,
a memory that we can never
go back and change.
HYO: I sang thinking about the memories
of the B:GINNER friends who have left.
HYO: I really feel like
I sang with all my heart,
HYO: and I think I was
about to cry a lot too.
BOHYEON bought us ice cream.
(Sometimes can become distant and close again)
- He bought it for me, thank you. - Thank you.
(That's what a friend is)
Let's see.
WANNA ONE BAE JINYOUNG: Well first,
the two teams did really well.
WANNA ONE BAE JINYOUNG: Well actually,
WANNA ONE BAE JINYOUNG: when
B:GINNER JIHWAN shed tears,
WANNA ONE BAE JINYOUNG: it
reminded me of the past,
WANNA ONE BAE JINYOUNG: and I think
I became deeply immersed in the moment.
WANNA ONE HA SUNGWOON: I also
remembered my old days a lot,
WANNA ONE HA SUNGWOON: so
tears slightly welled up.
(JIHWAN)
WANNA ONE HA SUNGWOON: Yes, so
WANNA ONE HA SUNGWOON: I was
also choked up...
(Seeing the emotional singing on stage)
(WANNA ONE got emotional
with old memories)
WANNA ONE LEE DAE HWI: I really felt like you guys
were singing with understanding of the song.
WANNA ONE LEE DAE HWI: While
empathizing with the storylines,
(A stage where everything was well shown)
definitely emotional expression as well...
Gestures, facial expressions,
all these things were a bit...
(A stage like a single team)
The team came together, and it felt special. I really enjoyed watching it.
WANNA ONE HA SUNGWOON: Felt like watching
one stage and watched without thinking.
This is the highest praise
isn't it? This is the best.
PENTAGON JINHO: If it's really good, you
end up watching without thinking
WANNA ONE HA SUNGWOON: Ah, and one thing
WANNA ONE HA SUNGWOON: I want to mention
is that HYO, as the leader, really kept things together,
(Energy+Full team that created the best stage)
WANNA ONE HA SUNGWOON: which made the stage even better.
Thank you.
YUJEONG: This really
becomes a mother's heart.
YUJEONG: Feels like
they're complimenting me.
WANNA ONE BAE JINYOUNG: And I think
the Beauty+Zetic team did a great job
WANNA ONE BAE JINYOUNG: with
their gestures and expressions,
WANNA ONE BAE JINYOUNG: really
matching the song Beautiful.
(Beauty+Zetic team that clearly
expressed emotions on stage)
WANNA ONE BAE JINYOUNG:
It was a stage with good immersion.
WANNA ONE BAE JINYOUNG: You guys
did well to match the song's mood.
PENTAGON JINHO: Well done, BOHYEON
started well, and overall he did well.
WANNA ONE LEE DAE HWI: The team's
atmosphere seemed to match better here.
WANNA ONE LEE DAEHWI: so it was
much better than Energetic.
- Thank you.
WANNA ONE LEE DAEHWI: One thing
I want to mention
WANNA ONE LEE DAEHWI: is
that WILLIAM seemed
WANNA ONE LEE DAEHWI: a bit
awkward on stage.
(Awkwardness revealed)
♪I miss you so much♪
WANNA ONE LEE DAEHWI: If you improve
on that, I think you'll be able to handle
WANNA ONE LEE DAEHWI: your part on stage
really well, so I want to give him some advice.
- Thank you.
WILLIAM: After hearing
the judges' feedback,
WILLIAM: I think I felt
quite guilty to the team members.
LIA KIM: You have to say
what needs to be said.
LIA KIM: After that, how
to handle it is up to them.
WANNA ONE HA SUNGWOON:
On the other hand...
WANNA ONE HA SUNGWOON: On the other hand,
LI ZHIWEI did really well, so it was nice to watch.
MC MIYEON: Both teams concluded
WANNA ONE round, so you worked hard.
- Thank you.
You worked hard, you did very well.
WANNA ONE PARK WOOJIN: I didn't
know they could do live this well.
- It was really great to sing Beautiful.
- It was really good.
HYO: I felt happy,
HYO: and I thought we were a good team.
AI: When I lack
confidence or feel worried,
AI: the members always tell me,
(Becoming family in a foreign land)
AI: "Here in Korea, we're family"...
- Well done.
- If I just try a bit more...
- You did so well.
KIM BOHYEON: We all did well.
KIM BOHYEON: I believe we did well
enough to rival the other team.
IKUTO: When we first started practicing,
the atmosphere wasn't good.
IKUTO: So, I wondered
if the team will be okay.
IKUTO: But, as we practiced
more, our teamwork improved,
IKUTO: so practicing was really fun.
Our members worked really
hard, thank you, and I love you.
(Two teams that became one
because they believed in each other)
MC DEX: B:MY BOYZ B:GINNER's PICK Match.
MC DEX: We'll start the second battle.
WANNA ONE BAE JINYOUNG: They
must be really nervous.
WANNA ONE LEE DAEHWI: Ah,
they must be nervous.
Burn+Merang team, fighting
(Burn+Merang team
starting with a high-five)
LEE JUNMYEONG: I just gritted my
teeth and prepared for Boomerang,
LEE JUNMYEONG: and I'll
definitely give it my all.
MC DEX: B:GINNER'S PICK Match.
MC DEX: The battle song is...
MC DEX: It's Boomerang and Burn It Up.
- Cheer up, guys.
- Really difficult songs.
Truly, a crazy song.
Boomerang.
(Boomerang, an electro-trap genre
with a strong beat and prominent synths)
(A stage with a sexy and powerful charm
unlike WANNA ONE's usual image)
(Dreamy piano melody and dynamic rhythm,
progressive House genre, Burn It Up)
(A stage where you can see intense
performances and charismatic appearances)
WANNA ONE BAE JINYOUNG: Burn It Up
is a debut song along with Energetic.
WANNA ONE BAE JINYOUNG: Powerful
and seems like it will catch fire...
(Cute)
It's a song that evokes
WANNA ONE BAE JINYOUNG: an atmosphere
that feels like it's about to catch fire.
WANNA ONE HA SUNGWOON: The song
Boomerang is
WANNA ONE HA SUNGWOON: a song where
we challenged an image transformation.
WANNA ONE HA SUNGWOON: Both
in terms of performance
WANNA ONE HA SUNGWOON:
and personal choice,
WANNA ONE HA SUNGWOON: it's
the song I treasure the most.
MC MIYEON: Yes, good, Round 3
of B:GINNER'S PICK Match.
MC MIYEON: The two teams that
will compete in the second battle.
MC MIYEON: Please come up to the stage.
(Burn+Merang team)
(Boo+It Up team)
Let's go.
(Nice to meet you)
(B:GINNER'S PICK Match starts)
WILLIAM: This is what
I'm most looking forward to.
SEO JUNHYEOK: Must be really nervous.
MC MIYEON: Please introduce what part
of the song each team took on.
Our Boomerang team
took on Boomerang's Verse 2
and Burn It Up's Verse 1.
Our team took on Boomerang's Verse 1
and Burn It Up's Verse 2.
(Looking forward to it)
Is there anything you feel
challenged by each other?
PARK SECHAN: In the other team,
KAI is...
(Doubt my ears)
Oh.
PARK SECHAN: There's a part where KAI
does in Boomerang as a highlight...
PARK SECHAN: When I hear it,
it gives me chills, so I chose KAI.
Wow, even though
they're the opposing team,
they're so impressive
that it gives me chills.
(Totally agree)
(We saw it too) It's something that
makes sense to be wary of.
He's good.
BAN DANIEL: The other team's members
dance so well.
(Laughing)
BAN DANIEL: It's a bit of a challenge,
but as we are cool, I think we can win.
I think we can win because we are cool.
(Confidence overflowing
from the gallantry)
BAN DANIEL: I think the only thing
BAN DANIEL: the other team
is better at than us is dancing.
BAN DANIEL: I'll get
my revenge on JAEIL,
BAN DANIEL: who pushed me aside.
(The Boo+It Up team is formed
by top B:GINNERs of the signal song)
(B:GINNERs of signal song
who ranked 1st/3rd/4th/5th)
There's JAEIL who dances really well.
(MOON JAEIL who dominated
the stage with dance alone)
Also, there's JUNMYEONG.
(All-rounder LEE JUNMYEONG)
He is good at dancing and singing.
YEONTAE is a main rapper.
They're members
with high-level skills, so honestly,
I think we're
basically like the Avengers team.
LEE JUNMYEONG: I'm glad because it seems
like the team I envisioned was formed.
(B:MY BOYZ Avengers
team has been formed)
LEE JUNMYEONG: JAEIL learns
choreography really fast.
PARK SECHAN: It's amazing how he can watch a video
once and the choreography comes out in just one second.
(Quite satisfied from the first harmony)
Wow.
(This is enough
to acknowledge as the Avengers team)
KAI: We...
KAI: We can't take it easy
with practice from now on.
KAI: We need to work even
harder than we are right now.
(Burn+Merang, Boomerang's Verse 2 practice begins)
Then, let's just think about the image quickly.
From now on, centered
around YUNSUNG and DANIEL...
- Match accurately, if you don't know...
- Understood.
Like this...
KAI: I thought that if we help the members who are
lacking and have the others focus on different practices,
KAI: things could progress smoothly.
(Practicing in each other's tempo)
♪Oh, don't go, my dear♪
(Choreography loading)
♪My dear♪
So fast.
- To speak slowly...
- Yes.
(Indicating each move slowly)
In the beginning,
YUNSUNG does this, right?
LEE YUNSUNG: KAI led the practice,
and it seemed to have been helpful.
Ah, okay.
JANG WON: KAI helped from the side
with the parts we were missing,
(Boomerang's Verse 2 completed under KAI's lead)
so I think his help was quite significant.
(Mid-check)
Wow, they are really...
(Boo+It Up team VS. Burn+Merang team)
♪Go crazy♪
Wow, these guys...
LIA KIM: Ah, this team is too strong.
- No need to feel defeated.
(Boo+It Up team,
Boomerang's Verse 1 starts)
(Nervous)
(Moving as one)
♪Go crazy♪
Wow, they dance so well.
♪I'm pretty okay too, hey♪
(Moving as one, like Avengers)
♪How can you make me feel so small♪
(We'll start soon)
♪Boom, boom, boom, boom, BOOMERANG♪
(Verse 1, Boo+It Up team, Team Switch,
Verse 2, Burn+Merang team)
(Attention focused on KAI from the start)
♪Wing, wing, wing, wing, BOOMERANG♪
♪Whether I'm fascinated
or enchanted by you♪
They do well.
(JANG WON full of spirit today as well)
♪Hey, throw it away♪
♪Boom, boom, boom BOOMERANG♪
They do well.
- I think it could be a good battle.
- Yeah, it's better.
(Unexpected development
from the Burn+Merang team)
We really need to be wary of them.
(Tense with comeback of Boo+It Up team)
This is bad.
Who is the leader of the second team?
(Raising hand)
Me, JANG WON!
- Do you think your team won or lost?
- JANG WON is the leader.
- I want to win.
(Fully sincere JANG WON,
everyone burst into laughter)
PENTAGON HUI: Objectively, this team
has members
PENTAGON HUI: who've been handling
most of the performances,
PENTAGON HUI: while the others
still need to improve.
PENTAGON HUI: I was worried about
whether it would be okay,
PENTAGON HUI: but now I think
it'll be fine.
- Thank you.
KAI: I think the members have parts
that suit the song really well,
KAI: so I believe we can win.
JANG WON: But since we
know we're still lacking,
JANG WON: if we work
harder, it might be doable.
(Boo+It Up team can't laugh)
I thought momentum would be important.
PARK SECHAN: Their energy and drive are so good
that I thought if we don't bring the same, we might lose.
LEE JUNMYEONG: "If we're
not careful, this could get risky."
I think we were thinking again.
Oh no, we can't let our guard
down. I'm not sure about this one.
MC MIYEON: B:MY BOYZ Round 3.
B:GINNER'S PICK Match 2nd battle.
MC MIYEON: Let's watch
WANNA ONE's Boomerang stage.
JINHO: Can they really
pull off an upset?
YUJEONG: I'm really looking forward
to this, can there really be a twist?
It's definitely
going to be a fierce competition.
WANNA ONE LEE DAEHWI: Boomerang
will probably be the hardest to perform.
WANNA ONE BAE JINYOUNG: That's right,
both the dance and the live are difficult.
- It's even hard for us too.
- That's right.
- OK, good, good.
- Fighting.
- Hey.
- Yes, fighting.
(Cute fighting)
Fighting.
KAI: I think we just
need to trust everything
KAI: we've practiced
and enjoy the stage.
LEE YUNSUNG: Our team is united
by spirit, so we'll answer with spirit.
LEE YUNSUNG: Our team can win.
YANG HYEONBIN: We were called the Avengers
team, so we'll do very well accordingly
YANG HYEONBIN: and
happily perform on stage.
LEE YEONTAE: I won't let what we
prepared so far go to waste or be in vain.
LEE YEONTAE: I'll just do
what I want and come back.
WANNA ONE BAE JINYOUNG: There's
something fierce in their eyes.
(Boomerang, original song by WANNA ONE,
Verse 1 by Boo+It Up team)
They are in sync so well.
(Admit it)
♪ALL: Wing, wing, wing, wing♪
♪MOON JAEIL: Boomerang♪
(Nailed it from the intro)
(That's right!)
(Okay)
Yes, you have to let go like that.
(Feels good)
♪MOON JAEIL: BOOMERANG♪
♪LEE JUNMYEONG: Go crazy♪
-♪MOON JAEIL: Boom, boom, boom, boom♪
- Wow, that's good.
♪LEE YEONTAE: I shot and threw it
toward your heart, but oh my god♪
♪LEE YEONTAE: The arrow goes pew and flies
back to me. It's tormenting me, no, no♪
♪YANG HYEONBIN, LEE JUNMYEONG: What
on earth is your true nature (What)♪
♪YANG HYEONBIN, MOON JAEIL: You
drive me crazy (You drive me crazy)♪
♪KIM JEONGHOON, PARK SECHAN: I'm
pretty decent too (Hey)♪
♪KIM JEONGHOON: How do you make me
so small, I don't know know♪
♪PARK SECHAN: Oh, every piece of your
face and action I love it, no, no, no, no, no♪
♪KIM JEONGHOON: No, no, no, no, no♪
♪YANG HYEONBIN: Look at me, only at me♪
♪LEE YEONTAE: Stay right next to me♪
♪MOON JAEIL: Oh darling, don't go♪
♪ALL: Wing, wing, wing, wing♪
♪LEE JUNMYEONG: Boomerang♪
♪LEE JUNMYEONG: Hey, go crazy♪
♪PARK SECHAN: Whether
I'm spinning or flung away♪
♪KIM JEONGHOON: Hey, go crazy♪
♪LEE YEONTAE: Boom, boom,
boom, boom, Boomerang♪
♪LEE JUNMYEONG: I run to you,
oh baby, come into my arms♪
♪PARK SECHAN: To be honest, there's
no man like me, never let you go♪
♪YANG HYEONBIN: I'm
a fool who only sees you♪
♪KIM JEONGHOON: Oh, what?♪
♪LEE YEONTAE: Teased by everyone
around, doesn't matter what they say♪
♪KIM JEONGHOON: You're
all I need, all I wanna do♪
(Team Switch)
(Applause)
Well done.
YUJU: At the end, just
throwing their shoulders...
(Team Switch)
(MOON JAEIL, so awesome)
(Boo+It Up team nailed it)
(Burn+Merang team comes on stage)
(It's cool)
KANG JUNSEONG: I'm looking forward
to it. I'm looking forward to it.
Will there be a change in atmosphere?
Their charisma is
- a slightly different kind of charisma?
- Let's go.
(Scream)
I'm going to defeat you
with my confidence.
LEE YUNSUNG: "This stage?
I'm going to own it."
BAN DANIEL: We will definitely win.
I'll show you everything we can.
(Excited)
(Immersing themselves)
(Boomerang, original song by WANNA ONE,
Verse 2 by Burn+Merang team)
(Team Burn+Merang
comes in with fierce aggression)
You're all doing so well...
it's giving me such a thrill.
(The trusted Avengers, Team Boo+It Up)
Since we're an Avengers team...
You could say we're
the Avengers team.
Looks like things are about to flip.
(The Avengers Team Boo+It Up facing doubts)
If I were to mention some areas where you could improve...
(Being flashy)
I notice you've got a bit of an odd flashy attitude.
KIM JEONGHOON: Looks like our team lost.
LEE JUNMYEONG: It felt complicated.
LEE YEONTAE: The Avengers ignite
the dawn of a turnaround, right?
(That moment is right now)
That moment is right now.
(Who are...)
We seriously gave it our all in preparation...
(the true Avengers?)
We practiced sweating buckets.
Because we put in a lot of effort...
(The comeback chaser and the revival dreamer)
We've worked the hardest
in all the rounds so far... Our
team is confident we'll win.
AB61X LEE DAEHWI (WANNA ONE): Now,
I really don't know who's going to win...
AB61X LEE DAEHWI (WANNA ONE): Both
teams are doing so well...
WANNA ONE BAE JINYOUNG: It's
hard to pick just one team...
WANNA ONE HA SUNGWOON: It looks
like their future depends on this...
(3 ROUND)
WANNA ONE HA SUNGWOON: To be
honest, I have a team I want to choose.
(Who will be WANNA ONE's TOP PICK?)
(B:MY BOYZ, August 9th (Sat) at 5:20 PM)
B:MY BOYZ, the fierce journey of boys
chasing the next-gen K-POP dream.
Round 4 online voting is now underway.
Here's how to vote.
You can participate once a day
through the SBS website,
My One Pick, and the Mysta app.
Please choose the boy you want to help
- fulfill his dream of debuting.