(Ryeo Un)
(Choi Hyun Wook)
(Seol In Ah)
(Shin Eun Soo)
(Twinkling Watermelon)
(Production sponsors)
(Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism, KOCCA)
(All people, organizations, locations, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
(Episode 13)
Hey, we're here.
I'm sorry, but could you make a lap around the house?
Sure. Let's do that.
I don't care who you are.
I don't care if you're a middle-aged woman.
I don't care if you turn out to be a zombie.
That's why we should...
stay together.
What do you say?
I'm hungry.
What? Then why don't we go somewhere and have something to eat?
I'm tired.
I want to rest.
Could you help me get home?
Hey, what next?
Sir. I'm so sorry. Could you make one last lap around the house?
That's enough.
Do you have a lot of money?
Sir, could you open up the trunk?
- Sure. - Okay.
Here.
What's this?
I think I just saw something that didn't make any sense at all.
What's wrong?
- Nothing. - Okay.
Thank you.
Hey.
Do you want to have ramyeon before you go?
What?
Can you start boiling the water for ramyeon?
Let me take care of the luggage first.
The kitchen is that way.
Shouldn't I say hello to your parents first?
They're not here.
- Both of them? - Yes.
I flew back to Korea from the US alone.
Then you've been staying here on your own the whole time?
At this rate, you might be too shocked to talk.
Then does it mean it's just you and me in this house?
Right?
- I'll put this away. - I'll boil the water.
Oh, no.
What's wrong?
What's that?
I think I just saw something that didn't make any sense again.
Nothing's wrong.
Okay. I'll carry this up for you.
Okay. Thank you so much. It's the 1st door on the 2nd floor.
- Okay. - Okay.
Gosh, that scared me.
(Who is the bandsman Mom loved?)
(Alprazolam)
Hey, be careful! Gosh. Please be careful.
What did you put in the egg? Why did it catch fire like this?
Why are you so angry about that?
You're scarier than the fire.
You live alone. Yet, you can't even cook a simple dish.
What have you been eating all this time?
How could you start such a big fire over just one egg?
Come on. Don't be like that.
You should be more careful next time.
Did you get hurt?
It sounds so nice.
Did you know?
People suddenly crave pancakes on rainy days because...
the sound of the rain falling and the sizzling pancakes...
sound similar.
Yes. So I have heard.
My mother used to cook me pancakes often on rainy days.
Was it like that with your family too?
- No. - What? Why not?
Having pancakes on rainy days is like a national law.
I was the only one in my family who could hear the rain falling.
It's ready.
Okay.
Gosh, it looks so good!
Thank you for the food.
Hey, this is so good. It's so crispy.
Don't tell me you were trying to go to the US to get some pancakes.
No way.
But why did you suddenly want to leave for the US?
Because I found out that my mother's first love was my dad.
- Hey... - No.
Don't ask me. I won't tell you anything.
This is all you're getting from me today.
I'm going to eat all the outer parts.
Hey, can you slow down?
- You might upset your stomach. - It's amazing. These are the best.
Come on. Tear a big piece for yourself.
I told you I wanted all the outer parts.
Hey, that's the tastiest part.
Come on. Let me have some too. I haven't had a meal today.
- I'm hungry. Let me have some too. - Hey.
Come on.
- Let me have some too. - Here.
- You'll get indigestion. Slow down. - I won't give it to you.
I want some of that too. Come on, let me have some!
Give it to me.
No. Wait.
Are you a CODA?
How did you know that?
You're the only one in your family who can hear the rain falling.
That's the word used to describe people like you.
No. That's not what I meant. How did you know the term, "CODA?"
Did that term not exist in 1995 yet?
Oh, that?
When I was in the US, I learned that from my deaf friend.
I see.
Ask me.
Ask you what?
- You don't have any questions? - Should I have questions?
That's odd.
When people find out that I'm a CODA,
they usually ask me a lot of questions.
At first, it starts off as curiosity.
Then it turns into compassion.
Afterward, it becomes pity which turns into kindness.
In the end, they worry and show concern.
That's just to name a few. I get all kinds of looks from them.
That's because people with questions...
want to hear that you're miserable.
That way, it will be proof that they are happy.
Gosh. What a way to kill my love for mankind.
That's how people are.
They want to offer sympathy,
instead of being on the receiving end of it.
Don't worry about them.
Let me give you an example.
Let's say you're super psyched about finding an interesting video.
But when you start to watch it, it's not what you wanted.
Then you would stop the video.
That's sort of what they're doing.
You should go home now.
Thank you for everything today.
Are you sure you can be alone here? You're not scared?
What? If I tell you I'm scared to be alone,
are you going to stay with me all night?
What? All night?
That's not what I meant.
Look at you.
You're already possessed by lust!
You're a lustful evil.
What?
Gosh.
You said I was a lustful evil.
Are you sure?
Am I sure I'm a lustful evil?
Not that.
Are you sure you can help me find my way back?
What?
I see.
Yes.
It will be hard.
I know.
I'm serious. It won't be that simple.
I know that too.
- You do? - Yes.
You weren't just referring to a mere way to go back to the US.
You're looking for a way to get to someone in the US.
I'll help you find that person.
Once I go back, I'll never be able to come back.
That's why, if possible,
I'll take my sweet time to help you.
I'll do my best to find a way,
but I will slow it down as much as possible.
That way,
I'll get to spend more time with you.
Yes!
I'll do my best to find a way,
but I will slow it down as much as possible.
That way, I'll get to spend more time with you.
What?
(Restricted Caller ID)
No way.
- Hello. - Good evening.
- Master? - Did you have a pleasant trip?
Gosh, you startled me. Wait.
Why are you asking me that in the past tense today?
You're indeed quick at noticing these things.
I think it's time to end the trip now.
My trip is going to end?
Then...
does it mean I'll go back to 2023?
Bingo.
Soon, there will come a day with two moons in the sky.
The door of time that connects the two worlds will open.
That will be the only day you'll be allowed to go back.
When will that be?
To make sure you don't get lost,
I will keep the light on at La Vida Music.
- Bye then. - Wait.
When will there be two moons?
As for that...
Coming soon.
Hello? Wait. Master!
Soon, there will come a day with two moons in the sky.
The door of time that connects the two worlds will open.
That will be the only day you'll be allowed to go back.
Newspapers.
(Snail Guesthouse)
"My left hand is there solely for support."
Goal!
Darn it.
The festival is over.
Don't come to see me ever again.
You and I live in different worlds, anyway.
Se Gyeong.
You're going to school early. Are you a model student now?
I'm an old man now.
I've been getting up early for no reason these days.
Sorry.
Did you wish that I would become an old man?
No. I'm sorry I ran away at the festival without telling you.
I see. Is that why you're here?
Yes.
I wanted to give you a sincere apology...
and tell you the truth.
Yi Chan. The truth is...
I know. You like Ha Eun Gyeol, right?
How did you know?
Do you think I'm blind?
I don't know if you're going to believe me,
but I had no intention of using or deceiving you.
Actually, there's a secret I can't tell people.
Thank you.
- That was random. - I know.
Thanks to you, every day has been exciting like a festival.
You made my heart flutter and I had fun.
I gave my all to my youth.
I also had a blast.
Although I lost the bet,
thanks to you, I have a great story.
Aren't you mad?
No.
Because you left, the festival became fun for everyone,
not a show about love.
You were perfect to the end.
What a bummer.
I should have chosen you.
It's too late now.
Hey, you don't even seem a bit upset.
Didn't you know? I'm a cold-hearted guy.
Did you even like me?
This is a story with an open ending... Oh, my.
It's too soon for touching.
I wasn't touching you. I was punching you.
Let's leave it as a story with an open ending.
(The début show of Watermelon Sugar)
What are you doing?
I'm trying to think of swear words for you.
When will you move all the stuff in the practice room?
The other guys have already pulled their stuff out.
Talk about having loyal friends.
What do you expect?
It was just a temporary band we put together for the festival.
Ha Yi Chan. Oh Ma Joo.
The principal wants to see you guys.
Did you guys get into trouble again?
Goodness.
What is this? What are you guys doing here?
What is this? I have a bad feeling about this.
Why...
No way.
Did they find out about our fight with Jindo Dog Gang?
Is everyone here?
Yes, sir!
Sit down.
- Sit down. - Okay.
So...
according to what I heard,
you guys completely destroyed the stage at the festival.
There's one more guy, right?
The one who goes to Seowon Arts High School.
What was his name?
- It's our fault. - It's our fault.
I committed a grave sin.
No, you didn't.
I think I can deal with the student who goes to a different school.
Come on.
(Baekwang High School)
You guys, sign here first.
(No! I can't drop out of school! I'll be a better person!)
(I need a high school diploma to inherit Ma Joo's Fabrics.)
- Please. - No.
It's an emergency.
We're in dire danger.
When the class... No, when you're done with cleaning,
come to the practice room immediately.
What's the matter?
What happened?
(Application for the 6th National Teen Band Contest)
What's that?
It's an application form for the National Teen Band Contest.
Men need a big stage.
Sign the application.
Enter the contest.
And kill the stage.
- Oh, my gosh. - But,
no matter what it takes,
you should beat Ilyoung High school.
Is Ilyoung High School that great?
The principal of Ilyoung High School is our principal's home boy.
And he's his arch enemy.
Because they always fight over the number of students...
accepted to Seoul National University.
And we lose all the time.
Their school band is good as well.
He said we should beat Ilyoung.
It means we should win the contest.
Let's do it then. It's not impossible.
He looked like Yi Chan's son just now.
The problem isn't just their talent.
You've written some songs, right?
Have you not?
Well...
We mostly do covers.
So we haven't written anything yet.
What?
What are you going to do then?
You must have your own song...
to participate in the contest.
What are you going to do now?
What have you been doing?
They wrote so many songs.
And you guys...
- We'll make one. - We'll make one.
What?
This is what happened.
We can make one. What's the problem?
He must be Yi Chan's son.
My son is right.
Let's write our own song.
Yi Chan, you must've bought a vending machine.
You just put coins in the machine, and a song comes out like magic.
We're as dumb as rocks. How can we write a song in a month?
We did it.
We practiced just for a month for the festival.
Do you not remember?
Close your eyes and think about it.
The blood, sweat, and tears we shed.
The hot breath.
As a result,
we received thrilling heat and cheers.
The great attention and love from our female fans.
Don't you want to feel it again?
Not with covers, but with our own song.
Yes.
I guess.
In that sense,
how about going to a song camp next weekend?
- A song camp? - A song camp?
Let's go and decide on the theme of the song.
To celebrate the revival of Watermelon Sugar,
let's encourage teamwork.
How about that? What do you say?
I think it sounds good.
- I like it too. - Yes. Let's go.
Yes. Let's go.
We're dumb,
but we will make something if we work together. Don't you think so?
Okay. Manager.
Find an accommodation and train tickets right away.
Yes, sir.
Train tickets and accommodation.
But we should tell Se Gyeong and Chung Ah too, right?
We need a hairstylist, makeup artist, stylist,
and photographer for the big stage.
Which of you will tell them?
Eun Gyeol will do it.
The meeting is over.
Let's go have tteokbokki. It's on me.
Ma Joo, please bring my bag.
- He... - He just left.
Are you not going to argue?
- Why are you guys not arguing? - Why are you not arguing?
It's weird.
Why are they not arguing? That's odd.
- We can do it. - As long as you concentrate.
- Okay? We're Watermelon. - As long as you do your job.
Sugar.
- Watermelon. - Sugar.
- Go. - Wait.
Let's go.
I have something to say.
Well, actually, I...
Should I become a priest?
Why does everyone want to confess their sins to me?
You're late, you punk.
Se Gyeong told me everything in the morning.
What? What did she say?
She said she liked you.
It must be nice to have a good look.
Hey.
Are you okay with that?
Would you be okay if you were me?
Just punch me then.
I was going to do it.
You should treat her well.
I'll be watching you.
If you make her cry,
you're going to bleed from your eyes.
All right.
We're still friends then, right?
Stay out of my sight for a while.
Until when?
After three minutes.
My 18-year-old dad is much cooler than I thought.
Why? Let's go together.
Is it...
because of Yi Chan?
No, it's not.
I'm busy preparing for the exhibition.
I told you.
Se Gyeong didn't choose anyone at the festival.
It's your chance.
So come with us.
I know you've been trying your best...
to make things work for Yi Chan and me.
But I'll take care of it myself from now on.
Don't be like this. Let's go to the song camp.
I'll help you.
It's my life.
Not yours.
I can do it by myself. Do you not trust me?
Let's now learn sign language then.
My 18-year-old mom is becoming stronger.
Chung Ah, let's go to the song camp.
You couldn't watch the festival.
You must come. I'll be waiting.
(Chung Ah, let's go to the song camp.)
(You couldn't watch the festival. You must come. I'll be waiting.)
No.
Gosh.
The band I thought was going to disband revived.
Everything is going well, but I...
I think it's time to end the trip now.
What are you doing here?
Well...
My teacher kept telling me...
to play the cello in front of the whole class.
Everything seems to be going well, but I...
I told him I didn't want to do it and that I'd rather die.
For some strange reason, I keep...
So I'm playing hooky now.
Pretend you didn't see me.
I keep wanting to stay here just a little longer.
Let's go.
No, I'm not going back in there.
Don't you know what "playing hooky" means?
I never told you to go back to your class.
Let's run away together.
It's not time yet.
Not today.
Right now,
we can be together.
Be honest with me.
About what?
You said you were smitten with me at first sight.
That was a lie, right?
What?
I'll give you three seconds.
You have three seconds to tell me when you started falling for me...
and why you like me. One!
When you came back from the US.
What?
The day I ran into you when you were working in Hongdae.
I liked that you were honest.
I wouldn't say it was love at first sight.
I fell for you while bickering with you.
- Why? What is it? - That's really me!
I'm serious!
What?
(Tteokbokki, Sundae, Fritters, Dumplings)
I said, no! I'm not going.
Let go, will you?
Are you really going to be like this?
Yi Chan.
Does the band need a designer or not?
You said she had already declined.
And she doesn't want to go to the song camp.
Right, so let's persuade her in person!
Why bother persuading her when she doesn't want to go?
And that girl, Yoon Chung Ah...
- She won't listen to me. - What?
Get Eun Gyeol to talk to her!
Hey, stop! Eun Gyeol rarely sees her these days.
And because of the exhibition, she’s been practically...
- living at the academy! - Hey, let go!
Let's go and persuade her since we need her!
If you want to persuade her, do it yourself!
Okay.
I'll do the talking, so just be my interpreter.
- Let go. - I don't know sign language!
I don't know either.
- I've just started to learn... - Oh, here it is!
My pager. Someone's paging me.
Hey, I'll go check this message quickly. Wait right here.
Seriously, stay put.
You know I won't stay put.
Oh, right.
Hey, get out of my way!
Sorry, sir. She'll be out of your way in no time.
The difference would be like a split second, you know?
Thank you. Have a nice day! Thank you again!
Hi, friend.
Have you been well?
Hey, the teacher said to go and eat something now.
The interim evaluation will begin in an hour.
- Shoot. I hate the evaluation. - Come on. Let's go.
Gosh, I'm tired.
- Hey, come on. - Yes, I'm coming.
Drink up.
You must be thirsty.
You don't need to be so guarded.
There's no poison in it, so relax and...
Hey, wait!
Wait, hey!
Hey, where are you going? Hey!
She can't understand what you're saying.
Sorry?
Hey, wait.
You go to the art academy over there, don't you?
I also attend an academy in the area, so I see you often.
I go to Dongwon High School. I'm in 11th grade.
You must be an art major at Seowon Arts High School.
Wait, one moment.
If you're free now,
how about we talk at a quiet café somewhere?
I'll buy you a parfait.
To tell you the truth,
you're so my type.
Hey!
Hey, do you take me as a joke?
Why do you keep ignoring me?
If you don't like me, just say so.
Hey, why are you flat out ignoring me?
- You little... - Hey, don't.
- She can't speak. - What?
She's deaf.
What? She really can't hear anything?
Is this real? Or is she just faking it?
- Come here. - Who are you?
You too. Come here.
- Hey, it hurts. - Ouch.
- All right, come on. - Hey, it hurts.
Darn it.
Do you think you're little kids?
Must you be so immature and childish?
Open your diary now and write this down.
"Dear Diary, a handsome guy taught me a lesson today."
"It was very impressive."
"He taught me that I was a real jerk."
"From now on, I should work hard to be a better person."
You won't write it down?
You'd better not cross the line.
I warned you nicely this time.
Lay a finger on her again, and you're dead meat.
Gosh.
Hey. Why did you have to pick her, of all the girls?
Hey, look.
That deaf girl was wearing earphones.
How was I supposed to know?
That's true. How were you supposed to know?
I told them not to cross the line. And here they are, moving the line.
- No... - Hey!
Drum rolls.
Okay, let me try that one more time.
(Dud)
- Try it on. - Yes, I must.
- It suits you. It's so pretty. - Does it?
It looks good on me, right?
Here, look.
What is this?
Here, princess.
I'm the frog prince.
I'm the princess.
(Succeed and get one more.)
You see, I'm very competitive.
- Are you? - Yes.
So am I.
Hey, watch.
Eat this.
- It's good. - Yes, it's good.
You have to keep smiling for 15 minutes.
- Like this? For 15 minutes? - That's right.
Are your eyebrows this thick?
They're very thick. Look.
My, you do have such thick eyebrows.
(Alprazolam)
I found this while moving your suitcase a while back...
but missed my chance to give it back to you.
Can I ask you why you need this?
Does it have something to do with why you hate the cello so much?
Or with why you ran away to the swimming pool?
Is it connected to the reason you can't find a way to go back?
My mom forced me to look happy,
while I expressed with my whole body that I was miserable.
We fought like a spear and shield.
When I pulled myself together, I was in front of a psychiatrist.
So I expressed how miserable I was after suppressing it for a while,
and the psychiatrist gave me that.
Ever since then, those pills and I have been best friends.
Does it answer your question?
What made you that miserable?
You want me to talk all about it?
In front of you?
Gosh, forget it.
If I tell you, I'll just sound like a spoiled girl.
I'll sound like a baby.
It'll do nothing but show you how fragile I am mentally.
Shall I still tell you all about it?
Shall we see which one of us is more miserable?
Welcome. We heard you could play the cello pretty well too.
I didn't want to argue with my mom,
so I listened to her and came here.
But what do you girls do here anyway?
This is like a social club.
You must know what it is.
Successful people make social clubs like this to help each other...
and build connections.
So, you're like Barbies invited...
to the connection-building club your moms created.
Okay, so what do you normally do here?
We bribe the judges at the competitions...
and find out which songs will be on the exams.
- What? - Oh, that's what our moms do.
All we have to do is look pretty like dolls.
Until when?
Until we conquer the world?
Our moms' vanity and ambition won't be satisfied until then.
Oh, didn't your mom tell you to befriend me?
Let's show her. Although, I'm just number one in the country now.
Smile, like a pretty doll.
We should make our moms happy.
One, two, three.
You must be devastated, but be mature about it and get over it.
You don't want people to say you won...
first place by default because of a friend who took her own life.
Don't let your mind falter.
But remember these emotions you're feeling now...
so you can think of them when you're playing sad music later on.
What's she doing?
I can't hear it.
I hear no sound.
I can't hear anything!
ENT specialists couldn't figure out what was wrong with me,
so I became best friends with psychiatric medications.
My mom, who wanted to be compensated for her failed life through me,
became best friends with alcohol.
It's such a cliché story.
A pathetic story about a mentally fragile mother and daughter.
Let's go.
Hey. Be honest, okay?
You guys stopped her.
You provoked, threatened, and made fun of her!
You got caught while extorting money from her,
so you're trying to dump it all on us.
- You little... - Quiet down, both of you!
You still haven't finished writing it?
Hey, you! If you keep this up, you and I will have a problem.
You refused to call your parents...
and don't want to write down what happened.
What am I supposed to do if you're being so uncooperative?
Sir.
She can't gauge the situation.
What can that deaf girl tell you when she can't hear a thing?
Hey, you little... Do you have a death wish?
Good for you that you're not deaf.
What did you hear so well...
that you're talking such trash?
Hey, granny. Who are you to butt in?
I'm this boy's grandmother.
They say you should wrap this up and let him go...
unless you want to put him behind bars.
Says who?
Kang Chang Sik.
Who is Kang Chang Sik?
(Warmhearted Trustworthy Police)
You mean, my chief?
Chang Sik...
stayed at my guesthouse while studying to become a police officer.
He had nothing and nowhere to stay.
He was stick-skinny, so I fed him well.
And this is how he's repaying me for my hospitality.
Has he not called you yet to tell you to let him go?
No, not yet.
I can't let him go yet as their statements don't match up.
And they'll be the ones getting released.
But the lady at the shoe store saw what happened.
What?
I visited every single shop in that area...
and managed to find a witness.
No, let me explain. I just wanted to talk to her.
Hey, be quiet!
See? Now, it all matches up.
Hurry up and let them go.
It's well past their mealtime. They must be hungry.
(Mapo Dohwa Patrol Division Station)
Oh, boy.
Since we met like this,
you should come...
and eat with us before you go home.
You didn't have to look for a witness yourself.
You've watched too many detective shows.
A witness, my foot. I lied.
What?
Grandma, that's considered perjury.
What were you counting on...
You, of course.
There are only two reasons you might hit someone.
It's always one of these two.
Actualizing justice or saving a life.
Do you like her?
What? Come on.
She's pretty.
If it's pity, forget it.
It must feel so cold and lonely...
to live in that isolated world all alone.
If you're going to hurt her down the road, don't even start.
I don't want to see you hurting.
I had fun today, thanks to you.
Get home safely.
Hey.
There's no scale that can measure who's hurting more,
and there's no one who can judge that.
No one has the right to judge others' pain,
and we have no duty to have it acknowledged by others.
You know,
if you're hurting, just accept it.
Only you know how much you're hurting.
I won't force you to look happy.
A competition to see who's more miserable? Forget that.
You know, from time to time,
I hope I can be your prescription.
Instead of those pills, I wish to be...
your best friend.
(Alprazolam)
Then when your life can twinkle again on its own,
I hope it twinkles as radiantly as possible.
I hope that day comes soon...
because...
I don't have much time left with me.
(Restaurant Waryong)
What took you so long?
I told you to come at the speed of a missile.
Hey, what happened?
What were you doing at the police station?
And how did you get that wound?
Hey, Eun Gyeol.
You get paid to do your job. What do you do?
- What? - I mean, it's the Jinsung Family.
They must pay you pretty well.
Do you only care about fattening your wallet?
What about Yoon Chung Ah? You don't care about her at all?
What on earth are you talking about? Explain so I can understand.
Chung Ah...
didn't come to the festival, but you didn't even care.
She doesn't want to go to the song camp, and you don't care.
Even if she gets insulted in the street, you don't care!
So tell me, you jerk. What do you do?
Chung Ah...
got insulted in the street?
Forget it.
I have an important job to do. You'd better cooperate.
Hey, wait. "An important job?"
Are you going to get back at those guys?
You should be ashamed of yourself if you can't even do this for her.
Yi Chan, don't do this. Calm down!
I'm sorry, Yi Chan.
Everything I said the other day was a lie.
I should get out of the picture for you and Se Gyeong to...
(I should get out of the picture for you and Se Gyeong to...)
Chung Ah. It's me, Eun Gyeol. Can you come to the practice room?
You need to stop Yi Chan. Please!
Sorry.
I figured you wouldn't come if I called you here,
so I asked Eun Gyeol to do it for me.
(You said first that we should be friends.)
You said first that we should be friends.
(And you said you liked me.)
And you said you liked me.
(How could you take it back after making my heart flutter?)
How could you take it back after making my heart flutter?
How could you not come to the festival?
How could you not go to the song camp with us?
(How could you be so mean?)
How could you be so mean?
I wanted to sing you a song at the festival.
But you didn't come to the festival.
If you can't come to the song camp either...
(Then I should just do it here.)
Then I should just do it here.
Watch carefully.
This is only for you and no one else.
Can you believe it?
In my dreams
You're a princess under a magic spell
Even though I always struggle
With my gestures toward you
I am strongly determined
To save you once again
I put my hands together and prayed
For endless courage and wisdom
Past the magic castle and across the swamp
From afar, I can see you deep inside the dark cave
Now, hold my hand
Then we feel our bodies floating into the air
Freely in the sky
Don't be surprised even if we fly away together
The world that will unfold before us
One moment.
Gosh, these fools. Don't they know what time it is now?
Darn it.
Hey, is Chung Ah really coming?
Yes, Eun Gyeol called me yesterday.
Hey, why are you so excited?
Well, she's growing on me.
Gosh, not that again.
Is she really coming with Eun Gyeol?
I don't know. I guess she'll be here soon.
Gosh, these two...
- Sorry we're late! - What?
What?
What's going on, you two?
Don't tell me you two are going out.
Yes.
What? You guys knew?
I knew when Se Gyeong suddenly left...
in the middle of our performance.
When Eun Gyeol skipped the wrap-up party and left,
I thought it was obvious.
Hey, then Yi Chan... What about Yi Chan, then?
My gosh. What if he's downing a whole bottle of water somewhere?
Make some noise, everyone!
Our designer is here!
What? You guys knew?
Yes. I knew when he couldn't stop...
talking about the guitar pick she gave him.
It became obvious when he made such a big fuss about Chung Ah...
not coming to the wrap-up party.
Am I the only idiot here? How come I didn't know anything?
You guys. Where did your discipline go?
You practiced the greeting, right?
Goodness.
Attention!
Parade, rest.
Greet our designer.
- Hi, friend. - Hi, friend.
- Have you been well? - Have you been well?
My gosh.
Hi, friends.
- I think she understood it. - It worked.
Guys, the train will depart soon.
Move it!
- Okay, let's go! - Don't forget your stuff.
- This way, guys. - Shall we?
Yes.
(Cheongnyangni Station)
Hello.
Hey, can you check?
Is this it?
No, this means "itchy."
- You try it. - I did, just now. How about "fun?"
- Show us. - Do it.
- "It's fun." - That looks like "itchy."
When it's the former...
- See that? - This is more...
The cruel consequences I must suffer for choosing you.
Got it? All right, you try it now.
Try "fun."
I lost all my fans. What will you do about it?
- Oh, boy. - Hey, try "fun."
Well...
I'll be good to you from now on.
Forget it. Just keep your promise.
"Promise?"
What promise?
Oh, how I said I'd find a way for you to go back?
- No, not that. - No?
What else did I promise?
You promised to work diligently to delay it.
I think I've missed my chance to take my life because of you.
Why should I give up my life because of my mom?
Now, I think it's unfair.
The star candy gave me a revelation.
So I'm going to try living my life...
and have fun while at it.
So...
you'd better not hurry.
If you give up on working diligently toward your goal,
and if you disappear without a word again,
you're so dead.
- Where's the restroom? - To say you like someone...
- Only I can do this. - Oh, there it is.
- "I like Chung Ah." - Hey, don't do that.
- I can profess my feelings too. - "I like you."
It's not time yet.
Not today.
For now, we can be together...
(1 Missed Call)
(No Service)
Shoot.
(Unisex Toilet)
This can't be.
How can this be here?
(Restricted Caller ID)
Hello?
Master, is it you?
Oh, my. I knew you'd welcome me.
When did I fall asleep again?
This is a dream, isn't it?
Well...
I do think that your dreamy trip is nearing its end.
Don't tell me I have to go back to 2023.
Soon, you will see two moons in the sky.
- Connecting the two worlds... - I don't want to hear it.
I don't want to go back yet.
If I do go back, it'll happen when I want to return. I'm hanging up.
No, wait.
You have only one chance to go back.
If you miss that chance,
you may get locked up in the past forever.
Are you okay with that?
I may get locked up forever?
Don't worry.
I sent a special helper to help you out.
A helper? What kind of helper?
Your helper...
and travel companion who will return with you.
Sorry?
Are you saying there's another time traveller besides me?
Who? Where is this person now?
How can I meet this person?
This person may be closer than you think.
Coming soon.
Wait, mister. I mean, Master! Hello?
Shoot. Why isn't this working?
Darn it. Please work.
- Hey. - What are you doing?
The time traveller Master was talking about...
The helper Master was talking about...
- It was you? - It was you?
(Special thanks to Cheong Kyu Soo, Lee So Hee, and Kang Yi Seok)
(Twinkling Watermelon)
How could you be the other time traveller?
So, you've been hitting on my mom?
I'll make sure I raise Chung Ah...
to be the future leader of the Jinsung Family.
I haven't completed all my missions yet.
I have yet to complete the most challenging one.
What is it?
You must've heard of White Night, the legendary rock band.
That man over there was the front man of that band.
Are there any magazines with articles about that band?
Yi Chan, help me. Come and get me.
What are you people trying to do in this house?
What brings you here?
I want to know about my mom.