So that’s today’s homework..
Okay,
class dismissed.
What’s with the stare?
Think I'm still mad at you?
I told you, it's fine.
Don’t be sad or feel guilty.
I’m waiting for you to pack up.
You kept staring,
so I thought something was up.
Goddess,
he’s a true introvert.
“Did you see the video?”
“The video Nam lost to Junior?”
“Nam Splashed, Nam Crashed”
“What a cheater.”
“He cheated but still lost,
I’d die from shame”
“So pathetic”
“It’s good, budd.
Let’s cheat better next time.”
“Students, be quiet.”
“I said be quiet.”
Move over.
I am moving.
Move over there.
Trust fall.
Will you be quiet?
Be quiet, or you’ll do
community service twice a week.
I have an announcement.
All clubs must hand in paperwork
to document their effectiveness.
Boo. Boo.
As for students without a club.
No matter.
I have created a new club for you:
the "Community Service Club".
Members of this club
will clean the old building
after class.
I hope I made myself clear.
You are dismissed.
Help me!!
We could have avoided this,
if you guys didn’t beef with Nam.
I'd rather clean than
deal with him.
Good thinking.
Unlike someone.
Why did you quit
the swimming club again?
You were already in a club.
I just...
like cleaning.
So how do we clean
all this mess?
Just do what you can, children.
School is cutting
budget right now.
Hang in there.
Do you want my help?
It's okay, Auntie.
Your hands are already full.
You go rest, Auntie.
Alright.
Children,
I'll leave the rest to you.
Okay.
Dust everywhere!
Not even paid to do this.
Our semester fee is 47,375 THB.
That’s 94,750 per year.
There are 825 students.
That equals 78,168,750
They could easiy afford
10 more cleaners.
Yikes, nerd alert.
Where should we start?
If I got into the book club,
I wouldn't be cleaning
right now.
I was so close to joining.
It's all your fault, Jeng.
Will you stop whining?
Are we gonna be free
for the whole semester,
if we get this done today?
That’s right.
Let's finish the job, folks.
Sun, Junior,
I take back what I said.
Thanks for leaving that club.
Second that.
We won’t get the job done
if it’s only Jodd here.
That felt like an insult.
Amazing.
So you do realize.
A nerd with a mouth.
No need to thank me.
You just leave all the cleaning to me.
I’ve never done this before.
What are you?
A spoiled rich kid?
Don't say that, Junior,
or Jodd will slack off.
When you clean,
start all the way up.
Then sweep down in one go.
if you’ve got some rags,
you can wet it and cover
the broom when you clean.
That way, dust and cobwebs
won’t scatter like this.
I read about it in a book called
“108 Ways to Clean Your Home.”
Aren’t you a bit too chill?
Your chair looks shaky.
It’s all your fault, Jeng.
Let me help.
Sweep the floor properly.
Just copy me.
Do not copy him.
Give it.
Do it this way.
Show me again?
Move aside.
You go left, I go right.
I can just do this myself.
it’s alright, I wanna help.
How is this helping...
The broom is too short.
No, you are short.
I should be short.
My name is Junior.
Sun, stay still. Don't move.
I’m gonna fall.
So, you two...
What? We were...
Just cleaning.
Cleaning.
Five stars for teamwork.
Gimme five.
Community Service Club, go go.
Give it, fam.
Where’s my fivers?
I’ll give you tenners!
Right.
Hooray!
They acted cool and quit the club.
And now they’re cleaning the school.
Pathetic.
Let's give them some.
Aren’t they having too much fun?
Look at this guy,
practicing like crazy just
to get the scholarship.
If he loses it,
he’s got nothing else going.
Are we good, buddy?
Just messing with you.
You look kinda stressed.
Hey, Nam-splash.
Bye Nam-crash.
Nam, you're one of a kind,
you cheated and still lost.
Respect.
Tonight, you two go handle them.
Open the door.
Junior. Junior.
Junior. Where are you?
Junior, are you alright?
Junior.
Junior. Are you alright?
Are you okay, Junior?
Stop panicking. I’m fine.
It’s them again, isn’t it?
Umm..
Let's go.
Come on.
I need ten minutes.
What are you doing?
Don't you feel cold?
When I get cold,
my brother would hug me.
Don't be shy.
Suddenly being locked up
doesn’t feel so bad.
Why's that?
I like feeling cold.
Are you alright?
It's Nam again, right?
It’s fine.
What are you doing?
You’re not getting into my class
looking like that.
What should I do then?
I was bullied.
This is my only gym shirt.
Don't talk back.
I won’t be in your class then.
“This is an announcement.”
“Student who took scissors
from the sewing room,”
return them at once.”
What the hell?
What's wrong with you?
I'm just returning what’s yours.
I feel kinda cute wearing it.
Nam is a good stylist.
I’m gonna grab the cleaning stuff.
I take that back, Nam sucks.
Are you gonna let Nam
get away with this?
I won’t.
I just don't want to
play by his games.
Jodd.
Are you alright?
It hurts, duh!
Come.
Don’t get in there.
You might slip too.
Gimme a hand.
It hurts.
Can you walk?
Jodd.
Quick, take him to the nurse.
I’ll take care of the mess here.
Careful.
Slowly.
- Don't slip.
- Careful.
What happened to you?
Jodd slipped and fell, ma'am.
Bring him to the bed.
Aw, it hurts too much.
Ouchy.
I haven’t started.
Please be gentle.
So what did you do?
I greeted the floor too hard.
Not hard enough.
Ouch! Easy, easy. Ma'am.
You deserve it,
cracking a bad joke like that.
Kids these days
just can’t stay out of trouble.
You, give me a hand.
No, no, no.
- No, no, no.
- Stay still.
It stings.
Ouch! It hurts.
Stay strong, kiddo.
Ouch! Jeng, easy.
You’ll need a soft cast
on your ankle.
It's just a sprain,
nothing serious.
A cast?
Ouch! It hurts.
Easy, please.
Come on.
Name went too far this time.
Why won’t he leave us be?
Nam will do it again.
What should we do?
It’s time we fight fire
with fire.
Alright, break into groups
assigned to you
for our volunteer activities.
Today we’re doing something
a bit different.
One of the groups
will clean the chicken coops.
Any volunteers?
Raise your hand.
I have faith in you...
Junior.
I am so proud of you.
Hey, Auntie Noi.
Children, are you here
with the school?
Do you live here?
Come inside to
have some water.
It's hot today.
It's okay, Auntie.
We have to do some work soon.
Come visit when you’re done.
Want my help?
Nah.
You’re bad at cleaning.
Just watch the chickens.
Wanna come out?
Who’s this human
talking to?
You. I’m talking to you.
So you know bird-speak?
Yup, I know it.
Wanna come out, then?
I’d love that,
human boy.
The thing is,
do you see that guy over there?
I want you to find out
what they’re scheming about.
Deal, babe.
Of course the night guard
would fall asleep.
Really?
I don't think so.
All night guards do is sleep.
He’s not gonna be asleep this time.
Okay, then...
You wanna bet on it?
If he falls asleep,
you gotta pay up.
I’ll throw in 2K.
He wouldn't.
Cuz you’re paying him
to sneak around at night.
What the heck?
Where are the chickens?
Jodd, Jeng.
Jodd, can you stall Ms. Samorn
for a bit? Jeng, you too.
Why?
Don't ask now.
Where are the chickens?
They ran away,
but I'll get them back.
We’re screwed.
Ms. Samorn is there, quick.
Go now.
- Just go.
- Jodd, come on.
I’ll signal you.
What should we do?
What the heck?
Ma'am, please. Ma'am.
Hello, boys.
What's wrong with your shirt?
Shirt?
Oh...The chickens surrounded
my friend, ma'am.
I guess
they must be fighter cocks.
Good thing
we made it out, unharmed.
But a button came off.
- Button.
- Oh...
Okay. Come on, I'll teach you
how to sew it on.
That is great.
A good opportunity to
bring theory into practice.
You want us to do it?
Learning by doing
makes you remember.
Go ahead.
Okay.
Just try it.
Sew it at the middle of the button.
That's it.
Just pierce it through, right?
Just do it. Be careful.
You don’t wanna cut his nipple.
- There. Be careful.
- All right.
Almost sewed into my hand.
Almost there.
Are you done yet?
Someone let the chickens out.
Oh, no.
Heck, no!
Jodd's shirt is torn too, ma'am.
But the chickens are out.
But, ma'am.
My nipple is showing.
At this point, we need to do
some hidden stitches.
Hidden stitches?
Let me show you.
Be careful.
Tonight they’re scheming something
at the old building.
But it doesn't seem
like a good thing.
So, this is it.
So you don't see
any stitches.
Why's that?
Because I hid them.
All right, hidden stitches.
All right.
Watch how I do it.
I'll do it slowly.
Okay.
Ma'am, I think I got it.
Okay, you are very smart.
But I still need
to finish this tiny bit.
The chickens!
Over here.
Help me.
Work together.
If you can't catch them,
you are not allowed
to go back to the school.
Help me, I hurt my leg. Ma'am.
You just catch it.
- One... two... three.
- Do it now.
Come on, catch it.
Catch it now.
How did I end up here?
Why are you surprised?
Oh?
Are you visiting your son?
No, no.
So, why are you sneaking peeks?
What are you doing exactly
in front of school?
I happen to be
a zookeeper.
I am looking for a penguin.
He escaped from the cage.
Penguin?
Like a penguin penguin?
Like...
an actual penguin?
- Um...
- Not a plushie?
Not a plushie.
You...
Sure you’re not daydreaming or...
Let's say it's a real penguin.
Got that?
And he is so smart.
Most importantly, he actually
understands human language.
This is so awesome.
Are you…
Are you on drugs?
Or in the unit
for secret operations?
Let's say,
it's all right
if you don't see him.
I just
want to show off my penguin.
He understands human language.
That's all.
It's okay.
I am leaving now.
He understands human language
for every word?
Yes, yes.
Like yellow.
Yellow.
Mango.
Ito!
Are you lonely?
I’ve been here for a long time,
seen many bonkers.
Parents can be cray-cray.
He is lonely.
This crazy guy
searching for a penguin.
Said he lost his penguin.
Too many things happen
to me in one day.
Wait up.
We are here.
It's Nam’s doing for sure.
What the heck?
What should we do?
Auntie.
Oh?
What happened, children?
And why are you still here?
We missed the bus.
Oh!
Come in first, children.
Beware of the mosquitoes.
Come in quickly.
Thank you.
Be careful.
Careful, dear.
And have you eaten
anything yet, children?
Not yet, Auntie.
Come sit and have a meal first.
Sit here.
There’s so much food, Auntie.
Is someone else coming too?
No one is coming.
It happens.
I planned to make a little bit,
but I always ended up making a lot.
I’ll go fry some more eggs for you.
Just a moment.
Yes.
Are you hungry, Jodd?
Starving.
As much as you can, okay?
So you won’t be hungry
when you go back.
Thank you.
That was close. Why didn’t you
watch out for the car , dear?
You might get hurt.
Are you feeling dizzy again, child?
Have you been taking
your medicine properly?
I can't remind you
when you're at school, you know.
All right.
Look.
What did you get on your clothes?
My friends asked me out for fun.
Are you going on
a trip abroad, Auntie?
No, child.
I’m moving in with my partner.
In Australia.
So, when are you leaving, Auntie?
I am not sure yet.
I need to finish all my errands.
I’m afraid that when I leave...
you all will miss me.
Oh, I'm already missing you, Auntie!
Where else could we find
a custodian as lovely as you?
You are too much.
But I will definitely miss you.
If the new custodian is mean,
I will miss you more and more.
I will miss you too.
Your food is the most delicious.
I'm afraid you'll end up
missing us more, Auntie.
I will surely miss all of you children.
You should go there.
There's no way
we’ll ever forget you, Auntie.
Oh, Sun. Are you serious?
Auntie might be kidding.
Right?
Sun’s talking a lot today, huh?
Normally, Jodd is
the most talkative one.
Oh.
Come on, hurry up and eat!
I will take you all back to school.
If we're late,
the teacher will scold you.
Sun.
Come here.
Did he go to sleep?
No.
It’s too warm.
I can't breathe.
Why are you so stiff?
You’re not soft like me.
Isn’t it good?
It's good. Stiff is good.
Don't come too close. It's hot.
I’m falling off.
Oh, no.
He already went to sleep.
You’re right.
Keep your voice down.
I'll be back.
Two...three...four...
five...six...seven...
It's good being a guard.
I am doing nothing
and still have money.
But if there were
hundreds of kids like this one,
I'll be rich.
So good.
Proud to be rich.
Cheers.
Oh.
I'll get some sleep.
Is it really this easy?
Let’s go now?
Wait for ten minutes.
Before I left,
I saw Nam still asleep.
So, Jeng made a plan.
What took you so long?
What did you guys do?
Jeng and I were here
for quite some time.
- Sun was in the bathroom.
- Sun was asleep.
What was it exactly?
Well,
we slept and went to the bathroom.
You slipped up.
You just go.
You are defeated.
Anyway, under the tree
is a path to the old building.
You and Junior wait for him there.
Then, Jodd and I...
will go wait for them
at the old building.
Okay?
Okay, go.
Quiet.
Go.
Oh, it fell down.
What are the lights in the sky, Sun?
They’re stars.
It's beautiful.
So, what is a star?
Well...
we are now on
something like a star.
It's called...
the planet Earth,
a big rock floating in the sky.
But actually,
planets don’t give out light.
The light from the sun
reflects on those rocks.
That’s why they sparkle.
Hey, what was
that light just now, Sun?
A shooting star.
People make a wish on it.
They believe that
their wish will come true.
Do you want to make a wish?
Palms together
and close your eyes.
Then, make a wish.
Try it.
Palms together.
Then, make a wish from your heart.
Why are you smiling?
What did you wish for?
I wish Sun would stop
wearing a stern face.
When did I wear a stern face?
All the time.
What did you wish for?
Nobody tells what they wish for.
Oh.
But you just asked me.
Just tell me.
Just a bit.
I wish to forget
the worst thing that happened.
So, this is about Nam.
What?
Don't speak like
you know everything.
So, I don't know then.
Nam is the one who hurt you, right?
You don't have to be afraid,
I will never hurt you.
You're smiling.
No, I didn't.
Really?
I didn't.
Alright, you didn't smile.
- No, I didn't smile.
- No, you didn't smile.
Don't do that.
You will fall from the tree.
What?
I'll do this.
Sun, you will fall down.
Just don't do it.
You will fall down.
Jodd, Jodd. Jodd.
Jodd.
Nam is coming.
I will take my revenge.
He'll pay
for what he did to me.
Quiet.
What did you just do?
When did you come in?
Mos, go and see
if the things you prepared
are ready or not.
Me?
Yes, you go.
What is it?
Whoa!
Ah!
Mos, go and see
what was that noise.
Me again?
I told you not to
come here around this time.
What the heck?
Where’s that creepy sound coming from?
Hey, not that.
At last,
you all have come to see me.
Nam.
I've waited for
this day for so long.
What the heck?
Nam, someone is calling your name.
I am going now.
You just can't go.
Ghost!
What the heck?
Hey, what's this?
Who did this?
What the hell is wrong with you?
And you? What's wrong with you?
You don’t know how to lose,
do you?
What the hell
are you talking about?
I don’t know what
you have been through in life.
If you mess with my friends,
I won’t let you get away with it.
I will live happily,
to the point where you have to
compare yourself to me every day.
I will make you feel defeated
and lose any hopes in life.
The one who’ll end up
with those feelings
will be you,
not me.
What should I do?
Have you seen his face?
He looks so funny.
You've put on a good show.
I am good at it.
Sun, follow me.
What's up, Auntie Noi?
Keep quiet.
Just don't ask.
Would you help me?
You all are so noisy.
Stop making noise now.
Just sleep,
so I can go back to my sleep.