I wish everything
was just a nightmare.
So that when I open my eyes,
Sun is still here.
But it's not.
I guess I have to accept the truth.
That Sun...
will never come back again.
(5 months later.)
This break I’m really lonely.
If it weren't for you,
I would never survived.
Did you watch the video I sent you?
What video are you talking about?
It's that video I sent.
The cat video,
the one with the chubby cat.
It's really cute, man.
Hey, man.
How are you doing?
I don't know how to contact you,
you don't use Line
and I can't DM you.
Junior, you see this?
What do you think
I should caption it?
What?
Are you okay?
I just miss Sun.
Soon the police will find Sun.
You have to believe me.
He won't disappear.
Matter never disappears.
It only changes form.
You're such a nerd.
What's up with you?
You see me like this, but I
actually read books, you know.
What if...
I try making a video
to search for Sun?
Maybe it will become
a trend on social media,
and people will help look for him.
Would it be a good idea?
Or should I try hacking the IP
to access the government server?
It's okay,
no need to search for him.
I think he probably won't come back.
What do you mean, ‘It’s okay’.
Didn't you tell me to
be true to my feelings?
If you're sad, just say you're sad.
What's going on with you now?
It's okay, man.
Hey, are you okay?
This semester,
I got really low grades.
There were subjects that
I thought I did well in,
but when the grades came out,
I got really low.
Hey!
If you're having fun, that's fine.
Forget about the grades.
I still saw you
retaking your F exam.
I don’t think I can just forget about it?
You might be better at other things
than just being
good at taking exams.
Maybe I'm just not cut out
for taking exams like this.
I don't think I'll continue
my studies anymore.
Hey, Junior,
think about it carefully.
Don't you like
swimming and computers?
You might not like or
be good at other subjects,
but that's okay.
I don't like studying either,
but I still do it.
If you're leaving,
at least stop by to see us sometime.
Hey, Jeng,
don't encourage him like that.
Let Ju make his own decision.
I think he already
thought it through.
It's up to you,
I can't force you.
But you have to
stop by and see us, okay?
You have to stop
by and see us, okay?
Hey, you have to come, alright?
Alright, got it.
At least we're
here for you, you know.
I'm always by your side.
I already told you in advance
that I wanted to leave early today.
You can't treat me like this!
I already told you!
I'm meeting my girlfriend
to watch a movie today.
I have to pick her up soon.
You can handle it for
me in the meantime, ok?
I've only taken three days off
this year:
two days ago and today.
Listen, you brat!
I can't take it anymore!
I'm quitting!
Well, if you want to go, then go.
But I'm not paying you for today.
Yeah,
it's just a few hundred,
I don't need it anyway.
Yeah, go ahead.
Penguin Laundry, clean
crazy refreshing,
just like having a penguin
stand there and
do the laundry for you.
No need to go
all the way to the Pole.
Just come right in and relaxed.
Penguin,
can I take a picture, please?
How did a penguin
ended up in such
a hot place like this?
Aren't penguins supposed
to live in the Pole?
I'm leaving now.
My mom will be worried.
Aren't you tired?
Listening to me,
praying for you every day.
I'm going to save money
to go to the North Pole,
and I will live there.
And if Sun comes back,
please tell him that
I've already followed my dream.
But if he doesn't come back,
it's all your fault.
Is it fun for you
to see me struggle as person?
Being human isn't that easy,
you know.
If you're going to get back at me
when everything in
my life is going well,
you didn't have to
bless me from the start.
Thank you, dear.
You're welcome, aunty.
Ever since
you started working at my shop,
we've had a lot more customers
coming in for laundry.
I really don't want you to leave.
I don't know where
I'll find someone like you.
Try to think it over first.
Jobs like this aren't
easy to come by these days.
Especially since
you didn't finish your studies.
Thank you so much.
I'm leaving now, Sun.
I won't come to see you anymore.
I won't wait for you
or cry for you anymore.
I'm going to Bangkok to find a job.
Once I have enough money,
I'll go to the North Pole.
And I'll never come
back to Thailand again.
I will get married there.
I will live my life there.
I will live my life happily.
And I will forget
everything about you.
If you don't want me to go,
then hurry back to me.
You told me you'd go to the
fair with me every year.
I'm sorry for being late.
Just you coming back makes me happy.
Thank you for coming to see me.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'm staying here with you.
I love you.
Are you being sulky?
Do you love me that much?
I love you more
than anything in the world.
So, are you going
to Bangkok now?
Who told you?
I heard someone
say,...
"I'm going to
Bangkok to make money..."
"I'm going to the North Pole
to find penguins."
"I'm sure I'll meet
someone better than Sun."
I'm only gone for a little while,
and you're already looking
for someone new?
I guess I have to move on, right?
No one knows where you've gone.
What are you doing?
That's inappropriate!
Shall we begin,
my love?
Are you crazy?
What are you going to do?
You're being inappropriate!
This is crazy!
Right here then.
Are you crazy.
- No...
- What are you looking at?
What?
Is that a person?
What is it?
A person.
Who is it?
Hey, Sun!
Sun!
Are you okay, Sun?
- Sun!
- How did you end up here, Sun?
Hey.
Sun!
Are you okay, Sun?
You, I think we should
take him to the hospital first.
Let's go, take it easy.
Take it easy, Sun.
Are you okay?
Take it easy.
Take it slow.
Do you still want to go to Bangkok?
I'm not sure.
If you disappear again, I might go.
In that case, we can go together.
I really want to face the
5 hours traffic.
A three-month
advance deposit, please.
How was today?
Did you enjoy your meal?
I'd rather have
stir-fried basil with squid.
Why is that?
The minced pork
doesn't taste that great.
It's tasty too, though.
Is something wrong with her, Sun?
She's crying again.
What are you going to do?
Listen, she's crying again.
Aren't we going to help her?
It's nothing.
How can it be nothing?
Didn't you hear her crying?
I heard it, but...
Let's just leave her be.
What are you going to do? Let's go.
I never thought
you would be like this.
Do you want to know
why she's crying?
Oh, Sun!
Can't you hear
her crying? There might be danger.
Aren't you going to help her?
Come on.
If you were pregnant,
what would the baby be like?
The face would be a black panther,
and the body would be a penguin.
Or maybe the face
would be a penguin,
and the body would
be a black panther.
I think
it's better if the face is a penguin
and the body is a black panther.
That way, the baby
will be strong like you.
But I'd prefer
a black panther face
and a penguin body.
I want our baby to be soft
and gentle like you.
But I can't get pregnant.
Oh, come on!
You bought a snack?
This is our baby.
I heard you say
you wanted to have a child.
I've seen many people
raising animals as their kids.
This apartment,
we can't keep cats or dogs,
so all we can have is fish.
I'll let you choose
the name for the baby.
What do you want to name it?
Alright, then I'll name it...
"Guinny"!
‘Black Bae’ over here.
Wait, you told me to pick a name!
Guinny! Guinny! Guinny!
Guinny, come to papa.
Black Bae, come to mama.
My son, come here.
Hey!
(Junior's dream: The North Pole.)
Do you remember
when we wrote down
what we wanted to do?
Should we do what
we once dreamed of doing?
What is it?
I want to go to the North Pole.
I said I wanted to
go to the North Pole.
Pay attention!
What do you think?
Alright,
we need to start saving up.
Maybe we should wait
another ten years to go?
Ten years, really?
Well, right now we
don't have any savings yet.
I think maybe in three years.
Why three years?
Did you go gambling?
No.
The birds just brought it to me.
So, you didn't gamble, but you had
the birds bring you money instead?
Are you crazy?
The birds brought it to me
themselves, I didn't force them!
If that's the case, it looks like
it's just me who has to work
hard to save money then.
You should write your own down.
Who said I didn't write it?
Where is it?
(Sun's dream: I want
to have someone by my side.)
Someone like you, wanting
to do something like this?
Hey,
are you still keeping this?
Why are you keeping it?
Did you see the number on the tag?
251100.
I don't know my
own birthday like you.
In one cage,
there are several penguins.
Suddenly, I thought that
this number might be my birthday
because it has been
with me since the beginning.
But looking at this number,
it's pretty close, isn't it?
Yeah, but it is trivial.
What do you mean by trivial?
What do you want for your birthday?
I want you.
You already got me,
what more do you want?
I want more.
I want you. I want you. I want you.
(4 years later.)
Oh, keep making me kick my legs
I'm so tired!
Keep kicking your legs like that!
I can swim all the strokes.
Is there anything harder than this?
Do you want it?
Bring it on.
Alright!
I will teach you a move
harder than the frog style,
harder than the butterfly.
Is there such a thing?
Yes, there is.
It's the penguin stroke, of course!
Cut!
Why didn't you fall down then?
When he finished
hitting, you should have
fallen down immediately,
pretending to be hurt
and falling right away.
After getting hit, fall
down immediately
and act like you're hurt. Okay?
I was so excited earlier that
I didn't even realize
when I got hit.
Huh, you didn't feel anything?
He hit pretty hard just now.
Alright, try again.
Hit him like you did before.
Okay?
- Okay.
- You hit hard, okay?
Try it out!
And action!
Cut!
Why didn't you fall down?
Did you feel it just now?
Did you feel when he hit you?
I already fell just now.
Okay, after hitting,
fall immediately.
No waiting, just hit and
fall, okay?
Okay.
One more time, okay?
One more time.
And action!
Cut!
He hasn't hit you yet.
He hasn't hit you yet,
why would you fall?
wait for him to hit first.
Once he hits, then you can fall.
One more time,
I'm giving you the last round.
You hit me as hard as you can.
Don't be afraid
that I'll get hurt, okay?
Ready?
And action!
Ouch!
Cut!
Freaking Finally!
Good job.
Thank you.
What are you asking for?
Do I have to tell you?
Hey, if you ask for something,
it's something I can give you.
You can't give it to me.
Jodd! Jeng!
Hey, keep your voice down,
this is a shrine.
Jod and Jeng is this...
What?
You guys can still be together.
Will you guys be
together until you're old?
Of course,
we are lovers.
What is your relationship?
Hey, you tease them, and then
you'll be jealous of them again.
You should come and stay with me.
You asked me
what I asked for, right?
This is it.
Sure, go ask for it.
Hurry up and ask for it.
Seeing a shrine like this makes me
think of the Goddess of Moles.
Right, I don't know where she went.
I think she's been reborn.
Who knows,
maybe she's still a ghost.
If it were me, I would
have been reborn a long time ago.
If you talk about her too much,
she'll definitely
come to see you tonight.
Come on, I'll wait for her tonight.
Do you guys know
what her dream is?
What is it?
Having a new shrine.
Is that all?
Well, the old shrine
where she used to live
birds like to poop on it, right?
And it's like
leveling up to upgrade
new shrines or something.
That's cool.
I'd better write a game out of it.
Oh, you audacious birds!
I ran away to set up a new shrine,
and you still come to shit on me.
Just wait until I’m promoted
to an even higher spiritual rank!
You’re going down
- Like the economy.
Just you wait.
- Hey!
I thought
the goddess had disappeared.
It's good that the goddess is fine,
but it's bad that birds still
come to poop like before.
Then why doesn't heaven lift
the curse of bird droppings?
What curse?
Nothing.
It's been a long time.
Ju.
I know what you're looking at.
What?
You ask the goddess
whether she still wants the
ten crates of red water
and silk outfit with a floral pattern.
Yes.
She asked if you wanted to talk.
She said she would possess someone.
No, no, no.
The statue will break again.
I'm too lazy to use glue to fix it.
"You're annoying."
She said that. I didn't say it.
- Yeah, I know.
Come see me more often,
I'm lonely.
The goddess.
This way.
Oh really?
The goddess.
May you bless Jeng.
Satu.
I'll give you 20 crates.
Hurry up and say Satu.
- Satu.
- I just said it.
Hello.
- Hello!
This is a gift.
Hey, thank you. Thank you.
Hey, Nut.
- Hello!
- How are you? Hello!
Have you traveled far?
Yes, it's very far.
Wait a moment. It's almost done.
Today we have some
food that you guys like.
Do you guys see her too?
This is my child.
Her name is Kong Khwan.
Is she cute?
Yes, she is.
You guys go play games
with Jod and Jeng first.
I'll prepare some food for you.
Okay.
You'll get it for sure.
Hey guys,
you don't care about us at all.
Don't bother me. I'm playing a game.
What the hell are you doing, Sun?
I lost.
Now that we've met,
please pay attention to us.
Yeah, you guys
don't care about us at all.
What the hell are you talking about?
Doesn't your house have internet?
I talk to you every day.
If you hadn't bullied me,
I would have beaten Jeng.
Someone like you can beat Jeng?
You guys are going to
the North Pole soon, right?
Really?
Shoot, that's great.
What's great?
Your life is better than ours.
You know I already
have 3,000 followers?
Shoot, this means
I'm about to become famous.
I didn't mean that.
I meant that
you're going to America.
Are you going to America, Jodd?
Don't you know this?
Kids, come help carry the food.
- Okay.
- Sure.
Let's go.
Have you ever eaten this?
Next time, I won't lose to you.
Kong Khwan has gone to bed.
And Kong Khwan, did you guys adopt her?
No, we let someone else
be our surrogate mother.
Since we got married,
we've been looking
for ways to have children.
So have you graduated yet?
We're done
but I might continue studying.
But Jodd,
once his visa is approved, he'll go
to America by the end of this year.
What are you looking at?
I didn't think
you'd leave this fast.
And will you
be there for a long time?
I'm probably just going along.
There's nothing special
to do in Thailand anyway.
I want to try out making content
about living alone in America.
Maybe I'll be famous.
Everything is content to you.
And you traveling away so far,
aren't you afraid that someone
around here will miss you?
Who,
who would miss me?
Jeng doesn't miss me.
He'll go to study in Boston.
He and I can easily to meet up,
unlike the two of you.
Hey,
they're probably having something.
Why are you whispering?
Everyone here can hear it all.
What's something?
There's nothing at all.
I think it's here.
I'll go open it myself.
- Hello!
- Noi!
Hi Timothy.
- Hello!
- Please come in.
How are you, aunty?
I am also fine.
Since I talked to you guys that day,
I've been staying with Timothy.
Thank you so much, you guys.
One way ticket to paradise?
Oops,
don't tease me.
Would you like some?
Would you like to join, Ms Samorn?
I'm not really used to it, but...
just a little bit is fine.
Junior,
it's your turn.
Truth or Dare?
I have something to tell you.
I am a penguin.
As for Sun, he is a black panther.
If you're a penguin
and you're a black panther,
then Jodd is a dog.
What's that dog barking sound, man?
If I were a dog,
I would be the cutest
and most loyal dog.
Is that right?
- Thank you.
- Please.
Are you okay?
I'm good.
You're totally drunk.
You, I'm still okay.
Walk carefully.
See you, guys.
See you, Ms Samorn.
- Bye-bye!
Take care.
Be careful, man.
- Be careful.
- Are you okay?
- See you, bro.
- Go home safely.
- Bye-bye!
- Okay.
We're going back first.
Don't forget about us.
It's not like you all left
and never came back.
I know.
Don't forget, man.
Don't forget what?
Now, it's probably
just you who forgot.
Let's go, Jeng.
Are you okay?
Come and ride on my back.
One, two, three.
See you, man.
See you.
What's going on
between the two of them?
Don't meddle in
other people's business.
This kind of thing requires
understanding. It’s chemistrying.
I never thought I'd get
to see everyone together like this.
I can still remember
the first day I met you.
The day you made a face
like you had fallen in love.
Really? But at that time,
I wasn't thinking about anything.
But you still liked me first anyway.
Well, you were
the one flirting with me.
And you kept chasing after me too.
Because I knew that you liked me.
So, I kept pursuing you.
Or do you not like me?
I like you, soft little penguin.
I'm happy for P’ Nut and P’ Ton too.
They got married and had a kid already.
Jodd and Jeng were finally
able to follow their dreams.
Ms Samorn also
got to dress the way she likes.
As for Aunty Noi,
she finally
started to find happiness.
It's great!
Everyone has done what they love.
You’re the same as well.
You will be going to the North Pole.
Are you excited?
I wish there were
penguins at the North Pole.
Here it is.
When you go to the North Pole,
there will be
one penguin there after all.
You're daydreaming.
Talking aimlessly.
What about you? Have you thought
about what you want to do?
It's the same as always.
I just want to
keep living like this.
But actually, there is one thing.
I want to be with
you for the rest of my life.
I said it.
Let's go home.
Wait a second.
Why?
(Arctic)
This place is even more
beautiful than the picture.
I never thought I
would come this far.
In the past, I just lived
a repetitive life in
that cage and at school.
But after meeting you,
I got to go to other places,
temples,
karaoke bars,
and even gambling spots.
And look at us now,
I've come all the way
to the North Pole.
What black panther would
make it to the North Pole, right?
Penguins too.
Do you know,
before, when I saw parents
picking students up,
I felt really lost.
Until I came here with you.
The place you've always dreamed of.
It feels like
my dream comes true as well.
Just for a moment,
I felt like
I finally made it back home.
You too.
You are like home to me.
I love you, Sun.
What? I can't hear you.
You said you have
good hearing, right?
Huh? I didn't hear anything at all.
I love you, Sun!
I love you the most,
more than all
the panther I've ever met.
Loud enough?
I love you too, Junior!
I love you the most.
I love you more than
any penguin I've ever met.
I can't hear anything at all.
I love you, Junior!
Thank you to each and every one of our fans!