"A Man Who Defies the World of BL Final"
Another perfectly ordinary day.
And that's just fine by me.
This is kind of sudden, but...
My little brother is a real pain.
After a get-together with my college friends,
I just got home.
But man, that ramen place was the best.
For some reason,
my dopey-looking little brother
is passed out in my room.
Judging by the scene,
chances are...
Ayato...
must've snuck into my room to borrow my glue stick.
Where is it?
Found it, found it.
Big bro, I'm borrowing this.
Huh?
Whoa, what a throwback.
This is so good!
And that's when...
he found a manga that caught his eye.
Look.
This is the classic.
Then he read while tossing the books all over the place.
And finally, he just fell asleep reading.
Anyway, let me say it again.
I want to sleep now, so my little brother is in the way.
Besides, this guy...
Like this.
Once he's asleep,
you can't wake him up no matter what you do.
Ow, that really hurts.
Hmm?
Did I mishear that?
(Episode 3: VS The Accidental Nap)
In that case,
there's only one thing to do.
Hup.
I can't be bothered to drag him back to his room.
I'm tempted to just dump him in the hallway...
Hup.
Mmm.
Mission accomplished.
Man, that was exhausting.
Carrying an unconscious person...
is way more work than you'd think.
Alright...
Time for bed.
Oh?
What a throwback.
Whoa, so good.
This guy took my manga from my room.
Hey.
Big bro, wake up.
Don't just barge into someone's room
and fall asleep, okay?
That's not it.
But, chances are...
you came into my room to borrow something,
found a manga that caught your eye,
and then read while tossing the books everywhere,
before falling asleep, right?
So,
your...
Oh, my.
You two slept together?
You brothers are so close.
It's nice to have a brother.
Such good kids.
That's...
Don't take any more.
I can't believe I accidentally fell asleep too.
Maybe I slept too well.
Somehow, today's meal tastes especially good.
Kuroki.
Are you kidding me?
Why did you suddenly show up at my place yesterday?
Ah.
No.
When I woke up, you'd already ditched me
and disappeared.
That's pretty cold.
Huh?
That's a harsh way to put it.
While you were asleep, Kyohei,
I washed you up in the bathroom.
What?
Washing an unconscious person...
That must've taken some serious strength.
You... You think that makes everything okay?
Look.
We smell the same now.
Let's go.
What is this plot twist...
For example,
whether Japan's economy as a whole is good or bad.
Oh no...
I ate too much for lunch.
Of all the times,
with his low, baritone voice luring me into a sweet slumber,
it's Professor Matsuda's economics class.
In contrast, microeconomics is
the study of how individual actions and decisions are made.
For example,
Oh no...
I'm going to fall asleep if this keeps up.
Since my little brother has a boyfriend,
it didn't turn into a BL situation.
But "falling asleep" is a BL flag in itself.
Oh no...
Huh?
Ah...
You're awake.
Professor.
You looked so peaceful sleeping,
I didn't have the heart to wake you.
I'm sorry.
It's quite alright.
If you don't mind,
how about I give you a special lesson now?
In my room.
Could this be...
the "professor and student"
forbidden BL plotline beginning?
What do you say?
What should I do?
What am I going to do?
This is the moment it comes in handy.
Stabilize the economy,
or solve unemployment,
inflation, and other issues.
Huh? Is that... my voice?
In contrast,
I knew this might happen,
so I recorded your lecture.
I see...
I'll review the lecture when I get home.
So, if you'll excuse me.
Ah... Wait.
And so, having escaped a BL development,
I'm home.
I went home to review the lecture,
or at least, that was the plan...
Regarding the differences
between microeconomics and macroeconomics,
first, macroeconomics is...
from a broad perspective,
the study of economic trends of a country or the world.
For example, whether Japan's economy
as a whole is good or bad...
Everyone,
be very careful not to fall asleep in class.
And don't fall asleep while studying, either.
"A Man Who Defies the World of BL Final"
After-School Tutoring Session.
Three Questions Per Person.
I'm off.
So annoying.
Why do we have to leave together?
The very sight of me with you...
What if people see us again?
Here, your lunch.
- Thanks.
- So you're just going to pretend you don't know me again?
They'll find out sooner or later anyway.
Oh, right.
I'm going to Tojo's tutoring session today.
Tell them I'll be home late.
Tutoring session?
Yeah.
What a suggestive phrase.
Which means...
Open your textbooks.
Alright, then...
Let's begin.
It must be something like that.
Oh, Tojo's hair.
It's not that color anymore.
Oh... is that right?
Seriously...
Stop letting your imagination run wild.
Oh.
Sorry.
By the way...
How did you know what I was imagining?
So, that tutoring thing...
Hmm?
Oh.
Yanagi, Minami, and I all bombed our midterms.
So we decided to ask Tojo to help us study.
- Uh-huh.
- Then word got out,
and everyone was like, "Me too, me too!"
So in the end, in a classroom after school,
the Tojo cram school opened.
Tojo cram school...?
Your Group Tutoring Session After School.
Let's get started now, but...
the rule for questions is...
a maximum of three per person.
Got it?
Yeah!
I like you.
Please go out with me.
Tojo... you might as well ask them to pay you tuition.
I already told you.
Tojo doesn't even wear glasses.
Wait, how can you see the fantasies inside my head?
Then, can you tell Mom and Dad I'll be home late?
A study session?
I wonder how this is going to turn out.
(Episode 4: Vs. The Study Group)
Alright, everyone.
That's it for today's class.
The exam is next week.
So make sure you all study hard.
An exam...?
What's this?
Why is my notebook completely blank?
Ah...
I've been so busy trying to dodge BL flags
and running simulations every day...
that I haven't been paying attention in class at all.
At this rate, I'm definitely going to fail.
I'll...
be a sophomore again next year.
And the year after that, still a sophomore.
And for every year after that!
What do I do?
Everyone...
May I have your attention?
Huh? Who's that guy?
That's Saionji, the most brilliant student
since this school was founded.
That's...
purple sage, a symbol of wisdom and respect.
I'm hosting a study group at my place tonight.
Anyone interested in coming?
- I'll go!
- Me too! Please teach me!
To escape the fate of being held back...
Should I go?
Should I go or not?
They both said they're going to a study group today,
so they'll be back late.
- A study group?
- Yep.
I see.
It's nice to see young people working hard.
This is insane!
It's incredible.
It's huge!
I thought he lived alone, but...
- There's a bronze statue.
- Why is there a bronze statue?
He even has a bronze statue.
No one's home today.
So everyone, please make yourselves comfortable.
Awesome!
What is going on?
Is he a genius and a rich kid?
This guy has to be
a main character in this BL world.
But it's fine.
With so many people here...
I just have to act like a background character.
If I stick to my role as a nobody,
I won't trigger any flags.
Okay, let's start the study group.
Okay, thank you.
I'll start by explaining the basic concepts.
Okay.
What normal person has a whiteboard in their house?
- The material on page 45...
- Is this guy the study group master or something?
First,
In short...
just remember that "the difference in perceived value
to consumers is the source of gains from trade."
And you'll have no problem with the exam.
Oh, I see.
I totally get it now.
Well... I have work, so I'm gonna head out.
Okay...
- Take care.
- Me too...
Thanks for teaching us.
Take care.
You're a really good teacher.
Thanks.
Well, I live pretty far, so I'm heading home.
- Take care.
- You too, thank you.
Yeah.
Take care.
And then...
before I knew it,
Alright.
Well...
I should probably get going too...
Huh?
You're leaving...?
I'm so tired of eating alone.
Here you go.
What about your parents?
They're abroad.
They haven't been back for six months.
Ever since I was a kid...
it's always been like this.
I'm always alone.
So...
to get my parents to pay attention to me...
I studied like my life depended on it.
But...
my parents don't care about me at all...
They're only passionate about their own work.
This whole sob story...
feels like it's going to take a while.
I really have to pee right now.
But I can't leave.
If my parents wouldn't...
I hoped my classmates would care about me.
That's why I...
host these study groups from time to time.
But,
everyone just comes to me for help with schoolwork...
No one cares about me as a person.
I'm...
still all alone in the end.
You...
You have such kind eyes.
Huh?
You...
You won't leave me all alone, will you?
What do I do?
What do I do, Mob Character A?
Huh?
We have guests?
Why are you guys back?
Dad...
Mom...
What do you mean, "why"?
Because today...
is your 20th birthday.
You remembered...
Happy birthday.
Happy birthday~
Dad... Mom...
- What's wrong?
- I think he's crying.
Big boys don't cry.
- Because...
- Oh, honestly.
Anyway...
thanks to the surprise return of his parents,
I narrowly avoided it turning into a BL situation.
But the problem is...
Ah...
I can't hold it anymore!
Ah, I managed to avoid the flag.
Everyone, remember to go to the bathroom
when you get the chance!
Bye-bye!
(Next Episode)
Next time on A Man Who Defies the World of BL:
The slight glimpse of a guy's collarbone
is pretty exciting, right?
Next time on A Man Who Defies the World of BL:
Vs. Contradiction
and Vs. Work Experience. Two stories.
Stay tuned.