In microeconomics,
the demand and supply curves are...
I've realized something.
I'm a resident of a certain world.
This is a very basic, yet important...
A so-called...
In other words...
I'm a resident of a BL world.
But...
as a background character
who absolutely refuses to be in a BL story,
I've been dodging every possible flag
that gets raised.
But...
Will you accept my feelings?
I guess I...
I can't forget you.
What do I do?
What am I gonna do?
Now this...
Hey, bro.
Bro.
Hmm?
Look, right here.
You've got a grain of rice on your face.
Huh?
Seriously, what are you doing?
Was all of that...
just a dream?
In other words,
I knew it.
I refuse to give in to this world.
Another bowl.
Whoa.
Another bowl!
Whoa, whoa.
Thanks for the food.
So much energy this early.
He's really something.
Who eats four bowls of rice for breakfast?
- Pretty cool, huh?
- What's cool about it?
Hey, you'll get a stomachache.
- He's growing up so well.
- Such a good man.
Yeah.
I'm heading out.
And so...
in a world where everything becomes a BL story,
as a man who refuses to be a part of it,
I'm just a background character.
My grueling day-to-day battle...
begins for the fourth time.
"A Man Who Defies the World of BL Final"
March...
That's right.
Speaking of March...
Today, we're having special chirashi sushi.
Oh, right.
- It's delicious, Mom.
- Really tasty.
Ah, Girls' Day is the best.
But...
we don't have any girls in the family to celebrate.
What are you talking about?
- We do.
- Huh?
Mom.
Congratulations.
Oh, stop it.
But thank you.
- Thanks.
- Don't be shy.
- Go on, Mom. Eat up.
- Okay.
- Here you go.
Time to eat!
The clam broth smells amazing.
Girls' Day.
Next up...
the second button.
Can I have it?
Sure.
Then...
can I have yours too?
Yeah.
Actually...
I've always had feelings for you.
Me too.
It's graduation season.
Graduation ceremonies.
And after that...
The cherry blossoms are blooming up north.
I see. It's flower-viewing season.
How about we all go flower viewing next week?
Huh? The whole family?
- What if people see us?
- Who cares?
It'll be nice.
Sigh.
Flower viewing...
We can drink now.
And other dangerous events
are coming one after another.
But...
the thing you need to watch out for most in March...
is something you're all very familiar with.
That's right.
It's...
Achoo!
Hay fever season is here.
(Episode 1: The Hay Fever Chapter)
A trade-off...
is a relationship where, in order to get one thing,
you have to give up something else.
Okay.
That's all for today's class.
Achoo!
Here.
Are you okay?
Thanks.
Watery eyes.
Flushed cheeks.
These symptoms of hay fever...
can accidentally raise a BL flag.
Hey.
Wanna go to a cafe with better air quality later?
Huh?
Yeah.
Let's go?
I knew this would happen.
Use this.
This is bad.
This is really bad.
This dangerous atmosphere...
I have to find a way to escape it.
Everyone.
Listen to me.
For the time being,
I'm taking a leave of absence
from school to go abroad.
To a world without hay fever.
So, farewell.
Unfortunately, reality isn't that simple.
Here.
Use this.
So I have no choice but to...
Are you okay?
I've decided to adopt a no-defense strategy.
That's right.
That's the idea.
If I can just push past the watery eyes...
and the flushed cheeks...
everything will be fine.
The only problem is...
my physical and mental strength...
will be slowly worn down.
But no matter what,
I have to survive this hay fever season.
It's been a while. My name is Mayama Masumi.
It's him... a treasure trove of inspiration.
I'm a BL manga artist suffering from severe hay fever.
Time to gather some more material for inspiration.
He's appeared once again.
That BL manga artist.
What kind of story will he create?
And what kind of "versus" awaits us up ahead?
Stay tuned to find out, everyone.
"A Man Who Defies the World of BL Final"
Just pretend to be my lover?
Just stand next to me and be introduced as my boyfriend.
Here's the curry rice.
- Sorry for the wait.
- Thanks.
By the way, I'm moving soon.
Huh? Why?
They found out our apartment building faked
its earthquake resistance data.
For real? That's insane!
- It's dangerous.
- So dangerous.
Sigh...
You seem down.
What's wrong?
Well...
The other day...
I told my boyfriend I was hanging out with friends...
but I was actually meeting the guy
I'm cheating with, and I got caught.
Oof...
You're so screwed.
It's bad. He saw my phone.
When people hear the word "pretense,"
they usually think of...
criminal acts or faking an alibi
for an affair, right?
Even in this BL world full of happy endings,
pretense still exists.
(Episode 2: The Pretense Chapter)
The "pretense" incidents that occur in this world...
are mostly harmless.
This is the main one.
Hey, guys.
I have a favor to ask...
Can someone please pretend to be my boyfriend?
Pretend to be your boyfriend?
Yes, please!
A male customer at my part-time job confessed to me.
I turned him down,
but now he's kind of started stalking me.
But I don't have any female friends
who can pretend to be my girlfriend.
It doesn't matter if my fake partner is a guy or a girl.
I just need him to give up.
So... please, just play along.
Please.
Thank you very much
for that detailed plot synopsis.
Please, anyone...
Fake Lovers.
In other words...
He's looking for someone to be his "fake boyfriend".
You should go for it.
Takehara.
Huh?
I'm sure you've all noticed.
Everyone here is a couple.
And another couple.
In a situation like this,
the one who's most likely
to be pushed into being the "fake lover"...
is obviously me.
To get myself out of this...
I decided to strike first.
Hey, why me?
Well...
if that stalker guy
finds out his lover is also a man,
as a man,
he'd naturally compare himself to him, right?
Ah... You have a point.
If a plain-looking guy like me shows up,
or someone meek-looking like Natsu,
he'll think he's the better man,
and that he'd be a more suitable lover, right?
But it's different with a well-built guy like you.
He'll feel completely outmatched as a man.
And then he'll back off.
That's not how it works...
Ooh, that makes sense.
Well, I guess that could happen.
Hey, Masaya, Yoji.
What kind of nonsense are you two spouting?
Please, Takehara.
Just stand next to me,
and let me introduce you as my boyfriend. That's all.
Please.
Just do me this one favor.
All right, fine.
Thank you so much.
I owe you one.
Is this really going to be okay...?
All right, let's go.
I feel a little bad for the actual couples here...
but think of it as us adding a little spice
to their love lives.
Anyway, today, once again,
in this world that will inevitably turn into a BL,
I've successfully dodged all the BL flags,
and survived another day unscathed.
Isn't that Ayato?
It's rare to see him without his usual group of friends.
Hey, you're pretending you don't know me.
Even though we're brothers.
Trying to pull the
whole "pretend we're strangers" bit, huh?
But...
It's probably just that typical teenage thing...
of not wanting your friends to see your family.
I can't say I don't get it.
So I'll play along and pretend I didn't see him.
Hey, isn't that Ayato's older brother?
Huh? No way. Who's that guy?
No, that's definitely him, right?
They have the exact same vibe.
Those genes are strong.
Busted in a second.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What's this? What's this?
He's so plain.
In any case,
my little brother's "Operation: Pretend to be Strangers"
was a total bust.
As for their "Operation: Fake Lovers"...
I wonder how that's going?
Thanks again, Takehara.
Thank you for pretending to be my boyfriend.
Thanks to you,
I finally got rid of that stalker.
That's great.
Um...
Hm?
There's something I want to tell you.
Is that okay?
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
So...
What did you want to say?
Well...
Um...
It's just that...
Hey, come on, spit it out.
Instead of pretending to be a couple...
From now on...
let's be... a real cou...
Takehara.
Will you be my real boyfriend?
Huh?
I...
I've liked you for a long time.
Stop!
Natsu...
Takehara and I are dating.
Is that true?
Yeah.
So from now on,
please stop this "pretend couple"
charade.
Natsu...
Even if it's to help someone,
this kind of thing...
I can't take it anymore.
Oh, so that's how it was...
I'm sorry, Natsu.
It's all my fault.
Koga...
I...
I had no idea you two were dating.
I overstepped.
I caused a rift between you two.
I'm sorry.
Koga.
You're a good person.
Don't worry about us.
Right, Takehara?
Yeah.
That's a relief...
Okay, let's head back then.
Thanks, you really helped me out.
Yeah, thank you too.
Let's go.
Um... Takehara.
Natsu.
Yeah?
Can we still be friends?
I know I just confessed to Takehara,
so it might be shameless of me to ask.
Of course.
Let's stay friends.
That's right.
The friendship we've built...
isn't fake.
I'm so glad.
My, what a heartwarming development.
- All's well that ends well.
- Wanna get some ramen?
- Oh, yeah!
- Let's go, let's go.
Huh?
I ordered a beef sandwich,
but this isn't beef!
Everyone, be wary of "fakes."
Bye-bye.
(Next Episode)
Next time on A Man Who Defies the World of BL...
The veins on a guy's arm.
For some reason, I just can't help but stare.
Next time, it's "VS Killer Moves."
And "VS The Study Group."
Look forward to it.
What am I gonna do?