Touch Your Heart
Episode 6
I have something to tell you, Mr. Lawyer.
But...
I don't want to tell you now. However,
one day I will definitely tell you
about this emotion that I'm feeling right now.
What is there for her to tell me later?
Samgyeopsal (lettuce wrapped  around grilled pork belly)
I wonder if she likes samgyeopsal. Oh Jin Sim!
Do you possibly... like it?
(Spoken without a subject, it could sound like he is asking if she likes him)
Th-that is... So...
Wait, I think so, but...
But since you're asking me all of a sudden,
I feel so flustered.
But how did you know that I like you? ( Spoken without the direct object. )
Because pretty much everyone seems to like it.
Pretty much everyone?
I guess you're more popular than I thought.
- Isn't it non-burdensome and relatively cheap?
- What?
Cheap, you said?
Isn't it cheaper than beef?
Samgyeopsal (Pork Belly)
Oh, wait a minute. So, right now, are you asking me
- if I like samgyeopsal?
- Yes.
So that we could choose what item we wanted since we came out to eat dinner.
Then what did you think I was talking about when you answered me?
Uh, that's... Um...
Gamjatang! About gamjatang...( Potato soup )
I thought you were asking me if I liked it and—
From what I know, there is no gamjatang restaurant within a one-kilometer distance from here.
Then let's eat samgyeopsal. I like samgyeopsal, too. Wow, samgyeopsal!
Alright then, let's go eat there. There are no people there, so I think it will be comfortable for you.
- Alright.
- Okay. Let's go.
Wow, samgyeopsal!
It seems like you really like samgyeopsal.
Yes. I really love it.
You catch onto things so quickly.
That's true. Maybe it's because I've met so many different types of people as I've been working as a lawyer,
but I think that I've gotten quicker at catching on to things.
Mr. Lawyer. You've never dated, have you?
- Why are you asking so suddenly?
- Just because. You just seem to be so bad at it.
Then, what about you? Are you good at dating?
Of course. Oh?
If you don't believe me, then look up some articles.
I was the MC of the center room of a couple matching program.
I coached them so well back then.
- Back then, my nickname was—
- You've been a solo since birth.
What?
The articles say that.
Why did you find something like that?
"As it turns out, Strong Coffeeshop Love Counselor Oh Yeon Seo has never been in a romantic relationship."
'Top Star Oh Yeon Soo,  a regular on tvN's new entertainment show Strong Coffeeshop as a genuine love counselor,
is currently making headlines for being a solo since birth and not having dated once in her life.
You should stop now.
'The producer said she couldn't have learned from experience. Because everything is unfamiliar and she is clueless,
"I want to thank her for her efforts because she reads guidebooks all  night
and after studying, she gives tips to the cast."
I told you to stop already, seriously!
I found it.
Eat some more, Solo Since Bir— Ah, I'm sorry.
We'll probably be busier from tomorrow onward.
Because we have to prepare a counterattack?
Don't worry too much. I told you this earlier,
but I think that you will win the case. Totally!
You're the most skilled lawyer out of all the lawyers I know.
Do you know a lot of lawyers?
Lawyer Choi, Lawyer Dan...
But anyway.
Starting tomorrow, I'm going to prepare myself and come to work with my fists clenched,
so let's cheer ourselves on together.
Yes.
So did you find a breakthrough somehow?
At last week's People's Trial, the story of Im Yoon Hui's receipt of 4.94 billion won in insurance money
turned the mood against you.
I'm searching for a way right now.
If we can't get Im Moon Hui's case declared as self-defense,  our firm is going to be disparaged by the whole nation.
Well, you know the netizens and social welfare groups are all on Im Yoon Hui's side?
I'm not trying to burden you. Don't feel burdened.
But if we get screwed with a case that the whole nation is interested in,
I don't think our law firm, having failed, will get any big cases anymore.
What should we do?
I'm not burdening you. Don't feel burdened, Lawyer Kwon.
If you've said all you have to say, I'll head out now.
What shall we do, seriously?
Even though we only have four lawyers at our law firm, I took out a huge loan and opened this place.
It was all because of a big dream that someday we would be able to out-do Jang &amp; Park.
If we lose this case, won't we only have left a huge loan instead of a big dream?
So feel burdened. Be burden— No, don't feel burdened.
Don't worry too much.
Someone said that I'll definitely win the case.
Who did?
Anyway, I also agree with those words.
So please believe in me until the end and wait.
What's with that? Who said that?
Did he see a fortune-teller? He did.
A baby?  Girl or boy?
Anyway, I would like just being a lucky person so that we can win the case.
No matter how much I search, there are no precedents worth referencing, Mr. Lawyer.
That's because there have been no precedents of cases being acknowledged as self-defense.
You should head home first today.
I'm okay. How could I leave you alone and go home?
I'm not that disloyal.
I don't want to be considered heartless.
Haven't you been working overtime the past few days because of me? Go home first today.
When are you going to go home?
- I still have work left to do.
- Hmm.
Yeah, Oppa? I told you that I'd get home on my own today. Why did you come?
What do you mean, worried?
Fine, I'll come down. Yeah. Yeah, Oppa.
- Then, I'll head home first.
- Alright.
Mr. Lawyer!
Let's go together.
You said that you had some work to do.
I decided to do it tomorrow.
In this profession, 52 weeks of work is in effect,
but as lawyers we should take the lead in being law-abiding.
Then why have you been working overtime all this time?
- That's—
- Oh, my goodness!
What's wrong with this? It's broken, isn't it? What should I do, Mother?!
- Yes, it's the control room.
- Yes.  The elevator stalled.
- What floor are you on?
- The third floor.
- Ah, I understand.
- Please be quick.
Sir, hurry!
Why is she taking so long to come down?
- Hey, Yoon Seo. When are you coming?
- Hey, Oppa.
Right now, the elevator is broken, so I'm stuck in the elevator with Mr. Lawyer.
Are you okay? Are you hurt anywhere?
No, I'm not hurt anywhere.
Someone will come quickly, so don't worry too much.
I'll call you if something happens.
Yeah, Oppa.
Nothing will happen to us, right?
I'm not sure.
In the last ten years, there have been 254 cases of major injury or fatalities in elevator accidents.
Why are you saying something scary like that at a time like this?!
I was just telling you the facts since you asked me.
Mr. Lawyer, where are you? Where are you?
Oh Jin Sim, are you alright?
Are you alright?
Yes, we're okay.
Yoon Seo, are you okay?
- Oppa.
- You're really not hurt anywhere, right? You were really scared, weren't you?
No, I'm okay.
What do you mean, okay? And you should get off work at the proper time. Why are you working overtime and—
Quiet.
Yoon Seo, wait a moment.
- Excuse me, Mr. Lawyer.
- Yes?
I was trying not to say this if at all possible,
but aren't you overworking my Yoon Seo too much?
My  Yoon Seo?
Yes, My Yoon Seo! From now on, My Yoon Seo is forbidden to work overtime or work outside the office.
Oppa, why are you acting like that? Are you insane?
I'm right! Why are you working overtime? You're not even an official employee here.
This Oppa seriously... Hurry up and go. Hurry up!
Mr. Lawyer, I'm sorry. Don't worry about him.
Hurry up and go. Hurry!
- No, wait!
- Hush!
- Did I say something I wasn't supposed to?
- Hush up!
You should've just stayed put! What's wrong with you?
Yoon Seo, why are you—?
Oppa, what's with you? How flustered do you think my Mr. Lawyer was because you did that?
I'm the one who's taken aback.
I did it because I was thinking of you. You were stuck in an elevator.  Do you know how worried I was?
What is there to worry about? I wasn't even alone, I was with Mr. Lawyer!
That's why I was even more worried, in case he would try to do something sly to you.
What do you mean, sly? Are you crazy?
Why would he do something like that?
Is the lawyer not a man? Huh?
Every single Korean man secretly wants you!
- That's right!
- Right?
Yeah. Huh?
Anyway, that's not true. Nothing like that happened.
Really?
But, Yoon Seo, are you planning to become a secretary for real or something? You've already worked overtime for the past few days.
When was it that you were telling me to work hard?
You shouldn't work too hard! Just get a feel of the vibe
and see how things run.
If I just pretend to work, then how would I be able to act naturally?
Stop saying such frustrating things!
- Yoon Seo, you really—
- No, that was—
You have really made up your mind.
Seeing your passion towards realistic acting,
your Oppa is really touched!
I'll work harder and even harder to help you with your realistic acting!
Bad acting is for the dogs now.
Fighting!
Alright, hurry up and get in. It's cold.
"Oppa"?
Aigo, Oppa did something so unnecessary.
Mr. Lawyer must already have been startled because the elevator stopped so suddenly.
But, the elevator stalling
was so romantic.
I thought that my heart was going to stop, too!
Why did the elevator stall?
Report of Results of Investigation of Unnatural Death
Newspaper articles on Defendant
Interview of Defendant Im Yoon Hui
The modern working woman, Oh Yoon Seo.
You look so sexy being addicted to your work.
- You're here?
- Yes.
Shall I make you a cup of coffee? Do you want some sweet instant coffee?
I'm okay. Didn't he warn me not to overwork you yesterday?
Your boyfriend.
What do you mean, boyfriend? Why would you say...?
Then, is he not?
Of course he's not! That oppa is my manag—
- He's my older cousin! The one who picks me up when we have company dinners.
- Ah.
That guy was him?
Yes. So please don't ever have such a scary misunderstanding ever again.
Yes.
So, are you really not going to drink any coffee?
Well then, can I ask you for just one cup?
Yes.
The fragrance is amazing.
Hey, did you know that other law firms don't offer such high-quality coffee?
They might just have oolong tea, adlay (Job's tear) tea, or coffee mixes, but I'm different.
For our Always family members, we—
I brought these coffee beans. I got them as a gift over the holidays.
We usually only have oolong tea, adlay tea, and coffee mixes. Just like the other law firms.
Ah, is that so?
You're better than me, Secretary Yang. You're better than me.
While drinking this coffee, let's rebuild a great dream.
- Ah, good morning, Yoon Seo.
- Good morning!
- You're here?
Ah, right. You worked overtime with Lawyer Kwon last night, didn't you?
Did something happen?
Something?
- I heard that the elevator broke down last night.
- Ah.
- Actually—
- I heard this from the security guard last night.
Yesterday, some people were stuck in the elevator and called the emergency line, so he ran down there in a hurry.
He said that a man and woman were embracing each other, about to kiss.
What? No, that's—
Isn't it possible that they weren't about to kiss?
Who in the world did he say it was? Who did something so daring?
I was really curious about that, so I asked him to describe their faces.
He said that he remembers them precisely.
He said that the man was tall with round eyes
and that the woman was as pretty as a celebrity.
A tall man with round eyes and a woman as pretty as a celebrity.
And they're among  the people who were working overtime yesterday.
Yoon Seo!
It's not me and Mr. Lawyer!
It seriously isn't us!
What?
What? Ah,
I was saying that we aren't the people who kissed in the elevator.
You're great at jokes. Of course it wasn't you!
Yoon Seo and Jeong Rok are like cats and dogs.  It's an obvious fact that it wasn't you two.
I was just telling you to take some coffee with you.
- Coffee.
- Ah, yes. Coffee.
Anyway, it must be an office couple that is dating secretly.
They could also not be dating.
If a young man and young woman are trapped together in such an enclosed space,
wouldn't romance appear even if they don't have feelings for each other?
Ex-excuse me! People are trapped in here! Please save us!
What the hell? What the hell?
Just what kind of situation is...?
This is squandering my valuable time.
Don't you think that there's not enough oxygen in here?
My breathing keeps...
Do you only breathe through your mouth?
You're right.
I must have misunderstood.
Anyhow, why did it have to be with Lawyer Choi?
What are you saying? I'm the one who feels so wronged that I'm stuck in here
with you who falls in love so quickly instead of Yoon Seo, Lawyer Dan.
Just in case, just because we're in an enclosed area like this,
it doesn't mean you can fall in love with me or anything like that.
Do you really have to purposely make such an ugly face?
Even if you were to stay still, nothing like that would ever happen!
Nothing like that would ever happen for me, either!
- Even more so for me!
- Even more and more so for me!!!
It's even more and more and more so for me!!!
Get off me!
Are you okay?
- You checked it, right?
- Yes, I did.
- And, put Jeong Ji Won's three natural food restaurants..
- Yes
and the two franchise stores as subjects of the search and seizure warrant.
- Yes, sir.
- Let's take a ten minute break.
I'll buy some coffee. What do you want to drink?
I'll go with you.
Forget it. I'll go by myself. I've got some things to think about, too.
Okay. Then I want an Americano.
Oh, did you hear about the trial last time?
Prosecutor Yoo Yeo Reum creamed Attorney Kwon Jong Rok.
Even if she's like that, they're friends. Isn't it too much for her to be going that far?
She must really have no heart.
Oh, and this is another rumor, but
they said that Prosecutor Yoo Yeo Reum made a deal that she would be sent to whatever position she wanted
if she handled this case well.
I know that she's always been ambitious, but don't you think she's really amazing?
You should stop there.
I don't want to hear anything else.
Why? Things are already over between you two.
Why are you deciding whether everything is over or not?
- Please give me one latte and one Americano.
- Okay.
♫  Just because I don't need you  ♫
♫  You'll be wondering  ♫
Please give me this, as well.
- What's with this?
- I thought that you might need something sweet.
I'm busy.
You look busy, even if you don't say it.
Is that the autopsy report? Goodness, look at you.
You want to look at something that horrifying at a place like this?
Do you have something to say to me?
I'm telling you to eat while you're working, even if you are busy.
Does that have anything to do with you?
It does. If you get sick,
my heart will feel uneasy.
I'll head out. You get going too. It seems like someone is waiting for her coffee.
Ms. Prosecutor, this is the document you asked for earlier.
Thank you.
The autopsy report and the appraisal statement both work in our favor, don't they?
The defense attorney's side hasn't been making any particular moves, so I don't think they have any bright ideas.
I guess it will be hard for them to get a ruling of self-defense, don't you think?
But still, it's too soon to jump to a conclusion.
I'll be back. Please leave a memo if there is an important call.
Yes, I will. But where are you going?
Are you going to meet with a client?
I'm going to Im Yoon Hui's house.
Im Yoon Hui's house? You mean the murder crime scene?
Yes. There are some things that are difficult to comprehend  by looking only at the records.
I should go see them personally and see if the report is valid.
I guess lawyers go around and work hands-on too.
It's an attorney's job to look for a chance  to impeach the evidence submitted by the prosecutor
through another piece of evidence.
There's a saying, "If the records cannot answer you, the site can."
Then, I also will come with you—
No, you can't. You don't need to look at such a horrible site.
But still. Who knows?
I may be able to see something that you can't.
I've been studying a lot, too.
I want to help you in some way.
Can't I come along?
Please?
So, this is...
Yes. It's Im Yoon Hui's house.
Are you sure you'll be okay?
Of course. I once had a detective role.
This kind of scene is familiar.
Dramas and reality are very different.
Follow carefully right behind me.
Please watch your step.
That's the bloodstains from the day of the murder, right?
Yes.
They say there is splattering.
Spattering?
When you stab someone and take the knife out,
the blood splatters in the air.
We can analyze the stains and roughly estimate the locations of the perpetrator and the victim.
Kim Hyeong Tae was
standing when he got stabbed.
What do you mean by that?
If she said she was being assaulted and stabbed him by accident,
she would've been ordinarily positioned lower than the other person.
But Kim Hyeong Tae got attacked from the front while he was standing up
and based on this, the prosecutor might argue that she intended to murder him.
Ah...
Let's look around a little more.
Okay.
Mr. Lawyer! Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Call the police for me.
Who are you?!
Are you okay, with your injury?
Should I give you a ride to the emergency room?
I'm okay. I'll write the victim's statement first.
Ms. Oh Jin Sim, are you okay?
What about you? Your wound...
Oh, goodness. It's still bleeding. What should we do?
Hold on.
Look at me, Ms. Oh Jin Sim. I'm okay.
But still... Your blood. Hurry and go to hospital.
I can't go now. I have to write a report.
Is that important now? When you are hurt?
Hold on. My handkerchief.
I think you are startled. I think you should go home and take some rest.
I will drive you home so—
No, I will go home on my own. So, you...
Hurry and go write a report and go to the hospital.
Daeseung Supermarket
I will call you later.
Alright.
Please take care of her, Mr. Driver.
Pardon? An intruder?
Who's the victim?
Lawyer Kwon Jeong Rok?
Okay, I'm coming.
Dongboo Police Station
Oh, you are here.
Oh, my. You were seriously injured.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
More than that... What did he say?
Well, he's a resident here, named Park Soo Myeong.
He was passing by and heard something from inside the empty house.
He said that he went inside because he thought it was a thief. He's "crime prevention staff" in this neighborhood.
Do you know him?
His mother owns a meat market. He delivers meats.
Can I talk to him, just the two of us?
Of course, go ahead.
Mr. Park Soo Myeong?
Very sick.
Excuse me?
Your head is bleeding.
I'm okay.
Well, I have a few things to ask you.
Go ahead, ask me.
You thought I was a thief.
Do you know Im Yoon Hui?
Besides today, have you ever been to that house before?
Noona...
Noona told me not to say it.
She told you not to say what?
By chance, did you go to that house on the day of the incident?
Did you see something or someone—
Oh, are you Prosecutor Yoo Yeo Reum?
Yes.
I called her since she's the prosecutor in charge.
Are you okay?
I'm okay. It's nothing.
This is him?
The one who came to the crime site.
POLICE
Are you sure it's okay to let him go like this?
Since he did it due to a misunderstanding.
Thank you for letting him go.
Soo Myeong, say thank you.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Bye, then.
Manager, this is Yoo Yeo Reum.
I'd like you to look up a person for me.
A man named Park Soo Myeong. He works at a meat market in Im Yoon Hui's neighborhorhood.
You know, Park Soo Myeong...
I'd like you to investigate where he was on the day of the incident.
Yes.
Yes, yes. Thank you, Mr. Manager.
What are you doing here, Ms. Oh Jin Sim? You took a taxi and left before —
I was too worried to leave. That's why I came back.
Is everything over?
Who was that guy? Why in the world did he do that?
No.
Let's go to the hospital first.
No, there is no need. It stopped bleeding. I'm fine.
That's something for a doctor to decide.
Hurry up. Come on.
Get in.
There is no need to worry.
The test result came out. It's a minor concussion.
But still, it will be better if you can take it easy for a while.
Okay. Thank you.
That's a relief, seriously.
I was so worried there might be a problem.
I can now breathe properly.
You really didn't have to drive me home.
You are not in good condition.
It's okay.
You came to the hospital with me.
I honestly went, not because of you, but
because of me.
Earlier, I kept feeling bad for leaving you alone back there.
I, too,
felt uneasy sending you by yourself.
That's why I drove you home.
So you don't need to feel sorry.
You must have been very startled today. Hurry inside and get some good rest.
Don't worry about me.  You  take a good rest, please.
Don't think about work for today.
Alright?
Alright, I got it.
Promise me.
♫   Full of something I don't know  ♫
Come on. Promise me.
♫   Honestly it's difficult for me umm  ♫
♫  Whether timing is what it is or  ♫
♫  Why did it get twisted as it pleased?  ♫
♫  My slow moving heart  ♫
♫  Searched for you with all my might  ♫
♫  Within a footstep's reach  ♫
Since you've made a promise, you have to keep it.
♫  I'm here.  Are you waiting for something?  ♫
Okay.
♫  Ooh love love is. What is it? What is love?  ♫
♫  Ooh love. What should I do?  What if love?  ♫
♫  Probably for me it's you  ♫
♫  one one one my one  ♫
♫  the only one one one you are  ♫
♫  If this is love love love if love  ♫
♫  What should I do? What should I do? What if this is the love?  ♫
You are late. You must be busy preparing for the second hearing.
Yeah.
By the way, you two... Please don't take the same case again.
It feels like I'm walking on thin ice every day.
Okay.  I will go against you next time then.
This punk.
What is it? You got hurt?
What happened? Who did it?
It's nothing.
Did you know Im Yoon Hui?
Besides today, have you ever been to that house before?
Noona...
Noona told me not to say it.
He must be a witness.
If he said Noona told him not to say it, that must mean that he knows something or saw something.
Then, he will likely be a witness, right?
I've asked the office manager to look up his acquaintances.
We're stepping into uncharted territory.
By the way, Lawyer Kwon, you should be careful.
I appreciate you working hard but you can't get hurt.
Exactly. I really thought he was going to die yesterday.
Why would I die?
I'm good with fights. Don't worry.
How can I not be worried? You got knocked over with a single blow yesterday!
Because you're wrong, you were put to shame.  If he hit you properly, you would be totally ...
I got hit on the right spot yesterday, though.
Ms. Yoon Seo, he's weaker than he seems.
As for me, back in the day,
while working on an illegal drug smuggling case, I got attacked by a gang.
- A gang?
- Yes.
Two gangs
I filed one of the lawsuits when two gangs sued each otherl, each blaming the other.
At the time, by virtue of my thoroughness and impartiality, we won the case.
The other gang that lost held a grudge.. A total of 14...  Fourteen?  Fifteen, 16...
Seventeen men attacked me at once but I was able to fight them all with my bare hands.
- Do you know what my secret was?
- What was it?
- Guts!
- Guts?
- Yeah.
It was because of my guts! I never get scared no matter what kind of situation I'm in.
But...
Our Lawyer Kwon might be smart but he doesn't have any guts whatsoever.
Let's use words. Words, words.
- Gosh.
- There was a hair on your clothes.
A strand of hair.
Lawyer Kwon doesn't have
guts but he has a really good eye, right?
How did he see that?
Impressive.
You are not scared. I guess he doesn't respond to anything.
Oh, gosh.
That guy... How did he see that (hair)?
Go on out.
Daesang Butcher Shop
- You know the beauty shop I go to, right?
- Yes.
Yes.  Then I'll be back.
- Hello, Grandpa.
- Hey.
- Soo Myeong, you must be going out for a delivery.
- Yes!
- I will be back!
-  Alright, alright.
Excuse me.
You are working hard on such a freezing day.
By the way,
I think you know the son of the meat market well.
I know him well, but what is it?
Soo Myeong had a crush on that woman.
So he'd follow her around all the time.
So you must have seen them together often, right?
Of course.
I go around every single alley in this neighborhood.
Huh? Three to four times a day!
Did you perhaps see them together on the day of the incident, as well?
Sorry?
You said that Mr. Park Soo Myeong went to Im Yoon Hui's house that night?
He said that he saw it clearly.
Where are you going this late?
I'm out for a delivery.
I should get going. Noona Yoon Hui must be waiting for me.
Noona is pretty.
He does like her so much!
Mr. Park Soo Myeong likes Ms. Im Yoon Hui.
Then isn't it possible that he's pretending like he didn't see the scene of the incident even though he did?
I think he's a witness for sure.
He might not be a witness.
If he's not a witness, then...
Were you close to Ms. Im Yoon Hui?
Noona is a good person.
You know that Ms. Im Yoon Hui  killed her husband, right?
I have to go out for a delivery!
Mom said there are many orders today.
Did you perhaps go to Ms. Im Yoon Hui's house on the day of the incident?
Did you witness the crime scene or—
Two kilos of ox tail to Mr. Jin Soo, 3kg of shoulder to Myeong Jin.
One kilo of stew meat to Gyeok Soo, and... and...
Where else? My mom told me.
Where else?
It's so frustrating that he's not answering your questions.
- I thought he might be a witness at first.
- Even if he is a witness,
he may not be of any help to us.
If Park Soo Myeong talks about the circumstances or the severity of Im Yoon Hui getting beat
on her side at the trial, that would be disadvantageous to us.
I guess so. I did some research and
it seemed like Im Yoon Hui and Park Soo Myeong have been quite close.
Let's stop here and let Park Soo Myeong go.
Oh? Are you going somewhere?
Yes. I have some things to ask Ms. Im Yoon Hui.
Oh! Then...
This. Please have this before you go.
- What's this?
- What do you mean what? It's red ginseng.
Please drink up. Go on.
- In front of me.
- Okay.
How is it? Do you feel better? I brought it just for you.
Since you are weaker than you seem to be.
What do you mean weak? I guess you didn't see it well because you were in shock yesterday.
I took a really good hit, right at the spot.
An average person would have been out for a couple of hours there and then,
but I was able to get up immediately and go after the suspect because I am me.
If you keep spreading rumors that I'm weak and I almost died, you might be punished for defamation.
You are going to punish me? Me?
I called 112 (the police) yesterday, took you to the hospital,
and even gave you the red ginseng extract.
Wow... You're seriously too much.
No, well... I wasn't going to actually punish you.
I'm just saying it could get you into trouble so please watch your words.
I got it. Anyway, be careful.
Yes. Then.
Nothing's going to happen today, right?
I'm so anxious.
Can I ask you one thing?
On the day of the incident, you had been seriously injured which would require nine weeks to heal.
But how could you stab your husband twice and kill him
when he's twice your size?
I was full of thoughts that I had to survive somehow.
I thought that was the only way to end it.
It takes more than just thoughts.
Unlike the movies or dramas we watch, organs and bones get in the way,
making it even harder for a knife to go through.
So it's typical for the people that stab for the first time to get their hands hurt.
By chance, do you know a man named Park Soo Myeong?
Yes.
He works at the meat market.
I heard that you were quite intimate.
- Who said that?
- Most of your neighbors said that.
What nonsense, with someone like that?
Today is the second day of Im Yoon Hui's trial, right?
Yes. I'm so nervous.
I'm very nervous too.
We should be able to get the atmosphere favorable to us.
Somehow I'm even more nervous than the time I was about to hold my first love's hand.
- Oh, Lawyer Kwon is here.
- Oh, you are here!
You can do it well, right? You have a hidden card to flip the table?
Let's have a talk, Mr. Manager.
His expression seems like he has something at least.
I guess he doesn't have manners but he does have an ace up his sleeve.
Well, were you able to persuade Mr. Park Soo Myeong to attend the trial?
He'd adamantly refused every single time I went to talk to him.
It would be hard but you need to bring him to the trial today, by any means necessary. Please, I ask of you.
I will give it a try.
I will go meet him with Mr. Manager and try to persuade him.
- I will wait for you in the lobby.
- Okay.
Ms. Oh Jin Sim.
I think you should not come to the trial today.
Sorry? Why not?
There will be more journalists than the last time. It would be too risky.
I got it. Then I will be back.
Everything will go well today, Mr. Lawyer.
The trial of Ms. Im who was charged with murdering her husband who was a domestic abuser proceeds again today.
It seems an issue will be whether it was justifiable self defense or premeditated to collect insurance.
When Prosecutor Yoo Yeo Reum of Department 3 of the Seoul Central District  Criminal Department 3
revealed further evidence in light of the cirumstances ...
she stated she is confident she can  prove that Ms Im committed premeditated murder.
Noona!
Noona.
Soo Myeong, where are you going? You have to go on a delivery!
Park Soo Myeong, shall we talk for a moment?
I'm not going! I'm not going. I'm not! I told you I wasn't going!
I will go.
Noona told me not to say anything. She told me not to say it.
Noona said that I shouldn't say it.
Mr. Park Soo Myeong.
Do you remember me?
You would have seen me at Im Yoon Hui's house that time.
I was beside the lawyer
that you attacked.
Actually, I was really angry at that time.
The person that you hit
is the person that I like, you see.
Because the person I like got hurt, I was really upset.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. So sorry.
Soo Myeong, you know how I feel.
You hate it when the person that you like is hurting or suffering.
I hate it. I hate it!
I hate it. I don't like Noona Yoon Hui hurting or suffering!
But if you stay like this and don't say anything,
Im Yoon Hui might be in more pain or suffer more.
You have to tell the truth, no matter what that is.
If you don't do it today, you may not be able to see your noona for a long time.
Acknowledge that it was self-defense!
Acknowledge it! Acknowledge it!
As a senior researcher for the National Institute of Science,
did you personally see and analyze the blood splatter at the scene of the crime?
Yes, that's correct.
Defendant Im Yoon Hui said she accidentally stabbed him when she was struggling with him.
Is the analysis of the blood splatter consistent with her assertion?
It is not consistent. The blood splatter of this case
when she stabbed him with all her might, on  the front of the victim was a bloodstain that would have appeared.
That is all.
- Defendant, do you have a cross examination?
- Yes.
Mr. Witness, how much can you discover from a blood spatter analysis?
You can figure out what happened at the site of the incident.
Did you find and blood splatter on the defendant Im Yoon Hui's clothing
which would have occurred when she stabbed the front of the victim?
Well, that's not the case, but—
Isn't it correct that no blood splatter was found on the defendant's clothing?
- Yes.
- Those words mean that there is a possibility that Im Yoon Hui is not the culprit, correct?
I have an objection! That is a leading question.
Objection overruled.
Witness, please answer him.
When you look at the blood spatter analysis, you can not rule that possibility out.
Noona.  Noona.
Your Honor, I'd like to call a rebuttal witness.
A rebuttal witness?  This is a request which was not discussed during pre-trial.   What is your proffer of proof?
Park Soo Myeong, whom I requested as an additional witness,
has had a long-standing close relationship with the defendant, Im Yoon Hui.
He also visited the crime scene the day the incident occurred.
He was excluded from the police investigation, but he could be the sole witness
or even another suspect.
Please allow him to take the stand.
Witness Stand
Mr. Witness, please do one thing before the questioning.
Will you write your name?
Do you use your right hand for normal activities such as writing or eating?
Yes.
- You currently live alone with your mother, who runs a butcher shop. Correct?
- Yes.
You're the person who delivers the meat.  Your mother  does all the cutting and trimming of the meat.
- Is that correct?
- Yes.
To state it again, there is nothing that you use a knife for, right?
- However...
When exactly did you get that scar on your thumb?
On the day and time of the crime,
- you went to Im Yoon Hui's house for a delivery. Is that correct?
- Yes.
According to your medical records which I obtained,
on the day that the incident occurred, you went to the emergency room and received stitches
for a three-centimeter wound on your right thumb.
We request the admission of the witness' medical records as evidence.
Usually, when a normal person stabs someone with a knife, the knife doesn't go in well.
There are many cases where their thumbs get cut.
Is this a simple coincidence?
Your Honor, the police only believed Im Yoon Hui's confession
and did not investigate anything about Park Soo Myeong at all.
Perhaps the police just wanted to quickly wrap up the case that was becoming a social issue from the beginning.
They neglected to find out the truth behind the incident.
I'm going to ask you.
Who killed Kim Hyeong Tae that day?
Objection, Judge.
At the crime scene, there was no evidence, not a single trace of fingerprints or blood of the witness.
Right now, without any evidence,
the attorney is misleading you and the jury.
That's out of his mere imagination.
No, that's not it.
Your Honor,  to prove Defendant Im Yoon Hui guilty, the only evidence provided by the prosecutors
were the defendant's confession and the autopsy report.
But even the autopsy report doesn't match the defendant's confession.
Like the prosecutor argued, she's been in a serious condition that would take about 9 weeks to heal.
It doesn't make sense she was able to stab her husband right in vital spots twice. It's impossible.
Park Soo Myeong went to the crime scene that day and
got a cut on his thumb.
Im Yoon Hui said she murdered him but she wasn't physically capable of doing so.
I'm going to ask you one more time.
The one who murdered Kim Hyeong Tae that day.
Who is it?
The one who stabbed that person...
The one who stabbed that person—
Soo Myeong, don't! Don't say anything!
Ms. Defendant, please stay calm.
Don't hit Noona! Don't hit Noona! Don't do that to her! Don't!
I stabbed him. I stabbed him with a knife.
Soo Myeong...
That bastard... That bastard hit her every day.
My Noona got hit again that day, every day.
So I stabbed him.
My Noona got hit again that day. Why? She got hit.
She got hit again that day, too.
Stop... .
Noona... Noona.
- Noona! Noona! Don't hit Noona! Don't hit her!
- Noona?!
Soo Myeong, run away, please!
Please!
I stabbed him, I did it. I stabbed him.
My Noona got beat.
My Noona got hit every day, every day.
She's coming!
Did you have an affair with the suspect?
There were only your fingerprints at the scene.
Why did you try to conceal the crime scene?
Why didn't you reveal that someone else killed your husband?
Please say a few words!
It's no different from me killing him.
Since I've killed him in my mind
dozens of times. No, hundreds of times already.
It has been revealed  that there is a real murderer who is responsible for Mr. Kim Hyeong Tae's death.
Mr. Park confessed himself that he is responsible for the murder.
He stated that he ended up killing him by accident.
The police have reported that they've found a pair of blood-stained gloves
in Mr. Park's bedroom and they believe the blood stains belong to
the late Kim Yeong Tae and Mr. Park. They will request a DNA analysis.
He's indeed our firm ace! I knew Lawyer Kwon could do it!
I know, right? I didn't even imagine that there could be a true perpetrator other than her.
Really? You really didn't know? I already knew that.
If you already knew, you wouldn't have just stayed put.
With your personality, you would've bragged about it all along.
What do you mean I'd brag? Are you done talking now?Huh?
We're back.
Lawyer Kwon!
Come here. You've worked so hard. Come.
No, I'm going to give you a hug today.
I love you, Kwon Jeong Rok.
We can't just let this joyous day go by without a celebration.
Let's have a firm dinner tonight. The first round will be Korean beef.
The second round will be karaoke.
Okay? Okay.
- I'm sorry but let's go on another day.
- What is it this time?
I'm a bit tired today. I'm sorry.
Then, we should celebrate without Lawyer Kwon.
What are you talking about? The main character won't be there.
Have you ever seen a fan meetup without a celebrity?
Have you ever seen a baby's first birthday party without a baby?
Let's  get our heads on straight, alright?
- You are getting off work on time today. It's been a while.
- Yes, well...
You must be so tired. Go home and get some good, good rest.
Ms. Oh Jin Sim. Would you go have soju with me?
Excuse me?
Oh Nam Gamjatang (pork stew)
It seems like you are not really in a good mood.
It's strange. My Mr. Lawyer usually feels really happy when he wins a case.
Ah, perhaps...
Is it because of Prosecutor Yoo Yeo Reum?
Do you feel uneasy because she's your friend?
Yes. That too...
Ms. Im Yoon Hui confessing in place of Mr. Park Soo Myeong,
and Mr. Park Soo Myeong committing a murder for her,
I could understand them both so...
It's a bit hard for me to just be happy and enjoy the day.
Here.
Goodness!
- Thank you.
- For what?
For telling me that I'd definitely win the case, and when I got hurt,
for worrying about me the most.
Don't mention it.
By the way ...
may I ask you one thing?
You said you were tired, so
you won't go to the firm dinner.
But why did you ask me to drink soju with you?
Today, I just wanted to...
I wanted to have a drink with you, just the two of us.
It's colder than I expected.
Why are you laughing like that?
I just remembered
the time we went to the arboretum together.
Then, you told me to put my hands
in (my) pocket if my hands were cold,
but I misunderstood and put my hands in your pocket, remember?
I was really embarrassed back then!
Because I was in a lot of dramas,
there are times when I lose my sense of reality.
To be honest, there was no need for you to offer your pocket
just because my hands were cold, you know?
I've become concerned.
As much as you worry about me and comfort me,
I also want to do the same now.
♫  Time, time is mystical  ♫
♫  You regret after it has passed. Oh, it's sad  ♫
♫  When a sweet dream wakes you up, even when it's clear  ♫
♫  it soon fades and disappears again  ♫
♫  La la  ♫
♫  Here you and me now to this moment  ♫
♫  I'm trying to put and hold in a place deep in my heart  ♫
♫  The touch of one hand comfortably over another
♫
Touch Your Heart
~ Preview ~
I wish it was someone that could move my heart.
Can't believe we are having a workshop with the universe's goddess Oh Yoon Seo.
Everyone is so worried that Yoon Seo might be cold but
how come you are so inconsiderate of Yoon Seo?
We went to get fish cake bars for you. He was empty-handed, you know.
She was expecting him to make a move but he won't.
- You are so mean, Mr. Lawyer!
- She's really mad.
There is no logic in love. You can't prepare everything ahead in love, you know.
Does he even like me?
I'm a slow person, so at my own pace,
I will walk towards you step by step.