Touch Your Heart
What is it that you wanted to tell me?
Episode 8
- Yoon Seo, you're having a really tough time, aren't you?
- What?
It's alright for you to cry.
Cry as much as you want and wipe your tears with this.
Yoon Seo, you foolish person.
If you were having such a difficult time, you really should have told me.
What do you mean, tears?
And I'm foolish? What are you saying?
I heard from Joon Seok that Lawyer Kwon has been really hard on you all this time.
He spoke harshly to you, spoke rashly, and even made you work overtime. Even when you took a day off work a few days ago,
I heard that it was because you kept trying to endure Lawyer Kwon's tyranny, but ultimately were unable to.
What do you mean?
With how I'm feeling, I wish I could fire Lawyer Kwon right now.
But, even though his personality is like it is, he's pretty skilled.
And there are a lot of trials going on right now.
So, that's why I'm saying this,
but what do you think about moving to Lawyer Choi's office for the rest of your time here?
- I don't want to!
- What?
Lawyer Kwon has never bullied me.
And taking the day off work was because of personal reasons.
It's not Lawyer Kwon's fault.
That's all a misunderstanding. It's a misunderstanding.
But why did you say you were going to destroy Lawyer Kwon
- and send him to hell?
- Oh, my.
- The CEO even told you that?
- Yeah.
Oh, that was just in the beginning.
I don't have any problems whatsoever now.
He teaches me a lot and is considerate of me. I'm so thankful to him.
Then from now on, you'll continue being Lawyer Kwon's secretary?
- Of course!
- Aigo.
That's a relief. Such a relief. That's such a relief. You don't know how worried I was
that you would take him on the road to hell yourself.
Yes, well.
That's a relief.
Why did the CEO say something so unnecessary?
My life without Lawyer Kwon is hell now, you know.
Wait. He doesn't have anything scheduled in the evening today.
Shall I ask him out on a date?
Restaurant.
This is making things difficut.
Restaurants that are good for dates
One without people
and private. Mm-hm.
Let's see.
Wow, it's pretty.
Then, I'll get in touch with you again.
- Alright, please head back.
- Alright.
- How are you feeling? Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Thanks to you.
Thanks for taking me to the ER that day.
Don't mention it.
Then take care of yourself.
Kwon Jeong Rok!
Isn't it wrong for us to keep being like this?
Let's have a glass of beer this evening.
One Star That I Love
I'm back.
- You're here?
- Mr. Lawyer.
Mr. Lawyer, do you have a star that you love kept in your heart, as well?
Yes, well.
A star...
Hello.
You're here? How did the trial go?
I won the case.
That's good.
- This evening—
- Ah!
I was planning on telling you anyway. I think I'll have  to have a glass of alcohol this evening.
Even alcohol? Sounds good!
- What?
I was telling you that I would be having a glass of alcohol with Prosecutor Yoo Yeo Reum.
With Prosecutor Yoo Yeo Reum?
Yes. We clashed with each other pretty badly because of the Im Yoon Hui case, did we not?
And in the end, it's true that I made things difficult for Yeo Reum.
We thought that it wasn't right for us to continue not seeing each other, and there are a lot of things that we need to resolve at this time.
Do you possibly... dislike that?
What do you mean, dislike it? What's the big deal about friends having a drink together?
I knew that you would say that.
What about the judicial precedent that you were going to find?
- It's right here. Right here.
- Alright.
Lovely: One Table Restaurant
Your reservation is complete!
Do you have plans today?
Well...
Who are you going with?
That's...
With Lawyer Dan.
I made reservations to go with Lawyer Dan.
Are you two close?
Of course. We're really, really close. We even talk to each other about our problems.
It's nice to see that you're close with someone at the law firm.
I will also support your friendship with her.
Then.
This is my first time coming to a place like this. It's so nice!
It's my first time coming, too.
It  is  nice.
But did you really make a reservation to eat here with me?
Just looking at it, it's a place for a date.
What do you mean, a place for a date?
I really did make a reservation to eat here with you.
This is the romantic couple course. Have a good time.
Not only did you come to a place like this with me,
you even reserved a romantic couple dinner course.
Yoon Seo...
You must want to date!
You need to hurry up and get a boyfriend!
Yes, well...
I'm sorry for being so small-minded all that time.
Actually, I wanted to do well on this case and get moved to a special department.
I think that I ended up thinking of this case as a ticket to that special department at some point.
Because my heart was in the wrong place, I ended up missing what was important.
I reflected on myself.
I was also mean to you.
Forget it. I was also sorry for suddenly putting an additional witness on the stand at the trial.
Right? You felt bad, didn't you?
You're really too much. How could you stab me in the back like that?
How could you reveal the true criminal there, you spiteful guy?
Yoon Seo, you took a day off a little while ago.
Did something happen?
I just wasn't feeling too well.
Ah, I see. I thought that you'd gotten into a fight with Lawyer Kwon again.
Well, what is there for me and Lawyer Kwon to fight about?
It seemed that there was a lot for you to fight about. Mr. Lawyer has an extremely prickly personality.
Honestly, when I saw him conducting the trial for Im Yoon Hui,
I was kind of surprised.
I've always known that Lawyer Kwon is cold-hearted,
but I didn't knoq that he'd be like that even toward Prosecutor Yoo Yeo Reum.
- How could he screw his first love over?
- Hm?
His first love, you said?
You wouldn't know, Yoon Seo.
It's a secret, but actually, but one of my classmates from law school
heard it from one of Lawyer Kwon's juniors at his school.
She said that he liked Yoo Yeo Reum.
Did those two date?
That's not it. Prosecutor Yoo Yeo Reum went out with Prosecutor Kim Se Won.
- Who is Prosecutor Kim Se Won?
- That...
Alright. This is Kwon Jeong Rok, this is Yoo Yeo Reum, and this is Kim Se Won.
These three were really close friends,
and Kwon Jeong Rok liked Yoo Yeo Reum, while Yoo Yeo Reum liked Kim Se Won.
And then, these two dated.
So they say that Lawyer Kwon's love just ended as a painful one-sided love.
- Don't be like that. Let's have a meal together sometime.
- Whenever is fine with me.
My heart was almost touched.
If you have time, shall we eat together? What about pasta?
I'm sorry, but will you head back first?
So he liked her?
So that's why, like that...
But, this is just my personal thought.
I think that Lawyer Kwon
has lingering feelings for Yoo Yeo Reum.
His gaze when he looks at Prosecutor Yoo Yeo Reum
is unusual.
Yoo-Yoon Seo, why are you doing that?
Well, because the macaroon is too small.
Shouldn't it at least be as big as the palm of my hand?
Ah, I'm pissed off, seriously!
Here. Eat all of them, Yoon Seo.
I won't eat this one.
Yes, Oh Jin Sim.
I was already planning on calling you when I got home.
Mr. Lawyer, could you come see me right now?
What? Right now?
Yes. I have something I have to tell you, right now at this moment.
I'll go to you. Where are you?
I'm near my house.
Then, I'll send you my address.
Is something wrong? You came all the way here.
I could have gone to you.
Mr. Lawyer,
I heard that you liked Prosecutor Yoo Yeo Reum.
I heard that you were in a love triangle with her and your close friend. Is that true?
Yes, it's true.
What are you so confident about?
Then, should I be embarrassed about it? It's already in the past.
But still, even if it is something in the past,
you drank with a woman that you liked so much a long time ago, just the two of you.
Doing that's a little strange!
What kind of girlfriend would like or be understanding of that?
But, we're just friends now.
That's what you think!
If you're still being good to her
and keep meeting up with her alone,
then other people who see you
could think that you still have feelings for her.
Kwon Jeong Rok!
What are you doing here?
Who is this?
Are you perhaps Jeong Rok's girlfriend?
Yes.  How are you?
Oh, hello. I am his roommate, Kim Se Won.
- Kim Se Won?
-  This is a real pleasure.
I really wanted to meet Jeong Rok's girlfriend.
Don't go home like that.  Let's go in together and order some chicken and beer together.
That's ...
Next time, next time.  I'll set up a dinner for you next time.
Why would you set up a dinner for next time?  This is something you can do right now.
Don't make it complicated.  Relax and let's have some beer.
Come on,  quickly.
- She's busy and ...
- Come on, come on.
Come with me.  Come on.
Hurry and come.
Here,  the chicken came.  This way.
-  This way.
- Hurry and grab a seat.
Ah...
Although I didn't set the table, please  help yourself.
Yes.
Anyway, I'm so glad to meet you.  Every time he talked about you, I was really curious as to what kind of person you were.
He told you about me?  Mr. Lawyer?
Of course. You and he went to a company dinner together a while back, right?
You also went to the movies. After seeing the movie, he  had the ticket like this.
He was looking at the ticket like this and that's when I sensed it.
Oh, this is love.
- Love has come.
-  Just eat the chicken and be quiet.
Why?  Are you feeling bashful? Shy?  Embarrassed?
But, don't you feel stuffy?
Why do you have to wear sunglasses indoors?
Oh, that is ...
Well, since I'll be seeing you often in the future, then ...
Wow.
You look a lot like Oh Yoon Seo.
I am Oh Yoon Seo.
Really? You're really that Oh Yoon Seo?
My goddess, your goddess, the universe's goddess?
You know the slogan, too?
Of course, Yoon Seo was so famous.
If you just turned on the television, a commercial she made came on.
Yeah.  Yeah.  Didn't you do the advertising for this chicken before?
"Morakana chicken  is here."
"The really sweet chicken is here."
"Mora, mora, morakana."
"Morakana chicken is here."
Wow, daebak!
Wow! Daebak!
Wait, but I thought that Jeong Rok was dating his secretary.
If that's so, don't tell me you are the person who is his secretary?
Ah.  That is ...  so ...
Because of a situation, I'm working for only three months.
Oh, I see.
Hey, Man.  If you were dating the universe's goddess Yoon Seo,
you should have lived showing her how undeserving you are!
Why the heck did you get her upset, huh?
How do you know ...
Actually, you two seemed so unusual before.
Considering both of you, I wanted to get involved.  He's such an idiot at romance.
Yoon Seo, what exactly did our boy do wrong?
- But...
- No, no, please speak freely.
It sounded like earlier that you said that there was some lingering attachment or regret.. something along those lines.
She said that she found out that I liked Yeo Reum before, and that the three of us used to be in a love triangle.
Oh, I thought it was something serious.
If that's the issue, you have no need to worry!
It was just a light interest when they were in college. That's not even something you can call love.
It was a very very small amount of interest.
If that was super serious, the two of us would have become enemies.
How would we be able to maintain such a good relationship together and even be roommates? Agree?
- Well, I guess that's true, but...
- And from what I can see,
only you have been able to enter Jeong Rok's heart, Oh Yoon Seo.
I've never seen him open his heart this much to anyone before.
- Oh really??
- That's what I'm saying.
So, please don't misunderstand him uselessly.
And please, take good care of him, although he is lacking and prickly.
What do you mean I'm prickly?
Do you really not know? I'll spill all the beans to Oh Yoon Seo.
During college, I forgot to do some homework for my class so I asked him to show me his,
and this guy said "There is NO way I can lend you mine, so do your own work
but if you really need to copy mine, pay me 500 won per page."
But, that's still better than what I had to go through.
The first day I started working as his secretary, I cleaned Lawyer Kwon's desk and whoa.
He got so angry and cold, saying things like
"Why do you touch other people's belongings without permission".
He made me feel really bad.
Ah, I can imagine without even seeing it.
"Why do you touch other people's stuff without permission?" Was he like that?
No no.
He frowned even more and said,
"WHY DO YOU TOUCH OTHER PEOPLE'S STUFF WITHOUT PERMISSION?" like that.
- Oh even more? Frowning more like this?
- Yes!
"Why do you touch other people's stuff without permission?"
- Yeah like that!
- When was I ever that severe?
I just said "Why do you touch other people's stuff without permission?"
- nicely.
- Huh?
I think you're still misunderstanding me.
When did I say, "Why do you touch other people's stuff without permission?" angrily?
- Yeah, he did it like that!
- See, I'm right!
You remember now, right?
Prosecutor Kim Se Won seems like a really fun person.
Yeah, he's a pretty cheerful, fun person. So he always was popular with the girls.
Oh, so that's why you lost Prosecutor Yoo Yeo Reum to him!
Oh, I'm just kidding, it's a joke.
Are you feeling better now?
Ah well,
when I first heard that you liked her, I was really jealous.
But now, like you said, it's all in the past.
And also,
as Prosecutor Kim Se Won said,
I'm the only one in your heart.
Thank you for thinking like that.
I honestly think that jealousy is the most useless emotion.
As long as we are true to our hearts, the past is insignificant.
Let's not waste our energy dwelling on the past, and instead, let's focus on the present.
Oh you're back, you thief?
Huh? Thief?
You're our country's third biggest thief.
1) Rice thief, the marinated crab, 2) Rain, who married Kim Tae Hee, and 3) You, who are dating Oh Yoon Seo.
You better behave properly in the future.
If it's Oh Yoon Seo, you're going to have a lot of competition.
If you don't want to lose her, treat her well!
- How is one supposed to do that?
- Huh? What?
Treating her well. How do I do that?
Why do you ask something like that? It's just like, if there is something she wants, do it for her.
If there is something that she's lacking, then be understanding and try to compliment her, just things like that.
It's not as easy as it sounds. Even earlier, if it weren't for you, I would have been in trouble.
Thanks.
Oh my, I can't believe I'm hearing those things come out of his mouth.
It definitely must be love, it's love.
It's moist.
Hm, why are you taking care of your lips?
Hm... what could it be...what are you trying to do?
If you have the time to tease me about it, why don't you start looking at houses?
- When are you going to move out?
- Jerk, always holding your house over my head.
How is it going with Yeo Reum?
What do you mean, how is it going? I'm just having lingering attachments, by myself.
Anyway, keep doing what you were doing. Put it on well, so they are moist.
Right... moist.
Dieu Castle
Oh Jim Sim, why are you here?
What do you mean why am I here? I wanted to head to work with you so I'm here.
This is the perk of dating someone in the same company, don't you agree?
Oh no, where did it go?
- You seem to have left something important.
- Oh, yes...
my jealousy!
I left my jealousy at home
since such unnecessary emotions make our relationship feel more distant.
From now on, I'm not going to carry any jealousy.
Anyway, shall we go?
Ah, wait.
- Please give me your car key.
- Huh? Why?
Since, Oh Jin Sim, you're pretty bad at driving and you find it difficult.
I can no longer let you suffer.
Wait, he's worrying about me again. Here he goes again.
I really can't take it!
The mirror is really small.
It's cute, isn't it?
It's my lucky mascot.
I was cast on the street the day that I bought this.
So I believe that this brought me good luck.
But you wouldn't need something like this, Mr. Lawyer.
Why? Because the Goddess of Luck who possesses this lucky mascot is your girlfriend!
Anyway, you make people feel so embarrassed.
Can I hold your hand?
What? Why are you asking something like that so suddenly?
As you have already deduced, today at our Always law firm,
these are the law school students who will be interning here. Introduce yourselves.
- Hello!
- Hello.
Each of you should give a personal self-introduction.
Hyung, you go first.
- No, no. You go first.
- Okay.
Hello! I'm Lee Jeong Hwan.
Hello, Sunbaes!  The man who will endlessly write
so that I don't miss a single pearl of wisdom to be learned from you, Kim Pil Gi greets you.
Okay.
But, Jeong Hwan, your name sounds kind of like a female name.
But you look really manly and handsome.
You're right. You're a bit below my class,
but... you're pretty good looking.
Then, please take care of us!
Lawyer Yeon Joon Gyoo, Lawyer Kwon Jeong Rok, Lawyer Choi Yoon Hyeok,
and Lawyer Dan Moon Hui.
H-How did you memorize all our names?
Was I caught? I looked on your homepage and memorized them.
Memorizing my senior's names in advance.
- Isn't that the advantage of the internet? Right?
- Yes.
I would have to carve out of my right and left brain
the brilliant and noble honor of the shining star-like sunbaes.
- It's truly, once more, an honor.
Ah, right, we're going on a workshop this weekend. Jeong Hwan and... Pil Se?
Pil Gi. Kim.
Pil Gi and Jeong Hwan, attend if you can.
- Thank you!
- Thank you.
I'm sorry. I'm late because I was answering a client's phone call.
♫  Oh I come alive. Oh I come alive. I come alive.  ♫
Did they come here knowing that Oh Jin Sim is here?
Of course, I told them beforehand. I got them to sign a non-disclosure agreement.
They've lost their souls. They've lost them completely.
Yoon Seo, please take care of these guys well.
They're going to be learning in Lawyer Kwon's office.
What? In my office?
Yeah. They're going to go through a rotation, and they're going to start with you.
- Lawyer Kwon, have a talk with me.
- Yes, sir.
It's so disappointing.
You must want to take Intern Lee Jeong Hwan right now and teach him how to work.
You're a maniac over good-looking people.
I'm good. I have a boyfriend now— Ah, my goodness. It's a secret.
Oh, really? Is he possibly working as a volunteer?
My boyfriend is the boss of the cafe out front. Look.
He's seriously handsome, isn't he?
I always went here and ordered an Americano in the morning, and he—
I'm sorry.  I'm bored.
He bought it for me! He bought it for me, I said!
Alright. Then, from now on, we shall begin the orientation.
There are several rules that you must keep in order to work with our Lawyer Kwon Jeong Rok.
Alright, the first one is that you must be strictly punctual getting to work.
Mr. Lawyer detests people who are late.
And the second on is, you must get off work right on time.
Mr. Lawyer also detests people who can not complete their work within working hours.
The third one, and this one is important,
is that Mr. Lawyer detests people who recklessly touch everything that they see.
Well, there are a lot of things that he hates besides this,
but you'll learn that slowly over time.
First, you must definitely strictly follow these three rules.
- Yes, ma'am!
- Yes, ma'am.
Then.
Umm, Ms. Oh Yoon Seo.
You can just call me Secretary Oh here.
Ah, yes. Secretary Oh, um, I...
I'm sorry, but can you give me your autograph?
My autograph?
Yes. I'm a huge fan, you see.
I... then could I take one picture with you?
Th-then can I shake your hand one time?
Then, can you say, "Jeong Hwan, good luck!"
- Then, can you say—
- Let's get to work.
- "Let's get to work" one time...
Wh-what should we do, Secretary Oh? Lawyer Kwon seems to be really angry.
I think that he detests me.
This won't do. I'll go beg him on my knees.
One moment! Don't misunderstand.
He normally looks like that.
Here. These are the documents that you asked for.
Yes, thank you.
By the way, you must be happy since your fans are here.
Honestly, I'd almost forgotten that I was a celebrity while I was working here.
But because they treat me like that, it's kind of nice.
But, are you possibly jealous?
Why would I do that? Did I not tell you?
There is no emotion more useless than jealousy.
I also left my jealousy at home.
I would be fine with you being jealous, though.
What?
Never mind. It's nothing.
Then, I will take my leave now.
After the examination of witnesses, I think the court is leaning towards a not-guilty verdict,
If so, don't you think the section head should be told that the charges might be dismissed?
No one knows until the verdict is announced.
Don't get afraid in advance.   Look through the documents closely again.
For anything missing, we can request again to submit more evidence.
So don't worry too much.
Thank you, Sunbaenim. Then I'll see you again.
Alright.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Because it seems like you've returned to your real self.
It wasn't like you to be faint-hearted.
Forget it. Set some time aside for me sometime. Let's eat.
I should pay my debt back.
You didn't even like meeting eyes with me.
Have we gotten back to the level where we eat together?
I told you that I was paying back a debt. If you don't want to, then don't.
No, I like it. Pay your debt back.
Pay it back properly. Ah, what about this evening?
There are a lot of documents I have to look at today. Then.
Then let's choose a date soon.  As soon as possible.
Ah, yes. Please give me a cup of espresso.
Yes, I'll submit the statement of my position by Wednesday.
Please read my submission and form your judgment.
Yes, I understand.
Then I'll call you again. Yes.
My boyfriend is the owner of the cafe out front!
He's extremely handsome, isn't he?
Here is the espresso you ordered.
Yes, thank you.
- You waited a long time, didn't you?
- Yeah.
I'll enjoy the drink.
I heard that you got a girlfriend.
What girlfriend? Because I'm nice, I'm letting it slide.
Why? I heard that she's really good to you and even has a good job. Isn't she a lawyer?
What's so great about being a lawyer? I'm not attracted to her.
Then you should just not date her.
I'm in a lawsuit with the landlord.
If I'm going to resolve it, then how expensive do you think lawyer costs would be?
On top of that, she buys me food and buys me gifts.
It's not without it's benefits.
Lawyer Dan.
Lawyer Dan!
Lawyer Dan. Lawyer Dan!
Are you alright?
I'm not alright.
I'm not alright!
I knew that he didn't like me.
Every time I wanted to meet, he would say that he was busy.
When I go to see him, he looks annoyed.
If he liked me, he couldn't do that.
But I still I thought that it would work if I just worked hard.
I didn't know he thought of me that way. I feel so foolish!
I can't end things like this.
I'm going to cuss him out thoroughly.
Lawyer Dan!
There's a limit to playing with another person's heart!
How could you do that?  How could you?
Jeez.
Did I ask you to date? Did I say I like you?
No way. Did you actually think I was dating you because I liked you?
What are you doing?
Because you wouldn't accept my feelings, I wondered how great the guy was that you were dating.
Did you ignore my feelings so you could meet someone who is barely trash?
What?  Trash?  Are you done talking?
I ...
can't give a woman to someone like you because she's too precious for that.
Let's go.
Lawyer Dan.  I don't want to give you advice at this time, but
from now on when you are looking at a man, instead of looking at his face, please look at his heart.
What?
There are so many good men in this world.  Why are you crying because of a guy like that?
Get home safely.
I thank ... you.
Yoon Seo,  do you have to go to the workshop?
You really aren't employed so why are you attending some workshop?
Why? You never know.  There might be a workshop scene in this drama.
I have to experience reality like this.
If such a scene does come up,  I could act it out realistically.
Don't you think you're packing too unrealistically for doing a real-life experience?
Are you going somewhere in Europe?
Won't it last just  one night and two days?  What is all this?
Hey, why are you bringing stuff to take a bath?
It's good for insomnia.  I'm going to have a bubble bath.
Yoon Seo, if you go to a workshop and take a bubble bath,
people are really going to be annoyed by you.
You'll be sharing a bathroom and will have to rush to wash your face and brush your teeth within three minutes.
Three minutes?
That many minutes?
I can't believe they are sending a newbie to a workshop who doesn't know anything. I feel so uneasy!
I will pack just one bag for you.
- There's too much clothing.
- You can't do that.
- There's too much.  Too much! Oh, make sure you take this.
- Oppa!
By the way. Don't forget to take one of the most important things.
- What's that?
- Your dignity as an actress.
Please don't make any mistakes after drinking.  Please maintain your dignity.
All right.
Now, although the workshop is important,  take care of your health first.
I'm almost there.
- One for Lawyer Kwon.
- What?
Lawyer Kwon, what do you think?  Perfect workshop fashion.
Doesn't it feel both trendy and elegant?
Elegant and trendy.  I think those two words escaped me.
I think you are a fashion ignoramus.
- Look.  This is exactly how ...
- A fashionista!
It's called a fashionista.  A young person knows one when she sees one.
I wasn't saying that to you, CEO. Over there. I was talking about Yoon Seo.
Seeing you outside, you shine even brighter, our Yoon Seo.
Seeing you every day, I'm in outer space. As expected, the goddess is a goddess.
I'll say. I'm so out of it, I want to pinch myself.
I'm sorry.  I was the last to arrive.
What's wrong with being late? I'm just glad you arrived safely.
You also take care of your health.  Two for you.  Thank you for coming.
What thanks.  I'm the one who is thankful. It's my first time on a group outing like this.
Really?  When you were a student, didn't you go on school trips?
When I was in middle school, I couldn't go because I had my appendix removed the day before the trip.
When I was in high school, I debuted before the trip so I couldn't go.
So I never went on a group trip or an MT.  (  Motiviation Trip )
So, I've been really looking forward to this workshop.
Well, if everyone is ready, let's go.
Let's go!
Aren't you going?
That is ... There are too many people at the rest stop.
That's true.  So many people  might be troublesome for you, Yoon Seo.
If you're really thirsty, you'll have to bear it.  I'll stay with you.
I will do the same. I will stay in the car with her.
No. Go and eat some tasty food and enjoy the air.
Well, I'll go to the restroom and come right back.
I'll be back even sooner.
Come back safely!
The hot bar looks yummy.
Danudog
Hot Dog Hot Bar; Sausages
One hot bar order please.
Hot Snacks
Hot bar. Hot bar. Hot bar.
I'm guessing you like hot bars?
Yoon Seo, please accept a hot bar from me.
Please try some of the few I prepared.  A flower bouquet, no, I mean a hot bar bouquet.
He didn't even spread ketchup on.  I spread the ketchup.
Please put it on to your liking.  I had it prepared with difficulty without the ketchup.
I also spread mustard.
I heard you were allergic to mustard so I had it made without any.
Ah? Well, I'll wipe the mustard off for you.
Yoon Seo doesn't like dirty things.
You heard that I've taken on the Im Yoon Hui case, right?
If I had been handling the case from the start, I would have resolved it neatly.
Because of someone who is hopelessly ambitious, I am exhausted from coming back a long way.
Kim Se Won!
Lee Joo Yeong!
Come over here.
Sunbae, have some more meat.
What's with you?  You eat it.
You're savvy about the hierarchy.  If someone were to see you, they would know you are employed.
Is it not allowed between a young man and young woman?
Yeah. All right, whatever.  You two look good together.  Be a couple.
I'll try my best.
Is that okay, Sunbae Yoo?
- Hey Lee Joo Yeong!
- Do you need my permission?
No. But as a courtesy, I am asking you whether I can do my best for Sunbae Se Won.
Don't make any effort.
- Why not?
- No matter how hard you try, it won't turn out the way you want.
I'm worried you'll be severely disappointed.
Sewoonsan Natural Forest Lodge
This is so nice.
When I was on a shoot,  I was alone in a huge hotel room.
Because I thought of being with others like this, I feel like I am on a school trip and I'm so happy.
It's great right.  But even though it's nice here,
if you go back of here,  the landscape is even more amazing than here.
That's right.  The walkway there is really nice. How about we take a walk.
- It would be nice to do that.
- Great.
Let's go on a walk. Let's unpack first and then go on a walk. Let's go.
This way.   You can use the two here.  Right, Left.
- Do you like her that much?
- What?
You like Secretary Yang.
Do I?
Isn't it hard?  You should exercise.
- Isn't it hard, Yoon Seo?
- It's not.  It's a lot of fun, isn't it?
This is the first time I've walked like this with so many people.  It's very exciting.
Yoon Seo.  It's like Princess Anne in Roman Holiday.
Tired of the royal family household, she ran away.  She was happy with trivial ordinary routines.
I'm so honored.  I really love Audrey Hepburn.
It seems you have caught a cold.
Does it?  It's chillier than I thought it would be.
Secretary Oh, use this.
This is an electric hand warmer. It's an individual electronic felt hot pack.
There's nothing to compare with it for keeping your hands warm.
- Oh, it's warm.
- Please keep it.
Excuse me, you need to wear this too.  It's very cold.
No, not at all, CEO. You must be cold.
I have light weight padding so it's enough.
It seems Secretary Oh's throat is dry.
Yoon Seo, have some vin chaud. ( mulled wine )
When it's cold, it's perfect for drinking.
This morning, all of a sudden the memory of drinking vin chaud,
while standing on the bank of the Seine River in Paris was evoked, so I prepared a few things.
It's so rewarding.
It's delicious.  I think my body is feeling warmer.
Everyone is concerned that she is cold, but why aren't you?
Anyway, you haven't done anything but just put your hands in your pockets and squished them.
How come you don't feel anything for Yoon Seo?
Yeah.  Earlier, everyone went to the hot bar for you but he came back by himself empty-handed.
If it were me, I would take better care of my secretary.
Lawyer Kwon is so heartless!
Yoon Seo is too cold.  Let's stop the walk and go down.
Let's go down and get ready for the barbecue party.   Let's go, go!
Stop climbing up! Come down!
- Are we going down?
- We're going down.
- Keep going?
- Yes.
- Yoon Seo seems very cold.
- It's okay. Let's go down first.
Oh my, you guys bought so much alcohol.
I don't see Yoon Seo, I wonder where she went.
It seemed like she was heading to her room before in order to prepare for the barbecue party.
Oh my... look
Why are you wearing a dress?
Because you said there was going to be a barbecue party tonight.
Is it not now?
Why are you all standing there like that? Aren't you going to get changed into dresses and tuxedos?
Ah well that's because the barbecue parties that we have during team workshops are only called 'parties'.
In reality, they are just for eating pork, soju, and beer.
- Feel free to wear anything comfortable that you want.
- Ah...
So it's that kind of atmosphere. I didn't know.
I'll quickly get changed into something else and come back.
Our Yoon Seo is kind of quirky. Don't you think it's endearing?
Yeah, she seems to be pretty innocent and pure.
Yeah exactly. At first, I thought she would be sly and stuck up, but she's surprisingly cute.
Ah, who would have thought she would have worn a dress?
What it is? Why are you smiling Lawyer Kwon? It's kind of scary.
What is scary about it? And also who bought this many snacks?
Did we come to eat snacks?
Why is he getting angry at me?
Whoa, whoa, be careful! Be careful! I will do this.
This might not seem like much, but it requires expertise.
First, the wind is blowing in... ah, this direction.
You have to put your back to the wind. Then you have to pick the wood... I see you have picked the wood well.
Then, you have to place the flame for exactly three seconds.
One.
Two.
Three!
Huh. Why isn't it working?
I'll try it one more time.
Can I try it once? It looks so fun!
You, Yoon Seo? Sure, have a go at it for fun. You may find it difficult.
Here we go.
One.
Two.
Three! Wow!
- How did she get it already?
- Yay! It's like a campfire!
Wow! It's my first time grilling meat outside.
Here, everyone please fill your glasses so we can have a toast!
Wow.
Eat a lot.  It's the 10000 won.  I prepared it with the 10,000 won.
The earthquake of the bar association.
The law firm society's coming giant, 'Always' (firm name).
Cheers. You worked hard.
Since it seems like the atmosphere is lively as well,
we'll start the 'Always Awards'.
'Always Awards'? What is that?
Oh, at every workshop, we have an awards ceremony.
Oh really? That's awesome!
It's nothing big. It's just since everyone is working so hard for Always,
people might appreciate receiving a few awards during the workshops.
It's just this CEO's small gift of appreciation.
So, we'll get started with the awards ceremony now. The first recipient.
Kwon Jeong Rok! Applause!
Here, the award's name is: "First in Sales Revenue Again."
Am I an insurance king or something? What do you mean revenue?
Why? It's witty and fun.
As a prize, I've prepared two volumes of  Humor Heaven.
Applause!!
Next winner is, Lawyer Choi Yoon Hyeok.
The name of the award is: "First Place Tomorrow."
We hope that you will work hard and surpass Lawyer Kwon and will be in first place. Applause!
Yes, it may be difficult but I will focus less on justice and sense of duty,
and will instead become a lawyer that focuses more on driving revenue.
Next is Lawyer Dan.
The award name is 'Please Be Less Timid' award.
- Secretary Yang. 'Always the same'.
- Award name:
Only your face is scary. Your face may be scary but your work ethic is very polished and soft.
And lastly, the idol of the reception desk! Applause!
I've also prepared two concert tickets. Applause.
And with this, we'll now be wrapping up the award ceremony here...
but today, we have prepared a special award. Today's special award
goes to...
Oh Yoon Seo!
Really? You're giving me an award too?
Please come forward!
As a prize, we'll be giving you a pair of slippers to wear comfortably at the office,
'Always Vitamin Award'! Applause!
Since the reception is so good, I'll specially read out the award contents.
'Always Vitamin Award', Oh Yoon Seo.
'This person, coming from a universe's goddess status, could have found it difficult to adjust.
However, with her diligent work ethic and bright smile,
as she has become an important, vitamin-like person in the 'Always Law Firm' we present this award.
Thank you!
Actually, I wonder if I should be allowed to accept this award.
But, I will consider it to be a catalyst to work harder in the future
and will accept it with a happy heart. Thank you!
Hearing Yoon Seo's acceptance speech, doesn't it sound like the end of the year awards ceremony?
She could have just worn that dress from earlier!
Here here. Let's clean up.
Ah yes. I will discuss the schedule with the prosecution side and will give you a call back.
We ran out of beer so I'm on the way to get some more.
You look very happy today.
Yes, extremely. These are all new experiences for me, so it's all very exciting.
And also, everyone seems like really good people. They're also very kind to me.
- I am also treating you we—
- What are you doing there?
- Oh? Why are you all coming out?
Because it's getting colder out here and everyone seems to be a bit tired.
Oh, it's already the end.
Let's go inside, Yoon Seo. Ah, something must have gotten into my eye.
- Does anyone have a mirror?
- I don't.
- I do!
- Oh really?
Oh.
The hand-mirror must take after its owner.  It's so beautiful.
I'll use it preciously and will return it to you. Let's head in.
Let's go.
But, are we just going to sleep like this? I feel like it would be a shame.
Hm, then why don't we can talk for some time and then go to sleep.
But, aren't you craving something spicy?
Since we only ate meat, which was a bit greasy.
Should we eat bibim noodles (noodles mixed with vegetables) then?
I bought extra ingredients for it earlier, since I thought we might end up eating it as a midnight snack.
As expected Secretary Yang. Someone who is so diligent at work is also great at preparing for the workshop too.
Wait for a bit.
Lawyer Dan, why do you have no appetite?
Your expression also isn't that good. Is there something going on?
It seems like she broke up with her boyfriend.
How do you know that, Hae Yeong?
What do you mean how do I know? You're the one that was staring at your phone the whole day, waiting for your boyfriend's response.
Now you're just looking off into space, just sighing loudly.
That means that there is no longer a boyfriend to hear from.
But, you liked him so much. How did that happen?
It turns out that he didn't have any feelings for me.
He just wanted to use me because he was in a lawsuit with his landlord.
What? He's such a crazy a**hole.
You're a celebrity. You shouldn't be saying such things.
But it makes me so angry.
Lawyer Dan really liked him, right?
How can someone use another person's innocent feelings?
I am not going to love again.
From now on, my heart is on temporary suspension.
There aren't any towels in the bathroom.
This is the last one.
Oh my Jong Hwa, Jong Hwa!
Then you shouldn't have used the towel and should have just dried off with your clothes or something.
What are our sunbaes going to dry off with?
You're overreacting too much.
They said there were a lot of towels at the women's rooms. Just ask them to bring us a few.
Okay. Then I will contact them right away.
But, you've been laughing for a while now. What are you looking at?
Oh this? This is the group photo that we took earlier.
Isn't Yoon Seo so beautiful?
Wow, she is really beautiful. And on top of that, she's so polite.
And also innocent! I used to like her before but I like her even more now.
Right? But for someone like Yoon Seo,
I wonder what kind of guy she would date.
So, I searched for Secretary Oh's ideal type.
'A guy who can make her heart feel touched'
is what she said.
This, this, this. She's talking about me.
Earlier, I bought her a hot bar and provided her with vin chaud. Imagine how touched she would have felt.
Stop it. Just a single hot bar and tsing tao, I mean vin chaud.
You brought the vin chaud to drink it yourself and you just shared a little bit.
She was probably touched by me, Yeon Joon Gyoo.
I bought her how many hot bars? A bouquet full.
And I gave her my coat so that she wouldn't catch a cold,
and with the 'Always Vitamin Award,' it's a three level combo. Bam! Bam! Bam!
You are truly impressive, sir.
I didn't give her anything other than a hot bar and an electric warmer.
I also did catch that she had a dry throat, but that's probably insufficient (weak) right?
- Too weak
- Definitely too weak. You should have done more.
The way I see it, I have the most potential, but
- the only thing that is for sure, is that it isn't Lawyer Kwon.
- Excuse me?
It's true. Out of all of us, who do you think the person who touched her heart the least?
It's Lawyer Kwon.
Don't even mention usually treating her poorly. Just think carefully about today.
Did you treat her well or not? Of course not!
- Lawyer Kwon, eliminated!
From her ideal type, you're eliminated!
Those eliminated, please bring out the blankets. Let's go to sleep. Let's clean this up.
Here, those who were eliminated, please spread out the blankets.
- At first glance, he seems good looking. However, he's too arrogant and cold.
- That's true.
Take a look at this.   I didn't use any photo app,  but I  don't show a single pore.
- You need to sleep, is this your pajamas?
- No, I'm going to wash up later—
Why, what's up?
What's the meaning of this?
Since you asked for blankets, I wanted to get them to you quickly.
I must have been too fast.
I think you were too fast. My hair is all ruined.
Why didn't he say something?
Can you give me the mirror?
I put the mirror that Oh Yoon Seo gave me in here...
I definitely put it in here.
I got it from Yoon Seo and put it in here.
Oh, I must have dropped it. I'm going crazy!
Oh my, where did it go?
But Secretary Yang, do you have any thoughts on dating?
What do you mean, me dating?
I'm so busy with company work and house chores that the day goes by so fast.
And, if I have such time, I should spend more time with Jin.
But, if there were  someone who knew your situation well and
could understand, wouldn't it be okay for you to open your heart to them?
I can't say.  I don't have the confidence to date anyone anymore.
Instead of doing this, should we drink some?
- What is this?
- Tada!
Whoa, is this wine? It looks like it's pretty nice!
Oh actually, I heard that there was a party
so I brought it, but I think this is the perfect time to drink it.
Even if it's not right now, I wish Secretary Yang would meet someone nice.
And also, Lawyer Dan, you should have some energy and feel better.
You can have some revenge on that jerk when you get back to Seoul.
Revenge?
Yeah, you've got to do something!
You should write, "A**hole*, and stick it on the cafe that he's running.
Thanks, Yoon Seo.
A celebrity, who is willing to cuss out and exact revenge on my behalf...
With everyone willing to take my side and cuss him out, I feel
a little better.
Anyway, it feels good to talk about my feelings and thoughts.
I also really really like this sort of setting.
To be honest, I've been a celebrity for a while but
I didn't really have any friends to talk to about my feelings and so I was a bit lonely.
But when you see TV broadcasts,
you seem really close to Kim Min Ji and Yang Soo Jin, is that not the case?
That's just for show. I don't even know their phone numbers.
Can you give me your phone, Yoon Seo?
Huh?
This is my number.
I'm not a fun conversationalist and there isn't much I can do for you.
If you want to eat bibim noodles, I can make it for you.
Here, let's have a toast!
- Cheers!
- Yes.
Cheers!
Drink it in one shot!
Yeah, the best revenge is
for me to get over it fast and to live happily.
I can just meet someone who is better than that jerk!
Olé!
Oh sorry! I thought no one was in here.
This is good. I was about to use a used towel and was feeling gross about it.
Nice timing.
Please be careful.
Olé!
Mr. Lawyer, what are you up to?
Are you sleeping?
Yoon Seo.
Oh hi, sir. You didn't go to sleep yet?
I don't know what to do, I'm so sorry.
Why?
I think I lost the hand mirror of yours.
I changed clothes and I definitely put it in here but
I don't see it inside. I think I might have lost it somewhere outside.
Oh it's okay. It's not that important. No need to worry!
- It's okay. It's just a mirror. I can buy another one.
- Is that so?
Oh, I was worrying for nothing. Anyway, I'm sorry.
Oh no, it's fine. Have a good night!
Okay, I'm heading in. Have a good night!
Okay.
It's okay, it's just a mirror.
You had a fun time today, that should be enough.
Oh Jin Sim.
Oh? Mr. Lawyer.
Why are you out here at this time, Oh Jin Sim? I thought you would be asleep for sure.
Ah, I have insomnia so I wasn't able to fall asleep.
So I just came out to get some fresh air.
And there is also something I need to find.
Why are you out here, Mr. Lawyer?
Ah, actually...
Oh my! How is this possible?
I heard the CEO mention that he lost it earlier.
I remembered that you said it was your good luck mascot (charm), so I wanted to find it for you.
So then, you were out here this late at night, in order to find it for me?
Thank you, Mr. Lawyer.
I finally was able to do something for you.
Huh?
Honestly, I wanted to treat you well, Oh Jin Sim.
If there were any request that you had, to do it for you. If there were anything lacking, to fill it for you.
That was what I wanted to do.
But I missed all those opportunities.
I would like to be the one to make you smile and laugh, Oh Jin Sim,
but other people keep seizing the opportunities first.
So I felt a little down today.
Mr. Lawyer, is that by any chance, jealousy?
Yes, that's correct. It's jealousy.
Jealousy. I thought it was an unnecessary emotion,
but it seems like if you like someone, it is difficult to control one's emotions.
Why are you looking at me like that? Am I being too childish?
Nope, because I like it.
Because it sounds like you like me so much it is difficult for you to control your emotions,
I'm so happy.
Mr. Lawyer.
May I please
give you a kiss, Mr. Lawyer?
Excuse me?
Ah, now?
But why would you ask that?
Just because you're so lovable right now, Mr. Lawyer.
Mr. Lawyer, next time, you should just do it without asking me.
If you're going to do it later.
Let's go inside since it's cold.
Since you told me not to ask you first.
♫    Full of something I don't know  ♫
♫   Honestly, for me it's difficult umm   ♫
♫   Timing is what it is     ♫
♫   Why did it get twisted on its own?  ♫
♫  My slow moving heart  ♫
♫  Searched for you with all my might  ♫
♫  Within a footstep's reach   ♫
♫  I'm here, are you waiting for something?   ♫
♫  Ooh love love is What is it? What is love?  ♫
♫  Ooh love How should I say it?  What if love?  ♫
♫  Probably for me it's you  ♫
Touch Your Heart
♫ one one one ♫
Ms. Jin Sim, Jin Sim, Jin Sim.  You're so beautiful.
Who are you? Our lawyer is someone who isn't able to say such sweet things.
Don't you think the people at our law firm will be suspicious of us?
I think we should be careful.
What is the reason for you to escort her home today?
Seriously, why are you being like this?
Why exactly are you unable to eat alone?
I will help you so why don't you practice a little bit at a time?
There is only one month left until you quit working at the law firm.
I wonder if Lawyer Kwon will be sad when Yoon Seo quits.
I felt that it wasn't right for there to be secrets between those who should be the closest.
Where did you say Lee Gyeong Joon is?
How did he know to follow us?
From now on, Oh Jin Sim's problems are my problems.