Touch Your Heart
Excuse me.
Mr. Lawyer,
do you perhaps, not like women?
- What?
- I mean,
Men...
Do you dislike women?
This might be disappointing to your wayward imagination.
What are you doing?
I,
like women. A lot.
I  totally like women.
Except,
I have zero interest in you, Oh Jin Sim.
Then will you please leave now.
Excuse me!
If you like women that much, let me give you a piece of advice.
Please fix your personality. What woman would like such a cranky character?
I won't ask you to like me, so don't worry.
Ha, who's worrying?
I hope you'll stick to those words!
- Why? You don't have confidence?
- Not confidence, I don't have time.
Since I now have to find the documents you lost, Oh Jin Sim.
I said it's Oh Yoon Seo. Oh Yoon Seo!
Oh Yoon Seo, we're having your welcome party this evening—
- Did I do something wrong?
- I think she's like that because she fought with Lawyer Kwon.
Why? Do they not get along?
- How would I know that?
- So why would you think they fought?
Just because.
What?
Episode 2
Kwon Jeong Rok, you jerk!
You mannerless *ssh*le!
You are so freakin' mean!
Oh, it's so cold.
Ms. Vivien said in Gone With the Wind.
"After all, tomorrow is another day."
It's so freezing. I really want to disappear with the wind.
Lawyer Kwon, what are you doing? Looking for something?
It's nothing.
Did you perhaps fight with Yoon Seo?
- There was nothing like that.
- Figures.
What could there be to fight about with a great secretary like Yoon Seo?
Lawyer Kwon, you know I don't acknowledge many people, right?
But I acknowledge Yoon Seo.
Looks, personality, they're all totally perfect.
A person like that suits my perfection better than you, Lawyer Kwon.
Doesn't it seem like the president mismatched you two?
Did you come to say that?
Look at me. I wanted to return this. It was very helpful.
Why do you have this?!
I told you I'd borrow it to look at it briefly ...
Right! I thought I'd tell you when you were back, but it slipped my mind!
Why are you taking someone's else things without even a word?
Oh, sorry, sorry. I needed to request  a preliminary injunction to preserve asset titles.
I looked at it as a reference briefly.  I didn't ask you first because I was so busy.
Because of my busy-ness, please overlook the minor slip in etiquette between us modern men.
Application for Temporary Injunction to Prohibit Transfer of Real Property
(TN. Attorney Choi, a divorce lawyer, wants  to prevent the spouses from moving assets to other people's names.)
3. Tidy up the desk!
I have a meeting with a client after court, so I'll leave  work right after.
Do that then.
And,
I'm sorry.
For what?
The document  you lost, Oh Jin Sim— No, the document  I thought   you lost,
Lawyer Choi took and had it.
What?
Sorry for not searching properly before blaming you.
Wait a minute. It wasn't my fault, but yours.
- Is that it?
- Yes.
- Apologies-
- Is a sorry enough?
The pain's already been inflicted, is an apology the end?
Right.  If the document was that important, you should've looked after it.
Why would you lose it and find another to blame it on?
I hope you won't be so hasty in the future.
Be thankful, not cranky, if I clean the desk.
That's not it. I apologize for my carelessness, but my desk is organized in a specific way,
so please don't touch it in the future. Well then.
Well then?
What is this? Is he apologizing or starting an argument?
Lawyer Kwon, you're coming to Yoon Seo's welcome party today, right?
I told you I have an appointment with my client.
Does it make sense for you not to come? It's welcoming your personal secretary.
Who's the one that decided without even asking about my schedule?
That's me. But then, even if you didn't have an appointment, I wouldn't have asked because you won't be coming anyway.
If you don't come, Yoon Seo's going to be really disappointed! You have to come.
Wait! Sir, please listen.
Enough! Are you the only lawyer?
Who are you making a criminal here?
Sir!
I'm sorry, President Yeon. That person
didn't want to pay taxes despite having a lot of money, so my sense of justice was ignited.
You did well, a sense of justice is important.
What if we don't earn much money? I will be just behind on my rent, that's all. I couldn't take care of the law firm's building but we upheld justice.
You did well. You know what I'm saying?
You did well.
At the least, I'm sure the evidence is enough and I think 15 years would be a reasonable request.
Good, make sure to clear it up.
Yes.
Department Head, about the woman who killed her husband,
please give the case to me. I will make sure to get her the verdict of imprisonment.
What is it?
She stabbed him to death, and her previous husband was caught in a fire. Something's fishy.
Maybe, her ex-husband was murdered, too.
What's your basis for thinking that?
I read the investigation journal. It seems like she could be a femme fatale.
I hear Kim Se Won is returning?
He's starting tomorrow. You didn't hear?
Don't you talk after breaking up?
Don't cause a problem.
I don't care what you do anymore, but I won't tolerate embarrassment in front of the prosecution a second time.
Yes, I'm sorry.
First floor.
- It's been a while.
- Yeah.
I heard the news. You're back to working here.
Yeah, it happened that way.
- Have you been well?
- Thanks to you.
- Are you on your way back from seeing the department head?
- Yeah.
- Lunch?
- I ate.
You'll have to eat a lot, you're skinny.
Welcome party? Do you have to go there?
If you make a mistake after getting drunk there—
Don't worry. I'll drink in moderation. I can't not drink at my own welcome party.
Anyway, I'll call you when it's done.
Okay. I'll be on standby around there so call me.
- And be careful with alcohol.
- I said I got it.
Oppa, I'm Oh Yoon Seo.
Are you worried I might fall for someone while drunk?
I'm going to be elegant and stay aloof, so don't worry.
So that's why I'm saying, I'm just going to try to do well.
I cleaned up his desk because I really wanted to help him.
You know that, right, Secretary Yang?
Huh? Ah, of course, I know that you tried hard.
Yoon Seo, I think you drank too much.
But Lawyer Kwon got all mad and looked down on me.
Does he perhaps have intermittent explosive disorder?
Mm-hmm. He does have that kind of side.
Earlier, I made a really small and human-like mistake.
But he was way too serious about it.
- Right? That's what I'm saying!
- Right?
That's right.
But why isn't Lawyer Kwon coming?
I really need to... talk to him.
She's crashed.
What should we do? I think she drank too much.
We should just wait until she wakes up. What else can we do?
By the way, what should we do for our Yoon Seo?
I think that she's clashing with Lawyer Kwon a lot.
CEO, this is what I was saying.
If you would have sent her to me from the start, this wouldn't have happened.
I could teach Yoon Seo how to work and help her to adjust.
- And become a couple.
- And we could become a couple.
What is with you, Lawyer Dan?
I'm sorry! It just seemed like you were interested in her.
Well, it's not like I'm not interested in her.
Why are you interested in her? Why are you interested in our Yoon Seo? How dare you.
What do you mean, how dare I? What's wrong with me?
I'm handsome, personable, physically fit, and competent.
And what's more,  I'm a filial son and ...
- A mama's boy.
- I'm a mama's boy!
Ah, are you trying to pick a fight with me right now, Lawyer Dan?!
No, I'm not good at fighting. I'm sorry.
Ah, seriously...
But will things be okay like this between Lawyer Kwon and Yoon Seo?
But when I looked at the gossip, Yoon Seo is also the type to get angry really quickly.
So won't things get totally messed up later?
Don't worry. Before something troubling like that happens,
it is my job as the CEO to spot those kinds of things in advance. So don't worry about it.
Ah, but why isn't Lawyer Kwon coming?
Lawyer Kwon is here?
You're here?
Lawyer Kwon?
Why do you look like that? It must because you get angry too much,
but your face is getting scarier and scarier.
So I think that it would be better to settle instead of filing a lawsuit.
Ah, that's probably true.
As you know, I'm a big fish.
It's also burdensome for me to file a lawsuit over such a small problem.
But what should I do? Because of that bull crap,
my kid can't concentrate on his studies and is failing college.
Really?
This is his 4th time. If he fails again—
I'm sorry. But if that's all for today...
Why? Ah!
Have a drink before you go, My Lawyer.
It is my principle to not drink with my clients.  And also...
CEO  Yeon Joon Gyoo
I will find a point of compromise soon with the opposing lawyer.
Alright. So just have one glass.
I'm sorry. I will leave first today. Then.
Alright, I got it.
But, Your Highness Mom, what do you think about having a celebrity as a daughter-in-law?
What? You said not over your dead body?
Ah, Mom. Mom, why are you so extreme?
Give me your permission, please!
Then I'll see you at home, Mother.
Are you going for the second round now? Then what about the wine bar across the street?
Let's go home. Everyone is tired and Yoon Seo is really drunk.
It's disappointing for us to part like this.
But where is Yoon Seo?
Ah, right now, with her manager... No, what is he? Her relative oppa.
She's on the phone with her relative oppa. He's going to come pick her up right now. It's her relative oppa.
Um, I'm sorry, but may I leave first?
It's time for Jin Hee to get out of her study academy.
Ah, go ahead and leave first.
Office Manager, please leave with her too. Your house is in the same direction, right?
Then please have light and bubbly hearts tonight just like the foam on the beer we drank today.
We'll be heading on.
Yes, please head on.
Wait a second. Beer foam?
What is he talking about, CEO?
I'm not sure what he meant by beer foam.
- Oh! Lawyer Kwon is here.
- Oh, you're here?
Ah, Lawyer Kwon, why did you just get here? We waited so long for you.
Our discussion went on longer than planned.
Oh! It's Kwon Jeong Rok. Kwon Jeong Rok!
Lawyer Kwon, why are you just getting here?
I have  sooooooo  much to say to you!
Are you drunk?
Who said anything about being drunk? I'm not drunk, you know.
Lawyer Kwon. Jeong. Rok!
Let's have a serious discussion with clear minds.
Did you just push me?
Kwon Jeong Rok!
- What's up with you?
- I start working tomorrow.
- So?
- I came here in a hurry, so I haven't found a house yet.
- And so?
- Let me use a favor.
Did you have a team dinner? It's late. Let's go inside.
Kim Se Won.
Huh?
I'm saying this because it's cold. I've been waiting here for two hours.
Take me with you. Okay?
Let's go.
Ah, it's so warm. How nice.
I heard you got a new secretary. Did you have a welcome party?
- How did you know?
- Joon Gyoo told me.
- He said that someone amazing came.
- Did he say who it was, too?
No.
Why? Is she someone I know?
You don't need to know.
Why? Who is it that you're acting like that?
What about Yeo Reum? Did you meet with her?
For a moment.
She wouldn't even let me really see her.
What were you expecting?
I know, right?
She's gotten skinny.
Is that so?
And she's still pretty.
I think this house is big enough for two residents. Shall we just live here together?
If you're okay with sleeping on the sofa without a blanket, then go ahead.
I can't sleep beside you?
- Will you leave, even if it's just right now?
- No, I'm going to stay.
You have beer in the fridge, don't you? Of course you do.
I'm so embarrassed. How embarrassing!
- How embarrassing!
- Yoon Seo. I understand, so calm down.
And what's with "embarrassing" ( slang )? An actress cannot use such a word!
Why? In a situation like this, that word fits perfectly!
I almost died of embarrassment earlier, Oppa!
That's right. You're right.
Kwon Jeong Rok, that horrible jerk.
How can he push me like that?
From what I heard, he didn't push you.
Of course, if that jerk would have just caught you then,
- you wouldn't have fallen like that on the floor.
- Right.
That jerk. Does it cost a million one, or ten million won to catch you? This cheap lawyer jerk.
Exactly!
I cannot let this go. I'm going to get revenge on that man.
What do you mean revenge?
I will do the revenge! What do you want me to do? Should I break him into pieces?
No! I will do it myself.
You are going to break him into pieces yourself?
No!
I'm going to become a perfect secretary.
I will make him a man who cannot do anything without me.
When I suddenly quit in three months,
I will make him feel my absence and I will make him cry a river!
That sounds like revenge on your ex.
I will crush Kwon Jeong Rok.
I will go to hell after getting back at Kwon Jeong Rok!
There must be no one if I go now.
Of course. Work hour begins at 9. It's only 8 now.
If you bump into your co-workers, it will be a bit embarrassing.
So hurry up and go. Stay in your office.
Right. I was going to go crazy over my work from today anyway.
I will stay in my office all day and totally focus on my work.
Focus! That sounds good. Right!
My Yoon Seo, let's go wild today!
Ready?
She shouldn't go too wild.
Why are you...
This fell down.
You're okay, right?
Of course I am.,
Yoon Seo.
- Good morning.
Good morning, everyone.
Oh, right. Are you okay?
You should have gotten some bruises, right?
Oh, no. I'm fine.
What are you talking about?
Yoon Seo fell really hard on the ground yesterday.
Fell hard?
Okay, listen. Lawyer Kwon came to the team dinner a bit late yesterday.
I guess Yoon Seo wanted to talk to him. She was dashing towards him and her heel slipped!
So, she lost her balance, but
Lawyer Kwon didn't catch her. He dodged her so she fell.
Oh my goodness.
- Lawyer Kwon dodged it?
- Yes.
He was completely wrong, wasn't he?
So Yoon Seo tried not to fall. She held onto a trash can and kept running to the end.
- In the end, she fell.
- Wait, I'm a bit confused.
What do you mean she ran pushing a trash can?
Well, that is...
So, like this.
Stop.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I just wanted to help her with understanding the situation.
Never mind.
I'm good.
Well, then.
Oh, gosh. It's so embarrassing.
I mean, why did everyone come so early today?
Ah, sheesh.
Lawyer Kwon!
Hi.
You were seriously too much.
You were too wrong.
Why did you do that yesterday?
- I did something?
- You really don't know?
You should've caught Yoon Seo a bit.
How could you dodge it like this?
I didn't move my leg that much. Just a little like this.
I saw you moving your leg like this.
It's in human nature to catch when a person falls. Look.
It should be your instinct to hold the bag.. when it falls. You should've caught it. Why don't you?
You are really something.
Anyway, I'm relieved that it was just us that witnessed it. What would've happened if there were others?
People could've uploaded pictures of her all over the internet saying "Oh Yoon Seo's Embarrassing Moments" and all.
Anyway, I wonder if she's doing okay, mentally.
She got seriously embarrassed and humiliated in front of all those people.
What if she says that she isn't going to work starting tomorrow?
Is that an option?
What is that expression? Are you looking forward to it?
If Yoon Seo quits, don't ever come to work, Lawyer Kwon.
- Are you serious?
- Of course, I'm joking.
Please treat her nicely.
Treat her nicely, nicely, nicely.
Treat her well, please. Okay?
Anyway, think of my cousin. Please treat her well.
I've never seen what he looks like.
He's cute.
- Good morning.
Hello.
I didn't know Lawyer was such a merciless person. I'm really disappointed.
I heard it too. I think you went a little too far yesterday.
Not a little. It was much worse.
Yoon Seo seemed she wasn't in a good mood. What are you going to do?
Right. She got a full load of embarrassment on her welcome party, not a welcoming bouquet. How could she be in a good mood?
Why did you do that?
I'm sorry.
If I made you feel bad, I want to formally apologize.
Good morning, Lawyer Kwon.
Well, good morning.
Would you like a cup of morning coffee?
No, thanks.
If you need anything, please tell me.
I've made up my mind
to be a perfect secretary from today.
Rather than that, about yesterday...
What is it? Is he going to apologize? I will gladly accept it then.
You drank too much, Ms. Oh Jin Sim.
It was hard to see.
- Excuse me?
- I think you should control how much you drink from now on.
What was that—
Instead of advice,
you should give me your apology.
My apology?
Yesterday... Because of you, Mr. Lawyer,
I fell, you know.
Frankly speaking, you fell yourself. Not because of me.
So... Are you saying you are not responsible?
I feel morally responsible.
Morally?
Involuntary criminal battery!
You stepped aside knowing that
I might get hurt if you didn't catch me.
You neglected a drunk person who couldn't even stand still.
You know some law, I see.
As you know, I went to law school.
That's not what's important here.
If you want to rebut, give it your best shot, Mr. Lawyer.
What do you think about your act of overdrinking to the point that you couldn't control your own body?
- Excuse me?
- You must be aware of your alcohol tolerance. You must have known that you drank too much.
Isn't this also willful negligence?
Well, then.
Well, then? Well, then, then? Then?
Gosh, so annoying!
How does it feel like to be back after such a long time?
Well, I'm just thankful to you for having me. This is why people say having good personal connections is important.
You must have gone through the documents, right? I'm sorry for bombarding you with so much work already.
That's what you brought me here for, no?
CEO Jeong Ji Won ... He's the one who was recently accused of gambling abroad, right?
Right. Prosecutor Park is in charge of that one. You dig into embezzlement.
You have evidence?
There was an informant. We had some suspicions for a while but couldn't accuse him.
- How come?
- What do you think?
Are you saying I solely take responsibility for this case?
No, I needed someone reckless like you to investigate this case.
Oh, goodness. Since you're speaking so highly of my capabilities,
I will do my best.
It won't be easy doing it alone. I will send someone. Good luck.
Thank you.
Wait. Well, are you Prosecutor Kim Se Won?
Yes, I am Kim Se Won.
Oh, yes. Hello.
I'm the Investigative Director, Kim Hyeong Sik.
I'm Yoo Hyeon Ji. I'm looking forward to working with you.
- I'm looking forward to working with you too.
- I'm Prosecutor Lee Joo Yeong.
I've been working on the case of gambling abroad with Prosecutor Park. I know about Jeong Ji Won well.
Then, we will be rolling quickly. Finish up organizing your stuff first and let's start with a briefing of the case.
Let's meet in three minutes.
In three minutes? We are not instant noodles or something.
I've heard of him through rumors, but still.
Is a meeting an instant curry?
Exactly.
Yes? This is Always Law Firm, the office of Mr. Kwon Jeong Rok.
Why bother picking up?
Yes, please wait a moment.
What are you doing? I transferred the call to your extension.
It's a client named Kim Myeong Hwan.
Alright.
Yes, this is Kwon Jeong Rok speaking.
Yes, I'm well aware of that.
Let's meet in an hour then.
Okay.
I'm going to meet my client.
Yes, I understand.
Right. I don't think I can have lunch with you today.
Alright, don't worry. About my lunch,
I will take care of it myself.
Okay, then. Sounds good.
Ah, what should I do about lunch?
Pho?
Okay, I will bring it to you.
Why pho?
Yoon Seo says she doesn't have anyone to have lunch with. She wants me to deliver it for her.
Is that right? Go ahead. It's not like she's asking you to buy a pho restaurant.
Go ahead.
Hey, by the way. Doesn't Yoon Seo look so pretty when she eats?
Of course, she eats well.
Right, right. She looks so pretty, right? I fell for that. I cast her from off the street, right there, right then.
Is that so?
She was  really  pretty.
14 years ago
I don't think I'm suited for this managing job.
Should I just get a loan and open a bar or something?
Four boongeobbang, please.   ( Fish shaped bread )
- Okay.
- Alright, I know.
Let's grab soju someday. It's on you.
Okay.
Oh, hey, hey! You are hiding boongeobbang, aren't you?
- No, I'm not.
- What do you mean you're not? Let's share!
Let me see!
Here they are! Four of them!
♬ Ghada ♬
-  Here they are!
- Here they are.
That one commercial gave her a big name.
Thanks to her, I have come to this. Time flies, you know.
I... I will see my Yoon Seo rising again.
- I suddenly got teary-eyed for no reason.
- Could it be male menopause?
- I heard that controlling your emotions becomes difficult with male menopause.
- Oh, really? Shut up.
Oh, Manager Yoo. What's up?
Is that so? Got it, don't worry.
Alright.
Min Ji is going on a business trip out of town. You should go with her. Manager Yoo is sick.
- Mr. CEO, what about our Yoon Seo's transportation?
- Tell her to take a taxi.
We are buying her pho. That's good, right? Min Ji is on the rise. We need to support her.
You are a manager, so how could you not know that?
What? Are you irritated?
It's still hot, isn't it? The noodles are not soggy, right?
This Oppa did everything to make sure I deliver the most delicious noodles in a perfect state.
You are everything to me, Oppa. Now, I can breathe a bit.
My hard work pays off. It was worth it.
By the way, why don't you eat with your co-workers?
After what happened last night, how could I eat with them? I'm too embarrassed.
Right. Did that rude lawyer apologize?
Apologize, my butt. He said he did nothing wrong worth apologizing for.
Wow, unbelievable, that rude jerk. I won't let this go.
That car! That's him, that's him.
- What? What do you mean?
- That rude lawyer.
What? That jerk—
Hold on.
He's really good-looking.
What do you mean he's good-looking? Take a good look!
I'm taking a good look, but he's still handsome.
Oh, now I'm looking at him carefully. He kind of looks mean.
Why did you hide by the way?
Why do you think? I've set the concept of being a law firm employee so I can work hard.
What am I supposed to do if I get caught being with my manager?
It's not so elegant to eat pho in a car after all.
I should hurry and get back. A perfect secretary never leaves her place.
That guy. He was really good-looking though.
This lunch box is good. We should get deliveries from here often.
It's good.
Right, why isn't Yoon Seo having lunch with us?
It's not that she's not having lunch with us, but it seems like she's not eating at all.
I think she feels too embarrassed to have fallen in front of all of us.
I mean she was drunk but I think she said she can't eat by herself or something.
- Who would she be eating with today?
- Would she have Job's tears tea again?
I saw her drinking Job's tears tea by herself whenever Lawyer Kwon was not present.
You are back.
Yes.
Then, why are you standing here?
Do you need anything?
- Let's go have lunch.
- Pardon?
Since you drank a lot yesterday, how about pho?
Pho?
I think I'm good.
Sorry? How come?
Well.
- I... I'm on a diet.
- Diet?
Yes, well. I thought I should go on a diet.
Okay. Well, then.
What lunch, out of nowhere? He should've told me earlier.
♬ I've chosen to be faithful. I've chosen to obey you. ♬
What was that? Why did she do that?
Hi, you are here again.
Hello.
You want your sandwich on a honey oat roll with honey mustard, right?
- Yes, Honey.
- Sorry?
Yes, yes. You're right.
How do you remember that?
How do I not? You are a special customer.
A special... customer.
Excuse me, Ma'am.
You look like my maternal grandmother.
Your grandmother?
I'm asking this because you feel like family. Can I call you "auntie" from now on?
Yes.
Lawyer Dan. You saw me but why didn't you say hi?
Why are you just leaving?
Please pretend  that you didn't see what happened back there.
Saw what? I was too busy eating. I didn't see anything.
- Really?
- No, not at all.
It was just that part-timer that you liked said you resemble his maternal grandmother.
He asked to call you "auntie." That's all I saw.
You must be happy to have a nephew now.
You should stop there.
Don't get too hurt. You will be able to
fall for someone else soon, anyway.
You are a hopeless romantic, Lawyer Dan.
Mr. Lawyer. How about a cup of coffee?
No, thanks.
It's 3 pm. People feel most tired at this hour.
I will bring you a cup quickly so you can focus on your work even better.
There's no need...
Ah, it's so embarrassing. Out of all people, why Lawyer Choi?
Why feel bothered? It's not something new anyway.
What did you say?
If I were a bit prettier... If I were skinny, pure, and beautiful like Ms. Oh Yoon Seo, I wouldn't have experienced this.
I guess she's never had such humiliating moments, right?
Of course not. Our lawyers said the same.
There are many male celebrities that said Oh Yoon Seo is their ideal type of woman. She was really popular, you know.
That's why she had that scandal with that large conglomerate's grandson, right?
- What do you think really happened?
- That drug scandal?
- There were negative results and she was acquitted.
- No, not that.
I'm curious what kind of relationship she had with that third generation chaebol.   (Chaebol - family thatowns a conglomerate.)
It must be a fact that she was there.
- Right. If she had nothing to do with him, she wouldn't have been there in the first place.
- I read some gossip—
Oh, you were all here.
You were having a tea time.
I'm going to bring Lawyer Kwon a cup of coffee.
- Sure.
- Oh!
- You are wearing makeup today, right?
- I always do.
Really?
It's extra nice today.
Yes.
Here.
Please have some. It smells nice.
Thank you.
What's wrong? Did something happen?
Nothing happened.
Why? Did the lawyer bully you again?
I'll tell the president to change lawyers.
Forget it. I told you I'm going to become a perfect secretary
to take my revenge on that person.
I had a lot of revenge today. I did extension connections, made copies,
and even gave him his coffee perfectly.
I'm proud of you, Yoon Seo.
Yoon Seo, you are going to need to go to and leave work tomorrow by yourself.
I can't pick you up.
Why?
I have military reserves training.
Then, what should I do?
Take the taxi, just for tomorrow.
I don't like taxis. It's also bothersome to find them.
I was going to stick a road manager with you,
but of all times, there's no one with an empty schedule tomorrow.
I get it. I'll figure it out tomorrow, so Oppa,
you do well on your training.
Yes.
- But, Oppa.
- Hm?
- Did you serve in the military?
- Of course, I did.
What do you take me for?
I went to a really tough place!
I've been too gentle on you, haven't I?
I'll speed up a little now.
- You came earlier than I thought. Did you eat dinner?
- Not yet.
I thought so. That's why I prepared these.
I'm a perfect roommate, aren't I? Doesn't it make you want to keep living with me?
If possible, find a house quickly.
You're so inflexible, you rascal.
Yeo Reum might call soon since she drank alcohol.
She received some stress because of me.
- So, can you—
- It's a problem between you two, so you two figure it out.
Why? Yeo Reum likes you.
She really trusts you and depends on you.
Then, she would've chosen me from the beginning.
- She would have, right?
- Don't show off, I don't want to see it.
You're so inflexible. Change your personality.
I can live with you because I am me. But, others won't be able to handle you.
That new secretary might also have a really hard time adjusting to you.
Forget it.
Application for Temporary Injunction to Prohibit Transfer of Real Property
I don't see the important documents that I need to review right now.
I told you to just sit around if you have nothing else to do. Don't you remember?
I am also trying to work hard in my own way. Do you have to get so angry?
I don't know how to do much.
However, if you teach me, I'll work hard to do well.
- I've read some gossip.
- Gossip?
Were you all here?
Drink it. The scent is nice.
Thank you.
Well.
This kind of feel should be okay.
If I don't get nervous,
I can arrive safely. Ready...
Action!
Ah, I get it.
Will you not drive properly!
I also want to do it properly.
Lower your window. Lower your window!
The law firm is right in front of me, why can't I go?
Will you not lower it? You won't lower it? Alright, you're dead!
Whoa, oh my gosh!
What the heck? Why doesn't he move?
Let's go, let's go.
What should I do? Did I cause an accident?
Actress Oh Yoon Seo got into trouble again.
Two years ago, due to her drugs scandal, actress Oh Yoon Seo who announced a temporary retirement,
this time, she is put under the spotlight again for her reckless driving.
Under the spotlight.
What should I do?
Get out. Hey, get out.
Get out, Ahjumma! First thing in the morning, this is so annoying.
She ran into it. If you ran into someone else's car, you should get out!
Madam Kim! Let me see your face!
Take off your sunglasses! Lower your window and get out! Come out here!
Why isn't he picking up?
If you ran into my car, you should get out and check. Should I break your car?
Look! Look at here! Here! Here! I'm breaking it!
Please stop it.
- Who are you?
- You can talk with me from now on.
I'm her lawyer.
Law-Lawyer?
If you are a lawyer, can you  run into someone's car like that?
We can't pretend nothing happened.
However, we can't pretend that the thing you did also never happened.
- What did I do?
- What you did can be considered as reckless driving and  road rage.
According to  Article 151 Clause 2 of the Road Traffic Act, you could end up with
up to  a year imprisonment or receive up to a 5 million won fine.
No, but right now, this woman,
she ran into the back of my car!
Yes.
For further confirmation, we can check the black box.
The fact that you changed the lane without signaling
has also been recorded.
Now that I look at it, it didn't leave a scratch.
Well, while you are driving, these things and those things happen.
We shouldn't raise our voices and go overboard with something like this.
I will let it go for a settlement. Let's do a settlement.
No, let's do it by the law.
Because I like the law.
Why are you looking at me like that?
When was I looking at you?
Then, why are you looking at me like that?
Because I'm wondering if you really don't need to go to the hospital.
I don't need to go.
I'm all right.
By the way, how did you know it was me?
I saw you.
Get out. Hey! Get out.
Get out, Ahjumma! First thing in the morning, this is so annoying.
If you ran into someone else's car, you should get out.
Anyway, for coming out and defending me earlier,
I'm really thankful.
To pay you back, I will work really hard today as well!
Yes. Well, do as you like.
- Good morning, Ms. Oh Yoon Seo.
- Yes. Hello.
Well.
Lawyer Kwon's expression is always so stern.
You are definitely inflexible.
When you see Ms. Yoon Seo in the morning, you should be smiling ear to ear.
You are working so close to her after all. How can he be so cold-hearted?
You would be strangers outside of here, aren't I right?
Yes. Well.
Smile.
A big smile.
It might feel like you are in the middle of Siberia when you work with Lawyer Kwon,
but I will help you a lot, so cheer up, Yoon Seo.
Yes. Well.
And Lawyer Kwon listens to my words well, so
If Lawyer makes it hard for you or bullies you, you can tell me any time.
Do not ever think of quitting.
I don't know. He may be a better person than I thought.
What did you say?
What? It's nothing.
Did I hear her wrong?
- Ms. Oh Jin Sim.
- Yes.
You went to law school, right?
Yes. Only for one semester. I wasn't kicked out.
I left on my own because I had too much on my schedule.
Have you ever looked up judicial precedents?
No.
If you search on the Supreme Court website,
you will be able to find some relevant Supreme Court precedent cases.
You just need to find anything relevant.
What should I look for?
Precedents related to pet dog noises.
Even if it's not about noisy dogs, anything between neighbors.
It could be cases about floor noises. It doesn't matter.
Yes. Since it's my first task, I will do my best.
Okay. Well, then.
There aren't as many judicial precedents as I thought there might be.
Especially, there were even fewer precedents of lawsuits over pet dog noise.
But, I did some research because I remembered hearing something before.
Not in our country, but in the U.S.,
there was an article about a man winning a lawsuit he filed over a noisy puppy next door.
But, do you know the damage award was?
It was five hundred million won.  Amazing, right?
When did you hear about such a case?
We did a mock trial in our first semester in law school.
I remembered some group did a presentation about the case.
It must have been long ago. You still remember that?
I have a good memory.
So, I didn't get compliments on my acting from my directors, but
I got a lot of compliments for memorizing my lines perfectly.
Oh, well. It's nothing to brag about though.
It is.
Excuse me?
Anyway, it was helpful. You can leave now.
Well, then.
♬  One day, that warm smile.  ♬
♬  I think I've changed. I've gotten curious about you.  ♬
♬  I'm so confused.  ♬
Is it because he's an ace in this law firm? He has so  much work.
♬  It feels like a whole new memory now.  ♬
He said he detests people who don't get off work on time.
Should I really go home?
♬  I thought of you.  ♬
♬  I just wanna be a star for you.  ♬
♬  With my heart that I've been hiding  ♬
♬  I will shine on you. I will hold your day  ♬
♬  That's sometimes dark and tiring  ♬
Didn't realize it's this late.
♬  I just wanna be your star with my heart  ♬
♬  With twinkling star light ♬
♬  I will lighten it up for you  ♬
♬  I will fill your dark nights that you thought you were alone  ♬
I didn't fall asleep.
I just went over your schedule for tomorrow in my head.
Why didn't you get off work?
Just in case there was anything else you needed me to do.
- Let's go eat.
- What?
I said, let's go eat.
Why are you like this today?
Why are you treating me so nicely?
When I got in an accident, you readily helped me.
You gave me a hard time, saying that doing nothing is helpful, but you gave me tasks today.
You even gave me compliments. And now, you are asking me to eat together.
You are acting so strange, don't you think?
No way! I'm getting fired, aren't I?
You are nice to me because it's my last day. It's a goodbye meal, isn't it?
It's nothing like that. I'm really asking you to have a meal with me, that's all.
Let's go.
Are you a regular here?
There are no people here. Is it a secret hole-in-the-wall place?
No. Its food isn't that great. It's a bit too chewy.
Then why did we come here?
Didn't you say you are not comfortable going to a busy restaurant?
Then, it's for my sake.
By the way, when are you going to take off those sunglasses?
Right. It's not just that there are no people who would recognize me. There is no one here at all, so I can take them off.
Oh! I did that soju commercial, do you remember?
I'm always the same?
It's because I always keep my original intentions.
So, I like drinks like me.
The same taste, from the beginning to the end.
Like the First Intention!
What the heck? I feel so awkward.
I can drink a lot today, right?
You drink a lot, often.
I drank a lot at my welcome party because I wasn't in a good mood.
Today, I'm going to drink a lot because I'm not in a bad mood.
Hi. It's freezing.
You should replace these posters.
Our company got a new model a while ago.
We don't get many people anyway. Who's going to see them?
That's why I brought new ones. I will put them up for you.
Okay.
I think we took the right seats, right? It would have been awkward if he recognized me.
Good bye!
I think you are much tougher person than I thought, Ms. Oh Jin Sim.
Well, I got stronger while working in this industry.
People always talk about me. They write hateful comments.
There is gossip about things that I didn't do.
I've experienced things like that for over ten years, so I'm used to it now.
It would be a lie if I say I'm totally okay with it, though.
How do you like working at the law firm?
It's been tough but it was okay today.
I had some work to do today.
I got compliments. I got this gobchang ( intenstine ) as a bonus!
Mr. Lawyer. I will see you tomorrow.
Please take care.
Ms. Oh Jin Sim!
I'm Oh Yoon Seo.
Yes?
I have never thought of you as my secretary up to now.
It is true that I considered you an annoying presence since you were leaving soon.
But I've decided to change that thinking from now on.
Pardon?
I want to give you a proper chance to work as my secretary.
Let's start again from the beginning.
For real?
Thank you, Mr. Lawyer!
I will seriously do my best!
I ...
I didn't dodge you this time.
♬   Here. You and me. Right this moment.  ♬
♬  I'm going to keep this somewhere deep in my heart.   ♬
♬  The touch of one hand comfortably over another  ♬
♬  Even today's air. Everything.  ♬
♬  Remember everything. They are so precious.  ♬
♫  So make it count  ♫
♬  Please remember today.  ♬
♬ A light wind and blooming flowers  ♬
♬  one minute one second make it count  ♬
♬  Then  make me everlasting.  ♬
Touch Your Heart
- Something's suspicious.
- I'm just saying she's okay as a secretary.
This is a list of tasks that you will be doing in the future, Ms. Oh Jin Sim.
He said he was going to give me a chance to work properly, but he's sweating me.
What do you think? No one will recognize you, right?
- Oh, you can tell it's me?
- Of course, I can.
The witness is lying right now!
What are you doing right now?
Right! What are you doing?
Hey!
You should watch your words.
What? Yoon Seo is arrested again?
This is my first time seeing you smile that big.
It's not a date.
- Not, my butt.
- We went to study.
♫  So make it count  ♫