Hello?
Mr. Jiao.
Jiao Shiheng.
Looks like this guy's time is up.
Tomorrow night?
Tomorrow night might not work.
I have plans tomorrow night.
What?
Tomorrow night?
I've affected the main plot!
Damn it.
Hello?
Mr. Jiao.
Mengyun will definitely be there tomorrow night.
Why does this voice sound so familiar?
Lu Chengwen.
You're up to your tricks again.
Chengwen.
Are you...
asking me to go on a date with Jiao Shiheng?
Well...
we can watch a movie any day.
He probably has something to discuss with you.
Why don't you see him first?
If you don't go,
I won't be able to explain it.
Chengwen.
Since
you want me to go on a date with him,
then I'll do as you wish.
Hello?
Mr. Jiao.
Didn't you want to treat me to dinner tomorrow?
I accept.
However,
the time needs to be changed to tonight.
Really?
Great, great, great.
I'll arrange it right away.
Tonight?
This is tomorrow's plot!
Stop messing around!
Gu Zhantian won't be able to save you this way.
You'll really be ruined by that beast Jiao Shiheng!
Mengyun.
Um...
Today, you
can't have dinner with him.
You can do it tomorrow.
Because tomorrow...
Anyway,
he's just not a good person.
Chengwen.
You asked me to go on a date with him,
and I agreed.
Now you're saying he's not a good person.
I don't understand what you mean.
Anyway, you can't go today.
Jiao Shiheng will drug you.
You know?
Drug me?
How do you know he'll drug me?
I...
You two conspired together,
right?
So,
you asked me to go on a date with him.
No.
Well...
How could I?
He just screwed over Leng Qingqiu today,
and I beat him up.
How could I conspire with him?
Enough!
You hit him for Leng Qingqiu,
and now
you're giving me to him as compensation,
right?
To think that after seeing your performance at the press conference yesterday,
I actually thought you had changed.
I didn't expect
you're still a scumbag who treats women as playthings.
Chen Mengyun.
You can't go to dinner with him today.
Who are you to me?
What right do you have to control me?
Right now,
I'm going on a date with Jiao Shiheng.
We'll get a room tonight,
and get engaged next week.
Our wedding will even be before yours and Leng Qingqiu's!
No.
Now Xu Xuejiao, Leng Qingqiu, and Jiang Shihan,
the key events of the three female leads,
have all been altered because of me,
leaving Gu Zhantian with no way to intervene.
If Chen Mengyun's side also...
I can't keep ruining the plot.
What?
Keep looking.
Young Master.
Our brothers...
Still haven't found Gu Zhantian.
I have to swallow my pride again.
Piece of shit.
Just to make you worry.
Hello?
What's wrong?
Qingqiu.
Well...
I need to find Gu Zhantian right now.
I just had a fight with Chen Mengyun.
She got mad and went out to find...
that Jiao Shiheng for dinner.
Now I must find Gu Zhantian immediately.
Only Gu Zhantian can find her.
You piece of shit.
Stop bothering me.
Lu Chengwen.
Whatever is going on between you and Chen Mengyun,
I'm really not interested.
Can you stop bothering me?
Nothing happened between us.
The most important thing now is to find Gu Zhantian.
Chen Mengyun went out to eat with Jiao Shiheng.
Jiao Shiheng will very likely drug her.
Only Gu Zhantian can save her.
I can't just watch her get hurt.
I don't care.
Drug her?
I can't find Gu Zhantian.
But...
I can check Jiao Shiheng's itinerary for you.
I'll send you the location right away.
Gangzi.
Go to Haicheng Holiday Hotel.
Call all the brothers.
Copy that.
Let me go!
Mengyun.
You're so beautiful.
Help!
What are you doing?
Lu Chengwen!
Are you crazy?
Drag him out!
This time, beat him hard.
Beat him to death!
Yes, sir!
Chengwen.
Save me, Chengwen.
Are you okay?
I told you not to come.
But you insisted.
Chengwen.
Why are you so hot?
It's okay.
Hang in there.
I'll call Xu Xuejiao to save you.
Let me help you up first.
Let's go.
Don't go.
Hold me tight.
I'm not...
Hey, why should I hold you tight?
I...
Don't move, don't move.
Testing me again.
I'm a man too.
If we keep hugging, you'll be in danger again.
Danger?
What danger?
What?
She can hear my inner thoughts too?
Chengwen.
Help!
Mengyun!
Lu Chengwen!
What's going on?
Xu Xuejiao!
You're just in time.
Hurry and save her!
She was drugged by Jiao Shiheng.
Oh.
Chengwen...
Oh my god.
Lu Chengwen!
What did you do to Ms. Mengyun?
It wasn't me!
Darn it, darn it.
So if Jiao Shiheng touches Chen Mengyun,
Gu Zhantian will show up!
I shouldn't have interfered.
Can someone explain this for me?
How about you turn yourself in?
I'll hold them off.
Right!
I'll turn myself in.
I'll take Jiao Shiheng and turn myself in.
It's hard being a good guy.
I got myself involved again.
Lu Chengwen.
We've finished our investigation.
You can leave now.
You can go.
Let's go.
Mr. Lu,
are you okay?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Just a trip back home.
What could happen?
No wonder
you turned yourself in so smoothly.
Chengwen,
I knew you'd come to save me.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have thrown a tantrum at you.
It's okay,
Mengyun.
It's all in the past.
Darn it.
I just took out
Gu Zhantian's entire team.
Since you're fine,
I'll head back first.
Qingqiu,
thanks for earlier.
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn't have arrived in time.
I owe you one.
And you said there was nothing between you and Chen Mengyun.
Fine.
Then I'll have you return the favor right now.
I want you to get engaged to me next month.
No way!
Good heavens!
Do villains have love triangles too?
Brother Chengwen chased you for three years,
and you played the innocent girl for three whole years.
Now you're throwing yourself at him.
How hilarious.
Brother Chengwen,
since you don't want to get engaged to her,
why not get engaged to me?
Why are you joining in?
Chengwen,
I knew you cared about me.
No,
Mengyun,
don't be like this.
Mr. Lu,
didn't you promise
to take me home
to be your wife?
Shihan,
why are you also...
Xu Xuejiao,
you couldn't even be bothered
to say a word to Lu Chengwen before.
Why are you fighting with me now?
If I want to fight for him,
I will fight for him.
I'll fight for him all I want.
Others can only watch.
Sister Mengyun,
I'm not talking about you.
You don't have to give yourself to Brother Chengwen
just because he saved you.
You know,
gratitude and affection are two different things.
Who says I have no feelings for Brother Chengwen?
I admire his talent,
and I like his kindness even more.
Marrying him
and raising a family together
is exactly what I want.
Chengwen,
isn't that what you want too?
I...
No, you...
What are you all doing?
Look at where we are!
And you're all getting jealous over me here?
Aren't you ashamed?
Yeah,
what's wrong with me?
But my heart really hurts.
The Lu Chengwen
who used to obey my every command
is really gone.
Why did I become unimportant to him
overnight?
Qingqiu,
why don't you all go home first?
I'll visit your place another day,
and we can properly
discuss this.
I believe there's
more than one way to solve this.
Right?
Okay.
I'll wait for your call.
Lu Chengwen,
you're not going to be her simp, are you?
Chengwen,
you're not going to get engaged to her,
right?
Xuejiao, Mengyun,
why don't you two head back first?
We'll talk another day.
Shihan,
let's go.