So it's Xu Xuejiao.
She seems to be
Haicheng's Genius Female Doctor, right?
This figure...
is really hot.
Where are you looking?
Ah!
I...
Hey!
Ah!
Why is her temper even hotter than her figure?
Being so violent,
does it do justice to her looks?
What did you say?
I didn't say anything.
His lips really didn't move just now.
Could it be that I heard his inner thoughts?
She should also be one of Gu Zhantian's spare tires.
I'd better make our relationship
a bit more strained first,
so we interact less in the future.
Oh.
As expected,
I can do mind-reading by looking into his eyes.
How fun.
Xuejiao,
I'm done saying hello.
I'll be leaving now.
Don't be in such a hurry to leave,
Young Master Lu.
In the past,
didn't you love pestering me the most,
asking all sorts of questions,
and even wanting to see me in a nurse's uniform?
What's wrong?
Have you changed your ways?
Mmm.
This figure...
This voice...
No way.
I must hold on.
I...
was just blind before.
I have no interest in you now.
Oh?
No interest?
Then just now,
whose eyes
almost fell into my cleavage?
Men who lie
have to swallow silver needles.
No.
If she keeps pestering me, there's going to be trouble.
Calm down.
Fight back.
Sis Xuejiao,
you care so much about where I look,
could it be that you're enjoying it?
Ah!
He...
How dare he!
Unfortunately,
I'm busy today.
As for your figure...
I've seen enough of it,
and it's just so-so.
Lu Chengwen!
You jerk!
Let go of me!
Sis Xuejiao,
playing with fire comes with consequences.
You're still too green.
Go on.
Go to Old Master Chen
and treat his illness.
Little girl.
Ah!
He actually called me a little girl!
And he dared to push me!
Go to hell!
However...
he used to be so disgusting and creepy.
Why is he acting so manly today?
He made my heart beat so fast.
That jerk!
You...
Just you wait!
That was a close call.
This girl is on another level.
I couldn't have handled her without playing hardball.
Good thing I've read a lot of power fantasy novels.
It actually worked.
But...
Where did this quack doctor come from?
Daring to call himself a Miracle Doctor?
You can't discuss ice with a summer insect.
What's all this about ice?
I think you're the one who's seriously sick.
Get lost!
Isn't that Gu Zhantian's voice?
I can't let him see me.
I better run.
Wait.
That's not right.
I've seen this kind of plot before!
It must be that Xu Xuejiao's medical skills aren't
proficient enough,
and she almost kills Old Master Chen.
Then Gu Zhantian steps in to help,
and wins her over.
Stop loitering around here.
Hurry up and leave.
If I run away now,
then Old Master Chen is definitely dead!
What should I do?
As long as you nod,
I can make this person
disappear forever.
Oh, well.
It's a human life, after all.
Besides,
I'll do Gu Zhantian a favor.
It might ease his hatred for me a bit.
If you don't leave, I'll call the police!
Butler!
Lu Chengwen.
Why is it you again?
How dare you call Young Master Lu by his name!
Get lost!
The butler is courting death!
Don't drag me down with you!
Don't be rude.
This is my friend.
Ah.
My apologies.
Mr. Gu.
Young Master Lu.
But today, neither of you
can see Old Master Chen.
This idiot.
If we don't see him today,
we'll never have to see him again.
Ah.
Well,
I just thought about it,
and I feel like I did something wrong.
I originally planned
to return these billions
to Old Master Chen.
But with your attitude,
I won't return it.
To get me through the door,
he's willing to spend so much money.
Young Master Lu,
what you're saying...
How am I supposed to respond?
Ah.
Hard to respond, right?
That's fine.
I'll go back and have someone tell Old Master Chen
that I wanted to return billions to him,
but you kicked me out.
Hey!
No, no, no, no, no!
Well,
you two
should just go in.
Just pretend I don't exist.
I don't exist.
Haha.
Let's go in.
Gu Zhantian.
Xuejiao.
Long time no see.
Hmm.
What's going on?
I feel like I'm sensing some
weird character dynamics.
Our engagement was arranged by our ancestors.
It wasn't my intention.
I hope you'll stop pestering me.
Okay.
Here comes the familiar trope.
I'm only here for the treatment today.
Hah.
I heard you used to be a security guard.
Now even gatekeepers
can treat illnesses?
Gu Zhantian,
I'm doing the treatment right now.
It's not your place to interfere.
Keep arguing.
This little girl is just too noisy.
Let's see you get slapped in the face later.
Lu Chengwen,
what are you doing here?
Ah.
I, uh...
Brother Zhantian and I are
friends.
I
came with him.
You guys continue.
Th-th-this...
What?
Ah!
This is the effect of King Wen's Medical Tome!
The acupoints are completely visible!
So amazing!
Lu Chengwen
has actually read
King Wen's Medical Tome!
That mass of dark qi near the heart meridian
must be the root of the illness.
This little witch
really did needle the wrong spot.
Gu Zhantian,
I'm counting on you.
Dark qi?
The root is in the heart meridian?
Could it be...
he possesses King Wen's Vision?
That was close.
I almost needled the wrong spot
and killed Grandpa Chen.
Xuejiao,
let me do it.
Don't delay the treatment.
Quiet!
You have no right to speak here.
Your medical skills are not yet refined.
Don't be impulsive.
*Cough, cough, cough*
She actually got it right.
Hmph.
Xuejiao,
you adapted to the situation
and changed the needle path in time.
Although
your technique was a bit rough,
and the force
and control were lacking,
failing to use one needle
to eradicate the root of the illness,
but
it still managed to avoid
the worst outcome.
No,
bro,
if you can't speak nicely, then shut up.
Who wants to hear that?
Rough technique?
Lacking control?
Are your eyes on top of your head?
Just now,
if it weren't for me...
I...
If I hadn't heard a certain jerk's inner voice,
Grandpa Chen would be gone.
Besides standing here
making snide remarks,
what else can you do?
Let me tell you,
our engagement,
from this moment on,
is completely,
forever,
and entirely void!
Disappear from my sight immediately!
Darn it.
Will I get caught in the crossfire later?
I better slip away.
Hey,
um,
Brother Zhantian,
I
just remembered
I have something to do.
I'll get going.
You guys
carry on.
Lu Chengwen,
you stay.