=The Best Man=
=Episode 24=
(I don't believe Chen Zhuo is
marrying Yin Muzi.)
(He must have his reasons.)
Zhuo.
Grandma's mourning period
isn't over yet.
Don't you think this is not appropriate?
Why did you ask me
to pretend to be Chen Zhuo
and date you?
Yue.
You pretended to be in a coma for long.
Haven't you missed me?
Do you think I will buy into this?
Chen Zhuo and Xu Meiying are
so lovey-dovey.
The sight of it makes me want to
destroy Xu Meiying.
As expected of the patriarch's wife.
You and I are really
a match made in heaven.
Well, it's also time for me
to settle the score with Chen Zhuo.
From today onward,
Chen Zhuo, the Chen Family's
11th generation grandson,
official takes over
as patriarch of the Chen Family.
Please accept the blade.
Chen Yue!
Chen Zhuo!
Zhuo!
Put your hand down.
Show me some respect.
Okay!
Chen Zhuo.
If you dare take over as the patriarch,
both of them
will meet their demise.
Chen Yue...
Let them go
and you can be the patriarch.
How ridiculous of you.
Do you think all I want is
to be the patriarch?
I'm also after
those hateful eyes of yours.
How about this?
An eye for a lady.
Who do you go with?
Both.
No, Chen Zhuo!
- Zhuo!
- Why not?
Well, stop screaming already!
Gosh, I really envy you.
Why are these women
doing things for you?
Huh?
Also,
since young,
you've had everything you wanted
without working hard.
You are a mere loser
through and through.
You are truly pathetic.
Pathetic, my foot!
Just look at me.
Yes.
I've gotten everything I wanted.
And you?
You can't even protect your sweetheart.
What are you waiting for?
You have three seconds.
Three.
Two.
One!
Stop it!
No...
Zhuo!
How dare you betray me?
Meiying.
Chen Yue.
Ever since I was violated by you
on my 18th birthday,
I've meant to take revenge on you.
Did you know?
I felt utterly disgusted
by all the physical contact we had
after that!
I know Chen Yue has come around.
We can join hands.
Why should I work with you?
I looked into what happened then.
I found out he forced himself upon you.
What's your plan?
Chen Yue is a sinister and cunning man.
To protect Meiying,
I will pretend to break up with her.
You will then lure Chen Yue out.
On the day of me taking over
as patriarch we will see how it goes.
I've claimed
all of your criminal evidence
and called the police.
You will be locked up in jail forever!
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
I know
you were trying to protect me.
Everything is okay now.
It's all over now.
(The eldest son of Chen Family in Panlong City
is brought for justice and is jailed)
(for kidnapping and murdering)
(after getting out of hospital.)
(The hard work of Chen Zhuo,
the new patriarch of Chen Family,)
(has enabled the family's business
achieve greater success)
(within three mere months.)
Say 'cheese'!
Congratulations, Ms. Xu,
on the successful listing
of Wanlong Hotel Group!
Congratulations, Ms. Xu!
♪My right eye twitched with luck♪
♪Just like your sudden silence♪
♪You kindly urged me to forget you♪
♪Told me not to be stubborn,
how thoughtful of you♪
♪As if I've always been unworthy♪
Ms. Xu.
Can I be your security guard forever?
♪How fragile my words sound
when I say I don't love you♪
♪I let you go and set you free,
but how can I free myself?♪
♪I can waste years
mourning this broken love♪
♪I can close my eyes
and burn alone in solitude♪
Congratulations!
♪Even a faint love can still feel grand♪
♪I can endure and accept
your love for her♪
♪I can spend a lifetime
slowly letting grief fade♪
♪I can survive lonely nights
choking back silent tears♪
♪Tears of maturity
surrender to loneliness♪
♪Blurring the memories of the past♪
♪As if I've always been unworthy♪
♪It doesn't matter
if you forget me someday♪
♪How fragile my words sound
when I say I don't love you♪
♪I let you go and set you free,
but how can I free myself?♪
♪I can waste years
mourning this broken love♪
♪I can close my eyes
and burn alone in solitude♪
♪I can find solace knowing
someone else loses sleep at night♪
♪Even a faint love can still feel grand♪
♪I can endure and accept
your love for her♪
♪I can spend a lifetime
slowly letting grief fade♪
♪I can survive lonely nights
choking back silent tears♪
♪Tears of maturity
surrender to loneliness♪
♪Blurring the memories of the past♪