=The Best Man=
=Episode 17=
What are you doing?
I wanted to use the iPad,
but I forgot the password.
I know you remember it,
so I thought I'd give it a try.
I see.
You don't need
to spend time trying it.
You could've just woken me up.
There's no need to be so sneaky.
I see.
I didn't want to disturb you.
Here you go.
Thank you.
I guess
you missed me a lot.
That's why you came up
with such a lame excuse to see me.
I'm not.
I'm just in a hurry.
In a hurry?
There's no rush.
After all, you'll be mine
sooner or later.
I won't disturb you anymore.
I'll go use the iPad
to search for something.
(She wants to use the fingerprint
verification to confirm my identity.)
(How could I not be prepared for this?)
Sir, here's your card.
The room number is 888.
Thank you.
Is he Chen Zhuo's twin brother?
He's so handsome.
Yeah,
they have the same face,
but the aura is completely different.
Why is he staying at our hotel?
(Is he Chen Yue)
(or Chen Zhuo?)
Mr. Yue.
I'm sorry.
I didn't expect Chen Zhuo
to be out of our control
and escape from us.
Find out Chen Zhuo as soon as possible
and keep him away from Xu Meiying.
Mr. Yue,
he now firmly believes
that he's Chen Yue,
and
he doesn't play by the rules.
It'll be very tough for us...
I don't want to hear your excuses.
Go and find him now.
Go now!
Sometimes, destruction
is also a form of art, isn't it?
It seems...
Someone is about
to disappear from this world.
In this world,
the genuine beauty is unique.
If you wanted to be the only one,
you'd have acted long ago.
Chen Yue,
you're not as bad as you think you are.
That was in the past.
Now that we've switched identities.
It's either me or him who exists.
Do you want to pretend to be Chen Zhuo
for the rest of your life?
Don't you find it interesting?
Honestly,
every day now
is more thrilling
than any day in the past 20 years.
How amazing!
Only a lunatic like you can match me.
Are you following me?
Have you changed your mind?
Or did you realize
I'm a better fit for you?
Yes,
no matter who you are,
I like any.
(If you have the birthmark
on your abdomen,)
(then it will prove
you're the real Chen Zhuo.)
Enough.
I'm not interested in women
who throw themselves at me.
How would you know you're not interested
if you don't give it a try?
You're Chen Zhuo's woman.
That's the only reason
I look at you differently.
I didn't expect it'd be
this easy to obtain you.
How boring!
Stop pretending.
I know
you're Chen Zhuo.
Meiying,
you're doing my laundry this late?
Your clothes were dirty,
so I washed them.
No need.
Washing them is tiring.
I'll do it myself.
No worries.
I...
What's this?
This?
A game card.
Give it to me.
Why are you so nervous about a card?
I told you,
it's just a game card.
Give it to me.
Chen Zhuo,
what's wrong with you?
Didn't you hear me asking you
to give the game card back to me?
Why are you getting so mad?
Do I look like Chen Zhuo to you?
I'm Chen Yue.
I'm here.
Let's talk somewhere else.
Alright.
Look.
I think
this is where
all his criminal evidence is stored.
You've committed a crime.
Come with me and turn yourself in.
What's wrong with me?
Why do you look down on me too?
Come with me and turn yourself in.
I won't go.
I won't!
Ahh!
Chen Yue didn't kill your mom.
But if he didn't commit a crime,
why does my memory remind me
he tried to kill me to silence me?
What is he trying to cover up?
Look,
there's a blood stain over there.
♪My right eye twitched with luck♪
♪Just like your sudden silence♪
♪You kindly urged me to forget you♪
♪Told me not to be stubborn,
how thoughtful of you♪
♪As if I've always been unworthy♪
♪It doesn't matter
if you forget me someday♪
♪How fragile my words sound
when I say I don't love you♪
♪I let you go and set you free,
but how can I free myself?♪
♪I can waste years
mourning this broken love♪
♪I can close my eyes
and burn alone in solitude♪
♪I can find solace♪
♪Knowing someone else
loses sleep at night♪
♪Even a faint love can still feel grand♪
♪I can endure and accept
your love for her♪
♪I can spend a lifetime
slowly letting grief fade♪
♪I can survive lonely nights
choking back silent tears♪
♪Tears of maturity
surrender to loneliness♪
♪Blurring the memories of the past♪