=The Best Man=
=Episode 5=
Chairman,
everyone is here.
Has he arrived?
Yes, he has.
Young Lady has already met him.
- Then let's begin.
- Yes, sir.
Welcome, everyone,
to the Jiangnan Group Charity Gala.
We will now begin
the charity auction segment.
All the auction items have been
provided by the Jiangnan Group.
All proceeds from the auction
will be donated
to Jiangnan City's charitable causes.
Please
use your invitation cards
to participate in the bidding.
This diamond necklace
has a starting bid of 800,000.
Chen Zhuo,
I'll bid for this necklace
and give it to Ying.
Take a good look around.
This high-class gala isn't a place
for a lowly security guard like you.
Lin Jiaqi,
this is about charity,
not showing off.
Even if you bid on it,
I wouldn't accept it.
Ying,
what's so good
about a poor guy like him?
I bet he's never even seen
an auction like this before.
Let's open his eyes, then, Madam.
One million!
Impressive.
Two million.
Chen Zhuo,
do you even have that kind of money?
Mind your own business.
2.2 million.
2.4 million.
Can you afford this?
Stop messing around.
If you can't pay, don't bid.
You...
2.5 million!
2.5 million, going once.
Spending 2.5 million on a necklace?
2.5 million, going twice.
This guy really is something else.
2.5 million, going thrice.
Sold!
Congratulations, Mr. Lin.
Congratulations.
It suits you.
You...
Let's see what you'll bid
for Ying tonight.
This is the final auction item
for the night.
Only SVIP guests are eligible to bid.
The starting bid is 40 million.
Who's the SVIP here?
A starting bid this high
and only for the SVIP.
We're all just VIPs.
Yes, that's right.
So, who's the SVIP?
50 million.
(VIP)
That's crazy!
This must be a joke!
50 million!
Do you even have that kind of money?
Hahaha!
50 million.
Do you even know how much that is?
Can you afford it?
Besides,
this looks fake.
(VIP)
It's even handwritten!
Hahaha!
Handwritten!
That handwritten card is valid.
=The Best Man=
That's
Jiangnan Group's Chairman, Huang Qinian!
Chairman Huang has always
kept a low profile
and stayed behind the scenes.
Why did he show up tonight?
That handwritten card is valid.
Tonight, the items
won by the SVIP guest
will be paid for
by the Jiangnan Group.
Wow!
Chairman Huang is so generous!
Chairman.
Grandpa.
You're looking sharp tonight.
I see you hold
the Jiangnan Group in high regard.
Dressing well doesn't matter.
It won't stop others
from looking down on me.
Oh?
Is there anyone who would look down
on the future heir
of Jiangnan Group?
The heir of Jiangnan Group?
How could it be him?
Tell me.
How did you figure out my identity?
It started when the bracelet
you gave me
caught Mr. Zhang's attention.
Mr. Chen, is this...
(VIP)
And he had someone deliver
the invitation to Xu Meiying's place
instead of mine.
Most importantly,
the founder of Jiangnan Group
also has the surname Huang.
You know me well.
As expected
of the successor
I personally selected.
Don't give me that.
You're just using me as a shield
to protect your granddaughter,
Huang Yuhuan.
Talking to smart people
is always a pleasure.
Chen Zhuo.
No.
I should say,
the second son of the Chen Family
in Panlong City,
who has never been publicly revealed,
Chen Zhuo.
What else have you found out?
Your mother fell to her death
in Jiangnan City a year ago.
The Chen Family sent people
to investigate,
but it ended without resolution.
The police concluded it was an accident.
Three months ago, you started working
as a security guard at Wanlong Hotel.
I suspect
my mother's death wasn't an accident.
On the day of the incident,
there was another man present.
Many years ago,
your mother helped Jiangnan Group
survive its toughest crisis.
I've been investigating
her death for the past year.
There should be results soon.
Thank you, Huang.
Chen Zhuo,
after all this is over,
can you help me support Jiangnan Group?
You know my granddaughter.
She's not cut out for business.
I'm sorry.
I can't take over
Jiangnan Group.
Why not?
So many are eager
to align themselves with Jiangnan Group.
Why don't you want it?
Well?
The reason?
The reason is...
I simply don't need it.
But thanks for the offer.
Grandpa,
I like the match you arranged for me
this time.
Too bad, though.
He's already taken.
That's all right.
I can take him down.
Chen Zhuo, let's talk.
About what?
About Huang Yuhuan?
Are you jealous?
Why would I be jealous?
I just want to know who you really are.
My name is Chen Zhuo.
I'm a small-time security guard
at Wanlong Hotel.
There's no way
you're just a security guard.
I ran a background check on you.
Nothing showed up.
You investigated me?
Because I don't understand
why you're working
as a security guard at our hotel.
Look.
Even the Chairman of Jiangnan Group
can work as a security guard
at Wanlong Hotel.
Why can't I?
Don't underestimate
the role of a security guard.
It's full of hidden talents.
(Brain Examination Report)
Stress-induced
short-term memory impairment.
Looks like Xu Meiying
really doesn't remember
what happened back then.
Chen Zhuo?
Why aren't you asleep
in the middle of the night?
What are you doing in the living room?
I'm experiencing what it's like
to sit on a rich person's couch.
It's very comfortable.
I feel like your purpose
for joining Wanlong Hotel isn't simple.
I joined to get close to you, of course.
After all,
you're the boss
who can pay me 40,000 a month.
That's only because
you kept pestering me.
♪My right eye twitched with luck♪
♪Just like your sudden silence♪
♪You kindly urged me to forget you♪
♪Told me not to be stubborn,
how thoughtful of you♪
♪As if I've always been unworthy♪
♪It doesn't matter
if you forget me someday♪
♪How fragile my words sound
when I say I don't love you♪
♪I let you go and set you free,
but how can I free myself?♪
♪I can waste years
mourning this broken love♪
♪I can close my eyes
and burn alone in solitude♪
♪I can find solace♪
♪Knowing someone else
loses sleep at night♪
♪Even a faint love can still feel grand♪
♪I can endure and accept
your love for her♪
♪I can spend a lifetime
slowly letting grief fade♪
♪I can survive lonely nights
choking back silent tears♪
♪Tears of maturity
surrender to loneliness♪
♪Blurring the memories of the past♪