(Glory of Special Forces)
(This series is Shanghai's
major literary and artistic project)
(Episode 16)
If you want to talk about friendship,
leave rules out of it then.
Cut the crap.
Just say if you'll give it to us.
I won't give it to you two,
just Squad Leader.
Cut the crap.
None of you can live.
Hua Ping, doesn't that
car look familiar to you?
Isn't that the commando's car?
These punks must have stolen their car.
And you want to join the commando?
Dream on.
Hearing you say that,
why am I feeling so good?
Let's go.
We're going to report them.
Just you wait.
I say,
why even bother
fighting for the supplies?
You should just rob the command post.
Squad Leader, seriously.
Nothing good will come
from leading these two punks.
Get in the car.
Get in the car?
We're leaving without the supplies.
Get in.
But why, Squad Leader?
Stop asking!
Squad Leader is so thin-skinned.
He lost his cool so easily.
He was hiding something.
If we really exchanged fire just now,
they were the underdogs.
He mainly did that
to protect Yan Po Yue.
Then, why didn't you
attack them just now?
If we really exchanged fire,
we didn't have the upper hand either.
At least two of our men
would be taken out.
Which two do you think it would be?
It's okay. Let them go.
They won't last much longer.
Didn't you notice
your squad leader's leg just now?
His leg?
What about it?
His leg is injured.
He's limping.
I don't think it's because of hunger.
Squad Leader's leg was injured before.
Are you the one who took the supplies?
Pity,
it was that car just now
took the supplies.
I wonder who shoots faster
between the two of us.
You won't shoot us.
Why?
You would've shot us already
if you wanted to.
Why wait until now?
You're out of bullets, aren't you?
I never thought
I would meet a smart one.
Well, Xiao, shoot him.
What are you waiting for?
Although you are wearing a mask,
I still remember you.
Hi, Bai Long. I'm Xiao Fei.
Have we met before?
In the 2013 selection,
you were the inspector
of the commando,
and you were their best soldier.
This is odd.
Why are you in this competition too?
You will find out,
if you can make it till the end.
Zhou Zi Jian, give him two magazines.
Xiao, we don't even
have enough for our own.
Hurry up.
-Here you go.
-Give him some food.
We don't have enough food.
Be generous.
This is all...
We don't have enough.
Fine. Take it all.
This is
our gesture of respect to
a veteran of special force.
True respect comes from heart.
I never take advantage of people.
What do you want?
Collaboration.
The three of us
will cooperate with you.
At this point,
all the remaining participants are pros.
If we work together,
I'm sure we'll have a happy ending.
Does this mean he agrees?
We're winning.
Why aren't you sleeping?
I couldn't sleep.
Squad Leader,
you should sleep.
I'll take the watch.
I'm not sleepy.
Are you tired?
No.
Are you tired of this?
Pardon me?
Leaving them the supplies
is the same as forfeiting voluntarily.
Even if we make it till tomorrow,
we won't even have the strength to run.
We're from the same company.
I couldn't bring myself to shoot them.
I know you couldn't,
but I could.
We were standing so close to them.
If we had opened fire,
how could you be sure
you would get out of there alive?
Well, they couldn't get away either.
Did we work so hard
and come to this hellhole
just to hurt each other
and end up
going back together miserably?
We still shouldn't have
let them off lightly.
Why didn't you shoot then?
When we teamed up,
I promised you
I would listen to your orders.
I know what's on your mind.
You took a bullet for me before,
so
I have to listen to you.
If you choose not to listen,
there's nothing I can do too.
Squad Leader,
next time,
don't stop me.
Can I really stop you?
There aren't many participants left.
I will be
one of the six winners.
It must be the sniper from just now.
What's wrong with him?
Isn't him giving away his position too?
He's using us as bait
to lure all the fish out.
I got three here.
Mine too.
We're dead, Yan.
We're surrounded.
Yan Po Yue,
don't forget what you just said.
You two must be
among the six winners!
Squad Leader!
What is he trying to do?
He's drawing the enemies away.
We got to save him.
He's trying to help us win.
Don't waste his efforts.
One ran away to draw fires,
the other two aren't helping him.
Aren't they from the same company?
They shouldn't be broken up.
I really do want this soldier.
But his knee...
It's such a pity.
Let's make a bet.
My Lone Wolf
will eliminate them all tonight.
I'll put a bet on you
If that really happens,
what's the point of this then?
When tomorrow comes,
only Bai Long and Lone Wolf are left.
Relax.
I can't run away.
You two teams
are from the same unit, right?
Yes.
It's nice to see that
you're not fighting against each other.
If we're in a real battlefield,
only your comrades are reliable.
Are you going to forfeit yourself
or do you want some help?
I'll save you the trouble.
I'll do it myself.
Good luck joining Cheetah.
Thank you.
Come.
Help me up.
See for yourself.
I really can't move.
What is going on?
Sorry, guys.
You just moved my body.
And you accidentally triggered
the booby trap under my body.
Booby trap?
Also known as suicide bomb.
You tricked us!
Hold on, man!
Hold on, hold on.
There is camera here.
They're watching through the camera.
Fighting is against the rule.
We're all dead now.
You drew us away to
protect your teammates.
Is it worth it?
Look at my leg,
I can't go on.
Before leaving,
I wanted to make my death
count for something.
I'm sorry.
It's so dark here, yet he still hit me.
Where did the bullets come from?
There is a sniper on the other side.
Accept your fate.
The sniper is in
a very concealed position.
I'll walk out and be the bait,
let him expose himself.
He's very composed.
He won't shoot
without absolute certainty.
What should we do then?
We can't keep hiding here like this.
It's foolish to challenge the patience
of a sniper and a stone.
Because a sniper is a stone.
Seriously, this is not the time
to talk nonsense.
We don't even know
if Squad Leader is still alive.
Five minutes later, put your helmet up.
When you hear a gunshot,
set this off.
What about you?
I'm going down to try my luck.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Yan!
Yan, where is he?
He got away.
What's wrong with your hand?
He bit me.
He bit you?
So many people are eliminated at once.
I bet we don't need to wait until dawn.
Only a few are left now.
Squadron Leader.
Save the formality.
All of you, get in.
Your supper this time
is hot noodle soup.
There's plenty for you.
I know that
every soldier who is eliminated
doesn't want to leave.
But you have no choice.
This is the rule.
Come on.
Hurry up.
It's okay. Train well
and come back again.
Squad Leader! Squad Leader!
Drive.
What?
Aren't you going to say something?
I'm a corpse now.
Go back and review this.
Come back again.
Drive!
Squad Leader?
Squad Leader!
♫ Are you ready ♫
♫ Soldiers, brothers ♫
♫ When that day really comes ♫
♫ Rest assured, homeland ♫
♫ Rest assured, loved ones ♫
♫ I will march on bravely for victory ♫
♫ Are you ready ♫
♫ Soldiers, brothers ♫
♫ When that day really comes ♫
♫ Rest assured, homeland ♫
♫ Rest assured, loved ones ♫
♫ I will march on bravely for victory ♫
That's his choice.
He chose to be eliminated?
Those soldiers in the truck just now
were all eliminated by him.
It's worth it.
But we came together.
Do you want to go back together?
I don't want to.
It's the pick-up truck.
Looks like many are out in one night.
There is probably
only a few left out there.
Ten men.
According to the rules, we have to
get to the designated area in an hour.
The target should be a warehouse.
There are ten men left.
Other than the four of us,
there are six left out there.
Seven.
What does that mean?
This is as far as I can take you to.
You'll have to rely on yourselves
to enter the central area.
Long,
we're so close now.
Put it down!
Six winners. We all can win.
Good luck.
Long!
I...
Xiao,
let's attack together.
Take him out.
You go.
My initial intention is that
he wouldn't take the initiative
to shoot us, for the sake that
we were on the same team.
This is the place.
It's too quiet.
Are we the first to arrive?
Is the competition ended?
I don't think so.
Let's go inside and check it out.
Someone is here before us.
Let's take them down.
Careful.
There may be traps.
Quite a party.
Are Bai Long and Lone Wolf
planning to wait for these guys
to wear themselves out?
Lone Wolf won't do this.
So does Bai Long.
If I hadn't run out of bullets,
you wouldn't have been able to shoot me.
Impressive.
You're good.
Really good.
I'll give you another chance.
See you in Cheetah.
Just eliminate two more guys,
and the selection is over.
There's a guy out there waiting
for us to wear ourselves out.
I'll take care of him.
You only need to eliminate
one more guy here,
and the battle is over.
What is this brat trying to do?
He is out of bullets.
How is he going to fight Lone Wolf?
Exactly.
Is he trying to get himself killed?
It's the grand finale.
Let's enjoy it with patience.
I'm out of bullets!
Come out!
You've been hiding for two days!
Let me see what you look like!
Are you a coward?
What are you afraid of?
I know you're aiming at me!
Are you this gutless?
Are you a coward?
I'm standing right here!
Can't you aim right?
Shoot here!
Or here!
Are you this gutless?
Are you a gutless turtle
or a ninja turtle?
You gutless turtle!
Are you just going to
hide in your turtle shell
and wait for the selection
to end?
Are you this gutless?
I'm out of bullets.
What are you afraid of?
Fire a shot!
Show me where you are!
Come on!
It's over just like that?
This is no fun.
I don't think it's over.
The smoke is coming out.
Clear as day. Only six are left.
It can't be that simple.
It's me.
Xiao, it's me.
Yan Po Yue is right over there.
Let's round him up,
put an end to this drill.
Go.
I'm sorry.
It's over!
Come out!
Xiao, we're a team.
We're comrades in arms.
Competition is just like war.
It's cruel.
All is fair in war, my friend.
Let bygones be bygones.
We are comrades in arms from now on.
No, thanks.
Squad Leader Xiao,
we don't want to be your
comrade in arms.
What does that mean?
Haven't you eliminated
other people before?
But we'll never shoot one of our own!
Be smart!
What is our purpose here?
To join special forces!
This is just a temporary team!
We're from the same regiment!
Is that temporary too?
My friend,
mark my words,
no one can stay in
the same troop forever.
How could you say that?
Do it yourself or I will.
What does that mean?
It's over.
It's not over for me.
You're a girl.
You want to see me.
Here I am.
May I have your name?
Guo Xiao Xiao.
Aren't you curious
where my smoke is coming from?
This is a red smoke bomb
I made with sugar and some soil
with nitrate from around the toilet,
plus a little chemical substances.
What do you think?
Its smoke looks like the smoke from
the smoke pack we carry
around our waist, right?
This brat.
Interesting.
You asked for this.
Yan!
Stay back!
I waited three years
for this opportunity!
I was betrayed
by my own teammate at the end last time!
This time, I have to win!
My squad leader
sacrificed himself to save us.
As a squad leader,
you shot your own comrades!
Stop lecturing me!
Bullshit!
(The competition is over.)
(Congratulations to the
five winners of the assessment.)
Bai Long.
Captain.
Welcome back.
Bai.
You managed to find nitrate around
the toilet. Where did you learn it from?
I wasn't just sitting around
at home over the past few years.
Lone Wolf.
Xiao Yun Jie.
Xu Yang.
Zhou Zi Jian.
Congratulations to you three.
Report!
I should be qualified too!
You want six men.
I'm the sixth!
You're eliminated.
They sabotaged me.
The rule stipulated that
the last six people are the winners.
I
am the sixth!
Xiao Fei,
I read your profile.
You've been an outstanding
non-commissioned officer for four years.
You won the first place in
the regiment's combat competition.
In your recommendation letter,
praises of you take up to three pages.
You are outstanding,
but there will
never be a place for you on my team.
Why?
Because you're not worthy!
For us, our comrade's life is
more important than our own.
And what did you do?
In order to win,
you killed your comrade!
This is betrayal!
Even if you got into the top six,
I would never let you
set foot in Cheetah!
This is not fair!
Last time...
At the end of the competition last time,
I was shot from behind
by my own comrade and eliminated!
That comrade of yours, Mao Huai Qing
was eliminated too.
Alright now.
Have a nice meal and go home.
This is not right!
You're being partial.
You're being partial!
Our smokes came out at the same time.
If he can stay, why can't I?
When did I say I would keep him?
All of you, just wait and see.
We will meet again one day.