(Glory of Special Forces)
(This series is Shanghai's
major literary and artistic project)
(Episode 6)
You didn't try hard enough.
Again!
Exert more strength!
You're the king of the new recruits.
You're the best!
Lu Xiao Tian!
Stop talking!
Relax.
You hit it, Yan!
I don't trust you.
Look.
Take a look.
My goodness.
You did it, Yan!
I hit it!
Hell yes!
Move.
It's for you.
It's the steel ball
that you fired just now.
Pick up the steel balls.
I've been the ball boy
for the entire afternoon.
It's safe to call me
the logistics support.
I should've just stayed home
and peeled potatoes.
Picking up steel balls
is a form of training, too.
Are you training a military dog?
Military dogs are our comrades too.
Hurry up.
That's all for today.
Meeting dismissed.
Company Commander Li.
I have something to tell you.
The kitchen squad of
Special Service Company
dealt with the drug traffickers, too.
I suggest
that they join
the actual combat together.
Is there no one else
in Special Service Company?
Don't get me wrong.
I merely think
that joining the actual combat
is more helpful to them.
Why is it helpful?
If the kitchen squad joins the battle,
who will be in charge of cooking?
Staff Officer Ai,
did someone
beg you to speak for them?
Yes.
But I personally think
that you should reconsider
Yan Po Yue's relocation.
I don't even have to reconsider.
Even if I reconsider,
the answer is still no.
He's not well trained enough.
Company Commander Li.
If you really want
to understand him better,
you can go to Staff Officer Zhao
and get his profile.
That lad
is not the stubborn simpleton
he seems to be.
Zhou Zi Jian!
Here!
Fan Jin!
Guo Kui!
Yes!
Yan Po Yue!
Report!
He's on duty.
Lu Xiao Tian!
Report!
He's on duty.
What duty is that?
Why is all them on duty?
Company Commander...
Report!
Stop dilly-dallying!
They're back.
Fall in.
Yes!
As of now,
the night roll call has ended.
Platoon leaders,
take your platoon back!
Yes!
Left turn!
Forward, march!
Quick, march!
Mission accomplished.
There’s food in the cookhouse.
Guo kept some food for you.
Thank you, Squad leader.
Begone!
The angle of your arm and the cloth
is 75 degrees.
I think
the wind is Force Four.
Is your assumption accurate?
A small discrepancy
can lead to a great error.
I got to know the formula from my dad.
I've never applied it in real life.
You're fooling me around again.
Am I a guinea pig to you?
My arm is numb.
Stand still.
How is the training?
Squad leader!
Squad leader.
How many times did you hit the target?
The wind is too strong today.
I haven't hit the target, not even once.
Is it really because of the wind?
My grandma has passed away.
If she's still alive,
I bet she could shoot
better than you with a slingshot.
I...
I've never learned
how to measure wind speed before.
Who on earth
knows how to measure
wind speed at birth?
I picked up the skill from training.
You didn't press yourself hard enough.
Let me teach you a trick.
Who in Squad 247
do you hate the most?
Me?
Count me in.
Who else?
Don't make me think for you.
Li Xiang?
Do you hate him?
Just tell me the truth.
One more.
Squad leader!
He's from Company One,
Squad One of Platoon One.
His name is Xiao Fei!
Yan works so hard to put him down!
Very well!
You're a man with spine!
Pretend all three of us
are standing here.
Hit us!
Vent out your anger on us!
Seek revenge all you want!
It doesn't work?
Let me teach you another trick.
That's how you measure the wind speed.
The wind speed...
Two slaps.
The distance
is 53 yuan and 20 cent.
Let's pack up and go.
(Fan Jin)
Little brat.
Staff Officer Ai.
Who are you looking for?
Is Yan Po Yue in?
Yan Po Yue?
He's hunting bird outside.
Hunting birds?
Since he's not allowed to use the gun,
he's satisfying his craving
with slingshot.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Are you not eating?
No, I'm not eating.
Who is that?
Move!
Staff Officer Ai.
Are you okay?
Aren't you taking a lunch break?
You must be really free
to play slingshot.
Lunch break is not my thing.
My marksmanship is terrible.
I need more practice.
How is the practice going?
Do you think that you're great?
Do you know
a large part of shooting
is mental attitude?
Shooting with slingshot and gun
are totally different.
When I shoot with a gun,
you may come and take a look.
Let me try.
Try what?
You're kidding me.
You're a staff officer.
Don't downgrade yourself to my level.
I'm more senior than you
and I'm your superior.
Give it to me.
This is an order!
Yes!
Do you admit defeat?
I'm not thirsty.
You need to drink
even if you're not thirsty.
Here's a toast to you.
People usually
propose a toast with alcohol.
This is the first time I see someone
proposing a toast with Coke.
Let's replace alcohol with Coke.
It'll turn into sweats anyway.
When there are sweats, there are ways.
What you just said
is for real men, right?
To me,
you're more manly than real men.
You're really something.
You insult others
without using curse words.
Do you know why I came to see you?
I don't know.
But I'm sure it's not for a good cause.
Tell me.
What kind of trouble do you think
you created this time?
I've never created any trouble.
I've fulfilled my duty as a soldier.
However, to some,
fulfilling my duty is a trouble.
Yan Po Yue.
Don't think that you're cool
just because you behave wilfully.
Don't expect everyone
to please you all the time.
This is a military camp, not your home!
You always behave
like an unruly spoiled brat.
You're so arrogant.
You think you're better than everyone.
That's right.
Many in Squad 247
don't like you
but more in the squad
are concerned about you.
I'm here today
on Xiao Yun Jie's request.
He wants me to talk to you.
He's really concerned about you
but he doesn't want
to hurt your feelings.
Don't be nosy.
Don't be ungrateful.
I wish I had so many friends
who are concerned about me.
You?
Do you lack friends?
Your father
was once in the force.
He's a hero.
He took part in
many military operations.
The troop that he was in is...
Did you read my profile?
I went to Recruiting Cadre
for inquiry.
That's how I found out everything.
He and I
are different individuals.
I fought for everything that I got.
It's not because I was his son!
In everyone's heart,
there are always secrets.
However, as time passes,
those secrets will start expanding.
Even if you have a big heart,
you'll find it difficult
to contain the secrets.
What about this?
If you can trust me,
you may talk to me.
I promise I won't tell anyone.
When I was seven years old,
I left the army compound
for the first time
to go to school.
On my way back from school,
a few adults abducted me.
Later, I found out
they're the accomplices
of the drug traffickers
cracked down on by my father before.
They did that to get back at my father.
Hello.
Is your father Yan Shi Xiang?
He told me to pick you up.
(They threw me into a dark hole.)
(The hole was really deep.)
(It was so big and cold
at the same time.)
(The entrance was really small.)
(There were many kids inside the hole.)
(All of them were abducted
by human traffickers,)
(waiting to be sold.)
(When there was food,)
(everyone fought like dogs)
(for food.)
(But no one dared to fight against them
or run away.)
(That's because we would be beaten up
if we failed to escape.)
(On one fine day,)
(I reached the top.)
(But no one was
willing to come with me.)
(They shouted at the top of their voice)
(because if I got caught,)
(they would get a corn in return.)
(I could only run away.)
(I kept running)
(as if there's no tomorrow.)
(I didn't know where could I go)
(or how long had I been running.)
(I only remember the sound of the wind.)
(It gave me a sense of security.)
(In the end,)
(I finally see the familiar
camouflage green)
(at the army compound entrance.)
(At that moment,)
(I knew that I succeeded.)
When I woke up,
I was in the army hospital.
He
was sitting by the bedside.
Starting from that time,
you fell in love with jogging.
Jogging gives me a sense of security.
That's great.
You can now speak freely about the past.
Facing up to it
is the real bravery.
After I was discharged
from the hospital,
he started to give me military training.
I learned military formation,
obstacle course racing,
diving, rock climbing,
and martial arts combat.
So, before joining the army,
you've been trained like a soldier
since you're seven years old.
No.
I didn't have comrades back then.
Cheetah Commando
is where
your father used to fight for.
It's also your ultimate aim
when you joined the army.
Am I right?
It's the sacred place
for the King of soldiers.
That's my sole target
for my entire life.
The dream is great.
But the reality
is awful.
Haven't you faced something worse?
An army cook
dreaming to be
a member of the Special Service Company.
What is there to be afraid of?
Staff Officer Ai.
That's all for today.
I am going to do this on my own.
I don't need sympathy from others.
Yan Po Yue.
We're comrades.
You're welcome to
seek advice from me anytime.
All the best!
Are you hungry?
Throw the targets into the river!
Take it.
Here.
Grab it.
Yes.
Hit the target
and you get to eat.
Here.
One.
Two.
Look.
Do you want to be the shooter
or do you want
to be kept in the oil tank?
Delicious food
is only limited to one portion.
The chicken goes to the person
who gets it.
Fight for it!
Yan, you're back.
I have something to ask.
What's wrong?
There's a huge tree and the atmosphere
was calm and peaceful.
Under the tree, a man and a woman
were having a private talk.
It's not a big deal, right?
I...
Begone!
What's wrong, Yan?
Did something happen?
In the afternoon,
I hit nine targets out of ten.
You must've hit all the targets.
Or else,
why did Staff Officer Ai come to see you
on purpose?
Was it because she's intrigued by
your heroic past at the sentry post?
That's not right.
I have even more heroic stories.
Guo, you're heroic too.
Why didn't she come and see you?
Please accept my interview.
Was it a pleasant experience
talking to the female staff officer?
That's an admission by silence.
Yan.
Jokes aside. I'm serious.
Let me show you the correct way.
You need to build a good relationship
with your superior at the organisation,
right?
Then, you stand a great chance
to leave cookhouse.
First and foremost,
I'll fight my way back to
combat platoon's squad.
Secondly,
Staff Officer Ai and I
are merely superior and subordinate.
Stop talking nonsense.
Childish.
Guo, do you think what I said
makes sense?
Isn't that a shortcut?
He practices so hard every day
but no one sees his effort.
What's the point?
I'm troubled.
He has no grit at all.
What can you do?
But I have grit.
One, two, three, four...
Stand there!
What are you doing?
Report, Squad leader!
The company commander is working
overtime to work on some documents.
He told me to send him some food.
Which company commander is that?
The company commander
of Special Service Company.
Who are you looking for?
Company Commander Li Xiang.
Register yourself.
Yes, sir!
One, two, three, four...
What is your name?
Lu Xiao Tian.
Thank you.
Have you eaten?
Go in.
Yes.
How dare you wrote
to the cadre to change the shift?
Is that necessary?
Fortunately, this incident
was covered up by Staff Officer Ai.
Or else, you would be
questioning by someone else,
but not me!
Sir,
Yan Po Yue is completely in the dark.
Am I right?
Report!
Sir!
It's my fault.
Think twice before you say something!
Whoever wrote the letter
did it for a good cause.
They want me to be better.
What stops you to be better
at the cookhouse?
Think again!
Fan!
Here!
I heard that you took him to the hill
for practice every day.
Does he fulfil his duty?
Report!
I fulfil my duty all the time.
Do you fulfil your duty as a cook?
Do you provide adequate logistic support
and cook for everyone?
How many dishes can you make?
Did you hear him?
He says one thing and do another!
Fan.
You need to educate your subordinates.
Yes.
Focus on your work.
When you're good at work,
you'll improve in life.
Don't encourage
the unhealthy tendencies.
Understood?
Yes!
Squad leader.
How was it going?
What?
Did the instructor say anything?
He told me to intensify
teaching and focus in work!
The supply vehicle
just delivered two tons of rice.
-Go get the rice!
-Yes!
Yan Po Yue.
Yes!
The instructor is right.
We do what we're supposed to do.
Come with me.
Today,
I'm going to teach you my final move.
Pay attention to it.
It's not difficult to learn.
(Braised tofu.)
(It goes well with rice.)
(Add tofu to a wok)
(and fry until the tofu
is golden brown on both sides.)
(Then, add the tofu
to the boiling stock.)
(Thicken the stock with starch.)
(Squad leader said, serving in the army
is no different from cooking tofu.)
(The tofu has to be fried
until golden brown)
(before being braised on low heat.)
(That's how it gets the flavours.)
(But I think I'm more like the stock.)
(Even when I'm alone,)
(I perform my duty well.)
It's time for assembly!
Fall in!
Calm down.
It's nothing to do with us.
We still have to clean the vegetables
tomorrow morning.
Stop fooling around.
It's late in the midnight.
Why are you making trouble for yourself?
It's a field operation.
Bring your equipment.
Squad leader.
Is it a combat?
Hurry up.
Squad leader.
We're heading to the wrong direction.
Why are we alone?
Get down. Get your equipment.
The kitchen squads of
Company One and Two?
What are they doing here?
Fall in!
Count the people.
Everyone from the kitchen squad
of Company One is here!
of Company Two is here!
Everyone from the kitchen squad
of Special Service Company is here!
We received order from the higher-ups.
The confrontation drill which was
scheduled at the end of the year
has been carried forward.
In order to find out
our comprehensive military capability,
the competition between kitchen squads
which was usually stood alone
will be conducted concurrently
with the confrontation drill.
Today, three companies
will compete with each other.
We didn't prepare anything.
What's there to compete?
Are we competing
in term of cutting skills?
The competition will be
the same as the front-line soldiers.
We'll do more than
the front-line soldiers for sure.
The kitchen squad competition
is a five-kilometre loaded march.
You're heading to the south.
Each squad is required to carry
all the equipment and ingredients
and bring them to the designated
destination in the shortest time.
The score of the bottom
will be the final score of the squad.
It'll be taken into the calculation
of the total score.
When all of you have reached
the designated destination,
I'll announce the next instruction.
Understood?
Yes!
My goodness.
The fight has started.
Finally it's happening.
Give it to me!
Let me help you!
Hurry up!
Squad leader!
I'm waiting for you!
Squad leader.
Just kill me.
Shoot me to death.
-I can't do it anymore.
-Don't talk rubbish.
I don't want to hold everyone back.
Get up!
I can't do it anymore.
I can't get up.
-Guo, help him.
-I can't do it anymore.
-Here, bring him up.
-Let's go.
Yan Po Yue.
Here!
Do you know the rule of the competition?
Report!
You've announced it earlier.
The score of the bottom
will be the final score of the squad.
Why didn't you take care
of your comrades?
Someone has to be the champion.
That's just an excuse.
That's my target.
Squad leader.
Have some water.
Report! The last member
of the kitchen squad of
Special Service Company.
has arrived at the designated spot.
That's all.
The bottom of Company One Kitchen Squad
took 25 minutes and 43 seconds to reach.
The bottom of Company Two Kitchen Squad
took 25 minutes and 54 seconds to reach.
The bottom of Special Service Company
Kitchen Squad
took 26 minutes and 37 seconds to reach.
Company One Kitchen Squad won.
Company One, come here!
Company One always
marches fearlessly onward.
There's something else.
Yan Po Yue of
Special Service Company Kitchen Squad
took 18 minutes and 27 seconds to reach.
He's broken the record
of the loaded march.
The next test is resisting enemy
and launching harassing attacks.
You're required to carry your weapons
and pass through the war zone.
In the journey,
you have to shoot moving targets.
Under the firepower exchange
of both the warring sides,
make sure you reach the hillside
at three o'clock in clock position.
The final score
is based on the number of members
who reach the hillside safely.
The squad with the most
surviving members wins.
Hide away, everyone!
We're merciless to the kitchen squad.
Isn't it a little too cruel?
If we don't train them in a cruel way,
they'll be butchered brutally
when they're in a battle.
Squad leader!
Watch out for 12 o'clock!
Enemies are at nine
and three o'clock, too.
We're surrounded by enemies.
We can't fight them head on.
We need to find another way.
Let me distract them.
All of you climb up the hill!
Come back, Yan!
You have only got one life!
Guo!
Come here!
Why?
Let's switch.
Give me your wok.
He's using the wok as a shield.
That brat is ingenious.
Company Two, hurry up, move!
Company One, surround them
from the side!
Squad leader!
I dropped my backpack!
Rubbish! Pick it up!
Yes!
Lu Xiao Tian!
Watch our belongings.
I'll eliminate them.
Squad leader, wipe them out!
This lad...
He's so crafty.
Didn't you see that?
Don't touch me.
We must abide by the drill rules.
It's all done.
Squad leader.
I'll go first.
Be steady.
Do it like how you shoot with slingshot.
Yan!
Let's switch.
It's full.
I can't hit the target anyway.
Don't waste the ammunition.
You need it more.
Take it.
You have to do the same
when you're at the battlefield.
The ammunition will be gathered
and given to the best shooter.
It's a move to improve
combat effectiveness.
You're the best shooter among us.
Take them down!
Strongest Yan!
Report! Four members
of Company One survived.
Report! Five members
of Company Two survived.
Report! Eight members
of Special Service Company survived.
All the members survived!
Fall in!
Yes!
Here's the result of the second test.
There are 20 targets in total.
Each target carries five points.
The full mark is 100 points.
Company One scores 80 points.
Company Two scores 60 points.
Special Service Company
scores 90 points.
Extra 40 points to Company One
as four members survived.
Extra 50 points to Company Two
as five members survived.
Extra 80 points to Special Service
Company as all members survived.
Adding two together,
Company One scores 120 points.
Company Two scores 110 points.
Special Service Company
scores 170 points.
In the second test,
Special Service Company won!
Tiger Special Forces
always win when they fight!
It's just a petty trick.
What is there to be proud of?
What's wrong with you, Zhang?
You're a sore loser.
You're carrying a wok too.
Why didn't you utilise it?
If we're on a battlefield,
can your wok withstand bullets?
You're cheating!
We utilized the wok
in a reasonable and clever way.
What plays a large part
when two experts fight?
Their brain.
In your world,
wok only serves its purposes
in cooking.
You're one wok away
from becoming an expert.
Since you're in the mood to bicker,
I think you've had enough rest.
Here comes the third test.
In the midst of a war,
you're required to build a stove,
start a fire and cook.
You need to cook
four dishes and one soup.
The company that
prepares a complete meal first wins.
Sure.
Let's do it here.