Why is His Majesty in such a hurry?
It's midday.
And he rushed to the Treasury.
It's not even our shift yet.
Don't be silly.
It's urgent.
Listen up.
Whatever they find out
about the muddled accounts,
we might have to take the blame.
Got it?
Yes.
I guess
His Majesty was frightened
after praying for rain.
He is
throwing tantrums like a kid.
=Episode 8=
Yes, Eunuch Li.
(The Way of Rebirth)
Everyone knows
you get to manage the Treasury
as the Dowager and Grand Marshal
favor you.
They favor me?
Do you hear yourself?
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Greetings, Lady Xiao.
Your Majesty, look.
This is only part
of this year's accounts.
Is there still a need
to check the Treasury?
Be quiet.
Since I manage the Treasury,
I've been working
very hard
for fear that my men
make mistakes.
Fortunately, they did a good job.
Currently, the accounts are clear.
These are accounts
from the former king's reign
to the current reign.
Ledgers of the Ministry of Revenue
and mine
are here.
Your Majesty.
Take your time.
After all, it takes a while
to check these accounts.
Please don't
wear yourself out.
I will prepare some tea for you.
Your Majesty.
What are we figuring out?
I just want to know
how the Treasury is
out of money.
You need money?
The Wu Army will attack.
Whether we fight
or not, we need money.
Money isn't the issue.
The point is,
why is it out of money?
However,
this year's salt tax revenues
and local tax revenues
are over eight million taels in total.
It was spent
right after being put in the Treasury?
Shall I
ask the kitchen staff
to cook some food
and send it here?
Your ledger
is really clear.
I didn't find a single problem.
I told you.
The accounts are very clear.
However,
no problem found
is the biggest problem.
Your Majesty, I'm completely unaware.
Do you want money
or your life?
If there is embezzlement,
auditing is completely useless.
These accounts can be balanced.
You manage accounts.
Money is put in,
and you can take it out.
Even if there is no balance left,
I can push you
to change the result.
Tell me.
Where did the eight million
in revenue go?
I don't know.
Good for you.
Then tell me
who to ask
and who knows?
Well,
the bulk of that money was
spent on repairing the palace.
So, you should ask
Zhang Chao, the Minister of Works.
Zhang Chao?
Where is he?
He should now be on duty at the office
outside Jingyang Gate.
Let's go.
Zhang Chao became
Minister of Works for his skills
in construction.
He used to ride with
Grand Marshal as an advisor.
One of Grand Marshal's men.
Will you keep following the clues?
Sure.
Alright, I'll do it with you.
Anyway, I've announced my mistakes.
I'm not afraid anymore.
My ministers say
I am wise
and brave.
Then I will show them
what a real wise ruler is.
What an unfavorable start.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Zhang Chao.
Yes.
How much did you spend
on the renovation?
The cost of materials and labor is
more than two million.
Specifically, how much?
Your Majesty,
you came here for the Treasury, right?
During the repair,
all accounts are recorded clearly.
But the Ministry of Works
only handles the construction.
As for the records
of the expenses
and appropriation,
you have to
ask the Ministry of Revenue.
I see.
Okay.
Let's go.
Your Majesty!
These are accounts
from the former king's reign
to the current reign.
Ledgers of the Ministry of Revenue
and mine
are here.
Your Majesty.
Take your time.
After all, it takes a while
to check these accounts.
Please don't
wear yourself out.
I will prepare some tea for you.
You come back!
No problem found
is the biggest problem.
I don't know.
Your Majesty.
I knew it.
Please spare my life.
Please.
I truly have no idea, Your Majesty.
You tell me.
This year, salt tax revenues
and local tax revenues
are over eight million, right?
Yes.
Is most of that money spent
on the Ministry of Works?
Yes.
Is the Ministry of Works
outside Jingyang Gate?
Yes.
Come on.
Ministry of Works.
Your Majesty.
Minister of Works...
Zhang Chao
once served under the Grand Marshal.
He joined the army once.
He's skilled in carpentry.
Father promoted him
to lead the Ministry of Works.
Your Majesty,
how do you know everything?
Of course, I do.
I'm the chosen one.
Right.
I believe so.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
This time,
I must follow the clues.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Zhang Chao,
you spent over two million
on house repairs,
right?
Yes.
But I should ask
the Ministry of Revenue
about the details?
Your Majesty, you came...
Just say yes or no.
Yes.
Did you send an assassin
to kill me?
Did you send an assassin to kill me?
Your Majesty.
I didn't.
I'm completely unaware
of the assassination.
I'll get back to you later.
Go. Ministry of Revenue.
Well,
are we taking a tour?
Go.
Got it?
Around that corner ahead,
an assassin is ambushing me.
A person
with a dagger.
Now,
we wait for you here.
You go and take him down.
Yes.
You're actually right.
Assassin!
Your Majesty,
how did you know?
You guessed correctly.
I told you.
I'm the chosen one.
Speak.
Who sent you here?
If you confess now,
His Majesty might spare your life.
You won't talk?
I have plenty of ways to make you talk.
Either talk or die now.
Come on.
Make it quick.
I can stab you 49 times
before killing you.
You sure you won't speak?
I'll speak.
Spare me. I'll speak.
Li Xuan sent me here.
Li Xuan?
You mean the Minister of Revenue,
Yes, it's him.
He asked me to ambush here.
Are you telling the truth?
Sure, I am.
Where is he now?
He's not on duty now.
He's in the yard over there.
It hurts so much!
Spare me.
I've said everything I know.
Let's go.
Arrest him.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, spare me.
Well...
I knew it.
(Ledger)
No wonder you objected earlier.
You feared it would lead to you.
As the Minister of Revenue,
you embezzle funds.
How dare you?
Your Majesty.
Initially, I didn't intend
to graft this year's salt tax revenues
or the revenues from the prefectures.
But someone told me
that I could cook the books
after the money was put in.
No issues would arise.
And no one would check it.
No one would dare to do that.
So I just...
So,
this is the real ledger, right?
Yes.
Who is it?
Speak.
Zhang Chao.
The Minister of Works?
Yes.
Should we arrest him now?
Continue.
Yes.
Your Majesty,
here's the thing.
There was an extensive renovation.
The Ministry of Revenue
quoted at two million.
The Ministry of Works
actually allocated only 1.2 million,
short by
800,000 taels.
It was short by 1.2 million
for the disaster relief in Chenzhou.
800?
Yes.
How much was embezzled?
Half of that money.
You earn more than I do!
Tell me.
How was it divided?
I only took 20 percent.
Zhang Chao took 30 percent.
He gave the remaining money
to the person behind it.
He said none of us could afford
to offend them.
The assassin
was sent by you?
Assassin?
What assassin?
I know nothing about it.
They only asked me to destroy evidence.
Your Majesty,
I have nothing to do with that.
I am indeed guilty,
but I have
nothing to do with that.
I am guilty.
Of course, you and Zhang Chao both are.
Spare me, Your Majesty.
Show mercy.
Speak.
The one behind it,
is it Grand Marshal
or Grand Tutor Wang?
Well...
Speak!
Well,
it's...
It's...
Don't move.
Wake up.
Wake up!
Leave it.
Shot in the heart.
He's dead.
How is it going?
Didn't catch them.
They escaped.
I'll order
a city-wide search.
It's over.
So, it's a dead end again.
Which step exactly went wrong?
Eunuch Li of the Treasury?
The Ministry of Works?
The Ministry of Revenue?
The Ministry of Rites?
The Ministry of War?
That's not right.
Which step exactly went wrong?
Your Majesty.
These people
are lawless.
Do they even regard me as their king?
In front of me,
they killed a man in broad daylight.
How about
we question the first assassin again?
Maybe the two assassins are connected.
Which step went wrong?
Since Li Xuan died,
we question some vice ministers.
Maybe we'll find some clues.
For questioning, we should start
with Zhang Chao.
He knows something.
Well,
Your Majesty,
what should we do?
No, wait.
Since Zhang Chao told us
to come to the Ministry of Revenue,
surely he has a backup plan.
You're right.
Even if you ask Zhang Chao now,
he will claim to be innocent.
I came to the Ministry of Revenue,
and they killed Li Xuan.
It means
I found the right clue.
Yes.
Li Xuan is dead,
and dead men tell no tales.
That's right.
I must be quicker.
Your Majesty!
It really hurts.
Since I manage the Treasury,
I've been working
very hard
for fear that my men
make mistakes.
Fortunately...
You old thing.
You shut up!
Nonsense!
Spare me.
Please, Your Majesty.
You liar.
Let's go.
Your Majesty.
What are we doing here?
Zhang Chao.
Go. Ministry of Revenue.
There is an assassin ahead.
I'll run.
You follow me.
Your Majesty. How did you know?
Can you
not ask the same question?
Long Qi.
There will be
an assassin over there.
They're much better
than the one with a dagger.
You
go there now and ambush them.
I reckon
it's about time.
But
how...
I...
Should I drop it?
There really is an assassin.
Long Qi.
You interrogate him.
Let's go in
and see Li Xuan.
I'm Li Xuan, Minister of Revenue.
Greetings, Your Majesty
and Lady Xiao.
You know I am coming, huh?
I will ask you one question.
Who's the one supporting you
and Zhang Chao?
Is it Grand Marshal
or Grand Tutor Wang?
Wait.
He took poison.
He's dead?
This is different from the last life.
Last life?
He's dead?
Your Majesty.
Speak!
Who is the person
behind it?
Your Majesty. I just found out
he is mute.
What?
Since that's the case,
I'll start over.
Your Majesty!
Since I manage the Treasury,
I've been working...
It hurts even more than last time.
Chest pain?
It's fine.
Have you thought of any new clues again?
Strange,
why did I say "again"?
Honey.
You know about my reincarnation?
Never mind.
Don't you have any questions?
Whenever you speak in that tone,
I better not ask
because
I might get hit.
Good for you.
Very clever.
Long Qi.
Have Imperial Guards
split into two groups.
One group goes to the Ministry of Works
outside Jingyang Gate
and brings Zhang Chao here.
The other group
goes to the Ministry of Revenue
and brings Li Xuan here,
alive or dead.
Remember,
as long as there's written stuff
on them,
including small notes,
bring it all back.
Yes.
I haven't finished yet.
Come closer.
Really?
Sure.
Go ahead.
Aren't you supposed
to check the accounts?
Why suddenly arrest the two ministers?
This doesn't make sense.
We're arresting people instead of
checking the ledger?
I actually think
it's quite interesting.
I will go to the kitchen
to prepare some food for Your Majesty.
Come back.
I'm not hungry.
No need to prepare food.
Eunuch Li.
You and I wait for them
to return.
By the orders of His Majesty,
Li Xuan, Minister of Revenue,
enters the palace.
You freaked me out.
Commander Zhou,
you startled me.
Why is His Majesty summoning me
to the palace?
Did His Majesty really find out?
Besides,
what's the plan?
He says
if you leave now,
he'll save your life.
The carriage is waiting for you
outside the city.
The guards at the city gate
will let you go.
Alright.
I will leave now.
(To Fan Kuan,
Minister of War of Wu State)
Still not confessing?
Alright.
No rush.
Your Majesty.
This is everything.
As expected,
the Imperial Guards
have moles.
(Ledger)
(To Fan Kuan,
Minister of War of Wu State)
(Secret Letter)
What about Li Xuan?
He's dead.
Again?
I was late.
Please forgive me.
Eunuch Li.
So, the mastermind,
are you going to confess?
You embezzled tax revenues
and betrayed the country.
You leaked our defense deployment maps
and weapon designs.
You colluded with Wu State
with hundreds of officials.
You spent the embezzled money
on the properties in Wu State.
Most of the money was transited
through Hanzhou
under the protection
of the Governor of Hanzhou.
Hanzhou is doomed.
Zhang Chao,
how did you become like this?
Who gave you the guts
to commit a capital offense?
You'll get your whole family killed.
You were righteous when you fought
alongside me.
What happened to you?
What are you laughing at?
Grand Marshal.
Why do you keep asking him?
Aren't you aware
of the military strength
of Chen State?
Wu State has raised an army.
Chen State is doomed.
Back off.
I don't intend to hurt anyone.
I just want to say something.
Is that okay?
Let him speak.
Why did I collaborate with Wu State?
Why did I embezzle money?
I did it all to leave myself a way out.
Due to the prestige
King Chen Wu established back then,
the Wu Army doesn't move for now.
But they'll attack sooner or later.
Why can't I plan for myself?
Chen Xiaohua,
you made the Edict of Self-Reproach
and then the rain fell.
You thought you were remarkable.
How many stupid things have you done?
Have you ever changed?
You never have.
The Minister of Revenue
has his reasons.
Ministry of Revenue? Ridiculous.
That ministry has no money at all.
When King Chen Wu was alive,
the Ministry of Revenue was rich.
Since you became king,
the Ministry of Revenue has been a mess.
Can you manage it well?
No, you can't.
What is the current level
of the soldiers?
How long has it been
since they practiced?
Grand Marshal.
You tell us.
Though I think
we all know.
You're short of money.
You are like a paperhanger
working on appearances.
You're helpless to change it.
Grand Tutor Wang.
He is not here, but it's okay.
Don't judge
the Governor of Hanzhou.
He has no money
or military supplies needed.
He only has
hundreds of old soldiers around my age
guarding the city.
Can he guard it?
He can't.
After one year, I'm poor yet patriotic.
After two years, I'm poor yet patriotic.
After another year,
I would starve to death.
We're loyal to Chen State.
But who can protect us?
Can Chen Xiaohua do it?
You're incapable
of fighting Wu State.
Shame on you.
Shame on you!
Chen State
is going to perish!
You shut up!
I won't
let it happen.
In any case,
you can't change it.
If you don't believe me,
ask your sister.
You'll know how much she's taken
in your name.
Your Majesty.
Please allow me to kill this wretch.
Let him finish.
Chen Xiaohua,
you are destined
to be a ruler of a fallen state.
The century-old legacy of Chen State
will all be destroyed at your hands.
Let me tell you the truth.
King Wu has declared
that they will seize the capital
within half a month.
Right now,
I'm just going to die ahead of you.
I love Chen State,
but who loves me?
Why are you all looking at me?
I'm fine.
I'm going out
to take a break.
Your Majesty.
The Governor of Hanzhou has
joined the Wu Army with his forces.
Governor Wang Kai and the general
opened the city gates
for King Wu.
All the officials and guards in the city
have all defected.
Why did it happen?
How could they defect?
Your Majesty.
Grand Marshal,
should we discuss this first
or another matter first?
What do you think, Your Majesty?
Imperial Guards!
- Yes.
Why?
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, why?
Come on.
Move.
Money is gone.
So are my officials.
Let me think twice
about fighting Wu State.
Court adjourned.
(Li Xuan, Minister of Revenue,)
(Zhang Chao, Minister of Works,)
(and Yi Xiangquan, Minister of War,)
(colluded with officials)
(in six ministries)
(to embezzle money.)
(The military funds embezzled)
(have reached millions.)
(It's unpardonable)
(and outrageous.)
(The people have long suffered
from corruption.)
(The current officials)
(should not deceive the superior
nor neglect the subordinate.)
(If the ministers are stagnant
and afraid,)
(they won't even dare
to do small good deeds.)
(By the edict of His Majesty,)
(execute the families
of criminal officials involved.)
(Hereby making it public)
(to serve as a warning.)
Get the carriage.
I'm leaving.
Quickly bring out my son.
We meet outside the city.
Why?
Do what I say.
Eunuch Li has given all of us away.
My brother will definitely not spare me.
If I don't leave now,
I won't be able to leave.
I heard he has already reached Hanzhou.
I need to go see him.
Once I meet him,
everything will be fine.
Yes.
Hurry up!
How dare you!
What are you doing?
Open the door.
Open the door!
I want to see my brother.
Brother.
I know you're there.
So this is your order.
Your Majesty.
Well,
her nature is not bad.
She must have been incited by traitors.
I do not believe
she's colluded with Wu State.
Well,
considering she's my sister,
I hope you can spare her life.
Brother.
When did you start siding
with Chen Xiaohua?
Didn't you say he was unreliable
and that he should be deposed?
Our family has been loyal.
We gave it all to Chen State.
But how has Chen Xiaohua treated you?
Let me tell you the truth.
I've indeed colluded with Wu State.
Chen Xiaohua.
Can you guess
how did King Wu quickly invade Hanzhou?
Half of the nation's tax revenue has
become the Wu Army's military expenses
for attacking Chen State.
Shut up!
Your Majesty.
Since she has lost her mind,
leave her alone here.
♪Even if time stops♪
♪Your silhouette
will still occupy my dreams♪
♪Circular argument proves♪
♪The unstoppable impulse brings joy♪
♪I haven't seen your smile lately♪
♪How I wish you were here♪
♪The way I exist♪
♪And the lost stories♪
♪Are not too far-fetched for you♪
♪I simply enjoy your company♪
♪Fantasizing that
we have a future together♪
♪I got used to you♪
♪Throughout the years♪
♪How do I put together an ending♪
♪I simply enjoy staying in your world♪
♪I once hoped you'd hold me to the end♪
♪Even if I had to start over♪
♪Even if I'm given endless choices♪
♪I will still♪
♪Break all the rules♪