(Grand Marshal.)
(I remember your favorite)
(is Shuozhou's beef jerky.)
I specially prepared this for you.
It was a long journey to Guishan.
Thanks, Your Majesty.
When I went to war,
it was inconvenient to cook.
During forced marches,
the beef jerky was a delicacy.
Grand Marshal.
You've fought countless battles.
Were you ever afraid?
Sure.
At first, I was indeed afraid.
I was afraid of losing my life.
I feared I wouldn't return home.
I was also afraid
I wouldn't see my family again.
But after seeing so much blood,
I came to realize
that it was useless to be afraid.
Just charge forward.
It's useless to be afraid.
You know what?
The Grand Tutor tried
to stop me from helping you many times.
So he
couldn't stop you?
Not so.
I just realized you had grown up.
Last time you came to me for help,
you played it by ear,
just like your father.
When I was young,
I was by the former king's side.
I felt there was nothing
he couldn't achieve.
He cared about the state.
He was resourceful and wise.
You fought against corruption
and made the plan this time.
Those are acts of a wise ruler.
I have not let him down.
I'm willing
to hand over Chen State
into your hands.
Rest assured, Your Majesty,
all the fallen soldiers here,
regardless of nationality,
will be buried with all due ceremony.
This is the situation,
and we all must accept it.
I'm so sorry.
At present, things are going on
as you wish.
I just hope
that these people have not died in vain.
(Yizhan Deng)
Your Majesty,
allow me to say one last thing.
Have you achieved your goal?
Is this the result
you wanted?
There's a carriage down the hill.
Long Qi, do you know the way or not?
It should be here.
- But we...
- Long Qi,
is there a person over there?
Go ask her.
Yes.
Miss.
=Episode 14=
(Isolated Village)
Chen State?
I never heard of it.
The patriarch has read a lot.
He might know.
You can ask him later.
Okay.
Zhao'er,
you're back.
Huzi.
Who are they?
They are people of Chen State.
Came from Guishan.
They want to return home.
But they got lost.
I'm taking them to see the patriarch.
Their hairstyle is different.
What is Guishan?
Where is Chen State?
Have you heard of it?
I haven't heard of it.
Is it downstream of the river
east of the village?
Definitely not.
Going downstream,
it takes a few days
to reach the great waterfall
with a sharp drop.
There's no way down.
Yes, I've heard of it.
What's going on here?
Another side quest?
So, shall we go?
Let's go.
I planned to chop wood.
Alright.
Be careful.
Mr. Fu.
Look, guests have come. Look.
Zhao'er, who are these people?
They are people of Chen.
They came from Guishan.
They want to return home.
Welcome all of you to Shangyao Village.
I'm Fu Yi, the patriarch of the village.
Sir, may I ask if this is the territory
of Chen State?
I've lived here for a long time.
But I don't know where Chen State is.
What about Wu State?
I don't know either.
Are you from the state of Chu
or Yue?
You must be
from beyond the mountains, right?
When Tong State was destroyed,
our ancestors
came here
to avoid the chaos of war.
By the time I took over as patriarch,
it had already been seven generations.
Tong State?
It was doomed long ago.
Since your clan survived,
why didn't you return?
Well.
We've settled.
It's quite nice to live here.
We are all very content.
Everyone is very content.
I see.
We came from Guishan.
We're returning home.
But we got lost.
Fortunately, this girl brought us here.
I see.
May I know how to address you?
They all call me Mr. Wang.
Mr. Wang.
Long Qi.
Mr. Long.
Caiyi.
Please just call me Xiao'er.
Xiao'er.
Look, they dress so oddly.
And they're sloppy.
Are you injured?
Huzi.
Get the physician here.
- Okay.
- They need to be treated.
Alright, I'll be right back.
Wait a second.
It's alright.
It's not my blood.
Bandits' blood.
It's good if you're fine.
It's good.
You have come from afar.
Why not rest here for a while?
Zhao'er.
Take them to the courtyard
north of the village
to have a rest.
Okay, follow me.
This way, please.
Come on.
Please.
This way, please.
A bit shabby.
I hope you won't mind it.
Of course not.
Thank you, Zhao'er.
You rest for a while.
I'm leaving.
Okay.
Your Majesty.
It's weird.
It might be a trap.
We can't totally
trust that patriarch.
Why are you getting so cautious now?
I think they look sincere.
Enough, we're all tired.
Take some rest.
We'll leave once we find a carriage.
Your Majesty.
It's getting late.
I've prepared clean clothes for you.
Why don't you stay for the night?
I'm here.
You must be starving.
I made food.
You eat while it's hot.
Go ahead.
This is the best physician here.
Mr. Fu has asked him
to treat your wounds.
Then take a look at him.
He has some bruises.
Alright, please.
Let me take the two girls to bathe
and change clothes.
Long Qi.
You stay here to look after Mr. Wang.
Yes.
Let's eat.
Let's eat first.
Xiao'er.
Zhao'er.
I made this rabbit toy.
It has an herbal scent.
It can help you sleep.
But it looks not very nice.
I hope you don't mind.
Everyone here is so thoughtful.
Outsiders rarely come here.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
Honey.
I dreamed about your rabbit toy.
You looked just like this in my dreams.
Your Majesty.
You...
I've checked.
The main room is okay.
Caiyi's room too.
I still find this place a bit strange.
So, I'll keep watch tonight.
(Your Majesty.)
(Is this the result you wanted?)
- Grand Marshal!
- Your Majesty!
Do you think their deaths
make any sense?
Dowager Zhang died for love.
She died
with the man she loved.
That may be their best end.
Though it deviated a bit from the plan,
we narrowly won in the end.
We killed Wu Liang
at the cost of dozens of men's lives.
But what we got is
that countless people
were spared from a disaster.
I think Grand Marshal would be happy
about that.
But I don't think
it was a narrow victory,
but a crushing defeat.
You think killing me will be the end?
Even if you kill me,
someone else will take over.
(After the death of King Wu,)
I found that this wasn't the end
I had imagined,
but a new beginning.
Yes,
King Wu is dead,
but the Wu Army still remains.
There will be a new king in Wu State.
Wasn't he on watch?
Who's there?
I stood guard the entire night.
It's safe.
Who gave me a blanket?
You slept like a log
the first half of the night.
I feared you'd freeze to death.
Today is a big day for our village.
You two are the most skillful
and strongest people in our village.
Butcher two pigs
and 25 chickens.
Come on.
Remember,
make sure to bleed the pigs.
- No problem.
- Go on.
Let's go.
Mr. Fu.
Is the carriage we need ready?
Oh right.
My memory
is getting worse.
Huzi.
Go and check if the carriage is ready.
Okay.
I'll go have a look.
I guess you haven't had breakfast.
Zhao'er, get some food ready
for the guests.
Okay.
It's still early now.
Please have a seat over there.
Breakfast will be ready soon.
Please.
Here are the dumplings.
Thank you, Zhao'er.
Thank you.
By the way,
why are those tables all put together?
Is it for a banquet?
Yes, on a happy occasion,
every household will
bring their own chairs and tables
and wine and dishes together.
It's so lively.
Really nice.
Mr. Fu.
It's all simple food.
Are you all accustomed to it?
- Delicious.
- It's already very good.
Mr. Fu, is our carriage ready?
Our villagers
rarely use carriages.
Yesterday, we found a problem
with the axle.
I'm not sure if it's already fixed.
There's another thing.
There are few people in our village.
Could I trouble you to do me a favor?
What is it?
Slow down.
How is it?
Ten centimeters further to the left.
What?
Ten centimeters is...
Three cun.
Three cun to the left.
Got it.
It's good now.
Let me do it.
Mr. Fu.
Is the axle already fixed?
It should be fine now.
That's good.
Huzi.
The axle is already fixed?
Axle?
There's no problem with that.
Once we finish hanging the lanterns,
we will set off.
Wait.
Axle?
Is the axle broken?
Mr. Fu.
The axle is okay.
Since the axle is already fixed,
we should set off.
When I arrive home,
I'll have someone
send the carriage back.
I'll also give you a big gift.
For the bride and groom.
Mr. Wang.
We're done.
Good.
Mr. Fu.
We're leaving.
It's time.
If there is a chance,
we will come back to visit you again.
Mr. Wang,
we mean no harm.
We sincerely invite you to stay
for a meal
and a drink.
You are in such a hurry to rush back.
Is there something important?
Yes.
It's a happy thing
to come to the wedding banquet.
Why not stay
and have a good time?
Xiao'er,
Mr. Wang, don't leave.
Stay, please.
What do you think?
Since it's a banquet,
we'll stay and join in the fun.
Great.
What are you doing?
Your Majesty, it takes so long to fish.
I'll go catch some fish for you.
It's fine.
I want to catch a fish by myself.
I'll be quick.
Caiyi.
You hold my sword.
No need.
I want to catch a fish by myself.
I'll be over there.
I won't disturb you.
I want to catch a fish by myself.
Long Qi.
Let him fish by himself.
You and Caiyi go to the kitchen
and prepare the ingredients.
Get the stove ready.
We'll be there later.
Yes.
Honey.
I just want to sit here quietly
and catch a fish myself.
I know.
I'm with you.
Mr. Wang.
Mr. Wang, you're good at cooking.
Come on.
You must try this fish.
Pour a drink.
Pour a drink for you.
Come on.
Mr. Wang cooked the fish.
It's so delicious.
Indeed, it is good.
Good!
Here they are.
Congratulations.
♪Even if time stops♪
♪Your silhouette
will still occupy my dreams♪
♪Circular argument proves♪
♪The unstoppable impulse brings joy♪
♪I haven't seen your smile lately♪
♪How I wish you were here♪
♪The way I exist♪
♪And the lost stories♪
♪Are not too far-fetched for you♪
♪I simply enjoy your company♪
♪Fantasizing that
we have a future together♪
♪I got used to you♪
♪Throughout the years♪
♪How do I put together an ending♪
♪I simply enjoy staying in your world♪
♪I once hoped you'd hold me to the end♪
♪Even if I had to start over♪
♪Even if I'm given endless choices♪
♪I will still♪
♪Break all the rules♪