Detroiters
season 11
If you can't get through the gate,
you can't repair the神经元.
It's just a waste of resources.
Someone came here to hurt you?
How can you inform you
about the crime and the Got nothin' to do with it?
It's good.
I should have just escaped first.
Tutor immortal
The begginer,
Please input the urgent training center in thirty seconds.
Otherwise they will start the alarm device
In sea and system
Emergency training center
They've got ten seconds before the alarm
Seven seconds.
Six seconds.
Five seconds.
Four seconds.
Three seconds.
Two seconds.
Without my red devil certification,
you can't enter the system.
Are you going to help him pass the test?
I can't watch him like this.
I won't do anything.
First, no one can change the game's script.
Even I can't.
Second, you help him solve the difficulties he faces.
It changes the way we make him face difficulties.
Solving the difficulties.
That's the essence of this.
If you want to save him,
you can only make him face difficulties alone.
And finally wake up.
But now it seems
it's too hard for him.
I always think you're a rational person.
You should understand that there are too many people
in this world who are as lucky as him.
Every day, every hour, every moment,
some people die because of radiation.
Everyone must live on.
One day after another.
Doctor, you don't want your experiment to end so soon, do you?
You also want to see him
repair the brain nerve in your experiment, right?
This will be a great achievement for the civilization.
Let me go in
and choose the strongest supporting role.
For example,
for example, Goddess of Dance.
Okay.
But you can't use the special skills of Goddess of Dance to help him.
I know.
I will only use the role of Goddess of Dance
to guide him
to face difficulties and solve them.
If that's the case, it's doable.
Do you know where the boundary is?
I know. I know it very well.
I want to say one more thing.
Why do you insist on doing all this?
You should understand that
as the manager of the core project of the brain brain group,
you have enough conditions to live on.
Even after a short time,
you have better survival conditions.
Do you think it's a mistake?
About what?
Why?
Why are you asking me?
I don't want to say it.
You don't want to say it?
I just breastfeed them.
So I...
You just...
You just breastfeed them.
My brand is Medx.
I just...
I'm worried about him.
I just want to confirm his gender.
I can control him.
The female god of martial arts.
It is necessary to remind you that after entering that world, all players will lose the foundation of the real world.
The
Where are you taking me?
Cold Palace.
To save Chen Xiaohua.
Are you sure you want to save her?
Although she is the eldest son of the former king, she has never been out of the Cold Palace.
I have also given her a chance.
But she is waiting for death all day long.
She has never done anything that is beneficial to the country.
She will only be happy.
I am sure that as long as she is released and returned to her throne,
she will focus on the government and lead the country.
All right.
It is enough to have you.
But you should not forget to promise me.
In case there is no country to break.
I promise you.
The former king.
You are right.
Izo.
The remaining chimneys.
I'm not sure if I can do it.
The King's Avatar
Episode 11
Honey,
do you think
I'm a failure?
No.
You've got the people of Chen
to come to Dayu
and punish the corrupt officials for them.
But the ministers
are usually
caught and chopped.
The King's Avatar
will break through the barrier and kill them at any time.
If it's really
like what Eunuch Li said,
the King's Avatar
will be in the capital in less than half a month.
Do you regret checking the accounts?
No.
Because the Qi Yu scene
is the first time in my life
I've seen your conviction.
This is definitely
the most important thing in my life.
For you,
I'm willing to do anything.
I want to make Chen State strong
and conquer the Five Kingdoms.
Then,
I'll go to the Ten-Nine Heavens with you.
It's over.
But what if
we can't conquer the Five Kingdoms?
In my eyes,
Chen State is like this lake.
I
watch them from afar
and see them
fight for power and power.
But I don't care.
I don't care
what they do.
Because in my opinion,
I'll leave here sooner or later.
Leave this lake
and not be the king.
Do you still think so?
Now I realize
I'm not standing by the shore.
I'm like them.
I can't get out of this lake.
When I have the courage
to look at this lake,
I find it's about to
disappear.
The lake is always there.
As long as you have the courage to face it,
everything is not over.
Everything is not over.
Really?
I believe you.
Wife.
Remember.
No matter what happens,
I'll be with you.
Your Majesty,
Grand Tutor Wang wants to see you.
Your Majesty.
I'm guilty.
I read the book.
I read more than half of the book.
I'm guilty.
I'm guilty, Your Majesty.
Forget it.
Let's call it a day.
Your Majesty.
I've made up my mind.
Tomorrow morning,
I'll resign
all the things in the court
and retire.
Grand Tutor, you can't go.
Your Majesty.
I'm guilty, too.
I was reckless.
I misjudged and misjudged.
I misjudged.
I'm willing to give up all my military power
and let you deal with it.
You...
I've said it.
The case of the corruption case is over.
You two are not friends at all.
Now the enemy of the Wu State is in front.
You don't care about it?
What?
Do you want me to fight against the Wu State alone?
The innocent are innocent.
You two are both the veterans of the two dynasties.
When the former king was alive,
the state of Chen was in a good state.
The power of the Wu State was strong.
Now the Wu State is going to invade our state.
Our state is weak.
If I still say something wrong,
if I still say something wrong,
it's my fault.
Report!
Your Majesty, I report to you.
The Wu State has been under the hand of the Han State.
They have been attacking and coming straight to the capital.
They are about to leave the capital.
They are less than 200 miles away.
Impossible.
The border between the capital and Chenwu
is separated by Han State and the border between Kang and Shaozhou.
How can it be so fast?
Your Majesty,
the border between Kang and Shaozhou is also narrow.
It's not safe to go there.
Kang and Shaozhou are still in danger.
I know.
Leave.
Yes.
If there's any more news, report it quickly.
Wait.
I'll be back soon.
Eunuch Li
didn't lie at least.
He only went to the capital
within half a month.
Old man,
they are at the gate of the house.
You still want to report to me?
You...
I'm not a coward.
Fine.
Then join hands with me to fight against the Wu State.
Let them see
that the Chen State is not easy to bully.
I'm guilty.
I deserve to die.
But the war is on.
After this battle,
I'll let Wang Chu Zhen do it.
We should gather all resources
and set up the city.
This is the best time.
Minister,
if the Wu State goes there
in a full speed, how long will it take?
Three days.
Three...
Three days to the capital?
Yes.
The Wu State is in danger.
We should go there.
Yes.
My wife.
I want to eat fish.
I'll call the doctor.
No.
I'll do it myself.
Okay.
We'll have dinner when we arrive.
Greetings, Your Majesty and Consort Rong.
Leave us.
Yes.
I just need it.
Okay.
Come and help me.
Let's go.
Don't be scared.
Let's use this big knife.
Cut the green onion for the fish.
Cai Yi.
Do you people
all like sweet things?
I know that
Long Qi secretly
gives you my sweet food.
If I remember correctly,
your favorite sweet food should be
osmanthus cake.
I read in the book that
every time it's spring,
the osmanthus fragrance is all over the country.
The osmanthus fragrance is all over the country.
I really want to go there.
You haven't been back for a long time.
You must miss home.
Cai Yi.
The war is coming.
If not,
you should go back.
Don't worry about
the Princess Consort.
I know.
The person you're most worried about
must be the head of the fish.
To be honest,
the head of the fish
really likes you.
If it weren't for the war,
I would have brought it to you
and made it say
what it was thinking.
Then,
I'll give you a long vacation.
You can go to the world
and eat what you should eat
and drink what you should drink.
Do whatever you want.
Actually,
I envy you.
You see,
Jiu Jiu and I
are so in love.
We just want to live
a normal life.
But if we can do it,
we can't win this battle.
In this way,
it's really good
to be with you.
Wang,
I brought the wine.
It's so hot.
I, Zhang Jinlong, have no future in this life.
I've been alone all my life.
I'm just Chen Guoluo.
Master.
I've been so gorgeous to you.
Was it because
I caused you become like that?
Because it's about you
I'm someone else.
You pushed me away.
I knew it.
But I still
china
It's been a long field day,
so why did you just walk away from me?
Back.
Chenzhou's army were strong in formation.
Zhaodu's Fan Li
fought four driveiors
with me and the former King of Qin.
They needed me there to kill them.
Chenzhou and your capital usage of ten days.
We just need to prolong that.
After Yuanbin arrives,
It's impossible.
The escort troops are so fast.
It must be Hu Xiaogu.
I'm afraid the guards who went to the city
must be very dangerous.
They're all here.
Let's go and meet them.
Princess.
The escort troops are coming.
Your highness, somebody cards the sketchbook.
allows the 노래入歌
Yes.
I did find the sketchbook.
Blade mirror source.
The authentic signature at the Darong calm.
Go, go, go.
Your Majesty.
Yes.
I think there's a trap.
Let him go.
Your Majesty.
Now Wu Jun didn't go to the city.
The city is not in danger.
There's still a chance for you to escape.
With me and Da Si Ma here,
Liu De and Qing Shan are still in the city.
I'm afraid they haven't been eliminated.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
Once the reinforcements arrive,
they will come back to save us.
There's no Prince Qin's body.
I'm sure.
The tree fell and the tiger was scattered.
Either the elephant fell,
or the official died.
But since the escape city
can save lives,
it's time to leave.
The country can be broken.
But the people are still here.
I'm the King.
I have to stay.
Protect the Crown Prince.
I'll be with you.
Let's go.
Madam.
There's a noise outside.
The soldiers are missing.
I'm afraid Wu Jun is coming in.
Madam.
The King is here to see you.
Wake up.
Madam.
The King is here to see you.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Greetings, Minister of War.
None of the brothers
of the Tiger Valley
have returned yet.
How many soldiers are there in the city?
I don't know.
Where is Lord Yu?
Yu...
The west gate is still open.
Let's escort the people to leave the city.
Yes.
Li's Mansion
Chen Xiao Hua.
Stop struggling.
Open the city gate and hand in the jade seal.
I'll spare your life
and let you be a rich and virtuous man.
You just said to open the gate.
If you're capable,
then come up yourself.
Our Chen State
is in a difficult situation.
We have enough food supplies.
If you don't prepare for ten days and half a month,
then hurry and go back.
I'm telling you.
In a few hours,
my soldiers
will have your asses wrapped.
I'll persuade you to go back
and fight with me.
I'll give you
a good laugh
from the old man who died of bone cancer.
Do you think I can't get in?
If you can get in,
then why bother talking?
Okay.
Come with me.
The city gate is closed.
Let's go.
Yes.
There are spies inside.
Lord Ping.
Go and guard the gate.
Yes.
Kill.
Lord Ping.
The city gate is closed.
Chen State is in danger.
I'll go and guard the gate for you.
Long Qi.
Lord Ping.
Long Qi has been in a bad situation all his life.
It's my fortune
to be with you.
If there's a next life,
I'm willing to be your bodyguard.
Cai Yi.
Next life.
I hope we can meet sooner.
Long Qi.
Wang.
You are the one chosen by the God.
No more gratitude.
I'll repay you in the next life.
Smile for me.
Be natural.
Have no fear of danger.
Be ready to fight quickly.
Now,
it's time for you to fulfill your promise.
How?
I'm not afraid of danger.
You have to do it.
I want to do it.
But I can't.
What do you mean?
I can't protect Chen Wen
through my power.
I can't protect Chui San Hua.
Why?
I'm a Martial Soul,
but I'm not.
What...
What are you talking about?
You can't use the special skill of the Martial Soul.
If you want to save him,
you can only make him face difficulties alone
and wake up.
I know
you must be in pain now.
But you'll only hurt him
if you do it now.
Circle your forehead.
Don't move.
Your back is off.
Big yao,
take a good rest,
and wait for the time to return.
Okay!
Please,
Ama!
No,
don't move.
Don't move!
Ama!
If you don't show your skills,
the gate of Chen State
will be opened by yourself.
You'd better surrender.
If you have the ability,
why are you playing with your mouth?
Come on.
Wait for me.
Go.
Kill.
A spring water flows into the mortal world.
The sky is still cold.
The sea is dry and the mountains are broken.
Even if there is no limit, it is just a dream.
The land is scattered.
The mountains and rivers are not dry.
The past is the grudge of victory.
The cold rain comes and goes.
The wind blows.
The people are all different.
Who is in the deep of the autumn?
The rain is light and the wind is strong.
The End