After a short break
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to do this, but I'm going to try.
I'm going to try to get the best out of this.
It's dangerous.
No, I don't understand.
What is it that you have to say?
I've actually told you many times.
But I don't think you'll believe me.
I believe everything you say.
I'm actually a man of the heavens.
You must be.
I can be reborn.
And I checked the accounts of the last life.
I caught a lot of important officials.
But then, the five countries invaded the capital.
You all died.
The last life and the last life, and the last life.
I actually have a wife.
Her name is Mrs. Xiao.
She's different from everyone.
She thinks I can be a good king.
But in the end, I still failed.
Do you understand?
If you don't understand anything, just ask.
Although it sounds a bit ridiculous,
I believe in you.
The point is, do you really have no impression of Zhang Xiao'er?
I don't know.
But I think His Majesty must really love Mrs. Xiao.
Do you think I'm crazy?
If His Majesty says so,
this time, are we going to attack?
Maybe.
I still didn't go to the morning court today.
I thought that when Qu Yu came back,
he would change his mood.
And also,
he's been looking for a beauty lately.
He said it was his own concubine.
The imperial guards all went out.
They searched the whole capital but couldn't find her.
Little bastard.
You're determined to be a king.
That's good.
That's good too.
The more he came to pick me up,
the closer we are.
King, what are we going to do next?
Fishing.
And then?
Still fishing.
At this moment, the army of the Wu Army is pressing in.
Shouldn't you be looking at the bright side and deploy against the Wu?
I don't want to.
Why?
I can't do anything.
I thought that I could save Chen Gu Yu from the fire
by chasing back the sleeping camp.
But I didn't expect that
it would speed up the progress of the Wu.
I don't want to see you and everyone
die in front of me.
King, don't worry.
I'm going to live well.
Yes.
As a human being,
you have to live well.
Then you say,
if I don't do anything,
maybe the result will be different.
You don't have to die.
He doesn't have to disappear.
King, I don't understand.
But if one day,
I die because of you,
I will not live alone.
Enough.
What do you mean by die?
You have to live well.
Brother.
Silly fish.
The most tempting is the most dangerous.
Why are you so silly?
I thought that the king's thunderous means
of punishing, corrupting and attacking the national treasury
had been directed by the Ming army.
I didn't expect to go back to the past.
I heard that
he buried the chicken of General Changsheng
and cried all afternoon.
I heard it.
The enemy is in front of us.
Is he afraid or
he has other intentions?
Dr. Wang,
you think too highly of him.
What does he want from another intention?
Tell me now.
How can he stop the enemy from coming?
He is hoping that King Wu will withdraw his troops.
I think that the king
is different from before.
I can't say it,
but I can feel it.
He couldn't do it before.
He did it in the court that day.
That kind of thing.
In public, I hugged you, Dr. Wang.
Master,
don't make jokes.
But I believe that
the king will not sit and wait.
I hope so.
News.
Sometimes I wonder
if he really appeared.
I'm not sure about it.
Long Qian,
is it possible that
I just had a dream
and he came out of my dream?
Wang,
after inquiring,
I found out that
this is the token
that was given to the mountain.
Wang,
the mountain is located in the intersection
of Chen, Wu, Chu, Yue,
and the four countries.
The area is mixed with fish and dragon.
Due to the danger of the terrain,
it has become a place
outside the power of the countries.
It is also the center of the trade
of the people of various countries.
So,
it is possible that
the jade seal is in the mountain.
Jade seal?
Jade seal.
Wife,
did I do something wrong?
I didn't be a qualified king
like you said.
The innocent people
are about to be beaten.
But this time,
why are you not here?
The
Good news.
I just upgraded the whole system.
If you go in again,
you can keep
all the memories of the real world.
Really?
That's great.
But,
I always talk about it.
You can't do it for him anymore.
I know.
Let me in.
Cai Ji.
I knew you would come back.
Do you know
that you were not here for a while?
They all said I had a disease.
They said I was looking for
someone who didn't exist.
Wife,
where are you?
Do you know...
Chen Xiaohua,
do you know
that you will die if you do this?
Then you will really die.
I will kill you.
Then you will never get out of here.
You can just
take a bath in the real world.
You have been here for so long.
You still do nothing
and ignore the court.
Do you know
how much effort I have put into saving you?
Can you give me a break?
Wife,
what are you talking about?
Are you my wife?
Yes,
I am your wife.
You are not dreaming.
Do you want me to
repeat that password for you?
You have a birthmark on your waist.
You always talk when you eat.
You snore when you sleep.
Do you want me to repeat that?
Wife,
Wang,
Longxian,
I told you,
my wife,
Mrs. Xiao,
Princess Consort.
You, you remember?
How could I not know Princess Consort?
Chen Xiaohua.
No,
I know.
If you are my second son,
I will ignore the court.
That's because you are gone.
If I am gone,
you can stop working.
You can stop doing anything.
The five-storied tree
is almost at the door of the house.
What have you done?
Do you want to see everyone
die again?
Longxian,
my wife is angry.
Wife.
Chen Xiaohua,
listen to me
carefully.
Everything here
is fake.
It's fake.
This is a game world.
This is a world.
Longqi
and everyone around you,
including the whole Chen State,
are all fake.
They don't exist.
Do you understand?
You must now
win this virtual game
with your own efforts
to defeat Wu State
and become an excellent monarch
so that you can survive.
Game?
Longqi,
do you understand
the virtual game?
No.
I don't understand either.
Wife, what do you mean?
You once said
that after this game,
you would take me to the Nine Heavens.
But with your current situation,
I don't think I can wait until that day.
So I beg you,
can you be more mature?
How am I not mature?
Have you tried your best?
How did I try my best?
You ask Longqi.
I even asked her to find the jade shoes.
We spent a lot of money, right?
Yes.
Did you find it?
Not yet.
But now I have an idea
that will definitely turn the tables.
Just you?
What idea can you come up with?
Yes.
Just me, Chen Xiaohua,
have an excellent idea.
And this time,
I have to see it
by myself.
Longqi.
Let's go.
Your Majesty.
Longqi doesn't understand.
You always love Mrs. Xiao the most.
Don't you think she's a little bit more fierce this time?
It's totally different from before.
Your Majesty.
Was she not fierce before?
What are you talking about?
Your Majesty, what should we do next?
Where is the bamboo?
Bamboo?
Your Majesty.
Okay.
Go.
We must find the way to the mountain
to get through the jade seal.
Benlong, do you know the way to the mountain?
You underestimate our secret position.
We've learned how to survive in the wild.
We can survive in the wild
through the sun, moon and stars.
You're really good at talking.
I'm really good at it.
Your Majesty, we have to climb the mountain
when we get to the bottom of the mountain.
I told you.
After you leave the palace,
don't call me Wang.
Call me Young Master.
Yes.
Young Master Wang, can you climb the mountain?
What are you talking about?
I'm a man of my word.
It's hard for me to do that.
We're here.
Let's go.
Go.
Sprンド
Sit down.
Wang, you still have a long way to go.
How about I carry you?
Carry what?
What do you mean?
I'm not Cai Ji.
Wang, slow down.
Fenlong, are you sure this is the right way?
This is not right.
It should be here.
Did you get the wrong intersection?
Which intersection?
Is it at the big stone?
Isn't it 20 miles away?
Chenguo is safe.
Isn't it like living in the wild?
You're a murderer.
Don't talk nonsense.
What have you done all the way?
You didn't do anything, and you're still jumping around.
How did I do nothing?
You make it clear.
You...
Take it.
What?
You're a man, and you want me to carry your bag?
And,
the Princess Consort asked me to follow you, to monitor you,
not to serve you.
You're a murderer.
Me?
I'm a murderer.
I've never lied to you.
I made a bet with the Princess Consort.
I'll see if Wang will keep being stupid.
Now,
I'll be the Princess Consort's maid,
and I'll be with Wang to protect him for a long time.
How can you say that?
What's wrong?
You said,
am I really stupid?
No, Wang...
No, Young Master.
I'm stupid.
What Cai Yi said is right.
Wang...
What are you doing?
You're smart, aren't you?
You don't know what to do.
Why did you say that?
I didn't mean it.
You're the one who's mad at me.
That's not what I meant.
What should I do?
This time, you must find the jade seal
and prove to my wife that
I can do it.
Young Master, follow me.
Young Master, I'll go and have a look.
Young Master,
we found two suspicious people.
There's no food.
You're not hungry.
How many things are you preparing?
I'm innocent, sir.
We just came here.
We didn't mean to rush you.
Please forgive us, sir.
Please forgive us.
Tell me.
What are you two doing?
Sir,
we're merchants
of the Shanjing Prefecture.
From Kang?
Long Qing,
he doesn't look like a bad guy.
It's not easy to do business.
Let him go.
Merchants.
Merchants have so many old ladies.
It's hard to do business.
They're not mercenaries.
Tell me the truth.
I'll let you go.
Say it.
We're soldiers of the Shanjing Prefecture.
A while ago,
the Shouhu Army was about to attack
and the border was in chaos.
My brothers
said the war was about to start.
The King of Chen was in a daze.
He was on the battlefield.
He should have fled.
He was dead when he was attacked.
He was dead when he was captured.
He was still alive.
He was out of military power for months.
We all ran away
as soon as we got together.
So,
you don't want to die for the King of Chen.
Exactly.
My wife and kids are waiting for him.
My brother is waiting for my sister.
We're going to the temple now.
We're not willing to die.
We are.
Let's go.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
We have to hurry.
We should be there soon.
How many times have you said that?
Look.
Let's go.
I told you we wouldn't go wrong.
Caiyi.
If I stand up one day,
don't do anything behind my back.
I want to understand.
Let's go.
Water.
Are you thirsty?
Sir,
do we still have buns?
we came from a long way.
It's dark here.
There's nothing to eat.
Can we still make buns?
We've sold out the buns.
Only these three left.
You can eat the buns in the morning.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
Eat.
You came from a long way.
Yes, I came from a long way.
Thank you.
What does he mean?
I don't know.
But he doesn't look like a beggar.
Then what should we do?
Forget it.
It's so late.
We're tired.
Let's find a place to stay.
Let's go.
This is the best inn in Guishan.
The whole Guishan is a one-way inn.
Let's go.
Sir,
three rooms.
Three rooms are all closed.
The bed sheets and the bedding need to be new.
No rooms.
No rooms?
Then the best room here
is three rooms.
Sir,
we came from a long way.
We have money.
We can't afford it.
We came from a long way.
We have money.
Let's see how we can afford it.
You're good friends.
You deserve it.
How dare you!
Do you know who he is?
He can be anyone.
It's up to me.
Sir,
we're not here to make trouble.
We just want to know
how we can afford it.
You have money, right?
Okay.
This room.
Humph.
He dares to ask us for so much money in this room?
It's a black shop.
I'll go find him.
Enough.
Don't get angry.
We came from a long way.
We need to be low-key.
He's so arrogant.
He must be reasonable.
Everything is important in the big picture.
Sir,
you've changed.
How?
You never said
the big picture before.
Enough.
Go and see Caiyi.
Don't let anything happen to Caiyi.
I'm going to the bathroom.
What are you doing?
What do you mean?
I...
Mr. Wang asked me to see you
in case you were taken away by the wolf.
But I think
even if the wolf comes,
it will be killed by you.
You...
Tell Mr. Wang
to call me if the wolf comes.
It's useless to have you as a guard.
I'm here.
I'm taking off my clothes.
Close the door.
Wang.
Wang Xin.
Let's sleep in the same bed tonight.
No.
I can't do that.
I'll sleep on the floor.
Where's Caiyi?
He's fine.
I'm exhausted.
Aren't you?
Wang, take a rest.
I think this place is a little strange.
I'll give you a hand tonight.
Yes.
This place is really strange.
But if you're tired,
who's going to protect me?
Why are you still standing?
Sit down.
Sit.
Mom.
I really think you've changed.
I said it.
What did you call me?
Young Master.
In the past,
the ministers always said
that you didn't go to the court
and that you were just trying to get the government.
But I know
that you didn't want to take care of it.
You just wanted to be a good son.
You didn't want to be a good son.
But you couldn't.
Young Master is actually
a very gentle person.
You are very good to everyone.
You are responsible for us.
But this responsibility is too great.
If it were me,
I might have done it before you.
Don't misunderstand.
I didn't mean to slander.
I...
All right.
I know.
You never hit or
slashed anyone.
Including the beggar today.
You are also very good to him.
But I always feel
that in your eyes,
we are all human beings.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Silly boy.
What are you not human beings?
I mean,
you never treated us as servants.
The girl next door
is the assassin who killed you
because she was a
murderer of Wu Guo.
You treated her the same way.
You really care about her life.
In my opinion,
we are all the same.
You are the one who
protects me.
And now,
I just want to be myself
and be the king of Chen.
Let my wife look up to me
and not look down on me.
I don't want you
to die under the sword of Wu Jun.
Because the Grand Tutor said
that life is short
and the grass is long.
Life is short,
but it can't be wasted.
They can kill me.
But if you,
you,
your wife,
Grand Tutor Wang,
and the Grand Tutor
die,
I will not allow it.