Mr. Shao
your Peacock Feather might not be recoverable.
But I've found
the real murderer of Yun Lingke.
This is Yun Lingke's costume.
Mr. Shao.
Now we just need to go to the county office together to report this injustice,
and we'll surely get justice for you.
I believe what you truly want
is to clear your name,
not the Peacock Feather.
Thank you, Young Master Chu.
Shao Heng,
you've accused Cheng Tianci and Wang Pengshu
of plotting against Yun Lingke.
Present your evidence immediately.
Your Honor,
this is the costume worn by the missing person Yun Lingke
before his disappearance.
It originally had peacock feathers attached to it,
but they were removed.
And this item was found in Cheng Tianci's residence.
Cheng Tianci.
How do you explain this?
Your Honor.
How could I not know this item was in my residence?
If it was found in my home,
someone must be framing me.
Who is this person?
I have yet to find out.
Your Honor.
I can testify.
The theatrical costume was indeed kept at Cheng Tianci's residence.
Not only that,
his secret chamber contained various torture instruments.
That beast Cheng Tianci
tortured me repeatedly with hot irons and other cruel methods,
making me wish I were dead.
He imprisoned others in his secret chamber too.
I saw with my own eyes
people who were taken into that chamber
and never came out again.
And before that,
he used the same methods
to torture Yun Ling to death.
Who knows how many
young men and women in their prime
have been destroyed by your beastly hands.
Cheng Tianci,
when you brought men to silence witnesses last night,
I left a dagger wound on your right leg.
Do you dare to show it in court?
Cheng Tianci,
what do you have to say for yourself?
Your Honor,
this Achun is working with them.
His words cannot be trusted.
This wound was accidentally caused during sword practice yesterday,
it has nothing to do with this case.
Then why
do I know the exact location of your wound?
Are we close friends?
Get to work now!
The magistrate ordered
that everything must be burned completely.
By order of the county magistrate,
I'm here to search for evidence.
Anyone attempting to destroy evidence
will be severely punished.
Constable Li, follow me.
Brother Chu has already told me
where that item is.
Your Honor,
Wang Pengshu's servant Bai Yue is willing to testify
that he was once in a secret room at the Cheng residence
where Cheng Tianci tortured him severely.
Please help this humble citizen, Your Honor,
the scars on my body can serve as evidence.
Your Honor,
I've brought important evidence.
This was found in Cheng Tianci's residence,
discovered during a search of the secret room.
Your Honor,
may I take a look?
Sir
these black fragments
are indeed the burned peacock feathers.
Master Shao's repeated reports
weren't to recover the peacock feathers,
but to seek justice for his beloved apprentice.
Master Shao.
I was a coward,
afraid they would silence me permanently,
too scared to report Cheng Tianci and Wang Pengshu
for murdering my apprentice.
I could only pretend to be looking for the peacock feathers,
while actually seeking an excuse
to expose these beasts' evil deeds to the authorities.
Sir,
I have nothing to do with this matter,
it was all Cheng Tianci's doing.
I was forced against my will,
please consider this, Your Honor.
Cheng Tianci, Wang Pengshu,
you two have conspired together
to harm innocent people.
The ashes in this jade dish are evidence enough.
What's even more absurd
is that you both worship evil spirits
and foolishly believe dark magic can protect you.
You are both ignorant and shameless,
truly unforgivable.
By my order,
take Cheng Tianci and Wang Pengshu to prison,
remove them!
Thank you for your wisdom, Sir.
Sir, I've been wronged!
Thank you for your justice, Sir.
Thank you, Sir.
Master Chu.
These 700 taels in bank notes are the final payment I owe you.
Now that Yun Lingke's case
has finally been resolved.
This is the reward you deserve.
Master Shao.
I cannot accept this money.
You've kept this theater troupe going all these years,
which hasn't been easy.
Master Chu.
If you don't accept it,
my conscience won't be at peace.
If it weren't for you,
this case would
never have been solved.
These old bones of mine
would have no reason to keep living.
Isn't teaching and passing on knowledge meaningful enough?
For solving this case,
the magistrate has already given me a reward.
I'm quite content with that.
You and the Chunqiu Troupe
need this money more than I do.
I've performed countless operas in my lifetime.
I've played many heroes.
I always thought that honor among men
was just fiction from storybooks.
Until I met you,
I never truly understood the meaning of chivalry and righteousness.
Thank you for your praise, Master Shao.
I will keep your words in my heart
and uphold the code of chivalry,
being strict with myself.
No matter what obstacles I face,
I will press forward bravely,
not disappointing your expectations nor dishonoring the name of a hero.
This resolve will never change.
Why are you crying?
Ji'an.
Here's 200 taels.
Take it.
Take good care of yourself
and the children too.
Please visit Little Five and Little Seven for me often.
This reunion
lasted longer than planned,
but it's given me peace of mind.
Brother Chu,
I can't accept this money.
You'll need it for your journey.
There will be many expenses.
I can't help share more of your burden,
I already feel so guilty and ashamed.
Don't blame yourself.
No one could have done better than you.
You'll always be our dearest little Ji'an.
I'm leaving.
Are you
really leaving this time?
With this farewell,
you must take good care of yourself
and don't worry about us.
The path ahead of us is filled with thorns,
and who knows when we'll meet again.
Take care.
Don't see us off.
Hurry back to your porridge shop.
Brother Chu,
when will the government reward be paid?
Even 1,000 taels would be good.
You're always deceiving me,
making me lose money on deals.
One shouldn't be too greedy in life.
Brother Chu.
Brother Liang.
I'll always be here
waiting for you to return.
Please take good care of yourselves.
Chu Bufan.
This time I'm really leaving.
Hurry up!
Once I leave,
who knows when we'll see each other again.
If it's meant to be, we'll meet again.
You're lying again.
Why so sad?
Tongzhou may be big,
but we always managed to run into each other.
But this time,
I'm afraid we might never see each other again.
Meeting or not meeting,
it's all part of life's destiny.
Sometimes,
seeing each other isn't the only way to express our feelings.
Between these meetings and partings,
we've learned to grow and cherish what we have,
haven't we?
I know
you have important things to do.
I don't know if I should say certain things.
You understand me,
and I understand you,
just like Sister Yun understands me.
I still want to say it.
When we first met,
I thought we were a perfect match.
But then,
my life took an unexpected turn.
I felt I was no longer worthy of you.
But I could feel
that you never looked down on me.
That's how fate works,
we met the right person
at the wrong time.
We can't force things.
Having met you
is enough for me.
May everything go well for you
and may you find peace and joy.
Ruoting.
You're wonderful.
You've always been wonderful,
never letting external circumstances
change your true nature.
All the hardships you've endured
are, to me,
nothing but cruel twists of fate,
not flaws within yourself.
How could the ups and downs of life
ever easily define
what we mean to each other?
Though time may be chaotic now
and the path rough,
your place in my heart
remains irreplaceable.
I also wish that your future
will be filled with happiness.
This is my gift to you.
Open it after I'm gone.
Chu Bufan,
no matter where you are
or what you do,
I hope you'll stay true to yourself
and do what you really want to do.
Ruoting,
be happy
and take good care of yourself.
Take care.
Brother Chu,
she's gone now.
Let's get going too.
Ruoting.
Having someone to talk to is already a great blessing.
But in life,
wherever there are choices, there will be regrets.
I have important matters to attend to
and cannot accompany you.
I only hope we both find our own happiness.
Goodbye,
Ruting.