Here it comes.
I am willing to be as a star, as a king, as a moon.
The world is here.
We are here.
I only want to watch every star day with my beloved.
I want to be with you forever.
The first demon is the master.
You and him are not the same person.
A demon is a star.
The world is here.
We are here.
I want you to tell the gods that the goddess of the stars will marry into the demon clan.
And then marry me in ten days.
What did you say?
Your memory...
It's boring to kill you or hurt you or be killed by you.
The goddess of the stars is in the world.
If you marry me, you will be the biggest insult to the gods.
Of course.
The gods can reject me.
But in ten days, the wedding will be a long and long one.
No matter what the ceremony is, I am happy to see it.
A marriage is a life.
The gods will choose it.
I have finished the wedding.
In ten days,
the goddess of the demons will be angry.
Do you really want to marry me?
Yes.
You are the goddess of the stars who is the highest and highest, right?
She is so worthy of your life.
The long and long demon clan is the cause of my three years of life.
The gods are so precious.
The lives of the world are so precious.
Since the demon gods are so suspicious about the past,
I am like the demon god.
It's just a wedding.
The life of the world is so precious.
The goddess of the stars loves the world so much.
In ten days,
I will marry the gods and be the gods.
Even if you only have hatred for me,
but before I disappear,
I can still stay by your side in this way.
Even if only ten days are left.
I didn't expect the gods to sleep so peacefully in the demon clan.
I have been here for a long time.
These are all the things that the elders have been used to.
Since you are awake,
you can choose yourself.
The demon clan is in the dark.
The gods still love to protect their bodies.
I don't want to marry the gods after ten days.
I am marrying a sick person.
How come your face is so pale?
Are you really sick?
I am not.
I am just a sick person.
Are you really sick?
I am not sick.
I am just a sick person.
Really?
If you are not used to it,
you can stay here and naturally become used to it.
If you are not used to the other people's worries,
you can choose yourself.
Qingyue, if we can be together,
if we can have each other again,
I think I will be very happy.
Why are you not coming to see me?
It's been a hundred years.
The gods of Demon God are getting stronger.
There are only three days left to get married.
You came here at this time.
You should have come earlier.
Why do you have to pretend to be stupid?
I made an appointment with you.
When I was in the battle with Xing Yue,
you destroyed the Star Moon Palace.
After the trial, we were together.
But you were so annoying.
You wasted my chance to plan it.
I made an appointment with you.
You destroyed the Star Moon Palace.
But I said that
the people who win the battle
are the gods of the hell.
But we have not succeeded.
We have already done it.
Besides, it's been a hundred years.
I'm afraid that today you came here
to do this.
I came here today
to take Xing Yue away.
He will become my god.
Don't be so selfish.
He won't fall in love with you.
Otherwise, how could you be so weak
in the battle with Xing Yue three years ago?
How do you know?
I have never
ever seen this pair of eyes.
Then you don't need to keep these eyes.
Stop!
This is the hell.
I think it's not appropriate
for you to do this.
Before I came here,
I saved Chang Qing from the Night Clan.
And I left.
Really?
I have always done nothing wrong.
It seems that the wedding of the three days later
should be held in my Night Clan.
And the person I want to marry
seems to be not the god of the hell.
After three days,
I will win the wedding of the sea.
I will be your bride.
I can't bear to do this.
Xing Yue!
Shouldn't you give me an answer?
This is the fate of your life.
He is so miserable.
Don't you want to teach him a lesson?
I always like to solve my own problems.
I will never be able to solve them.
You forced Xing Chen to break the law of the world.
I will be punished.
But you are not in the world.
I said three years ago
that your 100 years of friendship
is meaningless to me.
Why do you have to take the opportunity to marry yourself?
Xing Yue!
Master,
for me
only one problem solved,
I am really curious
if you are stucked by the Demonic Stone
because of a long experience.
If I don't make it,
will you be able to solve this problem?
I am really curious
about if you have been stucked
with the Demon God through Wallend
even during this lifetime,
If Shen Zun doesn't go,
are you really going to marry him?
The demon god broke out of the demon clan and was secretive.
At least I have to stay with him
to see how much he has power now.
Jing Yuan is even more than enough for your love.
God really didn't mean to hurt him.
Didn't you see my heart just now?
It's really a long-awaited goddess.
Only I can be with you in this world.
And only you can be with me.
After three days, Yueyin Sea is our wedding gift.
God!
Jing Yuan, how is he?
Even the power of the demon god is not enough to make him feel better.
The demon god has no answer.
I will send him to the demon clan as per the order of the god.
He was just a new god.
So he didn't notice.
When he wakes up,
he will know that the demon god has no power.
He has no power left.
He will not leave the temple easily.
Only he can see me killing Jing Yuan.
Only he can believe that the god of the demon god is true.
Only he can use the star of the demon god to trap him.
To kill him.
Xiu Yan, you did a good job.
God, if you are trapped in the demon clan,
you can't rush back to the New Moon Tai Feng Ni.
Your power will disappear faster.
I know.
I can feel the guilt of the power inside me.
I have not much time left.
God.
Don't do that.
Even if it's the god,
I will have a day to die.
But before I disappear,
I have one last thing to do.
The new moon palace has known the reality of the evil spirit.
Before I disappear,
I need to find the person who trained Xie Gong.
Kill him.
I need your help.
God, you say.
The whole god world, except me,
only Jing Yuan and Mo Li's power can be able to trap the three gods.
So I have to go to the demon clan.
If the person who trained Xie Gong is not Jing Yuan,
then only the shadow lord Mo Li is left.
I will keep the law in the demon clan.
And you
need to keep the information around Jing Yuan
to let the shadow lord know.
Yes.
Don't worry.
Everything will end in three days.
God, the demon god will wake up in three days.
He will know all this.
But you already...
Shuyuan.
As the god,
I should bear the responsibility of the god.
But as the new moon,
I wish he can live.
I have a dream in your eyes.
As long as you do this for me,
I can help you draw the god's face.
Are you willing to do it?
Very good.
From today on,
you are the eyes of the new moon.
I will tell you everything that happened in the new moon.
I will tell you everything.
One day,
you will get what you want.
Three days later,
I will let the god,
except the shadow lord,
be gone.
D.
Jingyuan.
Why are you here?
We are getting married.
I am not here.
I picked this one.
Is it pretty?
It's pretty.
Then we'll use this to
bring the spirit of the demon to our wedding.
I'll take it.
What are you looking at?
I'm looking at Ziyue.
When I was in the nightclub,
I often heard you say that the demon clan was lonely and beautiful.
I was always disturbed by the others.
I didn't pay much attention to them.
I was so stubborn at night.
Then do you like Zhuliu?
I like him.
Then let's stay here forever, okay?
If you don't like this, we can go together.
We'll stay here forever.
Xing Yue, are we really going to get married?
You know what I am.
Do you know when I fell in love with you?
When I gave you the firefly,
I was drinking with you.
Then we went to the moon and the sea together.
Do you remember the day you entered the nightclub?
I recognized you.
You fell in love with me?
Not really.
I was looking at you that day.
I thought that a demon god
would do such a thing.
To destroy the palace,
I wanted to be a little god.
So I got some interest.
I understand.
I am willing to see you
and be with you.
Xing Yue, I am very happy.
What are you happy about?
Everything.
I am happy that you are with me
when you are away from me.
I am happy that you are willing to see me.
I am happy that we are going to get married.
I am happy.
You are the blue earth in my life.
Let tears fall on you.
Xing Yue, if this is a dream,
I hope that I will never wake up.
I am happy.
Xing Yue, I am sorry.
You are the one who woke me up?
Yes.
He had a dream for me.
He trapped me in a dream.
But you forced me to wake up.
Xing Yue, what do you and your God want to do?
God doesn't want to do anything.
He had a dream.
Maybe he just wanted to make a wish.
Wish?
I think it is just a trick
to manipulate my hand.
Do you think I will be fooled by your lies?
God, didn't you find out that Xing Yue was dead?
Did I hurt you?
Why?
His power has gone weak.
Because of you.
Because of me?
Because God loves you.
Xing Yue, this is the best joke I have heard in my life.
I have confessed my sins to him.
He bullied me, hurt me, and used me.
If this is also a secret,
I will not be able to keep my promise.
Then I will be really in trouble.
All that God did is to protect your life.
Tell me clearly.
What is the name of my life?
Do you think God is a immortal without a heart?
He didn't have a choice.
Xing Yue is the God of the Universe.
God only wants to leave all his emotions
to use Xing Yue's power to use God's power.
Everyone thinks that Wu Nian Shi is the God of the Wind and the Shadow.
Actually, he is the God of the Universe.
But now, Wu Nian Shi can't seal his love for you.
His power in his body is scattered day by day.
In the end, even the beast can't keep it.
But even if he dies,
God didn't give up loving you.
He gave up the God of the Universe.
It's your fate.
God told me to keep it from you.
But how could I watch him take the wrong side?
I am so angry.
This is Wu Nian Shi.
He broke the God's seal.
I want you to remember everything.
Xing Yue.
I only want to see God's curse with his beloved.
And not Xing Yue's shadow.
I want to be with you forever.
Do you want to be my God?
Why?
Why should I kill him?
This is heaven.
I am the power of the heavens and earth.
My existence is the law of the gods and the gods.
If the heavens want him dead, I will lie to them.
You have practiced the Blood Palace.
The gods agreed to marry them.
They wanted to die in the heart of the Moon and to be together with him.
There is not much time left.
Maybe you can save him now.
Xing Yue.
Xing Yue,
you are my wife.
You are the god of the heavens and earth.
You are my wife.
From now on,
I will never let you down.
You want to kill me?
Mo Li,
you have practiced the Blood Palace and killed the gods.
The heavens and earth are not soft.
I am the god.
I am the master of this world.
Who is qualified to judge my sins?
The power of the stars and the laws of the heavens
and the peace of the gods are my wish.
Xing Yue.
Your power.
As you have seen,
I have already grown up.
If it is not the love of the moon,
maybe I can kill it.
But now you are too weak.
You can't set out the whole of the gods of the stars and the moon.
You are not my opponent.
But don't worry.
I won't kill you.
Even if I kill you,
I will have a new god of the stars and the stars.
Xing Yue is my only client.
You are the famous judge of the gods.
Why do you want to enter the Moon and Moon Sea?
Because as long as I can control Xing Yue's power
with your magic,
you can enter the world.
I am the one who will decide the future.
What else have you done?
This god of the moon
doesn't need another god other than my shadow tribe.
Today,
I am the main judge of the whole world.
Such a big day.
Of course, I need to use the blood of the Night Demon and the two tribes to celebrate.
Mo Li.
You deserve to die.
Xing Yue.
As long as you are angry with me,
I can protect your spirit and your spirit.
You can live forever.
And I, the master of the Moon and the god of the moon,
can't you?
Dream on.
It's okay.
When you and I get angry and suffer,
you will change your mind one day.
You have the spirit and the spirit.
When did you and the god of the moon get angry?
Mo Li.
The god of the moon is certain.
You can never control Xing Yue's power.
Even if you kill the god of the moon today,
there will be a day when the new god of the moon
will be born in the world.
By then,
it will be your death.
How can I not be as good as the god of the moon?
You chose him as your barrier.
You are not worthy of his body.
I have always loved you.
I will always love you.
You choose others.
Don't blame me for being ruthless.
I will never be your slave.
Xing Yue.
No matter what happens today,
don't face it alone.
I am here.
I will die with you.
But never fight.
Okay.
Since you are begging to die,
I will choose you.
After today,
the world will be my main asset.
Jin Ren.
Xing Yue.
Lan Gong.
Jin Ren.
Do you want to die?
Xing Yue.
You are the god of the moon.
Lan Gong.
Hurry up, Xing Yue.
You think you can kill me?
No.
You are heartless.
I will destroy the gods and the world.
Destroy everything.
I will not let you die.
Xing Yue.
The god of the moon.
The last thing I can do
is to protect this star.
Xing Yue.
You are my love.
Jin Ren.
Xing Yue.
Xing...
You are too strong.
With my power,
I can't destroy the world.
I will start a new life.
I will destroy the star.
The last thing I can do is to burn my power.
I will start a new life.
I will only use my power.
If I can't destroy the god,
the god will be gone.
But the world is still here.
It's not a dream.
The star is gone.
The world is gone.
My responsibility is to suppress the star.
Then, Xing Yue.
Your mission
is to kill the star
until Xing Yue's life is born.
No.
Xing Jun.
I am gone.
I can't.
I will destroy the star.
The star is gone.
The world is gone.
My responsibility is to suppress the star.
Remember.
Only the power of Xing Yue's power
can destroy the star.
Remember.
I will bring everything back to normal.
Xing Jun.
Xing Yue will definitely use his life to protect me.
To protect my heart.
To protect my life.
I will protect my life.
The heart will not destroy the place it is.
So, Xing Yue has become
the only place in the world.
To be honest,
you are the one I have to wait for.
No.
Xing Yue, Jing Yuan, and Mo Li
are gone.
Why can they re-establish the world?
The world has three gods in the universe.
The gods have life and body.
But the gods have no existence.
As long as the gods are there,
there is a possibility to re-establish the world.
But in this kind of possibility,
no one knows how long it takes.
It takes 60,000 years to wait for you.
It is a lucky thing.
But I met Jing Yuan ten years ago.
He was still in the world.
This is also the reason why I can't be the one to re-establish the world.
Maybe Jing Yuan only knows
the reason for re-establishing the world.
What about Chong Zhao?
You haven't answered me.
Why did the gods leave the world?
Because the heavens are in chaos.
The heavens are in chaos.
At the moment when the gods are gone,
they have entered the chaos.
They can't control the direction of the gods.
So, after Zhen Yu escaped from the gods,
they spent 60,000 years to find you.
Zhen Yu?
That little black snake is Zhen Yu.
It was the first time he was able to open the door.
So he couldn't control your desire.
The only thing he can remember is that
he was a trusted and respected person.
He was a good person.
He was also a mess.
Because of the endless increase in the life of the gods,
he fell into the East.
He hated you and killed Jing Yuan.
So he wanted to kill you.
I asked him why he didn't do it himself.
Instead, he wanted Chong Zhao to kill me.
Because only the gods can kill the gods completely.
60,000 years ago,
Xing Yue couldn't kill Mo Li and Jing Yuan completely.
It was because of his weak power.
If Chong Zhao really killed you,
you would have been in a deep disarray
and never have a chance to get back together.
So it was like this.
It's still not right.
60,000 years ago,
Wu Nian Shi was the only god in your hands.
But why did you say you were dead?
Why did Wu Nian Shi die in the forest?
The time he was in the forest
actually hit me badly.
I knew that I couldn't live long.
But I had to bear the promise of the gods.
I didn't want to let the gods die in the middle of the city.
So I went to the East.
I saw a cave.
The new scriptures and stories
that the gods have passed on to me
were all hidden in the forest.
I think that one day,
someone might come here
to witness the history of the gods
and the destruction of the world.
Wu Nian Shi was completely shocked
when he was in the forest.
I felt that the new god of Xing Yue
would be born in the East.
So I handed Wu Nian Shi
to the most holy god of the forest.
I left the god's jade
to each of the leaders
to wait and help a girl who can restart Wu Nian Shi.
Unfortunately,
the secret was not the key to the past.
After that, I returned to the Moon Sea.
I was left with no choice but to leave.
I kept my guard for a long time.
I left because of the injury.
The god left me in the jade cage.
So I could live a life of my own.
But why did you tell me now?
Why did you know my kindness?
Because you are just a human being
who has never experienced anything.
You don't even know what the fairy demon is.
You don't know what the guardian is.
The fairy is a good person.
She can help you to survive.
Now, you have experienced many lives
and you have been able to save the god
even if you have a new day.
If I am really a god,
why can't I return to the Moon Sea
and save the god?
I didn't expect
that the Moon Sea would be the Moon Sea
when I found the cave.
The seven stars and the soul are not my plan.
It's not what I want.
Now, I can only help you to keep it alive.
As for the rest,
I can't do anything about it.
But to be honest,
it's not the time for sadness.
I told you everything today.
It's because the Moon Sea can't hold on to the star.
Why?
It's been 60,000 years.
The power of the power of the power will disappear.
Without the power of the star and the jade,
the star will be gone.
The Moon Sea will not exist.
I can only use the five-spirit stone
in your body to keep the star.
But it's not the time for the long-awaited.
To be honest,
you only need to find the star and the god.
To completely destroy the star
to avoid the world.
The Moon Sea
Why do you always think of me?
Come on, come on.
My heart is so excited.
Wait for me.
The star is shining in your eyes.
You are the light I want to see.
You are the only reason I'm here.
Let this moment be with you.
I want to see the moon in the sky.
The star is shining in your eyes.
You are the blue earth I want to see.
Let this moment be with you.
I'm here.