[English subtitles are available]
Arsenal Military Academy
Episode 24
What?
The Rong Mansion invited me for their birthday celebration?
Ridiculous!
I'm not an opera performer.
Why do they want me there?
They're humiliating you.
They assume that you have no work to do
and your price is low.
Honestly, when they came to me,
I was pissed.
How about
I turn them down?
The Rong Mansion
is a house of royal members.
Attending their event isn't embarrassing.
Go to tell them
I'll be there.
Ask them to send a car to pick me up.
Can I get any lower?
Xiang,
stop, stop.
Xiaojun.
What are you doing here?
Gu Yanzhen is hungry
so he asked me to buy some food.
Aren't you sweet and thoughtful?
Knock it off. He's sick.
Go back quickly. It's late.
Tomorrow
is your day off.
Come to my place.
My mom's been asking about you.
I'm sorry I can't.
I have things to do.
What is it?
You're nosy.
I'll tell you if you need to know.
Go back now.
Go back.
Go.
Like I want to know.
Let's go.
OK.
See you.
Be careful.
What a quack!
Let me see.
You...you look much better.
You looked as red as
a lobster yesterday.
Today, it's a tomato.
Where are you going?
Business.
About what?
Why ask?
You want to go with me?
How can I go out like this?
That's it.
Just stay here and rest.
Come back quickly.
Bring back some food.
Can't you go eat in the canteen?
Gosh,
it's just nearby.
We're all classmates.
No need to be embarrassed.
I won't go out.
So spoiled!
You heard me?
I did.
Liangchen.
What's wrong?
Ji Jin,
may I borrow your bike?
Sure.
It's downstairs.
Thank you.
Is Shen Junshan not here?
Junshan?
He left last night.
Alright.
-I'm off. -OK.
Isn't this Shen Junshan's house?
You look sharp.
Young ladies in the Rong Mansion
may eat you alive.
If so,
I'll eat them alive first.
All gifts have been
placed in the trunk.
See you.
Manting.
Didn't you say a car would pick me up?
Where was it?
I didn't see it.
There are too many guests.
They're shorthanded.
I heard that the head of Yuanqing Troupe
also came himself.
So they hired opera performers?
Oh, well,
guess I'm no different from them.
Thank you for picking me up.
I'm new here.
I'm not familiar with the route.
You're welcome. Please.
Didn't you say all guests came themselves?
I don't know what's going on.
I want to kill you!
Miss,
your invitation, please.
I don't have it.
I'm a performer.
A performer?
Go to the backyard.
This way.
Where are you going?
Do your makeup here.
When it's your turn,
you'll be called.
Don't run around.
If anything is missing,
you can't afford the consequence.
Excuse me?
I'm here...
A performer,
has such a bad temper.
Sorry.
What did you just say?
Manting,
don't be mad at the servant.
It's not worth it.
I'm not mad at him.
I'm mad at you.
You asked me to take the rickshaw.
Come back.
Don't move.
You're dead!
Manting,
where are you going?
I'm about to explode.
If I see Yuan Pingting here, I may destroy her.
Then...
Then come back quickly.
Mr. Shen, the road ahead is blocked.
Go to have a look.
OK.
Junshan.
What are you doing here?
Get in.
Looking From Afar There They Are
The Eight Immortals are here to pay respects.
-Look how great it is. -My lady,
your servant Pei Shun,
together with my family,
my wife and kids
come to pay our respects.
-Rise. -Rise.
-Come on. -Get up.
Rise.
You've become a commander.
Don't call yourself a servant.
Others may laugh at you.
Am I right?
My lady,
I've only got this far
because of Lord Rong, my lady,
and Lord Chengrui's help.
I'll never forget that.
Pei Shun,
over the past few years,
you've been doing great.
You didn't embarrass our family.
What's more,
you're grateful to your old master.
That alone
is a rare virtue.
I grew up in the Rong Mansion.
Loyalty and righteousness
are in my blood.
I've kept telling myself
that I came from the Rong Mansion.
I should
always be responsible and considerate
so that I wouldn't shame my lord.
Good.
Well said.
In Feng'an,
everyone respects my lord.
No one dares to pick on me.
I've only
become who I am today
because of my lord.
That I'll never forget.
Good.
Aren't you going to reward him?
Sure.
Reward him handsomely.
Thank you, my lady.
Thank you, my lord.
How long have you been with Qu Manting?
Two years.
That man surnamed Shen,
what's his relationship with Qu Manting?
He's Manting's friend.
Friend?
More like her boy toy.
He isn't.
Mr. Shen's been in love with Manting for years.
Manting, Manting.
Who pays your salary?
I...I won't say it again.
Don't be like this.
Others would think I bullied you.
No, no.
Look at you,
only people like Qu Manting
would hire losers like you.
Tell me,
which one of us is prettier?
You're prettier of course.
I'm not your match.
Not you.
I mean between Qu Manting and me, who's prettier?
Of...of course
you're prettier.
You stuttered.
You must be lying.
Don't move.
So
you think I'm not prettier than Qu Manting?
I...
I'll go out
to see what's going on there.
It's great.
Chengrui prepared it.
Thank you, son.
Such a good boy.
Go see who let off the fireworks.
OK.
This part is my favorite.
What's going on now?
Who the hell are you?
How dare you make a scene here?
This is...
What are you doing?
Long time no see,
my lady.
I come to pay my respects.
What on earth is going on?
What's wrong?
Yeah, what's happening?
You're not welcomed here.
Get out.
You haven't changed a bit, my lady.
You still love kicking others out.
What a shame!
The time has changed.
Director of Huning Railway Bureau, Song Xiwen,
do you remember him?
Who is he?
Never heard of him.
It doesn't matter if you don't know him.
You should know
his daughter then.
She's He Ruyang's wife.
Mr. Song's daughter has quite a bad temper.
She used to whip a maid to death
who tried to seduce her husband.
You don't know
such juicy gossip?
Why should I?
Let me make this clearer.
Yuan Pingting,
according to seniority,
I'm superior to you.
I'm not afraid that you pick on me.
But before you do anything stupid,
think carefully if
you can handle the consequence
after you piss me off.
This is
custom-made in Liuzhou,
a cloud-patterned coffin engraved with the words "happiness" and "longevity".
It's made of fine wood
and painted 35 times.
Abbot of the Tianlong Temple
carved sutras and charms on the outside,
inside, which contains 9 layers.
It's as luxurious as the empress's coffin.
I believe such an honor
surely matches your status
as the former princess of Qing Dynasty.
Shut up!
Drive them all out!
Please.
I dare you!
Do you want to die?
I came to pay my respects.
Do you have to pick a fight?
If someone gets hurt,
and blood gushes out,
won't it spoil the mood?
Am I right?
Son,
don't waste time on her. Kick her out!
Get out.
You're so cruel.
Back then, you kicked me out.
I held no grudge and came to celebrate your birthday.
Not only wasn't I served
with tea or snacks,
but you also tried to
drive me out with swords
and threatened me.
I thought you'd grown.
Shut up.
Leave with your people.
It seems that even if I've prepared
a luxurious coffin
blessed by monks,
after you die,
you'll still be in hell
and be tortured with fire.
-You... Xianrong. -My lady. My lady.
-Don't stop me. -Don't push me.
Given what you've done,
if I wanted to kill you,
you'd die long ago.
You...
You'd better take care.
They…they…
they're killed.
Hurry!
I came today
to offer birthday congratulations
to Her Ladyship.
I'm sorry I interrupted you.
My apologies.
Regardless of the crimes she's committed
and her despicable nature,
it's still her birthday.
I'm obliged to
wish her
happy birthday.
Here's a friendly reminder.
Cherish the days you still have.
You may not be able to celebrate
another birthday.
You...
Don't.
Sorry, everyone.
Take care.
Have you obtained the objects?
I have.
Xianrong has left.
Let's go.
Go.
Have you heard what he said?
I was almost scared to death.
I didn't hear anything.
Xianrong.
I'm fine.
It's just a scratch.
The wound needs to be dressed.
What if you have an infection?
Liangchen,
thank you so much.
If it hadn't been for you,
Junshan would've been in danger.
Don't mention it.
Junshan and I are classmates
and friends.
Friends should help each other.
By the way,
why were you there?
I...
Don't get me wrong.
I have no other intentions.
I'm simply curious.
If you don't want to answer it,
it's OK.
There's nothing to hide.
I was investigating something
so I followed that Japanese man.
I had no idea
that he was going to hurt Junshan.
How did you know he's Japanese?
I saw that
he had free access to the Japan COC
and the way he moved and spoke
resembled the Japanese.
What were you investigating?
I only have a theory.
There's no proof yet.
Whatever you're working on,
it's dangerous.
You must be extra careful.
I know.
You know why I beat you?
I failed in my duty.
You acted on your own
and disobeyed my orders.
Boss...
Don't pretend that you don't understand.
Fujiwara,
you know what I'm talking about.
I dare not.
Really?
You're bold as brass.
I told you to stall him,
yet you took the liberty
and tried to kill him.
Not only did he
kill our soldiers,
but he also sabotaged our plans repeatedly.
I found you in the wild
and brought you back to be my slave.
Your only mission is to obey my orders.
Understand?
Yes.
I should've killed you
but I need you to do something for me.
If it goes wrong again,
don't bother to come back alive.
Yes.
Boss,
I fear that man
will weaken your morale
and make you forget your faith
and hatred.
It's none of your concern.
Father.
Is your mother asleep?
She just went to bed.
OK.
Why are you still up?
I can't sleep.
Are you still worried about what happened in the morning?
Don't worry.
I'll get back what we lost.
Even if you can get the lost things back,
those people we lost...
Father…
You've met Xianrong before?
I met her once on the train back to Peking.
Is she still working for
Hideyuki Oda?
Father, Xianrong…
Although Xianrong isn't my biological daughter,
I adopted her.
I didn't expect that she'd do such things.
Father, what happened before
isn't your fault.
She's stubborn.
Your mother refused to accept her and her mother.
Sadly,
after she left,
her mother passed away accidentally.
Now, she's blaming
your mother for it.
Hurry, hurry up.
Xiaojun, hurry.
Coming.
I'm coming.
Hurry up.
You know what,
I went to attend a birthday celebration,
yet I almost lost my life.
Yuan Pingting is a fool!
She can do nothing rather than barking.
Thankfully, I'm lucky and smart.
Otherwise, we'd both die there.
And?
And what?
And I came back.
Lord Chengrui said
they'd take care of the rest.
So we came back.
I guess
now he's in water.
During the celebration,
their foster daughter
came back.
And
she brought a huge coffin with her.
Her Ladyship was furious and almost fainted.
That girl's name is familiar.
What...
What's her name again?
Wait,
why did she bring back a coffin?
She just did.
There are all kinds of people
in those big families.
Wives fight against each other.
Besides, she's adopted.
Children are involved in the fight, too.
It's common.
You're ignorant.
It must be exciting.
How could you say that?
Xiaojun.
You know,
I literally thought I'd die there.
There was only one thing in my mind.
Guess what it was.
I guess
you wanted to leave all your property to me.
Of course not.
In your dreams!
I was thinking
I hadn't heard Gu Yanzhen saying he loves me.
I couldn't die.
You're helpless!
I'm serious.
As they say,
fortune awaits those who survived the disaster.
It's absolutely true.
I believe that one day, Gu Yanzhen
will fall head over heels in love with me.
And then
I'll wear a white wedding gown
and walk down the aisle with him.
He will say he loves me
in front of everyone
and promise
he'll look after me forever.
You must come to my wedding.
Of course, yes.
Lunatic.
Go do your work.
Why are you staring at me?
I don't know anything.
Off you go.
I'll sit here for a while.
Go ahead.
Hurry up.
Gu Yanzhen and I are getting married.
Your turn.
Excuse me?
What's wrong?
What brings you here
in the middle of the night, my lord?
You refused to see me
so I had to come in person.
Sorry for my abrupt visit.
Let's cut to the chase.
You should know why I'm here.
I'm sorry I can't help you.
You can't do it?
I can do it
but instead of
stealing things
to help your emperor restore his regime,
I'd rather leave it to the Japanese.
Aren't you Chinese?
I am Chinese
but I'm not your people's slave.
What a shame!
I thought you and me
would always be close friends.
If you have other business for me,
I'm willing to cooperate.
I shall take my leave.
Take care. Goodbye.
Boss.
Tell Xiaodao and Zhameng
to keep an eye on the Japan COC.
I think the one in charge
and the woman who brought the coffin
are the same person.
Boss,
are we going to…
Both sides are bad.
That object
should be in our own hands.
I see.
Where are you going, Miss?
The Qu Residence in Taoyuan Lane.
Got it.
Sir.
Come in.
Director.
What is it?
A woman outside
has a document issued by the police,
saying she needs to borrow
a student for business.
Go outside and
tell her
the exam is coming.
All students are busy.
Make her leave.
Yes.
Haven't I told you...
Are you?
Director Guo, right?
Hello.
I'm surnamed Qu,
Qu Manting.
What a lovely name!
Hey corporal,
bring a glass of water.
No need.
I'm not thirsty.
Make yourself at home.
Have a seat.
Ms. Qu,
what can I do for you?
Here's the thing.
Lately, I feel
someone's been stalking me.
I stayed at home for a few days,
but I can't always stay indoors.
So I talked to Director Wang
and he told me to talk to you.
He said
With students' protection,
I'd be safe.
Don't worry.
I won't ask them to work for free.
I'll pay.
You name the price.
It's up to you.
Someone's been stalking you?
Yes.
I think.
Do you know
who your stalker is?
I have no idea.
How about this?
I'll ask
some of our best students
to protect you 24/7.
No need.
One is enough.
I've picked one myself.
Take a look.
You know each other?
Are you sure
him alone is enough?
We aren't close,
but I know his kung fu is good.
He's smart
and righteous.
I trust him.
Also, I'll try to stay at home
as long as possible.
OK.
Here.
Have some water.
Thanks.
Ms. Qu,
do you mind if I ask
how old you are?
I'm 21.
21 is good.
That's right.
Right?
What's right?
Nothing.
How many people are there in your family?
My father, mother,
and a sister.
Your father is Qu...
Qu Huaishu.
He's my father.
Are you
a student now?
No.
I'm an actress.
I occasionally sing, too.
That's nice.
Where do you usually perform?
I performed in Shanghai.
Now, I'm back in Shunyuan,
I sometimes perform in Paramo.
You're welcomed to watch it.
Anytime.
I will.
I will go to watch it.
Is your hand OK?
It's just a scratch.
Not a big deal.
The old wound hasn't healed,
and now there's another one.
You'd better be careful.
We're done.
We're leaving.
Hey,
last time, you said
you were investigating something.
How did it go?
Any progress?
It's still a theory.
Junshan,
there's something you should know.
The Royal Seal we took
is missing.
Missing?
When?
Back in the hospital.
I've been looking for it these days.
You mean
it has something
to do with the Japanese who attacked me?
Junshan,
do you believe me?
I suspect that it has
something to do with Xianrong.
Xianrong?
That day when the seal went missing,
only Xiaojun, Gu Yanzhen,
you, Ms. Huo
and Xianrong came to my room.
Others are all clean.
She's the only one left.
So...
So you suspect that Xianrong stole the seal?
I have my reasons.
Jin Xianrong and I don't get along well,
but that day, she came to visit me
and offered to pour water for me.
But during the process,
she spilled the water.
She could've stolen the seal
when I wasn't looking.
Besides,
I followed her afterwards
and found that she had access to the Japan COC.
The reason I followed
that Japanese man who attacked you
was that I saw
she had contact with that man.
Accusing Xianrong of stealing the seal
is somewhat arbitrary.
Xianrong's family is doing business.
Contacting the Japanese
and accessing the Japan COC
is nothing special.
Besides,
how did you
rule out others?
There were Gu Yanzhen,
Tan Xiaojun,
Huang Song,
Huo Xiaoyu,
doctors and nurses,
and how could you be sure
that they didn't enter your room?
Plus,
even if what you said was true
that Xianrong did steal the seal
and she colluded with the Japanese,
tell me,
given the relationship between Xianrong and me,
would she have sent killers to kill me?
That does seem a bit unreasonable.
Not a bit,
it's totally unreasonable.
I may not have sharp eyes,
but at least,
I can tell others' attitude towards me.
Xianrong wouldn't do anything bad to me.
She would never hurt me.
Gu Yanzhen.
You're breaking the chopsticks.
Alright.
Stop looking at them.
Dig in.
I won't.
Shame on them!
Alright.
Eat your food.
It's getting cold.
Dig in.
Eat up.
Xie Liangchen,
Mr. Guo asked you to go to his office.
Now?
Yes.
I need to go.
You eat first.
What do you want?
You want to cause more unnecessary trouble?
I won't be easy on you.
Come on.
I'm not scared.
Shen Junshan,
do you like Xie Liangchen?
What are you trying to say?
I want you to
stay away from Xie Liangchen.
Because when we first entered the Academy,
we were really close.
Think about it.