[English subtitles are available]
Arsenal Military Academy
Episode 21
What am I thinking?
Why am I thinking of him?
Wake up.
Xie Xiang,
wake up.
Dad.
Morning.
What's wrong? What's with that look?
The Eight-Nation Alliance's waged war again?
Look what you've done!
The agency is moving fast.
How can you still laugh?
Dad.
This is unnecessary.
Grandpa arranged this marriage.
You also dislike Dong Huiseng, right?
Nonsense.
Invitations have already been sent out.
All the guests have arrived in Nanjing.
Your engagement is coming soon.
But you...
How could you do this?
You're embarrassing me
as well as our whole family!
It's not that serious.
You...you dare to talk back?
Dad.
Have the Dongs sent an envoy
to break off the engagement?
Not really.
But Dong Huiseng
did call me early in the morning
and asked me to discipline you.
He even gave me a lecture,
yet I couldn't say anything.
It's all your fault!
They aren't going to cancel it?
They have no shame!
Their family is well-known in Nanjing.
After such humiliation,
they still won't cancel it.
They are so thick-skinned.
Yanzhen.
Don't think I don't know
about your little tricks.
Don't even think about it.
You are doomed to get married!
Mr. Zhu,
keep an eye on him.
Don't let him go out today.
Yes.
Young master.
Hey, bro,
how far is this place from the town?
Four hours on foot.
But look,
after the rain,
the muddy road may take more time.
I need to spend the night in town
so I've brought Lingdang with me.
Can she walk that far?
She's used to it.
Once we speed up,
she may be faster than both of you.
It's OK, sweetie.
Calm down.
I'll get it back.
It's OK.
Liangchen,
can you look after Lingdang for me?
I'll go get the dog back.
Can you get it back?
I will.
It's OK.
Let me go with you.
No need, no need.
I'll be back in a moment.
Lingdang, don't be afraid.
Your dad will get your dog back.
He'll be back soon.
Why hasn't he come back?
I'll go check.
I'll go with you.
Stay here
and wait for me.
Lingdang needs you.
Lingdang, don't be afraid.
It's OK.
Don't worry.
Don't be scared.
Lingdang.
Wait here for me.
Don't go anywhere.
Got it?
Wait right here.
It came from that way.
Mr. Wei.
When I arrived,
he had already died.
Lingdang,
your dad died.
your dad is gone!
Liangchen,
she doesn't understand you.
Don't scare her.
It's our fault.
We killed him.
Over there.
Lingdang.
Junshan.
Leave now!
I'll cover you!
Run!
Go.
Split up.
This way.
Lingdang, wait here for me.
Don't go anywhere.
Got it?
Freeze.
Xie Liangchen. Xie Liangchen.
Congratulations, Vice Minister Gu.
May I interview you later?
Sure.
Vice Minister Gu.
Welcome. Welcome.
-Congratulations! -Congrats!
Congratulations!
This way, please.
OK.
Congratulations!
Are you happy with your daughter-in-law?
I am. She's amazing.
With all due respect, your son doesn't seem
too happy.
Congratulations!
He's just nervous.
I think it's understandable.
Am I right? Right?
-Yes, yes. -Excuse me.
-Thanks. Thank you. -Go ahead.
Vice Director Gu.
-Thanks for coming. -Congratulations!
-Welcome. -Congratulations!
Yanzhen,
What's with the long face?
It's your engagement
not a funeral.
Give me a smile.
Vice Minister Gu.
Congratulations!
-This way, please. -Congratulations!
Please.
Director He.
Vice Minister Gu.
Congratulations!
Thanks for coming to my son's engagement.
It's my pleasure.
Your son is getting engaged.
How could I miss it?
You're a handsome young man!
Your fiancee must be pretty, too.
Thanks for your compliment.
I'm indeed handsome.
As for my fiancee,
I'm not sure
if she's pretty or not.
He likes to joke around.
Director He, please.
-Sure. -This way, please.
See you.
OK.
-I can go in myself. -Sorry for the inconvenience.
Sure.
What nonsense?
I was telling the truth.
How come
she still wants to get engaged with me?
Do you really
want me to marry that shameless woman?
Don't say that again.
You can go inside if you like.
Vice Minister Gu, congratulations!
Please.
Hey, what's wrong?
You're already drunk before the ceremony begins?
I
am
Yu Shaotian.
Gu Yanzhen.
Listen,
I'm Yu Shaotian.
And?
I'm the heir of Sixi Restaurant
and Dong Xiaowan's ex-fiance.
Yu Shaotian.
I'm Yu Shaotian
Dong Xiaowan's ex-fiance?
Mr. Yu.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Are you here
to...
to teach me a lesson
or...
or to take Dong Xiaowan away?
Tell me now.
I can help you. Hurry up.
I won't hurt you.
I just came to have a look.
No, man.
How about you hit me?
You...
Come on. Hit me.
I just come to see
what kind of man
Xiaowan loves.
Hey man, don't cry.
He's crying!
Hit me now.
Take photos.
Hit me, then you may feel better.
Trust me.
What are you doing?
Young master, don't worry.
We'll take care of him.
Xiaowan!
Come here.
Wish you all the best.
Xiaowan!
You must be happy, Xiaowan!
Yanzhen.
What's wrong with him?
I don't know.
The ceremony is about to begin.
Come with me.
Dad, my stomach hurts.
I need to...
I...
You can't go anywhere.
Let's go.
Distinguished guests,
ladies and gentlemen,
welcome.
Today is
Mr. Gu Yanzhen
and Miss Dong Xiaowan's engagement ceremony.
I'm honored to be here upon Vice Minister Gu,
Gu Zongtang's invitation.
On behalf of the Gus and the Dongs,
I sincerely welcome
all of you...
Pull yourself together.
…to join us today.
Thank you all for coming.
Don't say anything stupid.
Thanks.
Don't worry, dad.
I'm in your hands now.
I won't go anywhere.
Now,
Let's welcome the stars of the day
Mr. Gu Yanzhen
and Miss Dong Xiaowan
to the stage.
How about
Mr. Gu and Miss Dong
perform the opening dance
for us?
Great!
What are you doing?
Stop.
What's wrong?
Shouldn't you invite me to dance?
No matter how reluctant you are,
under such situation,
you have no choice.
Damn it.
What's wrong?
Who is that?
Gu Yanzhen.
Will you keep your promise?
What promise?
That you'll escort me back to Shunyuan.
Of course.
Let's go.
Yanzhen.
What are you doing?
Dad, I must go.
Stop there.
Miss Dong,
wait a moment
if you
want to.
Qu Manting,
You're so cool!
What did you say?
I said you're cool!
Just so-so.
Xie Liangchen.
Lingdang, where's Xie Liangchen?
Answer me. Where's Xie Liangchen?
Be good. Don't go anywhere.
Liangchen.
Hello.
Please call 9537 for me.
Mr. Gu,
the line's been busy lately.
It may take a while for your call to be put through.
You can enjoy your meal first.
I'll call you when it's through.
You have to dress up for a meal?
I'm a star.
It's my job to look spotless.
There's a train going back tonight,
but the time is a bit tight.
If you're tired,
we can take the train tomorrow.
OK.
We will have time to hang out tomorrow.
I need to use the bathroom.
Miss,
Where's the man sitting here?
What's wrong?
He has a call.
I can answer it.
Hello.
Is this
Gu Yanzhen's fiancee?
I'm not.
I'm his friend.
Who is this?
What's wrong?
I'm his friend.
He called me just now.
He's in the bathroom.
Do you know
when he'll come back to Shunyuan?
In a few days.
OK.
When you see Gu Yanzhen,
please tell him
to come back immediately.
There's an emergency in school.
Emergency?
What happened?
Shen Junshan, Xie Liangchen,
Huang Song, and Ji Jin
escorted a batch of medicine
to Dandong Hospital.
On their way back,
they were hunted by some killers.
Now Shen Junshan and Xie Liangchen
are missing.
Huang Song and Ji Jin have come back.
Hello?
I'm listening.
When Gu Yanzhen is back,
please tell him about it
or ask him to call me back.
OK.
Are you done?
I'm done.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Let's go.
Thank you.
For what?
For helping me out.
Don't you blame me for sabotaging your engagement?
That engagement is
more like a disaster.
Hey look,
I've done you a huge favor.
A thank you isn't enough.
Tell me,
what do you want?
I'll give you anything
ex…except my body.
The least valuable thing you have
is your body.
That might be
the case before but not now.
I've changed.
I don't want
anything else.
Let me be clear,
We're friends
with no affection.
I know I'm charming...
Sir, no chili, please.
I want one, too.
What is it? Smells good.
Duck blood and vermicelli soup.
I want it.
Haven't you eaten already?
Are you a pig?
I have but I'm still hungry.
I want more. What's wrong?
I am a pig.
Go sit over there.
I'll go get it.
Add extra chili.
No shallot and cilantro.
Hello, excuse me.
I...
Lost your wallet?
Thanks. Thank you.
I'll tell your boss
to give you a bonus.
You have a good sense of humor.
Rest assured, sir.
In our restaurant,
all items we found
will be given back to the customers.
Check your wallet,
see if anything is missing.
No need.
I trust you.
Sir,
your call got through just now.
It did?
You were in the bathroom
so your friend answered it for you.
May I borrow your phone again?
Of course. Please.
What took you so long?
It's been so long.
There was a long line.
Smells so good.
So delicious. Don't you want some?
Qu Manting,
did you answer my call just now?
Yeah.
Why didn't you tell me about it?
What's the point of telling you?
We're going back soon anyway.
You're right.
Go on eating.
Gu Yanzhen,
what do you mean?
I like you.
I told you that long ago.
Don't say you don't know that.
How long will
your affection last?
Don't judge me.
You're no better.
Since you know what kind of person I am,
why do you still like me?
Qu Manting,
I'm in love with someone else.
Look,
I'm grateful
for what you did today.
In the future,
if you need my help
or anything else,
I'll
help you as much as I can.
Tell me,
why doesn't he like me?
He's blind.
He's an idiot.
Yeah,
he's an idiot.
But why am I still obsessed
with that blind idiot?
Go back and rest.
OK.
Get some rest.
Good night.
Thank you.
Why didn't anyone tell me
about Junshan's missing?
We didn't hear a word about it.
I just called back and asked them
to find him immediately.
Book tomorrow morning's ticket.
Yes.
Hello.
Hi, hello.
Is this Director Guo, Guo Shuting?
I am.
I'm calling from Dandong City Hospital.
We've received two patients today.
We believe they're your students.
I'd like to confirm it with you.
You must be punished
for your mistakes.
Boss,
on the train,
I saw Chairman Shen,
Shen Tingbai's brother.
Shen Junshan.
Was he involved in it, too?
He was just an accomplice.
Have him treated.
Be careful.
Come.
Luckily, the wound is on your leg.
If it were on your stomach or chest,
your identity would be exposed.
Then I wouldn't go to the hospital.
Great.
Just stay at home
and wait for death.
Your cover will blow soon.
You won't be lucky every time.
Things will work out in the end.
I heard Shen Junshan saved you again.
You two have gone through so much.
Tell me,
are you in love with him?
Shut up.
Are you shy?
What's wrong?
You don't feel well?
I'm fine.
I've asked for a three-day leave
to take care of you.
No need.
Huang Song will come later.
Xie Xiang,
just use your brain for once!
You're injured
and can't move freely.
Can he go to the bathroom with you?
I'm going home to get your lunch.
My mom heard you were sick,
so she cooked a lot of food for you.
And,
remember that little girl you brought back last time?
Ever since she came to our house,
she hasn't said a word.
She's always been like that.
Please take good care of her.
When I get better,
I'll find a place for her.
OK.
Take care of yourself first.
Don't worry about other things.
Be careful.
By the way,
Ms. Huo asked about you this morning.
She said she'd come to visit.
See you.
Bye.
Excuse me,
which is Xie Liangchen's room?
Over there.
Thanks.
You're welcome.