[English subtitles are available]
Arsenal Military Academy
Episode 47
Gu Yanzhen, time for breakfast.
Remember.
Our mission today is to hold them there.
We take action when the main force does.
No one should open fire without my command.
Yes, Sir.
Sergeant,
it's not right.
What did you find out?
I calculated the time for a shift.
It's quite accurate,
which is not like the bandits' doing.
Besides,
their marches are clean and strong.
It's quite unusual.
It's me.
Gu Yanzhen?
Why did you come?
Sergeant Lv asked me to tell you
something is wrong about the plan.
It's likely that we are the target.
We're set up.
Fire.
Stay down.
Sergeant,
why do the bandits have regulated mortars?
Everyone,
give up the fight.
Now.
Fall back.
Yes, sir.
Yanzhen, take that way.
Yes.
The rest of you, follow me.
Fire.
Watch out.
Junshan!
Forget about me.
Ji Jin!
Everyone, fall back to 10 o'clock.
Hurry.
Fall back.
Yes, sir.
We can't leave the wounded behind.
You go first.
Go.
Gu Yanzhen,
you cover the rear.
The first squad, follow me.
Let's go.
Get on the truck.
Hurry.
Get on.
Bastards.
Come on.
Get on the truck.
Where is Ji Jin?
Crap!
Ji Jin didn't catch up.
Junshan.
You'll get yourself killed.
Gu Yanzhen!
Hold on there.
OK.
If the information is right,
we still have a chance to
make another plan.
We might not be the one to lose.
Don't be silly.
How could they find us?
Why didn't the back-up come?
I guess our plan has arrived
first to the other side
before it came to us.
Besides,
we don't know whether
they are bandits or not.
It's not a bandits hunting.
It's murder.
Yeah.
Murder.
Our brothers didn't die in war.
They were murdered.
We have to bring justice to them.
Yeah.
Let's go to the Commander's mansion.
To the Commander's mansion.
We have to know why.
Let's go.
Stop!
Where are you going?
Sergeant Guo,
we're not afraid of being killed in war.
But we can't be killed in this way.
yes
We have to know why.
Listen to me.
Sergeant Lv and I are the ones who should go.
You guys stay put.
What do you want to do?
Sergeant Guo.
Our military action against the bandits
is totally a disaster.
Is it due to information breach
or inappropriate deployment?
The Commander's mansion has to give us a reason.
We ask for justice.
Stop it!
Lay down your arms.
Guo Shuting,
is that a mutiny?
We just want to know the fact.
Put the gun down.
All of you.
Guo!
Sergeant Guo.
Sergeant.
Guo Shuting is suspicious.
He led students from the academy
to attack the stronghold without orders.
It has caused severe damage to my unit.
That's a lie.
All of us
were helping the Commander to crack the bandits.
Where are the bandits?
Guo Shuting took actions on his own.
The Double-wolf Stronghold is the 1st Regiment's
secret garrison.
Bandits?
You take your own guys as bandits?
Didn't you see their uniforms
and the arms they use?
We were just following orders.
Whose orders?
The Commander's?
Or the headquarters'?
Where's the commission?
Show me.
I see.
It was you
who planned all this on us.
What do you want?
According to investigation,
Guo Shuting colluded with revolutionary party.
He gave them our military intelligence,
and ordered Xie Xiang to poison Commander Zhang.
And this time, he provoked students of Arsenal Military Academy
attacking the 1st Regiment's garrison.
His crime has been proved.
And hereby sentenced to death.
Effective Immediately.
Here is Xie Xiang's confession,
Lv Zhongxin's accusation
and a joint letter
signed by Mayor Bai
and 47 military officials.
According to the Commander's mansion's orders,
the Arsenal Military Academy is to be blocked out
until the case is solved.
I believe most of the students
are innocent.
You're from Shunyuan.
And most are from rich families.
How could you abandon your families
and collude with the revolutionary party?
So
now you have a chance
to prove your innocence.
What crimes did Guo Shuting commit?
Who and where are
his accomplices?
If you report in his crimes,
you can contact with your family
and leave this place.
I have a word for you.
Just admit it.
Don't be stupid.
Don't think with emotion.
You have a bright future ahead of you.
You're very brave.
What are you doing?
Liang Yong.
You wanna die?
Not about time.
I don't want to force you.
Many of you
are just common students.
You may not know any of his crimes.
So if you sign your name on
the letter reporting their crimes,
I promise
you can leave here.
I'll give you 24 hours to think about it.
If you can't think it through,
then you'll end up just like
Sergeant Guo.
Be careful.
Get in the car.
Easy, easy.
Be careful.
We'll be home soon.
Let them go.
They don't deserve to be our partners.
It's their choices.
Commander Song makes himself clear
that he wants to give us a lesson.
I think they just don't want to
sacrifice themselves.
It's normal.
It's normal?
Stop there.
Who is this?
Xie Liangchen, of the 7th batch,
Arsenal Military Academy.
Liangchen?
Liangchen!
You're still alive.
Why are you here?
Why am I here?
Why am I still alive?
Don't you know that?
Catch her.
Come on.
Let's see who got the gut.
Put the gun down.
I just want to get them out of here.
As for me,
you can bring me to a trial or else.
I'll be there.
You must be dreaming.
Before I came here,
I sent a letter to
Commissioner Feng of headquarter.
I heard he was not so close with Deputy Commander Song.
If he sees me here,
he would be very curious.
Or maybe you want me to stay longer,
so I can make it clear with everybody
that
why I'm still alive
and what terms the man who saved me
and your Commander Song
have agreed on.
Let them go.
Wait.
Junshan.
Let's go.
Xiaoyu.
I've arranged it.
You can leave in a few days.
I...
I've sent men for Gu Yanzhen.
They haven't come back yet.
You have to be prepared.
Don't get involved in things here anymore.
Now that Song Xicheng and the Japanese
are the most powerful men in Shunyuan,
a few students like you
won't make any difference.
Xiaoyu.
Go now.
I want to be alone.
How many times have you lied to me?
This time,
I almost believed you again.
Shuting.
Gu Yanzhen.
Get up.
Where are you?
Move!
Run.
Shuting.
I've revenged for you.
Song Xicheng,
when does the superior
appoint you as the Commander of Shunyuan?
How could I not know it
as the Commissioner?
The Commander Zhang died in an accident.
The commission from Peking hasn't arrived yet.
As the Deputy Commander,
I should take the office of the commander
in such a critical time.
It's all for the good of the military stability.
Why?
Commissioner Feng,
you have a problem?
I don't have time for your nonsense.
I just want to know
how Commander Zhang die?
What's going on with the attack
by the academy?
As for this,
I made it clear in the military report.
Do you want me to repeat it?
Well, I heard
Xie Liangchen didn't kill Commander Zhang.
It was the man
who wanted to replace him.
The attack of the 1st Regiment
was also this man's doing
in order to rule out different voices.
Absurd!
It's utterly nonsense.
If it's nonsense or not,
we'll find out soon.
Song Xicheng,
don't take that you can cover it all up.
The Commander is dead.
But I'm not.
Find Xie Liangchen.
Find him before Song Xicheng's men do.
Yes, Sir.
Guards.
Guards!
Commander.
Go for Oda Xianrong.
Tell her
I'll give her
what she asked for.
Why are you here alone?
So grateful in this life
Don't be upset.
Don't be afraid.
I'm here.
In dream shall we meet
Hope in this life
We'll love and cherish each other
Till death do us part
Don't idle away your youth
Dreams never stop
Where is Ji Jin?
He's severely wounded.
I trusted him with a doctor
whom I know well.
Where are the rest?
Sergeant Guo is dead.
Xiaoyu...
I don't know where she is.
Those alive are severely wounded.
Their families took them away.
We're close
with Sergeant Guo.
People of the Commander's mansion
won't let us go.
Shen Junshan's family has great influence.
They won't dare to hurt him.
But the others are in danger.
What should we do?
Miss Oda,
Song Xicheng doesn't have enough seniority
and capability.
All he has is ambition.
He can't make people oblige.
Why should we help him?
Let the dogs fight with each other.
Wouldn't it be better?
What do you want?
How dare you break in our house?
I'm coming to see Chairman Shen.
Mr. Shen is not at home.
Leave now.
Benzi!
Stop.
Miss Oda,
what brings you here?
Chairman Shen,
it's good to see you again.
What's your decision
on the mining contract?
That's between Lord Chengrui and me.
I don't see what it is to do with you.
I'm the only living soul
of Rong Mansion now.
Lord Chengrui's business
is my business.
It's not.
Now it is, I guess.
I want to terminate the contract,
no matter how much money I may lose.
Even it's all my property,
I will never collude with you Japanese.
I like your spirit.
But I don't know
whether your families
are as brave as you are.