[English subtitles are available]
Arsenal Military Academy
Episode 09
Liangchen.
It's said that
Sergeant Song was dismissed.
He privately gave orders to release the Japanese.
Sergeant Lv got angry when he came back.
When did it happen?
Yesterday.
Many people saw it.
He was taken away by the police.
Really?
I don't know it.
You seem weird.
Didn't you hear it when I called you
during morning exercises?
Nope.
You don't look well.
Are you sick?
I'm fine.
Sergeant Song is a good man.
He is just a scapegoat.
What do you mean?
Conspiracy Theorist.
At ease.
Attention.
Today
we'll take a periodic assessment
to exam your training during this period.
Your results
will be directly reported to the headquarters and the Commander's Mansion.
I hope you do your best.
Show me your progress.
Yes, sir.
Come on.
Liangchen.
Take my hand.
Forget about me. Go.
Hold me. Come on
Be careful.
Shen Junshan.
Yes.
Excellent.
Work harder.
Thank you, sir.
Ji Jin.
Yes.
Good.
Excellent, too.
Thank you, sir.
Zhu Yanlin.
Yes.
Qualified.
Thank you, sir.
Huang Song
Yes.
Excellent.
Good boy.
If only you did better in academic courses.
Thank you, sir.
I will try it.
Get back.
Yes.
Xie Liangchen.
All failed in
weight running, steeplechase, and physical confrontation.
Except shooting.
What happened to you?
I'm ashamed to take your bad results
to see the officers.
They have spent so much money
on training you as an elite officer.
Permission to speak, Sir.
I am not feeling well today.
No excuses.
When you go to the battlefield
and you don't feel well,
can you tell your enemy to fight another day?
Prepare for the reexamination.
If you still get this at reexamination,
switch to civilian staff.
Yes.
Sergeant.
It's not so serious.
Our school trains officers,
not soldiers.
Gu Yanzhen.
Don't dare to interrupt without my permission.
Look at your results.
Unqualified weight running.
The worst result in the squad.
You are a big man
but even Xie Liangchen runs faster than you.
What's wrong?
Were you sick as well?
Sergeant, I didn't sleep well last night.
I got up late
and didn't eat anything.
Shut up.
Reexamine with him.
If you fail again,
wait for my punishment.
Take it away.
Li Wenzhong.
Yes.
You crying?
Really?
I didn't get upset though I was the worst.
What do you feel bad about?
I'm not crying.
In fact, I got the worst result deliberately.
I did it in consideration of you.
Because I was afraid you would feel bad
if you were the worst.
Are you touched?
Repay me by doing my laundry.
No way.
You did it for the others.
Why can't you do it for me?
Xie Liangchen.
Aren't you feeling well?
No.
You don't look very well.
Are you sick?
I'm fine.
Go to your business.
A lot of clothes, right?
You know it.
Please wash your dirty clothes
when you change them.
I'm not your nanny.
What are you doing?
The water is too cold.
You have so many clothes.
The water is not enough.
Don't waste it.
I'll get more water if it's not enough.
Where to get?
Only one hour each day
for hot water supply.
Don't do that.
Then don't wash them.
My clothes are all wet.
Will you wash the clothes?
I will.
I will wash them.
Let me wash.
Get up.
Go out.
Out.
What are you doing with the box?
Where are you going?
Home.
For what?
The laundry.
It's a toilet?
Buddy.
Shen Junshan.
Who are you?
Allow me to introduce myself.
My name is Gu Qiqi.
G-U, Gu.
Q-I-Q-I, Qiqi.
It also means I'm looking forward to meeting you.
I am fifteen years old,
studying in Xinhua Girls' School.
Oh, my gosh.
I meet you here.
And I'm talking to you.
I'm so excited.
Stay with me.
I know you.
You are Shen Junshan.
Your brother is Chairman Shen of Shunyuan COC.
You studied abroad and just returned,
the student of the Arsenal Military Academy.
The most important is that
I admire you very much.
You got the wrong person.
I saw everything
outside the city,
on the road to Wang village.
Don't worry.
I won't say anything about it.
I swear it.
I don't know what you said.
It wasn't me.
My hero.
Believe me.
I'm not a bad guy.
Shen Junshan.
Stop.
I'm here for my brother.
What did you say?
I said I was here for...
What did you say to Shen Junshan?
I...
You said outside the city,
on the way to Wang village.
What did you see?
I...
I didn't see anything.
I was kidding with him.
What did you see on earth?
Tell me.
Did Junshan kill the Japanese in the car?
Are you crazy?
I told you I didn't see anything.
If my dad and my brother knew it,
you would die.
Really?
Your dad? Your brother?
You won't tell me, huh?
- No. - What are you doing?
Go.
- I'll throw you down. - How dare you?
Let me go.
Believe me I will do it.
Say it.
Let me go. Let me go.
I will say it.
I will tell you.
Don't play tricks on me.
Pang took me to practice cycling
outside the city.
Say the point.
I...I'm getting there.
I'm getting to the point.
I'll talk about Shen Junshan.
When I was riding,
a car suddenly drove by.
And mud splattered all over me.
You would be angry if it was you, right?
I was pissed off.
And I rode my bicycle and ran after it.
Guess what I found?
Yanzhen.
You want to die?
Say it.
No?
Are you alright?
He...
Is he dead?
None of your business. Go.
What should we do?
None of your business. Go now.
Wait.
Remember it.
You know nothing about
what Shen Junshan did that day.
You saw nothing.
Don't come to him again.
Don't tell anyone.
Get it?
Yes. Get it.
Gu Yanzhen.
Open the door.
Xie Liangchen.
What's up?
Shen Junshan.
I think I killed someone.
Sit.
Don't be afraid. Tell me.
What happened?
Li Wenzhong.
I think I killed Li Wenzhong.
Calm down.
What the hell is it?
What happened to him?
I overheard your conversation with the girl.
So did Li Wenzhong.
He chased the girl away.
I was afraid he hurt you.
So I followed up.
I saw him asking the little girl
about you.
She refused to say.
Li Wenzhong threatened to drown her.
Then
in panic,
I hit him with a stone.
Then he...
Shen Junshan.
Did I murder him?
Will he die?
Don't be afraid.
We don't know yet.
You tried to save people.
Not only did you save her,
you also saved me.
Now recall it.
Did anyone else see it?
Besides the little girl,
is there anyone else?
I...I don't know.
I'm not sure.
Clear the blood.
And have a rest.
Leave the rest to me.
But...
Don't worry. Everything will be fine.
Really?
Do you believe me?
Yes, I do.
Go.
Junshan.
- Go back now. - OK.
Let's go.
Junshan.
I was looking for you.
What happened?
Wenzhong was hit by someone.
He was hit?
Yes.
It's serious.
He's in a coma.
Ji Jin drove him
to the hospital just now.
Is his life endangered?
It's hard to tell.
He was hit on the head.
Do you know who did it?
Not yet.
But it should
be done by someone outside school.
We found
an unknown ladder outside the wall.
Don't be afraid.
I'll be back soon.
Shen...Shen Junshan.
You are so curious.
If you want to know,
why don't you come to me?
Why did you threaten the little girl?
So it was true?
The people in the car,
you killed them all?
Don't you think
they deserve to die?
Now you know it.
What do you want?
Snitch on me to the police?
Or...
To the Japanese?
Or go to the press
and claim bonuses for the clue?
I...
Li Wenzhong.
Our families have known
each other for many years.
You know me and my family very well.
You should know
I did this in secret
because I don't want any trouble.
But it doesn't mean
I'm afraid of trouble.
And It doesn't mean
I can't solve
the trouble if any.
You all thought I just returned home.
Actually, I didn't.
I have been back long ago.
I studied medicine in British
and served as a medic back here.
I took part in many battles.
Not large ones,
but they were all bitter.
At Pianma in Yunnan,
I killed many people.
I don't even know
the exact number.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm not to scare you.
I want you to know
who you're dealing with.
Lest you don't know the situation
and do something rash,
resulting in unpleasant consequences.
Of course.
If you don't care about this,
I won't mind
solving another trouble.
I'm sorry.
Patients should have more rest.
Goodbye.
By the way.
I forgot to tell you.
This hospital
is my family property.
Let the doctor know if you have any need.
If you have no inclination to this world,
they'd be happy to help you.
Good night.
Why is Liangchen here?
What is he doing in bed?
You ask too much.
You sleep in his room tonight.
Me?
Why?
No reason.
Don't talk nonsense. Go.
What?
I have my own room.
Thank god you're here.
What are you doing?
Which is Xie Liangchen's bed?
This one. What's up?
I sleep here tonight.
Who asks you to sleep here?
Where is Xie Liangchen?
He is in my room.
In your room?
Why is he in your room?
I don't know.
Anyway, he is in my room.
I sleep in his room today.
Who said that?
Shen Junshan.
When did he get to make the call?
Let's go.
What?
Catch up.
Am I so unpopular?
Gu Yanzhen.
Why do you sleep here?
You have your own room.
Get back with me.
Hurry up.
Xie Liangchen.
What?
I have a word with you.
Why does it have to be private?
Gu Yanzhen.
Don't be afraid.
Li Wenzhong is not dead.
Well...
Don't worry.
He won't say anything.
Thank you.
Are you done? Go back if you're done.
What's the silly smile?
Good night.
Tell that to me.
Junshan.
Something wrong with you?
Which is?
I don't know.
It's just a feeling.
Forget it.
Go to sleep.
I think I killed someone.
Don't be afraid.
It's uncertain yet.
You tried to save people.
Not only did you save her,
you also saved me.
Clear the blood.
And have a rest.
Leave the rest to me.
Don't be afraid.
Li Wenzhong is not dead.
Don't worry.
He won't say anything.
Go.
Xie Liangchen.
Yes.
Not fast enough.
Poor endurance.
Deficient explosive power.
Poor capability to counter-fight.
It's a disaster.
Excuse me, Sir.
Did he pass it?
Anyway,
you made some progress.
Barely qualified.
Great.
Great. Liangchen.
You made it.
Don't be too excited.
He's barely qualified.
If you get the same poor result like this next time,
you will be eliminated.
Yes.
Thank you, sir.
Tomorrow is the school anniversary holiday.
Three days off.
Pack up and get ready
to go home.
Hooray!
Look at you. You stick to me here
like a mud all day long.
Don't you have anything to do?
No. I have nothing to do
so I stick to you here.
Do you have any business?
Of course I do.
I review every day to prepare for the exam.
Don't you act in the movie?
What about Paramo's performances?
Canceled.
What about Shanghai?
The company puts me on vacation.
It has not filmed in the past two months.
You are miserable then.
So can I come here for a free drink?
Alright. Alright.
So you've been living in the hotel.
Didn't your parents come to see you?
Manshu?
Mr. Shen?
Manshu came once.
But she will study in Beijing.
She'll leave next month.
Shen Tingbai comes here each day.
It's understandable.
So many Japanese died.
He was supervised by them.
Very carefree.
He has nowhere to go but here.
Look at you.
You made such a big trouble.
What do you mean I made?
Who did I do it for
to be chased by them like a rabbit?
How could it be
a hero to save a beauty in your minds?
You have a point.
That's my wine.
It's just a drink.
I saved your life, OK?
You save my life?
Oh, god.
I carried you and ran
across the mountains, OK?
If it wasn't me,
you would have been engulfed by wolves.
Don't fool me.
Whisky.
OK.
My lady.
I was there to save people.
You knocked me out.
If I was eaten by wolfs,
you would be the murderer.
I didn't know it was you.
You were also an accomplice.
Your wine.
Thank you.
The Japanese
were killed by Shen Tingbai?
I do not know.
How come you don't know it?
I'm not interested.
Not interested?
I am just not interested in it.
Why do I have to be interested in him?
It doesn't make sense.
Why would he always take the credits
for killing the enemy?
Right.
These things shouldn't be
ascribed to Shen House.
I don't like them, either.
They wear their poker face each day.
I wonder why.
I can't get rid of them
whatever I do.
I think it was Shen Tingbai who did it.
No one else in Shunyuan
can do
such a pleasant thing.
Since you admire him so much,
why don't you pursue him?
Don't trouble me.
I can't do that shamelessly.
He is the husband of my friend.
Yes, you can.
It's not shameless at all.
Go and get him.
Read your book then.
Come. Let's drink.
Let's have a drink.
I didn't do it well yesterday.
You were already awesome.
I will work as hard
as you do.
So crowded.
Your wine.
Call me if you need something.
OK.
Xiaojun is here.
When did you come?
Just now.
Are you happy?
Very happy.
Superstar.
- Yanzhen. - Hi.
You are all here.
No training at night?
No, we rest.
Come on, let's eat something.
Goodies.
You didn't offer us just now.
Help yourself.
Xiaojun,
I brought you something.
What?
Take a guess.
Chocolate.
No.
Cake.
I can't make it.
Tell me then.
Cookies.
My dad brought it to me specially.
He asked his friend to buy it from Hong Kong.
Smell good?
So good.
I just want to have a look.
I didn't eat any of them.
I keep it for you.
So nice of you.
You take a bite.
I don't eat it.
Take a bite.
I don't like sweet food.
Just take a bite.
Come on.
Is it good?
Yes.
I think so.
What's up?
Right.
What?
Are you
lovers?
No.
Don't talk nonsense.
We are friends.
Friend?
Even a fool can tell you are not.
Do they look like lovers?
Yes.
- Definitely. - Gu Yanzhen.
What do you think?
I don't know. I can't see it.
It's obvious.
You are definitely lovers.
Tan Xiaojun.
You hide something from me.
Tell me now.
When did you two get started?
How?
How long?
Who introduced you two?
I...
I wondered why you came here to work.
You are here for him?
What?
She wasn't enrolled in school before I came here.
You knew each other recently?
We know each other for a long time.
You have a sister, right?
She is your friend.
So your sister introduced
you to her, right?
So you were seduced, right?
What seduced?
Be careful of your words.
We are just friends.
Tan Xiaojun. You are... You are...
You!
Where are you from?
Who are your parents?
Enough.
What are you doing?
I am helping you.
How do you know what the man is thinking?
It sounds as if you were experienced.
Of course I am experienced.
I know exactly what you're thinking.
What's that?
What do you mean?
Don't stare at me.
Liangchen.
Where will you go on the holiday?
She'll go to my family.
My mom has gotten the bed ready for him.
You said it's nothing, right?
He is living in your home,
and the bed is prepared.
You have met the parents, right?
No.
It's not like that.
You misunderstood it.
Xiaojun and I,
her parents and my parents,
have known each other for a long time.
My sister and I came here for study.
They take care of us a lot.
I visit them on holidays.
Can your house accommodate for them?
Yes, it's roomy.
Liangchen.
Why don't you go to my house?
My sister lives nearby.
It's close to the sea in the suburb.
You say you haven't seen the sea.
My sister has a boat.
We can go to the sea by boat.
We can catch crabs.
Go to your sister's home?
Liangchen.
You are a man.
It is inappropriate to live with Xiaojun.
There will be gossip
if you do that.
Maybe it's OK for you.
But Xiaojun is a girl.
It will be inconvenient.
You're right, bro.
You see, boy.
Even fools know better than you do.
No.
Who is the fool?
I didn't mean you, my dear.
I think it's exactly what you mean.
It's inconvenient as well
to live in your home, isn't it?
Of course it's convenient.
Liangchen
is my buddy.
Let go.
Don't touch him.
What?
Oh, my god.
Are you jealous?
It's just a touch.
Are you finished?
Alright. Alright.
I'll go with you.
Great.
No, you can't.