[English subtitles are available]
Arsenal Military Academy
Episode 16
Don't be hurried.
Wait a moment.
Chick.
Wait for me.
Wait for me. Don't go.
A poem says that "how do singers know our national crisis.
They are still drown in the entertainment".
Our country is at stake,
facing a serious crisis.
You joined the army at this time.
You are setting a good example for others.
There are many ways of patriotism,
as long as we want and do.
You studied in Japan.
Learning knowledge
is also a kind of patriotism.
Good eyes.
There is a saying of Hanfeizi that
when there is peace, the traitors are favoured,
and when there is a crisis, the loyal take the place.
We never lack of the intelligent
from the past to the present.
But
we lack of someone like you,
who dares to contribute
to our country now.
Now that you think highly of Military Academy,
why don't you join the army?
That's the meaning of my return.
Really?
That's wonderful.
Maybe we can be schoolmates.
Probably.
Now our country is in danger,
which matters the future of our people.
Study?
What's the use of study?
You can't say that.
It is still useful
to learn the advanced knowledge.
Is it entirely useless of our
long-term study in Japan?
Japan is near us and our cultures have similarities.
What we should do is studying
from each other to make progresses.
Xie Liancheng
has a different idea?
We are peers.
Just have a casual talk during the boring trip.
You are welcomed to show your idea.
I think
Japan gained a complete victory in the Sino-Japanese War,
then it conquered Korea.
What's more, it beat Russia in the northeast.
Japan has been invincible in Eastern Asia.
Japan's territory is not large,
but it is puffed up with ambition.
Under this situation,
I don't think it's right
to hold the idea of
studying from each other.
He's right.
You are right.
I didn't do a deep study.
Just say something casual.
These years,
reports of demise of nations are everywhere.
That's not fresh to the public.
But most people just blow off some steam.
They all talk books away,
but few of them
put them into practice.
10 years ago,
our government helped Japan against Russia,
which was cooperating with a wolf against a tiger.
You joined the army
in the north
during this stirring time.
Obviously,
you are not a talker.
I'm flattered.
After arriving in Peking,
we'll have meetings with students in there.
You are welcomed to join us
if you have interests.
Thank you.
If you are available,
come to my house.
Is there something?
Look at it.
Your affair with that actress
takes up a lot of space.
I can't be relaxed even when reading newspapers.
Really?
Let me check their photo technique.
So bad! I don't look handsome.
Is this your important thing?
I'll go back now.
Wait a moment.
Have a seat.
Your mom has arrived in Peking to see your sister.
I am leaving for Peking today.
Don't make troubles
during this time, OK?
Peking?
I'll go with you.
Why?
I'm bored.
There's no interest staying here alone.
Can you feel bored?
Wait for me. I'll pack up my belongings.
The train is leaving in the afternoon.
Xiang, you are back!
Give me.
It's mine.
Xiang, you are back.
You push me.
Go there.
Check.
Xiang, you are back.
How are you?
You become darker and thinner.
Are you overwhelmed at school?
Mom.
Keep it.
I am slimmer.
What slimmer?
Is the food in your school not good?
Pretty good.
Xiang.
Feng'an is not peaceful now.
I know from your dad that
the Japanese have submitted the Twenty-one Demands
to the government,
and sent more reinforcements there.
Meanwhile, the students are always
parading on the streets,
claiming that the war is coming.
Your dad and I are so worried.
There is no difference in terms of study.
You don't have to stay in Feng'an.
Mom.
By the way.
Mr. Sun has left Nanking, and he is teaching
in Zhongshan Medical University.
Your dad visited him just now.
Can you
study in Peking?
Mom,
I want to stay in Feng'an.
But...
Mom,
I know what I'm doing.
Please let me study in Feng'an.
My brother left us in there.
I'm always thinking
I can be closer to him.
Xiang.
Open the door.
Hi.
Xiang.
Who is out there?
Someone on a wrong path.
Someone on a wrong path?
The one is still here. Come.
Open the door.
Mr. Xie.
Nice to meet you.
Who are you?
He is my classmate.
You are studying at a girls' school.
Why do you have a male classmate?
Tan Xiaojun is my friend.
Through her,
I made friends with Xie Xiang.
This time,
I deal with some business with my father here.
So I come to visit you specially.
I apologize if I offend.
I see.
Come in.
Thank you.
This is...
Nice to meet you.
He is Xiaojun's friend.
Xiaojun's friend?
I am also Xie Xiang' s friend.
Sorry for my abrupt visit.
This is a gift for you.
Come. Come in.
Come, have a seat.
Please.
After you.
OK.
Tell me
who this boy is.
He is just a friend of Xiaojun's.
Why does Xiaojun's friend come here?
You are a good liar.
Tell me the truth.
Are you in a relationship with him?
You don't want to come back
because of him?
Mom, what are you saying?
I'm in a relationship?
Even though I'm in a relationship,
I won't be with him.
So why does he come here
and bring a lot of gifts?
How can I know?
Yunzhi.
Could you bring us some tea?
OK.
I'll ask you later.
Your father is Vice Minister Gu?
He often mentioned you to me.
He told me that you, the mainstay of
the Peking academic circle and education,
have a wide range of knowledge.
And you are a good example
for our young generation.
I also admire you so much.
I read carefully all of the articles
written by you on North Sea Daily
and Eastern Morning News.
Especially the latest one, the one about
primitive accumulation of capital in Western society,
is really amazing
and thought-provoking.
My father brings that newspaper
to Peking especially
to let the politicians
who don't fulfil their duties
know what
inspiring good advice is.
I'm flattered.
Is Gu Yanzhen crazy?
Where did he find these?
Mr. Gu
is the one who I respect the most.
The Japanese pressed us to sign unequal demands.
It was Mr. Gu who helped us
to reverse the situation.
If there are more officers
like Mr. Gu,
the future of our country
will be hopeful.
Thank you.
I'm telling the truth.
My father always says that
he is just an ordinary officer,
but the intelligent people
like you are the hope of our nation.
Especially during the turbulent days,
even 100 politicians
can't equal one intellect.
Since politicians can only balance the conflict
based on the existed situation temporarily.
But people like you
guide us to a brand new
and right way in dark.
Pickthank.
Mr. Gu.
Just call me Yanzhen.
Mr. Gu,
how did you get to know
our Xiang?
We met at a trip
organized by Xiaojun.
I see.
Have you been to Feng'an?
No.
You are from the south?
Yes.
I'm from Zhenjiang, Jiangsu.
It's no wonder that
you are elegant,
which makes you distinguished from others.
Since Jiangsu cultivates beauties.
From the moment I entered,
I have known that there must be
a well-educated hostess
in this family when I saw
the furnishing in this house.
What a sweet boy.
Yes.
Stay here for lunch.
I'll cook good food for you.
I'm preparing lunch now.
No!
Thanks.
I'm looking forward to your cooking.
Thank you a lot.
Come, have a cup of tea.
OK.
Who asks you to come here?
Why are you here?
I'm here to visit your parents.
Who asks you to do this?
It's normal that
I come to visit them
for we are close friends
and living under one roof.
Don't you think so?
You...
Hush.
Be quiet. Don't let your parents hear.
Rogue.
I know.
You are on purpose.
You can tell it.
You just want me to suffer.
I could have been enjoying my break
if you were not here to bother me.
It's weird that
you are not happy when seeing me.
I thought you missed me.
You think too much.
Actually,
I just want to visit
the parents who
bring up a daughter...
bring up a daughter disguising herself
like a man to study at a military academy.
It's none of your business.
Go back immediately after lunch.
Do you hear me?
Depends on my mood.
Gu Yanzhen!
Alright. I know.
Your parents don't know that
we have been living together for long.
Why would your dad ask me to stay?
I have no excuse to stay.
Mind your words.
Who has been living together with you?
You look quite good in the lady's dress.
You don't expose anything.
But man's wear suits you better.
Xiang.
Mr. Gu, come for lunch.
OK.
I'm going to have lunch.
Will you go with me?
We didn't know you would come today,
so we didn't prepare anything special.
These are homely dishes. Quite good.
Here's another dish.
Come.
Have a seat.
OK.
These are all homely.
Help yourself.
Smells good.
I should behave well
for this is my first time to come.
But I may wolf down
since the dishes are so inviting.
Please forgive me for my rudeness.
Help yourself.
Make yourself at home.
Can you drink?
Yes.
I have no reason to refuse it
even if I can't drink much.
That's good.
Let me do it.
Xiang,
how can you let our guest do it?
Leave it to me.
Dad.
Come.
Mr. Xie, toast to you.
Wish you and Mrs. Xie
healthy and well-off.
Thank you.
Sit down.
Come, have a seat.
Also have a taste
of the dishes.
OK. Thank you so much.
You are welcome.
I'm happy that you love my cooking.
I don't know whether you like this flavour.
So delicious.
Mrs. Xie, you are able to run
a restaurant in Peking with this skill.
I just cook as usual.
That can't be called as "skill".
Mrs. Xie, what I said is the truth.
I tasted the dishes made by
the royal chefs of Qing Dynasty.
I think
you are much better than them.
Really?
That's enough.
You performed too much.
Xiang.
Mind your manner.
Mom,
how can you stand
his exaggerated words?
This is courtesy.
He's not like you.
Look at you.
You are not restrained during this year.
Xie Xiang is too young
to understand this.
She's not young.
You are not much older than her.
But
you speak and behave
much better than her.
It's our fault that she is like this.
Yes.
Have a taste.
-Help yourself. -OK.
Who lets you in?
Get out.
Is this your room?
So small.
Of course it's smaller than your mansion.
Get out.
I'm asking you to get out.
Mr. and Mrs. Xie, I must leave now.
See you.
You will spend more days in Peking, right?
Hope to see you next time.
OK.
I'll miss here for
Mrs. Xie' s cooking is amazing.
Xiang,
show Yanzhen out.
Why do I have to show an adult out?
Please be courteous.
This is his first time to be here,
and he is our guest.
Do you think it's polite to treat him like this?
Right.
Alright.
I'll show him out.
Don't you go?
Mr. and Mrs. Xie.
See you.
Have a nice day.
Let's go.
Hello, Hong.
Why do you go so fast?
Alright, you go alone.
Don't be so hardhearted.
I saw you off at the train station when you left.
You talked nonsense at my home!
Did I go to your home?
You are welcomed to come.
Meaningless conversation.
I'll stay in Peking for several days.
I treat you meals.
No, thanks.
Don't be too polite.
I'll be waiting for you at here
at 8am tomorrow.
I'll find you at your home
if you don't come.
Gu Yanzhen,
don't go too far.
I'll take it as a "yes".
See you tomorrow.
What's going on?
Don't worry.
Everything is under our control.
Where are these students?
They've arrived.
Our men have gone into their march,
keeping a close watch on them.
When they get to Peking,
no one of them can live.
Now that these students
don't know what it means
and come to death in Peking,
we'll send them to hell.
He asked me to come but he is not here?
Run?
How dare you run?
Dodge?
I'll give you a bigger one.
How old are you?
Still play such childish game with kids?
Aren't you embarrassed?
I didn't come back for one year.
There's no change in Peking.
What change can it have?
I'll go back
if you don't have other things.
My mom is waiting for me to have lunch.
Good.
I'm hungry now.
Let's have lunch at your home.
You don't want me to go?
That's easy.
You accompany me to eat something.
Rogue.
I have put up with
this word.
What do you want to eat?
Hotpot is the best partner
of the cold weather.
He Restaurant?
Or Tan Restaurant?
Or we go to eat roast duck?
Lucky Here
or Cheap Tavern?
Choose one.
Give me some advice.
Don't be silent.
Barbecue, sheep soup
or western food?
French
or Japanese dish?
I want soya bean milk and fried bread.
Can you change to another one?
I can't eat these.
Whatever.
Enjoy your lunch.
Thank you.
This is not for people.
Stay hungry if you don't eat.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Lin Xianwei.
I'm Chen Rong.
This is Lu Yong, my classmate.
Nice to meet you.
They are our main members.
Are all our members here?
No.
To guarantee our safety,
only those most important ones come.
Others are awaiting orders at the rest area.
OK.
This is not a good place for talking.
Let's go to Lu Yong's house now.
Is it convenient to go there?
Yes.
There's no other one at my house.
It's a quiet place.
It's a safety zone.
Our classmates
are also waiting for us at there.
OK.
Let's go. OK.
Go.
Where is this place?
Would you like to go in?
Is someone living here?
No.
Why is it so clean?
The servants come to clean every once in a while.
Come.
Is this your family photo?
You looked quite good when you were young.
Of course.
I don't have my mom's photo.
This may be the last one.
Your mom...
She passed away
when I was eight.
I'm sorry.
You don't need to apologize.
Don't show me this expression.
My stepmother treats me well.
My mother was different.
The things in this house
were all the weapons she used to hit me.
My mom also always hits me.
Only mom does this,
which proves that she loves you.
Really?
Your mom is beautiful.
Yes.
She spent her whole life on beauty.
She fulfilled her wish by
leaving us at her most glorious age.
Take it for me.
Give me that when we get to school.
Why don't you keep it yourself?
I'm afraid that I lose it.
Don't blame me if I lose it.
Do you dare?
Xianwei.
Everybody,
welcome back.
Calamity is the touchstone of a man.
On behalf of the students in Peking,
I thank you a lot.
Chen Rong,
this is what we should do.
Now our nation is in danger.
Our young generation should do our best
to protect our country and people.
So many music instruments.
Can you play the piano?
Of course.
Who am I?
Is there anything I don't know?
Play it for me.
Why do I listen to you?
You were bragging.
My mom didn't have hobbies,
but she liked celebrating birthdays.
She bought music instruments on her birthdays.
In our family,
"happy birthday" means "I love you".
But she could dance.
Does it still work?
I don't know.
Can you dance?
Yes.
Dance with me.
Why do I listen to you?
Everybody,
the Twenty-one Demands
put forward by the Japanese
is a shame of our nation.
Looking back at the shames during our
hundreds of years' of history,
none was equal to the one we are facing.
If it goes on,
our nation will disappear soon.
Parades
and protests
are everywhere
in Guangzhou,
Shanghai, Hong Kong,
Nanking and Wuhan.
So,
we go back from Japan
to join the students in Peking
to make our voice heard,
telling the weak government
that we never compromise.
Never compromise.
The route of our parade is
going north from the west crossing of Legation Street,
and passing Wealth Road, Horse Lane
and North Street,
getting to Tan Restaurant.
We should contact the students in every school.
Wear our school uniforms and make slogans.
The slogans must accord with our subject
which is objecting to the Twenty-one Demands and
the Japan's occupation of Tsingtao.
Chop.
Students who studied in Japan have signed.
We are nobody now,
but we should have great ambitions.
The blood letter can prove this.
Hurry. Let's go.
Lu Yong!
Go.
I'll kill you.
Lin Xianwei,
are you all right?
All right.
We are patriotic students.
These are killers sent by the Japanese.
Lu Yong.
Hurry.
How dare you arrest me?
Are you blind?
Go.
Hurry.
What are you doing?
Don't touch her.
Do you want to die?
Stop wasting time on talking.
Arrest them.
Go.
It was the Japanese.
Didn't you see that?
The Japanese killed my classmates. Go.
Be quick. It was the Japanese.
Go up. Chop.
Hurry.
Go in.
Go up.
What should we do?
Go to Song Maogong.
Yes.
We didn't kill anyone.
It was the Japanese.
My classmate is still alive.
Be quiet.
Sir?
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
My family will be worried about me.
Don't worry.
Let me think of a way.
Xie.
Why do you pretend to be a man?
I have my difficulty.
You don't need to worry any more.
It has nothing to do with you.
You'll be released when they make it clear.
When did you meet these students?
When I was on the train to Peking.
Don't contact them frequently.
Follow me out later.
They are good people.
We can't leave them here.
There are many good people.
How can you take care of all of them?
Alright.
It's fine that you want to save them.
When I go out, I'll think about it.
But you must promise me
to follow me out.
Instead of catching
the murderers, you police
prison us with no reason.
Is there still justice?
We are patriotic students
who studied in Japan.
Let us out.
Why do you arrest us without a reason?
You don't have right to prison us.
Let us out.
So noisy!
Be quiet!
Stay quietly.
And you.
Don't make mess.
Why don't you students
live a peaceful life
instead of making trouble all day?
What do you want?
It takes me a lot of time
and strength to catch you.
Do you still want to go out
after this big event when
many people lost their lives?
They were not killed by us.
No. The Japanese did it.
We didn't kill others. Let us out!
The victims are our classmates.
Why should I trust you?
We have evidence.
Evidence?
Your evidence comes after the investigation.
What investigation?
Let us out!
Calm down. Is there still justice?
When is the hearing?
It's none of our business.
Three to five days at least.
Three to five months at most.
One or two years can also be possible.
Don't hurry.
You! You are flunkies!
You are traitors!
-Let us out! -Be quiet!