[English subtitles are available]
Arsenal Military Academy
Episode 42
Miss, keep chasing?
Why?
That was already ruined.
Wasn't this burnt?
There is another note book on the desk.
I got two.
Only one was burnt.
Brilliant!
How can I let such an important thing
be burnt?
What's on this?
I don't understand.
Can you?
Don't look at me!
I'm nearly illiterate!
Song,
we know this.
It sounds like
you can understand this.
We almost lost our lives
on making great efforts
to get this useless thing.
We don't even understand it.
No matter what it is,
it means a lot to the Japanese.
Or, Oda Xianrong wouldn't have come for this.
Isn't the man a translator?
But he has left.
Well,
let me try.
You are not the only one who can look it up.
I can, too.
Shut up!
Why should I shut up?
Don't say that.
- I want! - Stop that.
I want to say!
I…
Seriously?
I want!
I said it!
Really?
So what? I said it!
Can you understand?
Say it again!
Go.
Look at you.
What's wrong?
Why should I go?
Enough!
Hey.
Coming!
Song?
What's up?
What happened?
Liangchen,
I,
I want to ask you,
where is Xie Xiang?
I can't find her at her school
recently.
Did something happen to her?
No.
She has gone back to Peking.
Back to Peking?
When will she come back?
She won't.
What?
Then where will she go?
She will
study abroad.
Abroad?
She has already left.
She won't come back?
Song.
Huang Song!
What happened?
I don't know.
What's going on?
Coming!
Liangchen,
let's go.
Follow me to a place.
Where?
A good place.
Go dress up.
Now!
What's that?
Why so mysterious?
Cut your question.
Go now.
Dress neatly.
Got it.
OK.
Ready?
Wait a second.
Is your sister as tall as you?
Wait,
she is a little shorter than you.
That's fine.
I can stand on my toes.
Get down here!
You are taking photos with me,
and what do you have to do with my sister?
Be serious.
OK.
Sir, you can start.
Wait!
What again?
Liangchen,
stay close to me.
Closer.
You are so annoying.
More smile.
Smile.
Yes, right.
Is it OK?
Yes.
We can start.
One, two, three.
Why do you want to take photos now?
Nothing.
I just want to take photos.
After I earn money later,
I will take my sister,
brother-in-law and He
to take photos together.
We haven't got a family photo yet.
A photo doesn't cost so much.
Why should you wait later?
I can borrow a camera
and take photos for you and your family.
Really?
Sure.
Why should I lie to you?
Great!
Liangchen,
my sister is pregnant.
I will
become an uncle!
Really?
That'll be great!
We can go together then.
Perfect.
Huang Song?
Gu Yanzhen.
Why are you back now?
Grown up, huh?
You dare to drink here.
Aren't you afraid of being caught by Lv?
I'm sad now.
What happened?
I lost my love.
What?
Have you ever fallen in love?
No.
Then why did you say that?
I've made a decision
that I'll keep studying
and find a good job
with a good salary.
When I get enough money,
I'll build a big house for my
sister and her husband.
The biggest one in our village.
And after that,
I will think about marriage.
Come on,
cheers.
Tell you what,
I'm not drunk.
Yes, right.
Go get more wine for me.
You're not drunk.
Go wait outside.
I'll bring you wine.
Alcoholic.
I tell you...
Open the door!
Last time,
you said you would marry me.
Is that still counting?
Yes.
Why are you back?
Didn't I tell you not to drink so much?
Why are you drunk again?
I'm bored.
What could I do
if I don't drink?
You drunk because you were bored?
Are you hungry?
Yes.
Let's go back
and I'll make noodles for you.
Back to where?
Back to home!
Do you have a home?
The tavern.
The house
of the tavern is mine.
But that is my home.
Tell me why,
why did you come back?
You are not happy?
No.
I thought you wouldn't be back.
It was
like a dream.
On the 7th,
Evan went to Mozi Mountain with the translator
and stayed for three days.
On the 13th,
they went to Yushantun
and stayed for two days.
And then Gutainan
for one day.
On the 25th,
he took the translator to Xiantao Village
and stayed for days
until he accidentally
died in the gunfight on the 29th.
This is Evan's whole trip
in Shunyuan this month.
The location should be around here.
There should still be under the government's control,
and it's large.
It's not easy for us to get it.
Make an appointment with Mayor Bai for me.
Yes.
According to the contents,
this Russian
should be an excellent geologist.
The distribution of minerals in Shunyuan
is recorded in detail in the notebook.
I thought it should be something important.
What is important
is about the distribution of graphite ore.
What is graphite ore?
A kind of minerals.
Graphite has good
chemical stability at high temperatures.
The specially processed graphite
is corrosion-resistant,
heat-conductive and
has low permeability.
The most important
is that graphite can make steel.
If enough graphite were available,
Japanese steel production
would at least
be triple.
What do iron and steel mean
to the country?
Do I need to explain it?
That
seems to be their purpose.
They are so greedy.
I still have a question.
What
do iron and steel mean to a country?
I don't understand.
The iron and steel are…
Song,
you don't need to
understand this kind of things.
Just forget it.
Then what should we do now?
Here is it,
since this is so important to them,
it means that they still
don't know the location of it yet.
Then let's start first
and get the land.
This is mining!
It can't be this easy!
It's difficult for others,
but for me…
Wait for my news.
Let me see this.
Take this one there.
Go.
Master,
did young master cause trouble again?
This time
he did a good job.
Yes,
yes, right.
You are totally right.
Yes.
Don't worry,
I can handle this.
OK.
OK. Alright. Yes.
Then that's it.
OK.
Bye.
What's wrong?
The phone calls can't stop for the whole morning.
Who was it this time?
Vice Director Gu.
He asked me for help.
Isn't he in Nanjing?
Yes. So what?
Don't you know his power?
Since he has asked,
I should help him anyway.
Well,
what's that?
He wants me
to give the No.9 land
to Shen Family.
They want to mine that place.
What does it have to do with Shen Family?
Mr. Gu's son and Mr. Shen's second son
are classmates in the Academy.
Then just give it to them.
It's about Gu Family
and Shen Family.
That's not difficult to decide.
It's easy to say it,
but the problem is
that the Japanese COC also called me
for lands just now.
And the
No.9 land is in them.
I have already promised them.
Japanese?
Why did they get involved too?
Who knows?
So what to do now?
If you promise one,
the other will surely be offended.
Miss,
a call from the government
told us that
No.9,
No.10 and No.11 land
will be auctioned
at the City Hall
in seven days.
Auction?
Didn't Mayor Bai promise us
that he would sell these three lands to us?
Something must have happened.
Documents about the auction
have been formally issued.
There's no way to change it.
How to?
The auction
is open to people from all walks of life.
The main items are these lands.
The rest
are some antiques and shops.
Old fox!
It seems that someone
wants to compete with us for these lands.
Prepare the money now.
Yes.
Shop No. 10 on Shunyuan South Street.
120,000 first!
120,000 second!
Last chance!
3.
2.
1.
Shop No.10 is sold at the price
120,000 to the bidder No.4!
Congratulations!
Alright.
Next lot!
This one
is very special.
I think you have been waiting for it for so long.
Yes!
This is the No.5 lot!
You can look at the catalogue.
The No.5 lot
is at a good location with a large area.
It's a hot item at this auction.
We'll start at 50,000,
and every bid should be more than 2,000.
Now let's start!
No.41, 52,000.
No.88, 54,000.
No.63, 56,000.
No.18, 58,000.
Any more bids?
Anyone?
Any?
This is a bundle of the three lands.
And market value
of each of them is more than 30,000.
It's a good chance!
Any more bids?
Anyone?
100,000!
No.75 gives 100,000!
Any higher bids?
Anyone?
100,000 first!
What about us?
100,000 second!
No.44 gives 102,000!
No.44, 102,000!
110,000!
No.75 gives 110,000!
Any higher bids?
Any more?
No.44!
112,000!
150,000!
No.75 gives 150,000!
Any higher bids?
No?
150,000 first!
Wait a second.
150,000 second!
Last…
200,000!
No.44 gives 200,000!
Any more bids?
Looks like we don't have to do it anymore.
Miss,
our deposit is not enough.
200,000 first!
200,000 second!
Last chance!
3, 2, 1!
No.9, No.10 and
No.12 land at the suburb
are sold at the price 200,000
to the bidder No.44!
Congratulations!
This is the end of this auction.
Thanks for your coming!
Lord Chengrui!
Congratulations on
buying these three lands with 200,000.
This is a big deal in Shunyuan.
Lord is so generous!
That's nothing.
And I should thank for your help.
I wonder what you will do with them.
For some business?
I don't know yet.
I want to ask you
for your advice.
Stop kidding me.
You spent 200,000 on it.
You must have your own purpose.
Why did you ask me?
To be honest, I know nothing about them.
I came today because
I heard that
Oda Xianrong from the COC
wants to get these lands intensely.
And you, Shunyuan COC
is also interested in them.
I belong to the lost Qing Dynasty.
And I was too idle
to run a business,
not like you,
a business elite.
If you could
help me with these three lands,
and make some difficulties for the Japanese,
I would like to cooperate with you.
This is not a good place for talking.
Lord,
please.
Although news from Rong Mansion
said that her ladyship died of illness,
it must have something to do with Oda Xianrong.
If that's true,
then maybe we could
trust Lord's words.
Rong Mansion is rich and generous.
As for money,
none of us and the Japanese can fight against him.
And Lord Chengrui has studied abroad
and is open-minded,
who is different
from those
stubborn people who always want to
restore Qing Dynasty.
Except for these three lands,
he even paid 300,000 for the mining.
He is so sincere.
Compared with the Japanese,
he is already on our side.
Mine construction and mining are not that easy,
and we have no technician,
and no equipment,
although we temporarily get the lands,
there is still a lot to do.
Gu Yanzhen's father
transported a batch of equipments
for our early exploration.
Professor He of Peking University
introduced several experts to me in this field
and wrote us the recommendation letter.
We'll set off
early tomorrow morning
and visit them one by one.
We must invite them over.
As for the Academy,
I have talked to Director Guo.
OK.
Wish us a success.
This matter
is too important
for both our family
and our country.
Junshan!
You're back.
Are you going out?
Where are you going?
Let me send you to there.
Don't bother.
I will go with Gu Yanzhen.
I haven't seen you much lately.
I'm doing something for my family.
About the graphite mine?
Did you start?
Almost.
The machines will arrive this afternoon.
Didn't Gu Yanzhen tell you?
He also has shares.
He said he didn't want to care about this.
I'm leaving now.
Bye.
Professor Chen,
you must be tired.
Professor Wu,
welcome!
OK.
Let's go.
This way.
Please.
This is Chen Yue and Wu Jinzhi?
Yes,
both of them
came back from England,
and are Mr. Matsumoto's classmates.
They are famous in the field of geology.
Mr. Matsumoto
recommended them in particular.
We sent people to invite them for several times,
but they all refused.
Unexpectedly,
they went to Shen Family.
Mr. Miyazawa said
if they can't
work for us,
then they don't have to exist.
Professor.
Get on the car.
Professor Chen,
Mrs. Chen,
today is the New Year's Day.
We want to invite you for dinner.
OK.
Thank you.
Come on.
Watch out!
Come on!
Follow me!
Professor, are you OK?
I'm fine.
How is it?
Everything all right?
That's fine.
It's not safe here.
Get on first.
Hurry, I'll drive.
Hurry up!
Go!
Come on!
You got the tomatoes on sticks.
Happy now?
Yes.
That's great.
Dad,
the sugar falls on my hand.
Really?
Come here,
let me help you.
Let me see…
OK.
Let's go.
Only a few words.
I'll leave after that.
The three lands you got
are really important to me.
And if they are in your hands,
it's not good
for both of you
and the Rong Mansion.
Are you threatening me?
You can think so.
If you are willing to sell them to me,
I could pay you double the price.
I'm not.
You should know,
in order to get these lands,
we will do whatever it takes,
regardless of the consequences.
Not only our COC,
also the Japanese military.
You can't stop that.
If I don't give you,
what would you do?
You want to know what
I would do?
Yes.
But the more I want to know
is how black your heart is now.
I will give you three days
to think about it.
You'd better persuade him.
Lord.
Dad, let's go.
Lord!
- Chengrui! - Lord!
Chengrui!
- Lord! - Chengrui!
Lord!
What's wrong?
Chengrui!
- Chengrui! Hang in there! - Lord.
- Chengrui! - Lord!
Chengrui!
My Lord!
Lord!
Ms. Oda,
we meet again.
You have
been trying to kill them for a long time.
And now they have unknowingly become the
obstacles for you and General Miyazawa.
We used to be master and servant,
and we haven't seen each other for a while.
Just treat them as the gift to you.
Now I'm an officer in General
Miyazawa's troop.
We will often meet later.
See you.
Strengthen the protection to the professors.
If the machines broke down,
go order a new batch of them.
We lost a lot on the mine.
There were many workers and machines.
We also have been there.
As for the professors,
I'm afraid that we can't care about both of them.
How about…
You don't worry about this.
I'll figure it out by myself.
Tingbai! Junshan!
Bad news from Rong Mansion!
Gu Yanzhen, from the Gu Family,
is here to worship.
The old Lord
was always kind
to everyone
in Shunyuan city.
I never heard that
he ever offended anyone.
If he
hadn't been framed this time,
he wouldn't have ended like this.
Forget it.
Forget?
We all are the old servants in the Mansion.
If it hadn't been the Lord and her ladyship,
each of us
would have been homeless with a miserable life.
Now the Lord's family
was framed.
Are we who have received
his favor not brave enough
to stand out and speak for them?
The Qing Dynasty has fallen,
and why didn't you, slaves of Qing Dynasty,
all die?
I'm not a slave of Qing Dynasty!
I'm one of Lord's servants!
Without the Lord,
there would be no me today!
Today!
Today in front of Lord and Lord Chengrui!
I, Pei Shun!
This is not done yet!
Mr. Shen,
tell me,
what did the old Lord and Lord Chengrui
die of?
Captain He of the police station is here.
You shouldn't ask me
about this question.
I want you to tell me.
Lord Chengrui and the old Lord
died of the gunshots.
Gunshots?
I'm asking you
what did they die for?
Who killed them?
The Chairman of Japanese COC,
Ms. Oda Xianrong is here.
Stop there!
Xianrong.
You can't leave like this!
I want to know,
whether the old Lord and her ladyship,
and Lord Chengrui
were killed by you?
What if
it's me?
it's not me?
If you did this,
I'll risk my life
to get the revenge on you!
Then have a try.
You!