I'm horrible in kissing scenes.
My first time I did so many takes
the girl laughed at me.
Is that so?
My ex told me I was bad.
I must be a horrible kisser.
- Your ex?
- Mm.
I feel embarrassed talking about this.
Uh... By "my ex,"
you meant a female lover in the past?
Mm. That's right.
It feels weird asking you
who's younger than me.
But if you have a trick, please share.
So...
would you like to try?
Eh?
Rehearsing the kissing scene, I mean.
Uh.
Don't tell me
you're Momoshiro right now.
Eh?
Because Momoshiro
would say something like that.
That's correct!
Did I startle you?
Mm, a little.
Uh, I have to wake up early tomorrow.
I'm gonna take a shower.
Oh, be my guest.
Damn it.
I was trying to kiss Hajime Aoyanagi.
My ex told me I was bad.
Hajime Aoyanagi had a girlfriend.
Of course. It's not strange
for him to have an ex
since he's 25.
But...
Am I in shock he had a girlfriend?
This kind of thought
doesn't belong to a stan.
I have fallen in love.
(Alan Abe plays Yuijiro Akafuji)
(Nichika Akutsu plays Hajime Aoyanagi)
(Based on "I Became the Main Role of a BL Drama"
by Machi Suzuri)
(Opening credits)
(I Became the Main Role of a BL Drama)
(Episode 2)
Mitsutani is cute.
I think I'm gonna call him
by his first name.
Back off. That guy is mine.
Who determines that?
Fate.
Fate determines that.
Haruhi gets off early today.
- I'll ask him out for drinks.
- Don't joke around.
Would you like to try?
Eh?
Rehearsing the kissing scene, I mean.
What exactly was that kiss rehearsal?
Was that a joke?
No.
Because Akafuji looked serious.
But what was it if he wasn't joking?
Was it because he wanted
to make this drama good?
- Your eyebrows were about to entangle.
- Oh, Miss Tendo.
You can vent your worries
because I play your sister this time.
And I'm your confidant in this drama.
- So...
- Mm.
- It's about an actor I know.
- There's a kissing scene on a show.
- Mm.
And it seemed like this actor's co-star
asked the actor to rehearse
the kiss at the co-star's place.
There are line rehearsals,
but I'd never heard of kiss rehearsals.
So I assume other people do it.
Using a rehearsal as
an excuse is sexual harassment.
Oh? I don't think so.
That's abuse of power. It's despicable.
It creeps me out just hearing it.
- It creeps you out?
- Doesn't it?
No...
Apparently not.
Is that so?
Yes.
But it's possible that
the co-star has feelings for the actor.
Eh?
Has feelings for the actor?
Akafuji has feelings for me?
While talking to Miss Tendo,
Hajime Aoyanagi's subtle smile
is 30 percent of his expression.
No, it's more than 50 percent.
If I remember correctly,
a celebrity magazine from five years ago
said he liked older partners.
What is this anxiety?
Jealousy?
Or is this jealousy?
Akafuji! Can we talk?
Yes!
Aoyanagi!
- Can we talk?
- Yes!
Oh, go around that way.
I'm Hajime Aoyanagi.
I play Mitsutani Haruhi.
I'm Yuijiro Akafuji.
I play Momoshiro Akifumi.
"I Love My Childhood Friend"
is about to go on air.
- Please stay tuned.
- Mm, okay. Thanks.
- Thank you.
- Upload it.
- Yes.
Uh, I think if you're
putting it on social media,
it will go viral if we add
aspects from the drama.
- Like what?
- Like...
Stay in character
and do a hug from behind.
- I see. That's not bad.
- Really?
My feelings dictate my suggestion,
but am I being too self-indulgent?
- Mr. Hajime, is that okay?
- Oh. Mm, of course.
That's a relief.
Awesome. He dared present his own idea.
Akafuji takes this drama very seriously.
So, are you guys ready?
- Yes.
The last time I was hugged from behind
was by my on-screen mother
when I was a child star.
If I hug him from behind, I won't
have to look at Hajime Aoyanagi's face.
- So, may I?
- Yes.
I've always wanted to do this.
Don't leave my side.
I want to make you mine alone.
Eh? Why...?
How was that?
Shit. I might have hugged him too hard.
Good.
Great!
- That was awesome. Post it!
- Yes!
- So good.
- Thank you very much.
(Every Saturday at 11 PM)
I want to make you mine alone.
(Akayu? Awesome.)
(He's so Mitsutani.)
(Can't wait to meet Akayu's Momoshiro.)
(The live-action version might be a hit.)
(I wanna see the drama now.)
(I wanna be hugged from behind.)
All comments are positive.
What a relief.
Why...
was my heart beating so fast?
Finally we met.
I got into the show biz because
I wanted to meet you, Mr. Kiromiya.
When I found out you were filming here,
I figured my dream would come true.
Kiromiya! The producers want you!
Mr. Aoyanagi.
Sorry, I saw you were in trouble.
Oh! If I was meddling, I'm really sorry.
I...
I was scared to death!
Eh? You're not good with girls?
In high school,
I was stalked and harassed.
From then on, I've been scared of girls
who make blatant advances.
My selling point is arrogance.
I'm so pathetic.
You're not pathetic.
In our field, images dictate everything.
Even though we're grateful, we suffer.
Yuijiro is very different
from his image.
Mm, I guess.
I thought he'd be more composed.
And when he's with his cat,
he drops all pretense.
Eh? Akafuji has a cat?
Eh? You didn't know?
- No.
- Really?
He probably left it
in his manager's care for now.
Look at this photo.
Haven't you guys talked at all?
You're living together.
No. But we talk shop sometimes.
Yeah?
(With my co-star, Hajime.
#ILoveMyFriend Don't miss it!)
He calls him Hajime?
Without any honorifics?
Mr. Yukari, what does this mean?
He seems closer to Mr. Kiromiya
than to you who lives with him.
You...
didn't have to spell it out like that.
When I really think about it,
I only talk to Akafuji about work.
(Yuijiro Akafuji)
If I'm gonna look him up,
I might as well ask Kiromiya.
But that seems strange.
- Oh? Good morning.
- Eh? Didn't you have work?
I'm off today so I went for a run.
- Run?
- It's my routine.
Routine?
Morning runs are quite refreshing.
- Here's the thing, Akafuji.
- Yes?
What do you usually do on your days off?
On my next drama, I play a boxer.
On my next commercial,
I have to do archery.
Wow.
Wanna try, Mr. Hajime?
Eh?
Stretch your arm slowly.
On my next film,
I have to do indoor rock climbing.
Is that so?
All the way up there?
Awesome.
Even on his days off, he does
so many things to build his characters.
I have to train hard
because my manager is tough.
We ended up talking
about only work today.
Mr. Hajime?
You'd never done rock climbing?
No.
Talking about shared interests is fun.
Plus we relate to our characters more.
Thanks.
But this is not that.
The first time
my fingers hurt really bad too.
But why am I this curious about him?
For some reason, I'm upset that
Kiromiya knows him better than I do.
Huh?
Upset?
Mr. Hajime?
Huh?
Are you okay? Are you tired?
- Here's the thing.
- Yes?
The kissing scene's next week, right?
Eh?
Oh.
That's right.
I told you I wasn't good
in kissing scenes.
So I want to rehearse.
Eh?
Can we?
Well...
If this is about me saying
I wanted to rehearse,
you don't have to force yourself.
We can confirm on set.
No, I'm not forcing myself.
I want to rehearse, too.
So...
shall we?
Mm.
I'm sorry.
It's my family.
We'll do it later.
Mm-hm.
Mm-hm. I'm fine.
Mm. I'm great.
Oh, say hi to Grandma for me. Mm.
Yes. Yes.
Was I...
trying to kiss Hajime Aoyanagi?
Kiss Hajime Aoyanagi.
Kiss, kiss, kiss.
Kiss, kiss, kiss, kiss. I like. I like.
Awesome!
I like. I like. I like. I like. I like.
I like Hajime Aoyanagi.
I like. I like.
I like?
Hot! So hot!
(Genki TV)
"I Love My Friend"
will air in five days!
- Please stay tuned.
- Okay! Thank you very much!
- Okay.
- Oh, sorry.
- It's okay.
Yuijiro?
Eh?
Here's come my chance
to use his first name!
I noticed Kiromiya call you like that.
No. Should I call you Yuijiro?
I prefer calling you Akafuji.
Eh?
He's gonna go back to use my last name?
Sure.
Those two seem closer. What a relief!
You think so?
Huh?! You're into Hajime?!
Keep your voice down.
Mm.
But I have to talk through
my character to communicate with him.
- Hold on.
- Plus he talked to Miss Tendo during a break.
So I think he might like older women.
Stop right now!
I don't follow.
Why are you consulting me
on the matter of the heart?
I don't have a choice.
You're the only one I can talk to.
I guess you don't have friends.
I just thought you wouldn't tease me.
Plus you seem very close
to Hajime Aoyanagi lately.
That's normal.
You also called him by his first name
without honorifics.
- That's normal.
- It's not.
But why? Did you like him
since he was a child star?
About that...
It's a secret.
You wanted advice but won't tell me?
How should I tell him my feelings?
There's no use if you're into him.
But don't go too far.
Go too far?
I mean even though you live together,
don't get any ideas.
Like forcing a kiss.
Or anything more than that.
Because living together is a part
of the show's promotional plan.
If things go wrong,
the show will get shelved.
Get shelved?
Let's make this drama good.
"I Love My Friend"
will air in five days!
They posted the video.
(- Please stay tuned.)
(Akayu's awesome.)
(He's fully Momoshiro now.)
(I love Akafuji's Momoshiro.)
(Wait, they're both perfect.)
(I wanna watch Mitsutani,
not Hajime Aoyanagi.)
(He's just Hajime Aoyanagi.)
(Must this guy play Mitsutani?
But Momoshiro is okay.)
(He doesn't seem right
for Akayu at all.)
(They went with the Orange Juice Boy?)
Get shelved. Get shelved.
Get shelved. Get shelved. Get shelved.
But why? Did you like him
since he was a child star?
I'm back.
- You're back, Akafuji?
- Yes.
I'm a little tired.
I'm gonna take a shower.
I am cooking, and Hajime Aoyanagi is about to take a bath.
We look so much like newlyweds~
Uh, don't think about it...
Uh, Mr. Hajime?
Huh?
I'm gonna sleep on the couch tonight.
Why?
I can gauge the distance
between our characters now.
If I'm around him more than this,
I'm gonna go too far.
It's too risky.
Characters.
(I wanna watch Mitsutani,
not Hajime Aoyanagi.)
Mr. Hajime?
You're good, always thinking
about your character.
I have to take it more seriously too.
Eh?
Sorry.
I'm gonna go to bed.
- Who's Hajime Aoyanagi?
- The Orange Juice Boy.
- Oh.
- He grew up homely.
- He's no good.
- He's got no aura.
- That's hilarious.
- Did you negotiate his fee?
- I had no choice. There's less work.
Hajime Aoyanagi's era is over.
We want the Orange Juice Boy,
not Hajime Aoyanagi.
- Quit auditioning.
- It's too late. Too late.
Don't come here again.
"Good morning.
Please eat if you don't mind."
I'm gonna eat.
It's delicious.
No.
I can't get carried away.
- Mr. Hajime, I'm back.
- You're back?
I'm gonna take a shower.
- Akafuji?
- Yes?
- Thank you for breakfast.
- It's nothing. I'll cook it more...
Huh?
Could it be...
I must focus more on my character.
- Yes, I get it now. I'll look it up.
- Yes.
- Mr. Hajime, you must be tired.
- You too.
Because no one wants someone like me.
This is it. He's avoiding me.
Or did he figure out
that I was into him?
You were staring too hard.
What's up with you and Hajime?
I almost made a mistake
and turned into Icarus.
Huh? Icarus?
Maybe I should give in.
What happened?
Nothing.
I just...
don't want to cause
someone I like trouble.
(Aoyanagi )
That's it... that's it!
- Thank you for today.
Hajime, are you free tomorrow?
- I'm free. No filming.
- Then why don't we go out on the town?
- Eh? Mm, sure.
- Mm.
- Mr. Kiromiya, you're up.
- Yes.
- I'll text you the location.
- Mm.
- You snapped your fingers.
- I was happy.
Can you teach me do that?
Wow. So good. Wow.
I told you earlier that
Hajime has very low self-esteem, right?
- Yes.
- But that's due to his nature too.
What made him that way?
His parents divorced
when he was in junior high school,
and the custody battle was ugly.
Mostly over the money.
Hajime was a sensitive kid and became
so anxious he couldn't act for a while.
Plus he was a teenager.
And the public didn't want him
as a child star anymore.
So he started to lose confidence.
He used to be a famous child star.
Must have been tough.
Mm.
But this project has good crew and cast.
So I wanted it to help
restore his confidence.
I see.
That's why I've been
a little worried about him lately.
By the looks of it,
he might have gone to the dark side.
Or he had an issue with my Akafuji.
Mm. I don't know.
We have to wait and see.
- To be honest...
- Yes?
we act like personal managers.
We are.
Not right now.
Don't stare at me like that.
I'm gonna cry.
I'm sorry for making angry eyes.
But you were the one
starting talking shop.
Oh, you're right. I forgot.
Sorry.
Here.
Cheers.
He's late.
(Kiromiya)
Sorry, I can't make it today.
That's all?
I thought it was odd too
that Kiromiya of a famous idol group
wanted to go out on the town
with a homely has-been like me.
But I was...
secretly happy.
I'm spiraling.
My thoughts are turning dark.
Mr. Hajime?
Akafuji?
Why?
Are you crying?
Thanks.
It's nothing.
Why are you here?
I'm here to meet Kiromiya.
Sorry. Give me a sec.
(Kiromiya)
Don't let this opportunity slip away.
You can do it, Yuijiro.
That guy...
What's wrong?
Mr. Hajime?
If you don't mind,
can we go on a date?
A date?
Uh...
Mitsutani and Momoshiro
go on dates, don't they?
I see.
Actually, that's true.
So, shall we?
- What should we order?
- Desserts.
- Let's race.
- The loser has to pay.
Wait for me!
- Call when you're ready to order.
- Yes.
We went in here as soon as we saw it.
But should two actors go on a date
in a family restaurant?
It's like...
It's like we're students.
You can say that again.
Wow, what should we order?
Eh? What's this?
They have panko fried calamari.
It looks delicious.
The potatoes look yummy too.
It's huge.
Don't tell me you like
family restaurants, Mr. Hajime.
Actually I've never been
to family restaurants.
Eh? What about when you were in school?
It's embarrassing,
but I didn't have friends my age.
So I never went to
these restaurants after school.
Is that so?
That's probably why I'm excited.
So shall we stop by a game center
on our way back?
Let's have fun like
when we were students..
Can we do that?
Of course we can.
- Let's go to the beverage bar.
- Beverage bar?
- Do you know what a beverage bar is?
- Not much.
- Then let's go.
- Thanks.
I'm done.
This is a beverage bar.
- Wow. Melon soda?
- Mm.
Juices too. I'm getting nervous.
You can mix them.
I recommend these two flavors.
Get that flavor a little more.
- Oh. Take it.
- Damn it.
Though I've never gone out on a date...
going to places
someone I like wants to go
and having fun with that person...
- Cat ears are cute.
- Then go with cat ears.
Ready.
That's it?
Doing just that has brought me
this much happiness.
Wait. That's awesome.
It can make our eyes big too.
But the ones
without editing look premium.
- Let's go all out with the editing.
- Mm.
Then make them the biggest.
This is so fun. We can make it pink too.
- Pretty.
- You have light skin, Mr. Hajime.
- No, I don't.
- You really do.
You have light skin too.
I love big eyes like these.
- You like the big photos?
- Mm.
- Can I have them all?
- Of course.
I'm so relieved...
that you're in higher spirits.
Today...
why did you cry?
Many things ran through my mind.
Many things?
Like no one sees me.
When I was a child star,
people called me the "Orange Juice Boy"
more often than "Hajime Aoyanagi."
As an actor, being called
by my character's name
is considered lucky.
But sometimes it makes me sad
that no one sees me...
as Hajime Aoyanagi.
My parents included.
I see you.
Eh?
I'm looking at you.
Of course you're already
an amazing actor.
But...
after living together,
I've found a lot more
of your positive traits.
For example,
you always ask my opinion
before we do something.
In bed, you try to sleep on the edge
of the bed so I sleep more comfortably.
Your kindness has made me very happy.
That's why I like...
Thanks, Akafuji.
Mr. Hajime.
I feel better now.
Mr. Hajime?
Hm?
That park...
was the last place I wanted to
be able to go on a date with you.
Eh? Why's that?
Well...
Mr. Hajime,
do you consider kissing...
at the end of a date?
Eh?
Uh...
I mean...
If it were Mitsutani and Momoshiro,
I think they...
would kiss.
I...
have the same thought.
I'm sorry, Akafuji.
I lied.
During our date, I didn't think
about our characters at all.
Well...
we'll shoot this scene soon.
Can I rehearse more?
Mm.
Really?
(Genki TV)
- No kissing scene?
We thought it was necessary
for the climax at the end,
but them not kissing seems to go in line
with the characters more.
Yes.
Okay?
Are you two okay with that?
- Yes, I am.
No need to continue rehearsing.
Mm, I guess so.
Mr. Hajime?
Let's make this drama good.
Mm.
- The set is ready. Let's start.
- Yes.
- We'll shoot for real.
- Please prepare.
- Check everything.
- Yes.
- Please.
- Can you wipe my sweat?
- Very handsome.
- Thank you.
- Yukari-chan?
- Don't call me that on set.
Should we cancel
the living together thing?
Huh?
We'll shoot for real. Roll the camera.
Okay. Slate.
This is for real.
Ready.
Go.
(Next episode)
Once we wrapped, this life will end.
To be able to love or like something
this much is wonderful.
They hug.
You said we'd make this drama good.
I stopped lying to myself.