Come catch me.
Come here.
The Prince is over here.
Whoever gets caught,
belongs to me.
Your Highness.
Come on.
Over here.
Come here.
Where are you?
Come on.
I'm over here.
Caught you.
It's you.
Are you surprised, Prince?
Drink my wine.
Aren't you afraid I poisoned it?
Would you really?
Leave us.
Walking in like this,
means you've accepted your fate and are willing to be my woman?
I am here to make a deal with you, Prince.
A deal?
Don't you know
that your father has already sold you to me?
Framing the Song Army,
and luring them into the trap... that was all me.
Prince, doing business with a fool,
what good will that do you?
I like smart women.
Marquis Bai and Song Xuan are obstacles to your rule over Dasheng.
Make a deal with me,
and I guarantee they will die.
Then what do you want?
My father's life.
But I've already promised Chancellor Shen.
I can't go back on my word.
Prince,
dead men's words don't count.
Then...
what if you betray me?
I was never yours to begin with,
so how can I betray you?
The bet is on.
If you choose the Bai family,
I'll lose everything.
Anyway, you don't have much time left.
Don't come over!
Don't!
Should we call the Marquis back?
Maybe we should call the Marquis back.
No, the Marquis has been at the Palace these past few days.
He has more important things to do.
Young Master! Young Master!
Young Master, bad news!
There are so many people outside.
It's the families of the children who died at the academy,
along with some riffraff.
They're calling out by name, demanding Marquis Zhongyi's Manor hand over Miss Chuyi.
They also said...
Said what?
They said Miss is a bastard,
a jinx, and she must pay with her life.
Nonsense!
Who allowed them to behave so atrociously in front of the Manor?
Why didn't you stop them?
We tried, but we couldn't stop them.
We couldn't drive them away either.
They just keep saying they're delivering justice for Heaven.
They even called Marquis Zhongyi's Manor a cesspool of filth,
specially sheltering monsters.
Alright, go watch the gate.
I didn't kill anyone.
I didn't.
Chuyi.
I'm not...
I'm not a monster.
Of course you aren't.
Chuyi.
What's wrong?
I'm not a monster.
I'm not.
Chuyi.
Princess.
Princess. Princess.
Stay with me. Look at me.
Princess, snap out of it.
Princess.
What on earth is going on?
The Wolf King's blood is boiling inside the Princess.
I've heard of this.
The Yueshi royal family possesses the power of the Wolf King.
It manifests after they come of age.
Before that,
they must learn
how to control and use this power.
But isn't that after coming of age?
Chuyi is still young.
So her transformation isn't natural.
Someone must have tampered with her.
That's because someone used witchcraft
to forcibly trigger the Wolf King's power within her.
How can we break it?
This witchcraft is extremely subtle.
It hides within the Princess's body.
Whenever her emotions are intensely stimulated,
it triggers.
I can only suppress it temporarily.
I cannot break it.
If this witchcraft remains in Chuyi's body,
besides fainting like this,
will there be other effects?
As long as the witchcraft remains,
every time the Princess's sanity takes a hit,
the Wolf King's power inside her
will further devour her consciousness.
If this goes on,
sooner or later,
the Princess will become a monster
and never turn back.
This...
Then how can we root it out?
There is only one way to root it out.
The caster must die.
Bai Chuyi.
Just a few more days,
and your destiny will become my fortune.
By then, the throne,
the bloodline, everything will be mine.
Long time no see, Miss Song.
Miss Shen, what brings you here?
I heard Chuyi is unconscious.
I came to check on her.
Lingbo is knowledgeable.
Perhaps she can find something.
This is witchcraft.
You know of it?
I've heard a little about it.
Do you know who cast it?
I'm afraid only one person in the capital can cast this spell.
Princess Tuoya.
Are you so certain, Miss Shen?
I wouldn't joke about Manchuan's sister's life.
Manchuan, if you need help,
just tell me anytime.
I'm willing to do anything.
If you really want to help, Miss Shen,
why don't you tell us
how you know about this witchcraft
and how you know it's Tuoya?
Not everything in this world is a coincidence.
It's just that I've been investigating.
I care about Chuyi,
and I care about
you.
Then you should look into, Miss Shen,
the matter of the 500,000 taels of army provisions.
What do you mean by that, Miss Song?
You know what I mean, Miss Shen.
Lingbo,
regarding Chuyi,
if you can really help,
then I trust you.
I understand. I will help.
Manchuan,
I hope you don't trust the wrong person.
What do you think of her?
I think she must be connected to Tuoya.
Otherwise, she wouldn't have said that.
Will you still test her?
No need.
She is no longer the Shen Lingbo she used to be.
Shen Lingbo,
why did you bring me to such a foul place?
Don't put on airs with me.
If you want to live,
do as I say.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Father came to see you, didn't he?
What exactly do you want?
Give this letter to the Third Prince.
Tell him everything you know about Father's plot.
You want me to betray Father?
He treated you as a sacrifice long ago.
If you don't save yourself,
no one will.
How can you do this?
He is our father!
He is the Prime Minister.
He is a traitor.
He can be anyone,
but he cannot be our father.
Don't delude yourself.
Then why help me?
Because you are still useful.
Get the Emperor to give the Dasheng Token to the Third Prince,
then tell the Third Prince to go to the Marquis of Zhongyi's Manor.
I won't go.
You must.
What if the Third Prince doesn't believe me?
Then you will die.
What?
Scared?
If you are scared,
you can go ahead and burn the letter,
then go back and kill yourself.
Maybe you'll die with a bit more dignity.
I'll go.
Don't let me down.