Miss.
Xuelan.
Why are you here?
Young Master Bai.
This is news I heard recently at Baihua Tower.
Shen Zhao has close ties with so many people.
He intends to rebel.
The Emperor is unwell.
The court is in chaos.
Everyone is on edge.
Now that Marquis Bai is protecting the Third Prince,
the faster he moves,
the more likely he is to seize the initiative.
No wonder my father hasn't come back.
There is one more thing.
Shen Lingbo, the Second Miss of the Prime Minister's Manor,
is in close contact with Bulei.
You mean Shen Lingbo and Bulei?
Bulei has come to Baihua Tower many times.
He clears the place every time,
chasing everyone away,
to meet Shen Lingbo alone.
What exactly does Shen Lingbo want to do?
Perhaps she wants to use Bulei to get rid of Lord Shen.
Xuelan.
You told us all this.
Won't you be in danger?
I stopped caring about my life a long time ago.
If I can help Young Master Bai before I die,
that would be enough.
Don't be silly.
It's not that I'm not afraid of death.
I just think one should do something they won't regret.
Xuelan.
You helped me once.
I will definitely protect your life.
You can't protect me.
In this game, no one can protect anyone.
Miss Song.
I wish you two a long and happy life together.
Miss Shen.
I hate people who betray me the most.
I don't understand what you mean.
You really did harbor other thoughts about Manchuan.
I didn't.
If not, why did you go to the Marquis of Zhongyi's Manor?
Miss Shen, stop.
Those who betray me don't get a second chance.
Xuelan.
She was killed just like that.
If we don't escape,
we'll all end up like her.
Your Highness, why didn't you come with my father?
Marquis Bai went to deal with the grassland cavalry.
Your Highness.
This is what Shen Lingbo asked Shen Qiangwei to give me.
What does it say?
The letter is very clear.
How Shen Zhao used the Emperor's illness as an excuse,
forged a decree to seize power,
and used my departure from the palace to set a trap to cut off reinforcements.
It also details Shen Lingbo's fake alliance with Bulei.
She even mentioned that?
She wrote clearly about how Bulei infiltrated Dasheng,
documenting every movement.
And the location where Bulei is hiding the grassland cavalry,
is also listed clearly.
This is practically a written indictment.
I don't understand why she would betray her own father.
The letter didn't say explicitly.
She only said she regards her father as an enemy,
not out of personal grudge.
Perhaps it's because Lord Shen treats human lives as worthless.
Or perhaps she just wants to survive.
To preserve her own life and status.
But she knew long ago that Shen Zhao was colluding with Bulei.
Yet she only speaks up now.
So she doesn't stand with Dasheng,
nor does she stand with us.
She is only on her own side.
So she betrayed her father.
Was it just to save herself?
Whatever the reason,
we must prepare in advance.
Why did you reveal where Bulei hid the grassland cavalry
to the Third Prince?
To lure Marquis Bai away.
Didn't you want to deal with Bulei?
How ruthless.
You got close to Song Xuan,
wanting to make a deal with her.
I won't stop you.
Aren't you afraid she'll actually agree?
I'm warning you too.
Don't try to play both sides.
It will backfire.
I've said this before.
You don't want to be my enemy.
If you choose Song Xuan,
I guarantee your end will be ten thousand times worse than Bulei's.
Princess.
She dares speak to you like that?
I'll go kill her.
You can't kill her.
Then...
I intended for Song Xuan to deal with Shen Lingbo.
Now it seems we must change tactics.
The Emperor is critically ill.
He ordered me to preside over state affairs.
Marquis Bai Kui deceived the Third Prince.
The Emperor ordered me to bring the Third Prince back,
and take the Bai family back for trial.
Receive the edict.
The paper of the edict is old.
It is Dongcang paper.
This is no imperial decree.
It's a fake.
We will not accept it.
You dare defy the decree?
Lord Shen is flying into a rage out of shame.
Men, seize them!
Stand down.
Imperial Decree!
Shen Zhao plotted treason.
He attempted to usurp power with a fake decree.
His crimes are heinous.
I have served the Emperor for years.
What crime have I committed?
Shen Zhao, you...
You rats!
How could I lose to you?
Father, stop this.
Third Prince, my father committed treason.
I, Shen Lingbo, admit my guilt.
Rise.
The guilty official Shen Zhao is dead.
Shen Lingbo placed righteousness above family.
She deserves a reward.
You killed your father with your own hands.
For the greater good.
For the sake of the realm.
And for you.
Why did you kill your father?
I've lived by orders since I was a child.
Now I just want to act for myself for once.
You hate him.
It's not hate.
It's loathing.
Loathing that he saw me as a pawn.
Loathing that he treated me as a bargaining chip.
Loathing that he thought he could decide my life.
Manchuan.
Now nothing can stand in our way.
As long as you are by my side,
I fear nothing.
But he was your father.
You know,
he plotted to kill the entire Song Army.
He also killed my mother.
He deserved to die.
The law would have punished his crimes.
Don't you hate him at all?
He almost killed Song Xuan.
I killed him for you.
And you actually blame me?
I do hate him.
But that doesn't justify using your hands to kill him.
How can you say that about me?
I thought you were the only one who understood me.
Manchuan, I did all this for you.
I'm leaving.
Madam Hua.
Coming, Young Master Bai.
Why haven't I seen Xuelan lately?
She went back to her hometown.
Without leaving a word?
She said she didn't want to worry you,
so she told us not to say much.
I see.
What did that look you just gave me mean?
Did you want Manchuan to suspect me?
I... I didn't.
I wouldn't dare.
I didn't...
You're lying.
I... well...
While I was away,
did someone say something to Manchuan?
Spare... spare my life!
Anyway, if anyone did say anything,
I'll send you to join Xiang Xuelan in the grave.