Miss, do you remember the assassin from that day?
We have a lead.
A year ago, the Song Army fell at the Qilian Mountain border.
They were nearly wiped out.
But during my investigation,
I found a squad of a dozen men went missing.
They were not in the main formation at the time.
Is there a record in the military registry?
They were ordered to seek reinforcements.
And haven't been heard from since.
But the situation was chaotic then.
So it wasn't investigated immediately.
When you asked me to reopen the case,
I discovered this record.
If they are alive,
even if it's just one person,
I must find them.
If they are dead,
I must know where they are buried.
Hey, Daylily.
We are officially married now.
Look.
As they say, the husband is the wife's guide.
So,
have you seen any other wife
who doesn't give her husband some allowance?
Asking for a hundred taels isn't too much, is it?
You want money?
Sure.
A hundred taels?
Do you think the Marquis Manor is a bank?
A real man knows when to yield.
I'm just a bit short on cash lately.
Short on cash?
Chaohua asked me for cosmetic money again.
As her older brother,
I can't just ignore her, can I?
A brother giving his sister cosmetic money.
Reasonable.
Right?
Sister-in-law.
Chaohua.
Did you hear what your brother just said?
I heard you're short on cosmetic money lately.
Sister-in-law,
since you married into the family,
you've managed the household perfectly.
Our Marquis Manor lacks nothing.
What my brother just said was all a lie.
Bai Chaohua, you traitor!
Young Master, bad news.
Miss Shen is here.
Shen Lingbo?
What is she doing here?
You may leave.
Sister.
Miss Song, we parted in a hurry that day.
I didn't have time to thank you properly.
I have prepared a small gift today
as a token of my appreciation.
Peonies are also known as 'Parting'.
Miss Shen, this gift is truly unique.
Miss Song knows her flowers.
But you've misunderstood.
I just think peonies are peerlessly beautiful.
They suit you perfectly, Miss Song.
It's just a pity their blooming season is so short.
Miss Shen, why not speak your mind?
Marriage is like a peony.
It requires constant care.
If you want to keep this marriage, Miss Song,
don't let anyone take advantage of a weak spot.
Are you advising me to guard against others,
or are you hinting at yourself?
Sometimes, it's not good for a woman to be too confident.
Thank you for the reminder, Miss Shen.
You're welcome.
What did that woman come here for?
Spouting all that nonsense. What did she mean?
I don't know.
I really don't.
Why did you kick me?
Brother, you're done for.
I think you've offended my sister-in-law.
Go away.
Don't talk nonsense.
Why are you still standing there?
Go apologize to your wife.
Why should I apologize?
I didn't do anything wrong.
You think you did nothing wrong?
Shen Lingbo even sent flowers to the door,
saying those sarcastic things.
How is my sister-in-law supposed to deal with that?
I didn't ask her to send flowers.
Anyway, you and this Shen Lingbo,
your relationship is ambiguous.
I told you, I have nothing to do with her.
Can I stop her from doing what she wants?
Then why didn't you make your stance clear right then?
And now you're acting aggrieved?
Weren't you the one begging me back then
to help you marry Song Xuan?
Your Highness, Your Highness.
Your Highness.
I heard
Prince Duan wants to match you with General Song's daughter.
She's just the daughter of a brute.
If it weren't for my father,
why would I have anything to do with her?
Watch your words, Your Highness.
To hell with watching my words.
I'd like to see how long the Song family
can last on the battlefield.
What are you doing, Bai Manchuan?
I was just drinking my wine
when I heard a dog barking,
so I came in to check.
I didn't expect it to be you, Prince Duan's heir.
Who are you calling a dog?
You're the dog.
Your whole family are dogs.
He said I was a wolf last night.
I wasn't talking about you, naturally.
General Song's family is loyal and devoted,
yet here you are spouting nonsense,
judging his daughter.
Your behavior isn't even worthy of a dog.
Song Xuan is about to marry me.
Whatever I say
is my family's business.
It's not your place to judge.
The Emperor hasn't granted the marriage yet,
and you're already acting like Miss Song's husband.
You really are full of yourself.
Because I want to.
Bai Manchuan,
you dare to go against me?
Then let's settle this.
Bai Manchuan!
Let go of me!
Yuan Huai!
Do you really think I'm afraid of you?
Let me go!
Gentlemen,
calm down, calm down.
Stop fighting.
Baihua Pavilion is a place for fun,
not for fighting.
Young Master Bai, Young Master Bai,
stop fighting.
Someone's going to get hurt.
Bai Manchuan!
You dare hit my handsome face?
This isn't over!
Stop!
Come here.
I heard
you got into a fight with Prince Duan's heir at Baihua Pavilion yesterday.
So what if I did?
Someone accused you in court of violent assault.
What did His Majesty say?
He's not going to throw me in prison, is he?
Scared now?
What am I scared of?
I was speaking up for justice.
If I had to do it again,
I'd still beat that shameless man.
She'd be better off marrying me than him.
You like her?
So I really did say that.
You...
Husband, why are you still standing here?
Go back to your studies.
I have something to explain.
Explain what?
Why are you dodging?
Guilty conscience?
My relationship with Shen Lingbo isn't what you think.
I have nothing to do with Shen Lingbo.
Then why are you panicking?
Over ten years ago,
when Lord Shen Zhao went to Jiangnan to take office,
he took a fancy to Shen Lingbo's birth mother.
She got pregnant.
But she didn't dare say anything.
Later, he was promoted and returned to the Capital.
She was afraid of ruining his career,
so she gave birth to Shen Lingbo alone.
Get to the point.
Later, when Madam Shen found out,
she sent assassins to slaughter her entire family.
Her mother told Shen Lingbo the truth right before she died.
Later, Shen Lingbo traveled a thousand miles alone to find her father.
She was almost sold into Baihua Pavilion.
Then you must have...
played the hero saving the damsel.
I just stepped in when I saw injustice.
On Shen Zhao's birthday, I arranged a blood test for them.
But that day at Baihua Pavilion,
I clearly saw you two coming out of the same room.
I didn't do anything.
I probably didn't...
Then towards her,
didn't you feel anything at all?
I'm a very virtuous man, okay?
Since you're a good person,
you deserve to be punished even more.
Huanghuacai.
You...
W-W-What are you doing?
Husband, just study hard.