I want to see Tuoya.
Since you were able to find this place, Miss Shen,
you must be quite capable.
But do you know the rules here?
Rules?
What rules?
If you want to see someone,
you have to beat me in a gamble first.
How?
Among these five cups,
one is lethal.
Miss Shen,
you and I will take turns choosing a cup to drink.
If at any point you get scared
and dare not drink,
you lose.
You are the guest.
Do you want to go first or second?
First.
Miss Shen, it seems you've lost.
Wait a moment.
Your thoughts are too obvious, Boss Ji.
It seems you're not sure
which one is the actual lethal cup.
Aren't you afraid of death?
I just believe you value your life more.
You wouldn't actually use poison.
Interesting. Very interesting.
Why go to such lengths just to see me?
I hate the feeling of my fate being in someone else's hands.
But how many people in this world
truly hold their fate in their own hands?
Your Yueshi Kingdom retreats in order to advance.
The marriage alliance is a sham.
Spying and seizing power is the truth.
Correct. Since you know everything,
why come to me?
Shouldn't you report this to your Emperor first?
Whatever happens to Dasheng
is none of my business.
You want status and power,
while I only want a person.
I wonder who you want, Miss Shen.
That's none of your concern.
If I cooperate with you,
what's in it for me?
There is only one Wolf King on the prairie.
Surely you don't just want to be a kept dog.
I told you, touch me and you die.
Miss Shen, spare me!
Spare my life!
Miss Shen, have mercy!
I failed to recognize your greatness.
Beat us or punish us,
just spare our miserable lives!
Miss Shen! Spare us!
Have mercy, Miss Shen!
Miss Shen, Madam Hua ordered us to do this!
She saw your beauty on the street
and ordered us to kidnap you.
No, Miss Shen!
I just run a shop!
I don't know anything!
I really didn't do anything!
You're good at shifting the blame.
Did you ever imagine this day when you kidnapped me?
Miss Shen, spare us!
So you do know fear.
Too bad I don't like giving second chances.
Miss Shen.
Shut them up.
You are still useful.
Come with me.
Yes, yes, yes.
Miss Shen!
Miss Shen, spare me!
Miss Shen.
Work for me from now on.
As for today...
Don't speak of what shouldn't be spoken.
Yes.
It seems I was right.
The Lingbo Flower is poisonous.
In a few days, our dynasty will hold the annual Literary Gathering.
At that time, the children of the nobility
will all attend.
I'm not going.
Then I won't go either.
Why not?
Literary Gathering, Literary Gathering.
It's just a bunch of officials' sons showing off their literary skills.
It's utterly dull.
Exactly. Nothing but pretentious pleasantries.
Very boring.
Father, I won't go either.
But this year's gathering
will be hosted personally by the Third Prince.
Who?
The Third Prince.
Not only will the Prince host it,
but he will also set the topics himself,
and provide commentary throughout.
If someone makes a good impression on him...
Father, since the Third Prince is coming,
then I must certainly go.
Brother, please have pity on me.
No.
My good brother,
just pity me, please.
You can't let me make a fool of myself all alone.
Why do you want me to accompany you for embarrassing things?
Husband, you should go.
Why?
Because you need to astonish everyone at the gathering
and shine brilliantly.
Who do you mean?
Me?
Huanghuacai.
Why don't we do something interesting today?
Huanghuacai, you, you, you...
You really have a heavy hand.
What did you want to do, Husband?
Can't I just read books?
These principles are hollow and dull.
What is the use of reading them?
It's a waste of time.
Have you read the Spring and Autumn Annals?
I was forced to read a few chapters when I was young, that's all.
Then let me ask you.
Zheng Bo made a mistake.
Why didn't Jing Hou kill him?
If he killed Zheng Bo,
it would instead make the feudal lords fearful,
and damage his own prestige.
How many times have you read this book?
I just read it for a few days when I was young.
Bai Manchuan, what kind of person are you, really?
The world thinks Young Master Bai is a useless fop.
They believe it to be true,
and I am happy to be at ease.
Why?
Huanghuacai,
do you know how many eyes are watching the Bai Residence?
If I reveal my talents,
it would be inviting destruction.
In the end, I fear I couldn't even protect the Marquis Manor.
If you keep enduring silently like this,
the Bai family will eventually be in a precarious state.
Now that you have me to protect you,
you might as well try
how a truly smart person should act.
You really dare to trust me.
Bai Manchuan, I trust you.
I hope you will help me.
Prince, Princess, you have come from afar.
Great Sheng treats you with courtesy.
May I ask if you can state the purpose of your visit directly?
The purpose?
Naturally, we came for peace at the border.
But if your country refuses to make any concessions,
how can we talk about sincerity?
What is this sincerity
you speak of, Prince?
You cede the three border cities
as a betrothal gift for my sister, Tuoya, to become Empress.
Naturally, all will be well.
Those three cities are where the people of Great Sheng live and survive.
How can we cede them?
Besides,
the position of Empress is not something that can be given just like that.
Then there is nothing to discuss.
First Prince,
we came here to solve problems,
not to be threatened.
We are sincerely here for peace talks.
You speak of ending the war,
but have your cavalry at the border retreated?
Massacring villages, burning cities,
kidnapping people, and looting grain.
Is this the sincerity you speak of?
The situation is different today.
If you insist on resisting,
you are seeking your own suffering.
Those words are too arrogant.
If you don't agree,
you can come and try us.
Enough!
If you came to Great Sheng
just to show off your power,
then you might as well never go back.
Third Prince,
the Emperor of Great Sheng isn't dead yet.
Can you make such a decision?
I am the Crown Prince, appointed by my Royal Father to oversee the state.
Naturally, I have the authority to decide.
Your Highness.
Prince.
The peace talks need to be discussed at length.
Please, Prince and Princess, stay in Great Sheng for a while longer.
Unbelievable.
Chancellor, do you think there's any need to continue talking?
Your Highness, resorting to arms is not a long-term solution.
In my view, the Yueshi Kingdom is also sincere about peace talks.
His Majesty and Your Highness are both benevolent rulers.
Surely, you will prioritize the safety of the people.