What did you just say, you punk?
I'm sorry.
Hyung, stop.
Just stop and go inside.
Go inside?
Go inside your room?
Hurry.
Hey, what do I do?
He's asking me to go in with him.
Don't go.
Please, don't go, Daon.
Please.
From now on,
don't ever look at that bastard with
those eyes in front of me again.
What if I said no?
I'll kill him.
I'll kill that bastard,
Ju Seonghyeon, first.
If you understand,
behave yourself from now on.
"Secret Relationships"
(Episode 6)
Are you okay?
Did you get hurt anywhere?
It's none of your business.
I was so worried, I couldn't
do anything all night.
Worried?
Why do you have to worry about me?
Why? It's because…
After seeing what happened yesterday,
you're saying this?
This is the real me.
I'm all sweet with you,
if someone else shows up,
I can throw you away in an instant.
Every time something like this happens,
I'll let go of your hand...
I don't care.
I can wait.
How long do you think you can wait?
A month?
A year?
No.
You won't last even a few days.
Just like everyone else,
you'll give up soon enough.
You will be disappointed in me.
Don't be afraid of
losing your dignity now.
Just leave when I tell you to.
I'll never give up.
So don't even think about
pushing me away.
The door is opening.
(Albi Construction)
Looks like you didn't
get a wink of sleep.
Your face is a mess.
We're not so close that we ask each
other about each other's well-being.
Sorry.
It's just that yesterday,
you didn't know your place
and crossed the line.
So I thought maybe we
got close enough to ask.
The one who crossed the line
wasn't me, it was you, Director.
Want me to show you what crossing
the line really looks like?
Are you planning to show that habit of
grabbing collars in the office, too?
Seeing you react like this,
you must be really anxious.
Anxious?
Isn't that something only people who
have never possessed something feel?
Anyway, the person who has been with
him longer is me, not you.
Exactly.
It just looks like you're Anxious.
Bastard.
Since the site is close to the sea,
we should select wood
it's durable and not easily corroded.
- What do you think?
- Leave work with me later.
I made a list of suppliers handling
teak and cedar,
and many are available
for meetings next week...
I said, let's leave together.
We're in a meeting.
Let's talk later.
Well, everything sounds good.
Let's schedule another meeting
after the supplier meetings.
That's all for today then.
Get in.
Go.
Stop it already.
You saw it.
There's nothing between me
and Assistant Manager Ju.
You make that face and
expect me to believe that?
What exactly is the problem?
I don't even hang out with
Jaemin hyung anymore.
Why are you still acting like this?
Why bring up Shin Jaemin
all of a sudden?
You've been messing with me
all this time
because of Jaemin hyung, right?
It's not because of Shin Jaemin.
Then what is it?
Because I want to be by your side.
Like before.
Don't lie to me.
You just want to torment with me.
- That's not it.
- Be by my side?
Who do you think you are?
When I needed you, you were never there.
So why are you coming to me now?
I don't need you anymore.
Ever since you left seven years ago,
I erased you from my life.
So if you think you can just come back,
stop dreaming.
I'll never take you back.
Assistant Manager!
A last-minute meeting came up,
so I can't make it today.
I asked someone else to cover for me.
I'm really sorry.
Shall we go in?
Oh, that is okay too.
The wood is good, right?
The quality is great,
but the company wants a darker color.
Excuse me for a moment.
Sure.
Let's have dinner later.
Or watch a movie?
A new horror film just came out.
What are you doing?
Ah, if you don't like that, we could
check out an exhibit this weekend...
Assistant Manager Ju.
You said you'd let me stay by your side.
If it's too hard, just give up now.
If found it.
Follow me.
Happy birthday.
I wanted to have dinner with you,
but I don't have time.
It's okay.
I'm already partying with my friends.
Table 8, please.
Enjoy your meal.
Damn it.
It splattered everywhere.
Oh no. I'm sorry.
Sorry?
Then you shouldn't have done something
to be sorry for in the first place.
No, that's not...
What?
Huh?
What do you mean? Speak up.
- See you tomorrow.
- Yes.
Thank you very much.
- Tomorrow...
- Tomorrow, I'll come alone.
This isn't your job,
Assistant Manager Ju.
Hello.
Yes.
She's my sister.
Dasul?
Give it to me. I'll drive.
No. I have to hurry.
If you drive now,
you'll get into an accident.
(Emergency Room Open 24 hours)
The guardian?
We've contacted the patient's
older brother, and he'll be here soon.
You're here?
How did you know to come here?
Dasul is okay.
She just got a minor injury
while working part-time.
Part-time?
Brother.
How did you get here so fast?
- I'm fine...
- Are you asking for a scolding?
Huh?
I told you not to get a part-time job.
Why don't you ever listen?
How many times do I have to say it?
This isn't the time for a job,
you should be studying...
Studying isn't the most
important thing right now.
- I need to be independent first...
- You can move out later...
Then why did you leave home so quickly?
Dad was addicted to gambling
and never came home.
Mom was always lying down,
saying she was sick.
The twins were always looking to you.
You don't want to live
with those annoyances.
You dislike those things.
As soon as you got a job,
you left us behind and moved out.
- Didn't you?
- Jung Dasul!
If you're going to keep
acting like this,
then just live however you want.
Daon.
Calm down and listen to me first.
Dasul had her reasons too.
Pushing her too hard won't do any good.
Dasul's matter...
I'll talk to her properly.
No.
You don't have to worry about it.
What?
I said you don't have to worry about it.
This is my problem,
so I'll handle it myself.
I'll be going first.
Be by my side?
When I needed you, you were never there.
So why are you coming to me now?
So if you think you can just come back,
stop dreaming.
I'll never take you back.
What the hell did you say
to Hwasun Group's daughter?
Why have all the
matchmaking prospects disappeared?
Did I ask too much from you?
Just go on the blind dates,
meet someone decent, get married,
and take over Dad's company!
Why do you always go astray?
I don't need the company
or anything else.
I didn't go back to Korea
because I wanted a company.
What?
You're not taking over the company?
- What are you saying...
- You told me to study abroad
if I wanted to protect that person.
You said everything would be fine
once I came back.
So I did what you asked!
But why? Why? Why?
Why did it end up like this?
How long are you going to
keep bringing up the past?
It's already over!
No.
It's not over yet.
We can start over.
We can go back.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know you were
so worried about me.
Lying and working part-time,
saying those things earlier...
It was all my fault.
It's cold.
Come inside quickly.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have gotten that angry.
When I heard you were hurt earlier,
- I was so shocked, my mind went blank.
- You don't have to say it. I got it.
If you're not eating,
I'll finish it all.
How did you hurt your arm?
Oh,
I slipped while serving.
Brother, you see...
About Jaemin...
I think he's a bit strange.
I never told anyone that
I was working there.
Him suddenly showing up like that
was strange.
And the fact that
he appeared right after I got hurt.
It doesn't feel like a coincidence.
The amount you mentioned is different.
You should have done as instructed.
I only told you to scare her.
The one who caused the injury
and made things complicated
was you, wasn't it?
What do you mean by that?
It's like...
He had anticipated everything.
That can't be.
You know that too.
You know how much he looks after us.
It's just a coincidence.
Sorry.
Maybe I'm just being too sensitive.
Oh, right.
The person who came with you earlier...
Never mind, it's nothing.
I'm Daon's younger sister.
Can I see you for a moment?
Over here.
The guardian for patient Jung Dasul?
My guardian isn't coming.
- Why?
- Oh.
I have to explain about wound cleaning.
When will the guardian be here?
I'm here.
You are...
I'm Daon's coworker.
Is the wound serious?
Not too bad, but she needs to
clean it properly to avoid scarring.
Scarring?
Is the wound deep enough
to leave a scar?
There's no damage to the bone, right?
Yes, there's no issue.
The medication should be taken
three times a day after meals.
This is a scar ointment,
apply it regularly.
This is a heat pack.
Here's some water and snacks.
I also got slippers, just in case.
I found your number in
the guardian contact section
and called you.
Sorry for asking to meet so suddenly.
It's fine.
How much did all of that cost?
- I'll pay you back.
- I didn't buy them expecting repayment.
It doesn't sit right with me.
You remind me of your brother.
I wanted to help, so I did.
You don't have to pay me back.
But if it really bothers you...
Then do this instead.
Do you like my brother?
Ah, well...
My brother has a ridiculously
strong sense of pride.
And he's extremely stubborn.
Sometimes, I wonder if he's my brother.
Because he likes to say things
without thinking.
But...
He doesn't mean any of it.
So, even if he acts like an idiot...
Don't give up on him.
If you stay by his side,
he'll open his heart eventually.
I told you not to come.
I have something to talk to you about
regarding your sister.
There was no guardian yesterday,
so I got the explanation instead.
- You should know as well...
- I'll take care of it.
Don't worry about it.
How can I not worry?
Why?
Do you feel too sorry for me
to ignore it?
It's not like that.
- I've never thought of you as pitiful.
- I'm embarrassed!
What's so embarrassing about it?
I've shown you even more
embarrassing sides of myself.
Begging, pleading, clinging to you...
I've shown you all my lowest points.
So just stop it.
You don't have to try so hard
to be by my side.
But I can't stop, what should I do?
I hate that I'm like this.
I feel so pathetic and humiliated
that I just want to die.
But
I just can't let go,
no matter what I do!
Every day is hell.
I pretend to be fine in front of you,
but my heart shatters hundreds of times.
I said I'd wait,
but what if you never come?
I was so scared that
I couldn't do anything.
So...
Can't you just like me back?
If you tell me not to come, I won't.
If you say you don't want to see me,
I'll hide.
But please, don't abandon me.
Promise me you won't leave me behind.
No matter how long it takes, I'll wait.
Okay?
What did you want to say?
Why are you giving me this?
You said you'd accept
if I gave you a ring.
When did I ever say that?
Then, if I buy one, will you take it?
Alright. I'll take it.
This is how I feel.
Back then, and even now.
It's always been you.
Let's start over.
I promise I'll never leave again.
So please, don't abandon me.
Promise me you won't leave me behind.
I can't go back.
Too much time has passed.
It's too late to return.
Now I understand.
No matter how much regret comes
after losing something,
it's useless.
I'm not going to run away anymore.
I am...
going to follow my heart.
Where are you right now,
Assistant Manager Ju?
I have something to say.
No.
You can't.
You can't do whatever you want.
Let go.
You think everything will be fine
if I just step aside?
Take care of Shin Jaemin first.
The real problem isn't me.
It's that bastard, Shin Jaemin.
The thing that Park Junghoon
did to you...
The reason I had to go
to that overseas program...
Everything that happened to you...
It was all orchestrated by
Shin Jaemin behind the scenes.
That can't be true.
Jaemin hyung would never...
About Jaemin...
I think he's a bit strange.
I never told anyone that
I was working there.
Him suddenly showing up like that
was strange.
And the fact that
he appeared right after I got hurt.
It doesn't feel like a coincidence.
Are you free to meet, hyung?
Do you want to come over to my place?
Come in.
You haven't eaten yet, right?
Let's eat together.
I made pasta too.
Come on, sit down.
Was it you, hyung?
Did you do that to Dasul?
Was it really you?
What are you talking about, Daon?
The thing with Park Junghoon,
sending Suhyeon hyung abroad,
was that all your doing?
Yeah.
I did it.
Why?
Is that not allowed?
- Why?
- Because I love you.
I did it all for you.
You did it because
you love me?
That doesn't make it right!
Let's talk again later.
Hyung!
Tell me.
Which part of my face
is the most handsome?
No, I wasn't looking at your face.
I was looking at the ring on your hand.
The ring?
If you like it, you can have it.
Umm, no.
But...
how much does a ring like that cost?
This? Not much.
About ten million won?
Ten million won?
Don't worry, I won't ask you
to buy me one.
Why would I buy a ring for you, hyung?
Then...
if I buy it for you, will you take it?
Should I just go home?
What? You've been here less
than ten minutes.
Someone's coming.
Alright. I'll take it.