Hyung!
This is all your fault.
Because you like to open
your heart to people easily.
You give your heart away
to anyone who's kind to you.
So I had to resort to this.
Hyung.
First, put the knife down…
I don't have to worry about it?
You'll handle it yourself?
Do you know how much I worry about you?
How much I've sacrificed for you?
Now you don't need me anymore?
How can you throw me away like this?!
If you make me miserable again...
Daon…
Where are you?
Did something happen?
I'm worried. Let me know
when you see my text.
I'll be waiting.
"Secret Relationships"
(Episode 7)
Are you feeling a bit better?
We've only given you first aid,
so you need a full check-up.
Once you finish the IV,
we'll take you for a CT scan.
Excuse me.
The person who came with me…
Oh, he had something to do,
so he left first.
He left?
Oh, and he asked me to give you this.
All this time, you've sacrificed for me.
You've looked out for me…
And I'm grateful for that.
But
the thing with Park Junghoon,
and sending Suhyeon hyung abroad…
made me confused.
If you really did all that for me,
then please, don't do it anymore.
I have something urgent today,
so I'll be going now.
I've never followed my heart before,
but losing something and regretting it…
I don't want to do that anymore.
Assistant Manager Jung.
Why haven't you been answering?
Do you know how worried I was?
I'm sorry.
I was a bit busy.
What happened here?
Ah… That…
So the thing you wanted to tell me…
Was this?
- No, it's not that...
- I was the only one hoping
like a fool again.
So it was real?
I called you, and they said
you were at the hospital.
That you were alone without a guardian.
Weren't you supposed to meet Jung Daon?
At first, I wasn't sure,
but now that I'm here, I get it.
To him, we're nothing now.
You can't make him waver
as easily as before.
If you came all the way here
just to say that, then get lost.
That's why we should team up.
Look, you and I,
we can't do anything alone.
Wouldn't it be better
if we worked together?
Think about it carefully.
Right now, it's not about
whether you or I have it.
It's about making sure that bastard
Ju Seonghyeon doesn't get it.
So, we each find our own way
and keep in touch?
I don't care.
I have no intention of
teaming up with you.
Even after going through all that?
I've done enough.
So, what? You're giving up
on Jung Daon?
You?
Well, if after all this,
Daon still said no,
there's nothing I can do.
What are you scheming?
Think whatever you want.
I'm done now.
(Albi Construction)
Good morning.
- Hello.
Hello.
Alright. Since Assistant Manager Ju
is taking the day off due to illness,
if you need anything,
ask Assistant Manager Jung
or Assistant Manager Park.
And Assistant Manager Jung, report to me
right after your client meeting today.
The meeting just ended.
I'll report back as soon as I return.
I'll be waiting.
Assistant Manager Ju.
I was worried, so I came.
Where does it hurt? How bad is it?
Did you take any medicine?
Assistant Manager Ju.
About yesterday,
it was all a misunderstanding...
A misunderstanding?
Let me explain everything.
No need.
You don't need to explain.
I understand your feelings well now.
I had hope.
I rushed to you with hope.
I've been waiting for you for hours,
wondering where you were
and what you were doing.
Did something bad happen?
I was worrying myself sick.
I should've stopped when you told me to.
Honestly, I regret it.
I won't hold you back anymore.
I'll stop here.
I'll do as you want.
Please leave now.
I'd prefer it if you didn't come again.
Assistant Manager Jung! Water!
Isn't that person?
The recruit with connection?
Assistant Manager Jung.
Did you see the post?
The post?
Yeah.
(Al Construction Hiring Corruption
and Power Abuse Exposed)
The head of the
strategic planning
department at Al Construction
and Assistant Manager J
were from the same university.
The department head nearly went
to jail for assaulting someone over J,
but used family connections
to study abroad instead.
A few years later,
J got hired at Al Construction.
Didn't they obviously use connection?
I was the victim of that incident.
Recently, the Al Construction
department head
canceled a contract with
our company at the last minute.
He said it was because of me.
Getting assigned to a good department
because of family or school connections
is disgusting.
That J-guy must have
an insanely thick skin.
Must be pretty useless at work too.
These days, connections are
part of the qualifications.
Well, if after all this,
Daon still said no,
there's nothing I can do.
Think whatever you want.
I'm done now.
Is it because of Park Junghoon?
The collapsed contract
with Pilgang Construction...
That bastard Park Junghoon said that?
Damn it, I told him never to
show up in front of me again.
Why did you do that?
That's all in the past, isn't it?
If it's in the past...
Does it mean it will disappear?
And why can't it disappear?
If this is all because you're bitter
about going abroad for school,
then I'm sorry.
It was my call that got you in trouble.
Do you really think I'm doing this
because of going abroad?
Then what is it about?
Back then and even now...
You and Jaemin hyung
keep things from me,
never telling me the truth.
How am I supposed to know anything?
If you had told me the truth back then.
If I had?
What could you have done?
All you ever do is show up
and whine like this.
No.
- I would've tried to do...
- No.
You couldn't have.
What matters now is
not whether the truth
was told back then,
but now that you know
are you coming to me or not?
That's what's important.
This is all your fault.
Because you like to open
your heart to people easily.
So I had to resort to this.
I should've stopped when you told me to.
Honestly, I regret it.
I'd prefer it if you didn't come again.
No.
What could you have done?
You couldn't have.
It's all my fault.
I don't deserve to love
or to be loved.
Everyone around me just ends up
miserable and suffering.
Are you okay?
Daon...
What did you say?
Grandma?
Oh dear...
You're burning up, like fire.
I'll go make you some porridge.
Eat.
What's troubling you so much
that you've made yourself sick?
When your heart hurts,
don't keep it all inside.
If you do, it'll fester.
I did everything I could...
If something isn't working,
then maybe it just isn't meant to be.
I don't think I'm the one.
So I told them I'll stop.
I did the right thing, didn't I?
I did the well, right?
Oh dear, you did well.
My dear child,
you've been through so much.
Wow, Grandma, just one hug from you
and I already feel better.
I should hurry up and eat this porridge
and take my medicine.
That's right.
Eat up.
I'll go...
brew some tea.
It's a shame you're quitting
so suddenly.
I figured I'd take a break
while I'm at it.
Have you decided where you'll travel?
I think I'll be going far away.
I don't think I'll be back
for a long time.
I'm just going to wrap
everything up and leave.
Stay in touch.
I'll keep a spot open for you.
Thank you.
Did my puppy get to work safely?
Have you recovered?
Thanks to Grandma, I feel all better
and I'm heading to work.
You don't have to worry.
(Assistant Manager Jung)
Assistant Manager Ju.
Here's the data you requested.
Ah, yes.
Ms. Mina.
Is Assistant Manager Jung working
outside the office today?
I think he's not coming in
because of what happened yesterday.
What happened?
Yesterday, there was a huge fuss
because of an exposé about
Assistant Manager Jung and the Director.
It said they knew
each other from university.
But the post had
a lot of problematic claims…
So [people are saying he got into
the company through connections,
and that's how he joined the TF team.
There are tons of rumors going around.
Are you okay?
Assistant Manager Ju?
For the resort project bid presentation,
I think you should
prepare well for it.
Wasn't Assistant Manager Jung
supposed to present?
Well, it looks like
he's going to leave the TF team.
Because of yesterday's incident,
the higher-ups don't see him favorably.
So he wants to step down himself.
We don't have much time
before the presentation,
just endure it for a bit.
Watch where you're going.
For a Director, you don't seem
very interested in
protecting your employees.
Protecting employees?
Do you realize how difficult
this is for him?
Because of the post on
the community board.
Our company is quite free-spirited, huh?
An ordinary employee daring
to criticize their superior.
Whether I protect or defend
that employee, that's for me
as the director to decide.
A mere employee should stay out of it.
Make yourself clear
so I can stop caring.
If Assistant Manager Jung
gets removed from the TF team,
I won't just stand by and watch.
Jung Daon is leaving the TF team?
That's great.
I wasn't happy with it.
Great, you say?
Assistant Manager Jung
hasn't even come to work,
and you say that's great?
He didn't come to work?
Please take me to Yongsan,
Shinhui Apartments.
Whenever I feel uneasy,
there is this hill
I used to go up often.
That place
feels like a refuge.
Ah, driver, please take me to Mujundong
instead of Yongsan.
Jung Daon!
Hey!
The number you have dialed
is unavailable.
Please leave a message after the beep.
Assistant Manager Ju, why are you here?
You said you come here whenever
you feel uneasy.
Are you going to run away again?
- You think hiding will solve anything?
- Let go of me.
You worked so hard to prepare for it,
how can you just give up so easily?
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize to me.
You should be apologizing to yourself.
You said you finally had a dream.
You promised to work hard together.
How can you give up so easily?
Assistant Manager Ju,
you heard the rumors too, right?
How am I supposed to just keep working
and take charge of the
TF like nothing happened?
I...
have no right.
I can't do it.
Who decides who has the right?
Why do you assume you
can't do it before even trying?
Then what exactly am I supposed
to do in this situation?
You can do anything.
So please...
Stop running away.
Are you trying to drive me insane?
Where the hell were you
that you didn't answer my calls?
If you disappear without
a word one more time,
I won't just let it slide...
I heard you're leaving the TF team.
Then come work under me?
I'm not leaving the TF team.
I'm going to make sure we win the bid
and achieve my dream.
So I won't let down the people
who believe in me.
- And I will definitely go over...
- Why do you keep trying to go overseas?
Why do you keep trying
to escape from me?
Because I feel like that's the only way
I can truly find myself!
What?
I want to try living on my own.
Without you...
without Jaemin hyung.
Yes, Director.
Get ready.
We need to proceed as planned.
(Albi Construction)
(Jaemin hyung)
Hello?
I'm sorry about what happened.
I think I lost my mind for a moment.
As soon as I woke up in the hospital,
I wanted to apologize.
But you weren't there.
I had something urgent to handle.
Daon.
I think I'll be leaving soon.
Leaving?
Yeah.
It seems like the best choice.
Take care.
Be well.
- Umm...
- Assistant Manager!
Are you okay?
I was worried.
A client called.
This material looks good,
look at the blueprint again.
When reviewing the blueprint...
Assistant Manager Ju.
Can you check this for a moment?
Ah...
I think the details at
the end aren't enough.
What do you think?
The parking lot is too small
compared to car usage rates.
And for the elderly and disabled...
(Presenting the bidding for the
construction project of Dubai Resort 2024)
You can begin the presentation now.
You just need to turn on
the mic when you're ready.
- You're from Albi Construction, right?
- Yes.
Has Director Kim Kim Suhyeon
not arrived yet?
Ah... Just a moment.
Yes.
The number you have dialed
is unavailable.
Please leave a message after the beep.
He's probably to be on his way.
I'll inform you as soon as he arrives.
Ah, I see. Thank you.
Let's go.
Where are you?
It's ready.
Ah, and I think the phrasing about
property value is too direct.
I'm planning to adjust it a bit...
Before I leave the country,
I have something to give you.
Do you have a moment?
I happen to be near where you are.
I'll meet you at
the underground parking lot.
Okay.
Umm...
I need to step out to the
underground parking lot for a moment.
Ah, okay. Go ahead.
I'll start preparing for
the rehearsal in the meantime.
By any chance...
After the presentation,
could you spare me a moment?
I have something to say.
Then I'll be going now.
Okay.
The traffic is a bit heavy.
I'll be there soon.
Albi Construction,
let's start the rehearsal.
Okay.
Daon.
Come write your wish, too.
You said you wanted to
hang it on the tree.
I just said that in passing.
I didn't think you'd remember.
Wanting to write your wishes
just like a kid.
I saw in dramas,
people always write wishes and
hang them on the Christmas tree, right?
Then the next morning,
there are piles of presents.
It's something that would
never happen in my home.
I've always wanted to try it.
- This.
- This?
Got it.
Wait, let me hang it up first then look.
- Alright, alright.
- No, that one.
Huh?
It's snowing.
(Please make us happy)
(May we all be happy)
(May we be together until the
moment we leave this world)