Married Woman Abducted, Demand for 5 Billion Won in Ransom
Till death do we part... forever.
My Dangerous Wife
- Here.
- Wooo.
Here you go, Customer.
- Please have a taste.
- Oh, but eating at night makes me gain weight.
Just a little bit.
It tastes great.
But isn't it too much for just us two?
Why is this open? Do I need to get a new car?
Stop it!
You... you... Why are you doing this?
To set you free, Seonbae.
At least you should find freedom. It's all over for me, anyway.
But I won't go alone.
I will kill this piece of trash first.
I told you! Don't do anything on your own!
Seonbae?
I told you from the beginning,
I don't care if I get caught.
You just have to tell them that all you did was help me because I asked you to.
No, I did it because I wanted to.
I did it all on my own.
I don't want to cause you any more harm.
Yu Min, even if I get caught, at worst, it's obstruction of justice and fraud.
And I'll get probation, at worst.
Why are you obsessed with a piece of trash like that?
Why?!
You...
Honey!
Are you alright, Honey?
I forgot to retrieve the spare key from him.
I'm sorry. Are you all right?
So you planned this with him, too?
You two have both gone crazy.
That is really not true. That won't happen.
I will protect you and this house, don't worry.
- I will leave this house right now.
- No, you can't.
Please stop!
Do you think I can endure this any longer?
You have to. We are married.
Married? Are you joking? This is marriage?
You are a monster.  I cannot live with a monster.
You're the one who created this monster.
Are you blaming me now?
Everyone expects the woman to stay behind the man even if the woman is more talented, don't they?
So I stayed behind you and played being the perfect wife perfectly.
I've done all sorts of things, and even stopped you from committing murder.
Are you getting an idea now of how much effort I've made all this time?
Gosh, I'm so grateful.
Because you are a very high maintenance man.
You are insane. You are not normal.
No, I'm the most normal I've ever been.
I am more myself now than I've ever been.
And I'm more focused on you and me than I've ever been.
Do you know how long it's been since we've stood face to face like this?
Stop saying such futile things.
We are finished now.
- What will you do about the wine?
- Do whatever you want to!
I wasn't really trying to kill you.
So the person who committed the bigger crime can decide what to do. We'll each get punished for our respective crimes.
Then what about the five billion won?
You need that money. I have the five billion won.
- You can have the five billion won.
- Stop joking around.
That money was the price of my life.
You really did try to kill me.
You can't tell me you didn't try, can you?
And how could it be that wine?
At the very least, it shouldn't have been that wine.
I did want to kill you. I was suffocating, so I wished you were dead.
So I died, just as you wanted.
Why didn't you just let me die? Why did you save me?
Because I didn't really want to kill you.
I want to believe what you just said.
How would it have been, if I trusted you?
If I drank that wine?
But you never did trust me.
No, I couldn't trust you.
You didn't kill me with poison.
That smile.
The moment I saw that smile,
the me who wanted to trust you died.
Prepare 5 billion won. If you report to the police, your wife will die. -N31-
Whenever I see your face now,
I remember that smile. Do you know how horrible that is?
We are finished.
No, we will begin again where we ended.
Do you really not understand? This is the end!
This is the end of the line.
Do you know where the true end is? When we both give up?
But I haven't yet. We will go further.
Why on earth?
Because I want to.
Episode 6
The Wife Who Flies Above the Running Husband
Congratulations for being released from the hospital, Auntie.
Thank you, Chae Rim.
Stop! Stop this!
What are you doing?
Did that shock you, Honey?
Aren't you happy you came home early like I told you to?
I brought roasted chicken.
Without the wings.
Oh, Mother, thank you.
- I'm late in congratulating you.
- Thank you.
Chae Rim said she wanted to invite her Dad.
Don't use me to make your excuses.
I was worried she didn't have another man to invite here.
So I ran here quickly.
Please sit, please sit. Hold on for a moment.
Omo, hello. What brings you here?
Ah, yes, I am bringing you some paella to congratulate you on leaving the hospital.
We really enjoyed eating that.
Can you teach me the recipe?
Uh, the recipe?
Please teach me, too.
Aigoo, Chae Rim, are you bringing Dad some?
Your tastes haven't changed, huh?
Oh my baby.
Chae Rim, come here.
Then I should...
Oh, please leave it, let me clean that up.
No, it's fine. I should get going.
It would have been nice if Unni Eun Hye could join us.
Well, my wife hurt her back a little bit, so she is resting.
Omo, that's terrible.
Then, I'll be leaving now.
Yes, please get home safely.
Take care.
Gosh, who is the woman living with that gorgeous man?
The CEO of an internet shopping mall in her late forties.
- She's got skills, huh?
- Oh, I'm envious.
If I lived with a husband like that, I would want for nothing.
"You just take care of your looks, Honey."
What a great role model you are for our daughter.
Oh, who are you? I don't know you.
I'm following Song Yu Min?
Be careful, and don't overdo it.
- Yun Cheol, you come here, too.
Brother-in-law? Is there some problem?
Aigoo, why call him 'brother-in-law?'
Brother-in-law? Why are you so pale?
Just a little stomach ache.
I hear that a portrait of Jae Gyeong was found in Song Yu Min's art studio?
Yes, he stalked her.
- What is that?
- It's nail polish.
So the stalker abducted her?
But what if ... he wasn't just her stalker?
What if he was her assistant instead?
So if we consider that she plotted all this, like you were thinking...
So if we say that is true, then what do you think about that?
Appalled, of course.
It is unexpected. But isn't it a good thing?
You gave and received, after all.
Think about it in a positive way. In a way that is more advantageous to you.
You just have to make sure to get what you need.
So what is it that you need right now?
Trust and love between a husband and wife? No, not that corny stuff, I'm sure.
Team Leader Jin
Excuse me, I have to speak to one of our vendors.
Yes, Mr. Kim? I was going to call you, but some family visited us at home.
Good news?
Good news. I found his hideout.
I even confirmed his room number.
Okay, great.
With this, the five billion won is ours.
Don't stay there and go home for now. That crazy guy has a knife.
He tried to kill me with it earlier today.
He had a knife? You weren't hurt?
I did get hurt.
A very small cut. And thanks to this cut, I came to my senses.
He really is a maniac.
Now that I know where Song Yu Min is, you take care of her phone.
Got it. In fact, this is good timing.
Okay.
Since we've all gathered and it's been a while,
how about some wine? Some good wine?
I wonder what good wine we have?
Which wine did you pick?
Please pick the one you like, Honey.
This looks good.
Why is my cell phone here?
You are so out of your mind that you can't tell your phone apart from bread.
But what a relief that you found it.
As you wish.
This is the delicious wine that my wife selected. It's a very delicious wine.
Calls from Song Yu Min, 4 missed calls and a voicemail message
Here, have some wine, Brother-in-law.
Oh no, there are not enough glasses.
Seonbae, do you know where I am right now? Please hear it for yourself.
Was the paella a hit?
Yeah.
It's good to watch from afar, isn't it?
The light coming out of someone else's window
seems especially warmer, somehow.
When you don't know what's going on inside that home, of course.
So, this month—
I'll turn in first.
This month's deposit is late. Please send it by tomorrow.
I'm sorry, I will send it within a few days.
♫  Your bickering every day is wearing me out. Damn  ♫
♫  The game is boring. No ummm.  ♫
♫  After a long night, in front of me was  ♫
♫  another boring scene. No ummm.  ♫
♫  I giddily think whether I have it or not.  ♫
♫  Your eyes shine differently from the start, you are shaking again  ♫
(she's deleting the recording of Yu Min's attack in the garage)
♫  Oh, love me like you do  ♫
♫  We are a wall which has lost the way  ♫
(Deleting file)
♫  Tell me what you want now  ♫
♫  I'm sick and tired  ♫
♫  Even if it's something which will light a fire in your heart  ♫
♫  In the change of heart which no one was aware of  ♫
♫  I might be going crazy  ♫
♫  At last you want me.  ♫
♫  Firmly set at  ♫
♫  Orange moonlight night  ♫
♫  At last return my side  ♫
♫  At last you return my side  ♫
♫  Return my side  ♫
♫  You’re locked inside my heart now  ♫
♫  Orange-colored moonlight  ♫
♫  At last you return my side  ♫
♫  Return my side  ♫
Bar SUD
It was unexpected.
That Yu Min would do something so excessive,
I really never imagined that.
I warned you that not everything will go as planned. Maybe you should stop now.
No. I will take this to the end.
This is just the beginning.
I swear it to N31.
Then you should be thoroughly prepared.
So what should I do?
If it were me, I would ask him to die.
Je Chong Art Supply Store
Seonbae?
This really is the last time.
Thank you.
A little scuffle, last night.
You just have to tell them that all you did was help me because I asked you to.
I will protect you in my own way.
In July, on a bench with Seonbae
Seonbae's beautiful smile
Is this Yu Min?
Yes.
Do you want to meet now?
How is your injury?
It's fine.
What you did today, it wasn't like you.
I don't regret what I did.
If you need me to, I can change even more.
Yu Min.
We must return to where we both were now.
If you ever need my help with anything, tell me.
You're the one who needs help, Seonbae.
Leave that home. Seonbae,
come to me.
Now, for me, my original place is with you.
Please listen well and make a decision.
Then you will know what this original place for you really means.
So, what we were talking about ...
Now this, suddenly?
Do you still trust your husband?
Do you really believe that he has changed?
He has to change.
You should as well.
Don't worry about me, worry about yourself.
- Seonbae.
- Don't worry about me, I said.
Not sleeping, Honey?
Have you ever seen our neighbor lady drive before?
I don't think I have.
We should become closer to our neighbors.
There are so many things we don't know.
Are we close?
What more would you like to know?
Just,
it's nice to get along and not keep secrets.
What about you, Honey? Isn't there something you are hiding from me?
♫  We are travelling on the same train
Both of us. Both of us  ♫
♫  Both of us. Both of us  ♫
♫  And we are going in the same direction  ♫
♫  But I, I don't know you  ♫
♫  And you, you don't know me  ♫
♫  But in a short time, that will change  ♫
Didn't you say you will take that to the police?
You do it.
You do it. And tell them whatever is more advantageous for you.
So what do you plan to do now?
I just want an ordinary life with you.
Ordinary? Does that make any sense now?
Do you not realize that this is a chance for us?
Our last chance for us to start over.
Or perhaps the only chance I have left to run away.
Have a good day at work.
Our neighbors aren't home.
I may not be able to come by the restaurant to help today.
Good thinking. Rest.
- You found this in your bedroom?
- Yes.
We can only conclude that the abductor put it there.
Yes, probably.
Did you find this yourself?
No, my wife found it.
She said the angle of the outlet's wall plate was off, so she examined it,
and that's how she found it. My wife has
always been very meticulous and neat.
Did you install CCTV inside the home?
No, not yet.
If you had that one thing, everything would be solved.
Yes, I will discuss it with my wife.
I better go to work now.
Yes.
How meticulous is she that she can see that the angle of the wall plate is off?
It's certainly unusual.
But thinking back, the site was excessively clean.
Invitation: Masterpieces from Unknown Artists Discovered Online
I really hope that you will come, Seonbae.
If you don't take care of this debt, there will be difficulties.
Please take care of the principal balance and interest as soon as possible.
-Gentleman Capital-
Do you think I can endure this any longer?
Endure it. We are married.
Today we are having perilla seed porridge.
My always-smiling wife, I can never know what she's really thinking.
What brings you here so early in the morning?
What if you catch me cheating on you?
What do you mean? I will kill you.
Oh, I see.
This tastes good. Let me eat.
Let me eat, I said!
Let's breathe freely.
We'll take revenge on your wife by stealing the five billion won.
Standing by all day.
My only hope.
Jin Seon Mi, fighting.
Masterpieces from Unknown Artists Discovered Online
Museum of Mika
You've never met the artist while preparing for this exhibition?
No, this exhibition is for artists found on social media, so some have submitted their work anonymously.
You've never even spoken to him on the phone?
No, this artist is known for never showing his face, so we were hoping to meet him
at the opening of the exhibition, actually.
#Buyeong-dong Abduction
#Song Yu Min
It's that work over there.
#The relationship between crime and art
- Ah, yes.
- Please excuse us.
The Wife
Song Yu Min
Oil Painting
He's doing as he pleases.
We will have to hurry.
July 10 Thursday
I think he's finally moving!
Wait until I arrive.
I made my last request.
He won't deviate from the plan again, will he?
Don't worry, things will go according to plan.
♫  I see and trust only you  ♫
♫  There was a time like that  ♫
♫  A dream-like time  ♫
♫  I know the next story which only you don't know  ♫
You really have nerves of steel.
Even coming to the exhibition of your abductor's artwork.
What do you mean, abduction?
I don't think of it that way.
I trust in him.
I see that is so.
It's the opening of his exhibition,
but apparently, the artist himself can't be here, right?
I would love to meet him, even by chance, Artist Song Yu Min.
- Excuse me?
- Yes?
You haven't cleaned this room.
- I'm sorry, I'll do it right away.
- Never mind, please just bring the fresh towels.
- I had left something behind.
- I exchanged your towels.
- Thank you. Please clean this room tomorrow.
- Yes.
Samoyed
♫  You wouldn't know that I've got you now.  ♫
♫  Without knowing, you    ♫
♫  You dare tear all my heart apart  ♫
♫  Fearless you, right?  ♫
♫  Who’ll ever gonna get you out?  ♫
♫  Confined alone in a blocked tunnel  ♫
♫  Yeah no one gonna hide you now  ♫
♫  You better move. Run  ♫
I'm almost there.
Just wait, I'm coming.
The green light is now on in my life.
Why won't she answer my calls?
What? Is she screwing me over?
Oh, you startled me.
- Why won't you answer my calls?
- Kim Yun Cheol!
Why are you shouting at me?
I almost died because of you, do you know that?
What? What did I do?
Why would you send a text message at that time?
Did you ... did you go into that guy's room without me?
You're not trying to take the whole five billion won for yourself, are you?
Yes, sure, that's what I was doing.
We are so out of sync, could we even get five cents?
I'm obviously crazy. F*ck.
F*ck? Jeez.
Did you just cuss at me?
Oh, is my honey's pride hurt?
You're so slow, I had to step up.
You're always going here and there, we don't have time.
You can't do anything without me.
What did you say? I can't do anything?
And must I hear that from you, too?
If you don't like it, return.  Return to your perfect, psycho wife.
Jin Seon Mi, you are really...
Really what? ( room key card)
You are really
amazing. Wow.
Now it's your turn to show what you can do.
Don't worry and just trust in me.
- Which floor?
- 502
502, okay.
- What?
- Be quiet. Quiet.
- Song Yu Min showed up.
- What?
What? You said he left just a little while ago.
I know. He's going in and out so often.
What do we do now?
But for now, we have the key, so let's think this over.
For today, retreat. Let's withdraw.
I have a request of you.
Yu Min.
Yes, Seonbae?
I saw your exhibition artwork.
You went?
Are you ready?
Yes.
"How to Write Seductive Prose"
"Sentence Strengthening"
"Agatha Christie Package"
"Famous Influencer Sim Jae Gyeong was abducted"
"Influencer Sim Jae Gyeong has disappeared"
It should not have been that wine... that this wine would end my life, who could...
2004 Famous chef and chaebol daughter's wedding
L'Amour Eternel
Perhaps eternal love shouldn't be made carelessly...
Till death do us part...
You're home?
What will you write before you give up again?
I am going to finish this one.
Genre?
A married couple thriller.
Content?
A wife is abducted.
But it turns out, she planned all of it herself.
Is the title perhaps
"Please Don't Look for Me?"
(T/N: In Korea, the official title of the movie "Gone Girl" is "Please Look for Me.")
You're not uploading that somewhere or trying to enter some writing contest, are you?
I'm going to upload it to the police website and put your name down as the author.
Can't you just write it and keep it to yourself, like a diary?
You won't complain that no one is reading it or that you were rejected by the writing contest, and sink into hysteria—
Hysteria?
Looks like you misunderstood me. I'm talking about the  history  of your story...
I'm tired.
Mr. Seo Ji Tae?
How about putting that in the laundry basket?
Yes, ma'am.
Take your socks off, too. Don't turn them inside out.
Yes.
- Take a shower, too.
I will.
Samoyed
You're home?
You seem so busy lately.
I had some things to take care of at the company.
Everyone's crying that they miss me there.
Is that a new product you're launching? Is that mine?
No, I charged this on a credit card, for myself.
I haven't shopped in a while, so I felt the itch.
Good job.
Sorry.
Let's go together for a shopping spree soon.
What did you do today, Honey?
Me?
Thought about a business plan.
I'm hoping that you can take a rest from work.
You can't work in another job.
But I should prepare to be on my own, too.
If you take another job, that will be in breach of our contract.
Be faithful to me only.
"Amour." (2012 film)
Do you remember that movie?
The husband ends up killing his wife who is suffering from dementia.
But it was like he was killing himself.
Could you do the same?
That's a movie.
It made me think that I could marry if it was for that kind of love.
To protect each other until the end,
and to entrust him with my final moment.
Isn't that so beautiful?
No thanks. I can't do that.
I can protect you until the final moment.
No thanks to that, too.
You can't refuse.
You swore on this wine.
L'Amour Eternel.
Till death do us part, forever.
L'Amour Eternel
I'm going to keep that promise.
No matter what I have to do.
L' Amour Eternel
Sit down.
But I'm a little tired.
Just one glass.
Alright, just one glass.
Alright.
Drink.
The clinking of our glasses together.
This is the last time.
Oh, my head.
I'll go to work first and practice roasting beans.
Old Crop
Here is a delivery.
To: Sim Jae Gyeong
Old Crop Restaurant
From: Coffee Mill
Jongno-Gu
Sign here, please.
Samoyed
It's finally in my hands.
Successful revenge.
That there is infinite happiness hidden inside the black world of coffee,
My husband said this.
It is definitely just as he said.
♫   What can I do for your love?  Crazy every day, without you   ♫
♫   A silent cry, I'll let you go away   ♫
I knew that my husband was secretly following me.
♫   From me.  I know  ♫
And that he was after the money, also.
♫   You know, we know   ♫
Don't look to the right.  My husband is following me.
♫   Nothing is eternal   ♫
♫   I know, you know, we know.  So far away   ♫
That's why I showed him the money.
♫   Far way, get away   ♫
That there really was five billion won.
♫   Far away, get away right now  ♫
♫   Far away, get away   ♫
You surprised me, Honey!
♫   Far away, get away right now   ♫
♫   Without you, without you   ♫
Fresh coffee will get delivered early in the morning.
Delivery Expected: 7/9/2020
7:00 AM
My husband, who has a bad hangover, will not be able to wake up at that time.
When my husband has a goal, he becomes kind and close to my ideal man.
I need this money to do things according to my plan.
It's the lifeline that will tether my husband and preserve my marriage.
♫  I know you know we know  ♫
♫  I know it can't be undone  ♫
An unopened bean bag is the best place to hide a secret.
♫   I know, you know, we know.  So far away   ♫
♫   Far away, get away   ♫
In the past, my husband used to tell me often about the charms of coffee.
Though he kept talking about the same thing, I liked that face.
♫   Far away, get away right now   ♫
Because he seemed like a little boy.
♫   Far away, get away   ♫
The true story starts now.
Actually, I don't like coffee.
♫   Far away, get away right now
♫   Without you, without you   ♫
♫   Far away, get away   ♫
Please step back.
♫   Your bickering everyday is wearing me out, damn   ♫
♫   The game is boring, no umm   ♫
♫   After a long night, in front of me   ♫
♫   Was another boring scene   ♫
Whatever the reason, not keeping a promise
♫   I giddily think whether I have it or not   ♫
Is unforgivable.
♫   Your shining eyes are different from the start, you're shaking again   ♫
♫   Love me like you do.  We're a wall that lost its way  ♫
♫   Tell me what you want now.  Tell me what you want now  ♫
♫   I'm sick and tired  ♫
A dead end. The edge of a cliff.
The end of the line was not far away.
♫   At last you want me.  Locked inside my heart   ♫
It's right in front of my eyes.
♫   Orange moonlight   ♫
♫   At last you return my side   ♫
♫   At last return my side   ♫
♫   You're locked inside my heart now   ♫
♫   Orange moonlight.  At last you return my side   ♫
♫   Our crazy relationship really is strange, like a psycho.  Struggling, you try to read my face   ♫
♫  Tingling Tingling you hope. The devil whispers to me.  ♫
♫   Tell me what you want right now   ♫
My Dangerous Wife
Did she...? Did my wife plan this, too?
CCTV around this area, fingerprints, footprints, hair, make sure to scrape every last thing that may involve Kim Yun Cheol.
You reported me?
This is for your sake.
We finally meet. You're curious how much we know, aren't you?
I'm sorry.  I did something I shouldn't have.
Bring me the money now, or I will kill you.
Will you return it to me?
My five billion won.
♫   At last return my side   ♫