Married Woman Abducted, Demand for 5 Billion Won in Ransom
My Dangerous Wife
She killed Song Yu Min and disposed of the corpse without a trace.
How can she look so calm?
He left behind the thing that he should have burned first?
I knew that my husband was secretly following me, and that he was after the money, also.
You're not scared of me, are you?
I am more scared. Me!
I won't go down alone. I will kill this piece of trash first.
I told you don't do anything on your own!
You really have nerves of steel, even coming to the exhibition of your abductor's artwork.
What should I do?
If it were me, I would ask him to die.
How about we take the five billion won?
Do you know where it is?
Don't worry. Things will go according to plan.
There is infinite happiness hidden in the black world of coffee.
My husband said that.
I need this money to do things according to my plan.
A dead end at the edge of a cliff. The end of the line was not far away. It's right in front of my eyes.
Whatever the reason, not keeping a promise is unforgivable.
It was not the princess's kiss that made the frog into a prince.
The princess is disgusted by the frog, so she throws it to the ground.
The frog must die in order to become the prince.
Marriage is a type of a cruel fairytale, too.
You thought you married a prince,
but you come to realize that your husband is a frog.
Why did he die?
Why?
Honey, did you get the money?
This isn't the time for that. Song Yu Min...
he died. He is dead.
What? What happened?
Did... you do that?
No! No! He fell out of the window and I saw it.
No way.
- Excuse me.
- Yes? Is something going on?
We wanted to ask you something.
There was an incident nearby so we're gathering information.
- An incident?
- Yes, a man fell from a nearby motel and died.
- Was it suicide?
- For now,
it's hard to say that for sure. But have you seen anything?
No, nothing in particular.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Wait, hold on!
I was thinking that I saw you somewhere. Aren't you the husband of that woman who was abducted?
- You are mistaken.
- I'm sure I've seen you before.
I'm sorry, I'm in a hurry.
Wait a minute, sir, please!
Sir.
I think Song Yu Min was renting that room.
Detective,
I saw Kim Yun Cheol in the parking lot.
Seonbae, Kim Yun Cheol was in a nearby parking lot, he said.
- Are you sure?
- I confirmed it with his car license plate number.
Kim Yun Cheol, you don't think...
Everyone listen up. CCTV around this area, fingerprints, footprints, hair,
make sure to scrape every last thing that may involve Kim Yun Cheol.
This makes it look like I killed him.
Why did Song Yu Min die?
Did he commit suicide? If not...
No way, my wife? Did my wife plan this, too?
She knew I was planning to take the money, and she wanted to let me know she knew?
This could have all been part of her plan all along.
Old Crop
I think I made an enemy out of the last person whom I should make into an enemy.
Episode 7
Perfect Wife
Omo,
what brings you here at this early hour?
I wake up so early now because I've gotten old.
Since I was awake, I thought I'd get a free cup of morning coffee from Brother-in-law.
Ah, Yun Cheol isn't here, yet. If it's alright, let me make it for you.
Oh, I'd be grateful. But Jae Gyeong, you're at the restaurant by yourself so early?
I am learning how the restaurant works so I can be helpful. So I came early to get things ready.
Ah, yes.
Gentleman Capital
Let's see... it's already been two years since this restaurant opened, huh?
I know, right? Time sure flies, doesn't it?
Oh, it's done?
Thank you.
- It tastes great, indeed.
- I'm glad to hear it.
Have you had breakfast?
Breakfast? When I live alone?
How are you doing living alone?
It can be comfortable, but also uncomfortable, of course.
How about you? Are you two getting along?
It can be comfortable, but also uncomfortable.
Let's see,
how many years has it been since you two married?
Six years.
Six years. It's about time you're both very uncomfortable, huh?
Is that right?
I'm actually feeling more comfortable, lately.
Hold on just a moment. Let me whip up at least a simple snack for you.
Hello.
Yes, welcome.
- Your husband?
- He is probably at home. I came here a bit early today.
We meet again, Seonbae.
Want to share a cup of morning coffee?
I'm not in the mood. I will take a look inside.
What? Why?
Um, has anything happened?
Song Yu Min has died.
What? Why?
It appears he fell from the window of a room he was staying in.
Then did he commit suicide?
We don't know that yet.
It could be homicide.
Please stop being interested. I don't think it concerns you.
But it involves my family, how could it not concern me?
Just because I got divorced, does that end the affections that have accumulated?
There was something suspicious, so I came here to confirm.
Someone saw Kim Yun Cheol near the site of the death.
What?
Seonbae.
He's not here.
I sent an investigator to your home, too, and he's not there, and he's not here.
Is there anywhere else Kim Yun Cheol is likely to go to?
I'm not sure.
If he should contact you, please give us a call right away.
- Yes.
- Sorry for the intrusion.
Something is off. Let me check it out too.
Yes.
I'll have breakfast after.
I found out that he and Kim Yun Cheol's sister got divorced a few years ago.
Usually, he wouldn't care about his divorced wife, right?
There's only one reason he would be snooping around here. He smelled money.
He hopes to somehow get a rake-off.
He does other side jobs beside his pawnshop.
Does a pooping dog stop pooping?  He will do anything for money.
He didn't have enough money to even gamble on screen, so he stole confiscated items.
I can't believe he was a detective.  Seriously.
What is this?  Where are the coffee beans?
Delivery Expected: 7/9/2020
7:00 AM
Darling, didn't you follow her?
She wasn't there.
She really wasn't? She might have been tracking her accomplice to catch him.
I said she wasn't there.
What happened to him, Song Yu Min?
It would be nice if I were joking.
Driving me crazy, really!
But why did you run away?  It makes you look more suspicious.
Yeah, I know.  But, at the moment, I didn't know what to do.
Calm down.  What are you going to do now?
Let me think about that.
I think I should let it all out.
What?  Tell the police everything?
My wife and that bastard conspired to do the kidnapping,
the two had a conflict over the five billion,
she killed Song Yu Min
and you made me a criminal!
- Do you have any evidence?
- Evidence? Evidence.
Who will the police believe if she says she doesn't know?
Look. Yun Cheol, can you defeat your wife?
Honestly speaking, you went to the motel to steal the money, didn't you?  You did.
She will say you killed him while fighting over the money.
What should I do?
Is anybody home?
Miss Jin Seon Mi, we're coming in.
Jin Seon Mi, are you there?
- What has happened that you are here so early—
- I'm looking for Kim Yun Cheol.
Let me take a look inside.  This is a warrant.
-  Wait a moment.
- Excuse me.
When was the last time you talked to Kim Yun Cheol?
- I'm not in contact with him.
- Really?
I'm just a girlfriend he dumped.
I got a court warrant to examine Kim Yeon Cheol's communication records.
The records will say whether or not what you are saying is right or wrong.
When something happens to Kim Yun Cheol,
whom will he reach out for first, you or his wife?
I think it will be you.
What do you mean?
That's a compliment.
Really, because of that Sim Jae Gyeong!
Did you go and completely forget?
You're such a high maintenance person.
H-How are you here?
An anti-theft GPS is basic.
Wait a sec.  This is ... isn't this near the woman's house?
Are you still seeing her?
I think it would be better to rely on me than her.
Why are you someone I should believe and trust?
Because it's easier to trust me. Why do you keep going on the difficult path?
First, let's get rid of the car.  The police aren't dummies either.
Here, get out.
Hurry up.
Drink.
It's been a long time since we went on a date.
In the old days, you would order a cup of coffee and talk all day.
Here's your coffee.
Thank you.
I want to hear what you used to say.
Do you remember?  What you used to say to me?
"A perfect woman like you is too good for someone like me."
Cut that out!  I'm being chased by the police.
How did you know where Yu Min lived?
Why did you go find him? Were you following him?
Did you two plan it? To steal the five billion?
Did you kill him while the two of you fought over the money?
No.  It's not me.
It's not.
I believe you. You don't have the guts.
You have the guts.
Sim Jae Gyeong, you know you're the one who killed him.
Ridiculous.
That was the goal from the start. You were planning to make me a killer, right?
- After such a long time, do you want to ruin our date?
-  Stop kidding and be honest.
You did it, didn't you?
If it were me, it would have been different.
I would have done it perfectly, so unless someone knew,
it would be hard to find a clue.
No.  It's been done in order to make me the culprit.
You are pathetic.  Why would I make you the culprit?
If you were thinking about it, you would have put to good use a knife covered with fingerprints,
for example, like this!
What are you going to  do now? Are you insane?
There would be concrete evidence and the police would walk in and catch you red-handed.
They asked me to let them know when I saw you.
They have probably already surrounded you.
Did you report me?
It's for your sake.
Welcome.
It's okay.  If you remain silent until 4 o'clock, you will be proven innocent.
- What do you mean?
- Trust me. I'll rescue you. Give me the knife.
Mr. Kim Yun Cheol.
We finally meet.
Honey.
Let's go.
Are you okay?
Thank you.  I am a lot better.
From now on, don't work overtime.  You're in bad shape immediately after.
... suspect Song Yu Min was found dead this morning at a motel on Jongno 5-ga.
At the scene of the incident there was a painting, apparently painted by Mr. Song, and a knife,
and the police are considering both the possibility of murder and suicide.
Why did you turn it off?
Because I keep on becoming upset.
I'm sorry that I haven't paid your salary yet for last month.
Can you wait a little longer?
Okay.
Let me ask you just one question.
This morning, why were you near
where Song Yu Min's body was found ?
It's quite ...
So ...
- Hello.
Is it true that the president was taken to the police station?
He just was accompanied there as a reference witness.  He will be back very soon.
Will our restaurant be okay? His image keeps appearing.
It will be fine.  Just do your work as usual.
We will. We should try harder at times like this.
Could you prepare  a special dish before dinner?
You're very taciturn today. Well, there's no rush
because the evidence will wait.
To be honest, I was rooting for you.
I was sorry that I suspected you initially.
But this isn't right.  Money is the most important thing till the end.
What did she mean that by 4 o'clock my innocence will be proven?
Can I really trust my wife?
This is a video from a CCTV outside a convenience store in the vicinity of where Song Yu Min's body was found.
That's you, right?
I think you were very upset. It seems you're running away.
It's correct that's me.
It's because I was shocked to see the scene of the accident.
Could it be ... also ... that was a coincidence?
A morning drama coincidence? Was running away also a coincidence?
What do you mean by "running away"?
Wasn't it a suicide?
It was murder.
There was a knife near his body.
Song Min Yu's fingerprints are on the handle.
He probably jumped holding on to the knife.
Would a suicidal person jump holding onto a knife?
♫  Because you who are wandering in the endlessly dark night  ♫
♫  have put yourself in my hand  ♫
♫  Even if you try to run away you will circle  ♫
♫  inside my desolate maze without any opening  ♫
♫  Who’ll ever gonna get you out?  ♫
♫  You better move. Run.  ♫
4F Interrogation Room
Detective Seo.
All right.
You're wondering how much we know, right?
- Jeez! What are you doing?
- Young lady ...
Let go of me.
Hurry.
- Jin Seon Mi.
- What are you doing now?
Let her go!
Detective. I've come to save Kim Yun Cheol.
Wasn't your relationship that you neatly dumped each other?
Actually, we were supposed to meet at a nearby love hotel this morning.
We are still seeing each other.
Yun Cheol ran away to hide that fact.
He had nothing to do with the death of Song Yu Min.
It wasn't nearby was it?  It was the same motel.
I verified it in a video from a CCTV at the motel Song Yu Min stayed at.
I obtained a statement from  a member of the cleaning crew.
How would you explain that?
I ...
I felt sorry for him. He was like me.
After meeting him,  I wanted to persuade him to turn himself in.
But I coudn't meet him. Really.
I wanted to meet him.
Then, I could have prevented the ultimate choice.
If you continue to lie like that,
you will be liable as an accomplice or for criminal concealment.
Yun Cheol is innocent.
He was afraid I would be in danger. I told you we went together.
Are you really here for the sake of Kim Yun Cheol?
You must have come for yourself.
You thought it would be better to say it before you are discovered
seeing Kim Yun Cheol through our review of his phone records. You're very intelligent.
It's a compliment.
We're talking first in there.  Make yourself comfortable at home.
Your turn is next.
Is it Jin Seon Mi?
I'm the attorney representing Sim Jae Gyeong. Nice to meet you.
You're getting this as a favor from Sim Jae Gyeong.
You're going to need it.
What is this?
It's severance pay.
On condition that you never approach Kim Yun Cheol again.
The amount should be satisfactory.
Excuse me, I'll leave first.
Fine. Let's see where this leads.
Excuse me.
Thank you for your hard work.
I am Kim Yun Cheol's wife, Sim Jae Gyeong.
Could I please see my husband?
This was voluntary, wasn't it?
My client doesn't want to listen anymore. Right, Mr. Kim Yun Cheol?
Oh, yes.
Please release Kim Yun Cheol immediately.
Is this ... ?  What about waiting until 4:00?
I understand.
- Chief Seo.
- Inspector Seo.  That's enough.
Somehow, I am escaping.
Kim Yun Cheol,  thank you for giving so much time.
Detective Seo.
There, shall we return?
Wait a minute.
Kim Yun Cheol's blood was discovered
on the tip of the knife found at the scene.
DNA Examination Results
Sample 1: Kim Yun Cheol; Sample 2: Crime scene evidence
"Song Yu Min's fingerprints were on the knife handle."
It's conclusive evidence that the two people met.
I would like to request an arrest warrant.
No, no. Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
I am to blame.
It was all my fault.
I will tell... the truth about everything.
Jae Gyeong.
What are you talking about?
That guy attacked my husband in the garage.
Since he was driven to the edge, he said that he would kill my husband and then himself.
Wait a minute.
Are you saying that the kidnapper was Song Yu Min?
He said that himself.
The blood on the knife was from the fight that day.
My husband almost died because of that man.
You expect us to believe that?
I was in a state of panic, so I hit his head with this.
And he stole our car's spare key to sneak in and attack us.
I'm submitting these as evidence.
Isn't this enough evidence?
We will hold on to these.
Why... why didn't you report this to the police?
I suggested that he turn himself in
because that was the best thing for him.
He asked for time to think.
I was waiting for him to turn himself in.
How could this happen?
Then Kim Yun Cheol, what were you doing near the scene of the incident?
Yes, I was...
- I was—
- I had a bad feeling.
It seemed like that man would cause trouble somehow,
so I said that I was going to meet him because I was worried.
My husband went to meet with him instead because it was dangerous.
Yes, how could I not run away in shock?
When the person I went to meet was dead?
But then... why didn't you tell the truth from the beginning?
- The thing is—
- Honey!
Just tell the truth and tell them you were trying to protect me.
On the day he was attacked, my husband thought we should tell the police right away.
If not, there was a risk of committing the crime of hiding a criminal.
In order to prevent me from being accused of a crime for protecting my hoobae,
he didn't say anything until the end.
Honey.
I'm sorry.
No, it's alright.
Fine.  I understand why your husband was at that place,
however, that isn't evidence that he didn't kill Song Yu Min.
It's possible that his talk with Song Yu Min didn't go well, so at the end of a long argument,
an accidental homicide is possible.
My husband is not the kind of person who would do that even by mistake.
Seonbae.
This was delivered to the investigation headquarters.
N31
To all of you who are investigating,
please deliver this letter to Sim Jae Gyeong.
This is Song Yu Min.
Sunbae Jae Gyeong,
Since the day I drew you, sixteen years ago,
I admired you.
I wanted to be with you.
If I falsely accused your cheating husband of a crime,
I thought you would come back to me.
♫   I see   ♫
That's what I believed.
♫   And trust only you   ♫
However, when I saw how happy you looked on the day you left the hospital,
♫   There was a time like that   ♫
my dream of being with you collapsed.
But I couldn't give up.
If only that bastard would die,
♫   Joining you was enough   ♫
Then I thought that you could be free.
♫   In a love   ♫
I found out that your thoughts were different from mine.
♫   Which would last forever   ♫
♫  now, everything  ♫
Now...
everything has lost its meaning.
What I wanted wasn't money.
♫   It was just   ♫
I also burned all of the five billion won.
♫   Your plausible excuse.   ♫
Along with the money that made you miserable,
♫   It's a nice wish   ♫
From this world, I will...
♫   My flower   ♫
... disappear.
♫   Is falling   ♫
If possible,
♫   In your laughter   ♫
Please cremate me with the portrait I drew of you, Seonbae.
♫  Forever   ♫
Thank you, and I'm sorry.
With this, your charges against Kim Yun Cheol have all disappeared.
There's no doubt that Song Yu Min committed suicide.
We can assume that the kidnapping case has been solved as well, right?
Expected delivery date and time: 7/11/2020, 4:00 PM
Yun Cheol, if you can stay silent until 4 o'clock,
your innocence will be proven.
Was this your hidden card?
You really are perfect, Sim Jae Gyeong.
- Kim Yun Cheol is here!
- He's here.
- Kim Yun Cheol, any progress on the case?
- Why have you been summoned by the police?
How are you involved with the suspect Song Yu Min's death?
- I'm sorry.
Please refer to the police announcement for full details.
Kim Yun Cheol, I have one more question.
Kim Yun Cheol, please speak to us.
How are you related to his death?
Sunbae.
There is a high possibility that the handwriting will match Song Yu Min's.
What's going to happen?
We will have to re-do the puzzle. I can't see the picture.
There was something I missed.
What?
The fact that they're still a married couple.
I will start the briefing.
After abducting Sim Jae Gyeong and demanding a large amount of money,
the kidnapping suspect, Song Yu Min,
took a leap to his death this morning, and has died.
We, the police have concluded that Song Yu Min was the sole culprit,
and are planning to close the investigation.
She came out.
- Did you hear the police announcement?
- How do you feel right now?
All of you...
By chance, are you hungry?
The pizza is here.
- Is the food to your taste?
- Yes, and we were hungry.
You must have been hungrier since you have to work hard because of us.
If you need anything else, just let me know.
We need to give Madam a second look. Her idea is daebak.
There will be automatic publicity for the restaurant.
Try it while it's warm.
I'm sorry.
I did something I shouldn't have done.
The kindness that the boss showed me,
I interpreted the way I wanted to and crossed the line.
As another woman,
I committed an unforgivable sin towards you.
I wanted to apologize in person.
I take responsibility for all of it.
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
I want to continue to work here.
I will work harder than anyone else to repay you for my sins.
You can curse at me.
I will take all your criticism and work hard.
Please,
Could you...
let me work here again?  I beg you.
What are you doing?  Get up.
Anyone can make a mistake.
We can start again from the beginning.
Even in the future, please take good care of our restaurant.
Thank you.  Thank you.
Wow.  That's amazing.
Applause!
I knew you would say that.
Meat is all about timing.
You need to know the time when it's most delicious.
Eat up.
- I will eat well, Sunbae.
- Okay.
Eat up.  Here.
Investigating is timing also.
Relax, kid.  I'm just buying a meal for my hoobae.
This is just a person to person interaction, okay?
Go on.
From the police perspective, it would be best to blame Kim Yun Cheol, huh?
An unknown artist joined the adulterous husband to abduct the wife and get a ransom.
While dividing the money, there was a disagreement.
And Kim Yun Cheol got rid of Song Yu Min.
He appeared voluntarily at the police station.
But then get evidence and get a warrant.
He is my ex-wife's little brother.
So I just can't stand by and watch.
Should I get more food or not?
Thank you for the food.
Sit down.  Sit down.  Sheesh.
Oh, come on.
Ahjumma,
I'd like two more orders of ribeye!
My insides are burning up.
Excuse me?
The meat is burning.
So was there nothing special?
The cooler.
The cooler?
There was something strange inside.
What, was there charcoal briquets in the cooler?
There were coffee beans.
Coffee beans?
Coffee b-
Delivery to: Old Crop Restaurant
This was sent from our store.
Do you remember who bought it?
Why would you ask something like that?
I asked at the restaurant, and nobody knows.
Look, all sales are final, okay?
Of course. I need to know who sent it so that I can thank them.
It was a man, and he looked like he was in his thirties.
He didn't have any special features?
I thought he was the cook at that restaurant.
- The cook?
- Yes.
Well, he was pulling around that cooler, so I thought he was food shopping,
and that he must be ordering coffee beans as well.
- A cooler?
- Yes.
Old Crop Restaurant
Should we go home?
You're not going to ask me?
How I knew that the suicide letter was going to arrive at 4 o'clock?
It's fine, since I trust you.
So you trust me now.
Now that I think about it, I've only gotten help from you.
Truthfully, I'm thankful to you for that day.
Actually, I met Yu Min last night.
Don't say any more.
Listen until the end.
I asked Yu Min for a favor.
That he leave a suicide note, and...
hide somewhere as if he committed suicide.
You really didn't kill him?
I didn't do it.
Then... Song Yu Min really committed suicide?
The money.  What happened to the money?  Is it really gone?
What he wrote in the suicide note is probably the truth.
If you're worried about money, don't worry.
It's not a lot, but I have some saved up.
We can probably take care of the most urgent of your debts.
You need to protect the restaurant.
Bank Book
I really didn't think he would end up like that.
Let's go home.
Let's go eat, wash up, brush our teeth, and go to sleep together.
Those are the things that make a married couple.
Honey.
You didn't do anything wrong.  You did your best.
You... you're a good wife.
Old Crop __.17.05
Seonbae?
Song Yu Min?
Don't suffer on your own and tell me everything.
If I can help, I'll do anything I can.
I will make sure to protect you, Seonbae.
Seonbae, you are more important to me than art.
Would you die?
Could you die for me?
Leave behind a suicide note, and go somewhere
and live quietly, as if you'd committed suicide.
If I did that, would you come to me?
I wish that you weren't someone's wife
and that you'd just be a happy person.
Honey?
I will begin a new start today.
The early bird drinks the morning coffee, they say.
I am off to do a diligent day's work.
I remembered that feeling from yesterday.
My heart fluttered for the first time in a long time.
Indeed, my wife is first class.
What year were these beans purchased?
She was... almost perfect.
Indeed, my wife is first class.
The Old Crop coffee bean which must be cared for by observing the temperature and humidity carefully
should have been in the bag.
If even one bean was out of the bag,
it meant that someone opened the bag before it had ripened.
It was strange that the cooler was full of coffee beans instead of money.
So I thought that the money and the beans were exchanged at the market.
Someplace where no one would open the bag.
Right here. This was very like my wife.
Yes, let's say that this money is the price to be paid
for having opened memories that shouldn't have been opened.
If the money is here, that means the suicide note that he burned the money was not true.
Then Song Yu Min didn't commit suicide.
He was murdered?
My wife really was a scary person.
But who cares? I won't be seeing her face ever again.
The reason I loved the bittersweet taste of coffee
was because I was sick of all the grease that had I smelled since I was young.
- How many?
- Two fried chickens, please.
Ah, yes.
Hey.
What are you doing, not helping? Hurry and wrap those up.
Even if I ate only one meal, I wanted it to be a proper meal.
How to choose coffee beans.
Even if I drank only one cup, to drink it elegantly.
I became a chef, but the food I prepared was only put on the table of those who had money.
I was still hungry, so I had to climb higher.
This was my last ladder.
Wife
Good morning.
I just received a postcard in our mailbox.
Postcard?
It's from Song Yu Min.
There is a new cell phone number on it.
He was trying to tell me.
What are you saying?
It means Yu Min never intended to commit suicide.
Yes, it's not like there are just a few bizarre things about any of this.
Starting from why the knife that fell in our garage ended up there... ?
He was killed by someone. I'm sure of it.
But you know well who that killer is.
The person who had to become a suspect so that you could save me.
Then you shouldn't be calling me. You should be calling the police.
I'm worried about you, that's why.
You're not worried about something else instead?
Please be careful, Yun Cheol.
Yes, alright, alright.
There is an enemy that we don't know about.
I understand. Sure thing.
You're making me laugh. You're the one I have to be careful of you.
Rather than trust you, I will trust in this money.
♫  We are traveling on the same train  ♫
Why are you calling me so early?
Five billion won! It's in my hands now.
Five billion won!!
I found it in the coffee storage room.
We will take this money and run away together.
Got it?
Honey? Honey, what's wrong? Hello?
♫  Your bickering every day is wearing me out. Damn  ♫
♫  The game is boring.  ♫
♫  After a long night, in front of me was  ♫
♫  another boring scene.   ♫
♫  I giddily think whether I have it or not  ♫
♫  Your eyes shine differently from the start, you are shaking again  ♫
♫  Oh Love me like you do  ♫
♫  We are a wall which has lost the way  ♫
♫  Tell me what you want now  ♫
My Dangerous Wife
Preview
A tooth for a tooth. Poison for poison. I will use the poison that was going to kill me to recover my five billion won.
If we get caught, we don't know what she will do.
Your wife is certainly beyond my expectations.
My daughter Chae Rim!
Chae Rim has been kidnapped.
No! Don't go.
It was you who killed Song Yu Min, right?
Those who took what is precious to me must be mercilessly eliminated.
♫  Our crazy relationship is really weird like a psycho  ♫
♫  Struggling you try to read my face  ♫
♫  Tingling Tingling you hope.   ♫