Run for Young
Those sausages and bacon at Doggo's door
were made by us together
with Uncle Tu during the Spring Festival.
You miss uncle Tu too?
I used to see Uncle Tu and Doggo
making a noise and all that
whenever I stood on the balcony.
Now it's so quiet.
Why...
Why did it happen so suddenly?
Liang,
everyone has their own fate.
You'll understand when you're older.
Something's out of our control.
What's Doggo gonna do?
Will he move in with his mom?
I won't be able to see him then...
It's alright,
don't worry now.
This
depends on himself.
Actually,
I've long seen him
as my own child.
Whether he leaves
or stays,
I'll treat him just the same old way.
I'll make sure he's fed and kept warm.
Don't worry.
It's ok.
Episode 10 The Moon Speaks For Me
Who's on duty today? Why is the blackboard not wiped?
Tu...
Doggo should be back by now.
No idea.
He finally made it to the last term,
would he just drop out like this?
There's still the College Entrance Exam.
Will Doggo be astray then?
What're you talking about! Watch your mouth!
It's so strange not having him around.
You live so close,
don't you know what he's been up to nowadays?
He leaves the house early and comes back late.
We barely see him.
Stop being paranoid!
Let's go find him together tomorrow!
Let's go.
Looking at Doggo's empty desk these days,
I remembered when the term first started,
he told me he wanted to go to college.
Who would've thought
something like this would happen.
Yeah...
It was such a surprise to see someone
so cheeky like him want to work hard for once,
but then this happened...
Do you think he's not planning on coming back to school?
Looks like it.
It was his closest family member he lost.
Must be difficult to accept.
Looking at him like this
reminds me how I was like
back then.
He was the one that was there for me quietly,
waiting for me to come out of that phase.
Must have been difficult on him.
Who do you think
is taking care of him?
Will he keep himself warm and fed?
You're worrying too much.
There's Jiao,
Big Mouth
and Teaty.
They live together.
Surely they'll take care of him.
But I want to do something for Doggo too.
Speed it up!
I'm doing business here!
Yes, one sec.
Don't think you're my only client!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
You think you're my only client?
Hurry up and move your cart!
How dare he bully our Doggo!
Let go!
Don't make a scene here.
If you do,
you'll cause trouble to him.
Hurry up!
Move them quickly!
I can't do business like this!
Move them quick!
Or don't buy from me anymore!
Hurry up!
Are you not going back to school?
What about you?
Why are you doing this?
Are you punishing yourself?
Why aren't you coming to school?
It's almost graduation, Doggo.
I've been complaining about my old man all these years.
Blaming him for letting mom go.
Complaining that he's so stingy on me.
I only realized after coming here
that my old man worked really hard.
He's helped many people around here.
I've actually never really known him.
Have you thought about
what kind of person he wants you to be then?
I feel very sorry for how I treated him.
So I want to continue his business.
Thanks.
I'll do it.
Leave it to me. It'll get your clothes dirty.
It's fine.
You need to go to school later.
Don't worry.
I'll do it.
Fresh pork!
Have a look!
Fresh pork here!
Fresh pork!
Have a look here! Fresh pork!
Come over here!
Fresh pork!
Fresh pork here!
Have a look!
Fresh pork!
Have a look! Fresh pork!
You don't need to come help me tomorrow.
We're bros. What're you talking about.
This is my own business anyway.
Besides,
the other uncles at the market will help me as well.
- Doggo. - Doggo.
You haven't been eating properly these days, have you?
Come eat at our house then!
Don't worry, I eat very well every meal.
I'm fine,
don't worry about me.
Alright, go home now.
Look after yourself.
Remember to eat.
Let us know if you need anything.
Take some rest.
Dad.
What's the matter?
Feeling down?
Nothing.
It's just that I have a really good friend,
and something happened in his family.
I'm worried about him.
That boy?
Yeah.
His father passed away.
He might look like a cheeky boy
good for nothing
in your eyes,
but he's really kind to me.
Help him where you can then.
Nothing's bigger than life and death.
Jiao Jiao,
Sometimes,
you're like a boy,
and other times you're like a girl.
Your mom and I think it's such a bargain.
We only have to raise one, but it feels like we have two!
But now that you're growing up,
you're more like a girl now.
I'm not sure about that.
What I mean is that
actually
we could have
another boy
in the house... right?
Let me have a listen!
Let me listen!
What're you doing?
Let me have a listen!
Mom!
I can hear my little brother inside!
I mean Jun Jun!
Silly!
He's all by himself now.
We wanted to take him into our house.
You've always been like
brother and sister anyway.
Is that ok?
Oh you're so sweet, daddy!
It's just one more person at the dining table. We'll manage.
Mom, put two more eggs in it!
With more eggs,
it'd become egg fries meat,
not egg fries rice!
Put in more meat for Doggo then!
More meat here.
Enough, that's enough!
I'll put in more for him.
What if he doesn't have enough to eat?
I care for Jun Jun too,
but you can't mess with cooking!
Look how it's like now!
Now go and bring that bowl for me.
Thanks.
Yes yes. Have a seat inside.
Hi, Jiao Jiao.
Hello, aunty.
There's a fire here?
Doggo?
Anran?
Li Anran!
Why are you setting a fire here!
I'm making fried egg.
You're making fried egg?
You're setting a fire!
I'm really making fried egg!
All this smoke here,
I thought Doggo was gonna commit suicide!
This is your fried egg?
Dark as coal.
Putting up this grand stage,
I thought you're making an egg buffet or something.
Never mind, I'll teach you.
Turn off the fire first.
Watch carefully.
So you need oil for this.
A pampered kid like you
don't even know how to cook an egg for the person you like.
I don't like him!
You don't?
Why else would you be here making him breakfast this early?
Well, you know.
He did a lot for me before.
I want to be a good friend to him too.
Done!
Difficult?
You act so careless normally,
but you're actually so capable.
Isn't that normal?
You act so proud and cold normally,
but who would've thought you'd do this for others?
I'm not proud and cold,
I'm just a bit quieter than you all.
Don't tell this to others, can you do that?
Don't tell others you're quiet?
No, don't tell others
I came to his house to do this.
Ok.
I wanted to make dinner as well.
Really?
You? Making dinner?
What if I managed!
Besides, you're here to help me.
Seems like I'm the only one helping you.
Wow, so many in a pack! Such a deal!
This is so expensive. It has to be good.
This color is nice, it must be good then.
I've never even seen this. Let's pass this one.
You see the situation Doggo's in.
Why isn't anyone taking care of him?
Where's his mom?
His mom left when he was eight
to another city.
She has her own children and family now.
He aged significantly
since then.
That's why we call him Doggo.
Let's make up for the motherly love he missed!
Am I qualified?
Yes.
Don't suck up to me
just because you want me to help you make dinner!
I can tell.
But if Doggo has motherly love,
he won't be so aged then.
Does that make him...a puppy then?
Puppy.
So adorable!
Let's raise a puppy together then!
I like this color too.
Big Mouth got good grades this time.
He works hard at night by himself!
Jiao Jiao!
You're besties now?
Jiao is so capable now.
What do you think you're doing?
I went to your school
and the teachers told me you haven't been back.
I asked you to come to Chengdu with me
and you were unwilling.
What is it that you want?
I want to stay here.
Stay here for what?
Doing this good-for-nothing business?
Say something!
I'm working hard to carry on my old man business.
By the way, mom,
Do you know
how the people of this market
comment on my old man?
He's actually a very nice man.
Why did you leave him back then?
Your dad wasn't good-tempered when he was young.
Of course, mom was young too.
We didn't know better and fought a lot.
Now that I think of it,
it was probably all trivial.
Jun Jun, let mom ask you something.
Do you feel that
you don't have any chance to pay back to your dad
and you feel sorry for it.
Are you trying to make up to him?
When your dad was still around,
whenever he called,
as soon as he picked up the phone
he wouldn't stop talking about you.
He talks about your running,
you liking which girl,
you being happy
or unhappy.
Anyway, I think
I think...
He wouldn't want to
see you like this.
All of you are telling me
that my old man wouldn't want to see me like this.
But I also don't want to see
the most important thing to my old man disappear.
Every time I see that this pork stall is still here,
I feel that my dad's still here.
Mom.
Let me make my own decision.
Smash it then chop it, like this.
Not too much.
Be careful.
I'll grab you some toothpaste.
It works well on scalds.
Yeah!
Let me try.
Save them for Doggo!
You only care for your Doggo, not me!
I taught you to make these!
I'll take you out to eat then.
Let's go.
I'll eat the most expensive thing then!
Ok ok.
So terrible!
REMEMBER TO EAT
Why are the dishes of Teaty's house
so different?
Jiao Jiao is such a capable cook now.
Why?
Such big breakfasts every day.
Fried rice, fried egg, bread, coffee.
Chinese and western, combined.
But we only made you a bowl of fried rice!
Jiao Jiao?
Since when do you know how to make coffee and bread?
It wasn't me, it was Anran.
What has it to do with Anran?
She's very close with me these days,
so I looked at what she eats
and tried to make them.
Can you make me some coffee
and bread tomorrow then?
Don't just make it for him but not your old man.
That sounds so strange.
I'll see if I feel like it.
Uncle,
the fried egg is honestly so bad.
The fried egg is like a rock,
so rocky hard
you can't even bite into it.
That sounds scary.
What're you laughing at?
It sounds really bad.
You knew it was bad, didn't you?
You knew it was bad and you brought it to me.
What kind of friend are you?
Anran...
Anran surely won't cook this badly.
Uncle, aunty, thanks for the food.
Sure, Anran cooks the best!
Jiao Jiao,
a girl will have a hard time finding a husband
if she doesn't cook well.
Am I too late?
I'm sorry.
Do you remember it?
Back when we were in primary school,
we tried to copy the ceremony to become brothers.
We went to your old man's shop,
stole a pig's head out,
and stuck three incense sticks on it.
We were beaten into pulps by your old man.
Butcher was so scary!
Chasing after us.
How time flies.
Do you remember
what we said then?
We said
"My old man is yours
and yours mine.
My mom's yours
If one day,
we fell in love with the same girl,
we're damned
and fall out of love together then."
We were so silly back then.
Yeah...
I only realized now...
Growing up is actually so complicated.
Very complicated indeed.
My brother,
I really don't know how to comfort you.
I don't even know how to comfort myself.
If it's this difficult with training already,
what're we gonna do with the race?
Seems like Doggo is really not coming back.
No idea what he's thinking.
Can you persuade him somehow?
Doggo is a very stubborn one.
What's Doggo gonna do then?
Cut it finer!
Can you do it or not?
Do you wanna show me?
What?
I'm buying meat from you
and I have to do the job myself?
I don't mean it that way.
So all you do is hang your meat up?
I know it's not fine enough myself.
Enough, enough. Pack it for me.
What's this?
You haven't been to school for so long
you forgot I'm your "one-on-one" study pal!
No need for that anymore.
Why?
I'm not going back to school.
Don't be childish.
I'm being serious.
I saw an American film recently.
Watch this
if you don't want to read.
What film?
Forrest Gump.
What's it about?
It's about a man who seems to be a fool
but not quite.
He's a lot like you.
And then?
He's gained a lot
but none of them seem to be what he wants.
The things he really wanted, he didn't seem to grasp any.
All his loved ones
left him.
Sounds miserable.
What's he gonna do then?
And then one day,
he started running.
He kept running forward.
He kept running?
Kept running.
Why's he running?
No idea.
Well. he is a fool then.
How've you been recently?
I've been well.
Having enough to eat, enough to wear?
Their family are so kind to me.
So kind I feel a little embarrassed.
Don't be.
Don't starve yourself because you're embarrassed,
you understand?
The only thing is the level of cooking is really... random.
Some of the dishes are so bad.
Like which?
There was this fried cucumber with meat.
The cucumbers were black!
They fried it with their feet?
What else?
And the tomato and egg.
Normally in this dish,
you'd put sugar or salt.
But the one I got,
you have no idea what's inside.
Vinegar!
I suspect that the person
wasn't thinking about cooking at all when making...
You deserve to be starved to death!
Others worked so hard to cook for you,
how can you say that?
What're you mad for? You didn't make them!
It's just me!
It's just that I think
if others worked so hard to cook for you,
you shouldn't say it's bad like this.
But it really is very bad.
It's like food for dog.
It is food for dog!
You're called Doggo anyway!
What right have you to say the food is bad?
Why are you so angry? What's the problem?
It's one thing if the dishes are good,
it's another thing if you deserve them!
Hey, you're going already?
Not buying me dinner or something?
You don't deserve it!
So special.
Cares for me in one moment,
mad at me in another.
What! I'm working on my lyrics!
Super Girl.
Contestant, Zhu Weijiao.
Good luck!
Don't you know the most important thing now is the exam?
Why're you wasting your time on these?
Didn't you have enough at the new year's event?
Come on, go up and sing for the class.
Round of applause for her, everyone!
Come on.
Sir,
I think what you're doing is not right.
What did you say, Ma Tian?
I said, sir, I think what you're doing is not right.
I'm not right?
What you are doing will make students think
that having a dream and pursuing it
is something to be embarrassed and ashamed of.
I just don't want anyone to waste time
like this right now.
But I don't think this is wasting time.
Compared to this, being afraid of what others think
and not speaking out and realizing their dreams
for their whole life, that's really wasting time.
Sir, I think Ma Tian is right.
I've always thought the two of you
are good students.
Sir,
I also think Ma Tian is right!
Why,
you have a dream too?
Not... yet.
That's not true!
I have a dream!
Sir!
My dream is
Chen Yuanyuan!
Finally.
I signed up for you the other day.
Sign up for what?
Super Girls.
Chengdu Audition.
I haven't actually thought it through yet...
I'll be there with you then.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Ding Rongliang!
What did you do this time?
Wh... Wha... What is it?
Stop!
Your pant scarf.
For you.
I made it better.
And I'm keeping the other for myself.
Teaty my bro!
My guide is finally working!
This doesn't look like the style of Hercules Jiao...
Even two fish for me!
This painting...
looks so cheap.
They're surely getting tackier by the day.
They really think I'm a dog or what?
Never mind.
Your little brat's not gonna tell you stories today.
Today, I'm
gonna sing you a song!
The name of the song is
"The Moon Speaks For Me".
You asked me how deeply I love you,
to what extent is my love.
Thanks.
Anran!
You...
I... I...
I know!
You're here for your good friend Hercules Jiao, am I right?
Her house...
Her house is that way, not here.
I... I...
Since we're classmates,
I'll take you there.
No, I'm fine, really...
You don't know your directions around here.
Let's go!
Come on!
Jiao Jiao!
I brought your good friend
over to see you!
Jiao Jiao!
She was searching her way around at Doggo's place,
looking so lost.
You have to thank me!
Alright, alright, I see.
- See ya. - Jiao Jiao!
Be more careful next time you go to Doggo's place!
I will.
I really don't understand girls like you.
If I did this much,
I'd want the whole damn world
to know that I did it.
But you're
hiding around
in the corner and all that.
But if he found out
he'll surely be embarrassed.
I just think that
he needs someone to take care of him these days.
And he's not buying it.
He said your cooking was awful.
He said that to you too?
And he blames me for it!
Thank God he doesn't know it's me...
You really care this much about what he thinks of you?
You do like Doggo, don't you,
even just a little?
Of course I like him!
We're deskmates, after all.
Of course she likes you!
Just because you're deskmates?
You made...
those dishes?
I learned this from you.
Not everything you do for others needs to be seen.
If I knew...
those dishes were from you...
I would never have said those things.
I know they're bad myself.
They're... good.
So fake.