=The Future Lover=
=Episode 19=
Zhou Nanfeng,
I like you.
Can we be together?
Say yes!
Sorry.
Zhou Nanfeng!
(Zhiyi, I'm sorry.)
(I need more time to think it through.)
What's going on?
Xingyue!
Where did you go?
Why didn't you show up that day?
I never promised I'd come.
What's wrong?
We agreed yesterday.
- We...
- What do you mean by "we"?
We just met yesterday,
and I didn't promise you.
Don't contact me anymore.
What do you mean by "just met"?
I'm Zhong Ziye.
The boy who followed you around.
You shared candies with me.
You don't know me now?
No.
Then let's start fresh,
okay?
Let go.
It hurts!
♪Without a sense of belonging♪
♪I'm just an empty loft♪
♪Memories linger for too long♪
♪And my thoughts never stop♪
♪My heart keeps praying♪
♪Hoping you'd come to save me♪
♪I've made up endless reasons♪
♪I'll always wait for you♪
(Zhong Ziye,)
(I'm sorry.)
(I just lost you from another time.)
(I can't be with you)
(in this time and space for now.)
♪My heart's dam about to break♪
I turned down Zhong Ziye.
I also turned down Zhiyi.
Not sure if we should be together.
She's different from before.
I won't date with Zhong Ziye,
at least for now.
You're so certain.
I have many unfinished tasks.
This time
I won't be weak anymore.
I can't drag him down.
What's your plan?
What are you doing?
Let's get moving.
Business first.
No one leaves!
Explain yourselves clearly.
Then let me be clear.
We're together now.
Happy now?
Can we go?
Are you serious?
Yes, seriously.
We're together now.
Sorry, Zhiyi.
Will this really fool them?
I have no idea.
Anyway,
I'm going to find Gao Qiang.
See what he's up to.
After all, it's all because of him.
Alright, thank you.
Come with me.
Zhou Nanfeng.
Why did you
bring me here?
Are you and Zhou Nanfeng
really together?
Yes.
You're lying!
Since I started school,
I know every person
around you well.
You and Zhou Nanfeng
have no connection.
How could you be together?
It just shows
you're not observant enough.
Do you really dislike me?
So much that you'd lie
just to keep me away.
Yes,
I do dislike you.
I've disliked you since childhood.
You always followed me back then,
never letting me play with others.
And you're still the same now.
You're so annoying.
I don't want to see you again!
How can I...
♪Watching you from afar♪
♪Escaping in the past realms♪
♪Silent love, never spoken♪
♪Secrets buried, left unbroken♪
♪Regret builds, piece by piece♪
♪Scattered like rain, muddied in dust♪
♪I beg the wind to keep you for me♪
♪And to blow away my uneasy memories♪
♪You say love's too hard to measure♪
♪A loss without return♪
♪I say time flies, wind fades♪
♪But your heart is constant still♪
♪Midnight, starlight shining bright♪
♪With clouds and moon to guide your night♪
♪A gentle breeze, the insects sing♪
♪A tune of love, soft whispers bring♪
♪Spring, summer, autumn, winter
all bless you♪
♪Space and time begin to bend too♪
♪My universe still burns for you♪
♪Even if we're worlds apart♪
♪Your words still echo♪
♪Loneliness, a vow we keep♪
♪A faithful chase in troubles deep♪
♪Habits blur, pale and confused♪
♪Ahead, a light breaks through♪
♪Though each step burns, I walk for you♪