=The Unbreakable Bond=
(Adapted from Xiao A'man's novel)
("After the Ugly Concubine Divorced,
She is Wooed By Big Shots of the Capital.")
=Episode 17=
You shouldn't say that, Miss Yu.
Since the beginning of time,
women have had the monthlies.
That's human nature.
It's just like eating and sleeping.
It's nothing shameful.
Don't believe in those taboos
and end up crippling yourself.
Don't worry, I'll think of something.
Waiter.
Go to the nearest clothing store
and buy a coat.
The gameplay is a mess.
The past is but a dream.
Only sighs remain.
Not just sighs.
What happened back then
will surely come to a head.
I only wish Chuxia not to be hurt again.
To be happy.
With me here,
she will be.
Luoluo, there's something I have to do.
I have to go now.
(There's no news from Liefeng.)
(Did something happen?)
(I guess I'll have to go
to the Prime Minister's Residence.)
Chuxia.
Thank you for your help today.
I'll make a trip to
the General's Residence soon,
and show you the new designs
for my embroidered handkerchiefs.
You're welcome. See you soon.
Don't stop me.
Have you never wondered
how a housebound woman like Madam Qu
could have such remarkable capabilities?
Are you saying that
there's someone controlling her?
I don't want you to endanger yourself.
I'm not letting you
put yourself in danger.
Step aside.
If you hadn't given me
the porridge back then,
I would've died from hunger.
I even bit you.
I had been looking for you
all these years.
I only know that you're a daughter
of an official,
but I didn't know which family.
You're the little boy at Yuyao Pass?
At the time, a Shuhuang person
captured numerous young beggars
during the chaos
and tied us up.
I managed to survive
and never thought I'd see you again.
Since you're indebted to me,
why won't you tell me
who's instructing Madam Qu?
You won't be able to beat him.
You should give it up.
Yunniang's safety
trumps everything else.
I won't be able to help her on my own.
I need to go see him.
Yunniang.
Yunniang!
You've suffered.
I vow to avenge you.
Liefeng.
Wake up, Liefeng!
Miss Chuxia.
There.
Liefeng.
Watch over Yunniang's body for me.
Is Your Highness
looking for Ling Chuxia?
You dare appear before me again?
I suppose you have a death wish.
As it stands, Your Highness should focus
on Ling Chuxia's safety instead.
The Prime Minister's Residence
is heavily guarded.
Ling Chuxia ignored my warnings
and snuck into the grounds.
If Your Highness
doesn't make a move now,
you'll likely be collecting a body.
Also, your dim-witted bodyguard
is there, too.
Let's go.
Ling Chuxia, you dare show up!
I'm going to beat you to death!
What are you doing?
Step back.
Or else I'll kill her.
Do as she says.
I'm my mother's only daughter.
If anything happens to me,
my mother will not spare you all!
(Prime Minister's Residence)
Your Highness.
You show up here unannounced
with a group of men.
Is there a problem?
Where is Ling Chuxia?
Chuxia?
Chuxia didn't come back.
(Prime Minister's Residence)
Stand your ground!
I'll have her head today!
Get her!
Chuxia!
Are you alright?
I'm okay.
Kill that woman!
No!
Huiniang, what are you doing?
Who are you, really?
Who am I?
I am none other than your,
Prime Minister Ling Feng's
legal wife, Qu Huiniang.
As well as a pawn sent by Shuhuang.
You are a Shuhuang native?
That's right.
I'm from Shuhuang.
I just didn't expect
it would come to this so soon.
How could that be?
Mother, you're lying.
This can't be true.
My only regret is
not killing Ling Chuxia.
Because of that,
the troublemaker
caused your little brother's death.
Arrest her!
Wait.
I want to ask her something.
I'm the person you're after.
Why did you kill Yunniang?
That stupid maid, Yunniang.
She just had to lure you to your death.
She served her purpose.
You're wicked.
Who is giving you orders?
No one is giving me orders.
I'm the one who wants you dead!
I will wait for you in hell.
Mother.
Mother!
Huiniang.
Huiniang...
Chuxia.
Liang Junye.
Hush.
I'm taking you back.
I should've gone with you.
You wouldn't have gotten hurt, then.
It's my fault.
Chuxia. Chuxia!
Chuxia!
What happened?
Lord Ling.
You promised me
that you'd keep Chuxia safe.
Is this what you meant
by safe and sound?
I agreed to let you stay
at the General's Residence
because I thought
you'd be Chuxia's support.
That you'd keep her safe and happy.
Seems like I was wrong about you.
De, see the guest out.
Liefeng.
Chuxia.
Chuxia, you're awake.
Yue.
Yunniang, she's...
♪Morning glows through the window
as I lazily get ready♪
♪Whose young lad is that,
sitting idly on the porch?♪
♪The spring of plum blossoms intoxicates,
apricot flowers bloom gold in the mist♪
♪Rain falls gently on banana leaves,
fish play beneath the lotus pads♪
♪Gazing at the green mountains,
they blend into the distant horizon♪
♪The wild geese call out,
sharing their heartfelt thoughts♪
♪Looking at the bright moon,
sending thoughts of longing♪
♪Neither burdening nor forgetting♪
♪At sunset, the sound of Zen echoes♪
♪Sweeping away the dust
and frost from the heart♪
♪Holding hands with the one
who knows me best, we face each other♪
♪Gazing at the green mountains,
they blend into the distant horizon♪
♪The wild geese call out,
sharing their heartfelt thoughts♪
♪Looking at the bright moon,
sending thoughts of longing♪
♪Neither burdening nor forgetting♪
♪Watching the smoke gently rise♪
♪We share the long,
leisurely years together♪
♪Free and content♪
♪The greatest joy in life
is the beautiful springtime♪
=The Unbreakable Bond=