=The Unbreakable Bond=
(Adapted from Xiao A'man's novel)
("After the Ugly Concubine Divorced,
She is Wooed By Big Shots of the Capital.")
=Episode 26=
You're here, Chuxia.
Greetings, Your Royal Highness.
What is this?
You and I need not stand on ceremony.
Your Royal Highness is soon to be
Great Yue's emperor.
It's only right to practice decorum.
May I know why
you asked me to come today?
Your behavior
is making it awkward.
Right.
Who would've thought
I'd eventually become the Crown Prince?
Chuxia,
although I designated Luoluo
as the Crown Princess,
it doesn't mean
I've forgotten about you.
If you're willing,
I can ask Luoluo to vacate the seat.
Please don't do that,
Your Royal Highness.
If Luoluo found out,
she'd surely be upset.
She's stayed by your side for so long.
Did you not notice
her feelings for you?
Moreover,
I've given my heart to Lord Ling.
I'm sure you could tell
we're in a relationship.
I just don't want to leave any regrets.
Regrets?
Why would it be a regret?
When I was ugly,
you had no interest in me.
But after I regained my looks,
your impression of me changed.
What I want is not someone
who cares about looks.
No, Chuxia. I was...
Say no more, Your Royal Highness.
Or else you might ruin
any past affection we had.
Now,
you're about to become
Great Yue's powerful emperor.
I wouldn't dare to go against you.
But if you do it by force...
Chuxia!
I'm willing to die
to show my resolution.
Chuxia,
I would never force you in any way.
When Father was alive, when he was about
to appoint me as Crown Prince,
my first request was
for me to wed you once more.
If not because of...
Luoluo asked me this before.
Why am I so attached to you?
Why do I like you so much?
I didn't answer her then.
Now,
what you said...
It finally made me comprehend.
Chuxia.
You may go.
I take my leave.
My lord, your hand.
It's fine.
I just bumped it.
My lord,
why are you feeling bad?
You have me to keep you company.
As well as your child,
staying by your side.
My child?
When did this happen?
I just found out today.
Although the Preceptor is gone,
I promise to take good care of you.
I found this letter
in the secret chamber.
Maybe it got mixed up
among the other letters.
(Dear Lord Ling.)
(Since bidding farewell at Yuyao Pass,)
(I'm pleased to learn
that Your Highness)
(has been keeping a low profile
in Shuhuang.)
(May you be safe and sound
and your wish granted.)
When a Shuhuang native is born,
this mark is tattooed on
using Red Yin grass ink.
How did you know that corpse cicada
came from Shuhuang?
Corpse cicadas are found
only in Shuhuang.
You seem to know a lot about Shuhuang.
Why are you so interested
in the Yuyao Pass incident?
Because it concerns
an old friend of mine.
Liang Junye.
How much of what you said
is true and false?
What are you hiding from me?
You're here, Jiang Li.
You said you have a task for me.
What is it?
I read the letter.
Help me look into
the person mentioned in the letter.
Do you mean Liang...
Lord Ling.
Mr. Baili.
What were you mumbling about
to Jiang Li just now?
You two were this close.
It's nothing.
If you're feeling well enough,
you should go back to your mansion.
Staying so long
at the General's Residence
may stir up unwanted rumors.
Did I do something wrong?
Why are you chasing me away?
Nothing of that sort.
It's just that Your Highness
have stayed a long time.
It's time to leave.
Yue,
I'm a little tired.
I'm going to take a rest.
Give her some space.
Maybe she's in a bad mood.
I think you should let her be.
Liefeng.
What do you think of my letter?
Your Highness' writing is excellent,
sincere and moving.
Too bad she's not reciprocating
my feelings.
What is she up to these days?
My lord.
I bribed Jiang Li
with a lot of darts
and poisoned needles
in exchange for the valuable intel.
Tell me.
If it's indeed valuable,
you will be rewarded.
Recently, First Young Lady Ling
has been reading medical books
in the study
and going for walks with Mr. Baili.
She didn't do anything else.
You call that valuable?
Receive your punishment.
I should at least be credited
for my efforts.
So she's been idle these few days.
Why is she angry with me, then?
I know.
It must be because
I didn't write enough.
Looks to me like Your Highness
is out of ideas.
Shut it.
Deliver the letter.
We're still delivering?
Why?
Do I have to get your permission
before I do anything now?
Will do, my lord.
(To Ling Chuxia)
Something seems to be weighing
on your mind today.
No, there isn't.
I'm sure there is.
Don't forget. When you were little
and something was on your mind,
I could tell right away.
I've made you worry.
You're my only family.
How can I not worry?
Then, haven't you thought about
getting a new family member?
Like Princess Ziyuan?
I guess we're not meant to be.
Do you trust her though?
I do.
But what if one day,
you realize the person you trusted
can no longer be trusted.
What would you do, Yue?
♪Morning glows through the window
as I lazily get ready♪
♪Whose young lad is that,
sitting idly on the porch?♪
♪The spring of plum blossoms intoxicates,
apricot flowers bloom gold in the mist♪
♪Rain falls gently on banana leaves,
fish play beneath the lotus pads♪
♪Gazing at the green mountains,
they blend into the distant horizon♪
♪The wild geese call out,
sharing their heartfelt thoughts♪
♪Looking at the bright moon,
sending thoughts of longing♪
♪Neither burdening nor forgetting♪
♪At sunset, the sound of Zen echoes♪
♪Sweeping away the dust
and frost from the heart♪
♪Holding hands with the one
who knows me best, we face each other♪
♪Gazing at the green mountains,
they blend into the distant horizon♪
♪The wild geese call out,
sharing their heartfelt thoughts♪
♪Looking at the bright moon,
sending thoughts of longing♪
♪Neither burdening nor forgetting♪
♪Watching the smoke gently rise♪
♪We share the long,
leisurely years together♪
♪Free and content♪
♪The greatest joy in life
is the beautiful springtime♪
=The Unbreakable Bond=