=The Unbreakable Bond=
(Adapted from Xiao A'man's novel)
("After the Ugly Concubine Divorced,
She is Wooed By Big Shots of the Capital.")
=Episode 5=
Miss Chuxia is dressed
in camouflage clothing
and headed towards the Royal Cemetery.
Not sure what she's up to.
The clues before also point
to the Royal Cemetery.
I'll go and check it out, too.
Let's see what I'll find there.
I'll go with you
in case something happens.
No need. The Royal Cemetery
is full of danger.
I'll go in on my own.
You'll stay watch outside.
Got it.
(The Supreme Poison can only
be cured with Blue Grass.)
(And Blue Grass only grows
in the most favorable place.)
Who's there?
You, come with me.
Yes, sir.
You again.
Seems like we share quite the affinity.
We're always bumping into each other.
What are you doing here?
For something specific.
Me, too.
(Is he here to grab
the Blue Grass from me?)
(Why does she need the Blue Grass?)
This place is cold and scary.
I have an idea.
Why don't we partner up?
Watch each other's back?
With your skills,
I don't think you need a partner.
I'm a royal member.
I'm visiting the royal tombs
to clear my mind, have a stroll.
But there's no reason
for you to show up here, is there?
Then why haven't you
called for the guards?
That's because I want you
to owe me a favor.
Can't have you saving me every time.
I have my pride.
Since you're here to clear your mind,
I won't disturb you
chatting with your ancestors, then.
What is this place?
Looks like the royal rumors are true.
To get to the center
of the Royal Cemetery,
one has to pass through
the Maze of Illusions.
I wasn't going to enter the cemetery.
I only wanted to grab
the thing I wanted and leave.
Wanting to leave now
isn't going to be that easy.
Stay close.
Chuxia.
Liang Junye.
How much longer
are you going to keep it from me?
Liang Junye.
Liang Junye!
Where are you, Liang Junye?
Ling Chuxia.
Who is it?
Stop with the tricks.
Blue Grass pollen?
It is written in medical books
that the Blue Grass pollen
has hallucinogenic effects.
It causes people to become confused.
Ling Chuxia.
Who are you?
Do you not recognize your own self?
I am you.
Ling Chuxia.
What are you doing?
Liang Junye.
You like me, don't you?
Don't be ridiculous.
Why would I...
You're not Ling Chuxia.
What do you mean I'm not Ling Chuxia?
You've been troubled
by what happened before.
Why didn't you tell me?
You remember our past?
Of course I do.
When we parted at Yuyao Pass back then,
didn't you
think about taking me with you?
It wasn't my intention.
But I couldn't disobey
the emperor's command.
I didn't expect my rash decision
to put you and your family in harm.
Never mind those people.
As long as we're together,
it's all good.
Don't come any closer.
Why won't you face your true self?
If you had learned to please Father,
and not just mastering pen and sword,
then your position
in the Prime Minister's Residence
would've been secured.
Mastering the pen
means having wisdom and etiquette.
And mastering the sword
means I can protect myself.
I have no intention
of becoming a pretty vase
like Ling Qiuqing.
If you fixed your face,
you'd be able to marry Lord Ming.
The sparrow will turn into the phoenix,
whose power is only second
to the emperor.
Who would dare bully you, then?
My marriage
is not some bargaining chip
to gain power.
I am not marrying someone I do not love.
Then,
what about Lord Ling?
Liang Junye?
Isn't he the best candidate for you
right now?
The jade medallion royal heirloom
has the ability
to disperse hallucinations.
Liang Junye!
Chuxia!
What's wrong, Chuxia?
I found the way to escape.
Chuxia.
(She is poisoned.)
You want the Blue Grass
to cure the poison.
Why didn't you say so earlier?
(It was Liang Junye
who brought me back.)
(Did he leave this here, too?)
(I finally got rid
of the Supreme Poison.)
Liang Junye.
This time,
I owe you one.
If Your Highness
really wants to win over
Young Lady Ling,
I do have some ideas.
It could help Your Highness
and make Young Lady Ling
slowly change her mind about you.
Do tell.
What should I do to win her back?
Your Highness could...
♪Morning glows through the window
as I lazily get ready♪
♪Whose young lad is that,
sitting idly on the porch?♪
♪The spring of plum blossoms intoxicates,
apricot flowers bloom gold in the mist♪
♪Rain falls gently on banana leaves,
fish play beneath the lotus pads♪
♪Gazing at the green mountains,
they blend into the distant horizon♪
♪The wild geese call out,
sharing their heartfelt thoughts♪
♪Looking at the bright moon,
sending thoughts of longing♪
♪Neither burdening nor forgetting♪
♪At sunset, the sound of Zen echoes♪
♪Sweeping away the dust
and frost from the heart♪
♪Holding hands with the one
who knows me best, we face each other♪
♪Gazing at the green mountains,
they blend into the distant horizon♪
♪The wild geese call out,
sharing their heartfelt thoughts♪
♪Looking at the bright moon,
sending thoughts of longing♪
♪Neither burdening nor forgetting♪
♪Watching the smoke gently rise♪
♪We share the long,
leisurely years together♪
♪Free and content♪
♪The greatest joy in life
is the beautiful springtime♪
=The Unbreakable Bond=