=The Unbreakable Bond=
(Adapted from Xiao A'man's novel)
("After the Ugly Concubine Divorced,
She is Wooed By Big Shots of the Capital.")
=Episode 16=
The mountains are dyed yellow
by the autumn foliage.
The Qing magistrate accumulates
a mountain of silver.
Liang Junye,
you said it before.
Ring the jade bell
and you'll appear.
I expect you to keep your promise.
Hurry up and wake up.
I was incompetent.
I deserve to be punished.
No one could've predicted the accident.
We'll wait for another chance to strike.
No more mistakes.
Yes, my lord.
(Jiang Li, Shuhuang assassin)
Don't push, don't push.
There's enough.
There's enough for everyone.
Don't push.
Give me a bowl.
This one is soiled. Don't eat it.
It was her.
After all the twists and turns
over the years,
this is how I meet her again.
I suppose I should repay you
for your kindness back then.
You're awake.
Careful.
Have you been at my bedside
the whole night?
Of course not.
I spent the morning sword training.
I just dropped by
on the way back.
Chuxia.
Did you watch over him the whole night?
Keep still.
Your wound is a deep one.
You have to rest for a few more days.
Lie down.
I can't have that.
That would mean
you'll have to accompany me
for a few more days.
That's too much.
What are you doing?
Giving you acupuncture.
Acupuncture?
Do stab wounds require acupuncture?
Yue,
it's going to get a little messy.
You should go outside.
Don't go, Mr. Baili.
Quick, let's go.
Stay, Mr. Baili!
Chuxia,
I was just joking.
Chuxia.
Miss Chuxia.
I haven't gotten the herbs
you had asked for.
Now we have the Blazing Kirin.
We're just missing those herbs.
Oh, no.
Liefeng still hasn't returned
from looking for Yunniang.
That must mean he hasn't found her.
Yunniang.
Please be safe.
Miss Chuxia.
Liefeng.
I searched for Yunniang
the whole night last night.
I didn't see her anywhere.
Could something have happened to her?
Liefeng.
Take this medicine to Lord Ling.
I'll go and look for Yunniang.
Yunniang!
(What happened to Yunniang?)
(Where has she disappeared to?)
I know who you're looking for, miss.
Who are you?
Why are you following me?
Don't misunderstand, miss.
I know where the person
you're looking for is.
You can stop with your trickery.
It's you, you evil rat!
I'm going to hand you to the magistrate!
Do you remember me, miss?
When we were kids...
(Young Jiang Li)
This is soiled. Don't eat it.
I went to look for Yunniang
and came across the assassin
from yesterday.
Are you hurt?
No.
The assassin was acting oddly.
He told it like it is.
He said Yunniang
was taken by Madam Qu's men.
Yes, I tried to kill you yesterday.
But because you look like
an old friend of mine,
I held back.
I don't intend to hide it.
I was sent by Madam Qu
from your family to kill you
as revenge for her dead son.
As for the person you're looking for,
she was probably taken by Madam Qu.
If you don't believe me,
I could go back to Ling Residence
with you to find out.
I don't know if I should believe him.
Seems like
the person who wants you dead
is none other than Madam Qu.
Hence I'm thinking to go back
to Ling Residence.
If Yunniang is indeed
held captive at the mansion,
I have to get her out.
I'll go with you.
You're still injured.
You need to rest.
I can go on my own.
Chuxia.
Why not ask Liefeng
to scout it out first?
What if this is a trap set up
by the assassin
to lure you into it?
That's why he said Yunniang
had been taken by Madam Qu.
Liefeng.
We'll split up, then.
Please go to Ling Residence
and look for clues.
I'll go to the tea house
and check if Yunniang's been there.
I'll wait for you there until 5 o'clock.
If you're not back, I will
immediately head to Ling Residence.
Rest assured, Miss Chuxia.
I will be thorough.
Be careful.
Mother gave orders
to capture the ugly thing's maid.
Now we'll just have to wait
for her to walk into the trap.
Watch her closely.
Yes, miss.
I have to hurry back and report this.
(Shuiyun Teahouse)
(Yunniang.)
Miss, welcome.
Luoluo.
It's you, Chuxia.
You seem restless.
Is there something bothering you?
It's not convenient for me to stand up.
Could you come over for a chat?
Could you come closer?
I came out without my servant today.
I didn't expect
my monthlies to come.
My clothes has been stained.
If other people saw it,
I wouldn't dare face anyone again.
♪Morning glows through the window
as I lazily get ready♪
♪Whose young lad is that,
sitting idly on the porch?♪
♪The spring of plum blossoms intoxicates,
apricot flowers bloom gold in the mist♪
♪Rain falls gently on banana leaves,
fish play beneath the lotus pads♪
♪Gazing at the green mountains,
they blend into the distant horizon♪
♪The wild geese call out,
sharing their heartfelt thoughts♪
♪Looking at the bright moon,
sending thoughts of longing♪
♪Neither burdening nor forgetting♪
♪At sunset, the sound of Zen echoes♪
♪Sweeping away the dust
and frost from the heart♪
♪Holding hands with the one
who knows me best, we face each other♪
♪Gazing at the green mountains,
they blend into the distant horizon♪
♪The wild geese call out,
sharing their heartfelt thoughts♪
♪Looking at the bright moon,
sending thoughts of longing♪
♪Neither burdening nor forgetting♪
♪Watching the smoke gently rise♪
♪We share the long,
leisurely years together♪
♪Free and content♪
♪The greatest joy in life
is the beautiful springtime♪
=The Unbreakable Bond=