She doesn't think physically.
A father who's been through a lot.
Exciting and heartwarming
bluntly andribly to me,
an punches she took every single third I configuration
sat down fighting to protect my siblings
She let me have power
that she sat down fighting for
even without considering my stations
It was simple that we had no future
Was something mad or spicy to her?
Will that make her not just as good as the thumbs you caught?
Something was wrong and hurt her
What are you doing?
If you're going to get drunk, you'll fall asleep.
Are you out of your mind?
What is it?
Don't pretend to be asleep.
Get up.
Bomi, are you okay?
What?
Why are you still?
He's just...
But you're fine?
I'm drunk.
It doesn't matter if you're drunk.
You're a jerk.
Are you really sleeping?
You're showing off, aren't you?
You're still not getting up?
Hey!
Bomi!
Why are you so late?
I've been waiting for you.
I slept.
Bomi.
What is it?
7,300 won!
3,000 won!
What is this?
You were so mean yesterday.
Don't you know manners make people?
Manners make men.
I'm going to tape my mouth and sleep from today.
Are you kidding me?
I'm going to puke because of your alcohol.
Why are you so angry since this morning?
Bring him down for dinner.
He said he won't have dinner until after 7.
Hi, Sangyeop.
Good morning.
What is this?
I want to eat seaweed soup.
Who drank?
Kim Bomi, is it you?
It's not me.
She drank so much.
I don't know how to find her.
Sangyeop, did you drink yesterday?
Who? I'm a drunkard.
I drank a lot. I was drunk.
What did you say?
I think someone's talking about it.
Me?
No way.
I drank enough and came in and slept.
Good job.
Ma'am.
Yes?
I don't usually make this soup.
I'm going to add 2 tablespoons of alulose to organic tomatoes
and grind them.
Okay.
You're rich. I'll do anything for you.
For your information,
bean sprout soup is 10,000 won extra.
She's so mean.
10,000 won for meat without meat?
20,000 won extra for meat.
15,000 won extra for tofu.
I didn't do this.
It's expensive these days.
Kim Bomi, you made it, so take responsibility.
Bomi made it?
Oh, my.
You're the best for breakfast.
No wonder it tastes so good.
Kim Bomi.
It's chilly.
You remember everything, right?
Us?
Bomi.
Stop thinking about it, Kim Bomi.
Is this how you're going to be?
Why are you following me around?
Stop it.
You're like you've had a drink.
Don't be rude to Bomi.
She's one of the many girls you can easily meet,
but to me...
No.
You're the only one who can stand it.
I've never been easy on you.
You said it.
You liked Bomi first.
But you can't have everything you like.
Love doesn't have a order.
You two, relax.
You'll get in trouble if you do well.
I have something important to see you about.
Bye.
I hope you get along with my first band.
The beginning is the school band,
but the end is the band.
What about my brother?
I don't know. I'm not interested.
He left earlier.
Did something happen?
Did he say nothing?
Why are you all worrying about him?
Let's go.
Isn't this too much?
How can a person
not have as much eye-flash as a mole?
I would've been heartbroken
if I thought of my brother.
I would've lived without opening the car door
with my own hands.
I wouldn't have a manager,
no stylist,
no car.
I would've been in a daze.
I can't do this even if my house is ruined.
What are you doing?
How was it?
Was it okay?
I'm trying to act free today,
but I can't get the right emotion.
What if I don't cry later?
I'm a professional method actor.
I should try.
I don't think I need to explain
why I came to see you.
What's the reason?
Why are you wandering around me?
That's it.
In case you get caught by the anti-fans.
So you're following me?
Why do I feel like I'm more concerned about Bomi?
I'm worried about you.
Why are you taking pictures?
You told me to report to the Kim Boms
and the Street Women's League.
Why are you so interested in Bomi?
Leave the house right now.
Eat, hit, and quit school.
Don't hang out with Kim Bomi.
Don't do anything.
Even if you don't know what you're doing,
if you're going to fight with Mr. Cho,
even Kim Bomi will be in danger.
Because of you.
I'm telling you this because I care about you.
Is Bomi in danger because of me?
Why?
What's the reason?
There's something I need to make sure of.
If you touch a single finger of Kim Bomi,
I won't stay still.
What?
Let's look at the structure of the major and minor chords.
There are three common keys in the two chords.
Is there anyone who wants to talk about the common keys?
You don't look like you've seen it before.
What is this?
What do I do?
Hello, Professor.
I'm Lee Hwakbeom, a senior in the department of entertainment.
I came to the lecture because I really wanted to hear
your lecture.
You did?
Yes.
My best friend recommended this class.
This is Kim Bomi sitting here.
Hey!
When did I...
You said we should do good things together.
I'm sorry.
As one of the many artists who lead K-pop,
I'm here to participate in this class
because I understand and need to have a deeper understanding
of practical music.
The movement starts with the chord.
The movement is composed of two notes.
The two notes are the vibration of the two notes.
The vibration is the physical number of the vibration
toward the note.
For one second, the interaction of the two notes
is left one after another.
Don't listen to me if you're going to do this.
I'm so embarrassed.
I didn't sleep.
You must have fallen for me.
Forget it.
You didn't come all the way here, did you?
Where are you going?
Oh, I'm going.
I'll wait for you.
You...
You really can't come?
You have nothing to do?
Look.
Everyone's looking for me.
I'm pretty busy too.
Yes, sir. I'll buy it.
Now?
It's a bit difficult now.
Where did he go?
How could he just go around
all the time?
That's soggiating.
I'm sorry.
Junsun!
It's been six years.
Bomi's angry smile.
The number you have dialed is...
You're going home without a word?
You're so out of it.
What are you carrying around?
You're so annoying.
Come in.
Hey.
What brings you here?
Weren't you in the States?
I was in the States for a while.
You must be busy.
No, I'm fine. I'll be away for an hour.
Sit down.
I thought you were an antiviral.
Have you ever been awake?
I came because I had something to tell you.
Okay. Tell me.
What would you like to drink?
What is it?
Tell me.
A car accident six years ago.
You remember, right?
Help me.
I think I'm going to die.
This is a big deal.
We both drank.
Why are you talking about that all of a sudden?
A witness appeared.
A witness?
Guys!
The festival...
The first performance of the second and third season is finally here.
We're in the official lineup of the festival.
We're going to perform with the same band.
I picked the band.
It's the first performance.
You know, right?
The opening is the highlight of the show!
Hey!
I'll be in charge of the planning.
You don't have any complaints, right?
No, we don't.
Then I'll be the sound operator.
I'm perfect at manipulating equipment.
I'll show you the sound of my sensitive hearing
that's like Beethoven's.
Beethoven's hearing is slow.
Hey!
Please point out more often!
I don't point out your fashion terror either.
What about my fashion?
Gosh.
How is it?
I'm amazing, right?
I'm a lucky swindler.
This is what a leader should do.
Hey!
What are you really bad at?
Well, finding what I'm bad at?
I can't do that.
Loopy, check!
Yes!
We should decide on the song first.
What should we do with the song?
What about the concept?
Of course, hip-hop rock.
From the opening, we'll show you
the real hip-hop rock!
Who says it's hip-hop rock?
This is a university festival, not a concert.
That's why we're going with hip-hop rock.
It could be a discrimination against a Korean band.
It's also a genre I want to challenge.
If you're going to do what you want,
why are we here?
It's the leader's right to decide on the song.
Why are you the leader?
Did anyone agree to this?
Do we really have to agree on that?
I made the band, Twosugat.
I'm sorry.
Did you hear me?
I was the head of the band in Hanzu.
I've never been a leader.
I'll be the leader of this band.
I can't give up on my position.
My guitar skills are world-class.
You don't remember
how I broke your skills?
I just stopped because the guitar string broke.
I was happy with the song.
I never broke my skills.
Can't you figure out that much?
You're so stingy.
Get her.
Are you coming this way?
Hey!
Stop it!
Que! Open up!
How dare you!
Stop it!
What kind of performance is this?
Let's discuss the position.
Hey!
Hey, hey!
I didn't see it.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey!
What are you doing?
Why do you have to forget about that?
You don't have to be in hell on your own.
Are you sure?
Are you sure the four saw it?
How can you remember the scene of the accident without doing that?
And you're living with the daughter of the deceased.
The daughter of the deceased?
Did she have a daughter?
You didn't say she had a family.
I didn't say it because I didn't want to bother you.
There was nothing to die for.
You're so mean.
Why do you know so much about me?
What's really strange is that
Taeyang came into the house of the deceased.
What do you mean?
Where is he going?
Secretary Kang confirmed that
he lives in the same house as the four of them.
Kim Bong?
So the woman who died that day
is Kim Bong's mother?
Do you know Kim Bong?
Yes.
I've known him for a long time.
Since middle school.
You're making things weird.
It can't be a coincidence that the three of them live in the same house.
I can't explain why you're doing this.
But it's already closed.
The car slipped and died on the rain.
If there's a witness, we can change the story.
Do you want me to tell you?
Maybe Kim Bong already knows.
That's the place where his mother died.
If he knew, he wouldn't have stayed still.
I'll meet Kim Bong.
Why are you taking off your clothes?
You're not even feeling well.
You don't even think about the people who see you.
What are you saying?
Is it because you're jealous?
Then you should get some rest.
Why are you turning off the lights? Can't you see I'm studying?
Turn them on now.
The person who needs them does.
You did it on purpose, didn't you?
Me? I don't know because I can't see.
Darn it. Why are you stepping on it?
Shut up! Please leave!
I can't live in this house.
No.
I can't let this go down like this.
Shouldn't I at least attend a rock festival?
Gosh.
Notification.
A new band from the band club is going to be empty.
At 1 a.m. at 9 a.m.,
we'll start the school business.
You'll get a fine of 1,000 dollars.
Empty?
Why are you suddenly empty?
The atmosphere is so bad.
It's a big party.
That's why I'm going.
I want to bury someone.
Hey, here!
Wow! What is this?
Are we riding this?
This is the celebrity van that we heard about.
It's so cool!
Good morning.
You're not late, right?
No.
Mr. Jo Jinho.
Kim Beom, how have you been?
I heard you're friends with the band.
Yes.
How have you been?
Thank you for lending me your car.
Thank you.
I haven't been to a music school in a while.
But I don't want to tell Mr. Jo about today.
Don't worry.
I can manage without my dad.
Mr. Jo, can you come with us today?
We need to get rid of two people here.
Okay.
We don't have enough time to clean up.
I don't have time.
Rich, let's go together.
I'm really into this.
I'll do my best to make you happy.
Isn't that great?
Yes, Rich.
We can pay you back.
Just pay me back.
Let's go.
Hey, that's not right.
You're going to get hurt.
Why aren't you getting better?
What?
What are you doing? You did that on purpose.
Sorry.
Oh, my.
I'm sorry. I did something wrong.
This is what happens.
When you get your favorite music,
you get so excited that you drive so tough.
You forget what you're doing.
It's okay, Rich. You can do it.
I'm fine.
Sangi, what's wrong with your car? Is it broken?
Are you crawling or standing?
Is it a stroller?
The top is all dead.
Why are you doing this to Sangi?
Hey, park it in the rest area.
You go to the bathroom.
Okay.
Go to the bathroom.
I'm going to eat fish cake.
What fish cake?
Hey, stop.
I told you to stop by the rest area.
I forgot.
If we go to the rest area,
we'll be about 100km away.
Just a little more.
Hey, wait.
Wait.
Sangtae, you can do it.
You can do it.
Hey, Bomi.
Let go of this.
I'll do it.
Hey, Seo Taeyong.
Do your best.
Oh, this.
I'm a professional.
And this.
I'll help you.
I'm a professional.
And this.
Roll it up.
Okay, and turn it on.
Hey, Bomi.
Let's go together.
Taeyong, can you do this?
What?
This.
Oh, my.
One, two, three.
Hey, Seo Taeyong.
Sit down there.
Why are you being so rude to someone who's not doing anything?
Who's being rude?
You can't be more rude.
From now on, call me brother.
That's right.
I can't call someone who doesn't have a learning ability
brother even if I die.
But if you want to hear it,
give up the lead guitar.
It's my pride.
If I take it, there's no reason to be in a band.
Then we're done talking.
I'll let you know as a leader.
Please leave our team right now.
You're annoying me all of a sudden.
You're the one who's annoying.
Why are you following Bomi around like that?
Admit it or not.
I'm the identity of the two companies.
Please stop it.
Seo...
Darn it.
Hey, hey.
Let go of me.
I said let go of me.
Hey.
Bomi.
Darn it.
Let go of me.
Move.
This is a crime.
Sanghae.
Bomi.
No!
Stop!
Darn it.
Bomi, drink this.
Shouldn't we go to the hospital?
I don't think we should go to the hospital.
It'll be okay soon, right?
Hold on a second.
I'm here to buy medicine.
I'll be right back.
Sorry, Bomi.
I won't fight anymore.
I'll do as you say.
Position and angle...
You decide.
Don't be sick.
I'll follow your orders.
You're lying.
I don't believe you.
Hey, no!
Hey, really!
Hey, look.
Guys get along like this.
We're now best friends.
From today,
we're best friends.
Are you serious?
What if we fight again?
No.
I swear to God.
Then...
I'll decide for real.
You guys have no complaints?
The lead guitar...
is ruined.
Oh...
Really?
Is that okay?
I don't have to do anything.
But Taehyung can decide the song.
Whatever you want.
I'll do that.
Then what about the band leader?
Don't say that if you're tired.
I don't care.
I don't have to be the leader.
The leader...
is me.
You?
Yes.
I'll be the leader.
I can't trust you guys.
I'll have to drag the lead guitar.
I'm planning it anyway.
Mom!
Mom, are you okay?
I bought you medicine.
How's your cough?
It's getting worse.
I don't know if I should take the medicine.
Really?
How did you fall into the water?
What's wrong with a girl like you who's good at swimming?
That's the thing.
Bomi...
swims?
Yes, she's really good at swimming.
She went to the boys' competition when she was a kid.
You didn't even get a license to save people in the States.
Stop it.
A license to save people?
Kim Bomi, so you...
You lied?
You pretended to be in the water on purpose, right?
Then you caught a cold?
You caught a cold?
Yes, I lied.
Why would anyone come all the way here and lie?
I thought I was going to die if I made her apologize.
Hey, Kim Bomi!
Hey, hey!
Hey, stop!
Kim Bomi
The number you have dialed is busy...
If you know Kim Bomi...
If the police investigation begins...
Game start! Game start!
I.M. Ground, start now!
What? What?
What are you doing?
Why is he so funny?
He's not funny at all.
Hey, hey, hey!
It's a brand new song.
Why didn't they sell this?
Hey, get the money.
Oh, really?
Then give me 10 seconds.
Hey, this is a foul.
I'm not going to let you get away with this.
I'm not going anywhere.
Kim Bomi
Did you have fun?
Here it is.
I'm so nervous.
There's nothing to be nervous about.
I'm not committing a crime.
I'm just curious.
I'm just curious about how much money there is.
If there's a lot, I'll do better than now.
Who is it?
You're so annoying.
Who's playing around?
I'm going to kill you!
You little punk.
Oh, my God.
I'm...
Who are you?
I'm Seo Tae-yang's father.
I left my child behind and I'm late for a greeting.
Oh, yes, Tae-yang's father.
Tae-yang's father.
Teacher!
Oh, my mother, teacher!
Oh, you know, you know, you know, you know.
Oh my god.
You're on TV a lot.
I saw it all before you came out.
Oh my God.
Is Tae-yang not home right now?
Oh, yeah, he's not home right now.
Tae-yang went to the band's MT yesterday.
He said he'd sleep for a day and go to school today.
Oh, my.
Oh, I didn't tell you.
That's what kids these days are like.
They don't know how parents feel, right?
Can I see Tae-yang's room?
What?
I have to take my child's luggage.
Oh, my. Why do you need luggage?
I didn't hear you say you were moving out.
I just need to take the books.
Can I go in for a second?
Oh, yes, of course.
The house is small and pretty.
It is pretty.
When Bomi was alive,
this house was the best in this neighborhood.
There are so many flowers in the garden.
Oh, here. Have some coffee.
How did Bomi's mother die?
A car accident.
The car slipped on the way.
It was such a strange day.
It was the first day of my life like that.
It was an accident.
What a shame.
Don't you remember?
Why six years ago?
The news was all about the weather change.
I don't know.
I don't remember.
I know.
Everyone forgets about it.
We should forget about it too.
So you live with your aunt.
Yes.
When Tae-yang went to the U.S. for his study,
he met Bomi for the first time, right?
Yes, he said so.
Bomi studied music and went to study abroad early.
As soon as his mother died,
he left everything behind and came back,
but if he hadn't, he would've been in a lot of trouble.
Gwangsan Kimchi is smart.
Yes.
I'd like to meet Bomi.
Can I get her number?
5 billion dollars?
Are you serious, Mr. Cho?
You're donating so much money.
I'm so touched that I'm crying.
We can build another science museum
in the water pipe business.
That's right.
I'll name the building
after Mr. Cho and make it a memorial building.
I have a favor to ask.
Tell me anything.
I have to do something to make it happen.
I'd like to give a scholarship
to Kim Bomi, a freshman at the Department of Engineering.
A scholarship?
What kind of a request is that?
Please let Kim Bomi leave here as soon as possible.
The sooner, the better.
Okay.
Hello, Mr. Cho.
It's been a while. How have you been?
Have a seat.
I saw you at school once in a while.
I'm sorry I'm late.
It's okay.
Please feel free to talk to me.
Why would I talk to someone I don't know?
I don't hang out with anyone.
Okay.
Taeyang was at the house, right?
You heard from your aunt, but I went to get my things.
I really didn't know Taeyang came out without permission.
If I had known, I wouldn't have accepted it.
I'm sorry.
You're sorry to the end?
Now that you know, you can act like you're right.
Why did you ask to meet me?
My daughter is doing something she didn't do
when she was a teenager.
I didn't mind her being a band member
when she was in the department of gastronomy,
but she's a major now and she's studying.
I asked her to stop her club activities
and she left the house.
She's been skipping classes these days.
Did you know?
No, I didn't.
So I'm telling you,
send her back to her house somehow.
And don't get close to her.
What?
Don't even contact her.
You can't let her come into your house.
She needs to study.
She's a top student in a difficult school
and she's better than anyone else.
I hope you don't try to
make her feel bad.
Do you understand?
From now on, I want to work with my daughter
to save lives in the same hospital.
Please don't let my dream go to waste.
Enjoy your meal.
I'll go and make up for it.
I'll set the table.
What's wrong with him?
He's not eating.
I feel empty without him.
I'm not used to him around.
They're not dating, are they?
They're dating a lot.
No, the con man is following them.
The con man?
Yes.
The culprit?
He's following them.
I was going to talk to you,
but can you come out for a minute?
I'll wait at the bus stop.
I forgot about my promise.
I'll be right there.
Where are you going?
Are you going to the beach?
Are they trying to get us together?
Don't be so selfish!
Did you wait for me?
Why are you asking me to meet here?
Let's go to a cafe.
No, do you want to eat first?
No, your father bought it for me.
It's an expensive tenderloin steak.
Did you meet my father?
What's wrong with you?
You're still in puberty.
Why are you acting like a rebel?
Don't make other people tired.
Go home, young man.
If I were to go home,
I wouldn't have come out.
I'm sorry.
He already took your stuff.
What?
How could he do that?
Listen to him.
Go home and fight, whether you're in a band or not.
Get your permission before you come out.
You're missing classes these days.
Why would he hit you when you're so bad at it?
Because I don't get along with him.
Then what's wrong with you?
How can you live with the right thing?
You died,
and your business went bankrupt.
Do you know what I thought then?
You selfish brat.
You lived with the things you wanted to do.
You gave up everything because of me.
That's why you swore.
You'll do everything I want
to do whatever I want.
That's why you're working part-time.
You want me to do whatever I want.
Do you think I'm living with
everything I want?
Yes.
You don't have to worry too much.
You're acting like a kid who's worrying.
Kim Bum...
I don't want you to come back to your father again.
Because
I was so jealous.
Because I had a dad who nagged me.
Bye.
What?
How heartless, Kim Bum.
Bye.
You should've come earlier.
Where's the food?
I ate. What time is it?
With who? When and where?
Stop it.
Are you trying to make me lose my mind?
Can't you listen to me?
There's nothing wrong with being careful.
The world is so cruel.
I've lived in this neighborhood for 20 years.
I'm a woman who got a black belt in Taekwondo.
Okay.
You should be careful.
What about Seokhyeong?
What happened?
She was all gone.
Did she get dragged into the house like you said?
She's not independent.
Does she look like a pop-up?
You must be happy to be alone in your room.
You must be happy to be out of the house.
You should've been nice to me.
How do you feel about coming back?
Promise me you won't miss the class.
You should keep your promise.
That you won't go to Bomi again.
As long as you don't break your promise, I won't go to her.
I'll make sure the band is organized.
Don't ever get involved with her again.
Why?
Why do you hate Bomi so much?
It's not fair.
I don't want my parents to die.
That's not her fault.
If you think about it,
I'm the most mean person.
If you don't want to meet her, don't meet her.
Even if the sky breaks, she'll never be with you.
When I meet her again,
I don't know what I'll do.
You didn't forget to attend my surgery today, right?
It's at 2 p.m.
It's a major surgery that extracts liver, heart, and kidney
from a patient with a brain death.
It's a difficult surgery to see.
I think of you as a doctor's father.
Come with a thankful heart.
It's a perfect condition.
It's a study that only one person in our school
can get.
Bomi has good grades
and the professors' evaluation is good,
so I gave her a chance.
I don't have good grades.
It's at 2 p.m.
2 p.m.?
What grades?
You get good grades from all over the country.
Don't feel pressured or worried.
Go to a study that has a good budget
and a good technical department.
You can't even support your parents
who are in need of you.
That's true, but it's too random.
It's hard for parents to come to you
because they lost their children early.
But you're worried that they'll
compensate you here.
Come on. Sign here.
Sign here, Bomi.
I won't.
Why not?
Thank you for the suggestion,
but I don't feel sorry for you.
I'm not even allowed to apply for the training.
I have a lot of things to do here.
I have to perform here.
I bet two people are here to see me.
Bye.
I'm off.
Kim Bomi!
Hey, Kim Bomi!
128, please.
I'll take a look again.
I'll begin the surgery.
Yes, sir.
Mom!
Mom! I'm home!
Jota, get a grip.
Dad.
You're a jerk.
You ran over your mom and got beaten up.
How could you do that?
Don't tell Mom.
Who did this to Mom?
People who are weak always make excuses.
Did I raise you like that?
It's shameful that you're my son.
I'm sorry.
Did I raise you like that?
It's shameful that you're my son.
You weren't a proud father to me.
If you want to hit me more, hit me.
I'll beat you to death.
And don't ever talk about her again.
Again? Again?
You...
I don't know how much I have to let you go.
I know.
How can you give up on me?
If you can't dream again as a doctor,
will you give up on me?
What?
What are you doing?
If you have to be a doctor,
I'd rather be a button.
Seonjae! Are you crazy?
Are you a fool?
Why did you hurt your innocent son?
Where are all the people who fought with me?
You didn't know the basics of fighting?
Did you pretend to be good?
Are you going to hit me with your teeth or your feet?
Let go of me.
You should fight properly.
Don't bother.
I don't think you should get involved.
Is that so, sir?
I thought you liked getting involved
because you're so broad-minded and you like Bomi.
Let me do what I want because of Bomi.
Enjoy your food.
I'll pay for it.
I'll set the table.
Sir, you have to go in.
You can't even take care of yourself.
If your father was a scapegoat for Bomi,
you don't have to do that.
I can't touch your father or Bomi.
I'm a stalker for Kim Bom these days.
I'm a total stalker.
You should go.
I'm going even if you tell me not to.
If you don't live the way you want,
you'll only be in trouble.
Think about it, Seo Taeyang.
Why is he doing this?
Did he forget about the practice?
I know.
He's the one who made the song the hardest.
How many hours has it been?
Wait a little longer.
You never kept your promise.
Do it.
He's waiting for his dear fraud brother.
You don't have to go home like me.
You didn't go home yesterday either?
How do you always stay in the club room?
Don't you have a house?
No.
Do I look like I have a house?
No, not at all.
Are you crazy?
Did you sell your pride to a thug?
If you're two hours late,
you should apologize first.
Stop it.
Did you finish your class late?
You should've answered the phone.
It's okay if you're here.
Just open your eyes.
Okay.
I'm going to start now.
One, two, three, four.
How did he know?
What?
Why is it not in balance?
It's not making any sound.
Do I have to turn up the volume again?
No.
How can I go on stage
without any foundation?
Is this why I can beat the Hanzo Band?
Let's do it again.
One, two, three, four.
Who keeps making mistakes?
This isn't a beat, it's a synch.
Come in half a beat in advance.
I went in right.
I went in right too.
They're not always like this.
Do it again.
Do you want to keep talking about it?
The part where the syncopation comes in.
If one person doesn't get the timing right,
the sound gets messy.
Look into each other's eyes and make a harmony.
Bandana, harmony.
Harmony.
One, two, three, four.
Come on.
Come here.
How is it?
Good.
Come here.
Hey, you're stuck in the head.
Stand there.
Hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
Here again?
Let's try to get the timing right again.
Here we go.
One, two, three, four.
Who is it?
I'm so hungry.
Ro-a.
We're going to perform at the wedding.
We should come see you.
Right?
You're the one.
Yes, Dawon.
Hye-yeon.
Juyeon.
Are you up?
What time is it?
Three in the morning.
Three in the morning?
Then you should've woken me up.
You're so sleepy.
How can I wake you up?
We have to go.
If we stay out all night,
we'll die right away.
Take your time.
The building is locked.
We can't leave now.
What?
What do we do then?
We have to sleep here?
I know.
We can't leave.
We have to sleep here?
You should've woken me up!
Why do you have to make it up to me?
You couldn't sleep and you couldn't go home.
Who are you to tell me this?
Aren't you sorry?
You...
You didn't apologize to me.
What do I have to apologize for?
About that...
You know.
About what?
Are you really going to stop being a drunk?
You hugged me while pretending to be drunk
after drinking, remember?
But why did you leave without saying anything?
Why should I apologize?
I didn't do it because I was drunk.
I just did it because I liked you.
Didn't you also like me and stayed still?
When did I like you?
I just...
I just thought of you.
Oh, no!
I think I turned off the lights. I'm scared.
See?
You like hugging me.
It's dark now.
I'm scared.
Are you feeling better now?
The moonlight is so bright.
But why do you live so hard?
I thought I was the hardest worker.
I have to live twice as hard as my mom.
I have to live.
And another reason is...
You.
Me?
I want to raise you as my number one artist.
You didn't know, right?
That's why this performance is so important to me.
Honey.
Do you want to...
Do it again?
You should show them too.
No matter how weak you are, you're still number four.
You want to raise me?
You?
Do you have a contract?
Why?
Is the contract expensive?
Yes. Of course it is.
You said you're number four.
You're being so mean.
You have a lot of money. Just make it cheaper.
You can give me more when I make money later.
I'll give you wings.
You have to pay for the contract
so that artists can fly or fly rockets.
First, if you sign the contract,
I'll give it to you.
Really?
Then I'll sign it.
Now?
You know you can't waver when you sign a contract, right?
Bong.
I'm in your dream. I love it.
I love you like my pain.
You wrapped me up warmly
and left me alone.
You look at me and tell me.
What should I do?
Hey, four.
Should we really go on a date?
We met because it was our destiny.
I've never been this happy.
I think I'm dreaming of Yeji.
Are you all ready to rip the stage?
The weird guys came together
and pretended to be four's fans?
Is this your father's doing?
What are you doing?
Where's Bomi?
Where is she?