[Love Endures]
[Episode 21]
Who got you breakfast?
My neighbour gave it to me.
Your neighbour?
Looks like your neighbour
can't really cook.
It doesn't look good
but it actually tastes good.
All right.
(Change your profile picture.)
(Done.)
Why are you hitting me?
Can you try to be more serious?
I was walking.
What should I be serious about?
This is not about walking.
Then what is it about?
What do you think?
I got it.
It must be because
the weather forecast says
there will be rain later.
That's why you...
No...
Wait for me!
Why are you mad at me again?
This is the love announcement I made.
The first one has been completed.
The second one...
When the atmosphere was so good earlier,
you interrupted.
This is why, for the third one,
I'm going to make it harder for you.
It's just wear matching outfits.
It's not a big deal.
Let's go.
Now you know how to hold my hand.
Still want to play video games?
Nope.
Jiang Yi.
Are you done?
Wait a minute.
Not yet.
I've done putting on the shirt.
What takes a grown-up man like you
so long?
It's just...
We have known each other for so long.
Can you let me off the hook?
No way.
Let me see.
You look good in pink!
This is embarrassing!
It's not cute at all!
Stop it.
No.
You promised me.
You said you want to wear
matching couple outfits with me.
Forget it.
Let me go.
No!
This is what I wanted to feel!
That's the way to wear it!
It is!
Miss!
Checkout!
Can you urry up a little bit?
The list says we need to do
a puzzle together.
Why don't we go do one?
I'm good at it.
You wish.
You won't get away with any of them.
If you keep playing like this,
you won't get anything
until Chinese New Year.
Show me how you do it, then.
If I manage to get
the biggest one,
can I change my outfit?
Watch me.
For you.
I'll go get changed.
Please come in.
You're still here?
You haven't eaten anything, right?
I noticed how busy you've been.
I bet you haven't eaten anything.
I bought your favourite oden
and stir-fried rice cake.
Do you cook by yourself now
or you eat at the school cafeteria?
I used to eat at the cafeteria.
Since I'm staying at Jiang's house now,
I am becoming an expert
when it comes to instant noodles.
Instant noodles?
Since you're staying
at Jiang Yi's house,
you must be sick of their pink bubbles.
Since when you knew that?
Of course.
When Yingzi went to her dates,
guess who picked her clothes
and lipstick shades.
Based on Jiang's character,
they've been fancying each other
all these years,
who instigated him to confess?
I think all these years,
we seem like living in circles.
Everything is the same
as when we were young.
I have changed.
I know myself.
I don't think you've changed.
Tell me your opinion.
Always striving to be the best,
competing in everything,
even if the opponent is your fiance.
You're right.
Regardless of who it is,
I'm not willing to lose.
As long as you are willing to strive,
you can definitely make it.
I believe you will definitely succeed
in this performance review.
Thanks for your blessings.
I give you my blessings.
Help me find that piece.
This?
Are you sleepy?
No, I'm not.
I'm not sleepy.
You finally became my boyfriend,
I want to do more things with you.
What do you mean?
Do you want to break up in morning?
Touch wood!
What nonsense are you talking about?
Truth be told,
which couple would do a puzzle at home
on the first day of dating?
Show me his eyes again.
Here.
By the way,
please don't forget.
Return the test papers
with your parents' signatures tomorrow.
Anyone who dares sign them
by themselves,
I will invite their parents
to school
and sign for 100 times each person.
Am I clear?
Yes, sir!
Great.
Oh, right.
Our school
will be having its anniversary.
We need to change the bulletin board
at the back.
Huang Yingzi,
you are in charge of this.
Sir,
what did you say?
All of a sudden you're deaf!
When you listened to CDs in class
while shaking your head,
you didn't seem deaf to me.
Sir.
I...
What?
Decision made.
School's over!
Mingyu.
Mingyu!
A sea of people...
Zhuang Yuan!
My mom's waiting for me
to deliver goods.
Bye!
What are we going
to draw for the poster?
Hold on!
It's only me,
not us.
Well, I can help out too.
Until now, have you ever passed
your art classes?
Everyone has their shortcomings.
Even Huang Feihong can't draw!
In primary school,
you drew a spaceship.
Remember the teacher's comment?
It looked like a winter melon.
My first pair of basketball shoes,
you drew a whale on them.
What did everyone else think it was?
A tortoise.
So,
this time,
we will draw "One Piece".
It's school anniversary,
yet you are drawing "One Piece"?
Not bad, Jiang Yi.
If Huang Feihong were here today,
I'd still bow to you.
You're amazing!
I'm blown away!
Even if Huang Feihong were here,
you still owe me a month worth
of Magnum ice cream.
Wall's ice cream will do, right?
Alright! Magnum it is!
Why are you so impatient?
Don't you think those guys
look like us?
Us?
If you had to choose
one among them,
who would you want to be the most?
Of course it's Luffy.
He's the most brilliant of all.
Luffy?
Pretty good.
What about you?
Who would you choose?
Me?
Chopper, I guess.
Good choice.
Among these six,
you chose the only one
who's not a human.
Chopper is cute.
It looks just like like me.
However, to be honest,
why did you pick Chopper?
Chopper was actually pretty pathetic
when he was a kid.
His parents didn't care about him,
nobody wanted to be his friends,
until he met Luffy.
Luffy was the one who got him
into the Straw Hat Pirates.
Since then,
he knew
how it feels to have friends.
Who would have thought
that Chopper and Luffy
ended up being together.
It's getting late,
is Zhuang Yuan still waiting for you?
Wait a minute.
On your list,
isn't there one last task?
There isn't.
The last task is
to put a puzzle together.
It can't be.
Look, I clearly remember...
There's still...
Enough.
Stop looking.
That's what it says right here.
Kissing is the last task...
What's wrong?
Are you scared?
Scared?
Impossible!
Come on!
Unexpectedly,
who would thought
our Hangtian City's Yi
to be so handsome?
Small and slender eyes,
high nose bridge,
and fair skin.
What's wrong?
Why are you blushing?
I'm not!
How could I possibly blush?
I'm a really good kisser.
You don't even know that.
A good kisser?
You're definitely someone who came back
from overseas!
Alright.
Come, show me
what you've got.
Sure.
Let's begin!
I'm moving.
Okay.
No way!
It feels
like
something
is off.
Is it because
we know each other too well?
You're right.
I am sure it is because
we have been buddies for too many years.
From friends to lovers all of a sudden.
We are still getting used to it.
Yes...
You're right.
If we don't see each other clearly,
would it get any better?
I think so.
Maybe this will work.
Come on.
Stop!
I feel like I'm kissing Wong Kar-wai!
It's really funny!
Forget it.
Whatever.
Forget it!
Just go with the flow.
I'm sleepy.
Sleep with me for a while.
Anything for you.
You're not allowed to leave.
I'm not leaving.
Jiang.
How's the preparation going?
Not so bad.
Do your best.
You too.
Wish us luck.
(Dear leaders and my fellow colleagues,)
good day, everyone.
I'm Guo Kai, the purchasing manager.
Thanks to your trust in me,
I'm able to stand here and campaign.
The company has accompanied me
from a newly graduated intern
to my current position
and witnessed my growth.
I want to build an ambitious
and self-driven team.
This is also a requirement
I have for myself.
Four years ago,
I switched from the business department
to the human resources department.
This change in roles
has allowed me to have
a more comprehensive
and in-depth understanding
of the company.
I got insight into the core decisions
to shape the future of the company
and our talents.
As long as it involves
the company's assets and benefits,
regardless of the size,
it will be my responsibility.
Talent is the core asset of a company.
Only employees with sufficient trust
and a sense of belonging
can unleash tremendous value
and energy for our company.
I am also confident and capable of
becoming a qualified
executive vice president
to continue fighting for the company.
I have one more question for you two.
Promotion will inevitably
involve team changes.
What plans do you have
for your new team members?
Of course I will prioritize
our company's interests
and build a new team.
I might have some different ideas.
I feel that it is easier
to adapt to the position
than to adapt to people.
If I have the power,
I prefer my previous team.
It seems Ms. Fang is a nostalgic woman.
That's all for today.
The final result
will be announced after discussion.
The meeting is dismissed.
Let's go eat together.
I have a date today.
A date?
Come clean,
have you gotten into a relationship?
It's a secret.
I'm off!
I brought you
some seaweed-wrapped rice rolls
and octopus takoyaki.
Do you want anything else?
So much ketchup.
What about you?
You can't eat this.
The problem is when I bought this,
I said it's for my girlfriend.
So he squeezed more.
Then I'll have to eat a little more.
I'll have a taste.
It's quite delicious.
What are you laughing at?
Silly girl.
You have my lipstick stains
all over your face.
Really?
You look so dumb.
I got it.
Ming Yu, are you busy?
What's the matter?
Nothing.
I just miss you.
I'm here to see you.
No, I'm just curious
about the grading matter.
Did Mr. Feng tell you something?
No.
Aren't the results coming out soon?
You are the person he recommended.
If there is any news,
I wonder if you'll be the first to know.
Don't worry, just wait for the results.
These small rumors
are meaningless.
What do you want for dinner?
It's finally the end of
performance review.
We finally have time for a good meal.
I'll think about it later.
Well, I'll leave you to it.
I'm off.
Will you join me later?
What do you want to eat?
Yesterday's mail.
Did you get it?
I got it.
The entire company got it.
It's impossible
to keep this matter a secret.
Is that so?
Why did she help with this matter?
I know, right?
Here she comes.
Ms. Fang,
Mr. Feng wants to see you in his office.
Did he say what it was about?
He didn't.
(Someone in the company knew)
(about your pregnancy.)
(That person has also found your report
at the gynecological hospital)
(before joining the company.)
(But I wasn't the one reporting all this
to the company.)
(It's not your fault to get pregnant.)
(From a legal perspective,)
the company doesn't have the right
to dismiss you
just because you are pregnant.
I find it really hard to understand you.
Who are you standing with?
(I wish I could help you.)
The email says
that you instructed Yue Tong
to conceal the truth
and told the company
she found herself pregnant
after the formal entry,
is this true?
Mr. Feng.
It was my negligence
for not conducting
a proper background check.
But I did indeed find out
about it afterward.
Ming Yu.
From a moral standpoint,
I don't see any issue
with your words.
When I was younger,
I might have handled it the same way
if I encountered the same situation.
As the HR manager,
you should
consider the company's interests
when you're handling issues,
not just based
on your personal emotions.
Mr. Feng, I'm sorry.
This time is pretty sensitive.
Certainly, the person who sent the email
must have harbored some bad motive.
But regarding this matter,
I might not be able to help you.
Mingyu.
(Who do you support?)
(Support who?)
Guo Kai and Ms. Fang.
Everyone is betting
who will get the position
of vice president.
You're worrying for nothing.
Just wait for the announcement.
Initially, Guo Kai seemed unstoppable,
but after the performance review,
Ms. Fang clearly did a better job.
But who knows,
now it's revealed
she helped a former colleague
to conceal a pregnancy.
Who got exposed? Was it Ms. Fang?
And then?
Hard to tell.
Maybe, in the end,
she worked so hard for nothing.
I'm leaving.
Your pizza looks a bit questionable.
Will I get poisoned after eating it?
Don't worry, it won't kill you.
Really?
You try it, then.
Let me see what it tastes like.
It is burnt.
It's burnt.
Why did you let me eat it, then?
My bad.
I thought you said it won't poison me?
He's back.
Zhuang Yuan.
Jiang Yi baked us pizza.
But it's all burnt.
Impressive, huh?
Just relax,
I've ordered takeout.
Tonight,
I will make sure you all
get to eat some hot pizza.
No need.
I'm full of your pink bubbles.
What's the matter? You seem troubled.
Did something happen
at your workplace?
I'm a bit worried about Mingyu.
Mingyu?
What's it with Mingyu?
She got set up by Guo Kai.
Guo Kai?
Aren't they a couple?
The Smiths?
Guo Kai is way more shameless
than the Smiths.
Now the whole company is
gossiping about Mingyu.
When they got engaged,
Guo Kai spoke so sweetly.
Now, for a position,
he turned his back on her.
Don't worry for now.
Our childhood friend, Fang Mingyu,
won't be easily set up.
(This time is pretty sensitive.)
Certainly, the person who sent the email
must have harbored some bad motive.
(Mingyu, I'm sorry.)
(I know whatever I say now won't help.)
(When I resigned,)
I did suspect you,
so I was a bit cautious
and recorded our conversation.
But I really had no intention
of using that recording for anything.
Until Guo Kai found me.
(I've helped you to settle the matter)
(with the company.)
(I can give you money too.)
(I want only one thing from you.)
(It won't cause you any harm)
(by giving this to me.)
What thing?
Your chat records with Mingyu.
I can't give you that.
For you,
this is the most favorable choice.
You'd better do as I say.
Otherwise, I don't know
what might happen.
I came to tell you
Guo Kai is terrifying.
He can do literally anything.
Thank you for your trust, everyone.
It's an affirmation of what I've done
and an encouragement for my future work.
Maybe some of you here
still don't know me well,
so you might still have doubts about me.
But that's okay.
I will prove myself
in my future endevors.
Why are you here?
Sorry for interrupting.
I have something to say to the leaders.
I understand your emotions,
but we haven't finished the meeting yet.
Whatever you have to say,
wait until after the meeting.
Li, no matter what,
Ms. Fang is still
the HR manager of the company.
She has the rights to join this meeting.
Mr. Feng.
The reason why I'm here today
isn't to listen to Guo Kai's speech.
I'm here to hand in
my resignation letter.
Regarding Yue Tong's matter,
I have a few words to say to everyone.
As the company's HR manager,
my job responsibility
is to weave a dense web
of company's rules
and contract terms
so as to safeguard
the company's interests.
But in all these years of work,
I found
that this web
sometimes becomes
too rational and heartless.
There's never a law that says
a company can dismiss an employee
for being pregnant.
And personally speaking,
I don't think a woman
should hide her pregnancy
for a job.
When Yue Tong
had to hide her pregnancy for this job,
my first instinct
was to cut her some slack.
I may not be suitable
for a human resources role.
Fang Mingyu,
I've also worked in human resources.
I completely understand
what you have said.
You didn't handle
Yue Tong's situation properly.
But it also exposed flaws
in the company's system.
The company will make
necessary adjustments.
Resigning over something like this?
Is it necessary?
Don't be so impulsive.
I'm resigning
not just because of this.
I've been working in our company
for eight years and three months.
To pursuit my career success,
I lost some of myself.
I have also lost
the opportunity to love publicly.
If I fell in love with a colleague,
I'd have to hide it.
But today,
I don't want to hide it anymore.
Guo Kai,
I think we should all be brave
to make our relationship public.
How long has it been?
More than a year.
Mr. Feng, I'm sorry.
As the HR manager of the company,
I did what I shouldn't have done.
So I have to resign.
I'm sorry.
Well, fellow leaders,
I think
I can explain our relationship.
Fang Mingyu.
What was that?
Did I not make myself clear?
I'm tired of hiding it.
It's not that
you didn't want to hide it.
You just did that on purpose.
Yes, I did.
Why are you so short-sighted right now?
What am I doing all this for?
I'm doing this for us.
Guo Kai, we're done.
Mingyu.
Mingyu!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Just now, you and Guo Kai...
I said,
I'm fine. Don't worry.
As you said.
If you need something,
call me anytime.
Zhuang Yuan, I quit.
Why did you quit your job?
It's not a big deal.
I just want to find a new job.
Don't tell Yingzi and Jiang Yi yet.
I don't want to make them worried.
Promise me.
Keep it a secret.
I'm off.
What the...
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'll go... I'll go get the door.
I'm sorry.
Zhuang Yuan, here you are.
The dumplings are wrapped.
Which one
you want to eat?
Zhuang Yuan,
which dumplings you prefer?
Zhuang Yuan?
There's something wrong with you.
I'm fine.
You look dispirited.
Did something happen to Mingyu?
What could happen to Mingyu?
Fine, if you don't tell me,
I'll call Mingyu and ask her.
Don't.
Tell me what's going on, then.
I found you're not yourself
the moment you came in. Tell me.
This really has nothing
to do with Mingyu.
I'm just tired from work.
Is that true?
Enough, you two stop being suspicious.
I'll cook dumplings by myself.
Why are you the only one here?
Yifei and Yingzi accompanied Grandma
for the acupuncture session.
I stayed to look after the store.
Do you want some?
Did you make it? Is it edible?
Why? You don't want it?
Nothing.
I'll have one.
Eat up.
Have you eaten?
Yeah.
One person?
Why don't you sit here?
Where is Lan Yifei?