[Love Endures]
[Episode 32]
(Hi, Stefanie.)
(This is a story
of an old fan of yours.)
(My childhood friend)
(has been your fan since you debuted.)
(She would buy every album of yours.)
(She knows how to sing
every song of yours.)
(She even knows)
(every lyric by heart.)
(Thus,)
(my entire youth)
(is filled with memories
related to you.)
(In 2008,)
(I went to your concert with her,)
(but due to my mistake,)
(we couldn't get in.)
(I made a wish)
(at that moment.)
(I have to go to your concert with her.)
Hello.
I'm Sun Stefanie's manager.
It's about your article online.
Who are you?
Hi, Mr. Jiang.
Stefanie and I
have read your Weibo post.
Stefanie asked me
to give you her best wishes.
She hopes you will
have a perfect ending.
Thank you.
Yifei is gone.
Grandma is also gone.
We're also leaving Hangtian City.
I've made up my mind.
I'm not going back to Jiangzhou.
Our lives are our own.
I'm going to live life the way I want.
At thirty,
our lives are just beginning!
What about you guys?
Is there anything you want to do
but you haven't done yet?
I want to be happy
and give myself a nice answer right now.
What about you, Jiang?
Me?
It's a secret.
Why are you keeping it a secret?
We told you ours,
and you are keeping yours a secret.
That's his style.
He must be sure that he can wow everyone
when he's done what he wants to do.
Tell us about what you want to do.
Me?
I'm the same as before.
My goal has always been the same.
I want to be a great journalist,
to find the truth,
and to put the bad guys in their place.
But I think something has changed.
Someone asked me
if I became a journalist for Yifei
or for myself,
and I couldn't answer.
It was more or less for Yifei,
but from now on,
I'll continue
to work hard for myself.
Chief Editor.
How's your vacation going?
I can go back to work next week.
I'm afraid you can't come back.
What does that mean?
I did apply for annual leave.
It's not that the company
doesn't want you.
There's a new place.
I don't know if you're interested.
BeijingTimes invited me back
to Beijing as chief editor.
I can take someone with me.
I was hoping it would be you.
Chief Editor, you're saying
that I can join BeijingTimes again?
Beijing is,
after all, the most developed place
in the media industry.
There will offer you more opportunities
than Jiangzhou in the future.
So you're the first person I thought of.
But Chief Editor,
I have friends and family
in Jiangzhou.
And I'm kind of adapting
to my life here.
I'm a little...
Huang Yingzi,
you were kicked out of headquarters
in the first place
because you offended someone
by reporting the truth.
Haven't you been
wanting to go back?
Well, now's your chance.
If you hesitate, it's gone.
Wait for me.
I can't do it anymore.
I have to stop.
Don't sit down.
Stretch.
Give me a hand.
Look, my hand is getting sore.
Have you decided
when you are going to the farm?
I'm planning to go this weekend.
You're welcome to come visit anytime
once I get settled.
You promised me that.
But haven't I
been talking about
going on trips before?
I couldn't go last time
because of Yingzi's birthday,
so I need to plan
and schedule something.
So, have you figured out
where you're going?
Why should I tell you?
We know each other so well now.
Why can't you tell me?
Are you thinking of coming with me?
Yes.
Actually, I'd love to go on a trip too.
It's always the six of us
hanging out together.
When can the two of us go out alone
and meet each other again
in a new place?
We will meet each other again.
We haven't gotten separated
for 12 years.
No matter where we go,
we'll always find each other again.
Yes.
This is a new beginning.
You know what, let's race.
To under the bridge.
If you win,
I'll tell you where I'm going.
You want me to run again?
Do I look like Guan Chao to you?
Do you want to know
where I'm going or not?
I do.
Get ready.
Three!
Why are you cheating?
Yingzi!
You guys went jogging again.
Yours.
It's still warm.
Actually, I've called you here
to tell you something.
What if I tell you
I might be leaving Jiangzhou too?
Where are you going?
I'm going to Beijing for work.
Does Jiang know about this?
I haven't told him yet.
Things are starting
to go well for us now.
If I have to go to Beijing now,
I really can't bear to leave him.
Yingzi, in my opinion,
don't overthink it.
Just follow your heart.
Talk to him.
There's nothing you can't handle.
It's been a long time.
Yes, long time no see.
Have a seat.
You're fine now?
Yes, I am.
That's good.
I haven't gotten the chance
to thank you.
Thank you for finding Lan Bin for me,
and helping me face Yifei's death.
Why are you thanking me?
The person you should really thank
is Jiang Yi.
Are you writing a novel?
How's it going? Are you almost done?
No, not quite.
How are you?
There's a good chance
I'll be transferred to Beijing.
Isn't that a good thing?
Go back to where you were
and start over.
I came here to say goodbye to you.
Although we must part ways,
it's been great knowing you.
All the best.
It's been great knowing you.
I also brought you a gift.
Here's a picture
of the sea sparkle I took.
I think it's perfect for you.
You can have it.
It's beautiful.
Thank you.
I'm leaving now.
Good luck,
great writer.
I'm looking forward to your new work.
Huang Yingzi.
I'll send it to you immediately
once I've finished writing it.
Sure, I'll be waiting.
Bye-bye!
I'm off!
I've been looking for you.
What are you doing here?
Come on.
Check this out.
What is this?
Our home.
Our home?
Look,
your house is 40 square feet
and so is mine.
Let's merge them.
You mean
we're going to live together?
That's right.
I've checked out
several nice neighborhoods
near your office.
This way,
it would be convenient
for your daily commute.
Just think about it,
I have a motorcycle.
A twist of the throttle,
and I'll be there.
Let's get a two-bedroom unit.
There will be enough space
for your desk and my computer.
We can even have a big kitchen
to match your profound culinary skills.
And the balcony.
You can decorate it however you want.
We can plant 30 pots of Crimson Saber.
Decorate it however you like.
Oh, and the bathrooms.
We need to have two.
It will spare us the hassle
of fighting over shower time.
As for the cinema,
we could turn it into a home theater.
Let's schedule a midnight screening
every weekend
and invite friends over.
What do you think?
Jiang Yi.
What's wrong?
I need to talk to you about something.
Go ahead.
If I tell you
I might be going to Beijing,
what do you think?
It's great.
Business trip or traveling?
What if it's for work?
Work?
That's good too.
Long term or short term?
Long term.
I'll need to stay in Beijing
all the time.
What does that mean?
Jiang Feng, editor-in-chief
of New Perspective,
has been poached by BeijingTimes
to be their editor-in-chief.
He wants me to come with him.
So you said yes?
I haven't said yes.
That's why I thought
I'd come to discuss with you.
But don't you already
have an answer in mind?
Huang Yingzi, honestly,
if you really want to go to Beijing,
I can go with you.
I'll quit my job at ATG
and start all over again.
What's the big deal?
Don't be ridiculous.
No way.
You've
worked so hard to get where you are.
How can you give up
just because of me?
But is that what I want?
Don't you know
what I want?
At the end of the day,
you don't know me at all, Huang Yingzi.
Jiang Yi...
(Incognito mode has been activated.)
(Would you like to play?)
(Player Huang Yingzi,)
(welcome to play in incognito mode.)
Yingzi,
what's wrong?
Are you feeling down?
Is it because of Jiang Yi?
Actually, it's because of myself.
I went to see him today.
I wanted to talk to him about it.
Then, I saw him sketching something
on a piece of paper.
When I took a look at it,
he was sketching the house
we're going to live in.
Listening to him talk about it,
I felt so sweet and touched.
I didn't know how to tell him.
When I finally mustered the courage
to tell him,
he was disappointed.
(If only you had seen his reaction.)
(When I saw it,)
(I thought I was being cruel.)
(If you really want to go to Beijing,)
(I'm sure Jiang Yi won't stop you.)
(He didn't stop me.)
He even wanted to quit his job
and go to Beijing with me.
But Yifei,
I can't be that selfish.
So this is a dilemma
for you.
Yes.
Yingzi, tell me,
why do you want
to go to Beijing so badly?
Are you thinking
that I want to go to Beijing
for better career opportunities?
Actually, that's not it.
It's for that topic on sexual assault.
The chief editor told me
that if I go to Beijing,
they would assign me
the topic on sexual assault.
(Every time I see news like that,)
(I think of)
(those vulnerable and helpless girls.)
(They want to protect themselves,)
(but they don't have
the power to do so.)
If no one
reaches out
to help them at times like this,
they may become
more and more disappointed
and fall into darkness.
I know that I alone may not be able
to solve the problem,
but I still want to contribute
my meager efforts
to help them.
I want to write this news report
to make more people
aware of this issue,
to draw attention to it.
Yingzi,
I think you should be honest
with Jiang Yi about this.
But he'll still quit his job
and go to Beijing with me.
That's his choice.
In a sense,
you have no right to interfere.
Yingzi, you and Jiang Yi are 30.
You should decide for yourselves
what you want to do with your lives
and take responsibility
for your decision.
(Congratulations on
passing the game trial.)
(Please check out the gift
from the developers.)
(Happy birthday to you!)
(Today is Huang Yingzi's 19th birthday.)
(This is the first time)
(she's celebrating her birthday
without the five of us.)
(Happy birthday, Yingzi.)
(Whether I'm in your wishes or not,)
(I'll be by your side.)
(Let's cut the cake.)
(After a twelve-hour flight,)
(I finally made it.)
(Yingzi is graduating
from college today.)
(Happy graduation, future journalist.)
(Let's take a photo)
(to commemorate this important day.)
(Huang Yingzi.)
(Look,)
(This is how Huang Yingzi is
when she's nervous.)
(Once this interview airs,)
(I'm definitely going to keep it.)
(Then, when she becomes
a great journalist in the future,)
(I'll show it to her)
(and have a good laugh at her expense.)
(Congratulations, Huang Yingzi,)
(you're getting closer to your dream.)
(Over the years, I've read
every one of your articles,)
(and I know all about your hard work.)
(Ms. Huang Yingzi,)
(this is your takeout.)
(I didn't order any takeout.)
(You're Huang Yingzi, right?)
(You're still the same as before.)
(You skip meals when you get busy.)
(Huang Yingzi, I'm sorry.)
(In many important moments
of your life,)
(moments when you need me,)
(I can only be there for you
in this way.)
(But I know)
(that when you're seeing this video,)
(it means we've succeeded.)
(I believe that by then,)
(even if with the heavy memories,)
(you can still bravely move forward.)
(Anyway,)
(I'll always be around you.)
(Hello, Chief Editor.)
(There's something I'd like
to talk to you about in person.)
(I'm going back to Jiangzhou now.)
(Mr. Jiang, sorry for this sudden call.)
I'd like to talk to you.
The Huang Yingzi I know
is an extremely talented journalist.
If her spot hadn't been taken,
she actually had a chance
to join BeijingTimes.
I know.
Joining BeijingTimes
has always been Huang Yingzi's dream.
Then why did she tell me she wanted
to pass up the opportunity?
What does that mean?
She passed up the opportunity?
She told me
there's
someone very important
waiting for her in Jiangzhou.
I hope you can change her mind.
Thank you, Mr. Jiang.
I know what to do.
(At 30 years old,)
(you must have become)
(a very famous journalist.)
(There's no justice you can't uphold,)
(no truth you can't uncover.)
(The bad people will
have nowhere to hide.)
(My goal hasn't changed since I was 18.)
(I will become a journalist)
(and expose the truth.)
Hello, Yingzi.
Where are you?
I'm right behind you.
What are you doing here?
I need to talk to you.
Jiang Yi, let's get married.
Jiang Yi, I saw the Easter egg
in your game.
I only found out
that you've been with me
all these twelve years.
I knew nothing about this.
I used to call you stingy,
but now I realize
I've been
the ignorant fool.
I get it now.
Nothing is more important than you,
not Beijing or anything else.
From now on,
I'll be your shadow.
Where you go, I go.
If you want to stay in Jiangzhou,
I'll stay here with you.
If you want to return to Hangtian City,
I'll return with you.
If you want to go to the UK,
I'll go with you.
Jiang Yi,
you've always been there for me,
now it's my turn to be there for you.
Will you marry me?
About this,
maybe we should
think about it.
So...
So you're saying no?
I just hope you didn't make a decision
in a moment of impulse
without thinking it through.
It's not an impulsive decision.
I've thought it through.
But I haven't.
I know exactly
how much courage it takes for a girl
to say something like that.
And I know
how much
this means
to you and me.
So I think
we should both give each other
a little time
to think it over,
okay?
Ming Yu.
Hello, Yingzi.
Are you feeling better?
You didn't forget everything, did you?
You were crying and saying
you wanted to break up with Jiang Yi.
Don't you remember?
Jiang Yi...
When will you know my heart?
What did you say?
You're saying you love me?
I love you too,
Yi!
Why am I kissing a globe?
Crimson Saber,
from now on,
you're an orphan.
Or do you want
to call your dad
and tell him to come back?
It's your dad.
Hello, Huang Yingzi.
Your dad is talking to you.
Tell him.
You pricked me!
You bad son!
Is this Mingyu?
I proposed to Jiang Yi.
And he said no.
Yingzi, are you drunk?
He doesn't love me at all.
It's because Jiang Yi...
♪He doesn't love me♪
♪I know he doesn't love me♪
(What are you thinking?)
I, Huang Yingzi, have been single
for 30 years.
If you don't want to get married,
it's fine.
I can wait a little longer.
Why aren't you replying me?
I get it, I get it.
You want to break up with me, right?
No problem, no problem.
Let's break up, then.
It's no big deal!
I'm sorry.
Can we not break up?
I won't say I want to break up anymore.
Okay. Still not replying?
Fine.
If you don't reply, then we're over.
Completely over. I'm blocking you.
Completely blocking you!
Yingzi?
Are you okay?
Are you still there?
Mingyu.
Are you sober now?
Yes.
What should I do?
What else can you do?
You've deleted
all his contact information,
even Taobao's Wangwang chat.
He couldn't reach you.
So he asked me to pass you a message.
What did he say?
He said
even if you want to break up,
do it amicably.
I don't want to break up.
I know.
So
he asked you to meet him
on the evening of the weekend.
Talk things out
with him.
I'm out on a trip with my parents,
so I won't be able to go with you.
Update me on whatever happens.
Bye.
Huang Yingzi.
Chloe.
What are you doing here?
The press conference of "The Maze"
is being held here.
Today is the first day of rehearsal.
Jiang Yi asked you to come?
Yes.
He said he wanted
to talk to me about something.
This guy is becoming
more and more unreliable.
Who would arrange a discussion
with his girlfriend
at a press conference venue?
Where is he?
This is the highest
holographic projection
exhibition hall in Jiangzhou.
He says even though the game
can't be called "Sky City,"
the press conference
must be held in Sky City.
Take a break here.
I've got things to attend to.
Go on.
Yingzi.
What are you guys doing here?
It's such an important occasion.
It's his debut press conference.
How could we miss it?
Isn't today a rehearsal?
You're going to Beijing, right?
He said, as your friend,
he asked us to come
and see you off.
As my friend?
Did he tell you that?
He told us he broke up with you.
Now you're just friends.
We broke up?
Did he tell you that too?
Yes.
Yingzi, you're in the wrong here.
You two just got together,
and you're leaving for Beijing.
He must be feeling terrible, right?
No...
And even if you're going to Beijing,
when he offered to go with you,
why didn't you agree?
I...
Even if it's
a long-distance relationship,
it's still a relationship.
What's the big deal?
It's not like that.
I was drunk that day.
That was my drunk talk.
Even if you were drunk,
it was still wrong of you
to ask to break up.
Are you a child?
Exactly.
I know I was wrong.
So after I sobered up,
I regretted it.
Where is he?
Where can I find him?
I haven't seen him.
Hello everyone.
I'm glad you could all make it today.
Without all of you,
there wouldn't be the game "The Maze".
I'm not good
at expressing my gratitude,
but I still want to tell you all this,
thank you.
The initial inspiration
for creating this game came from a girl.
We grew up together.
However, when we were eighteen,
a friend of ours
left us permanently,
leaving her
in a state of perpetual pain.
So I wanted to
create a parallel world for her
through this game.
In that world,
there is no death,
no parting.
I also want to use it
to make up for the regrets
of our youth.
It is because of this girl
that this story exists.
And because of her,
I've been able to persist until now.
In reality, the story of "The Maze"
has not concluded.
Today, right here,
I want to write
the most perfect ending for her.
(Huang Yingzi,)
(saying goodbye to you face-to-face)
(is too hard for me,)
(so I'll do it this way instead.)
(Do you remember)
(when you asked me
when I started liking you?)
(It was March 5th, 1996,)
(the day we first met.)
I'm Huang Yingzi.
I'm in Senior Class 2.
(You always have many strange ideas)
(and plenty of bad ideas.)
(The truth is,)
(your taste is average,)
(but your narcissism is real.)
(You always claim to be
the dancing queen of Hangtian City,)
(the descendant of Huang Feihong.)
(You always want to protect everyone,)
(standing in front of everyone.)
(But to me,)
(you're the one)
(who needs protection the most.)
(When did this idea)
(first come about?)
(Maybe it was during that summer,)
(during that game of truth or dare.)
(I couldn't help
but look at you in secret,)
(and draw you in secret.)
(It could also be when I saw
the helpless look in your eyes)
(when I was leaving.)
(I don't know when it happened,)
(but suddenly I realized)
(that I'm more than just fond of you.)
(Huang Yingzi,)
(today marks)
(25 years and one month
and three days since we first met.)
(During this time,)
(we've spent half of it together)
(and half apart.)
(We're about to part ways again,)
(but there are still
so many things I promised you)
(that I haven't done yet.)
(Like...)
(Hello, Yingzi.)
(I'm Stefanie.)
(I think you must be
a really great girl.)
You're surrounded
by people who love you very much.
(Actually, over the years,)
(I've received a lot of letters)
from all places.
It's all sorts of letters.
(Over the past decade or so,)
(I've also received letters
from Jiang Yi.)
(He shared with me many stories)
(about the girl he liked.)
(And these letters and stories,)
(I've kept them all in mind.)
I'd like to convey my best wishes
to you.
I wish both of you happiness.
I'm sorry.
When you proposed to me that day,
I rejected you.
I just couldn't bear to let a girl
do such a thing.
Besides, I've prepared
for this day for far too long.
I couldn't just let you have it.
We've known each other for so long,
and you know
I'm not very good at doing cheesy stuff,
but as long as it's for you,
I'm willing to do anything.
Do you remember that wish card?
Actually, when I was 18,
I already had my wish in mind.
You said
that whales are
the gentlest creatures in the sea
because they only have
one partner in their lifetime.
No matter how far apart they are,
they can always find each other.
They will never leave each other.
Ms. Huang Yingzi,
will you marry me?
I will.
(When I grow up,)
I'll ask Stefanie Sun
to sing in front of you,
in front of your house.
(You're bluffing.)
Thank you.
Yingzi,
we are going to be fine.
Go.
Stefanie...
Stefanie, is this really you?
Oh, my God.
I can't believe it's really you.
You really are here.
I love you.
I've loved you since I was little.
I've been your fans for over ten years.
Oh, my God.
I know how to sing
every one of your albums.
I even had a sing-off with others
when I was little, Stefanie!
I almost went to your concert one year.
Oh, God! My Stefanie!
Yingzi...
I can't believe this is happening.
Yingzi, you're being too much.
This is my boyfriend, Stefanie.
Yes.
I love you so much, Stefanie!
When are you going
to release your new album?
When are you going on tour?
Take a breath.
Will you come to Jiangzhou?
Yingzi...
Take a breath with me.
(Dear you,)
(what songs)
(accompanied you)
(and saw you through
the most important time of your youth?)
(Perhaps, at some moments,)
(they even gave you
some encouragement and strength.)
(That's the most precious thing.)
(In those long stretches of time,)
(we've all left behind
various versions of ourselves.)
(Some happily laughing,)
(some tearfully crying,)
(some looking miserable,)
(and some shining brightly.)
(It's these different versions)
(that piece together who we are now.)
(Let's live on)
(with these precious memories.)
(Because of them,)
(you are unique.)
(And because we have each other,)
(even if life is full of ups and downs,)
(we will always
shine as brightly as ever,)
(forever young.)
Louder. I can't hear you.
Calm...
Stefanie...
Where is my Stefanie?
You scared her off.
Stefanie got scared off.
Stefanie!