[Love Endures]
[Episode 25]
Zhuang Yuan.
I've been looking for you everywhere.
What's wrong?
Are you giving up the chance
to stay on campus?
Don't you want to complete your thesis?
Hey,
why are you giving up easily?
Tianlin,
I've thought a lot recently.
What is my life goal?
Why did I study so much?
I've figured it out.
I don't want to be bothered
by things like my degree
or staying here.
Mom?
Why are you here?
Madam... Madam Xu.
If there's nothing...
I have something to do.
I'll take my leave.
If Professor Ma hadn't called me,
I had no idea you'd do this!
Zhuang Yuan,
what exactly are you doing?
I just want to do what I love.
Then get admitted directly first!
You can do what you want later.
Do you know how rare it is
to remain here?
Rare?
Do I have to accept it
because it's a rare opportunity?
All I want is to focus on real research.
That is only temporary.
After enduring for a few years,
you'll get to be a university professor.
Isn't that your dream?
That's your dream.
Not mine.
Fine, it's my dream!
Zhuang Yuan.
Your dad and I
didn't study much,
but I know
only through education
can you change your destiny
and
live a life different from ours.
This is the best option
I can think of for your future.
The opportunity
is right in front of you.
I won't allow you
to be willful
and give up without thinking.
Let's go meet your professor together
and ask him to give you another chance.
I won't go.
Let's go!
I said, I won't go!
What do you want, Zhuang Yuan?
I'm going to celebrate
Yingzi's birthday tonight.
What's wrong with you?
You all came to celebrate my birthday.
Yingzi,
when Guan Chao and I got married,
you helped us a lot.
It's only right for us
to celebrate your birthday.
Yes.
Guan Chao told me
you loved birthday celebrations
when you were young.
Really?
I don't think so.
Did you forget?
During your 17th birthday,
we didn't prepare any gifts
and gave you a wish card.
You kicked up a fuss,
wanting to sever ties with us.
Regarding the wish card,
they have fulfilled my wishes.
You're the only one left.
Yingzi,
I canceled
my vacation and flight ticket for you.
Do as you see fit.
That means
you never planned
on celebrating my birthday.
I thought
you wanted to spend
some alone time with him.
What alone time?
Yingzi.
I have a surprise for you.
Look that way.
Happy birthday.
Are you crazy, Zhuang Yuan?
When Guan Chao got married,
you said it only happens
once in a lifetime,
so you attended his wedding.
Yingzi can celebrate
her birthday every year.
Is it worth
giving up your future?
Mom,
you've got it all wrong.
It's not that I'm giving up
my future for Yingzi.
This is
exactly what I want.
Since when did you become this willful?
I've never been willful,
so I'll be willful this time.
Mom.
Since young,
I've been an obedient child.
You make arrangements,
choices,
and decisions on my behalf.
However, have you asked me?
Have you asked
if this is what I want
or if I'm happy doing this?
I'm 30 this year.
I can be responsible for my own choices.
I've had enough
of your previous arrangements.
I forced you.
You've had enough.
Got it.
Okay.
Not bad, Yingzi.
Your car is quite spacious.
My car
is the same brand as yours.
Let's play a song.
I think that's a good idea.
It has been years,
but your song list is still the same.
The songs we listened to
when we were young,
the singers
sang really well.
These few years,
there are many new singers
and new songs,
but they are different.
Back then, besides Stefanie Sun,
we have Jay Chou,
Mayday, and Jolin Tsai.
Thinking back,
it really was the golden age
of the Chinese music scene.
It should also be our golden age.
Mingyu.
Do you remember Yifei and I
had a promise regarding Stefanie Sun
when we reached the age of 30?
Of course.
I was your witness.
Yifei remembers that, too.
This promise
is about to be fulfilled soon.
Mom.
Why are you here?
I've been looking for you
the entire day.
The rain is getting heavier.
Come back home with me.
Mom, I'm sorry.
I
went overboard today.
Every time I come to campus,
I'll imagine
you as a professor.
Sitting on the field,
you're surrounded
by a bunch of students
listening to your lecture.
You'll share your knowledge with them.
I'll tell everyone,
"Look,
that's my son,
Professor Zhuang Yuan.
He's the biggest pride
of my life."
I might never
be able to see that scene, ever.
In fact, since young,
I've always
lacked a mind of my own,
so I've gotten used
to following your orders
and arrangements.
I thought the best gifts for you
would be my doctoral degree
and my graduation certificate.
But now I understand
that the best gift I can give you
is me growing up,
being responsible for my own choices
and not regretting them.
You've grown up.
You can choose your own path
and don't need me
to plan for you anymore.
Mom,
where are you going?
I'm going to find Professor Ma
to thank him for his guidance and trust.
I also want to apologize to him.
My son
is going to take
the path he wants.
Do you have a cigarette?
Do you have a lighter?
No.
When did you start smoking?
When I was 18. What about you?
Same.
Did you bring everything?
Do you think
we can hide it well
just like in the past?
I don't know,
but this is the only way.
You're still the same.
Yingzi would rush ahead
to protect everyone,
and you'd hide behind her
to protect her.
Why are we still standing here?
Let's go dancing!
My heart is about to jump out.
I should go home and do my homework.
Why are you so diligent?
If my mom finds out,
she'll kill me.
We've celebrated our 18th birthday.
What's wrong with dancing?
Come on.
Just this once.
No more next time.
Come on.
Let's go.
Let's dance together.
Let's battle.
Good.
Are you here
to take selfies or have fun?
You know nothing.
This is a camera phone.
Do you have it?
My second mock exam's score
passed the cutoff line,
so my dad gave it to me.
It's the only one.
Mingyu, let's go to the restroom.
Okay.
We're going to the restroom.
Go ahead.
I'll bring you there.
The restroom is that way.
That way.
Come on.
Why do I feel
dizzy?
What?
I said, I feel dizzy.
I feel dizzy!
Stop drinking, then.
It isn't that lively today.
Oh, isn't this Lan Yifei?
Stand right there.
What do you want?
I miss you.
Why?
Wasn't the previous beating enough?
Don't fight.
If you lose, you end up in the hospital.
If you win, you end up in jail.
You're just a bunch of kids.
How dare you act all arrogant?
Let's see how you'll act arrogant today.
So what if you outnumber us?
If you dare, let's fight one-on-one.
Don't fight!
If you lose, you end up in the hospital.
If you win, you end up in jail!
I'll fight one-on-one with her.
Scoundrel.
Scoundrel?
You make it sound sweet.
Mind your mouth!
We... We're in trouble.
Come, we're in trouble!
Let's go.
Yifei, Guan Chao.
Are you okay?
We're fine.
Little Chicken Chiu?
Huang Feihong?
Why did we run into you again?
Darn it.
Is he the only thug in Hangtian City?
Why is he everywhere?
What do you want?
Don't you try to trick me this time.
You're just a high school student.
Stop pretending
to be Huang Feihong's descendant.
Guys,
teach them a good lesson today.
What do you want?
We can't end up
in the police station again.
Are we not fighting?
We can't fight today no matter what.
Let's scare them
and then run.
Do the countdown.
Three,
two,
one.
Go after them!
Are we not going after them?
If you lose, you end up in the hospital.
If you win, you end up in jail.
I can't.
Slow down...
So?
Huang Feihong's descendant
isn't only skilled in martial arts.
She's also smart, right?
Yes.
Yi, let me tell you.
As long as I exist,
you exist as well.
Okay.
I'll keep protecting you,
okay?
Okay.
You, too.
As long as the six of us are together,
we won't be scared anywhere we go.
Get it?
Yes.
I have a question.
Why does she
keep saying she's a descendant
of Huang Feihong?
Why?
Her surname is Huang.
She also loves fighting.
She made that up.
That's it?
Yes.
Well,
Huang Feihong was born in Guangdong.
Perhaps
she is the descendant
of his descendant,
many generations removed.
What are you
muttering about?
Greetings, Heroine Huang.
You, come here.
You, go.
Don't always single me out
for blame, okay?
Come, let's go home!
Slow down...
Why can't you
walk straight?
How can you say that?
Who is the one not walking straight?
Did you know
what this is?
Walking daintily.
Foshan Shadowless Feet.
Wudang Elevator Jump.
Okay.
I had no idea you're a martial artist.
I am a great master of martial arts.
What's wrong?
Jiang Yi.
Don't cry
if someone bullies you in the future.
I'll be there to take care of you.
Don't worry.
Okay.
Let's go home.
I won't go there again.
It's fine.
You need to cover up
so your parents won't realize it.
Hear that?
I can't breathe.
Fine.
Okay, I'm leaving.
Where is my phone?
My phone.
Where is it?
(Are you sober now?)
Phone.
Where is my phone?
Has anyone seen my phone?
What is this?
Where is my phone?
Has anyone seen my phone?
(Why hasn't Huang Yingzi replied to me?)
Jiang Yi.
Uh, the supermarket has
a buy-one-get-one-free offer on yogurt.
I bought a bottle for Yingzi.
Yingzi isn't with you?
Isn't she home?
She didn't answer her phone,
so I thought she was
doing her homework at your place.
But I left her at her doorstep
before leaving.
Oh dear. Where is she?
Huang, go find her now!
Coming.
Don't just wait. I'll go look for her.
Madam Guo, I'll go look with Mr. Huang.
Okay.
You can wait at home.
If there's any update,
let me know immediately.
I... I'll wait for your call.
Hey,
we meet again.
Where is Huang Yingzi?
I'd like to know that, too.
I was about to ask you that question.
Why did you come instead of her?
Don't you want it?
Give me the phone.
Give it to me!
The phone isn't yours.
Why are you so agitated?
You beat us to a pulp
and we were locked up
at the police station.
Now you want us to be honest?
That's too much.
Tell me.
What do I have to do
for you to give it to me?
Let's do this.
Let us beat you up
the same way you beat us up.
Do you still want it?
If you don't, forget it.
The phone is the latest model.
Selling it will be enough
to cover the losses.
Sure. Go ahead.
You should wait at home.
I can't stay at home.
Huang,
where do you think she'll go at night?
Calm down.
She's an adult.
She can protect herself.
Two days ago,
I read about
a female high schooler's disappearance.
In the beginning,
they lost contact with her.
When they found her,
she was
dead.
Can you stop
scaring yourself?
Let's call the police.
You have to wait for 24 hours
before reporting a disappearance.
Why do you only
read half of the news?
Mr. Fang, any updates?
Madam Xu,
did Yingzi contact you?
What?
Someone saw her
at the disco this afternoon?
Nearly fought?
Okay, thank you.
Okay, let's keep in touch.
Didn't you say she's an adult
and has the ability to protect herself?
Huang Yingzi!
Huang Yingzi.
It's late. Where...
Where could she be?
Huang Yingzi.
Look. What is that?
What?
Isn't that Yingzi?
Yingzi!
Yingzi...
Wake up...
Yingzi, look.
It's me, Mom.
Huang Yingzi!
You got drunk
and even fell asleep here?
That's enough.
You're scaring her.
There, there.
Dad, Mom, I'm sorry.
I lost the phone
you just bought for me.
I couldn't find it.
It's fine. Good girl.
I'll buy another one for you.
I'm glad you're fine.
Okay.
Let's go home.
Will you not buy a new phone for me?
I will.
Where is my phone?
Anyway, my mom said
to make me learn this lesson,
I won't get a phone this semester.
How do we contact you?
You can call my house
or find me at my place.
What a pity.
I took many photos with that phone
at the disco yesterday.
I can't see them now.
Now,
I can only isolate myself from the world
and focus on my studies.
Am... Am I daydreaming?
Or did my memory deviate from the truth?
I remember bringing this phone
to the disco.
I couldn't find it after coming home.
You drank too much
and remembered wrongly.
This is great.
I'm glad it's back.
I got scared
thinking I lost it.
See if anything inside was lost.
How did this phone return to my drawer?
Be careful.
Is throwing balls
fun?
Stop.
Jiang Yi, what are you doing?
Show me.
Let me see.
What happened to your face?
Who hit you?
I didn't fight. I fell down.
You got injured just from a fall?
Your face is all bruised!
Yes, I fell because
I was playing with my phone
and not watching where I was going.
Is it bruised?
No.
Not at all.
Playing with your phone again.
How many times have I told you
not to play games
when you're walking?
You suffered injuries from the fall.
What about next time?
What if you got hit by a car
and died?
You're no longer a child.
Falling when you walk?
How embarrassing.
Why didn't you fall to your death?
Why?
Why didn't you tell her
you got injured to help her
get back her phone?
You know nothing.
I'm a man.
Drink.
You... You don't have to stand up.
Sit down.
Sit.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Don't drink too much, Guan Chao.
Take good care of Yang Fan.
What's wrong with you both?
It's nothing.
I don't want to talk about it.
Yingzi,
let me take a photo for you.
Sure.
What's wrong with you two?
I want to pick songs.
Move.
Go.
Uh...
I...
Make way.
Hello?
Where are you?
I'm celebrating my birthday
at the karaoke today.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I didn't inform you in advance
and made the arrangements.
It's fine.
I'm quite happy that they are here.
Good.
Did you come out
just to apologize to me?
You're not prepared to tell me
about the email, right?
There's nothing to talk about, then.
Got it.
Happy birthday to you!
Thank you, everyone.
I'm happy you're here.
What wish did you make?
My first wish
is to have a successful career,
earn a lot of money,
and be healthy.
Yingzi, you're so greedy.
You've already made three wishes.
Let Yingzi continue.
My second wish
is that I hope you all can be with me
on my birthday every year.
Of course.
My third wish is
that there are no secrets
between me and the person I love,
and we can be open
and honest with each other.
Done.
That's enough, Jiang Yi.
Stop keeping it a secret.
Take it out already.
Take it out.
Yingzi is getting anxious.
Look, she's getting upset.
A surprise.
Take it out.
Okay.
Here.
What is this?
A surprise.
When we were in the corridor,
I nearly spilled the beans.
Yifei told you to give me this?
Yes.
Yifei is too busy
with her overseas tour.
She asked for my help
to confirm the order.
That was why
I logged into her email account.
It took a long time for it
to finally reach your hands.
Let's take a look.
Okay.
That's a lot.
Look,
overseas special edition.
(Here you go.)
I went to
CD shops all over Hangtian City
before managing to buy this.
Yifei,
I announce
that besides Stefanie Sun,
you're the woman I love the most.
When Stefanie Sun
released albums in the past,
you weren't this anxious.
I didn't win.
When can I
get to attend Stefanie Sun's concert?
Don't be sad.
At least we have her album.
Yifei, I'll redeem my wish.
What is it?
I don't want Stefanie Sun's album.
When we're thirty,
let's attend
Stefanie Sun's concert together.
Sure!
Pinky promise.
So? Do you like them?
You must be elated.
Thank you,
but I don't think you know
that Yifei's promise
wasn't to give me CDs.
This isn't from Yifei.
How could that be?
Urban Village, Jiangzhou Avenue.
Urban Village.
I'm sorry.
I might not
be able to stay for
today's birthday celebration.
Ding Ye found Lan Bin.
I need to go find him.
Yingzi...
Look.
Wait.
Chao and Yang Fan
traveled here from their hometown.
You should at least cut the cake, right?
Yes.
Yang Fan also said
she wants you to give her child a name.
Yes.
We were wondering
what names you'd give to my child.
Hurry, cut the cake.
Cut the cake.
Let's eat the cake first.
Jiang Yi, don't just sit there.
Get the stuff to cut the cake.
Okay, that's enough!
I...
I really don't know
what's wrong with you.
Did I do anything wrong?
You were all there
on the day Lan Bin left, right?
You were there
when Yifei cried for her dad, right?
All the while,
Yifei wanted to find her dad.
You know that well, right?
Now that we've found
Lan Bin,
why are you stopping me?
I really don't get it.
Can you tell me why?
And you, Jiang Yi.
You've been acting strange recently.
Can you explain about
Yifei's email account and the CDs?
What exactly is going on?
Can you all explain?
Yingzi.
Stop! I'm not a fool!
I know you're hiding something from me
just like him.
Fine.
If you're not willing
to tell me the truth,
never mind.
I'll find the truth myself.
Yingzi.
Don't follow me!
Especially you.
Why is Ding Ye causing trouble now?
We can't let Yingzi see Lan Bin.
Both of you stay here.
Jiang Yi and I will stop Yingzi.
Okay.
Yang Fan is pregnant.
You stay with her.
I'll head there with Jiang Yi.
Come on.
Enough!
All of you stay here.
I'll go alone.
Wait for my news.
Ding Ye.
Where is he?
Bring me to him.
Does your friend know
you're looking for her dad?
Yes.
I sent her an email
to tell her about it.
What did she say?
She told me to stop finding him,
but I knew deep down
she wanted me to find her dad.
So no matter what happens,
you must find him?
I must see him.
Everything has been strange recently.
I feel extremely confused.
I think everyone is hiding something
from me.
I must see Lan Bin.
I want to know what happened.
All I want is an answer.
Even if the answer is a nightmare,
you'll still persist?
He's inside.
Thank you.
Mr. Lan.
You are...
Yingzi?
Is it really you?
Yes.
I'm Huang Yingzi.
You still remember me?
Do you remember your daughter,
Lan Yifei?
I'm a scum.
I wronged her.
Over these years,
have you gone to look for Yifei?
I don't have the courage to see her.
I'd rather not know anything!
Stop asking me!
Mr. Lan,
Yifei misses you a lot.
I'm sure she wants to see you.
Yifei might be overseas now,
but she'll come home one day.
You can meet her, then.
Yingzi,
didn't you know?
What?