[Love Endures]
[Episode 14]
Ding Ye. Hey.
Anything else?
I want to return your coat.
Thank you for last time.
You didn't dry clean it?
No, I return it in its original form.
As your agent ,
do you have anything to tell me?
You are quick to get into character.
Come with me somewhere.
Let's go.
Okay. I will call a cab now.
Why the cab?
We are here for the collar coaster.
Not for me.
You can ride it yourself.
I wait for you down here, okay?
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
Well, you are here.
Why can't you join me?
Dude.
I can accompany you
to do anything .
But this
is really out of my depth.
Isn't this a self-punishment?
Forget it.
I'd better go.
Are you afraid of riding roller coasters?
Nonsense.
I think
we should wait for Yifei
and let her decide.
Maybe Yifei
likes this.
Roller coasters are pretty good.
Our goal is to make Yifei happy.
She can ride this
to scream her stress out.
Mingyu, you have a wild preference.
Actually, roller coasters are safe rides.
Due to the conservation of energy,
gravitational potential energy transforms into kinetic energy,
and then vice versa.
Humans' fear of riding it
comes from the sensation of weightlessness.
Speaking of weightlessness...
She is here.
Yifei.
Guan Chao.
What took you so long
to fetch Yifei here?
Yifei...
Maybe I should go home.
I'm not in the mood to play.
Don't go.
We can't let you
stay at home alone.
What do you want to play?
We are with you.
That's right.
How about the carousel?
I think Pirate Ship is more thrilling.
Carousel is more romantic.
The Ferris wheel is good too.
We can enjoy the view.
Sure, the Ferris wheel is a good idea too.
Bumper cars are over there.
Yifei.
Which one do you want to try?
I...
This one.
The roller coaster.
What is wrong?
Why are you laughing?
Nothing.
Because we all want to ride the roller coaster.
Come on.
Let's go.
Where is the queue?
Over here.
Come.
Um... I...
Just so you know,
I'm not riding with you all.
No?
I will never ride that in my whole life.
It is not that scary.
Well, stop forcing her.
Yingzi.
You can wait for us down here.
Sure.
I will wait for you.
But there are five of us.
Is that a problem?
There are two seats in a cart.
How are we going to sit?
You... You can decide for yourselves.
I will sit with Yifei.
Let's go and queue.
I sit with Jiang Yi.
I sit with Mingyu.
I... I will sit on my own.
Zhuang Yuan, I will sit with you.
Wait.
I suddenly remember
the doctor told me
that I keep staring at the computer
and my retinas might detach.
I can't ride on the roller coaster.
It is good.
You can sit with Mingyu.
Let's go.
Is there really something wrong with your retina?
Guess.
I guess it is fake.
You were lying.
Zhuang Yuan can ride it even with a high myopia.
Why can't you?
Why would I lie to you?
I don't know .
Maybe you just dare not ride the roller coaster,
but you pretend otherwise.
Fine.
When you are ready
to ride roller coasters,
I will accompany you.
What if...
What if I never dare ride it?
I won't ride it either.
So, has his retina detached?
No.
He has eyes like a hawk's.
So he was afraid?
No.
Then why did he stay with you?
Everyone went for the ride
while I was alone. Poor me.
He is my friend.
Of course, he would stay with me .
Am I not pitiful?
You want me to ride alone?
Are you not my friend?
Well...
Why do you insist on having me ride with you?
Are you scared to ride alone?
What is there to scare?
I just don 't want to sit with a stranger.
Please check for me.
Am I all right?
Yes.
Is this safe?
Yes, very safe.
Check again for me.
Is it all right?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Do I need to tie my hair?
No, it is fine.
What... What about my necklace?
You are asking too much.
I'm not scared. I'm not nervous.
Because roller coasters are very safe.
Due to the conservation of energy,
its speed is lower than driving cars.
Can you stop?
I'm nervous if I don't talk.
I'm scared.
I will try my best
not to shout later.
Ready.
Three, two, one.
Are you all right?
Can you walk?
You were scared,
but you insisted on taking the ride.
What for?
Near-death experience.
Are you afraid of death?
Yes, of course.
Why?
I'm afraid
that I can't meet my family and friends.
I haven't had a chance
to do many things.
Also,
I'm afraid of missing out on the person I like
if I die.
It means you are a blessed person.
Because you have so many things you can't let go of.
You sound like
nothing in this world can keep you.
Is there anything in this world
worth staying for?
There's certainly a lot.
There are many beautiful things in this world.
If there is something that keeps you ,
you will realize
that you won't give up so easily
in the face of illness, suffering, and death.
You seem to have an interest in this topic.
No.
You brought this up.
I'm just following along.
You saw it.
The bucket list.
So the list is real?
Yes.
Sorry.
I didn't mean to pry into your secret.
That day...
Since you know it is a secret,
you should pretend that you know nothing about it.
Don't worry.
I assure you that your secret is safe with me.
I won't tell a soul.
When I was young,
I always dreamed of meeting you one day.
I would like to see the person
who wrote such novels.
Finally, my wish has come true.
I met you.
But I didn't expect something like this to happen.
I feel sorry.
You shouldn't be sorry.
You should be happy.
Because you met me at the perfect time.
If it were a little later,
you wouldn't have met me.
I'm quite interested in the things
on your bucket list,
I can complete them with you.
Out of sympathy?
How could that be?
What is it, then?
Like I told you.
I'm also interested in the things
on your bucket list.
Since you are going to accomplish them alone,
why not I join you?
Tell me if there is a place you want to go.
I will go with you.
- Keep your word. - Certainly.
Why?
Do you want another ride?
Let's go.
Wait.
Help me up.
Are you all right?
No.
Hello, Mom.
Yuan.
I couldn't reach you on the phone.
So I called Tianlin.
He said you weren't staying in the dorm these days.
What has happened?
Where are you staying?
Don't scare me.
I... I will come to see you.
Mom, I stay at Jiang Yi's place.
Jiang Yi rented a big house.
It is better than the dorm.
All right.
It is quite good that you stay at his place.
You can have a good chat with him.
What is Jiang Yi doing now?
I want to talk to him.
He is out to work overtime.
He hasn't come back yet.
Well, Mom.
I will hang up.
I'm working on my thesis.
Bye-bye.
Why didn't you answer my call?
Answer me.
Now is working hours.
I don't want to talk about this.
Fine.
I know you are still angry.
I mishandled the incident of Yue Tong .
I apologize.
Fine.
Tell me, then.
Are you apologizing
because you think you are wrong,
or are you trying to please me?
It doesn't matter.
The things that matter are
we have a common goal to accomplish.
What goal ?
Using others as your stepping stone?
This is your goal,
not mine.
Guo Kai.
I think we need to spend some time apart.
Please come in.
Are you discussing something?
Yes.
We are done.
I have sorted out these materials for you.
The plot lines and character analysis
of "The Maze".
I have listed everything
for your reference.
Aside from the three novels,
Ding Ye published another seven articles.
I believe three of them
are related to "The Maze".
I have attached them to it.
You can refer to them.
Why are you giving me that look?
Did I say anything wrong?
Where did you go yesterday?
Amusement park.
With whom?
Ding Ye.
He wanted me to ride the roller coaster with him.
Did you do so?
Yes.
You used to be scared,
but now you are not.
Because of Ding Ye?
Jiang Yi, please listen to me.
Here's the thing...
Huang Yingzi.
In what identity
are you talking to me now?
A friend
or Ding Ye's agent?
Are these two identities contradicting?
Of course.
Don't you find yourself
overly concerned about him?
You were so nervous
when he just coughed a little.
It's not like he is dying.
Touch wood !
Don't be so harsh.
Talking about death doesn't sound good.
My words are harsh.
What about him?
Yes, he speaks harshly too.
In fact, I used to think the same as you.
I thought he was strange
and difficult to get along with.
But now I realize
his life is tough.
What do you mean?
Why tough?
He is not the only one who has a tough life.
I don't know how to explain it to you.
Because
- this concerns his privacy... - You don't have to.
I couldn't care less
about his privacy.
Jiang Yi.
(The higher-ups are considering)
the candidates
for the deputy general manager.
But in yesterday's meeting,
I proposed a new candidate.
Who do you think
this new candidate is?
The person you are talking about
is me?
Excellent. As expected of my aide.
Although your current rank is a director,
that is not a problem.
I have already applied to the company
to give you a promotion.
Mingyu, you have been here for eight years.
I believe the Mingyu I know
won't back off
when such an opportunity arrives.
Thank you so much, Mr. Feng.
All right.
You should
get ready for this.
I'm very confident
about my choice.
So you should be more confident
in yourself.
Hello.
Hello, Jiang.
I need your help.
Just how big the conflict is
that made you decide to move here.
Jiang, you are here.
I would rather stay here
than see his face every day.
Come on in and sit.
What do you want me to do ?
I don't want my mom to worry about me.
So I told her I was staying at your place.
When you get home later,
please send her some pictures.
That will put her mind at ease.
Also,
if she video calls you,
tell her I'm on my campus.
Sure, I can do that.
But are you sure
you can focus on your thesis here?
The environment here isn't as good as the dorm.
But this place is quiet.
I bet it is.
It only happens sometimes.
All right. Let's go.
Why?
Move to my place.
I'm not going.
I don't want to be your hassle.
I used to copy your homework back then.
I was once your hassle too.
Jiang...
Enough. Stop dawdling.
Pack your things now.
Are you sure this won't be your trouble?
Yes.
But you have to keep a secret for me.
What secret?
(I think I have been to this neighborhood before.)
It seems familiar.
Isn't this where Yingzi stays?
You two
are living together?
Shut it.
Keep walking.
Put your things down first.
Look at this.
Can you see
the warm yellow light opposite us?
Isn 't that...
This is the secret you have to keep for me.
(Sorry.)
(The subscriber you have dialed...)
(Are you still angry?)
(I can accompany you anywhere you want.)
(Hello ?)
(Jiang Yi, don't you ghost me.)
You ignore me.
I will ignore you too.
No wonder you never told me where you live.
Well, this is a coincidence.
When I was planning
to find a job in Jiangzhou,
the housing agent told me
this apartment is pretty good...
Jiang Yi.
Look into my eyes.
How many years have I known you?
Twenty-four years.
I have known you for 24 years.
Do you think I can' t tell
if you lie?
You are so stubborn.
I feel tired for you.
To be frank,
Yingzi and I are like
two planets on different orbits.
There is always a distance between us.
Yes, I can stay by her side.
But I feel like
I can never get close to her.
Physically speaking,
if a planet
reduces its speed,
the centripetal force changes,
it may change its orbit.
Excellent.
You really are so excellent.
Only you
will answer my question
in a serious manner .
That's why we are friends.
However, Jiang,
you should change
your speed.
Otherwise,
both of you will never meet.
Ding Ye.
What is next on the bucket list?
The next one...
One moment.
Visit the aquarium at deep night.
Okay, let's do it now.
Tonight?
Tonight, I...
Are you calling it quits
just after the first thing?
Do you have the spirit of the deal?
No, it is not that.
Forget it.
I will go myself.
I will go.
I will go with you.
No rush.
The aquarium closes at 8 PM.
Don't come too early.
What a relief.
I can rest assured
of seeing you both together.
You can take care of each other.
Zhuang Yuan
only knows about studying.
He doesn't know how to take care of himself at all.
Jiang Yi, please keep an eye on him.
Don't worry, madam.
All right, Mom.
We are not young kids anymore.
Okay, I won't nag.
I'll leave you guys to it.
See you, madam.
Bye.
Finally, this is settled.
Do you have an extra bed sheet?
I want to lay it on the sofa.
Sleep in my bed.
How can that be?
I'm already a hassle to you.
It is fine.
Actually, I always stay up late to work on my game.
It is convenient for me to sleep on the sofa.
No need to be so courteous.
I'm not.
How about this?
I will pay you half of the rental.
You are still a student.
How are you going to pay?
All right.
Don't stand on ceremony.
You can pay me back
once you make big money.
I'm like a freeloader.
How about
buying me some beer?
Finally, you came.
The aquarium is closed.
Perfect timing.
Come on.
Is it okay if we go in like this?
Everything is arranged.
Marine life has excellent hearing.
Visitors swamp this place during the day,
which causes disturbance to them.
Only at night,
when everything quiets down,
it is the best time to observe them.
So you chose
to come here at this hour.
Now is their calmest
and freest moment.
Hello. We meet again.
Do you think this ray
looks like a emoji on QQ?
What is wrong?
Do you think
the fish would reckon the aquarium as their home
after spending so much time here?
Possible.
Some of them are born in the aquarium.
The birthplace
is considered their home.
I disagree with that.
I believe every fish
has a concept of the ocean.
Maybe they want to go home,
back to the ocean.
(I told you)
there was no whale in the aquarium.
This place is too small for it.
This is Indo-Pacific sergeant .
Golden trevally.
And Verduya's hap.
Tuwei!
Hello, Jiang Yi.
Nice to meet you, Jiang Yi.
It looks like you, right?
This is ugly.
Come, look at this.
This shark is known as
nurse shark.
It is the most submissive
and mildest shark in the world.
How do you know so much?
Although there is no aquarium in Hangtian City,
it has a bookstore.
I often read about them.
Then why don't we just read books?
The difference between books and real creatures
is the difference between our IQs.
Understood?
Fine.
What is this?
This is ray,
also known as devil fish.
Devil fish?
It reminds me of the emojis on QQ,
Silly and Grumpy.
Well, I can see why it is grumpy.
But why is it silly?
It is over here.
I bite you.
I'm that shark.
What is wrong with you?
You have been silent since we left the aquarium.
Was it not fun?
It is not that.
The aquarium is too beautiful.
Let me see what is next on the list.
Sing "My Sun" in the bathhouse.
Dude, I really can't help you with this.
You make a copy of it.
Yeah.
In case I miss out on something.
I don't want the chance to slip off.
Are you not curious
why I have a bucket list?
That is your privacy.
If you don't want to say,
I won't ask.
But I know
why you wanted to visit the aquarium at night.
Why?
Your first novel is
"The Man Who Dreams of Whales".
So I suppose you love the ocean.
But the nearest place to the ocean in this city
is the aquarium.
It is a shame that there is no whale there.
And I suppose
you don't want to see a confined whale.
Whales belong to the ocean.
Yes.
I looked up online before.
There was once an aquarium
that tried to keep whales,
but they failed.
Because whales can't carry on
when they lose their freedom.
They are creatures of character, unlike humans.
Yeah.
You like the ocean
and movies.
I bet you like to watch
"The Big Blue".
Is there any connection between them?
This is just my guess.
I'm always emotionally overwhelmed
when watching this movie.
So, are you the type
who forcefully introduces your favorite movie
to others?
Yeah.
I have five friends
whom I grew up with.
Some like to watch sports,
some like animations,
and some like doing homework.
Hence, we always
argued about
our weekend activities.
At this time,
I would make everyone
watch a movie with me.
What did you watch?
There are many movies I like.
Films by Wong Kar -wai,
Lee Chang-dong,
and Shunji Iwai.
Which Shunji Iwai movies do you like?
"Picnic".
How special.
Normally, girls prefer "Love Letter"
or "April Story".
"Picnic"
may seem
like a dark movie ,
but to me,
it is a warm story.
The female lead is mentally ill.
But she has a friend
who always keeps her company,
no matter how the story ends,
whether it leads to the ocean
or death.
I used to imagine all of us
staying in the same city and often eating together
after graduation
just like what we did when we were kids.
But then I realized it wasn't realistic.
We all work in different places
and have partners.
Do you really think it is like "Friends"?
To be honest,
I have never expected
to be your housemate.
Besides, we are next to Yingzi's place.
Do you remember the last time
you went to the aquarium?
When I was in my senior year
in Jiangzhou.
It has been a long time.
With that childhood friend of yours?
During our time together,
I have found myself
doing things
I haven't done in a long time.
Sometimes, I wonder
if I'm in the present
or back in my childhood.
It was fun to do the same thing with the same group of people
when we were kids.
But it becomes less fun after we grow up.
Perhaps it is us who become less fun
as we grow older.
Thank you so much.
These days
often takes me back
to the days
I spent with my childhood friends.
Even though we have done many meaningless things,
I'm happy.
I have arrived home.
I will get going.
Huang Yingzi.
Throughout your life,
have you ever lost someone important ?
I did.
At the age of 18,
I said goodbye to him.
Back in that time,
I never thought of saying goodbye
would mean losing him.
But later, I realized
bidding goodbye
means the last farewell to many people.
Even if they meet again,
they can never return to where they used to be.
Whatever you lose
will come back to you in another way.
Do you believe in this?
I did.
However, now I fault.
I'm the exact opposite.
I used to doubt it,
but now I begin to believe it.
Why?
No reason.
Being able
to meet a lost friend
means you're lucky.
I'm off.
(Whatever you lose)
(will come back to you in another way. )
Being able
to meet a lost friend
means you're lucky.
Shall we start now?
Do you think you are a pessimist?
You could say that.
During the time with you,
I discovered
that you have experienced many strange things.
Being a taxi driver,
serving as a waiter in the restaurant,
reading poems aloud at the dating corner,
and even visiting the aquarium late at night.
Everything you have done
give me an impression
that you are an exploratory optimist.
Have you ever read " The Myth of Sisyphus"?
What do you think
about Sisyphus rolling the boulder up a hill every day?
Perpetual
and without any purpose.
But why does he seem to enjoy it so much
in Camus's narrative?
In my opinion,
perhaps he simply enjoys
the rolling process,
just like you,
You did those things because you enjoyed them.
Right?
I did enjoy them.
But I believe if Sisyphus were given options,
he would definitely not choose to roll the boulder up a hill.
Is there anything else in this world, in your opinion,
worth trying?
Nothing.
I have experienced
family and friendship.
Except for love relationships.
That's why you don't believe in love?
Not all things are certain.
What about you?
What do you think of love ?
I'm interviewing you.
Why the other way around now?
Can't I interview you?
Just a casual chat.
Well, you can.
However, I have already
sent my love relationship away.
Is it
Jiang Yi?
What do you think is the difference between a friend and a lover,
or
between a friendship and a love relationship?
Love means mutual destruction.
When you are in love with someone,
you will have to enter their life.
(Selfishness, ignorance,)
(cowardice, softness, kindness, and generosity,)
(all of these qualities will be laid bare.)
(Your true self will have to face a trial.)
(Still, this is also an excellent opportunity)
(to know yourself deeper.)
(But friendship is different.)
(Friendship won't lead to mutual destruction.)
(No matter how close you are,)
(there is always a distance between you both.)
(Sometimes far and sometimes near.)
(You wouldn't pull your friend)
(into your own life.)
So
friends walk shoulder to shoulder?
While lovers stand head to head.
So, what is the result
when you and Jiang Yi face each other head-on?
The rain hasn't stopped yet.
I forgot to bring an umbrella.
I never brought one with me.
Because I will always lose it.
Why do people always lose their umbrellas?
Because rain stops eventually.
When the rain stops,
they won't need an umbrella.
Do you think you can find
the lost umbrella?
It doesn't matter.
The moment you lose the umbrella,
it is meant
for the next person who finds it.
Aren't you my godsend?
Come.
The rain is heavy.
The umbrella can't shelter us.
Your head is big.
My head is smaller than yours.
You never fit in my hats
since we were little.
Fine.
Take this.
Why do you have two umbrellas?
I picked it somewhere.
You don't want this?
Give it back.
I want it,
of course.
Did you really pick this up?
Yeah.
Give it back to me if you don't want it.
It is too late.
The umbrella is now mine.
Where did you
pick this umbrella from?
A bubble tea place.
Speaking from your experience,
how much time is needed
to draw this whale?
If waterproof glue is used,
it is around three to five days.
How did you know about the waterproof glue?
Oh, please.
This is an umbrella.
How come the whale is missing an eye?
Let me see.
Is it?
The eyes
are here.
Why are you so nervous?
It was a mistake.
This person chose to paint the whale
on a transparent umbrella.
I suppose he must have hope
that the whale could be seen at once
when the umbrella was open.
I think
the painter
must be very gentle.
The whale is drawn so beautifully.
He must be talented and handsome.
Why are you smiling?
I didn't.
You did smile.
No.
You smirked.
I didn't.
You heard that wrong.
You did.
I did not.
Why did you smile?
I didn't.
Care to share?
I didn't smile.