MANTI
Hi
The high autumn is refreshing.
For a year, Wutong Middle School
the students are looking forward to
the most stressful activity.
Autumn trip.
Dear teachers,
the most important thing
is to ensure the safety of the students.
We have to make sure that
as many people come back.
You hear? Because every year,
get hurt and get lost every year.
and sneaked out to play games.
It's not a big deal for parents to blame.
What if they report it to the Education Bureau?
Oh no, it's all over.
Mr. Tan, why are you choking?
Chili.
Mr. Tan, where are you from?
You have such a strong taste?
No, I didn't put it.
It's obvious that your students gave it to you.
Fight with poison and cool down.
That's enough.
The hat I'm sending now
Don't take it off before the event ends today.
Do you hear me?
Because when you wear this hat,
in the park,
When the students look away,
this is our teacher.
They won't dare to act recklessly.
Sergeant Guo,
Why is there a phone number on this hat?
If I go out for one day,
my WeChat will be exposed.
What are you complaining about? Who abused you?
Isn't that easy for everyone to remember?
Right?
When we get there
the first activity is
the real shooting battle of the class group.
You can form your own teams.
Two classes in a group.
Let's play together.
You can form your own team.
Can we play against Class 18?
Sure.
What for?
There are many boys in your class. It's fun to fight.
What? Are you scared?
Dream on.
I'm afraid you'll lose badly.
Stop.
You two are very motivated.
You two can form a team.
Okay.
It's almost time.
The head teacher will organize students to get in the car.
Let me remind you one last thing.
The most important thing in the car is to count the number.
We didn't order in the beginning.
After the event,
it's even more impossible to order all of them.
Remember, never.
Don't let the students go home
after the event.
Yes.
24 25 26
27 28 29 30
You can go up directly.
You don't have to wait here.
I want more people.
I'm ordering.
It's okay. I'm good at math.
Don't move.
Stop running around.
Did I count you?
Don't go to the toilet. We're leaving.
If you don't cooperate,
you can't go anywhere today.
I won't leave if I can't count people.
I'll deduct one in the group chat.
Buckle one. Buckle one.
Okay.
This is the group chat.
Pull me up.
You think too much.
Wait, the one who forms the pesticide will roll in the back.
The one on the left in the front of the werewolves
Leave the front to the one who got carsick.
I have carsickness pills and plastic bags.
You can come to me if you need.
I have a card.
Come to me if you want to play.
If you win, you can skip one day of homework.
It sounds like we're going to do it.
Are you imitating a spicy teacher?
It's too late to be hypocritical.
No one is sitting with you
Ms. Song, isn't there a seat over there?
I saw you lonely
I'm not.
You were dilly-dallying down there.
Are you afraid
when you get in the car?
I need to look at the board.
There's no one sitting beside.
The tag is quite stable.
It's activated. Hurry up and fasten your seat belt.
Rule 7 of Growing Worries.
A group activity makes a group of people happy.
and let the other know
how lonely they are.
I miss this feeling.
It's the same as the previous autumn outing.
Will we not let us in if we go like this?
The amusement park is not booked.
It doesn't matter.
Then I'll pretend to meet Tan Shu Tong
and look familiar with her.
and impressed her students.
It's the weekend.
We've been wanting to watch
Chen as a teacher. Perfect.
Of course, Tan Shu Tong.
What did I hear?
Wei, to be honest,
what happened between you and Tan Shu Tong
what happened between you and Tan Shu Tong?
Shu Tong.
Where have you been these years?
To me,
you are like
that mathematicians can't solve.
It lingers in my heart
Looks like I missed a big show.
You didn't miss anything.
Let's go.
I haven't finished packing the snacks.
Do it yourself.
Guys,
We're going to take class
in the real shooting battle.
Put your bags down later.
Let's wait for our opponent, okay?
What?
Class 18!
Are you kidding me?
Yes, our opponent
is the Class 18 led by Ms. Tan and her.
Why? Isn't it Class 2?
What's there to fight with Class 1?
Yeah.
Are they going to study?
Listen to me.
Be polite when we go in.
They are all girls.
Although we use colour,
we can't beat them up.
Do you hear me?
It's not about being polite.
Look at them.
You don't even know the rules, do you?
Yes, he'll explode himself later.
Sir, I quit.
Let me do my homework.
Tan Shu Tong, what do you mean?
So what?
This isn't a physical test.
Exactly. Why do you look down on me?
It's just a shooting game. Everyone can do it.
Right.
Class 1-1
Why not?
Just kidding.
Class 1, kindergarten?
This is a group operation.
It's not like we win by brute force.
We need strategies.
Sihao is right.
Do you have any idea?
We have Seok Da, the military genius.
We have seven sets of loyal fans.
He can make us
a military strategic that can defeat 100.
Is it okay?
It's not impossible.
Watch carefully.
One hour later,
the team with more members will win.
Each team
has a leader's sleeve badge.
If the leader is out,
the whole team will fail.
Do you hear me, Wu Yichen?
Say no more.
Just watch me kill everyone.
Be polite.
You are Team A.
Remember, you are Team C.
Cover.
You are Team D.
You're in charge of cooperation, right?
Yes.
That sounds like it.
Come on.
There are ants.
Forget what I said.
Has it started?
Right?
Aren't we covering up?
Who?
It should be the vanguard.
I remember Chae Sihao said
near the river.
Where is the river?
What happened?
You got shot.
What do you mean?
Am I eliminated?
I think so.
Oh my god.
This is too simple.
It's so simple that it's boring.
This won't do. Has it started?
It started. Didn't you hear the whistle?
No one says whistle is the beginning.
What else do you want?
Do you want to hear the broadcast?
It's only been three seconds.
We haven't found the location yet.
This is cheating.
Sister, this is how you play the game.
How can you say it in the real war?
Wait. to find a hidden place before we start?
What are you doing?
Then you're dead too.
You're already dead.
How can you be revived?
When the war is real,
I can use my last bit of strength to take revenge.
It's poisonous, isn't it?
Is there a referee here?
Someone here doesn't even know the rules.
Yes.
Oh my god.
Clear.
Keep up.
No ambush.
Forward.
Go!
Get ready to join Team C.
According to the plan, they should be nearby.
They're nearby.
Where?
Sam, I've set up a gun line for you.
Go ahead.
Taek, keep an eye on the cover of 330 southeast.
Leave the rest to me.
What's going on?
Didn't you say there was no ambush?
It's said on TV.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Go away.
Taek.
You're way worse than when you were eating chicken.
That's right. What the hell did you hit?
Enough!
There aren't many of them left.
Okay.
You guys continue. I'm going down.
That's all.
She's a genius.
Did we give her the task?
No, I remember she was in Team A.
Forget it. She's a good judge.
I'll leave this to her. Let's go.
I have something to tell you.
I forgot to ask your name last time in front of the bathroom.
Who are you?
I...
Zhong Wan Zhen.
You don't know me?
Last time you said...
Forget it.
It's better if you don't remember.
I remember now.
In front of the toilet.
I remember that day,
you tricked Chen Jia Qian.
What did you say your name was?
Zhong Wan Zhen. How do you write it?
What are you doing?
Don't do anything stupid.
I saw your
your answer cards.
It doesn't matter.
Just say it if you want to.
You don't want me to report you, right?
Shouldn't you
let you win?
Sure.
I just want to ask who has the flag.
The gun is so heavy.
Are you hurt?
Ms. Song.
Lin Lu.
Mr. Song, Ronghao.
Why are you two alone?
If it weren't for us,
both of us would have died.
The vanguard is dead.
You'll come with us later.
and cover us.
But we work together.
Be flexible, understand?
We can't find Team C now.
I think it's already decided.
Don't change.
Otherwise, it will be messy.
It's already messed up.
Plan B now.
Listen to me.
Coming.
You go there first.
When they go behind the tree,
when they go behind the tree.
Go.
Go!
Why am I the first?
You're the first.
But you're the team leader.
Hurry up. They're coming.
I'll die if I go out.
That's why it's called cover.
Why didn't you go first?
I'm the last.
How can I go to the front?
I shouldn’t have let Lin Lu be the team leader.
No one was convinced.
The blue team leader is dead.
The game is over.
I announce that there are 28 members left in the green team.
There's one left in the blue team.
The green team wins.
It's too easy. It's not difficult at all.
You know what?
That woman lost, but she's still cheating.
I'm speechless.
No one is coming.
They were playing cards.
But they didn't even hand out the cards and ended it.
Let me tell you the most exaggerated thing.
Someone is trying to wash the paint by the river.
We're laughing to death.
Sister Han, I'm so scared. Protect me.
So fierce.
Do you regret it now?
What did you say?
You lost and you're still denying it.
I'll hate you to death looking at your students.
What do you know? That's what I want.
Meeting here at 6 p.m.
Next is free time.
Have you got your lunch vouchers?
Okay, dismiss.
Be careful.
Is there anything else you want to play?
I'm fine with anything.
I want to play that.
I want to play that too. Let's go.
What about you?
I want to eat sausages.
Shall we go buy some first?
It's over there too.
Sure.
Let's go.
Take it. Go.
That one.
Why are you alone, Lin Lu?
Chinese book.
No way, Lin Lu. Look at the Chinese book.
It's free time now.
Can't you read?
Fine.
Remember,
The vast world is the structure of upper and lower.
I've already remembered it.
It's full of bad luck and bad luck.
Is this all you have?
I'm not hungry.
Feng and Tang are old and Li Guang are hard to get.
Do you want these fries?
No, thanks.
There are no holy potatoes in Changsha.
No one wins.
No winner.
I'll sing a song
Ms Song, let me carry it myself
I'm just reminding you
Why are you alone?
My luck is not in sync and my life is hard.
Feng and Tang are old and Li Guang are hard to be conferred.
There's no master without Jia Yi in Changsha.
Go ahead.
I won't take the exam anyway.
No
I haven't learned the content of 12th grade yet.
What are you doing here?
Who knows?
What if you pick all the tests we don't know?
Don't worry.
What's next?
You'll know when you meet him.
It's useless to prepare in advance.
How can you calculate students?
This...
There is no such rule in the class.
Miss, is anyone here?
Tan Shu Tong, what a coincidence!
What a destined encounter.
Isn't it only Wu Di?
Why are you here?
We haven't been to the amusement park for a long time.
Last time it was the autumn outing in sophomore year.
Right, you were here too.
Speaking of which, the autumn outing in 12th grade is really...
The bass sat on Feixiang to catch couples.
He punished us to copy 30000 words on the spot.
but we didn't get anything.
Right.
Catch a couple.
It wasn't me.
Yang Hai insisted on catching us.
to give Wu Di a surprise.
We were all caught.
I still remember
the love poem Yang Hai wrote.
Let me revise the scene for you.
Dear Di
I remember when we first met,
you were like a basketball basket.
It's the only direction in my eyes
You're like a black storm
in my life.
Before I met you,
I was just a lonely caterpillar.
After meeting you,
I finally broke my cocoon and became a butterfly.
and fly with you.
Baby, the sea I love you
How do you remember it so clearly?
I can't remember a word in the textbook.
I can't forget such things.
Honestly, Wu Di,
when I saw you that day, you were still in grade 12.
I knelt down.
How long have you been together?
Five or six years.
One, two, three.
It's longer than all the girlfriends I've dated.
We're an old couple.
Are you jealous, Wei?
Let me treat you to something.
What do you want?
I'll go with you.
You're really a girl group member.
I want double-fried bacon rice.
I want half-fried egg and heart-fluttering.
Half fatty pork.
Stand up.
Come with me.
Where's Wei?
I can do whatever I want.
Your friend Lin...
Dog.
I didn't think
Is there something wrong with his eyes?
It's rare that you don't go to play.
It's too hot.
It's better to get some air.
I'm too traumatized in this haunted house.
Forget it.
I guess Song Chen is inside too.
We haven't seen him all morning.
I don't think he's in the mood.
He insisted on fighting
in the morning.
But we lost so badly.
Song Chen and Class 18
Class 1 and Class 18.
Little Sheep versus Gosla.
I was convinced.
Mr. Tan, I'm Chen Jia Qian.
Chen Jia Qian.
What's wrong?
Long Yihan is missing.
Missing? What do you mean?
We entered the haunted house together.
We got separated in the dark.
But we've been out for half an hour.
She hasn't come out yet.
Her phone is off too.
Is she lost inside?
Please wait for her.
But this haunted house is not big.
And I'm a little worried about her.
What's wrong with her?
Her parents scolded her
because of dropping out.
Wasn't expelled settled?
I don't know what her parents said.
She looks pale.
Are you still in the haunted house?
I'll be right there.
What's wrong?
A student in my class is missing.
I need to find him.
I'll go with you.
Boss.
I'll do it 50 times first.
Okay.
50 times.
You like this?
Isn't this a hobby?
It's not a hobby.
Then what is it?
It's a punishment.
It's quite accurate.
In the shooting battle today,
If I can defeat
I can defeat all of Class 18.
We'll win!
It's all because of my poor skills
because of my poor skills.
Our class lost 27 people from Class 18.
Your shot is not the only difference.
Is the smart brain so strange?
Boss give me 50 times
Okay put it here
Look at me.
(What kind of spider is my biggest fear?)
What is human network?
QQ space from ancient times?
We are in the same class. Can't we give a discount?
I've transferred my WeChat to you. I'm leaving.
Is there any other information in it?
Like her dark history.
And a encrypted photo album.
If you break it, you have to pay for it.
Why do you look like a salesman?
Do you want me to get a card next?
I'm coming. Let's go.
It's too late. It's more suspicious to retreat now.
Who's that?
Oh no, my brother.
Why is he here?
Jia Qian.
Brother, why are you here?
Have you found Long Yiyi?
No.
She hasn't come out since she entered the haunted house.
Hello, I'm a teacher at Wutong Middle School.
I lost a student in the haunted house.
Can you stop the project
and find him first?
I'm afraid it won't work.
There are more than ten haunted houses.
There are at least 100 tourists
There are at least 100 people.
It's troublesome to evacuate.
And I don't have the right.
What should I do?
Can you inform the staff
to see if there are similar high school students
Most of them
are basically middle school students.
Let's split up and look for them.
Go in.
Forget it if you don't want to go in.
Question.
Of course. Let's go.
Sir, you can't use flashlight in haunted house.
This will affect other game experiences.
And ghosts will be swayed.
There's really a ghost.
It must be the staff.
Teacher
This is my last bag of balloons.
How about giving others a chance?
Okay.
Pick any gift you like.
Boss, I want that demon-out doll.
That's for the shooting machine across the street.
in the shooting machine.
How many points do you want to vote?
That's a grand prize. Five thousand points.
5,000? You think she's an iron arm?
It can't be helped.
How many points can you get in that game?
It depends on personal level.
Normally, 200 points.
I'll play ten times first.
Okay.
Thank you.
You really want to play?
Is there anything special about that doll?
I want to give it to Cheong.
This is her favorite anime character.
Her birthday is coming.
Can you play?
I got full marks in three steps of high school entrance exam.
This is different from three-step shooting.
This basket is so close.
Is the ball too big?
Why did it pop out?
You'll get at most 20 points in one round.
You can't finish it even if it gets dark.
Forget it.
Let me show you something.
What are you waiting for?
What's wrong with them?
Where are they?
I went to the toilet
How many days have I not eaten vegetables
It's been so long
But they both disappeared.
Could it be...
I have a feeling.
Today's progress will be very fast.
Hurry up. Take the food and follow him.
What's wrong?
Something grabbed me just now.
Then why don't you walk ahead of me?
I told you not to act tough.
Aren't you afraid of the dark?
I thought it wasn't that scary after a few years.
You overestimated yourself.
What was that?
Let's go.
I suspect you hit the ghost.
Mr. Tan.
It's me.
What's wrong?
I suddenly remembered
Ryne said she left her coat at the shooting range.
Maybe she went to look for it.
Really? Let's go and take a look.
Get out of here.
Why is this amusement park so big
We've been walking for a long time.
but I didn't see anyone.
We didn't make it to a project.
I think we're a bit stupid.
Found it!
Over there
Ms Song
Why don't you take a rest and let me invest?
Forget it. It's a waste of money.
You should think about how to thank me.
Why don't you help me guide some students?
Is there anyone as simple and easy as you?
Please introduce him to me.
Oh.
Why are you here
We're here to watch Ms. Song's live lesson. No.
Don't disturb the audience
and affect my image in front of my classmates.
Lin Lu, they are my high school classmates.
You came at the right time.
I’ll assign you some tasks.
Lin Lu, this is Lin Gou.
In high school, he was famous for being tall and thin.
Wu Di, her boyfriend is a professional.
Poacher.
He's also a supernatural sailor.
Why did my style change?
AN MA
Cut the crap
I'm in a hurry to win the prize for the students.
Hurry up. Just start.
Spend 200 yuan for shooting here.
I’m sure we’re idiots.
What do you think, Lin Lu?
Wow, so many people win a doll for you.
Thank you.
Can we go now?
We haven't played anything yet.
Okay, I haven't played either.
Let's go.
Do you want to come with us?
Do you choose red?
OK.
Come on, Linlu!
Go that way.
Ms. Song
Ms. Song is so nervous.
Long Yiyi.
Long Yihan.
Why is it so messy here?
It's different from the morning.
Calm down.
How can I not?
We'll gather soon.
Maybe she'll go to the meeting place first.
This spider is worth it.
Did you put my coat?
It's right across her.
Perfect.
Isn't that Long's jacket?
Are you going there?
Your wound can't get wet now.
But I think she's over there.
How could a girl
put her coat so far away?
And think about it.
haunted house, spiders,
They're all things you're afraid of.
Don't you think those students are messing with you?
What if she really takes things too hard?
I said so much in front of her parents.
What if I really stimulate her?
I don't think there's a high chance of that.
I'll go.
Wait.
Your wound is like this now.
How are you going to get there?
I know you're blaming yourself.
But it's not entirely your fault.
If you want to find her,
you should inform the school and the amusement park.
to help us find them.
And I think they are probably
they're probably playing tricks on you.
According to my previous attitude,
I deserve it even if they want to mess with me.
Don't be so stubborn.
Even if you find them
and find them,
they won't accept you right away.
I know.
It's not easy for Class 18 to trust you.
Maybe because there are too many teachers like me.
I don't expect to be a teacher like my dad.
But if I don't make up for what I did wrong,
I won't let myself go.
I've made up my mind.
whether I can be a teacher or not,
I won't resign
I won't resign.
If you insist on going,
I'll carry you.
Hello?
Ms. Tan, this is Long Yiyi.
Long Yihan, where are you?
I'm not feeling well, so I'm going home.
I'm home now.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
That's good.
Take a good rest.
She's fine.
That's good.
Let me help you.
Cheong, I won this shot. This is for you.
Gosh, I love this.
Lu Lu, you're so nice.
Yu Meng asked me to give her this position.
I'll sit in the front.
Sorry, Lu Lu.
Let's go on a spring outing together next time.
Ms. Song
Did your friends leave?
They left first.
I heard that you live in the same building.
The four of us live together.
Can high school classmates be so close?
Of course.
Actually, every autumn trip,
every autumn trip.
But today,
I feel like I really went on a autumn trip.
You should have.
Ms. Song, my arm is about to get a job injury
You are so relaxed
really got into a good university?
Lin Lu, actually we didn't.
I want to be like this too.
He's good at studying and playing.
I have many friends.
Can you teach me how to become such a person?
Did you send the doll?
Lin Lu,
I’ll teach you the first thing.
You don't have to force yourself to make friends.
If you don't meet someone with the same goal,
learn to get along with yourself first.
The 7th rule of growth.
As Song Chen said,
are all here.
So tired?
How dare you say that?
I didn't do anything. I only shot for you.
This exercise is as strong as military training, Chen.
What's going on, Tan Shutong?
It's because of Class 18.
Wei, your sister is so cruel.
Didn't they say Class 18 is quite gentle?
I guess I was overthinking.
Let me do it.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Ms. Song, this is Yang Zhouming.
Hello.
My kid attended an event during the autumn trip today.
and got hurt by Class 18.
They should be responsible for this.
Read
ETHE
Over there
Really?
Really
RETHE
Let me ask you.
Hello, Ms. Song, this is Seok Da's mom.
What happened?
He said he was hit by Class 18 today.
He sprained his leg.
No.
He's fine on the school bus.
Yes.
Hello?
(Hello?) Hello.
Yu Xiao Qing's mother.
The shooting game is not that serious.
But...
Fine.
I'll ask him now.
Okay.
Is this part of your plan?
Class 18 is so mean. Can you bear it?
What do you mean? Get it back.
We can't just let it go.
I think I've lost my mind.
Ban Jin Peng as the delivery man.
Liu Zhiqiang as Qin Miaomiao's father
Yenhua Wang as Auntie Song Chen
Yang Shuqiu as Auntie Song Chen
Jiang Yi as a volunteer
Song Xiangyu as the courier
King Qin Xiu Ping will be born.
Zhang Haotian, Peng Zibo, Yang Yanqian, Lin Jialong.
Huang Liu Qian Chen Cai
Jiang Yan Zhenzhen, Luo Yi, Luo Yi, Li Yi, Li Wen, loves Qiqi Man. Li Mingming, Li Mingming, Li Mingming, Li Mingming, Li Mingming, Li Mingming, Li Yanyan, Wu Yu, Wu Yu, Wu Shu, Li Dongmin.
Huang Liu Qian, Chen Cai Yu
Jiang Laozhen, Liang, Xia, Luo Yichen, Zha Siping. Victoria Li, Xu, Wen, Wang, Tang, Zhong Ai. Qiqi Esther Li, Liu, Qin, Flora He, Wu, Yu. Tao Tao
Huang Liu Qian.
Jiang Yanxia, Guo, Xia, Luo Yichen, Yu Siping. Victoria Li, Xu, Wen, Wang, Tang, Zhong Ai. Qiqi. Esther Li, Liu, Qin, Flora He, Wu, Yu. Tao, Tao, Zhang, Qin, Lin Xin, Huang Shutai. Lee Dong-min, Ma, Yes.
Lynne, Li Shiyi, Liu
Class 04, Zhou Qi Xin, Wu Changyue, He Junyan Alan, Li Zhihua, Liao Shu Chicken, Li Chia Le. Li Yuxuan, Li Zheng Xin, Zhang Quan Yun, Yu Zeheng Luo Liwei, Li, Handsome, Beard Dragon, Chen Xinqi Yu Wei, Wu Sida, Liu Zhijie, Gu Jiawei. Xu Wen Qing, Li Jia Zhu
Zhou Zhixin from Class 4, Wu Changyue, He Junhao, Alan Lee, Li Chicken, Li Yuxuan, Zhang Quan, Zhang Zeheng, Zhang Quan, Zhang Zelong, Zhang Sida, Wu Siwei, Bowen David.
Chen Yihao. Jeremy, Zhang Shize, Li Hou Lin, Wu, Sui. Juan, Li Shuren, Nong Yushan, Wang Xinru Lai Yurui He Yifan Huang Li Ning Li Ziqi, Zhou Evil carbon, Wu Kexin, Chi Yuzheng. Wang Lu, Zhang Xin, Yin Jingyu.
Chen Yihao, Jeremy Jeremy, Zhang Shilin, Wu Lu, Chen Juan, Li Jingyu.
Ying Chuan Culture Media (Hangzhou) Co., Ltd.