[English subtitles are available]
[Pledge of Allegiance]
[Episode 8]
Li Dongfang.
This is the key
to the file storeroom of Investigation Bureau.
It's yours now.
From now on,
all cases
relate to the year of Hone Wu in Investigation Bureau
need to be checked by you.
If any of the confidential information
within the file storeroom lost,
you will be held accountable.
You can see this
as a thank you gift.
Thank you, my lord.
It's soft.
Bite them one by one.
It's worth 500 gram.
So tonight,
no one is allowed
to save money for me.
[Meng's Eatery]
Meidou.
Here you go.
My drumstick.
Cheers.
Li,
we'll go back first.
Keep drinking.
I, Li Wu,
On...
On the top of my head,
once hung up the biggest cloud.
Now, it's gone.
It's gone.
From now on,
my life
will only be filled with
sunlight
and the blue sky.
Good.
I'm okay.
It's all because of this...
This key...
Where is my key?
Because of it.
Let me see.
Don't touch.
So stingy.
I've opened more than 10,000 locks in my life.
But only this key can open that lock.
Goodbye.
I'm here saying goodbye to the past.
I'll say goodbye to you too.
Okay.
Thank you.
To me,
to me,
you're like
my real mother.
Who wants to be your real mother?
You gotta to be kidding me.
Meidou.
What?
You're like your own son.
Silly.
Give it to me.
Come here.
It's fake.
Come on. Come on.
Meng has a good taste.
Come and let me see.
It's valuable.
Really?
It must be true.
It feels fake.
Look at this.
Where did he get it?
Where is he going?
A rag pocket.
Don't expose yourself.
It's a rag pocket.
For all these years,
thank you for taking care of me.
I, Li wu.
Thank you.
Li Wu.
Goodbye.
I'll never see you again.
Li Dongfang.
What's wrong?
Meidou.
Prepare a blank paper
and follow my plan tonight.
Put the blank paper in the bamboo lantern and let it go down with river.
Do you get it?
Got it. Don't worry.
What did Li Dongfang say?
Do you want to die? Spit it out!
Let go!
I'm your leader.
Cut the crap.
What did he say?
Show some respect to the leader.
Otherwise,
wait for me to get it out and see for yourself.
Something is wrong.
What's wrong?
Everything is not right.
Sometimes I have this feeling.
Everyone else is a jerk.
But then I think,
everything is fine.
People are good.
But I'm the wrong one.
You're the jerk.
What's wrong with me?
Hush.
Li Dongfang said
he saw that
you came with me when I took up my assingment.
He was not satisfied
with your performance.
What's wrong with me?
You didn't even sit on the sedan chair.
You walked to the courthouse with your own feet.
You're the wife of the Sergent.
You're not a countryside girl who came to the city to get married.
The courthouse has read the document.
They know I can't fake it.
Don't talk back.
Why don't you hire servants in our house?
Maids, cooks, and charwomen...
Where are they?
You let the Sergent
sweep the floor, wash the clothes and cook all by himeself?
How can a Sergent live such a poor life?
We need to spend money hiring these people?
These small points are the easiest parts to see through.
Those Brocade-clad Guards are all smart.
I have no money.
No money?
I'm so sorry.
Maid, cook, and charwomen...
You need to do their jobs all by yourself.
You want me to be your charwoman?
Calm down.
Li Dongfang asked you to do this.
Also,
And...
Li Dongfang
think you look unhappy all day
as if everyone owes you money.
You have to change.
With this expression on your face,
you'll be caught on the street by Brocade-clad Guards.
Not to mention pretend to be the wife of Sergent.
You look like there are words on your face saying
"I'm a traitor and I'm going to rebel."
Did Li Dongfang
really tell you these?
What he said is
worse than this.
I've made it very easy for you.
And I think he's right.
How can a Sergent's wife be like you?
I've never seen the wife of Sergent before.
I can teach you.
This is my strength.
So we are
a team.
Wu Tang team.
Wu Tang team?
Sounds like a team working in a bathhouse.
It's decided then.
I'll teach you how to work in a bathhouse.
No.
I'll teach you how to become a wife of Sergent.
High five and that's an agreement.
Do you want me
to hire some servants for you?
I've thought about it. No need.
Do you want me to be your charwoman?
I'll do everything.
Do you want me to smile at you?
I suddenly feel that as the wife of Sergent,
you're more dignified if you don't smile.
Cases of Li Dongfang as the Sergent of Brocade-clad Guard,
are detailed documents
saving in the lieutenant.
So,
you must remember all of those.
In the 25th year of Hong Wu,
The Mus rebelled.
The daughter of Mu Jinggao
carried the method of making An Nan firearms,
fled from the Imperial prison to Ying Chang Road and turned to Northern Yuan.
The case was handed over to the Northern Investigation Bureau by Nanjing.
Sergent Li Dongfang
was ordered to kill the daughter of Mu Jinggao.
Got it?
To be honest,
based on my experience of deceiving people,
all of these are not enough.
I need to summarize Li Dongfang's personality.
Knowing him from his inside to his outside,
and then becoming the real Li Dongfang from my head to toe.
Of course.
I'm not only
need a good memory,
but also my excellent acting skills.
Remember what I'm going to say.
Li Dongfang's good friends in Jinan Office are
Sergent Gao Tiejun,
Sergent Hu Jingyi,
Detective Wang Zhijian.
Gao Tiejun,
Hu Jingyi
What are you looking at?
The way Sergent hides silver
is really special.
Aren't you afraid of hurting your feet?
This is for you.
You need to learn how to walk like a Sergent's wife.
You have to do this.
You did this on purpose, didn't you?
You think the Yingtian Prefecture only has flat and smooth stone roads?
I racked my brains to come up with this.
This is the only way to make it quick.
I quit.
Learning artial arts is easier than this.
You just want me to walking strangely
and faking a smile.
Sure.
If Mr. Li asks,
don't say I didn't teach you.
You're wasting things.
It seems that Lord Sergent
is really good at sewing.
Whoever marries Lord Sergent and becoming his wife
must be blessed in the past and future.
I'm flattered.
But I just analyzed,
Sergent of the north cold place
is really an official.
But after coming to the capital,
it's nothing.
You're right.
There are too many dignitaries in the capital.
So, the most important quality of Li Dongfang
is
his integrity.
His wife Shutang
has some power
in the official of north.
So the second feature of him
is that he was afraid of his wife.
I'm thinking...
Sewing things
like this,
I'll do from now on.
It's my pleasure to serve you.
But at ordinary times,
I have to act as a Brocade-clad Guard in the courthouse.
So the sweeping and washing work...
Don't look at me like that.
I'm just discussing with you.
If Mr. Li’s mission is delayed
because of these chores,
that would be the worst.
What do you mean?
We're a fake couple.
Indeed we're fake,
but our life together
has to be real.
How about this?
Let's do this:
we use single-day and even-day to arrange those things.
Single-days, you do those chore.
Even-days will be my turn.
Then today...
Today is a single-day.
Tomorrow?
Tomorrow is the first day of next month,
it is also a single-day.
Thank you.
You...
You only know sleeping.
What's going on?
It's not hard.
I did all these.
Let's go.
Please show mercy.
Take our clothes back.
Okay.
I'll cook for you later.
Eat.
I'm really good at cooking.
What are you thinking?
How much did you pay those two charwomen?
One tael...
There were no charwomen.
You are really good at cooking.
How much did you pay them?
One tael.
Didn't you say you have no money?
I...
Don't move.
Someone is watching us.
Li Dongfang's experience
and the name of your colleague,
do you remember them all?
No.
Are you worried about me?
People in the Investigation Bureau of the capital
really like to fight with sects.
Lu Yulin and Si Xiangnan
will try their best to win you over.
They will also try to find everything about you.
Because
you came from the north.
And remember,
After pushing your hands as the salute,
remember to fold your hands in the lower abdomen.
Why?
It's a secret code used by Night Scouts to meet secretly with each other.
It means heart-to-heart.
This is the snacks
charwoman prepared for you to eat on the way.
Okay.
Li Wu.
Who?
I'm investigating a man called Li Wu.
Have you heard of this name?
[Investigation Bureau]
Greetings, Sergent.
Please wait.
Let's go.
These are the rebels we just caught.
They have criminal records in the Imperial prison.
My indicators for this month have been completed.
Would you like to take two with you
to make up the numbers.
Lord Li.
Greetings, Lord Li.
It's getting late.
Please.
Lord, this way please.
Lord Li.
I heard that when you were in the north,
you solved plenty of mysteries.
For example, the Nine-head Corpse case.
Tell us about it.
The Nine-head Corpse case.
You can guess first.
Where were these nine heads?
I heard they were on the ship of the water transport wharf.
Wrong.
The nine heads
were in the deck.
It is said the water transport envoy had a dream about the boat being flooded by water.
So he ordered a search.
That's how he found the heads.
Wrong again.
The boat building
was too haste.
Besides, the quality of an official's boat
had poor quality.
I think this person
can only enter or leave.
What's the name of this report?
Report?
On the first day of every month,
all the officials in the courthouse
have to make their reports to the deputy commander
about what they've seen or heard
and what they've been thinking in a month.
It is
snitching
to the deputy commander
Your Lord is wise.
My lord.
This way, please.
Your Lord.
Li Dongfang.
Yes.
Get this done.
Let's talk somewhere else.
I
have yet to ask your name.
Si Xiangnan.
You are so kind.
Like a compass always pointing to the capital in the south.
Wonderful.
According to my family book, my surname was Sima.
Later, my father followed the late emperor.
The late emperor thought Sima was hard to pronounce.
So he gave the last name Si to our family.
The pharse "loyal to the country"
is engraved on your family book.
What happened
to that one was always "loyal to the country"?
I...
should slap myself.
You should.
Get up.
You don't even know how to flatter me.
Let's go.
Sorry.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Bad comes from the mouth.
Nine.
Lord. Ji is a lesson.
He forgot he had only one head.
How dare he mentioned the Nine-head.
I heard that when you were in the North,
you solved plenty of mysteries.
For example, the Nine-head Corpse case.
So, from now on,
you must be careful with your words and actions.
Don't gossip about the six ministries.
Sit down.
Didn't you say
the ships made by the Industry Ministry couldn't work?
I've never mentioned it.
If you never told me,
how would I know?
The ship building
was too haste.
Besides, the quality of an official's boat
had poor quality.
The officials' ships
were made by the Industry Ministry.
If you question the boats,
you're questioning the Ministry of Industry.
And you're questioning His Majaesty's decisions.
Careless talk leads to trouble.
You can say,
people can listen, too.
Please forgive me.
[Log]
Me, myself
enjoy giving people more choices.
I really hope
someday,
there will be someone giving me more choices.
Thank you a lot, my lord.
I understood.
I wanted you to adjust for a few more days.
But the rebels' case
is a rare opportunity.
I want you
to get into your position in advance.
I
will be at your disposal.
The rule of the Brocade-clad Guards working is
two people in a group to work together.
In this way,
they can take care of each other.
Who do you want me to team up with?
Lu Zheng.
My lord.
Li Dongfang, look.
This pot of red maple
is
safe when it only cares about itself?
Or,
it is safer when it cares about the big picture?
I don't know about plants.
Xie Tanran is gone.
From now on,
you and Lu Zheng are partners.
I asked you to keep an eye on him.
Tell me what he did
every day.
Si Xiangnan wants me to work with Lu Zheng.
It's dangerous.
I have to find an excuse to refuse.
If you agree,
I have another thank you gift.
No matter what Lu Zheng will find out,
you'll always be Li Dongfang
when people ask me.
This old man knows everything.
How did he know?
Everyone has their own difficulties.
If everyone like to dig to the bottom
and find out the truth,
nobody can survive.
Yes.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Take this flower out.
Yes.
Left!
Don't let them get away!
Yes.
Catch him!
What are you praying for?
According to the official document from the courthouse,
from now on,
we two work together.
This is the Tiger Head Gate of the Imperial prison.
The late emperor of Hong Wu year burned the execution tools.
Then the Imperial prison stayed closed.
There is no one
in here right now.
Only ghosts wander around.
Really?
I'm just kidding.
Although the imperial prison is closed.
The file storeroom is still under use.
Inside are guarded
day and night.
The file storeroom
is a place storing log books and papers.
Log books are always be with Brocade-clad Guards.
If someone dies,
the body goes inito coffin,
the log book goes in here.
People whose log books store in here
try to sneak in all the time.
They want to steal the papers.
They want to destroy the evidence.
If he succeed,
his sins
will all be gone.
I want you to help me get into the file storeroom
to investigate someone
called Li Wu.
The papers relate to the year of Hong Wu...
[File Storeroom]
[Ten years ago]
Run!
Where
are you going?
Excuse me.
There's no Li Wu.
What?
There's no Li Wu's case file.
Search carefully.
There's no record of the case of Li Wu in the Hong Wu year.
If you don't believe,
find it yourself.
Let's go, Lord Lu.
If we lose any important document,
the Commander
will punish me.
Lord Lu.
We've checked the file storageroom and the case files.
I don't know
why are you still suspect of me?
I
have no reason
to suspect you anymore.
From now on,
you and I
can trust each other.