[English subtitles are available]
[Pledge of Allegiance]
[Episode 6]
[Yi Gate]
Lu Zheng, you've really kept your word.
Give me his badge.
Let me tick it.
You don't deserve it.
My Lord.
[Xie Kengran]
Lu Zheng, the son of the chief commander
of the Investigation Bureau,
is actually a rebel.
He's even a rebel who is hiding this identity so deeply.
Confess!
Confess now!
Lu Zheng.
We're colleagues after all.
We don't want to beat you.
Just admit it.
Then we can save the time
and arrange Xie Kengran’s funeral.
Wang,
a rebel like this has appeared in the Investigation Bureau.
How can we keep our heads up outside?
My Lord.
Flog him 50 times. Beat him hard.
If a noble young man makes a mistake,
he should be punished in the the same way as a commoner.
I'm just afraid that someone will gossip behind us,
and say that
with abuse of illegal punishment,
we made him confess by torturing him.
Is there anyone else who wants to seek justice for Detective Lu?
Take it.
Each of us beats him once.
Beat him!
Beat him hard.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Make him sign it.
My Lord.
Lu Zheng is back.
Got it.
Xie Kengran is dead.
Give Xie Kengran's family
a sum of settling-in allowance.
Go.
I killed Li Dongfang.
The Yuming Lock is still in the hands of Li Wu.
Li Dongfang.
You're not dead?
Right.
It's me.
Kill me.
Escape by yourself.
Hurry up!
Hang in there.
My Lord!
-My Lord. -My Lord.
Okay. Go.
Stop!
-General Commander Cui. -Open it and let me take a look.
What's written on the announcement?
A rebel.
Lu Zheng, the son of the chief commander,
is a rebel.
The world is really chaotic.
He's a rebel?
Let's go. Stop talking about it.
[Investigation Bureau]
Meat-packed rice.
Vegetable-packed rice.
Cabbage-packed rice.
Omelet rice.
Meat-packed rice.
And sugar-packed rice.
Right away.
Have you heard about it?
That person
might die during these few days.
Even a high-ranking father can't do anything about it.
He's dying soon.
His father didn't help him.
His father
has been living in seclusion for days.
Now all the affairs of the Investigation Bureau
are decided by the deputy commander.
Sir, it's ready.
Get lost!
Well...
Sir, I really can't leave now.
I'd like to ask you something.
Is Officer Xie Kengran here?
He's dead.
He stinks in the courtyard now.
Xie Kengran
is an example of warning for you.
He was marginalized when he was alive,
and he made a place stink after he died.
Lu Zheng will end up like him, too.
Just go!
You're awake.
Are you okay?
It was you who saved me?
Where are you going?
I can't let his body lie in the wilderness.
Do you know how hard I've tried
to save you?
Do you think I'll be grateful
just because you saved me?
There's no gratefulness in my heart now.
There's only hatred.
I saved you,
and you hate me?
If I stab you to death, I'll become a good person?
What kind of nonsense is that?
Let me tell you.
If I kill you,
I'll only become a murderer,
and I'll always be in panic.
Forget it.
Let me tell you the truth.
He didn't want me to tell you.
But listen carefully.
Li Dongfang is not dead.
I saw him...
Someone plotted against him.
There is a traitor
among the Night Scouts.
He doesn't trust anyone now,
including you.
What do you mean?
I'm your superior now.
Only Li Dongfang and I
will keep in touch with each other.
He doesn't trust me,
but he trusts you?
A small potato like me,
who marks the price clearly and doesn't gang up with others,
at this moment,
is the most trustworthy.
Why should I trust you?
Do you have any evidence?
Believing it
or not
depends on your choice.
If you choose to believe that he's dead,
he would be
lying in the withered leaves of Mount Guanyin,
rotting and stinking there.
If you believe that he's alive,
then he's hiding in the dark
and looking for the traitor who plotted against him.
If one wants to live,
he has to choose to believe in something.
Am I right?
Come with me to the city to recuperate.
I'm going to the Investigation Bureau to take up my post.
You?
Go to take up your post?
Actually, I should be the one
who died on Mount Guanyin that day.
Why did the Brocade-clad Guard Xie Kengran
protect me from being stabbed?
I don't understand anyway.
For this deal,
he sufferred loss in every aspect.
He was an officer,
and got seven piculs of grain every month.
And these two stacks of cloth
equal to his monthly salary.
Why was he working so hard?
His body is now
lying in the office of the Investigation Bureau, and is stinking there.
None of his colleagues
helps to arrange his funeral.
Why did he save me?
Because I can save Lu Zheng?
But I'm a fraud.
I'm a thief.
Why did he believe me?
I've never seen anyone like him.
So,
I really want to know why.
I promised him that
I would go to the office of Investigation Bureau to save Lu Zheng.
I've been making a living in the society for so many years,
and I've never owed anyone anything.
To him,
I have to keep my promise.
My Lord.
I'm Detective Wang Chan. Greetings, Sergeant.
How have you been, Detective Wang?
Li Wu.
Do you want to die?
How dare you fool me?
Do you know that you'll be beheaded if you pretend to be an official and lie to an official?
Well,
please show mercy, My Lord.
Tell me.
How do we put an end to this?
Plus the money you owed me last time.
100 taels.
Your price is so high.
Fine.
I have something here, too.
Just see whether you want to buy it.
What is it?
Your ear!
Bastard!
Li Wu.
How dare you!
You want to rebel?
You dare to hurt a Brocade-clad Guard?
Killing a detective is nothing.
We've even killed a deputy commander.
You are really a rebel?
Don't you have evidence?
Lord Li,
I have a big family to support.
Please spare my life.
How much are you going to pay for your ear?
100 taels. 100 taels.
100 taels?
Then we are even.
We are even now.
Lord Li,
I’m leaving now.
I won't disturb you.
Stop.
How much are you going to pay
to buy your ear?
There's another ear.
[Investigation Bureau]
Lord Li, you're so kind.
They are not here yet,
and the gift is given first.
This is not a gift.
It's etiquette.
Greetings, Chief Commander.
So this is Li Dongfang?
The sergeant transferred from the north?
Okay.
Li Dongfang has just come to the bureau's office to report duty today,
and you've already known each other?
Yes.
Li Dongfang.
It's been a long journey.
You must be tired.
Are you hurt?
My Lord,
it's
Officer Xie Kengran's blood.
On my way here,
I came across the Prince of Yan's spies, the Night Scouts.
It was hard for me to fight with them alone.
Luckily, Detective Xie helped me,
and I managed to escape unscathed.
However,
Detective Xie was killed by the Night Scouts,
and died for fulfilling his duty.
I have a question.
Li Dongfang.
You mean
Xie Kengran was killed by the Night Scouts?
I saw it with my own eyes.
You've just arrived in the capital,
and you may not know some things.
Lu Zheng, the detective of the Investigation Bureau,
has already signed the statement of confession,
and admitted that he killed Xie Kengran and Wang Kegong.
Wang Kegong
was also killed by the Night Scouts.
The Night Scouts took Detective Lu's sword
and killed Wang Kegong.
I also saw it with my own eyes.
You've just been transferred to the capital from the north.
You haven't reported for duty yet.
Then why did you go to
Wang Kegong's mansion?
I got a secret order
to protect Lord Wang Kegong,
as well as chase and arrest the Night Scouts.
In Wang Kegong's mansion,
Lu Zheng saw me fighting with the Night Scouts,
so he took out his sword to help me.
We made acquaintance with each other because of it.
Since I've decided to step forward,
I've never thought of leaving unscathed.
I'm willing to
testify for Lu Zheng
and clear his name.
As for why Lu Zheng
admitted the crime he didn't commit,
and whether there were
torturing and beating during the interrogation to make him admit it,
I'll
report to His Majesty to make a verdict on it.
If anyone wants to make a big fuss
with the affair of rebels
to repeat the same plot as that in the period of Hongwu,
I don't think His Majesty will agree.
Nor will the people
of the whole country agree.
I've just come from the north.
I don't know how to beat around the bush.
Please forgive me
if I've offended you.
It doesn't matter.
You've just said
someone wants to repeat the same plot as that in the period of Hongwu.
Chief Commander.
Please analyze
what kind of
plot is it?
His Majesty has made
a verdict on Lu Zheng's case.
Lu Zheng is my adopted son.
I'm guilty of disciplining him inappropriately.
I'll go to the palace and ask for punishment later.
His Majesty is very kind,
and granted Lu Zheng a
bowstring.
At 9:45 tonight,
Lu Zheng will be executed at the office of the Investigation Bureau.
Xie Kengran,
I did everything I could.
Even Lu Zheng's father doesn't help him.
There's nothing I can do now.
Give some peace to my son
and me. Okay?
Chief Commander, you're wise.
Li Dongfang.
Step forward and let's talk.
You helped my son so sincerely.
I should thank you.
Don't say that, My Lord.
Tell me what you want.
Tell me.
To be honest,
I
was entrusted by Xie Kengran.
I promised him that
I would save his best friend,
Lu Zheng.
His Majesty wants to kill Lu Zheng.
Only Lord Yuan from the Wenhua Hall
can save him.
I'll go to the palace at once
and find Lord Yuan to intercede for Lu Zheng.
But I'm afraid there is not much time left.
How much time do you need?
At least four hours.
Thank you, My Lord.
I should thank you.
[Wenhua Hall]
9:30 p.m.
Who will do it later?
Ma Han, you do it.
My Lord, we all know that
whoever does it
will have a grudge with the chief commander.
Please spare me.
Li Dongfang.
What are you doing here again?
I've found out that
Lu Zheng did collude with the rebels.
He told a big lie to me.
In just a few hours,
you found out about the truth
we had been seeking for a long time.
That's amazing.
It's all thanks to Detective Wang Chan.
I've just come to the capital.
I'm not used to the new environment and I'm a little dizzy.
Please forgive me, My Lord.
My Lord.
I've told the sergeant
about the whole story of Lu Zheng's case.
Lord Li used to be muddled as an insider,
but now he's clear about it as a bystander.
I'd like to
execute Lu Zheng off personally.
My Lord,
please give me a chance
so that I can
show my loyalty.
This is a nice move.
Finish this for me.
For your career path in the future,
I'll lead you.
Thank you, My Lord.
9:45 p.m.
Do it.
My Lord.
It's not 9:45 p.m. yet.
Please let
Lu Zheng have his last meal.
As the saying goes, one can be executed in a better way after he gets full.
Anyhow,
he used to be our buddy.
My Lord.
Chief Commander.
Please go back.
His Majesty has made it clear.
Eunuch Wang,
for the sake of our previous friendship,
please
inform His Majesty again.
Congratulations, Lord Lu.
Your case is closed.
It's you.
Look at you.
You can only escape
by listening to me.
Eat.
Eat slowly.
If you choke to death,
I can't afford to be blamed by the superior.
My Lord,
please go back.
It's not that I don't want to help you.
There's nothing I can do about it.
Then inform His Majesty again.
Just say that Lu Yulin
has something important to report.
It concerns
an old case which happened
on April 25 in the 25th year of  the Hongwu period.
Lu Yulin,
do you admit your crime?
Yes.
If I know
the old case which happened
on April 25 in the 25th year of  the Hongwu period
it's the crime of deceiving the emperor.
If I intercede for my son with this excuse,
it's the crime of offending the emperor.
Which one did you commit?
I know what happened
in the past,
and I also want to intercede for my son.
You want to trade the old case of the previous dynasty
for your son's life?
You want to make a deal with His Majesty?
I dare not.
9:30 p.m.
Hasn't he just announced that it was 9:30 p.m.?
Why is it still 9:30 p.m.?
What kind of time reporting is this?
I know what is the right thing to do
between an emperor and a minister, and a father and son.
Lu Zheng can die for Your Majesty.
It's the honor of our family.
However,
if Lu Zheng's death
is harmful for Your Majesty,
I can hardly
absolve myself from the blame even if I die.
During the period of Hongwu,
you were not the only one who worked
in the imperial prison.
Wang Kegong
is an example of warning for you.
Come on.
Tell His Majesty
what else you want to say.
I know
where the secret edict of the Yuming Lock is.
Lu Zheng
is the son of the guilty official, Song Heming.
His original name is Song Zhen.
That night ten years ago,
Lu Zheng
was also in the imperial prison.
I couldn't bear to see him die,
so I saved this child.
But later, I was afraid that it would implicate myself,
so for these ten years,
I've kept this secret and didn't dare to tell anyone.
Your Majesty.
You didn't report it
and hid the family of a guilty official.
Of course you dare.
You really had the guts!
If you reported it then,
His Majesty wouldn't have waited for ten years
before he knew where the Yuming Lock was.
I deserve to die.
The insiders of the case which happened ten years ago,
Song Heming and Wang Kegong,
are no longer alive.
Lu Zheng is the only clue.
Lu Zheng knows the secret edict of the Yuming Lock?
May I ask Your Majesty
to summon Lu Zheng to the palace?
As long as the Yuming Lock is still there,
that child
will be useful for Your Majesty.
Please have mercy.
Please spare his life.
Let him serve His Majesty.
Give him a chance.
Kill him.
As for me,
I deserve to die.
Please kill me, Your Majesty.
There's an order from His Majesty.