Hello.
I'm the guy who's dating Yeong.
Seo Yeon and I...
Right.
I'm the guy who's dating Yeong.
I...
love her a lot.
You remembered, didn't you?
Then...
you can't do this to Seo Yeon.
(Yeo Ha Kyung)
One second.
- Yes, Anchor Lee.
- Tell Ha Jin to leave right away.
She's doing a fan signing event.
She'll be done soon.
I have no time to explain.
You have to stop the event
and get her out of there now.
(Yeo Ha Jin's Fan Signing Event)
- What?
- Ha Jin!
- Ha Jin, what's wrong?
- Wake up, Ha Jin. Hey.
- Ha Jin!
Can someone call 911?
(Find Me in Your Memory)
(Episode 25)
Ha Kyung.
You're here.
What happened?
Nothing's particularly wrong
with her.
She must have been overwhelmed
with a lot of work lately.
Did you see anyone suspicious
during the fan signing event?
There was a huge crowd,
and no one stood out.
Today, a lifer ran away
from the National Forensic Hospital.
He ran away in that direction,
so I got worried and called you.
This isn't a dangerous situation
for her, is it?
Don't worry.
He'll be caught very soon.
I see.
You won't have any trouble
with your everyday life...
if you continue to do
your rehabilitation exercise.
Ha Na.
I can do this by myself.
Right. I'm sorry.
I can do this by myself, so go.
I'm sorry.
But sadly,
you won't be able
to do ballet again.
Hey, Jeong Hoon.
I'm at Ha Na's hospital.
Yes. I think so.
Ha Jin, where are you going
at this hour?
Yeong was here,
but I avoided seeing her again.
She must be heartbroken
because of me.
It's late,
so let's call her again tomorrow.
I mean, it wasn't her fault.
Do you think she'll be back?
Of course.
Don't worry about that
and go to sleep.
Hello.
You're Yeo Ha Jin, aren't you?
Who are you?
Seo Yeon and I...
Right.
I'm the guy who's dating Yeong.
I've heard a lot about you
from Seo Yeon.
She said you're her best friend,
and that you're
the most precious person to her.
Yeong said that?
Yes, so much so that I get jealous.
Seo Yeon is the most precious to me.
That's why
I always wanted to meet you.
Right, and I have
a favor to ask of you.
A favor?
Seo Yeon and I got into a fight,
and I wanted to make up with her,
so I prepared a surprise for her.
But I still don't know the passcode
to her practice room.
I thought you might know,
so I wanted to ask you.
Ha Jin, you're up.
Are you feeling ill?
Are you all right?
I have to go somewhere.
Can you drive me?
Right now?
You can't go anywhere
in this condition.
Ha Jin.
Ha Jin!
Why are you doing this?
Why haven't you told me?
Why did you lie to me?
Why did you let me forget? Why?
Ha Jin...
How could I forget Yeong?
Don't you remember how Yeong died?
Don't you know who caused her death
and why she died? How can I...
I should visit her.
Where was he last spotted?
He was spotted three hours ago
at J Shopping Mall.
That was the last of him.
No one has spotted him ever since.
The police put out an APB.
Where have you been amidst all this?
- Come join the meeting right now.
- Okay.
The main news team didn't have
enough time,
so they're only going to brief
the viewers in the beginning.
I think our program will have
to give an in-depth briefing.
That means this will be
breaking news.
Right.
Gosh, which news
am I supposed to omit?
How about receiving
real-time reports from our viewers?
Are you serious?
Yes. Moon Seong Ho was arrested
for murder.
We need to catch him
before he commits another murder.
That is true.
Since the police
have put out an APB,
let's ask them
to share their information.
And let's ask for real-time reports.
Do you think we have enough time?
We can make time.
But what if they catch him
before our news begins?
I mean, that's good news.
It won't be that easy.
He risked his life
to escape from prison.
He's going to hold out
until he gets what he wants.
I'll report this to the higher-ups.
First, contact the police...
and look up information about him.
Okay. I'll call the police.
I'll look for a forensic artist.
Wouldn't it be helpful to show
photos of him...
with long hair or glasses?
Smart move.
If you have any other ideas,
share it with us.
Let's get busy.
Yes, ma'am.
(Ha Jin)
I'll wait here.
(Jung Seo Yeon)
I'm sorry.
It took me so long, right?
I'm truly sorry for being so late.
I really am.
Father.
What happened?
The police called.
Did you get into an accident?
It's only a mild concussion.
You don't need to worry.
Did Jeong Hoon call you
by any chance?
Why would he?
Seo Yeon's stalker
escaped from prison.
What?
There's only one reason why
he'd escape.
He probably wants
to avenge Seo Yeon.
He's probably after Jeong Hoon
or Yeo Ha Jin.
I didn't tell the police
about Jeong Hoon,
so keep an eye on him.
The stalker had harmed himself
in order to escape.
I should've caught onto it.
Let me get this right.
Seo Yeon's murderer escaped,
and you're involved in all this?
That's not what's important
right now.
How far are you going to take this?
Are you sane?
Do you even know how much danger
you had put yourself in?
What were you planning to do
after meeting with the murderer?
What's going on in your head?
Don't you dare talk
to your father that way.
If...
something happens
to Jeong Hoon or Ha Jin,
I will never forgive you.
Ha Jin, I'm coming in.
Ha Jin.
I'm going to open the door.
Ha Jin, don't be like this.
Are you going to repeat
what you did in the past?
No sleep, no food. Are you going
to not take care of yourself?
It's about time you stopped.
It's been eight years already.
You should focus on yourself now.
Ha Kyung, please.
Let me be alone for some time.
(Information on Moon Seong Ho)
(Wanted: Escaped Prisoner)
This is the first batch
of information from the police.
They'll keep sending more,
so make sure you get them.
There's the number of the detective
who was in charge.
Call him if you need to.
Okay.
Did you find a forensic artist?
Of course.
And a very competent one, at that.
I'll write up a list of questions
and give them to you.
Come on. I can do that much.
Just trust me
and focus on your script.
Okay. Let me know if you need help.
All right.
(Warden Kim Byung Yoon)
Hello, sir. This is Lee Jeong Hoon.
Hello. You're calling
because of Moon Seong Ho, right?
Yes. How did he escape?
I believe he was already planning
an escape...
when he had harmed himself.
I should've known.
We decided to talk about him
on our program.
"Where is the wound
that he caused himself?"
"How big is it?"
"How is his mental state as of now?"
"What should we watch out for
if we run into him?"
I need as much information on him
as possible.
All right.
I'll send you his doctor's note
and other documents on him.
Thank you.
Ha Kyung.
Yes?
Did you throw away my belongings?
What belongings?
My old diary and the photos
Seo Yeon and I took.
Did you get rid of them?
Why do you ask?
I guess you still have them.
I'd like to see them.
I'm not going to harm myself.
Don't worry.
I just want to see them.
(Ha Na and Yeong's Exchange Diary)
(Let's wear the lipstick
we bought today tomorrow.)
(My dear Ha Na)
(Anchor Lee)
Hello.
Hi, Ha Jin.
I got worried
when I couldn't reach you.
Where are you?
Did you get discharged?
Do you know
someone named Jung Seo Yeon?
Jung Seo Yeon.
You said you got injured
and stopped doing ballet, right?
When exactly was that?
After Seo Yeon passed away,
he was in so much pain.
She was his first love.
Ha Jin?
(Anchor Lee)
Hello? Ha Jin.
Ha Jin.
I thought something happened to you.
I was worried.
I need to talk to you
about something.
What's wrong? What is it about?
Didn't you ask me once...
if I knew Jung Seo Yeon?
By Jung Seo Yeon, are we...
talking about the same person
we both know?
I remembered everything.
Everything about Seo Yeon.
You already knew...
that I was Seo Yeon's friend, right?
I wasn't trying to deceive you.
I wasn't sure
if telling you the truth...
was the right thing to do.
I shouldn't have asked you out.
I should have stopped pursuing you
when you pushed me away.
I am so sorry.
I think I caused you a lot of pain
all this time.
No, it's not your fault.
No, you don't know anything...
and what I have done.
I just realized
why it was hard to figure you out.
It sounded like you were
always telling me the truth,
but it didn't feel completely true.
It felt like
you were telling me a lot,
but you weren't telling me anything
at the same time.
It was all because of Seo Yeon.
I finally learned
everything about you now.
But I don't know what to do.
I did expect that you would regain
your memory one day.
My heart was always heavy...
when I thought about the pain you'd
feel after getting your memory back.
I'm sure you must be
very confused right now.
But nothing will change, Ha Jin.
It's all in the past.
I really can't think right now.
I don't know what to do.
Okay.
Our country is in a ruckus
because of Moon Seong Ho.
Make sure to get all the subtitles
for the callers and the photos.
And if you get any useful calls,
let me know right away. Okay?
- Yes, sir.
Okay.
Assistant director,
what about the photo?
I'll bring it up now.
(The most recent photo
of Moon Seong Ho)
How did you get all of these?
Jeong Hoon gave me these photos.
All of these photos?
Yes.
My gosh,
this is what I hate that guy.
He's too perfect.
How did he get all of those photos?
When he's done with his lines,
put these photos on the screen.
Yes, sir.
Hey, Jeong Hoon. How did
you get all of those photos?
I got the tip through
my personal connection.
I see. You're still a journalist
with connections.
The screenshot of the footage
is the most recent photo.
When I checked, it was clearer
than the one from the CCTV.
Use that as the main photo.
Okay. Run the title.
Be on standby.
Three.
Two.
One.
Anchor Lee.
Hello, everyone.
Let us begin
"Lee Jeong Hoon's News Live".
This afternoon, a prisoner
serving a life sentence...
at the National Forensic Hospital
escaped from a hospital...
- while he was being treated.
- Get his photo ready.
As soon as the police received
the report, they put out an APB.
They're using all of their resources
to locate Moon Seong Ho.
However, they still haven't
located the prisoner.
In an attempt to help
the nationwide search...
and the police
to locate the prisoner,
we will be taking calls
from the viewers.
Wait. Are they short-staffed?
Please call the number below...
to report anything
about the prisoner.
- This is the 40-year-old prisoner,
- Get the video ready.
- Play the video.
- Moon Seong Ho.
We captured this photo when
he was just leaving the hospital.
Please take a good look
at the man on the screen.
This man, Moon Seong Ho, brutally
murdered a woman eight years ago...
and was locked up
at the National Forensic Hospital.
- Yes. I see.
- His height is 180cm.
- And he has a slim build.
- This is "News Live".
- And he has gray hair.
- Yes. Go on.
- Close up on his wrist injury.
- As for a distinctive feature,
he has an old scar
on the left side of his neck.
And he also has a recent injury
on this left wrist.
It's been confirmed that
his mental state is very unstable.
In order to catch
the prisoner swiftly,
getting cooperation from the public
is the most important.
Please take the initiative
to call us with any reports.
- Hello? Yes.
- Hello.
- This is "News Live".
- Did you get it?
What's happening?
A lot of people are calling
the police and our TV station.
Answer them and give the police
any information we get.
Okay.
Hello? Yes. This is HBN News.
Ma'am, you have to answer that.
You need to answer it.
Hello, this is "News Live".
A murderer who brutally
murdered a woman...
escaped today.
He managed to escape
from our legal system.
And the man who inserted himself
among the people was smiling.
Will you watch him point his knife
at another innocent victim?
- Here.
- It's time for us...
- It's 2 dollars and 20 cents.
- to make it aware...
that Moon Seong Ho...
is nothing
but a shameless prisoner...
who won't be able to do anything.
I'd like to ask for your cooperation
and attention to the manhunt.
Excuse me.
I'll put them in a plastic bag.
This is all for today.
- Have a goodnight.
- Wait.
Excuse me!
We got a lot of reports,
but we didn't get anything
to confirm his whereabouts.
Nonetheless, a lot of people are
aware of his escape now.
We'll be able to catch him soon.
Thank you.
You can thank me
after you catch him.
Call me if there's progress.
Okay, sure.
You did very well with today's news.
The more I think about it,
the more frustrating it seems.
We could have gotten him
if they were a few minutes faster.
We need to lock him up
before he harms innocent people.
Why is our world filled
with crazy and bad people?
Goodness. It's horrible.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Please pour me one too.
I guess something is up.
A lot has happened.
Too many things have happened.
That's the problem.
Did you have a fight with Ha Jin?
No. It's not that.
Yes, that's it.
Actually,
there's a favor...
I need to ask you
and confess something to you.
A confession? What confession?
The girl I used to date before...
died because of Moon Seong Ho.
What?
That's why...
I can't tell you that today's news
was completely professional.
I'm sorry.
But until Moon Seong Ho
gets arrested,
I want to continue receiving calls.
Please let me do that.
My gosh.
How...
Yes, Tae Eun.
Did you watch the news?
Are you worried
because Moon Seong Ho escaped?
I'm sorry, Jeong Hoon.
Why are you sorry?
Moon Seong Ho escaped...
because of my dad.
My dad went to see him
as an outpatient.
And he held my dad hostage.
Is he hurt badly?
No, he's okay.
That's a relief.
I didn't know
your dad was involved in this.
Will you be okay?
According to my dad, he'll probably
go to you or Ha Jin.
Actually, he already did.
Who? Ha Jin?
Yes.
That jerk showed up
in front of Ha Jin.
Please don't tell me she did.
She did.
Her memories came back.
She's in a lot of pain
and confusion.
Does she know
about you and Seo Yeon too?
Yes.
I want to run over to see her
and stay by her side,
but I'd be asking for too much
if I do that right now.
I'd be way too selfish.
It must be tormenting for her
to see me right now,
so I'm just waiting.
I thought time is
what she needs the most right now.
I knew this would happen in the end.
Who have I been blaming for this?
We can't do this.
Why not?
We'll regret it.
I won't regret anything.
You will.
You might regret this
more than I would.
I finally learned
everything about you now.
But I don't know what to do.
I can't even bear to stand here
and look at you right now.
(Ha Jin)
Yes, Ha Jin.