(Episode 17)
- Hello?
- It's me.
You know me, don't you?
How did you find...
Where are you right now?
Where else would I be?
I'm locked up.
Do you know how much I had to spend
to make one phone call?
Why are you suddenly calling me?
Are you with her right now?
Yeo Ha Jin.
What?
Make sure you protect her...
if you don't want to lose her.
That idiot...
He's quite the character.
What are you talking about?
What do you mean,
"he's quite the character"?
How much do you know?
You have too many questions.
You can come and see me
if you're that curious.
You didn't stay long
the last time you came.
Stop talking nonsense
and tell me right now.
Who is he?
Hey, hang up already.
I have to go now.
See you soon.
Thank you.
Hello?
(Find Me in Your Memory)
Anchor Lee.
Hey.
Why are you out here?
I was going to be there soon.
It's way past a minute.
Who were you on the phone with?
It was for work.
I'm making some honey tea.
Is that all right?
Yes.
Grab a seat. This time,
it'll really take a minute.
Here.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I talked big
and said you don't have to worry,
but this is all I can do.
You don't have to be sorry.
This is what I needed the most
at this moment.
It's perfect.
Warm and sweet.
Drink up and lie down again.
You won't be able to fall asleep
if you wake up completely.
Are you leaving?
I'll stay here,
then I'll drop you off at
Ha Kyung's hospital room tomorrow.
I told you that I won't go anywhere.
Who was that jerk?
So he knew exactly where we'd be?
What's wrong with you?
Reporter Jo?
I'm sorry.
Why are you still awake?
Are you having trouble sleeping?
Yes.
If it's because of me,
I'll close the door.
No, don't.
I think I'll be even more scared.
Could you just...
chat with me for a bit?
I think that'll help me go to bed.
Sure.
What should we talk about?
It would be nice to chat
about simple things...
such as your interests and hobbies.
But you have neither.
Did you always want to become
a news anchor?
When I was little,
I wanted to become a writer
like my mother.
But I had no talent
and had to give up.
After I matured,
I wanted to become a reporter.
Your dream came true.
Did you become a reporter...
to make a righteous society?
No, I didn't have
such a grand dream.
I was upset.
People would go back
on their words...
and lie.
I was upset that they didn't
even feel guilty.
Don't get me wrong. I didn't become
a reporter to vent on them.
I just wanted the public
to know the truth.
I bet you can easily see...
how selfish and full of lies
people can be.
That must be painful.
What do you like?
Me?
I already told you that
I enjoyed taking pictures.
I like working out and shopping.
I also like listening to music
and watching movies.
I enjoy reading as well,
but I like eating the most.
Why are you laughing?
I think I asked you
the wrong question.
There might be no end to this.
You could be right.
I do like many things.
I like seeing you smile.
I know I shouldn't feel this way
in this given situation.
But I like this moment.
I like that it's just you and me.
I thought you were injured,
but you look just fine.
By the way, why did you
open the door so suddenly?
I was going to kill you
if you were the stalker.
What brings you here?
I just wanted to visit you.
I thought you'd be bored.
I was hospitalized once
when I was young.
I was bored to death.
That's why I came.
Your presence alone
won't be entertaining.
That's exactly why
I've prepared some stuff.
What is all this?
Ta-da.
Are we going to play games
while having snacks?
Come on. Just wait there.
Watching movies is the best way
to kill time.
You pretty much have the VVIP seat.
Sit down.
This one looks interesting.
It'll help relieve stress.
What movie is it?
I'm not sure. I don't think
this is suitable for a patient.
Let's watch a comedy
so that we can laugh...
No, this looks really fun.
Let me raise the volume.
Don't tell me you can't watch
scary movies.
I love horror movies.
I enjoy getting scared.
Gosh, my hair's a mess.
Hey.
Where are you going?
You should play with me.
What is it?
What are you doing down there?
I was picking up the remote control.
Why did you throw it?
You startled me.
You startled me even more.
Your hair's a mess.
My hair tie got loose.
I think this is the first time
I saw you with your hair down.
You're right. I always had it up.
Don't stare at me.
It's uncomfortable.
I mean, you look like a ghost.
But you also look like
you live in the wild.
Anyway, you look better
with your hair up.
You should always tie it.
I want to tie it as well,
but my shoulder hurts too much.
Then give that to me.
Why?
I'll tie it for you.
Forget it.
Why would you tie my hair?
You look too frightening.
I'm good at this.
I used to tie
my younger sister's hair.
Done.
You look so much better.
Don't go.
How did you...
end up here?
Did you sleep well last night?
I didn't even know I fell asleep.
You didn't snore, so don't worry.
Did you not have nightmares?
No.
I think the honey water
did the trick. I slept like a baby.
I'm glad.
Are you sure you slept well?
I hope you didn't stay up all night
because of me.
I didn't. I slept well.
I'm glad.
- Hello?
- Are you up?
Yes.
I'm on my way there.
Did you sleep well?
It's freezing.
What? Come on.
Hey.
Why is he sleeping here?
He's so weird.
Gosh, it's freezing.
It's so cold.
Yes. I slept well. I did.
Yes. Yes.
- Do you need anything?
- What's wrong with you?
No, I don't.
- So where are you?
- I'm almost there.
You're almost here?
I missed my sister.
Yes. Me too.
Hurry. I missed you too. Gosh.
Where are my shoes?
Oh, my gosh.
Ha Kyung, I'm here.
You're here.
Hi.
Mr. Jo?
What brings you here at this hour?
I came to see how she is.
I just got here.
He just got here.
I see.
Ms. Yeo Ha Kyung.
The doctor is ready
to tell you the test result.
Okay.
Let me come with you. I'll join her.
You're not busy today, right?
What? No.
Then, can you drive them
to your place later? Do this for me.
Me? What about you?
I have an important meeting.
Okay.
Are you with her right now?
Yeo Ha Jin.
Make sure you protect her...
if you don't want to lose her.
(Warden Kim Byung Yoon)
Hello, this is Lee Jeong Hoon.
I know I'm asking a lot,
but I have a favor to ask you.
My gosh, we're home.
Thank you for driving us here.
Do you want some tea?
What's wrong with them?
They are all shriveled up.
Right. This was your place.
Yes.
We're treating
the owner like a guest.
I thought they were fake.
They are real plants.
You have to make sure
they get enough sunlight.
Thank you for helping us out.
- No problem.
- Oh, right.
Let's postpone our training
for about a week.
Will that be enough time for you?
I think you should rest up
for a whole month.
A week will be enough.
You should still be careful.
You might not have fully recovered.
Okay.
But what training?
I promised to be
a physical trainer for Mr. Jo.
Why all of a sudden?
That sort of happened.
What is this?
There's something going on
between you two. What is it?
- What is?
- What do you mean?
There's nothing weird about this.
By the way, where did
Anchor Lee go so urgently?
My gosh, I don't know.
He doesn't tell me these things.
Is that so?
You're here.
You should've hurried.
I've been waiting for you
since morning.
Talk now.
- About what?
- Everything you know.
How much do you know?
Who is that jerk?
Oh, you mean Yeo Ha Jin's stalker?
I don't know.
We just exchanged a few letters.
That's all.
- Letters?
- Yes.
He sent me the letters first,
so I just answered
some questions he asked me.
And I asked him some questions too.
Right.
And I got some photos as well.
So...
what did you talk about?
Answer me right now.
What kind of reaction is this?
By the way,
are you serious about her?
Do you really like
that woman, Yeo Ha Jin?
Do you?
My gosh, you're one crazy guy.
You're completely out of your mind.
Mr. Lee.
Wake up.
You're the one who should
be locked up here, not me.
Come inside. Let's switch places.
Just answer my question.
You answer mine.
Don't you feel bad for Seo Yeon?
Why can't you answer me?
We could have been happy together
if you didn't get involved.
But you killed Seo Yeon.
And now, what do you think...
you're doing with her friend?
If she sees you like this,
I wonder how Seo Yeon must feel.
Poor Seo Yeon.
Darn it.
Ha Jin. Ha Kyung.
My gosh, what is this about?
It must have hurt so much.
Are you sure it's okay
to get discharged already?
You should get all the treatment
you can at the hospital.
There's nothing to treat here.
I'm all better now.
After hearing the news,
my hands were shaking.
I don't even know how I drove here.
Ms. Park, let's sit down.
At this rate,
you might faint before we do.
Sit down and calm down.
Ha Jin. Ha Kyung.
Let's officially request the police
to investigate the stalker.
It's not the time to worry
about your image right now.
Who knows
what that jerk would try next?
I agree with you.
On my way here,
I talked to our lawyer.
The lawyer says it's better...
to report the break-in incident
at home and this attack together.
Then, what about the letters
Anchor Lee received?
Those letters will be hard to be
considered as criminal conduct.
It might just end up
piquing people's curiosity,
so the lawyer advises
not to share that.
And I agree.
And I feel bad
in case this affects Anchor Lee.
Not disclosing the letters
might be better.
Yes. Let's report this
as soon as possible...
and catch that stalker first.
Once I catch that stalker,
I'll break his wrists, so he never
does something like this again.
Ms. Park, leave that to me.
Yes.
So Ha Jin, don't worry about this.
Just take care of yourself
and trust us.
Okay?
I will.
Do you really like
that woman, Yeo Ha Jin?
Don't you feel bad for Seo Yeon?
But you killed Seo Yeon.
And now, what do you think...
you're doing with her friend?
Yes. Hello?
It's me. Is it a bad time to talk?
I just wanted to let you know...
that Ms. Park
suggested officially...
requesting the police
to investigate.
To report my stalker.
I see. Yes.
Given the turn of events now,
I think it's better too.
The media will probably
publish a lot of articles on this.
Probably, right?
Be extra careful for the time being.
Ask the police to protect you.
And have bodyguards accompany you.
Okay.
I'm sorry that
I'm not much of a help to you.
You are such a big help. I mean it.
Stop saying stuff like that.
I'm not the only one in danger.
You're also in danger.
Be careful, okay?
By the way, you don't sound good.
Are you sick?
No. I'm fine.
Rest up. I'll call you again.
(I'm always watching you.)
(You're mine, Ha Jin.)
(I want to make you happy.)
We will try our best to investigate
as quickly as we can.
Please catch the stalker.
We'll try.
Given the evidence,
it seems he's been
inside the house several times.
Are there any suspects
you can think of?
Someone who knows the house well
and Yeo Ha Jin's schedule.
Usually, for cases like this,
there's a high possibility that
an acquaintance is the culprit.
There is someone
I've been suspecting.
("Yeo Ha Jin to Take a Severe Action
Against Her Stalker")
My goodness. I can't believe this.
Yes? Hey, come in.
You're here.
Come here and take a seat.
Sit.
How's Ha Jin doing?
She must've been shocked.
Yes.
He better be caught soon.
She'll be way too anxious.
Hey, so I gave this a thought.
What do you think about
doing a report on this incident?
Around Ha Jin's case?
As you know,
everyone agrees that
stalking is a crime.
But it's tough
to get a stalker arrested,
and even if they do get caught,
their sentencing isn't much.
So let's take this chance...
to change the idea people have
about stalking and stalkers.
I think that could
help out Ha Jin a little too.
I know what you mean
by making that suggestion,
and that you're making that offer
because you're concerned about her.
But...
if I mention her stalker
on the news,
it'll provoke him even more.
What's more important now is
to keep Ha Jin safe...
instead of worrying about
the stalker's punishment.
You have a point too.
I understand what you mean.
Anyway, if you need anything,
let me know whenever.
Yes, thank you.
Okay. You can go now.
It looks like something is
definitely going on between them.
("Yeo Ha Jin's Stalker
Breaks into Her Home")
("Yeo Ha Jin Shows Up
After Revealing Her Stalker")
("Nation's First Love, Yeo Ha Jin,
Harassed by a Stalker")
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
(Moving files)
Darn it, this is so slow.
Man, I can't believe
that got noticed.
(Left alone at 9 p.m.,
headed to a movie theater.)
(Are you sure
you wish to delete everything?)
Please...
(Moving files)
I'm here to inspect your gas pipe.
Sir, over here.
Taxi!
(Inbox: From Lee Jeong Hoon)
This is the script
for today's "News Live".
Turn yourself in and keep
a little bit of dignity you have,
or be publicly acknowledged as
human garbage. It's your choice.
You have exactly four hours left.
I just got some money
from that stalker...
and sold him Yeo Ha Jin's pictures.
I'm serious. I'm telling the truth.
I just did whatever
that jerk asked me to do.
Darn it.
(To Park Soo Chang, No subject)
(Read)