[English subtitles are available]
[The Fragments Of Kylin]
[Episode 10]
Fight against me!
Why didn't you use the power of a demon?
Believe it or not, I'll kill you.
It's not that I didn't choose to use it.
I just don't know how to use it at all.
I only have one power that may be a demon's power.
Because I have such a power,
ordinary weapons cannot hurt me,
except Moye Sword.
What a self-healing ability you have!
Am I really unable
to kill you?
You said ordinary weapons can't hurt you,
except Moye Sword.
That's because it's a magical weapon to kill demons.
I see.
Thank you.
Go to hell!
Though I don't have Moye Sword,
I'll try killing you.
She failed to stop you.
Lan Jia is so useless.
I told you
that you can't make decisions for me.
I also told you
that when you lose your judgment,
I'll have to make decisions for you.
Why can't you just trust me?
She is so suspicious.
Why can't you kill her?
Let me say it again.
You can't hurt her.
If you do this again,
we will
have a battle against each other.
Step aside.
Mo Yan.
How come you were brave enough to confront Lan?
I confronted Mo Lan voluntarily.
I wanted to know something from him.
Just now,
another fragment was absorbed by me.
Can you
feel this?
You said you wanted to get close to me.
Looks like
you just wanted to get close to the fragment.
You got to know I wasn't Xuanyuan Yu long ago,
right?
If I'm a demon,
will you kill me?
The other day,
you asked me
if I knew what my heart wanted.
I know nothing
about many things.
For the past three years,
I've been in emptiness and confusion.
I didn't know where I came from
and I didn't know
where to go
until I married into the Mo family
and met you.
I'm very dumb.
But I know
I want to get close to you and rely on you.
It has nothing to do with the fragment.
Those fragments
only make me feel unsatisfied.
But when you're standing in front of me,
I know
that you are everything I want.
Everything you did for me
made me feel at ease,
made me obsessed with you,
and even made me lose myself in your love.
I feel I have changed a lot recently.
When I saw those rich ladies
look at you,
I was very mad.
♫The person in the dream♫
♫Falling like a flower♫
When you were close to me,
♫The heart withers into a desert♫
my heart
would beat very fast.
When you were so angry that you ignored me,
♫The wind and the rain have seen through the vagaries of fate♫
I was so sad.
♫Where do you wander off to?♫
Do these mean
I have changed?
♫Can't see through♫
♫The karma of destiny♫
The other day you said
you would wait for me a little longer.
♫Who will accompany the song in my heart?♫
Have I
caught up with you now?
♫Time goes by and desolates love and hate♫
♫The past is like a dream♫
♫Sounds echoing♫
♫Your smile is like the spring breeze♫
You've said so much.
Do you know what it means?
♫My heart is like jade and I used to be crazy about you and I don't regret it♫
Yes, I do.
I really know.
♫Flowers bloom♫
In your eyes
♫Flowers fall♫
♫They're so fragile♫
I'm so stupid?
♫Pretty faces will get wrinkled♫
You're not only stupid,
♫Love will change♫
but also stubborn.
♫All will fade♫
♫Can't see through♫
♫The karma of destiny♫
Thank you for catching up with me.
♫Who will accompany the song in my heart?♫
Mo Yan.
♫Time goes by and desolates love and hate♫
Actually, my real name is
♫The past is like a dream♫
Shi Si.
♫Sounds echoing♫
♫Your smile is like the spring breeze♫
Thank you for telling me this.
♫My heart is like jade and I used to be crazy about you and I don't regret it♫
I wish I were not a demon.
If I weren't,
I could be with you forever.
♫The destiny brought us so much misfortune but we remain stubborn♫
♫You made me a promise♫
♫Spring comes and flowers bloom again♫
♫I just smile♫
Bad news!
Mo Yu, where are Her Ladyship and Young Master Yan?
I think they've gone to the front yard.
What's wrong?
A thief broke in.
All our food was stolen.
Even the hares we just hunted are gone.
Oh no.
It must have been done by demons.
Go report this to Young Master and Young Madam.
Where are you going?
The kitchen was robbed by demons.
I'm going to report it.
Who is she?
She is the demon who robbed the kitchen.
How timid you are!
How come you're afraid of a young girl?
You...
You are that snake.
You're so rude.
I'm Soaring Snake.
I'm not an ordinary snake.
Shut up!
You ate all our food.
How are you going to compensate us?
I'll go hunting.
I promise I'll bring back
much fresh meat.
No one will eat what comes out of your mouth.
You work hard here.
Don't worry.
I'll be obedient to you.
Brother Mo Lan.
I should go now and I'll be back soon.
Mo Lan, you...
Why are you
colluding with that demon?
I made that demon work for us.
Don't tell me
you want to go hunting yourself.
There is someone who is really colluding with a demon.
I don't know what he is thinking.
The food is good today.
Let's have a drink.
Here.
How is the food?
All of them were hunted by me.
Why are you here?
I'm here to hunt for you.
Brother Mo Lan.
Brother Yan.
I asked her to come to apologize to you.
Sit.
What are you doing?
You know her?
No.
Can I eat now?
Yes.
Let me ask you.
Why did you attack her?
I didn't.
Wutan Baluo did.
I'm telling the truth.
The other day, he came to me
and asked me to stall Mo Yan.
I asked why.
He answered that he wanted to kill someone.
Are you the person he wanted to kill?
Stop cottoning up to us.
The fragment
was given to you by Wutan Baluo?
Yes.
He knew I was no match for you.
So he gave it to me.
He said that could make me stronger.
So I thought I'd better have it.
So later,
you ate a few villagers?
I didn't.
Wutan Baluo did.
He made you believe I did so many horrible things.
The flesh of those villager is old and smelly.
I don't like it.
I mean
I like eating small animals.
Just like you.
What does Wutan Baluo you talked about
look like?
She's a stupid short-sighted snake.
She can't see people's faces clearly.
But I remember
that he has feathers
and he can fly.
He also runs fast.
He's the poison-eagle.
The one who attacked you in the ancestral hall
was Wutan Baluo?
I didn't hear him introduce himself.
But
he has features that are similar to those you said.
And that day he called me...
I didn't expect Wutan Baluo to kill you in person.
He is the best killer in Demon Realm.
Sister, looks like you're really an important person.
Do you know
who sent him to kill her?
Only a few big shots
are able to get him to do that.
They're the demon lord,
First Young Demon Lord, Second Young Demon Lord,
and some elders.
But I don’t like to get involved in those things in Demon Realm.
I just want to be a free demon in the mountains.
So I don't have any more information to share.
Brother Yan.
Can I have a word with you?
Don't worry. She dare not hurt her.
[Xiao Xuan Village]
Brother Yan.
I don't know what you're hiding for her.
But now we've almost figured out everything.
Wutan Baluo wanted to kill her for some reason.
And he has asked many demons to find her.
Shi Si...
Let's call her that for now.
She might be a demon in the camp that is against Wutan Baluo's.
She may have something to do
with the battle between high-ups in the demon clan.
According to Lan Jia,
Wutan Baluo
wouldn't have tried to kill her himself otherwise.
What Lan Jia said
is not necessarily accurate.
Since she could be used by Wutan Baluo,
it's very likely
that what she told us is false information.
What is your real body?
I...
I'm one of the Five Mythical Beasts.
I'm Soaring Snake.
So it was you who injured my husband
and poisoned him?
I...
I had no other choice.
I'm just a pitiful snake.
I was supposed to be carefree in the mountains.
But
I was tricked and threatened by Wutan Baluo.
That's why I made mistakes.
Sister.
I really didn't mean to hurt you guys.
So you really don't know
why Wutan Baluo wanted to kill me?
Do you know
what a fragment is?
I get to decide whether Lan Jia can be alive or not.
She dare not fool us.
You've always hated to have anything to do with demons.
How come you trust Lan Jia so much this time?
Lan.
You should realize
that not all demons are bad.
Some of them are...
If it weren't for finding out her real identity,
I wouldn't have anything to do with demons.
Brother Yan, be rational.
What on earth do you want me to do?
I just want you to face the truth.
So,
I suppose you don't need me anymore.
What do you mean?
Brother Yan.
Take care.
Lan.
I'm thinking about
Lan Jia's words.
What words?
She said
she seemed to have met me before.
I feel I've met you somewhere before.
Where?
Let me think about it.
I blame my poor eyesight.
But I must have been very close to you back then.
Oh, I see.
A long time ago,
I was taken to Demon Realm.
They forced me to treat some big shot.
They wanted me to use my poison to cure him
and they asked me to suck blood out of the demon's bloody wound.
It was so disgusting.
What happened next?
I tried to escape on the way to Demon Realm.
But then a lot of demons came to catch me.
Of them, there was a beautiful girl.
When I was about to escape from them,
she suddenly caught me and squeezed my heart.
Speaking of which,
her face and scent
are somewhat like yours.
But...
Her hands were like burning fire.
I felt so uncomfortable when she touched me.
Her hands were totally different from yours.
Shi Si.
She might be in the camp that is against Wutan Baluo.
According to Lan Jia,
Wutan Baluo
wouldn't have tried to kill her himself otherwise.
What's wrong?
I'm thinking
how reliable Lan Jia's words are.
I don't know.
I can't remember.
I don't remember
anything of what she said.
Mo Lan
has left?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
I didn't handle it well.
He and I grew up together.
We spent more than ten years together.
Since that misfortune happened to his family,
he has been in my family.
We've never been apart before.
This is the first time he has been so determined to leave.
What happened
to his family?
Originally,
there are four high-class demon races in Demon Realm.
[Righteousness]
The dragon race is one of them.
But since many years ago,
the dragon race has been loyal to the human race.
The dragon race even contributed a lot to hunting demons.
Lan's mother, Suyun,
was one of those helpful dragons.
I used to think
this marked the beginning of the peaceful co-existence between the two races.
However,
things didn't go that way.
All right.
Stop arguing.
I'll let Yun Qi
complete the mission this time.
Yes, Boss.
Yun Qi.
You'll go to West Liang Prefecture to hunt Monster Taowu.
You must be very careful.
Don’t worry, Boss.
Boss.
He’s a member of the side family
This is such an important demon-hunting mission.
If he messes it up,
our clansmen will blame us.
That's right.
What should we do if Madam Dragon
colludes with the demons?
Lan.
Father.
Young Uncle.
Honey.
Is it settled?
Yes.
Boss let the side family complete the mission.
Great.
When we get the payment,
we'll have money to give salaries.
Let's reduce the number of our maids and valets later.
We'll try to give disciples of the side family reward
as much as possible.
They've been following us for years.
Life is not easy for them.
Don't worry.
I've made all the arrangements.
We three
can take care of each other.
We don't need servants.
Lan.
What do you think?
Mother, you're right.
I don't need servants.
I can do anything myself.
Your mother and I will stay in West Liang Prefecture for some days.
Be a good boy at home.
Okay?
Okay.
Young Uncle.
Let Lan stay with me in my house.
We haven’t practiced magic together for a long time.
Lan.
Do you want to stay with him?
Yes.
Then stay.
Yan'er,
Please take good care of him. Thanks.
No problem.
Yan'er has become more mature.
I believe
Sister Fangfei will be happy when she knows this.
Mother, I've become more mature too.
Look, I'm almost as tall as him.
You've really grown taller.
Suyun, look.
You're sweating.
Why are those jinxes here again?
I hate them.
They're going to take money from the main family again.
They're demons and should earn money the way demons do.
Do you think
that boy will grow dragon horns in the future?
I think he will.
I think so too.
What a brat!
Stop. Let's go.
Mother.
Yan'er.
We know we've done nothing wrong.
We don't need to quarrel with them.
Lan, I'll protect you from now on.
Even if you have dragon horns,
that'll be something great and impressive.
Brother Yan.
Thank you.
Hurry up.
Coming.
This way.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Yun Qi, what should we do now?
Elders,
take a rest here.
I'll go have a look.
Yun Qi, it's dangerous out there.
Don't act rashly.
But we must destroy Monster Taowu this time.
I'm afraid the monster will escape.
Wait.
Monster Taowu is one of the Four Fierce Beasts.
We humans only have limited ability.
I'm afraid we're no match for the monster.
How about this?
Let the Madam Dragon go there and check the situation.
If the situation favors us,
we can attack the monster together.
Elder.
Yun Qi.
Madam Dragon can transform into a dragon.
Just let her fly there and check.
Monster Taowu won't be able to hurt her.
Yes.
Madam Dragon can fly.
If we go, we'll just be killed.
Madam Dragon, please fly there and check.
Don't panic.
Suyun.
Remember to come back and report the situation to us.
Don't kill the monster alone when the monster is injured.
Don't take all the credit.
You...
Hurry.
What happened next?
What happened to Young Uncle and the others?
Later,
Monster Taowu died.
[Mourn]
After Mo Lan's parents died,
the elders of Mo family
wanted to kick the dragon family out of the Mo family.
The son of the head of the side family is still alive.
What should we do about him?
After all, Mo Lan is a descendant of the demon clan.
It's inappropriate for us
to let him continue to stay in the main family.
From today onwards,
Mo Lan
should be seen as my real brother.
He should be taken care of by the main family.
From now on,
he and I are the children of the Mo family.
He should not be treated differently.
Only in this way
will the deceased be satisfied
and others be content.
I'll do as Yan'er said.
No more discussion about this.
From now on,
no one
can bad-mouth the deceased.
[Mourn]
Let's go.
Let’s go.
Lan.
I’ll be your brother.
No one will bully you.
Brother Yan.
[Mourn]