[English subtitles are available]
[The Fragments Of Kylin]
[Episode 18]
Brother-in-law,
what do you think of the scenery of our demon clan?
it's your first time here.
You're not feeling well, huh?
Look.
Both of you are humans.
But Xuanyuan Sheng is fine.
Do you know why?
Thanks to Second Young Demon Lord,
it's not the first time I've been to Demon Realm.
You've contributed a lot to me.
Once I ascend the throne,
you'll be rewarded.
Thank you, Second Young Demon Lord.
Uncle,
why did you...
What is this, Brother-in-law?
You can talk.
Throughout the journey,
I thought you were a mute.
Brother-in-law,
what do you want to know?
Come on, let me answer it for you.
Brother-in-law,
are you curious about
why Xuanyuan Sheng has become my lackey?
That's what you want to know?
It's easy.
Of course it's a deal.
Isn't that what the human race is best at?
What kind of deal did you make?
It's no big deal.
Xuanyuan Sheng helped me lure you here
so that I could get the sword
and kill my dear sister.
As for me,
I promise him that after I become the demon lord,
I will not invade the mortal world anymore.
Yan.
Don't look at me like that.
Although I have sided with the Second Young Demon Lord,
I'm still a human.
Of course I will consider the interests of the human race.
I just hope there will be no more war in the future.
The Second Young Demon Lord has the same thought as mine.
So I had a cooperation with him.
As for you guys,
I'm sorry.
Xuanyuan Sheng.
What are you talking about?
Why do you feel sorry?
Am I not good to my brother-in-law?
Didn't you see how friendly I treated him
all the way here?
Look.
He's bleeding.
This means
I pulled no punches
but took good care of my brother-in-law.
Are you insane?
Brother-in-law, you even know I'm sick.
Brother-in-law,
you are really my soulmate.
I feel relieved.
I feel so relieved.
Yan.
Brother-in-law.
You didn't believe me when I said
I wouldn't invade the mortal world anymore, did you?
Actually,
the first thing I want to do
after I become the demon lord
is to eliminate the human race.
Lunatic.
What's wrong, Brother-in-law?
Don't you recognize him?
He is Sikong Shaoyun.
He's also Wutan Baluo.
They are all my lackeys.
What's wrong, Brother-in-law?
You're curious about him too?
Wutan,
tell him.
About what?
Wutan.
Come over here.
Don't you have a brain, you idiot?
Can't you tell that my brother-in-law
is curious about your identity?
Second Young Demon Lord...
Reply to my brother-in-law.
Brother-in-law...
You still have one chance left.
Dear
Mo...
Lord Mo Yan,
over a year ago,
I possessed Sikong Shaoyun.
My true form is a poison-eagle,
one of the assassins
of the Second Young Demon Lord.
Brother-in-law,
are you curious about
how he hid his aura?
Brother-in-law,
you are too narrow-minded.
Look.
You humans
always think so badly of us demons.
In fact,
as long as the possessed one
willingly obeys the demon
and hands over their consciousness, they'll become one with the demon.
Naturally, you can't distinguish each other after a long time.
It's hard to tell whether the human has turned into a demon
or vice versa.
Not to mention the sensation.
Wutan, tell me,
who are you
at the moment?
I'm Wutan Baluo.
I'm also Sikong Shaoyun.
Great.
Alright, Brother-in-law.
After coaxing you all the way,
I've treated you well enough.
I told you everything I know.
It's been years
I haven't talked so much.
Now,
you are supposed to let me take over the Mo Ye Sword, aren't you?
Alright, Brother-in-law.
We're not in a hurry.
Go back and have a good rest.
Wutan.
Take my brother-in-law away
so that he can get some rest.
Yes.
Let's go.
Second Young Demon Lord.
Shut up.
Is it because I'm now in the Demon Realm?
My power has been weakened a lot.
So this is how you felt
back then.
It's all my fault.
If I hadn't proposed
to seek refuge from my uncle in Yandu,
Mo Yan wouldn't have gone missing,
and you wouldn't have gotten hurt.
Even if we didn't come to Yandu,
we couldn't have escaped from it too.
You even got hurt because of me today.
No one ever
protected me like you did.
Thank you.
Don't flatter yourself.
I would do the same if it were someone else.
Even at this point,
you're still being mean.
Can't you tell I'm very upset?
I didn't expect the Second Uncle to lie to me.
Maybe
he had his reasons.
Since young,
no one in my family
understood me
except the Second Uncle.
Only he told me
to free myself from the family
and do what I wanted to do.
So I left the Xuanyuan family.
But I never thought
things would turn out like this.
Mo Lan.
You're bleeding again.
I'm fine.
Actually it has nothing to do with you.
First, the possessed Sikong Shaoyun deliberately approached you.
Then, your second uncle
lured us into the trap set by the demon clan.
Everything came prepared.
We both became pawns
without knowing.
You...
gave it to me...
Aren't you cold?
You even got hurt.
I'm just injured.
I'm not cold.
Can we find them?
Shi Si and Mo Yan.
Definitely.
Okay.
My Lady.
What are you worried about?
Are you thinking about the one from the human world again?
I don't know why.
I've been restless lately.
Is there anything wrong with Shi Qi recently?
It seems...
Nothing special.
He just colluded with his men
to do all kinds of evil everywhere.
But I heard that he has been
closeting himself in the Zhegui Palace recently.
He must have been worn out a few days ago,
so he wants to rest for a few days.
But what doesn't change is that
many demon corpses
are still being carried out every day.
That's what you called nothing special?
My Lady,
you have no idea.
You were not in Demon Realm for three years.
After the Second Young Demon Lord took over the power,
he has been behaving in this way.
A fatuous, self-indulgent ruler of the human world
might be lustful and indulge in sumptuous feasts.
But for him,
he thinks killing people is fun.
He even killed our own people when he went crazy.
We're already used to it.
My Lady.
My Lady, have a seat.
Is the fragment in your body acting up again?
I don't know why.
It's been a month
since you and Bei Zuo
gave me the two fragments.
The fragments in my body keep urging me to polymerize them.
So annoying.
You really disappoint me.
I told you,
whoever can pull out this sword for me
will become my general-in-chief in the future.
Why
are you so unambitious?
How are you going to achieve great success
with me in the future?
You...
Pull it out.
Yes.
I beg your pardon for my incompetence.
Useless!
Go to hell!
Hold on, Second Young Demon Lord.
You'd better have a good idea.
Otherwise...
In my opinion,
it is better for the doer to undo what he has done.
Mo Yan is the owner of this sword.
Instead of waiting for him to hand over the power voluntarily,
we should control him
and force him to pull out the sword,
and then we'll cripple him.
You're right.
Why didn't I think of that?
I only thought about how to take over the power two days ago.
I forgot there is such a direct way.
Xuanyuan Sheng, get up.
Xuanyuan Sheng.
You indeed belong to the human race which is the most sinister.
You're not blushing
even when you intend to maim your fellow man.
You will achieve great success.
I admire you.
Thank you, Second Young Demon Lord.
I'm willing to help you as best I can.
My brother-in-law has been locked in the dungeon
for days.
I wonder if he'll be more obedient.
Second Young Demon Lord.
Mo Yan...
Mo Yan ran away.
That's my brother-in-law.
He always surprises me.
I will surely
cut him open with my own hands.
[Yan]
I've accumulated magic power for days,
hoping it could support me to find you.
[Yan]
It really works only in Demon Realm.
If the First Young Demon Lord wants to recover,
we have to find all her fragments.
Elder, I'm so anxious.
We need to gather all the fragments as soon as possible.
Exactly.
Who is eavesdropping?
Mo Yan?
Mo Jialuo.
You...
Why are you in Demon Realm?
I was caught by your Second Young Demon Lord.
You're not telling the truth.
I want to meet Shi Si.
What do you want
from Her Ladyship?
It's between us as husband and wife.
My Lord.
According to the records,
they divorced not long ago.
If I remember correctly,
you and Miss have divorced, right?
I don't remember I agreed.
You...
Young man,
your marriage with the First Young Demon Lord
was an accident.
Demons and humans
are on different paths.
You can't be together.
Why are you so obsessed with it?
I know
she didn't leave me because of this.
I'm willing to endure the hardship with her.
Unless she doesn't need me anymore.
But besides that,
I will never abandon her.
At this point,
what's the use of saying this?
The countdown has started.
The polymerization of the kylin in her body
will never stop no matter what.
If we can't gather them as soon as possible,
I'm afraid...
What will happen to her?
She will die.
She has been
in bad shape lately.
How could it be?
Aren't those fragments
helping her improve her cultivation?
Why...
Those belonged to her from the beginning.
It's the source of kylin's magic power.
If she loses it,
she will die sooner or later.
The most important thing now
is to find the remaining fragments as soon as possible
to save her life.
Mo Jialuo.
Take me to her.
Shi Si.
My little brother.
You can't hold on any longer, can you?
Don't worry about me, Sister.
Why don't you lend me some magic power?
Why don't you just die?
Fulfill my wishes, can you?
How can I die
if you don't die first?
Sister.
Why didn't you tell me you wanted to fight with me?
You're not moral.
Do I still need to make an appointment to smack you?
Brother-in-law.
Shi Si.
Shi Si, you...
What's wrong?
Why are you here in Demon Realm?
Why didn't you tell me about the fragments?
And why did you fight Shi Qi here?
I could feel that
you were looking for me with Wanwusu.
So I suspected that you were in Demon Realm.
I wanted to see
if my brother was up to something.
Coincidentally, I ran into him
and his men,
and they came here to catch you.
Looks like he already knew
I left the dungeon today.
The dungeon?
You were locked in the dungeon before?
Yes.
How many days?
Not long.
Only five days.
Are you concerned about me?
I'll take you back.
-Shi Si.
-My Lady.
This is inappropriate.
Young man,
now you have fully understood
the First Young Demon Lord's current situation.
Yes, I have.
She is carrying a lot of responsibility now.
As a human,
what's the point of you being here?
I can help her.
You'll distract her if you stay here.
However,
if you are willing to marry into the Demon Realm,
you'll be
an effective tool
in increasing the First Young Demon Lord's strength.
After all, the Mo family has the right to have a say
in decisions among humans.
I'm sorry.
I was expelled from the Mo family
because I colluded with demons.
What else do we need you for?
What a sin!
What a sin.
It must be very painful.
What?
Those fragments
have been yelling in your body to get together.
It has nothing to do with you.
That's why you left.
Right?
You thought I couldn't help you.
Just take it as a yes.
I didn't do well enough.
I couldn't make you trust me wholeheartedly.
It's all my fault.
Now that I've come to the Demon Realm,
I've lost all my power
and become a useless person.
You just didn't want me
to fall into your brother's hands.
You pitied me,
so you brought me here.
Why do you think so?
Am I wrong?
If not,
why did you divorce me?
You are a human while I'm a demon.
We are destined to be on different paths.
No one is right or wrong.
No.
I was wrong.
I shouldn't have married into the Mo family.
I shouldn't have married on behalf of Yu.
Do you mean it?
At this point,
does it matter?
I thought
at least you wouldn't regret it.
Our fate has ended.
Let it go.
Shi Si.
You did well enough.
It's not that I pitied you.
You're strong.
Never doubt yourself.
First Young Demon Lord.
Please allow us to
go to the human world again
and search for the remaining fragments.
Do you think
I should
send Young Master Yan back with this opportunity?
My Lady.
The Second Young Demon Lord has spread rumors
that
you colluded with the human race
and worked with Mo Yan
to overturn the rule of the Demon Realm.
In just a day or two,
many people have betrayed us
and defected to the Second Young Demon Lord.
It's no use to persuade
those fence-sitters to stay.
First Young Demon Lord is right.
But we can't keep Young Master Yan here
for a long period.
My Lady.
You...
Are you reluctant to let him go?
Well...
When he recovers,
send him back to the human world.
That's more like it.
My lady has always been carefree.
You don't need to care about a passer-by.
Shi Si.
You came at the right time.
What brings you here?
I'm looking for Shi Si.
You...
How shameless you are!
All right.
You may leave now.
Thank you in advance for the fragments.
-Yes.
What is it?
I heard you say
you'd send me away.
You can leave
after you recover.
Since I'm already a passer-by,
what's the difference whether I recover
or not?
Since I've caused you a lot of trouble here,
I'll leave today.
Fine.
But I have a request.
You have to give me a ride.
After all, your brother
is really sinister and cunning.
As you know,
in Demon Realm,
I have negligible magic power.
If I leave alone,
he will kill me halfway.
We were husband and wife once.
You don't want me to
die in his hands, right?
It seems that I have caused you a lot of criticism.
When we were fleeing,
I also caused you a lot of trouble.
How did you know?
Where did you hear that?
Is that why you...
I'm not as great as you think.
Aren't you Young Master Yan?
Why are you here in Demon Realm?
You used to be arrogant.
Now you're just like a loser.
Get up.
Do you still dare to be arrogant?
Stand up.
What are you waiting for?
Get up, Young Master Yan.
Get up quickly.
Stand up.
Hurry up.
Go on.
I'm talking to you.
Can you get up or not?
Shut up!
First…
First Young Demon Lord, please spare my life.
You were so arrogant just now.
You're like a loser now.
I was wrong.
Go back and tell Shi Qi
no one
can hurt my people.
Got...
Got it.
Apologize.
I'm sorry, First Young Demon Lord's...
-Lady.
-Is that what we call him?
What should we call him then?
First Young Madam?
It's inappropriate.
Well...
What should we call him?
I don't know.
Get lost!
-Yes.
Are you leaving or not?
Troublesome.
♫The person in the dream♫
♫Falling like a flower♫
♫The heart withers into a desert♫
♫The wind and the rain have seen through the vagaries of fate♫
♫Where do you wander off to?♫
♫Can't see through♫
♫The karma of destiny♫
♫Who will accompany the song in my heart?♫
Let go of me.
♫Time goes by and desolates love and hate♫
♫The past is like a dream♫
♫Sounds echoing♫
You were pretending?
I should have asked you to protect me earlier
If I'd known that pretending to be vulnerable would work.
♫Your smile is like the spring breeze♫
Didn't you divorce me?
Why did you say I'm yours?
♫My heart is like jade and I used to be crazy about you and I don't regret it♫
I'll send you back.
I'm not leaving.
♫Flowers bloom♫
♫Flowers fall♫
♫They're so fragile♫
You don't want me to be bullied.
♫Pretty faces will get wrinkled♫
♫Love will change♫
But why do you keep hurting my heart?
♫All will fade♫
Shi Si.
I don't want to divorce you.
Do you agree?
♫Can't see through♫
♫The karma of destiny♫
Shi Si.
♫Who will accompany the song in my heart?♫
Do you still want me?
♫Time goes by and desolates love and hate♫
Do you know
♫The past is like a dream♫
you can't go back to the Mo family anymore
♫Sounds echoing♫
if you are together with me?
I don't care about it.
♫Your smile is like the spring breeze♫
You're my wife.
You can't abandon me.
♫My heart is like jade and I used to be crazy about you and I don't regret it♫
Don't leave me again, okay?
♫The destiny brought us so much misfortune but we remain stubborn♫
♫You made me a promise♫
♫Spring comes and flowers bloom again♫
♫I just smile♫
Okay.