[English subtitles are available]
[The Fragments Of Kylin]
[Episode 9]
Young Master
This beast is way too scary!
So it is a Tengshe,
one of the Five Mythical Beasts.
So it has been hiding here?
Young Master
You know it?
More than that.
I have badly injured it before.
Consider this as a reunion.
Lan Jia,
long time no see.
Oh it's you, Mo Yan.
We're in the middle of nowhere,
I don't suppose you are here to chat?
You have been doing evil in this vicinity,
so I'm here to kill you.
Nice timing.
I want to test
the treasures I have collected recently.
Young Master
what is this?
This is Lan Jia's snake poison.
It's extremely corrosive.
Extremely corrosive?
Snake!
Snake poison?
Hang on.
Her snake poison's
potency has became way stronger.
What happened?
My Lady.
What's going on?
Xiaohe.
Don't panic.
That's great My Lady.
The water has stabilized.
Mo Yan
how long you intend to cowardly hide in the barrier?
Oh no
My power hasn't fully recovered.
Mo Yan
Why is it still the same trick?
While the wound you slashed before
will never heal,
now,
you can't even touch me.
Mo Yan
you haven't improved at all.
I'm very disappointed.
My Lady.
What should we do?
The water is moving again.
Are you alright?
Young Master Mo Lan, you're back.
What happened?
I don't know.
Not long after Mo Yan left this morning,
the poison came flooding in.
Where did Brother Yan go?
He said there were unusual mountain activity
and he just left.
He said he's going...
Oh no!
My Lady, calm down!
You won't be able to help,
worst still, you might cause trouble.
Something must have happened to Mo Yan.
Young Master Yan is so powerful.
With Young Master Mo Lan going as well
they will be fine. Don't worry.
Please calm down.
That's right.
He will definitely be fine.
Brother Yan
Before I find you,
please do not have any mishap.
Young Master
Young Master!
I'll kill you!
Alright,
if you are killed by me,
it's worth it.
You this stupid snake.
Do you want to die?
You're just a half-baked dragon.
I have a fragment.
Why should I be afraid of him?
Brother Mo Lan.
I was wrong.
I didn't mean it.
I just wanted to try this fragment.
This treasure can enhance one's power.
I just wanted to give this a try,
I didn't want to kill Mo Yan.
I can give it to you.
Don't kill me.
If I kill you,
I can still take away the fragment.
Mo Yan is poisoned by my snake poison.
You don't want him to die, do you?
I can give you the antidote.
I promise
I won't come out and commit evil again.
Brother Mo Lan.
I'm still young,
and immature...
Could you give me one more chance,
please?
Brother Mo Lan, I'll give you the antidote.
Get lost!
Don't let me see you again.
I don't want to see you too.
Brother Yan
Brother Yan!
Mo Lan
Why hasn't he woken up?
He just took the antidote for snake poison,
the effect won't be that fast.
Is he badly injured?
Yes.
Do you know he got hurt because of you?
What?
He used Lightning Chasing to disperse your poison last night,
and almost exhausted all his power.
As for his meeting with that stupid snake today,
if I hadn't arrived in time,
he would have reduced into a pool of poison.
But he told me...
Lightning Chasing?
He said he can use it at will, right?
Lightning Chasing is a technique used to increase power.
In battles,
it is the crucial move to win in a blow.
It was never meant for doing treatments.
Depending on how long the treatment takes,
equal power are needed to maintain the physical form.
It is akin to the meridian points
being pierced by extremely sharp powers.
You know how
damaging it is to his body?
Three years ago,
the head of the Xuanyuan family was poisoned
by the Demon Lord Shuntian's demonic aura.
The poisonous gas
is hundred times more poisonous than bats.
Dozen of Xuanyuan's family sorcerers
used Lightning Chasing to disperse the poison.
They died exhausting their power and imploded their meridians.
Even so, Xuanyuan Chang still did not recover.
You know
about this, right?
Xuanyuan Chang is your father,
you surely know that.
Unless...
you are not Xuanyuan Yu.
Is it strange that I know?
You tried so hard to hide it from us
to help the Demon Clan in harming him.
What?
You are entangled with the Demon Clan,
do I need to spell it all out?
I'm not.
You're not what?
Have you been truthful to him?
You both have been married for so long.
How many times has he saved you?
He did so much for you.
Do you think you're worthy of it?
I'm sorry.
Young Madam is out.
Young Madam!
Is Young Master awake?
Well...
No way they are fighting now right?
But why does she look like
she is crying?
Lan
Brother Yan
You...
Why are you back?
What?
If I don't come back,
you'd have been killed by that stupid snake.
You saved me?
You transformed into a dragon?
If I didn't transform into a dragon, how can I...
Nonsense!
How could you...
Brother Yan
In that situation–
Your life is shortened by five years every time you transform.
Why were you so impulsive?
As long as I can save you,
I don't mind reducing my life by even 50 years.
Brother Yan
You gave me my life.
No matter what happens to me,
I won't let you die.
If you die,
I will kill all the people I need to kill.
Lan
don’t do this again.
As long as you're not in danger again.
Did you kill Lan Jia?
No.
She negotiated with me with your antidote,
so I let her off.
This girl is quite sensible.
Although Soaring Snake is known as a small dragon,
it's not worthy before you, a real dragon.
It's just a worm.
However,
unlike before, her snake poison
became more poisonous.
It is because of this.
That's why her power improved.
No wonder.
No wonder she can break my barrier.
Just say it.
Xiao Xuan Village was attacked today.
My wife...
Your fake wife is fine.
I came back initially
to discuss with you to capture Lan Jia
but ended up saving your wife.
Lan
thank you.
I just think
if she dies because of a snake bite,
It's too embarrassing to be killed by a snake bite.
A snake.
You mean Lan Jia?
That's right.
I suspect it's a diversionary tactic.
On that note,
this stupid snake is usually very lazy.
Since the last time you subdued it,
she hasn't caused any trouble.
However, this time the scout reported that
it had eaten several villagers.
I suspect something is amiss.
And sure enough,
it was because of this fragment
Just like the bat.
You mean
Lan Jia was also ordered to kill her?
Yes.
You're not cultivating today?
You don't seem happy that I am awake.
No.
I'm happy.
You're crying?
I'm sorry.
Why?
Please,
don't get hurt because of me anymore,
okay?
My injuries were caused by the demon clan.
It has nothing to do with you.
It's cold outside.
Let's go back inside and rest.
Mo Yan,
I really don't know what to do.
I’ve told you before
not to trust me anymore.
But whenever I was in danger,
I always hoped you would come to save me.
I know it's wrong,
but I just can't help
thinking of you.
You're so kind to me
even though you don't know who I am.
Then why won't you tell me？
If I say,
I don't even know my own identity,
would you think I'm lying to you?
I don't want to deceive you anymore.
I don't know since when,
but I just don't want to do that to you anymore, Mo Yan.
Even if you ignore me,
or despise me,
I accept it.
Do you even have a conscience?
I've become like this because of you.
Yet you still say I despise you.
Yes.
Lightning Chasing is so dangerous,
but you used it to heal me.
Why didn't you tell me?
You were so badly injured.
I was completely helpless.
Why didn't you tell me?
Do you know
these calamities may even be caused by me?
I don't want to see you get hurt.
If you get hurt, then I...
I just don't want to lose you,
Mo Yan.
Alright, alright.
Don't cry anymore, don't cry.
I...
Do you even know
your own heart?
I don't.
You are crying over me,
don't you know by now?
Will you cry for Sikong Shaoyun?
What about Mo Jialuo?
No.
Mo Yan.
You...
You may not know,
but I already know.
About what?
I'll wait for you.
But hurry up.
The demon clan has been attacking you frequently of late.
Your magic is still insufficient to defend yourself.
To ensure your safety,
I'll entrust you with the authority over the Mo Ye Sword.
In case any misfortune occurs
when I'm not around.
This...Mo Ye Sword
is the sacred artifact of the Mo Family.
You're going to give it to me?
Don't worry,
I'm just sharing it with you.
The sword remains under my control.
No.
You know what I've told you
about my identity...
It's irrelevant.
I just want to
do everything in my power to protect you.
I will bear
all the consequences.
But I can't...
If you don't want to see me get hurt again,
then do as I say.
Mo Ye Sword is a top-tier demon-hunting artifact.
It's selective and demanding in its choice of master.
Therefore, when gaining control over it,
you must calm your mind and focus.
Ensure that the magical energy in your meridians
does not flow in the opposite direction
to the sword's energy.
It's already midday.
Why is there still no movement?
Mo Yu,
have My Lady and Young Master Yan gotten up yet?
It’s still early.
Let me tell you...
Yesterday, they...
No kidding!
Really! I'm telling you...
What's the big idea!
Don't fill your head with nonsense at such a young age,
or you'll wear yourself out too soon!
If you haven't seen it,
how do you know what I'm watching?
Did I say I haven't seen it?
Then tell me...
My Lady, Young Master Yan, you're up!
Young Master,
you just recovered from your injury,
please take care of yourself.
For what?
In a broad daylight like this,
try to be a bit more discreet.
That's right.
Both Mo Yu and I are still young.
What are you talking about?
It's so hot.
Here, have some water.
It's normal to feel this way right after the ritual ends.
Be careful not to catch a cold.
Okay.
You had gunpowder for breakfast?
It's okay.
You go ahead and eat.
I'll go and take a look.
OKay.
My Lady, you don't look well.
Are you okay?
Mo Yan
has shared the authority to wield
the Mo Ye Sword with me.
My Lady,
the meal is ready.
Why aren't they back yet?
It's getting dark already.
Xiaohe,
it looks like it's going to rain soon.
Take an umbrella to the bridge to meet them.
Okay.
Just come out.
Where is Mo Yan?
I found an excuse to trap him.
In these mountains,
there are still quite a few demon clan members
who will listen to me.
As long as he's safe,
I'm relieved.
I’m afraid you’re the only one who can put him in danger.
You, Young Madam, have truly good tactics,
even gaining the control over the Moye Sword.
Without the authority,
perhaps you can't even touch it, right?
What exactly do you want?
I know what you want to ask me.
But I really can't
answer that question.
You're hiding something.
No.
I lost my memory three years ago.
I don't remember anything.
Three years ago.
Neither too early nor too late,
indeed
intriguing.
You suspect
I'm affiliated with the demon clan?
Is there even any doubt?
All your behaviors are beyond common sense.
That fish
also called you "My Lady".
Since we came to Xiao Xuan Village,
the demon clan has been after you time and time again.
Who exactly are you?
I don't know.
Then at this point...
Please don't.
Are you still trying to quibble?
You pretended to be Xuanyuan Yu from the beginning,
hiding everything from Yan.
He knew early on all the doubts about your identity,
yet still treated you like ever before.
How can you
trample on his sincerity like this?
You mean
Mo Yan thinks I belong to the demon clan as well?
Unfortunately,
he's been blinded by you
and naively believes that
you would confess to him voluntarily.
He can tolerate it.
But I can't.
I didn't mean to deceive him,
nor did I intend to trample on his sincerity.
I just...
Even if I misjudged,
I shall take
all the blame alone.
I know I can't defeat you.
If I die,
please tell him for me,
thank him for trusting me.
Mo Lan,
please make sure
to always protect him well.
You need not say more.
I'll eliminate anyone or anything
that could do harm to him.
Come at me!