Any characters, actions, places, organizations, professions and events in this series
are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to guide or encourage any behavior in the story. Viewer discretion is advised.
Oh.
You awake now?
Yeah.
Are you still hangover?
Do you have anything else you would like to say to me?
I'll go get dressed first.
Have you finished packing your luggage?
Yeah.
Check it carefully to see if you've forgotten anything.
I checked it.
But we have to go back to Thailand.
I probably have to leave a place of peace
and good atmosphere like this?
Normally, don't you like lights, colors and sounds?
Have you already gotten used to it?
Sometimes...
when we're in a peaceful space
with a good atmosphere like this,
it makes us hear our hearts more clearly, don't you think?
Hey.
Have you finished packing your luggage?
Yeah.
Done.
I'm here.
4 flavors, 4 cups.
Choose it.
Isn't it just hot noodles that can help relieve a hangover?
Are you out of money?
So you eat noodles.
If you run out of money, you can borrow it from me.
No.
I just thought that we should try it
since we're in the home town of ramen, don't you think?
Look.
It has many flavors for you to choose from.
I can't choose it.
I prefer this flavor.
Hey.
You hurry and grab it before anyone else.
Hey!
I have something for you.
Here!
Hey.
This is a clover leaf.
Where did you get it from?
I looked and bought it for you.
Here.
Wow.
You're really dedicated.
You buy it for your friends.
Just think of it as a souvenir from me.
Here, one for each person.
Thank you.
I will preserve it well.
From now on all our wishes and miracles
will come true, right?
Let's do this.
To thank fate for bringing the four of us together.
So before you guys go back to Thailand,
I'll take you to some places.
This place is famous for its blessings.
Many people make wishes here and their wishes come true.
Is it a temple?
Yes.
Is there a temple like this?
Sure.
What about our baggage?
Where will you put it?
Your house?
Wow...
It would be a waste of time if we leave it at home.
Just take it with us.
I think there are lockers nearby for storing things.
We can keep it there before traveling.
We can go back and get it when we finish our trip.
And we went to the airport after that.
Let's do this.
Leave your luggage at my house first.
I will call the moving service to the airport later.
I'm okay with it.
Then hurry up and eat all the noodles
and let's go.
Okay?
Okay.
Right there.
The big red lantern over there.
We've arrived.
Sensoji Temple.
Let's go.
Go.
Hey.
We've arrived.
The front gate of Sensoji Temple.
Wow!
So beautiful!
P.
I saw my Facebook friend
take a photo with this lantern
and set it as their profile picture.
I never thought I would actually see it.
But...
What does this letter mean?
This letter is pronounced Kaminarimon.
It means lightning gate.
This gate has two angels protecting it.
They are...
On the left is Fujin, the god of the wind.
To the right is Raijin, the god of thunder.
You really have a lot of information.
Because I learned a bit about it.
I applaud you. You're really amazing.
Uh.
Since we reached the check-in point,
let's take a group photo?
Hey, I agree with you. Come on.
Let's take a photo.
Use Beboy's camera.
My camera. Hurry up.
Ready?
P! This way.
Yeah.
1...
Well.
Did it come out well?
It's so beautiful.
Hey, good.
Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go inside, shall we?
Hey, guys.
The gate we are about to pass is called Hozomon.
Its meaning is a treasury.
Well...
It's really meaningful.
Japanese people recommend that after walking through this gate,
we must predict our fortunes first.
Really?
So what are we waiting for?
Let's go predict our fortunes.
Let's go!
On the left.
Here.
The step is to insert coins.
Put 100 yen in.
And pick up this one.
We have to shake it like this.
And wait until it's like this.
And check the number we got.
It's bad.
What about me?
Let me see.
Good.
It came out good.
Wait. Wait. Wait.
Are my results good?
Please read it for me.
I can't read it.
Your luck is good too.
- My luck is good?
- Yes.
- Is your luck good too?
Let me see.
Wow.
Pan's fortunes are really good.
Everyone's fortunes are good.
What about you, P?
Not very good.
Is that so?
Uh.
Do you know what it's called?
This is Omikuji.
It's like a shrine in our country that has siamsi for divination.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
After we get it, it is called our destiny card or our destiny.
If we get a bad one, we have to tie it here.
If we get a good one, just take it back with you.
That's all. Nothing much.
Then I have to bring it back.
Let's go.
My fortune is bad.
- Tie that.
- Yeah.
Let's go.
Can you do it?
It's okay. Let's go.
Wow, there's a lot of smoke.
P.
Can I put incense sticks somewhere else after making a wish?
You can't, Beboy.
Incense smoke is very important.
Why?
There is a belief about beckoning good luck smoke to oneself.
- Yes.
- Really?
Yeah.
So I'll do it.
Hey, wait wait wait.
Calm down.
You can't just beckon smoke towards you.
How is it?
First of all, you need to buy some incense sticks.
After that, you will be able to pray.
After that, you put incense sticks.
When you finish putting incense sticks, you can beckon the smoke towards you
to bring good things towards you.
- And...
- Let's pray, shall we?
Where is the incense?
Right there.
Let's go.
Uh.
Some say that beckoning with smoke is taking a smoke bath.
The smoke will cleanse bad things from your body.
Something like that.
I don't know what to say
if I don't succeed when I return to Thailand
after beckoning with smoke like this.
Look.
You will definitely succeed.
Before you succeed, why are your eyes red?
Huh?
My eyes hurt.
Hold on. There's another place.
- Where?
- Follow me.
- Inside here.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
Hey, before we make a wish,
we have to cleanse our bodies at this holy spring.
P.
Just now I saw people using ladles to scoop up water and wash their left hands.
Yes.
They scooped it up again and washed their right hands.
They scooped it up and washed their mouths.
Why do they do it?
They cleanse their bodies before making a wish.
Do I have to do it too?
Let's go.
Let's do this.
Look.
Yeah.
Do I have to pay respects?
Very refreshing.
Let's go.
I'm here.
Just a moment.
I'm looking for coins.
Coins?
What will you do with it?
We will ask for blessings from the god Kannon inside.
Coins are tossed there to seek blessings from the gods.
So I need to find a 5 yen coin.
Why does it have to be a 5 yen coin?
Can't we use other coins?
The Japanese 5 yen coin is called 'Go-en'.
It's pronounced like 'Go-en' which means asking for blessings from God.
Oh.
Is it this one?
I have it too.
Yeah.
Pan, can I get 5 yen from you?
Hey.
I see you have it.
Why do you have to steal from other people?
I want to keep it.
Shouldn't you just keep one coin?
Hey, I have many coins.
Just take it.
Please give it to me.
This is for you.
Thank you.
Here, for you.
Why do you have to buy it?
We already have a clover leaf.
It's more comprehensive than a talisman.
Alright.
Hey.
But Japanese talismans are not like Thai talismans.
It has an expiration date.
If possible, you should change it every year.
But for a better way, you should change it to the same place.
The place where you bought it in the first place.
I wouldn't buy it if I had to replace it every year.
I'm so hungry.
Hey, should we go our separate ways?
Yeah, good idea.
Beboy, you're going to shop around there, aren't you?
Yeah.
I'm going to the Edo antique market.
I've never been there.
I'll go with Beboy.
What about you, Pan?
Well, just go.
I'll walk around here.
Hey, let's do this.
We called each other to the meeting point after finishing.
Okay.
Bye.
I'll text you.
Hey.
Where are you going?
I'll walk around here.
Why don't you go with me?
Come with me.
I didn't think you wanted to go with me in the first place.
Alright.
Please?
Yeah.
Let's go together.
I really envy you that you get to live in Japan.
Why?
Look.
It has many trees.
Wherever we look, we see it.
Even your neighborhood has a park.
Do you like it?
So much.
When I don't have ideas for lyrics,
I usually stay in places with lots of trees like this.
Why?
What do trees help you?
Yeah.
When I am surrounded by green space,
it relaxes both my eyes and my mind.
When I got home,
I immediately had an idea.
If you don't believe me,
please try changing from the bar
and going near the tree.
It might make you feel better.
Normally, how do you use nature to help you?
It's not difficult.
I'll show you a simple one.
Well.
First of all, you have to close your eyes.
And think only of good things.
Take a deep breath.
Something like this.
Do you want to try it?
No.
Hey.
Let's try it once.
No.
Close your eyes.
Close your eyes first.
Alright.
Take a deep breath.
Think only of good things.
How are you?
Do you feel anything?
Maybe good?
Can I request something from you?
Yeah.
I want you to think of trees when you're stressed.
So that you'll miss me sometimes.
Here.
Thank you.
Pan.
Why?
Uh...
I have something to apologize to you.
What?
When I annoyed you when we first met.
I think it's something else.
I want to clear everything up.
Because you are going back to Thailand.
I don't want anything to be left unresolved.
That's okay.
I can't.
Otherwise, it will stay in my heart.
I'm worried.
But...
you...
can forgive me, right?
Sure.
Why not?
Really?
Yes.
I also have something I want to tell you.
Yeah.
Many people say that a teenager's life only happens once, right?
We must use it worthwhile.
I think it's true.
But I want you to plan your life.
So that you will be happy in the future.
So that you can be yourself.
Yeah, I know.
Do you know?
Since the first day I met you.
Yeah.
There is never a time when I feel bad about you.
On the other hand,
I like everything about you.
Especially confidence and faith in yourself.
Please maintain it well.
I believe that no matter what you hope for,
your faith and belief will make you successful.
Well, I promise you.
Hurry up.
It has many shops.
Yeah.
Shall we rest here?
Great idea.
Really refreshing.
Are you tired yet?
A little.
But I feel better after drinking water.
It will be finished after we look at a few more shops.
Would you like to go back and buy something else?
I will walk with you.
Don't be considerate of me.
No.
(Where are you?)
(What are you doing?)
(You didn't answer me at all)
(There is no signal after I call you)
(Did anything happen to you?)
(Now I know in my heart that I love only you, Plai. I want to apologize to you.
Please forgive me. Please come back and love each other like before.)
Answer him.
Don't make him wait long for your answer.
It's not good.
Just answer him.
I even chose for you some outstanding clovers related to love.
Achieve it.
So that you won't regret it later.
Beboy.
Huh?
Before I answer his phone,
can I ask you something?
Yeah, just ask me.
At the temple that day,
what did you pray for?
Are you really want to know it?
I'll tell you.
I made a wish about
finding someone who is nice,
cute,
and has a sweet smile
beside me,
and that person is...
the person in front of me right now.
Your clover is truly amazing.
It can really make miracles happen.
Are you getting better from tiredness?
Yes.
Are we going to continue or stop here?
Let's continue looking for P and Pan.
As for shopping, stop here.
Let's go.
Hold on.
What?
I have something to give you.
5 yen coin.
Yeah.
P said that Japanese people call 5 yen coins 'Go-en'.
It's pronounced like 'Go-en'.
Its meaning is to ask for blessings from God.
People who carry 5 yen coins, single people will find a good soul mate.
Whoever already has a lover, they will love each other for a long time.
Another meaning is...
to meet again.
Thank you.
I kept it especially for you.
Here.
I have one coin.
For you.
It will make us meet again in Thailand.
And love each other forever.
It's like the coin's prediction.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Shall we go?
Please pull me up.
P.
Beboy.
I'm going back.
Yeah.
Thank you.
My pleasure.
Please come see me sometimes if you have time.
I have many places I want to take you to.
Sure.
Hey.
Don't cry.
I told you not to cry.
Why are you crying?
Huh?
Well, I won't cry.
But, P.
Yeah.
Do I have a chance to meet you in Thailand?
I don't know.
Sometimes, I might go back to Thailand.
Who knows?
You said it.
Yeah.
If you are going back to Thailand, you must tell me first.
I don't know.
Take care yourself.
Yeah.
Thank you, P.
For not abandoning me and Pan that day.
My pleasure.
I apologize if I did something that offended you.
Same as me.
I hope we will meet again.
Good luck.
Plai.
Hurry up.
P.
Yeah.
Do you know?
That this trip
has brought me great happiness.
Thank you so much.
Don't forget to keep my promise.
Yeah.
I promise you.
Pan.
I have something important to tell you.
Uh...
I...
I wish you good luck.
Can I hug you one last time?
Sure.
♫ No matter how long we've been close to each other ♫
Safe flight.
See you.
♫ I'm still disappointed and can't get over it ♫
Good bye.
♫ I still feel the warmth of you hugging me ♫
♫ I'm still on the same path we walked together ♫
It's really art.
Hurry and take a look at this.
♫ I'm still on the same path we walked together ♫
♫ But when I looked at it again, there was only emptiness left ♫
Is it beautiful?
Good.
♫ But when I looked at it again, there was only emptiness left ♫
♫ I look at your picture, all I can do is look ♫
♫ I see you in my dreams every night, I imagine it every time I close my eyes ♫
♫ Some pictures made me cry ♫
♫ Record the moments when you are still with me ♫
♫ I want to go back to the old days, when we were still in love ♫
♫ No matter who I'm with, I still miss you ♫
♫ The better the memory, the more painful it is ♫
♫ I can never forget you ♫
♫ The old love is still deeply etched in my heart ♫
♫ Every word is still the same as in the past ♫
♫ I know it hurts, but why doesn't it end? ♫
♫ It's painful every time ♫
♫ I just need time to forget it ♫
♫ But don't be longer than this ♫
♫ Just being able to let go for a minute, ♫
♫ I'm pleased ♫
♫ You just come through and leave ♫
♫ You left a love story, I can't forget it ♫
♫ I want to thank you for making me know ♫
♫ the love that I thought was good ♫
♫ Today I got the answer, you don't need to explain ♫
♫ No matter who I'm with, I still miss you ♫
♫ The better the memory, the more painful it is ♫
♫ I can never forget you ♫
♫ The old love is still deeply etched in my heart ♫
♫ Every word is still the same as in the past ♫
♫ I know it hurts, but why doesn't it end? ♫
♫ It's painful every time ♫
♫ I just need time to forget it ♫
♫ But don't be longer than this ♫
♫ Just being able to let go for a minute, ♫
♫ I'm pleased ♫