Yes, tellQuin Affair
Episode 5
Cut
幹
Have
Cut
CHI
Should Stop
It's OK
C'mon
Cut
Stop
I'm afraid I'll be late.
Episode 8
Sister.
Why are you here?
You have such a broken wine house.
You don't like your own body.
Why do you treat Jin Niang like that?
Why do you mention him?
He left us behind.
He was only a piece of broken red cloth.
You're not a mother.
How dare you!
You hit me.
Do you have time to hit me?
Lang Zhong said that
you are already fatigued.
You won't be far from death
if you fight with the tiger.
Am I a bad man?
Yu'er.
Do you hate your mother so much?
Or else,
don't you hate her?
She left us behind.
There's no such mother in the world.
Mother, I want this red cloth.
It must be beautiful.
It's not suitable for a young girl.
I can't wear it
if a young girl wears it.
I want it.
I won't buy it for you.
Yu'er, I may not have money.
Am I your own sister?
You tell me.
Yu'er, wait for me.
Do you want this dress?
Brother, give me a discount.
Yu'er,
come out.
We have prepared the surprise.
Come out.
Yu'er.
Who are you?
You.
It's you.
Mother.
So my mother didn't abandon us.
So Xiaoyao
was also the one who lost her.
That's right.
Who is the murderer?
Did you find the murderer?
Father,
such a big thing happened.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I want to tell you.
You will put his dead body on your head.
I don't want you to live that life.
Your mother will not want it.
I won't.
I have kept this secret for years.
Now I tell you.
I am a good father.
Father.
I am sorry.
Yu'er.
I believe
that time can change everything.
Mother.
I will find the murderer to avenge you.
Yu'er.
Live well.
That's the biggest revenge for your mother.
Since I entered the Xunhuang,
I will go back to the past.
Don't let my mother die.
I want to change everything.
Yu'er.
I am back.
This dress is for the little girl.
It's not suitable for you.
Mother, I don't want this dress.
Yuan, this dress is not your favorite.
It's a foreign dress.
I just hope that you and mother can be by my side.
Father, you are so smart.
It's not important to me.
Yuan, you have grown up.
You are getting more and more mature.
Yuan, you are great.
Mother, we should be together forever.
We will never be apart.
Of course.
Otherwise, where else can I go?
Mother, let's go home.
Today is your birthday.
Don't you want to go out?
Let's go home.
Let's go.
Ghost King,
you haven't killed the Gu Yu'er you wanted in ten years.
I think you are not willing to do it.
You are more and more bold.
I will arrange for you to do it.
First, I am not your killer.
Second,
What is second?
I love her.
She only likes the third and fourth little girl.
She doesn't like you being the princess of Gao Gao.
If I am the princess of Gao Gao,
can I listen to you to invite me here?
You are useless.
Even if you become the empress, I will still be your brother.
If you don't go, someone will.
I am not your killer.
I love you.
You are useless.
Don't be silly.
I love you.
I can afford a zu murder for every hour of the night.
I don't want to be your lover,
I want to share our ordinary life experience.
Do you get angry?
The name is great, he only asks me to kiss
Hug, hug, hug
He only jokes with me, I'm far away
I don't want to be a bird in the sky
I don't want to be a bird in the sky, I don't want to be a bird in the sky
It turns out that this is a dream
This dream is great
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh