=Designated Love=
=Episode 8=
You said
Jiang Han wants to get back with you.
So?
What do you feel about it?
Nothing.
Did you have a change of heart?
What are you talking about?
Am I someone that looks for
the next lover as soon as I break up?
Isn't that just like cheating?
True.
If you like someone,
how long will it take?
For me,
just one second.
So you're the love-at-first-sight type?
I don't mean the second I meet the guy,
but the second
I develop feelings for the guy.
Maybe it's something he does,
or something he says...
You came.
Most likely it would be
because of physical contact...
Hey.
What are you thinking about?
Nothing.
I have one more question.
Say it.
What if
when you are about to kiss,
that person runs away?
Runs away?
Run where?
Just...
Runs away.
Will you get mad?
I won't get mad.
Because in my mind,
he is already dead.
I have to face him sooner or later.
(Game begins)
This is for you.
What do I need this for?
You suddenly left last time
and disappeared for days.
I figured you must be very angry.
You can stab me with it.
I won't get hurt or die anyway.
Yeah...
Jiang Xiaohan, you are really...
Really what?
What's so funny?
Isn't this enough for you to vent your anger?
I'm not some psycho killer.
This is...
Alright.
I'm not mad.
Really?
But,
you can't do that next time.
You must respect women.
Do you get it?
Yeah.
Next time when I want to kiss you,
I will ask for your permission first.
So...
Can I ask for your permission now?
Jiang Han. Xi.
What a coincidence.
Let's play together.
Is she also an NPC?
She is not sentient.
The system just got updated.
Not only are there new maps,
what's more, when you reach
a certain level of friendship level,
the game will
unlock special characters and storylines.
The creators of this game must be crazy!
Purposefully creating
this person to cause trouble!
Or maybe they think their playerbase is huge
and doesn't care
about their customers' satisfaction!
Were you the one that created her?
You are the only one in the game
that knows about my hatred for Shen Jingjing.
It's not me.
The game must have designed it
according to the players background.
I will never do anything to upset you.
It really wasn't me.
What can I do to make you believe me?
Forget it.
She is here already.
I don't think I'll come here often.
I don't want to be bullied
in both worlds.
What about me?
Are you leaving me?
I'll still come,
just less often.
Don't worry.
Don't give up on me
just because of her existence, okay?
She is just a character
forcibly added in by the system
while I am self-aware.
I know one thing for sure.
I don't care if she's Shen Jingjing,
Chen Jingjing, or Wang Jingjing.
I see no difference.
All I can see is you.
Why are the NPCs in this game
so good at flirting.
He says everything without feeling ashamed.
What are you guys talking about?
Let's talk together.
What's with you guys?
Tell me.
It makes me sick
when I hear the word 'together'.
You guys have fun chatting.
I need to go.
Don't go.
I don't care what storyline
the system has implanted in her mind.
In my eyes she is just a stranger.
Besides,
I'm not Jiang Han.
I'm Jiang Xiaohan.
Why aren't you guys holding my hands, too?
Let's hold hands together.
What did you do?
A game item I just got.
Sedative spray.
What do you think?
You didn't expect me
to use it on my kind, right?
Did what I do
make you believe me?
Not bad.
Ah...
I forgot.
This is a prank game.
If you don't get punched,
you won't get your salary.
In order to improve your survival abilities,
I've made up my mind.
I'll slap you every time I enter the game.
Am I good to you or not?
Just now...
I shouldn't have let her hit on me, right?
What do you think?
(Does being jealous mean I like him?)
(Is it wrong to be possessive?)
(Can humans date an NPC?)