♪When the whistle blows♪
♪No matter how hard the process♪
♪This time we're giving it our all♪
♪So what if we've failed before♪
♪When I look at you♪
♪No matter what the result is♪
♪One look and we understand♪
♪It's worth it if we give our all♪
♪You are my first choice♪
♪An unbreakable team♪
♪With a burning heart, dreams don't fade♪
♪This moment, let's give it our all♪
♪Give it all♪
=Go! Beach Volleyball Girls=
=Episode 11=
(Occupied, Xingang Haibo)
Come on. You two.
A captain and a team doctor.
It's natural to care for teammates.
But why drag me into this?
Aren't you part of our team?
I'm not the only one on the team.
Because Lang Yueting has caused
a psychological shadow for Weilan.
You and Lang Yueting are...
We don't want to know
about your relationship with her.
But you're the best in our team.
We need you to solve this problem.
Yeah.
You're the star player.
You're better than anyone.
You guys are just kidding around.
Gao, we can't do this without you.
Coming, coming.
- Grandpa, hello!
And you are?
I recognize this young lady.
Aren't you Weilan's roommate?
Yes, Grandpa.
What's your name again?
I'm Li Guoduo.
Yes, yes, Li Guoduo.
- Here to see Weilan?
- Yes, we're here to see her.
- Is Weilan home?
- Yes, yes.
Come in.
- Grandpa, I'm Shao Nian.
- Hello, hello.
- Grandpa, I'm Gao Ge.
- Hello, hello, hello.
Alright.
Please sit.
You all sit here for a bit.
I'll go call her.
She's still asleep.
She's always sleeping these days.
Sit for a while.
- Thank you, Grandpa.
- Sure.
Weilan,
wake up.
Get up.
Friends are here to see you.
Weilan's grandpa's house is so beautiful.
The environment is so nice.
It's quite lovely.
But the house
seems quite old.
Weilan.
Get up.
- Let's go check.
- Stop sleeping. Get up.
Weilan.
Duoduo and the others are here to see you.
Grandpa, let me take a look.
Weilan.
Grandpa, she's not here.
She was just sleeping here.
But now she's gone.
Weilan?
Grandpa.
Are these all Weilan's awards?
Yes.
These are all hers.
(Advanced Award, Certificate of Honor)
- Weilan has been
very independent since she was little.
She's very proud and competitive.
(Certificate of Award, First Place)
Her mind is also very simple.
Anything she sets her mind on,
she has to do it perfectly.
She didn't have many friends growing up.
People who don't understand her
think she's arrogant.
But really,
she needs understanding and companionship.
We all understand that.
(National High School Volleyball Tournament)
She won this trophy
(MVP)
in her first year of high school.
She's rarely lost on the court
since she was young.
Especially her powerful spikes.
They're impressive, right?
She won this trophy
with that move.
Truly impressive.
Okay, you all wait here.
I'll go find her. She won't have gone far.
- Alright.
- Sure.
Weilan?
Bro.
I shouldn't have come.
She must've heard my voice.
Chen Weilan isn't that sensitive.
Don't overthink it.
(Chen Weilan won first place in the First
Xingang City Beach Volleyball Game)
(Beijing No.8 High School Volleyball Club,
Advanced Award)
Found her.
Don't worry.
So, you are here.
Do you know how long we looked for you?
Why were you looking for me?
After your training that day,
you came to your grandpa's house,
and disappeared.
Do you know that I...
we were very worried about you?
I'm an adult now.
What could possibly happen?
We were just concerned about you.
What's there to worry about?
I just got tired from practice,
so I wanted some rest.
I came here to have a meal with my grandpa.
Do I need to report everything to you?
Chen Weilan,
people are worried about you. Please cooperate.
How long has it been since you trained?
Come back and continue training with us.
Do I need to report
whether I train or not?
I'm practicing every day.
Don't take what Li Guoduo said
on the beach volleyball court
too seriously.
She really wants to help you.
You know how she is.
She's impulsive
and thoughtless.
But I have to say.
She's right.
Your problem is because of Lang Yueting.
What does this have to do with her?
In the National Youth Team tryout,
Lang Yueting won the MVP.
This has always been
a knot in your heart, right?
Bro, you're obsessed with her,
but please be rational.
She won the MVP in that match,
but the one who won was me.
I won that match.
We watched the video of your match.
I reviewed
every detail carefully.
Every time Lang Yueting blocked,
you weren't in your best form.
You couldn't spike the ball successfully.
And this was just like
your performance the other day.
- So?
- Chen Weilan.
Volleyball
is about winning.
But before you beat others,
you have to beat yourself first.
Finished?
Here we are.
- Grandpa, Grandpa.
- Grandpa.
Come on, everyone. Sit at the table.
Let me serve, Grandpa.
- No problem.
- Let me do it.
- Thank you so much.
- Be careful. It's hot.
- Thank you, Grandpa.
- Careful with your hand.
- Careful.
- Well.
Let's not wait for them.
Let's start eating, okay?
It's alright, Grandpa. He found Weilan,
and they are coming back.
- Found her?
- Yes.
Speak of the devil, here they are.
Where did you go?
Everyone's been looking for you.
I just went for a walk.
Who knew they would come?
Alright, take a seat.
- Okay.
- Well.
I've prepared many dishes today.
Duoduo.
This is the steamed crab
you smelled earlier.
- Thank you, Grandpa.
- It's fresh.
- Try some.
- It smells amazing.
I wanted to eat it earlier.
You have some too. It's definitely delicious.
- Here.
- Look at that.
Look how easygoing Duoduo is.
Learn from her.
No, Grandpa, she's more easygoing than me.
Come on. Eat up.
Young man,
you're too thin.
Eat more. Get some nutrition.
- Okay, Grandpa.
- Eat more.
Grandpa, join us.
No worries. I have two more dishes.
They'll be ready soon.
Make sure everyone eats well.
You all eat first.
- Grandpa, thank you.
- Thank you, Grandpa.
Thank you.
Start eating.
You handled
that crab very well.
So meticulous.
No wonder you're in the arts.
Let me tell you.
That's called professional ethics.
If you gave me a needle and thread now,
I could sew it back together
and send it swimming.
- Really?
- No way.
Not eating anymore?
Finally, something I'm better at than you.
Come on.
I find it bothersome to handle.
Thank you.
It's pretty good.
Gao, I want to eat a crab from you.
From me?
Alright.
Then sew one for me.
Sure.
Take a break.
Rest for a while.
- Come on.
- Good for you.
You've improved your skills.
You know how to block now.
It was just luck.
Getting it right once is good enough for me.
But you should
improve your own skills.
Why learn from others?
Actually,
we already know
about you and Lang Yueting.
And
that your hand injury has healed.
We all know.
So,
tell us about your past.
So we can help you.
Weilan,
sharing isn't scary, nor is it shameful.
Look.
You have to face your problems
to have a chance at winning.
Look at me.
To play this match against you,
I've been practicing for a week,
from morning till night.
And you praised me for my progress.
I'm not like you.
I don't know so much about theories
and strategic tactics.
I just know
when facing my weaknesses,
I have to bravely overcome them.
I have to face them,
so I can change
and become stronger.
Weilan,
Guoduo has really done a lot
to help you.
I think you should trust her
and trust us.
Why do you love meddling in my business?
This isn't meddling.
We're partners.
We'll win many championships together.
Your business is my business.
Actually, my wrist
got injured
during a match with Lang Yueting.
It was the first time
my powerful spike got blocked.
I couldn't accept it
at the time.
So, every time I spiked after that,
I would use
more and more force.
So, my wrist got dislocated.
Lang Yueting seemed
to notice my problem,
and blocked me firmly.
So every time I was about to spike,
when I saw her,
I would instinctively
avoid her and get scared.
That's my biggest problem.
You need to learn from me.
Get blocked a few more times
and you won't be scared.
You're so good.
With your skills,
it takes some effort
to not block you.
Okay, okay.
From now on,
I'll focus on improving my skills,
and you
will work on your mental issues.
Let's work hard together.
Okay?
Actually, in psychology,
there's a method to treat psychological issues
called systematic desensitization.
If you want,
we can try it.
Weilan's
skills and physical fitness aren't perfect.
You don't have any other options.
You just have to accept it.
You're back.
Duoduo, Duoduo, Duoduo!
Before your dad was hospitalized,
he used to stand beside me
and give pointers.
I learned a lot every time.
Ever since he was hospitalized,
my training efficiency has plummeted.
Don't worry.
If you have any questions, just ask us.
We're all here to help you.
Come on.
You and Weilan
are always together, coming up with big plans.
Wen Xin and Xiaojing
don't even bother with me.
Jingxuan,
be fair with your words.
Haven't I been helping you?
Haven't I been correcting you?
Yes, you have.
I'm just anxious.
The Seven-School League is coming.
Gao Ge is competing.
I want to compete too.
Let's hope
you can compete in your senior year.
Only by competing in the Seven-School League
can we qualify for the national competition.
So each school can only have one team.
I want to compete.
I must compete.
Let's find a coach first.
Without a coach,
how can we register?
A coach...
Don't worry. I'll figure it out.
Leave it to me.
Duoduo, let me tell you something.
Go ahead.
Today, during practice,
I noticed...
Gao Ge.
Coach Gao.
Can you
find some time to teach me
about the one pass attack?
Sure. I'll teach you when I have time.
About this wristband.
How about
I buy you a new one?
Why?
Why waste money?
This one's fine.
Alright.
If you like it, keep it.
Weilan, did he give you
that wristband?
- No, I...
- Well.
It's okay.
No need to feel awkward.
It's fine. Really.
He can give it to anyone he wants.
This
quite suits you.
What?
Slow down. No one's taking your food.
I can't.
I have something important to do after eating.
Are you firing your dad?
You're posting an online ad for a coach?
The Seven-School League is about to start.
The beach volleyball team is in chaos.
Morale is down,
and so is the training efficiency.
I'm worried sick.
My hair's falling out.
Your hair's falling out?
I'll get you some anti-hair loss shampoo.
Relax. Tomorrow, I'll go to the hospital
and ask Uncle if there's anything we can do.
That's all we can do.
Hope someone sees the job posting
and contacts me soon.
This food is really good.
Did you make it?
Uncle and Auntie aren't here.
Who else would make it?
You're quite the talented one.
Making great progress.
When facing my weaknesses,
I have to bravely overcome them.
I have to face them,
so I can change
and become stronger.
Chen Weilan.
Volleyball is about winning.
But before you beat others,
you have to beat yourself first.
Dad.
Uncle Li.
- Uncle Li.
- What are you doing?
- Slow down, slow down.
- Slow down.
Why are you getting up? Stay in bed.
Lie down.
Slow down. Take it easy.
Slow down.
- It's okay.
- Are you okay?
I'll be fine after a rest.
It's okay.
Where's Mom?
The rent for the shop hasn't been paid yet,
so she's gone to sort out the bills.
Your mom's right.
I'm lying here
like a useless person.
The business is suffering,
and your training is being delayed.
It's really causing trouble.
Don't worry about it.
Since you're lying here,
just rest well.
Think of it as taking a vacation.
I've got things under control with the team.
I'm the captain.
Rest assured.
I'm not worried about others.
I'm worried about you, the captain.
You're always
so headstrong.
You'd be better off
helping your mom skewer meat.
Dad, didn't we agree?
During this year,
you do your coaching.
I play my beach volleyball.
We don't interfere with each other.
Of course, I remember.
But I'm telling you.
This six months is almost up.
I came today
to ask you about the coach situation.
Without you around,
we waste more time
every day.
The Seven-School League is coming.
We're in a hurry.
Look. Wait a minute.
Former renowned beach volleyball player
is returning from abroad.
He accepted the invitation
from the National Youth Team
to become their head coach.
Coach Lu is low-key by nature
and declined all interviews,
saying he wants to leave the spotlight
to the young players with more potential.
It's really him.
Uncle Li, do you know Coach Lu?
How could he?
He's the National Youth Team coach.
Twenty years ago, we were partners.
We were evenly matched,
but I got injured later.
Really?
I've never heard you mention this before.
It's nothing to talk about.
We were old partners
and played together for a long time.
I don't dwell on past glories.
Don't you know that?
You were the one who brought it up.
Uncle Li,
do you think Coach Lu
could coach
our beach volleyball team?
How could that happen?
Just wishful thinking.
(Turn Off, Turning Off)
I'm tired. I want to sleep for a bit.
Then take a nap.
Slow down. Don't move.
Slow down.
Let's go.
- Let's go.
We're leaving, Uncle Li.
Uncle Zhao, it's Shao Nian.
I know you have a lot of connections.
Can you help me find someone?
Yes, Lu Daxing.
Yes, yes. The National Youth Team coach.
I'd like his contact information.
Only a landline?
That'll do. Thank you, Uncle Zhao.
If you need anything, let me know.
Got it.
Paying back the money?
I will.
I'll pay you back when I have the money.
We've been friends for so many years.
I'll transfer the money when I have it.
Alright, alright. Stop talking.
I know.
I told you...
P2P lending?
I'll pay you back.
No need to threaten me.
Come on.
You see.
I invested
in a robotic vacuum company,
and now the company
is about to distribute dividends.
A million a month.
A month.
Okay, got it.
Just a month.
How much debt do you have?
Every call is about debt.
Clean it up.
You were doing well in the sailing team,
with good results.
Why did you quit
to do some unreliable business?
Alright, alright. Daxing.
You're right.
The sailing team
was my dream,
but now I want to start my own business.
I'm pursuing
a career
and taking high risks.
It won't go smoothly.
It's destined
to be dark
and unnoticed.
I've already thought it through.
It's destined to be a lonely journey.
Give me a break.
You've learned nothing in the past two years,
except how to talk your way out of things.
Who is it?
Hello, property management.
Don't open it.
You...
Which one of you is Lu Xiaole?
Lu Xiaole?
It's you, right?
It's so late,
and you're still sleeping on the sofa?
Lu Xiaole,
you owe Mr. Bao a million yuan,
and it's due.
Pay up.
Get up, get up.
Nice to meet you.
How about a drink?
No drinks.
Stop it.
- Just pay up.
- No money.
No money?
Come on.
Well. Rest assured.
I'm his cousin.
I'll make sure he pays up.
We're professionals at collecting debts.
We have countless ways to deal
with people like you who don't pay.
I know.
I've seen your methods.
Let me explain again.
Well.
A few years ago,
I invested
in a robotic vacuum startup.
The company
has been acquired by a large corporation.
In a month,
they'll distribute a million yuan in dividends.
Your money isn't a problem.
Enough talk.
All this talk
just means
you don't want to pay, right?
No, no, no.
No? Then pay up.
This is our first visit,
so we're being nice.
Three days.
If we don't see the money in three days...
Okay, three days.
Three days.
No problem.
It's settled then.
Well.
You two
can go now.
Go to the next place.
Three days.
- Three days.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Modern people complain
that life moves fast.
Can't we slow down?
It's just a month. Is it long?
They said three days.
Think about it.
Daxing.
Stop nagging.
I'll handle it.
Go do your thing.
They're chasing debt to our home.
My home.
Yes, it's your home.
It'll be okay.
- Where's my clothes?
- What clothes?
My coat.
Clean it up.
Be careful on the road.
No money.
Hello.
We're looking for Coach Lu Daxing.
Coach Lu isn't here.
We're from the Xingang Beach Volleyball Team.
Please let him know
we want to hire him
as our head coach.
Okay, got it.
(The Big Player)
You can't do this.
Not bad.
- Come on.
- Join us.
Liqiang.
Come here. I need to tell you something.
What's wrong?
- What's wrong?
- Today,
I got good news
about our beach volleyball team.
- Good news?
- What's wrong?
You're Duoduo's boyfriend now?
Can you be serious?
Remember Coach Lu
from the National Youth Team?
He agreed
to coach us.
What?
National Youth Team coach?
- Yeah.
- Coming to Xingang University
to guide us?
You heard right.
Not bad, Shao Nian.
Didn't think I'd get lucky
in my senior year.
Shao Nian.
How do you know people
from the National Youth Team?
I don't, actually.
But Uncle Li said
he and Coach Lu were partners.
So,
I connected them.
So, it's Duoduo's connections.
You just ran errands.
Without me running around,
he wouldn't agree.
Alright, alright.
You get the credit.
Now it's great.
With the National Youth Team coach,
Yan Xiaojing will win the league for sure.
The recommendation quota
for graduates is settled.
How about this?
I'll get a membership card
at Duoduo's BBQ place
and eat there every day.
You're not getting a card.
You're just looking for a bargain.
I'm boosting
their business.
Right. Stop joking.
Go tell the teacher
to arrange a dorm for Coach Lu.
He can't have nowhere to stay.
Dorm might not be good.
He's the National Youth Team coach.
He might not like it
and not coach us well.
We don't have extra funds
for lodging.
I don't think a coach like him
would mind.
What do you suggest?
Gao.
Think of a solution.
Fine.
The National Youth Team coach coming
is good.
I'll go to the restroom.
You guys talk.
What's up with Gao?
Upset about it?
He seemed fine just now.
I think
he's upset the coach is coming.
His thunder will be stolen.
You're being ridiculous.
Gao isn't like that.
When is Lu Daxing arriving?
Bought the ticket this afternoon.
He'll arrive tomorrow.
That's quick.
He must be short on time,
so he wants it to be quick.
Let's pick him up tomorrow afternoon.
Sure.
The dorm manager was helpful today.
Right.
Thanks to my face.
Oh, please.
Don't forget to buy some fruit
- for the help.
- Got it.
I'll leave it to the current captain's
future boyfriend.
No problem. I'll handle it now.
Come on, Liqiang.
Clean up.
Bye-bye.
That kid.
(Everyone thought I could
join the National Youth Team,)
(including myself.)
(But reality)
(often hits you hardest)
(when you're most confident.)
(That's when I realized)
(I was too naive.)
(National Youth Team Information,
Bulletin Board)
Mom, I made it.
Yes, I made it.
How about you two?
- As expected.
- Not a chance.
Another year wasted.
Try again next year.
Let's see it for you.
Look.
How could he fail?
Impossible.
I saw the teacher nodding.
You're still young.
If you don't make it this time,
there's next time.
I think
you should
go to college first.
After that,
you can switch to sports, right?
Actually,
life has many paths.
If this one doesn't work,
you can take another.
A thousand-mile journey
begins with the first step.
Let's take our time
and live well now.
(Beach Volleyball Activity Room)
Xia.
- No training?
- No.
The new coach is coming.
I'm organizing training plans.
The National Youth Team coach?
Gao told you?
How's that? Exciting, isn't it?
I'm okay.
But Gao Ge
didn't seem excited.
No way.
The National Youth Team coach is coming.
How can he not be excited?
Is something wrong with him?
You know your buddy best.
Xia Liqiang.
Did you ask the teacher for leave?
Yes. What did you do?
What else?
Writing my thesis and training.
The team
isn't training, right?
Can't I train extra?
The Seven-School League
is important to me.
I'm dedicated. Okay?
Fine.
Listen.
Do you know Coach Lu Daxing
from the National Youth Team
is coming to guide us?
The National Youth Team coach?
You're joking.
Why would he come to Xingang?
Why not?
Xingang is a hidden gem.
Our players have huge potential for their team.
Just Chen Weilan. Who else?
Me and Gao.
Who and Gao? I didn't hear it.
Stop teasing.
A National Youth Team coach coming
isn't exciting?
It's exciting.
It's the National Youth Team coach.
How long is he staying?
Just sightseeing?
You
are overthinking.
He's the National Youth Team coach.
Even a day's guidance
helps with our skills.
I envy your optimism.
Always happy.
Do all women
like to tell people off like this?
All women?
Besides me and your mom,
what other women do you have?
No, don't be so suspicious,
okay?
Are you going to tell me or not?
Which woman told you off?
Tell me. Tell me.
Chen Weilan.
Chen Weilan?
She said I don't care about Gao.
But actually, Gao
seems to have tried out
for the National Youth Team before.
Really?
I don't think Gao Ge
looks like someone with ambitions.
True.
He doesn't seem keen on things
that require drive.
He almost got suspended
because he didn't get along
with Coach Wang Dong.
Anyway,
the National Youth Team coach is coming.
That's a good thing.
Who invited him?
Shao Nian did.
He put in a lot of effort.
Make sure to keep this a secret
from Mo Xixi.
He wants to surprise Li Guoduo.
Look at him,
and then look at you.
What's wrong with me?
What surprises do we need?
We've been together for so long.
Stability is what's important now.
Oh, forget it.
What are you doing?
I just topped up my meal card,
and I also got one for Coach Lu.
So he can eat at the cafeteria when he arrives.
Is everything set?
Liqiang is cleaning the dorm right now,
so I came over to top up the meal card.
It'll be ready when he arrives.
Do you think
a National Youth Team coach
can live in a dorm
and eat at the cafeteria?
Honestly,
I'm a bit worried about that too.
They're used to better living conditions.
But with limited funds,
there's nothing we can do.
I'm curious to see
what changes he'll bring to our team.
There will definitely be changes.
But seven days of training seems too short.
Still, it's good that he's coming.
Let me check these two meal cards,
so they don't get mixed up.
I've already checked.
(Balance)
Didn't you say there was no budget?
This card is my meal card.
I was going to top it up with 300
but accidentally added an extra zero
and ended up topping it up
with my whole 3,000 living allowance.
I wanted to top up another card
with 1,000 for the coach,
but I'm afraid
I'll mix up the 3,000 and 1,000 cards.
- So I...
- Wait.
So, everything's okay, right?
Yes. Everything's fine.
Alright then. Let's eat.
Have you heard?
Heard what?
About the National Youth Team coach coming?
I heard it a long time ago.
Oh, so you already knew.
Is he handsome?
Can I get an autograph or a photo?
Xiaojing told us this morning.
You're behind on the news.
So, I'm the last to know.
Let me tell you.
Ever since being with Xia Liqiang,
I haven't needed to follow
hot topics or trending news.
Are we all going to pick up Coach Lu?
- Of course not.
- Why not?
Shao Nian invited Coach Lu
without telling Duoduo.
He wants to surprise her.
We can't spoil the surprise.
Got it.
Shao Nian is really sweet to Duoduo.
The three of them will pick up Coach Lu.
We'll stay here and wait for Duoduo.
Alright then.
Back to training.
Hey, bro.
How did you get
such an expensive car?
Do you have a secret way to make money?
Tell me.
Liqiang,
if you want to rent a car,
I can introduce you to this rental place.
You're so handsome.
They might give you a discount.
A rental?
Mascot,
you're spoiling him.
Who's not spoiling him?
What's Yan Xiaojing up to these days?
No, no. Put your phone away.
Why?
We're a team.
No infighting.
Seriously though,
how did you find
the National Youth Team coach?
Uncle Li mentioned before
he had a teammate in the National Youth Team
named Lu Daxing.
Uncle Li is hospitalized,
so I thought of reaching out to him.
Don't worry.
I've arranged the accommodation
and topped up the meal card.
Do you think he'll find
our arrangements too shabby?
He won't.
If Coach Lu was Uncle Li's teammate,
he must have been a student
at Xingang University too.
So,
he's our senior.
Got it.
Thanks, bro.
Your contributions to the team
will never be forgotten.
Don't flatter yourself.
He's not doing it for you.
He's doing it for the captain.
What are you doing?
Don't distract the driver
while driving.
Hello?
This is Lu Daxing.
Coach Lu.
We're on our way
to pick you up at the airport.
Go ahead.
There's no need to pick me up.
I'm already at your school's entrance.
You're already there?
Yes.
Just come to the school entrance
to pick me up.
Alright then.
He's arrived at the school?
Let's head back to the school.
We came all this way for nothing.
Didn't he say he was at the school entrance?
I'll call and ask.
Can't tell who it is.
Well.
Hello?
Are you Coach Lu?
Hello, hello. I'm Lu Daxing.
Hello, hello.
I'm Xia Liqiang,
the former captain
of the beach volleyball team.
This is my teammate, Gao Ge.
Coach, hello.
- This is our doctor and assistant coach.
- Hello, hello.
Shao Nian.
Hello, Coach Lu, I'm Shao Nian.
You said you were the former captain, right?
Where's the current captain?
Our current captain is Li Guoduo.
She's waiting for you at the court.
Alright.
Let's head to the dorms.
Coach.
We have limited funds,
so you might have to rough it out
with us in the dorms for a bit.
Staying in the dorms, huh?
Yeah.
Well.
Staying on campus is nice too.
A bit nostalgic. I like it.
Sorry about that, Coach.
How about we head to the dorms now?
No need.
Since I'm here to work
with the beach volleyball team,
I should go
to see the team first.
- Alright.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Off we go.
- Let's get in the car.
- The luggage.
I'll take care of it.
Nice car you've got there.
It's okay. It's rented.
When do you think the new coach will arrive?
Not sure.
They went to pick him up. They'll be here soon.
I'm really curious
what kind of person he is.
If he's a strict coach,
I'll put on more sunscreen.
But
if he's handsome,
I'll make a good impression.
What about your Longlong?
We've been training
on our own all this time.
I think we need a professional coach.
What do you think?
I'm not counting on a coach.
We'll just keep going on our own.
Keep pushing forward.
Everyone,
I have some good news.
Come on, Duoduo, Weilan, have a seat.
What's the good news?
You'll know in a moment.
Such a mystery.
Here they come.
Come on.
Let me introduce everyone.
This is
the coach from the National Youth Team.
Lu Daxing.
Everyone, let's welcome him.
- Welcome, Coach.
Welcome.
Welcome, Coach.
♪The more you're denied, the firmer you become♪
♪Being close to the dream
is already a blessing♪
♪With countless injuries, you're still joyful♪
♪Why care about those questioning voices♪
♪Even if everyone denies you♪
♪You still need to spread your arms♪
♪To embrace all with courage♪
♪No one can♪
♪Stop you from pursuing your dreams♪
♪Even if everyone denies you♪
♪You still need to spread your arms♪
♪To embrace all with courage♪
♪No one can♪
♪Stop you from pursuing your dreams♪