♪When the whistle blows♪
♪No matter how hard the process♪
♪This time we're giving it our all♪
♪So what if we've failed before♪
♪When I look at you♪
♪No matter what the result is♪
♪One look and we understand♪
♪It's worth it if we give our all♪
♪You are my first choice♪
♪An unbreakable team♪
♪With a burning heart, dreams don't fade♪
♪This moment, let's give it our all♪
♪Give it all♪
=Go! Beach Volleyball Girls=
=Episode 20=
Duoduo, Duoduo.
Come here.
Check this out.
This looks great. It's so cool.
This is good.
Right?
This...
Shao...
Xixi, look.
I told you it was cool, right?
(Shao: Monster attacks.)
(Gotta save the world.)
(Don't worry.)
Mom, what are you doing here?
Why? Can't I be here?
How else can I pick you up?
I didn't mean it like that, Mom.
Do you still remember I'm your mom?
You just gave ice cream to a girl.
Is she your girlfriend?
She's not.
She's just a friend.
I don't think your relationship
is just friendship.
Wasn't the money spent
on your credit card for her?
No, it wasn't spent on her.
Then where did the money go?
I...
I spent it elsewhere.
Really, it wasn't for her.
Not for her?
Why are you staying
at her family's barbecue place?
Mom, are you spying on me?
Sweetie,
I'm not worried about the money.
I'm worried you'll be deceived.
There are many girls
who are vain
and manipulative these days.
They say
they don't want boys to spend money
on them to enhance their appeal.
Sweetie, don't get tricked.
She stays close to you
and lets you stay at her place.
Isn't that manipulative?
Mom, please stop
making baseless accusations.
Duoduo is not like that.
Fine, I won't say more.
You're coming home with me.
I'm not going.
Alright, then.
Should I go to your school
or her barbecue place?
You choose.
Mom...
This looks great.
Looks good.
- This one.
- You've improved.
Yeah.
What's going on?
- Who's that?
- Who is it?
Isn't that Du Weilong's car?
- Check it out.
- Let's go.
Oh, my.
What are you doing?
Driving like that?
Exactly.
Seriously, who is this?
What are you doing?
Can you actually drive?
That's too dangerous.
I'm really sorry. I apologize.
Good thing nothing happened,
or who would be responsible?
Xixi,
I apologize
for my previous behavior,
and I also apologize
to all your teammates.
I acted rashly.
Can you forgive me?
Are you done?
If so, leave.
Can't you see you're not welcome?
Hey,
I'm really here to apologize.
Won't you give me a chance?
I even brought gifts.
Don't you want to see them?
Please consider it.
Let's talk privately,
okay?
Why are you so persistent?
I'll call the police.
It's okay, Duoduo.
Alright.
I'll talk to you privately.
- Xixi.
It's okay.
What's going on between you two?
If you don't want to go,
we won't let you.
It's fine. Don't worry.
Let's go.
Let's talk privately.
Okay. Don't be mad.
I'm here to apologize.
I'll treat everyone to dinner.
Please forgive me.
No way.
This guy really has thick skin.
They're...
reconciled already?
That was fast.
All good now.
Let's go over there.
Weilong said he wanted
to join us for the celebration.
He genuinely apologizes to everyone.
Maybe
we should let him join us for dinner.
He's treating us.
Yeah.
Don't get me wrong.
We've come to know each other.
Duoduo.
Weilan.
Fine.
We can pretend he's invisible.
Think it over.
There are a few seats left in Weilong's car.
- Who's coming with me?
- Not me.
How about we go with Xixi?
We'll go with you, Xixi.
Alright, let's go.
- Drive safely.
- Let's go.
Xiaojing? Why?
Don't worry.
I need to accompany her.
Let him drive slowly.
Let's go have something good to eat.
Let's go.
They're back!
(Congrats to Xingang's
Beach Volleyball Team)
Welcome, welcome!
Welcome!
Congratulations.
Congrats, great performance!
Great performance! Hurry.
Let's set the table.
- Time to eat.
- Let's go.
- Let's eat!
Great, fantastic!
- Congrats!
- Come on in!
Xia Liqiang.
Let's celebrate properly today.
Come on in.
Dafu, you should restock later.
The back room doesn't have much left.
Okay.
Mrs. Li,
I think our promotion
was really effective this time.
We have a lot of customers coming,
and many investors are impressed with us.
Next time, I'll increase our efforts.
I haven't thanked you yet.
You're good at doing business.
Right?
The business has really picked up.
Thank you.
No problem.
It looks
like the beach volleyball team is on track now.
Coach Lu,
keep an eye on the girls
and make sure they train well.
Don't worry. Leave it to me.
Bring a plate over.
Coming.
- Alright, good.
- Here.
- Eat.
- Leave it to me.
Okay.
Welcome, everyone!
Eat more.
- Enjoy!
- Coming.
Definitely. We'll dig in.
Kebabs are here.
Eat up, everyone.
Plenty to go around today.
Thank you, Uncle.
Li, just in time.
The first drink
is to thank Dafu
for the training plan.
Without his meticulous plan,
we might not have made it today.
- Come on!
- Thanks, Coach.
- Cheers!
Well.
I just talked.
The real credit goes
to your talent and hard work.
This drink is for you.
- Thank you, Dafu.
- Thank you.
- Thanks, Coach.
- Thanks, Uncle.
That's enough, Dad.
Good drinkers!
- Duoduo, get everything ready.
- Okay.
- You go.
- Enjoy.
I'll handle it.
Eat up while it's hot.
Come on, eat, eat!
- Try this.
- This.
- This is good.
- Coach.
Sure.
Coach, you eat too.
You two are so sweet.
Please stop.
Let me tell you.
We're mostly single here.
If you don't treat us well,
we'll outdrink you.
I'm so scared.
Let's bow to the power.
How about we punish ourselves with a drink?
Go on.
Fill it up.
We'll drink on our own.
- Not with us.
- Cheers!
- Just us then.
- Coach!
We'll drink.
- Coach, come on.
- Sure.
- Well.
- Eat up.
I was wrong last time.
I'm apologizing again today.
Can I refuse?
Of course.
It's your choice.
Well said.
Apologizing is your choice.
Forgiving is mine.
And who had the right to smash the shop?
I was impulsive.
You won't hold grudges, right?
Stop.
I'm petty.
I can't let it go.
I'm the type to seek revenge.
So, what do you
want me to do?
What do I want?
It's simple.
Open a shop,
and I'll smash it
to vent my anger.
How's that?
Alright, alright.
What's with all this?
We're here to celebrate, right?
Let's raise a glass to wish
Xiaojing and Xixi success
in their match the day after tomorrow.
Yes, to Xiaojing and Xixi!
You can do it!
- Go for it!
- Thanks, everyone.
You can do it.
- Cheers.
You have to win.
Seems we got
to know each other because of it.
We didn't actually fight,
but we still got acquainted.
Xixi, Xiaojing, come here.
Make sure to perform well
in the next match.
You're quite strong.
- Don't slip up.
- OK. Thanks.
- Go for it.
- Do your best.
- We'll do our best.
- Cheers.
Won't let you down.
Ladies,
give us some face.
Xixi's still here.
Though what Du did before
was pretty scummy,
he did apologize.
Right?
Let's all calm down.
Calm down.
Just endure it
for Xixi's sake.
Alright?
Fine, fine.
I'll just ignore him.
But I won't change my attitude
towards him.
I'll try to be a bit more natural,
but talking to him depends
on my mood.
I'm really scared of you two.
Here come the kebabs!
Xixi, why aren't you inside
eating with everyone?
- What would you like?
- Take this.
Sorry, Uncle and Auntie.
I came out to apologize
for what happened last time
when my boyfriend caused trouble.
It was our fault.
He's here today
and will come out to apologize.
The one who smashed our shop
was your boyfriend?
He is here?
It's packed. I didn't see him.
I need to talk with him.
Auntie, don't be angry.
He came today
to celebrate
with Duoduo for Xiaojing and me.
What happened was our fault.
I didn't ask him to apologize right away
because I was worried
you wouldn't accept it.
If you want,
I'll call him out to apologize.
I'll go now.
- Xixi, Xixi.
- I...
No need.
Let your auntie calm down first.
You go back inside.
Go.
Sorry, Uncle.
Sorry, Auntie.
It's alright. Go on.
Okay, I'll head back now.
Sorry, sorry.
It's fine. No problem.
I keep my word.
- Duoduo.
- I'll drink.
Listen to me, Duoduo.
Duoduo,
last time, I was impulsive
and said the wrong things.
I'm sorry. This is to you.
Xixi, you don't have to do this.
Xixi.
Xixi, don't drink so much.
Just a sip. No need for so much.
- Don't drink anymore.
- Xixi.
You've had too much.
It's okay. I'll drink with her.
If you don't forgive us today,
we'll keep drinking
until you do.
- Come on.
You can't do this.
Pour her less, please.
Don't stir things up.
It's all my fault.
- Stop drinking.
- Xixi.
What are you doing?
Stop drinking.
Give it to me.
You've had too much.
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong?
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
I'm sorry.
It's alright. It's not your fault.
No one's blaming you. Not your fault.
- Okay?
- I'm sorry.
No one's blaming you.
Stop blaming yourself.
- Don't cry.
- I'm sorry.
Duoduo, I'm sorry.
- I'm not blaming you. No one is blaming you.
- Sorry.
Stop blaming yourself.
It's all my fault.
No.
No one is blaming you, right?
No one.
Not your fault.
You've had too much.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. It's really okay.
Sit down.
Stop drinking.
You've had too much.
What do you mean by this?
Did you not see how badly the shop
was trashed last time?
I even hurt my back.
And now he has the nerve to eat here?
I have to go say something to him.
Alright, alright.
Young people
can be impulsive sometimes
and make mistakes.
It's normal, right?
It's understandable.
Right?
Besides,
with so many customers here,
causing a scene
would affect business.
Think about it.
He's Duoduo's classmate's boyfriend.
If we fall out,
how will Duoduo handle it
at school?
I think
we should let it go.
Why do I always do this?
It's all my fault.
- Stop blaming yourself.
- Okay, got it.
- We trust you.
- We're coming.
Okay. Alright.
It's okay. There, there.
- Sorry.
- Don't cry.
I think
let's end here.
Let's go.
My friend has a room.
Let's go sing.
- My treat!
- Yeah.
Let's go sing.
Let's go have some fun.
So you're suggesting
the girls go drinking with you?
That's not appropriate.
You can go on your own.
No one here wants to go with you.
Take care.
You're not going anywhere.
I'm not.
It's fine.
If you want to go, call me anytime.
My friend runs a place.
I'll get you a discount.
Xixi, we're leaving.
- Let's go.
- I...
- Xixi.
Everyone, I'm off to have some fun. Bye.
Xixi, no...
- What?
- She's had too much to drink.
I need to check on her.
Xixi, Xixi.
This is...
Xixi.
(Dafu BBQ)
Duoduo.
You're drunk. You can't go anywhere.
She's had too much. I'll take her back.
We have a room here. She can stay with us.
You're not reliable to me.
I'm her boyfriend. Don't worry.
Let go.
Fine.
Since you're drunk,
you should stay here.
Call me if you need anything.
Goodnight.
Take good care of her.
Let's go.
(I must save the world. Urgent.)
You need to tell me if you're safe.
What if aliens abducted you?
(Don't worry. Wait for my safe return.)
You've been silent
since you came home.
What?
Giving me the silent treatment?
Right?
If you don't speak, I will.
Work and relationships
are major life events.
You need to think carefully.
This girl is not suitable for you.
Even if you're together now,
you'll eventually break up.
When you're more mature,
you'll look back
and regret
wasting this time.
Why would I regret it?
Why would we definitely break up?
We have true love.
True love?
You finally admit you're in love.
Let me tell you.
There's no such thing as true love.
Everyone is selfish
and has their own agenda.
Don't be naive.
(1 message on WeChat)
Are you asleep?
What? Have you defeated the monster?
♪Under the sun, the waves are shining♪
♪Who's laughing around♪
The monster is too strong.
I need to come up with a plan.
♪Your courage burns bright♪
Do you need backup?
♪The shadow is like the sketch of a memory♪
Of course not.
This little trouble is no match for me.
Just wait for my safe return.
Will you make it
in time for the match the day after tomorrow?
You promised to watch it with me.
♪Wanting to hold you tight♪
♪Let the time stop♪
Of course, I will.
I wouldn't
break a promise.
Don't worry.
♪I like every second of you♪
♪I want you to know♪
♪My love for you is hidden in my smile♪
♪You let me know♪
♪I like your shine♪
♪Waiting for your coquetry♪
♪That moment is wonderful♪
(Dafu BBQ)
♪I like your smile♪
Xixi.
Are you up? It's time to eat.
Xixi?
♪Let the time stop♪
♪Ferment the beauty♪
♪See tomorrow's tide♪
♪I like every second of you♪
Why are you alone?
Where's Xixi?
I woke up and didn't see her.
I thought she was here.
She's not here?
She's not.
Li Guoduo.
Yan Xiaojing. Warm up.
- We'll start practice.
- Got it.
Maybe she drank too much last night
and hasn't gotten up yet.
I'll check on her after practice.
Where's Chen Weilan?
She's on sick leave.
She's on sick leave?
What are you doing, Gao? Keep going.
Sure.
Your wrist used
to dislocate habitually.
From this X-ray,
it's healing well.
But you need to be careful,
or it might recur.
But recently,
whenever I exert too much force,
it hurts a lot here.
Is it a bone problem, or...?
No.
It's not a bone issue.
It's
neural pain
caused by hitting.
It didn't damage the bone.
Rest for a few days,
and the pain
should ease.
But be careful in the future,
or you won't be as lucky
next time.
- Okay.
- Get some medicine.
Thank you.
(Room 6)
Hello, Coach Zhang?
Weilan,
how have you been?
Keeping up with training?
I'm training every day.
It's a pity you didn't
make the NYT last time.
Though there's nothing
wrong with your skills,
your playing style is too solo-focused.
I believe
you've noticed this issue yourself.
Coach, are you calling
to mock me?
You silly girl.
Of course not.
By the way, I have good news.
The NYT
is coming to your university
to scout players soon.
This is a great chance to prove yourself again.
Perform well
and aim
to rejoin the team.
The NYT is coming to our school?
Yes.
How's that?
I...
What? Is there a problem?
I'll think about it.
What's there to consider?
Coach Zhang,
I have something to do. I'll talk to you later.
Why are you here?
Is your hand
okay?
It's fine.
I overheard you considering
leaving the beach volleyball team
for the NYT.
Is that true?
I haven't decided yet.
Why?
Why what?
The is just getting on track.
Leaving now seems
irresponsible.
Irresponsible?
I'm an indoor volleyball player,
now playing beach volleyball.
Who's responsible for my future?
So, you still have that idea, don't you?
I don't.
If you leave,
what about
Li Guoduo
and me?
You don't care, do you?
Fine.
I get it.
Li Guoduo,
can you
hit the ball harder?
That's easy for the opponents to and score.
Do you understand?
And you, Yan Xiaojing.
Are you still half-asleep?
I... I...
Lu!
Xiaole!
Long time no see!
What?
Not going to greet
- an old friend?
- Yeah.
You're free today?
Yeah. Just passing by.
Thought we'd drop in
to visit you.
Should we discuss
our matter
here
or elsewhere?
Definitely not here. Let's go over there.
Let's go.
Coach,
is everything okay?
These two are my brothers.
- Brothers.
- Let's go.
Good brothers.
The wind is giving me a headache.
Excuse me. Which one of you is Coach Lu?
Coach Lu just left.
What do you need?
The administration is having a meeting.
It's urgent.
Maybe one of you could go instead?
- Okay.
- Sure.
What are you doing?
Mr. Lu, we'll take these two with us.
Please cooperate and come with us
to make a statement.
Explain to the police.
Debts should be repaid.
You need to explain this.
- Let's go.
- Coach Tian...
You should come with us.
Get in that car.
Secretary, you asked for me?
Li Guoduo, come in and sit.
I heard your beach volleyball team
is doing well.
Making it to the finals in the league
is quite an achievement
for our university.
We have some strengths.
We also owe it
to the school's support.
Actually, I called you here
not for something important.
I heard that your team
was criticized by other schools
for accepting sponsorships
and promoting ads
during matches.
This shows
our school's influence.
They knew we had limited resources,
so they donated supplies out of goodwill.
We, in return,
upheld the virtue
of gratitude and helped
spread their goodwill.
You are
a good speaker.
It's not that your actions were wrong.
After all,
getting sponsorship
is a legitimate commercial activity.
But don't forget.
You represent the school
and the beach volleyball team.
It's about the school's reputation.
So, the administration
has decided to supervise
the sponsorship funds
to prevent
any controversy
and ensure everything
is in order.
Don't be surprised.
The supervision
isn't to take over
but to verify your accounts.
This way,
if any issues arise,
the school can step in
to resolve them.
This is crucial
and also a form
of protection for you.
Understood, Secretary.
I'll bring the financial details right away.
Liqiang,
the school wants us to inventory
the sponsored items.
I'll go home and check,
and you guys check the stuff
in the activity room.
Where did it go?
Twenty-six.
There are five of these.
Okay, five.
Oh, my.
What's going on here?
Don't ask.
Someone was jealous
of our sponsorship
and reported us to the school.
Now we have to inventory.
Why are only you guys here?
Where are the others?
- Duoduo went home.
- 18 red flags.
Lu Xiaole
went to find
business partners.
I haven't seen Chen Weilan all day.
Yan Xiaojing went to find Mo Xixi.
- So it's just
- Pack this up.
the three of us left.
Alright, stop dawdling.
Hurry up and help out. Hurry.
- Ten.
- Okay.
Can you check that for me?
- Sure.
- Alright, thanks.
This one has ten.
Hello, Duoduo, what's wrong?
Liqiang, the ledger is missing.
What?
Duoduo, are you sure
you've checked everywhere?
I've checked everywhere.
I even asked my parents.
They said they
didn't touch it at all.
But only our team
and your parents knew
about this ledger.
Yes.
Who would take the book?
What's the use of it?
I'm back.
What's going on? What happened?
The ledger is missing.
What?
Where's Coach Lu?
He left with business partners.
Business partners?
He said they were partners,
but it didn't
seem like it.
Those people were pretty intimidating.
Who's in charge of the funds?
Coach Lu.
He said we need money for meals,
transportation, and other expenses.
You suspect Coach Lu?
No way.
Coach Lu doesn't seem like the type to do this.
We trusted him so much.
Yes. Besides,
he only took a ledger.
What could he do with it?
Come in.
Weilan, have you seen Xixi?
No.
Ledger?
What ledger?
The sponsorship ledger?
Are you suspecting
that I took it?
You suspect me?
I understand.
Though I'm a loser
and my life is a mess, I have principles.
I would never steal.
Do you think I would?
I wouldn't.
Besides,
if I took the money...
If I took the money,
would I be so miserable?
Would I be heartbroken?
Coach, calm down.
We believe you.
Just a few days.
Can't you wait?
Can't you give me a chance?
Just a few days.
You doubted me.
Where did Coach Lu go?
He got upset.
How could the ledger disappear?
Did a thief break into our shop?
But if a thief broke in,
why just take the ledger?
What's the use of that?
Yeah.
I have a plan.
(Kitchen)
What's this?
- Mo Xixi.
Wasn't she drunk yesterday?
How could she...
This...
Why did she do this?
It's quite obvious.
She's trying to destroy evidence.
That can't be.
Xixi isn't like that.
Duoduo,
I know you don't want to doubt your teammate,
but the evidence is clear.
The school is investigating our accounts.
You're the captain.
If you don't have it,
do you know what it means?
Xiaojing.
Something's wrong.
What happened? Take your time.
I can't find Mo Xixi.
What?
We're here. This is the place.
I heard from Xiaojing
that Xixi used to come here
with Du Weilong.
Let's split up
once we go inside.
- Alright, let's go.
- Let's go.
Welcome. Please come in.
Let's check over there.
Let's go.
Xixi.
Why are you here?
Yao Xiaojing told us about you
and Du Weilong.
He's threatening you, isn't he?
Don't be afraid. We're here now.
Let's go. What are you scared of?
It sounds scary.
Is this your first time?
What do you want to drink? It's on me.
Did you drink too much?
Let's go home.
Don't touch me.
I'll go home by myself.
What's wrong?
Black is waiting for us.
Let's go.
Didn't we have a BBQ with her yesterday?
Come on, join us.
She's not here for fun.
She's about to leave.
Don't make Black wait. Let's go.
I'll give you a discount. Find me.
Wait, wait.
I came here to have fun.
What else would I do here if not drink?
Let's go. Come on.
Let's go.
Black,
this is Xixi's teammate,
Chen Weilan.
She came to our bar.
I brought her over
to have a drink with you.
Alright, come. Xixi.
Come over and sit.
Come here.
Long time no see.
You've lost weight.
Really?
You've lost a lot
since I last saw you.
Really?
You're flattering me.
It's true.
You're so thin now.
- This figure is so attractive.
- Really.
- Black, let me toast you.
- Cheers, cheers.
Why is your friend so quiet?
That's
just her nature.
She's not talkative.
Chen...
Chen Weilan, Chen Weilan.
Weilan. Come on.
Let's all have fun.
- Have a drink.
- Alright.
Alright.
- Drink less.
- Come on.
Come on.
Black, don't get drunk.
Cheers!
Great.
Weilan's a good drinker.
Weilan can hold the liquor.
Today, you must drink more
- with Black.
- Okay.
Black, I'll drink with you.
Black, let me.
This drink is for getting to know you.
For the next round, let's change the game.
Change the game?
OK. Sounds interesting.
Sure.
- Come on.
- Stop drinking.
Come on, come on.
Anyone else? Wanna play?
- Come on. I'll go.
- Come on.
- Go on.
I'll go.
Come on.
I lost.
I'll drink.
- Drink.
- Great.
Black, good for you.
Again.
Come on.
Roll.
- Let's see.
- Come on.
Xixi lost.
Drink!
- Lost.
- My fault.
Can you handle it?
Bottom up.
- I'll go.
- Come on.
- I'll play.
- Go on.
- What game?
- One dice.
Let's compare the number. Come on.
Roll.
- Same, same. Roll again.
- Drink, drink.
You lost. Make her drink.
Don't come over.
I'll drink. I'll drink.
I'll drink.
Great drinker.
I'm fine.
- Fill it up.
- Black.
The investment I mentioned earlier
is a sure thing.
If you don't invest, you'll miss out.
Have a look.
Weilong.
Not today.
Let's discuss this later.
Let's focus on drinking
and having fun.
Black, listen to me.
Come on.
- Drink.
- Black.
Black.
What's the matter?
She's going to puke.
I'll take care of her.
Hurry back. I'm waiting for you.
- Be back soon.
- Come on.
Come over. Come, drink.
Come here.
Let's drink.
Slowly, slowly.
Oh, my god.
Xixi, how is she?
Look at her.
I'm fine. I'm okay.
Let me tell you.
She and Du Weilong have debts.
He's dragging her into drinking
with investors.
Weilan, Duoduo.
Don't worry about me.
You should leave first.
Mo Xixi,
do you think we can
leave you here alone?
It's just a few drinks.
It's not a big deal.
Don't worry about me.
Mo Xixi,
do you know who those people outside are?
Are you crazy?
Do you think
a few drinks can solve this?
You still want to drink?
Fine, we'll leave.
Go drink outside.
We'll leave you here.
It's not like that.
I didn't write those IOUs.
I didn't.
So many.
So many IOUs.
- Get up.
- I didn't.
- I didn't write them.
- Get up.
- I never wrote them.
- There's a seat. Let's go.
From what we understand,
this campus loan
involves serious fraud.
This group is skilled
at forging identities
and deceiving women.
When they succeed,
they'll use victims' info to lend
high-interest loans.
They then transfer the debts
to these women
and use threats to force them
into borrowing more.
Officer,
do you know their identities?
We only recently
caught two thugs near the school,
which led us to some clues.
According to our current information,
their leader is someone named Du Weilong.
- Du Weilong?
Do you recognize this person?
I didn't.
It's not me.
I didn't write those IOUs.
Was it Du Weilong using your identity?
I wanted to report it,
but he threatened me.
He said he'd kill me
if I went to the police.
What should I do?
I'm scared.
I'm so scared.
It's all because of Du Weilong.
He's got something on me.
I don't want my life to end like this.
What does he have?
Take this.
All good now.
Let's go.
What about the ledger?
♪The more you're denied, the firmer you become♪
♪Being close to the dream
is already a blessing♪
♪With countless injuries, you're still joyful♪
♪Why care about those questioning voices♪
♪Even if everyone denies you♪
♪You still need to spread your arms♪
♪To embrace all with courage♪
♪No one can♪
♪Stop you from pursuing your dreams♪
♪Even if everyone denies you♪
♪You still need to spread your arms♪
♪To embrace all with courage♪
♪No one can♪
♪Stop you from pursuing your dreams♪