Yes, hello?
Yes, right.
It made me wonder if she was the same person from last night.
She was in perfect Team Leader mode.
Am I the only one who hasn't snapped back to reality?
Yes, Mr. Park.
Let's go with Plan A.
If any issues come up, contact me immediately.
That look in her eyes...
Several times a day,
it lifts a person up and brings them down.
Ms. Lee Hayoon.
Do you have a moment?
Yes, Ms. Kwon.
The competitor analysis data I requested.
Is this the best you can do?
Oh, well...
I tried to organize it based on the most objective data possible.
This figure and this figure...
They're from two different sources.
How can you just list them
without any standard for comparison?
This isn't an analysis; it's just a copy-paste job.
Don't you consider the reader's perspective?
I'm sorry.
I must have overlooked that part...
It's basic. This is fundamental.
Since you're new, it's understandable that you might not know.
But if you keep repeating mistakes,
it's not a mistake anymore, it's a lack of skill.
By 3 PM today,
get this up to an acceptable standard.
Bring it back to me.
This is the rule we set.
At the office, we are perfect strangers.
With the same lips that said "I love you" last night,
she now hurts me.
[Hey, Team Leader Kwon was on fire again today.]
[She was especially focused on Lee Hayoon, wasn't she?]
[She's always tough on newbies.]
[But with Lee Hayoon...]
[It seems particularly so.]
[I wonder if there's something going on between them?]
[Ms. Kwon: Break room. 5 minutes.]
You have to eat.
You'll upset your stomach.
Ms. Kwon, this...
I was too harsh earlier.
Still, you need to show me results, Ms. Lee Hayoon.
I'm expecting a lot.
Focus.
This is her way.
The ice-cold whip,
and every once in a while,
a very small carrot.
And with just that one small gesture, my foolish heart skips a beat again.
What's the problem?
Are you stuck?
The layout in this section looks too cluttered.
Align the text,
and reduce the image size a bit.
And as for this data,
if you visualize it like this,
it will be a little more persuasive.
Ms. Kwon...
If you do this here...
You're my undoing.
But...
I can't breathe.
You need to focus, Ms. Lee Hayoon.
Just finish organizing this and go home.
It's too late.
Ms. Kwon...
I'm not 'Ms. Kwon' right now, am I?