"Ashes of Love"
"Episode 14"
You must have mistaken.
How would that be?
Well...
since Jin Mi is no longer in danger,
I shall not disturb you all any longer.
I'll visit again another time.
Everyone has done something
right and wrong,
all the immortals have
their own stories.
Right now there are no outsiders,
you all have no need to
conceal it from me.
I know that you all have
sworn an oath to Zi Fen.
I won't make things
difficult for you all.
Just now I've just
checked Jin Mi's spirit,
even if you all want to hide it
from me, you won't be able to.
I'm only going to ask you one thing.
Is Jin Mi born during the frost fall?
It's true.
Mi...
These 4000 years,
I have never done anything
a father should.
Zi Fen has passed away,
I am ashamed to see her.
Mi...
Let father help you up.
Here...
This...
Father?
Immortal,
you have mistaken.
Is my fault that I didn't
look after you well.
If you are not willing to
recognise me as your father,
I will not be angry at you.
No...
It's not like that.
It's not that I don't want to
recognise you,
it's that you have mistaken
me as someone else.
I'm just a normal grape fairy,
raised by nature.
Even if I want to scam or pretend,
I wouldn't dare to
do it to you, right?
Silly girl,
how can you be a grape fairy?
Just now I've checked your spirit,
you are indeed the child
of Zi Fen and I.
Zi... Zi Fen?
Which? Which Zi Fen?
In all six realms,
who dares to have the same name
as late Floral immortal?
The late Floral immortal?
I'm the child of
late Floral immortal?
Oh my!
I cannot simply dream.
State of illusion,
I've pretended to be the late
Floral immortal's descendant,
scammed the Heavenly Emperor
for 5000 years prowess,
indeed now I'm facing
retribution from it.
Late Floral immortal,
please forgive me.
Quickly wake up.
One, two, three...
I'm... I'm not dreaming?
Is... Is this real?
I...
I've been a grape fairy for
the past 4000 years.
Right now, am I...
a drop of water or a flower?
You spirit must have been sealed off
by Zi Fen using the Garan Seal.
Therefore your true form
is not this entity.
Also because of this, training your
prowess was an obstacle.
Your body also looks a bit younger.
I'll bring you to my Master,
Xuan Ling Lord Doumu,
to seek for the counter spell,
then you'll be able to
get back your true form.
Chief Peony,
is that true?
Late Floral Immortal
concealed the truth...
to protect you.
Since you've exposed your true
form in the Heaven Realm,
it can no longer be concealed.
It's good that Water Immortal is
protecting troublemaker like you.
Are fathers so easy
to be found nowadays?
Yesterday I had one,
today I have another one.
But since Chief Peony has
already confirmed it,
it must be true.
I didn't think that I would have
a father and mother.
Fa... Father.
Are you really my father?
Let me bring you home.
I will never leave you
behind anymore,
causing you to be so lonely.
Okay...
It's okay.
But you all told me that I'm the
late Floral immortal's child...
but the late Floral immortal
passed away for 4000 years ago.
I've never even seen her once...
or to know what she looks like.
Although you mother is
not around anymore...
but you still have father.
As long as I'm here,
I will accompany you forever.
By the way.
Mi.
Right now your body is filled with
yang energy that's burning furiously.
Where did you get it?
To solve it, we must find
the one that casts it.
In this current state of urgency,
we have to find that person...
to retrieve the prowess
that's working against you.
I... I didn't ask for it.
He gave it to me.
He gave it to me,
do I really need to give it back?
In this situation, why are you still
thinking about the prowess?
If you don't give back,
you'll die from vomiting blood.
No. Last night, Heavenly
Emperor brought my spirit...
to the state of illusion.
He gave me 5000 years of prowess,
it has nothing to do with me.
Heavenly Emperor?
What did he say to you?
He said...
He...
He is also my father.
What a joke.
Indeed the biggest joke in the world.
This shameless person,
how can he be the master
of the Heaven Realm?
If it wasn't for Heavenly Emperor,
the late Floral Immortal's soul wouldn't be
destroyed and wouldn't die in hatred.
Calling him the murderer of Jin Mi's
mother will not be too far off.
Father?
What a joke!
How could he?
Begonia!
What did you just say?
What was the cause of
Zi Fen's passing?
It's been 4,000 years,
how long will you hide it from me?
How did late Floral Immortal pass away?
Speaking about that,
you were also part of the cause.
Today, even if I have to go against
the oath I swore to the late Floral Immortal,
and destroy my own spirit,
I'll have to tell the truth.
All the men in the world are
fickle when it comes to love.
Right now Jin Mi has grown up...
everyone claims to be her father.
Where were you then?
Do you know that the
late Floral Immortal used...
all her prowess to protect this child?
Four thousand years ago,
Jin Mi came into the world crying,
when late Floral Immortal closed her eyes...
it was the same night when
Water Immortal had his wedding.
You are all happy and well-contented,
don't even have the time to
watch the peach blossoms.
Why would you even think of
people from the past?
Enough, Begonia!
Jin Mi is still inside.
If Jin Mi hears all these,
we all have to share the blame...
and drag Jin Mi into the affair
of the past generation.
What for?
That means that...
Zi Fen died in the frost fall
of the year 28612...
and not Summer Solstice
in year 28613?
Floral Realm has hidden the news about
Zi Fen's death for almost a year?
- Why?
- That year...
Begonia!
Are you not going
to even listen to me?
All the chiefs have already sworn
an oath to the late Floral Immortal,
please don't force
us to tell you anymore.
Chiefs, today Little One
has found her father.
Please don't make her upset anymore.
Why don't you all go
inside to accompany her?
If you would like to talk
about the old days,
why don't you talk to me?
Mr. Hu,
you are considered someone
who was close to Zi Fen.
You must know what had happened
back then.
Since the late Floral Immortal had always
wanted to keep this secret,
I'm afraid she intended
not let you worry about it.
However, since you are not willing
to become a confused fool,
then why not become a sad but
understanding person?
Back then when Heavenly Emperor
was still the second prince,
he planned every move carefully...
to win over the late Floral Immortal's heart,
I am sure you are
more aware of it than I do.
In order to rise to the throne
as Heavenly Emperor,
he formed an alliance
with the bird tribe...
and married the princess of
bird tribe, Tu Yao...
and betrayed the late Floral Immortal.
When the late Floral Immortal knew about it,
she was desperate and heartbroken.
Luckily,
luckily your kindness...
to the late Floral Immortal was
the same every day.
Her love for you had grown
stronger in time.
This was supposed to stop her
before it was too late.
Who knew?
The Heavenly Emperor acted the same
even after he was crowned.
He continued to harass
the late Floral Immortal...
but the late Floral Immortal refused to yield.
That made the Heavenly Emperor
even more frustrated and...
he forcibly defiled the late Floral Immortal.
He used force on Zi Fen!
But the late Floral Immortal
didn't know that...
she was already pregnant with Jin Mi.
In anger,
she went to the
River of Unmindfulness.
Lady.
You already made your choice
between power and me.
We have taken different paths,
but you've shamed me
and made me betray Luo Lin.
Only by jumping into the
River of Unmindfulness...
could wash off the shame
and heartbreak.
The late Floral Immortal wanted to drink
from River of Unmindfulness...
to forget her sorrow
but Heavenly Emperor stopped her.
She then jumped into the river
to destroy her own spirit...
but the Heavenly Emperor
cast a spell to stop her.
I am the Heavenly Emperor.
The entire of Heaven Realm is mine.
I won't allow you to die...
and I won't allow you to forget me.
Let me go!
The Heavenly Emperor imprisoned the
late Floral Immortal inside Qi Wu Palace.
Brother!
To get the late Floral Immortal
to give up on you,
the Heavenly Emperor plotted to get
you and Wind Immortal to marry,
he even purposely let the
late Floral Immortal hear about it.
The Water Immortal and Wind Immortal
have arrived.
His Majesty,
why did you summon Lin Xi and I?
Brother.
My heart belongs to someone else,
even if I'm not the one she wants...
I've already decided that I won't
marry anyone else except for her.
Forming a marriage
between Lin Xiu and you...
is not an idea of just my own.
Due to the unrest in the six realms,
a marriage between you two...
would boost up the morale of
the soldiers in the Heaven Realm.
Luo Lin,
are you going to defy my order?
Thank you your Majesty
for your kindness.
I wish that Princess Tu Yao and you
would be happy together forever...
but to go against my heart,
even if you have to take away my
immortality and make me human,
I will not obey your order.
Your Majesty, please calm down.
Luo Lin, Zi Fen and I had been...
cultivating in the same
school for thousands of years.
We are as close as siblings.
I cannot just take away
their loved ones.
Tu Yao was already married to
the Heavenly Emperor as she wished,
what else was she not satisfied with?
Due to the situation then,
the Heavenly Emperor...
has no choice but to
make Tu Yao his wife.
But in his heart, he has always
missed the late Floral Immortal.
He even wanted to make the
late Floral Immortal his concubine.
"Linyuan Terrace"
Tu Yao found out about it...
and how could she not hate him?
- Chief!
Why are you hurt so badly?
After I've rejected the
marriage proposal,
I went to the Floral Realm
to visit Zi Fen...
but she told me...
she has never loved me.
From the very beginning till the end,
I only love the Heavenly Emperor.
Why don't you just go and
marry Lin Xiu?
The spirit and internal organs of late
chief were already severely burnt.
She knew she couldn't live any longer.
That's why she had been cold to you,
in hopes that you would be
able to let her go easily.
She didn't want you...
to cause a scene for something
that can never be undone.
She hoped that the Wind Immortal
and you could be a loving...
and contented couple.
I wanted to spend the rest
of my life with Zi Fen...
but this world is unpredictable.
Without Zi Fen,
how can I be contented?
Jin Mi lost her mother
when she was so young,
she was lonely and helpless,
how can I forgive myself?
I must kill that poisonous
woman with my own hands.
Even if my spirit will be perished,
I'll have to avenge Zi Fen!
The deceased is already gone.
The late Floral Immortal's spirit
has been destroyed,
even if you have finally avenged her,
she will not be resurrected.
Also, the late Floral Immortal's
last wish...
was for the Floral Realm
to be peaceful...
and stop seeking revenge
on each other.
The late Floral Immortal was worried that the
little grape would be like her,
develop infatuation
and die in grief.
That's why she ordered all the chiefs
to strictly protect this secret.
Even made Grape to dress up
like a man when she's out...
and trap her in the Water Mirror
for 10,000 years,
even asked me to
watch over her closely.
I thought that the little one...
would be happy and carefree
for the rest of her life.
Who would have thought that...
fate messes with people?
Jin Mi,
it's you after all.
There's a limit to taking revenge,
how could you use Jin Mi...
and put the young chief
of Floral Realm in danger.
Do you know that...
the Heavenly Empress almost
killed her that day?
Hurting her is the Heavenly
Empress's doing,
not what I wish for.
I will no longer help you.
Chief Magnolia , do you really want to
break the agreement?
You broke faith first.
I've already told you...
there's a limit to taking revenge,
it must not involve the
people from Floral Realm.
Since we have already
decided to take revenge,
of course there will be risk.
If you dare to cause anymore
harm to Jin Mi,
I will not forgive you.
Chief Peony has always
been just and stern,
if she finds out that
we formed an alliance,
what would be your consequences?
No matter what,
we are on the same boat right now.
Since we've started it,
how can we stop now?
Take care of yourself.
"Xuanji Palace"
Your Highness, how's Jin Mi?
Luckily, Water Immortal
was there to help.
Jin Mi is fine now.
Jin Mi is actually Water
Immortal's daughter.
According to the arrangement
made 4000 years ago,
she is my fiancée.
Isn't she...
the child of Heavenly Emperor?
The magical prowess that father passed
to her goes against her own prowess.
Water Immortal has already
personally checked it.
He confirms that Jin Mi
is his own child.
Soon...
he'll announce it publicly.
Your Highness,
I can see that you're very happy.
I've never been this happy...
but I've also never
been this nervous.
I overheard the conversation between
Water Immortal and Chief Peony...
about the relationship between father
and late Floral immortal, Zi Fen.
The Water Immortal hates
father and mother.
I'm afraid that he might not
approve this marriage.
Even if there was
any misunderstanding,
the engagement was made long time ago.
Promise made by the Immortals
must be obeyed,
no one can break it, isn't?
But I know that...
Xu Feng likes Jin Mi too.
He might be able to fool others...
but I won't be fooled by him.
I can't bare to hurt him.
Then can you bare giving her up?
When Lord Fire Immortal was young,
he had so much love from
Heavenly Emperor and Empress.
He is also the firstborn.
He already has too much.
Unlike you,
you're always alone,
beast of dream and the night
are you only companion.
You never fight for anything.
If...
If you give your wife away, that's...
This one time...
Xu Feng,
I'll wrong you just this one time.
I'll repay you for hundred
and thousand times in the future.
Would you still blame me?
Chief Peony,
while we're here today,
tell me the honest truth.
Jin Mi,
is she or is she not my child?
In the spirit of the
departed late Floral Immortal,
no matter how many
times you asked.
I will only have one answer.
Jin Mi is not your descendant.
Don't try to hide it from me.
Zi Fen...
passed away after giving birth on
summer solstice in the year 28613.
Based on the time calculation,
no doubt that Jin Mi is
my own flesh and bone.
Your Majesty, you've mistaken.
Jin Mi was not born on
the summer solstice...
but was on the frost fall
a year before that.
I understand that..
I've wronged Zi Fen...
and caused her to die in hatred.
I also know that...
you all feel injustice for her.
But these past thousand years,
I've tried every chance given
to make up for the regret.
I'm sure that you all
would not want Jin Mi...
to become an orphan.
Has Your Majesty forgotten
how and why did late Floral Immortal died?
Only a few days ago,
Heavenly Empress came
to the Floral Realm...
ruined the tomb of late Floral Immortal...
and almost killed Jin Mi,
Your Majesty should know
about it, right?
Your Majesty, for the sake of
the relationship that you had,
then please don't endanger
late Floral Immortal's only child.
Regarding the Heavenly Empress,
please be at ease.
I will talk to her,
make her and everyone else in
the Heaven Realm to accept Jin Mi.
It is just Jin Mi.
Who dares to trouble the
Heavenly Emperor for it?
When the King and Queen are fighting,
Heaven Realm becomes unrest,
Jin Mi will not be able to
bare the blame for it.
In the Heaven Realm,
mistakes can be made easily.
Even the late Floral Immortal, which is also a
Supreme Immortal was plotted against,
let alone a weak child.
Jin Mi has a place in the
Floral Realm,
it will be enough.
Please Heavenly Emperor,
give her a way out.
Fine.
This needs further consideration.
But you should know,
although time has passed...
I've not changed my mind.
One day, I'll have to
recognise Jin Mi as my own.
I want to proudly get her
back to the Heaven Realm.
It'll be considered as
giving Zi Fen some justice.
In that case,
I'll patiently wait for it.
Former Floral immortal,
I'm here to visit you.
Can I call you mother now?
Mother,
I've recognised father,
which is the Water Immortal.
He told me that you loved
having these flower biscuits.
What a coincidence, fresh flower
biscuit is my favourite as well.
I've brought some for you.
They don't look good...
but I made them by myself,
they are quite good.
Please don't mind it.
Frankly speaking,
these past 4000 years,
I've been thinking...
how would you and I reunite?
But I've never thought that...
we would reunite this way.
I even thought that,
after meeting you,
I'll have many heart-to-heart
talks with you.
But I've never thought that,
I've already spoken enough with you.
You are really a surprising mother.
I've always been jealous of Lian Qiao.
Because every time during meal time,
her mother...
would ask the butterflies to ask her
come home to have her meal.
I was thinking,
how nice would it be
if I have a mother.
My mother would ask me
to have my meal.
But now that I've know that
I have a mother,
I'm even more jealous of her.
How in the world is there
a mother like you?
You didn't care about me
after giving birth to me.
Even trapped me in the
Water Mirror for 4000 years.
Even asked Chief Peony to lie to me,
said that I'm an orphan grape.
You even hid my true form,
caused my prowess to be so low.
What did father and
I ever do to you?
In the love letter, I found the place
where we meet in every life.
There I'll wait for us to
watch the setting sun.
In the love letter, I found the place
where we love in every life.
There I'll sing in the moonlight.
It's fine...
although you didn't treat me well...
at least you have brought me
to this world.
Okay, I'll have to go now.
I'll be fine with father.
When I have the time,
I'll come visit you again.
I'm leaving now.
Water Immortal.
Now that Jin Mi has gone
to pay her respect to Zi Fen,
I'll like to ask you about something.
Water Immortal, you are too serious.
I'll tell you whatever I know.
When I was checking on
Jin Mi's true form,
I found that besides the
Garan Seal in her body,
there's also another restriction.
I've asked Mr. Hu...
but he wouldn't tell me
no matter what.
Do you know anything about it?
That restriction was planted
by the late Floral Immortal.
She has predicted that Jin Mi
will face a trial in 10,000 years.
It's for Jin Mi to block
out that trial.
Regarding the details,
we are not sure of it.
Is that right?
However, please be at ease.
The late Floral Immortal planted
this restriction...
out of a parent's love.
It does nothing bad to Jin Mi,
please be at ease with it.
Since it's Zi Fen's idea,
I'll let it go.
Sister Zhang,
the Water Immortal is Jin Mi's father.
Why can't we tell him the
truth about the Yun Elixir?
Water Immortal has always
been kind and soft-hearted,
adapts to nature.
Based on his temperament,
if he knows that the Yun Elixir...
is used to suppress
Jin Mi's true nature,
most likely he will remove it.
In case late Floral Immortal's prediction
has come true,
Jin Mi will face a 10,000 year
love trial.
How do we explain ourselves
to the late Floral Immortal then?
Next time, at the Highest Palace,
you can't just speak as you like.
Please be at ease, father.
I'll just sit here quietly
and listen to you all speak.
I will not speak as I want...
and will definitely not
speak to Heavenly Empress.
She won't have any excuse
to go against me then.
If she tries to trouble you,
you don't have to be afraid of her.
Water Immortal! Water Immortal!
Rat Immortal.
Where are you going, Water Immortal?
I'm bringing my daughter to
the Empyrean Cloud Palace.
This is my daughter, Jin Mi.
Mi, greet the Rat Immortal.
Greetings, Immortal.
You look like you are in a rush,
are you going to Mortal Realm now?
I was about to go look for you.
What's the matter?
Why are you looking for me?
- Fairy Jin Mi.
- Fish Fairy.
- What a coincidence.
- Are you going to patrol the night?
I am not in the rush for it
as it's still early.
Oh right,
you just went back to the Floral Realm.
Did the chiefs punish you?
That's good.
You must be really careful
coming to the Heaven Realm.
The Heavenly Empress is still angry,
I'm worried that it'll be
a disadvantage for you.
Why don't you let me accompany you,
so that you'll be looked after?
You don't have to worry about me.
You must not let me hold up
on your duty time.
By spending time speaking to me,
I'm guessing I've already hold up
your time to form the night.
By spending time speaking to me,
I'm guessing I've already hold up
your time to form the night.
No, you don't.
Courtesy to your kind words last time,
saying that you liked me,
I've been grateful for it,
from the bottom of my heart.
It's my pleasure
to be able to serve you,
just that I have an
engagement since young,
I'm worried that I'll have to
let you down on your kindness.
What's the big deal?
We are friends.
Fish Fairy,
even if you have an engagement,
I would still like you.
I like you too.
Greetings, Immortal.
I was careless and did not
notice your presence,
please forgive me.