"Ashes of Love"
None
"Episode 47"
It seems you’re in good spirits today.
None
What brings you here, Moon Immortal?
I don’t want to
None
stay in Heaven Realm any more.
Ever since Run Yu became the Heavenly Emperor,
None
Heaven Realm is as deserted as the Xuanji Palace.
It’s the landscape here
None
still with the feeling of warmth.
Moreover, Yuan Ji has left.
None
Now I can talk to no one,
so I come here to divert myself.
None
Fairy Yuan Ji is in charge of the fates of human beings.
Where has she gone?
None
Experience hardships in Human Realm.
She goes to Human Realm to experience hardships
None
as a fairy in charge of the fates of human beings?
Does she observe the conditions of the people?
None
She is shrewd.
She won’t experience hardships herself.
None
It's Run Yu,
who is filled with hate.
None
He keeps thinking about what Xu Feng and Jin Mi
have experienced in Human Realm,
None
so he made an excuse
to send Yuan Ji in Human Realm too.
None
Now
nothing can stop him.
None
Well, has Jin Mi regained consciousness?
Don’t mention her.
None
She has come to herself,
so I don’t want to stay in Heaven Realm.
None
She has come to herself?
Why didn’t she summon me?
None
You still want to meet her?
Such a ungrateful one
None
should be hacked to death,
throw into Taihu Lake
None
and be eaten by the catfish.
I still don’t understand something.
None
It’s known to all that
she likes Xu Feng,
None
but at last…
Maybe
None
she has made a choice
between Xu Feng and Run Yu.
None
Could it be...
What?
None
The late Heavenly Emperor
destroyed his own primordial spirit,
None
but he was just poisoned
with the Evil Incense Ashes.
None
Why was he so cruel to himself?
He witnessed
None
his son died
and the other son seized the throne.
None
Maybe he was utterly dissipated.
He is to blame.
None
If he didn’t destroy his own primordial spirit,
he wouldn’t have come to this
None
as he was protected by the Phoenix Hairpin.
Strangely,
None
after that day,
Xu Feng’s Phoenix Hairpin was missing as well,
None
leaving no hope for me.
Run Yu is to blame.
None
You know what,
Run Yu is my brother.
None
Su Li
was my foster mother.
None
What?
I have suffered too many blows recently.
None
You…
But I didn’t help him seize the throne.
None
I am different from him.
But I have known Jin Mi for long.
None
She stands to sense.
I saved her by accident back then,
None
and she insisted to return
the 1,000-thousnad-year magic power to me.
None
So I think
Xu Feng must have done something unforgettable.
None
I think
I shouldn’t stay here.
None
All the people in the world are blind.
I,
None
I’d better go to experience hardships
in Human Realm with Yuan Ji.
None
You’re old.
You should have a benignant look.
None
Jin Mi, I become an accomplice at last.
How can I face you now?
None
Hope I can
make it up to you in the future.
None
"Qiwu Palace"
Immortal.
None
Where are Liao Ting and Fei Xu?
Moon Immortal has summoned them.
None
Can we help you?
No need.
None
I just want to walk around.
I am putting on weight,
None
but I find other parts don’t grow fat,
except for this part.
None
Phoenix flower blooms in two seasons.
One brings fate,
None
and the other takes away fate.
People will part with each other eventually.
None
Blooms and dead flowers will fall without exception.
How could this happen?
None
Come to life.
Why are they dead?
None
Why?
Why are they dead?
None
Come to life.
Why are they dead?
None
Come to life.
How could this happen?
None
Why are they dead?
Jin Mi, what are you doing?
None
He killed your father.
It’s really you.
None
How dare you come here?
Fox Fairy, I…
None
Stop that!
I tried hard to bring you and Xu Feng together,
None
but you took this opportunity to kill him.
He killed my father.
None
Impossible!
He is not a man of that sort.
None
I have known him since he was a little boy.
I know him well.
None
He wouldn’t do that.
I don’t want to believe it,
None
but it’s the truth.
My father was killed by Glazed Pure Fire.
None
Phoenix personally admitted that
the matter was related to him.
None
Moreover,
the dream of the Beast of Dreams can prove it.
None
I saw it personally.
Dream?
None
Just a dream?
It is Phoenix’s real dream.
None
He killed my father personally.
How can you make sure it’s real?
None
The real dream shows
what one sees in the daytime.
None
Seeing is believing.
How could it be false?
None
Seeing is not necessarily believing.
I don’t believe it,
None
because I just believe here.
Even if the Heavenly River flew backward,
None
Xu Feng would never be a murderer.
Why do you bring me here secretly?
None
Do you know
who entered the Qiwu Palace?
None
Who?
Jin Mi.
None
Jin Mi?
How shameless she is.
None
The Heavenly Emperor
took care of her all the time
when she was in a coma,
None
so we didn’t have any opportunity.
Now she has come to herself
None
and can go everywhere.
I think
None
it’s a good opportunity.
What do you mean?
None
The second Prince loved her dearly,
but she killed him in return.
None
The second Prince was nice to us.
We must avenge him,
None
or we will fail him.
What’s your plan?
None
Lead her to Linyuan Abyss and push her down.
No.
None
There are the spies of
the Heavenly Emperor everywhere.
None
It’s too noticeable.
I have an idea.
None
Shoot it.
First, we have to figure out
None
where the Internal Dan essence is in her body.
Then,
None
we pretend to forgive her
and ask her out to drink.
None
While talking about the old days,
make her drunk
None
and stab her Internal Dan essence.
Then she will die.
None
Good idea.
Let’s do it.
None
-Go.
How do you figure out
None
where the Internal Dan essence is in her body?
Mister Immortal.
None
If I knew you wanted to court death,
I wouldn’t have saved you
None
and taken you to the House of Marriage.
If you really want to kill Jin Mi,
None
the Heavenly Emperor won’t spare you.
And I’ll also be implicated.
None
Mister Immortal, she killed the second Prince.
Yes.
None
If you kill her,
will Xu Feng come back to life?
None
When I met her just now,
I wanted to hack her to death.
None
But it’s useless.
Xu Feng won’t come back to life.
None
It’s a doomed love affair.
I shouldn’t have brought them together blindly.
None
Mister Immortal, we…
You’d better
None
go back to the House of Marriage.
You can’t hurt Jin Mi
None
just by yourselves.
Live a peaceful life from now one.
None
Don’t implicate me.
Yes.
None
As a man sows, let him reap.
No.
None
I haven't made a mistake.
No.
None
I like you.
I,
None
I like you as well.
Fish Fairy?
None
Kuang Lu?
Fish Fairy, let’s be together this life.
None
What do you think?
OK.
None
Don’t betray me.
Jin Mi.
None
Tjhe Yun Elixir really cracks.
Mi,
None
sorry.
Even if you don’t know what love is in this life,
None
I don’t want to lose you.
Forgive me, okay?
None
Fish Fairy. Mi.
Sorry.
None
Fish Fairy,
I like you.
None
I like you as well.
Fish Fairy,
None
let’s be together this life.
What do you think?
None
I know it’s a dream,
but I don’t want to wake up.
None
Yun Elixir?
What’s it?
None
Is that the Yun Elixir?
Why is it in my body?
None
Why did Fish Fairy repair it without telling me?
The flowers have been
arranged properly in Human Realm.
None
Please do it for me.
No problem.
None
I’ll go to visit Jin Mi in Heaven Realm tomorrow.
I wonder how she is.
None
Chief Peony.
Little one…
None
Little one is back.
Jin Mi,
None
you have avenged Water Immortal
and Wind Immortal
None
and done your filial duty.
They don’t want to see you’re sad.
None
You should bestir yourself.
Chief Peony,
None
I come
to ask you something.
None
What’s it?
In front of my parents
None
and Auntie Lin Xiu,
please tell me the truth.
None
What’s the origin of Yun Elixir in my body?
How do you know about this?
None
I accidentally saw it from
the dream of the Beast of Dreams.
None
And I saw Run Yi repaired it.
Repair?
None
It’s gone.
How could this be?
None
Sure enough.
It’s really related to Yun Elixir.
None
After I stabbed Xu Feng to death that day,
I was heartbroken
None
and felt something exploded in my body.
Phoenix!
None
I thought I had such a feeling
because I hated him deeply.
None
Now it seems to be caused by Yun Elixir.
But why is Yun Elixir in my body?
None
Your mother gave it to you.
My mother?
None
She was lovesick
and suffered much when she was alive.
None
I love the Heavenly Emperor only.
Go back to marry Lin Xiu.
None
So when you were born,
she gave Yun Elixir to you.
None
The one who takes Yun Elixir won’t fall in love.
Without love, she will be strong
None
and live a carefree life.
This is the best blessing I can give her.
None
You won’t fall in love.
She hoped you could be strong
None
and live a carefree life.
It’s for your own good.
None
She didn’t want you to repeat her mistake.
Without love, I will be strong.
None
Why did she think that?
The current Heavenly Emperor
None
doesn’t have an amorous nature as his father.
We can see that
None
he loves you only.
You should cherish his love
None
and don’t fail him.
But I just
None
feel guilty for Fish Fairy.
You still miss Fire Immortal?
None
I don’t know.
I always miss him.
None
As long as I miss him,
I’ll feel pain in my heart
None
and guilty.
He killed my father.
None
I fail my father.
But,
None
but I can’t control myself.
As long as I close my eyes, he appears.
None
I…
The late lord didn’t want to see this,
None
so she gave Yun Elixir to you.
Since you have got rid of Yun Elixir,
None
you have to suffer.
Don’t think about rights and wrongs anymore.
None
Now you’re Water Immortal with mighty power.
The new Heavenly Emperor takes the throne
and enjoys a good reputation worldwide.
None
He stands high in popular favor.
You’ll become the new Heavenly Empress.
None
Everything will go smoothly,
and you’ll have a good life afterwards.
None
Mom,
thank you for being considerate to me.
None
But as my mom,
you can’t deprive me of the right to love.
None
I was controlled by Yun Elixir,
so I did many stupid things
None
as I was childish.
Now I have got rid of Yun Elixir,
None
so I can’t avoid love anymore.
"Linyuan Tower"
None
Get out.
I can rest my heart
None
as you lead a miserable life.
You killed my mother,
None
and your son killed my father.
I killed Xu Feng
None
to avenge my father.
Avenge?
None
For what?
You killed my son?
None
Yes.
Xu,
None
I told you repeatedly
to leave this woman alone,
None
but you didn’t listen to me
and asked me
None
whether I killed Luo Lin.
What did you say?
None
Did you ever fight against Water Immortal?
What’s wrong with him?
None
He and Wind Immortal were killed.
Did this have something to do with you?
None
Now Run Yu has lost his advantages.
He won’t shake your standing
for the Heavenly Emperor
None
even if he marries Jin Mi.
Even the prison can’t keep your ambition.
None
You thought you did these for me,
but you just put me in an immoral situation.
None
Impossible.
Son, how stupid you are.
None
I tried every means to plan and prepare
for you,
None
but you
trusted this woman.
None
I’m the most sincerest to you in this world.
If you listened to me,
None
you wouldn’t be killed by her.
I didn’t…
None
I didn’t kill him by mistake.
Tell me.
None
If Xu Feng didn’t kill my father,
then who killed my father?
None
It’s me.
Impossible.
None
When my father died,
you were in prison.
None
You couldn’t kill him.
The murderer must be someone else.
None
Who is the murderer?
Tell me.
None
Listen.
You will never know.
None
I won’t tell you.
Moon Immortal.
None
Liao Ting, Fei Xu,
drive her out.
None
I may kill Phoenix by mistake.
You want to reverse the case?
None
You have wronged one.
Don’t wrong anyone else.
None
I know
you hate me.
None
I know you all hate me.
Don’t worry.
None
If I find out the truth
and really killed Phoenix by mistake,
None
I’ll kill myself.
It’s useless.
None
If
I really killed Phoenix by mistake,
None
I don’t want to live alone.
Even if you die,
None
Xu Feng won’t come back to life.
But,
None
but Xu Feng can’t be wronged.
"Pixiang Hall"
Hurry up. The guards will wake up soon.
None
Mi, have you found it?
Not yet.
None
Where did you find it last time?
Right there.
None
Why can’t we find it?
We can’t give up.
None
Go on.
Look for it separately.
None
The ward.
It’s sealed.
None
It’s strange.
Let me help you.
None
How could this be possible?
The Beast of Dreams didn’t go to the Qiwu Palace.
None
It stayed in my room.
How could this be possible?
None
It’s impossible.
Jin Mi,
None
what you have seen
is your own dream.
None
No.
You suspected Xu Feng.
None
You dreamed of what you though
in the day at night,
None
so you had such a dream.
Impossible.
None
It’s different from what I saw before.
It’s fake.
None
It must be fake.
The authenticity of the Dream Register
remains to be verified.
None
No matter whether it tells the truth,
someone must cause trouble.
None
The blue one is a real dream.
The blue dream is real.
None
I…
I didn’t witness my father’s death.
None
So it’s not my dream.
If it’s my dream,
None
I must have an impression.
Impossible.
None
It’s not my dream.
Impossible!
None
Jin Mi,
Maybe someone
None
did something to the dream on purpose.
Phoenix.
None
I really wronged Phoenix?
I killed him by mistake.
None
Mi.
-Immortal.
None
Immortal.
Immortal, you’re finally back.
None
Where have you been?
His Majesty is worried about you.
None
Where is he?
In the Qizheng Hall.
None
Mi, I don’t see you all day.
I’m quite worried about you.
None
You just came to yourself,
so you should have a good rest to recuperate.
None
Before you recover completely,
please don’t go around.
None
If you really want to go out,
take Kuang Lu with you.
None
With her company,
I can feel at ease.
None
I’m afraid
I really wronged Xu Feng.
None
Why did you say that?
After my father was killed,
None
I saw a dream from the Beast of Dreams.
It was about Phoenix killing my father.
None
I thought it was Phoenix’s real dream,
but today
None
I went to Pixiang Hall with Moon Immortal
and found the record of the Beast of Dreams
None
about that day.
Then I found that
None
the Beast of Dreams didn’t go to the Qiwu Palace.
Instead, it stayed with me.
None
Your Majesty,
It wasn’t Xu Feng’s dream.
None
It was my dream,
but I didn’t see personally Phoenix killed my father.
None
If I had that dream because I had a doubt,
it should be a yellow imaginary dream.
None
But I remember clearly
I saw the blue real dream
None
that day.
So,
None
so
someone must have done something to that dream
None
and turned the imaginary dream
into the real dream.
None
Who do you think did it?
You led
None
the Beast of Dreams there that day.
Mi,
None
to investigate the case of
the late Water Immortal’s death,
None
I collected thousands of dreams.
Before I checked them one by one,
None
my father took them away and sealed them.
I really didn’t see the dream you mentioned.
None
The Chief of the Pixiang Hall
is responsible for the files of Heaven Realm.
None
He should have an impression
whether it’s a yellow imaginary dream
None
or a blue real dream.
OK.
None
I’ll call in him
and ask him about it.
None
"Qizheng Hall"
Your Majesty,
None
the Pixiang Hall reports that
the chief committed suicide.
None
Your Majesty.
Why are you scared?
None
I saw Water Immortal
wasn’t her usual self today,
None
so I followed her secretly.
I found that
None
she and Moon Immortal
slipped into the Pixiang Hall secretly.
None
The Chief of the Pixiang Hall must die.
"Pixiang Hall"
None
Your Majesty.
Why did he commit suicide?
None
Your Majesty,
this is a suicide note we just found.
None
In the note, he confessed
he changed the file without authorization.
None
So he suicides for fear of punishment.
Have you compared the handwriting?
None
Yes, I did.
It was really written by him.
None
Since he committed suicide for fear of punishment,
why did he take the trouble to
None
write this note?