"Ashes of Love"
None
"Episode 22"
It was probably Duke Nanping
None
who poisoned my food
and colluded with Liangguo people
in ambushing me before.
None
How ambitious he is!
I must get back to get rid of him soon.
None
Why does my heart beat so fast
and feel so sore?
None
I’ve never felt like this before.
It was urgent, so I offended you.
None
Since we were separated by the veil,
you didn’t offend me.
None
Never mind.
" Dongting Lake"
None
My Lord. My Lord.
Yong, Lian, how’ve you been?
None
My Lord, please behave yourself.
Master has been waiting for you for a long time.
None
You’re so boring and monotonous.
"Yunmeng Lake "
None
Master, how have you been doing recently?
You haven’t been back since Rat Fairy died.
None
If I didn’t summon you today,
you would never
None
step in Yunmeng Lake again, right?
I don’t dare.
None
You don’t dare?
Maybe you don’t dare,
None
but you have such an idea.
My sincerity to you is visible.
None
I know the death of Rat Fairy
was a heavy blow to you,
None
but since he was dead,
it’s useless to dwell on the past.
None
You should look ahead
and let it go.
None
What’s your order, Master?
Get up.
None
I got the message that
Spirit-Vanishing Arrow appeared again.
None
Go to snatch it
and kill Xu Feng for me.
None
Oh, my Gosh!
My adopted mother always does whatever she likes.
None
It sounds like Spirit-Vanishing Arrow
is just a knife in her kitchen
None
and Xu Feng is a chick raised by her.
Mom, I’m afraid I can’t do it.
None
Rat Fairy and I got help from outside or in last time,
but we still failed to kill Xu Feng
None
and Rat Fairy even died because of this.
I really don’t have confidence
None
that I can get rid of Xu Feng alone.
He’s a mortal now
None
and even weaker than he was during nirvana.
Since the great cause is unachieved,
None
someone must die for it.
How can you give it up just for his death?
None
Did you just regard Rat Fairy
as a pawn?
None
I know you don’t agree with my behavior,
but we have no way to back down.
None
Rat Fairy was loyal to me
and masterminded with painstaking effort
in Heaven Realm for so many years
None
so as to collect a lot of precious information for us.
If we give up halfway,
None
we’ll fail him.
Before Rat Fairy died for justice,
None
he repeatedly asked me to tell you
haste makes waste.
None
Water Immortal saved you
from Heavenly Empress despite everything
None
and offered you this place to live.
You just mentioned that
None
it is useless to
dwell on the past.
None
Why do you
get yourself into endless hatred
None
and implicate more innocent people?
Cut it out.
None
Stop telling me
an eye for an eye
None
will only make the whole world blind.
In such a big world,
None
I may still exist, but I have ceased to live,
and have nowhere to make my home.
None
Have you ever tried to
live on the charity and compassion of others?
None
You saved me,
so I’ll die for you without any hesitation.
None
After Rat Fairy died,
I’ll still pledge allegiance to you.
None
If I die,
I wonder who will pledge allegiance to you.
None
Yan You, I can only depend on you.
You must take care of yourself
when dealing with Xu Feng.
None
I can’t afford to lose you.
Li.
None
Mom.
I have seen you.
Come out.
None
Little boy, what species are you?
I’m a carp elf.
None
I don’t believe you.
She won’t adopt a real carp.
None
White loach, who are you?
I’m another Li.
None
But we are the same and both of us are false.
Little loach, are you happy here?
None
I have plenty to eat and drink
and nice new clothes to wear here.
None
Surely I’m happy.
But I prefer rolling in the mud puddle.
None
I can’t let her go on anymore.
I promise to send you back to the mud puddle.
None
Where is he?
I can’t find him anywhere.
None
Was he captured by King of Gu City?
It’s forbidden to get in and out of
the sleeping chamber of His Majesty.
None
Even if Princess Sui He
wants to borrow something,
None
you must report it to me first. Got it?
Yes.
None
I didn’t expect that you are
not only good at martial arts
None
but also good at cooking.
Great.
None
Medical fees.
Claw me and I’ll claw thee.
None
You saved me, but I was
unable to repay your kindness,
None
so I cooked a simple meal
to express my gratitude to you.
None
Here. I don’t need it.
Although you’re my patient,
None
I’ve regarded you as my friend.
I grew up in Saint Doctors' Family
and seclude myself from the world.
None
I’m really glad to meet you.
If you heal me,
None
I’ll achieve one of your dreams someday.
How can a bandit achieve my dream?
None
Thank you,
but you may not achieve my dream.
None
If you have a dream,
maybe I can help you achieve it.
None
That’s a deal.
You don’t stand on ceremony at all.
None
You get a promise from me then.
However, I’m sure
None
we’ll never see each other again in the future.
You bandits lead a bloody life.
None
Although I don’t have to fight,
I’m on tenterhooks every day.
None
In fact, we have the same destination.
I’m just taking one day at a time.
None
Although I have learned medicine for 15 years
and been proficient in medical science and pharmacology,
None
you’re actually my first patient.
Isn’t that funny?
None
As Saint Girl of Saint Doctors’ Family,
the meaning of my life
None
is to prepare Elixir of Life for King Yi.
If I fail,
None
when King Yi.
passes away,
None
it’s also time for me to die.
When King Yi is alive,
None
I have to decoct herbal medicine for him
and when he dies,
None
I’ll be buried with his coffin
in the imperial mausoleum as a burial object
None
to expiate his sins with my holy and pure soul.
But I heard that King Yi
None
fights battles everywhere
and has killed many people.
None
I guess he may die young as well.
So I can’t live for long.
None
Here.
Crow, I substitute wine with tea
and propose a toast to you.
None
Thank you
for letting me know
None
the meaning of being alive
in my humble and insignificant life for the first time.
None
Although I don’t know
whether you can be cured or not,
None
you let me know
how wonderful it is to help someone
None
when I’m still alive.
I have a poor memory.
None
I have forgotten that you can’t hear me.
Anyway, Crow,
None
thank you.
What kind of person are you?
None
Jin Mi.
I’m afraid that Duke Nanping has plotted for long.
None
If I return to Palace of King Yi now,
I may be in danger.
None
It’s better to go to Beiyuan Mountain Villa first.
It is the place where my trusted troops are stationed,
None
so it is the safest.
I can have a further plan after reaching there.
None
Crow.
How come
None
he vanished like the night drew?
Dear Madam, I’ve been sick
for more than one month
None
and thanks to your careful attention,
I was cured yesterday.
None
Something happened in my family,
so I have to leave without saying goodbye.
Please forgive me.
None
We met by chance,
but anyway we have different paths.
None
I never make a promise easily,
but since I do,
I’ll keep it by any means.
None
Take care of yourself.
Goodbye.
None
You left the same night as soon as you were cured.
You didn’t even have time to say goodbye to me
None
in person?
I won’t charge you for medical fees.
None
Peony.
Peony?
None
Peony.
I’ve planted some carrots.
None
Would you like some?
Mr. Hu,
None
what’s wrong with you today?
Do you think
None
you live too long
and want to die?
None
Peony, you do lack a sense of romance.
It’s romantic to die for a beauty.
None
Moon Immortal really wants to be fertilizer.
Someone,
None
put him in the rabbit house.
Yes.
None
No.
No. No.
None
You…
I won’t go in.
None
Let me out.
Help!
None
Chief Peony, I was wrong.
Let me out.
None
Chief Peony, I was wrong.
Let me out.
None
Hong Hong.
Don’t cry.
None
It was all your fault.
Old fox,
None
why don’t you make fun of
those fair children in the heaven
None
but play tricks on me
in Floral Realm?
None
Jin Mi and Xu Feng both are absent,
so I’m really bored.
None
You’re bored, so you played tricks on me?
How dare you offend Chief Peony? Chief…
None
Chief…
How dare you make fun of Chief Peony?
None
You’re so bold. You…
There is only one man
None
in Floral Realm.
I could only tie the red rope to you.
None
Did you just see
how furious those rabbits were?
None
They came at me.
You know,
None
a rabbit almost peeled me.
Please let me pass.
None
A rabbit almost peeled me
just now.
None
Fortunately, I have a weapon with me.
Mr. Hu, you don’t dare to provoke Chief Peony.
None
How about…
Lian Qiao?
None
Are, are you kidding me?
I’m a great-great-great-great-grandfather
None
of the great-great-great-great-grandfather of Lian Qiao.
No way.
None
Stop kidding.
A usually love story
None
must be usual
or it won’t be impressive.
None
Am I right?
You have become dull
None
because of playing matchmaker all the time.
I’m leaving.
None
Jin Mi, Xu Feng,
when do you go back after experiencing hardships?
None
I’m so bored.
Sister, are you worried about Jin Mi?
None
I wonder how she is going in the mortal world.
Now she has become
None
a weak mortal.
Don’t worry.
None
If she really has an accident
in the mortal world,
None
she can finish experiencing hardships
and return soon then.
None
What happens in the mortal world is not terrible,
as it can cultivate her.
None
I’m afraid that it isn’t mortals who want to harm her.
Jin Mi has no enemy
None
except Heavenly Empress.
Heavenly Emperor specially issued a decree
None
ordering all immortals not to intervene
in Jin Mi’s experiencing hardships.
None
This is issued for Heavenly Empress, right?
Yes. Take it easy, Sister.
None
Moreover, Night Immortal
keeps an eye on Jin Mi every day,
None
so I think
Jin Mi will return safely
None
very soon.
She is always a child in my mind.
None
I was afraid that she might hurt herself,
so I didn’t dare to let go of her in the past.
None
It’s time to let go of her
and allow her to experience something outside.
None
Catch me.
Go and catch me.
None
It’s a serious fault for taking away the Millennial Ginseng.
I don’t know how they will punish me.
None
Anyway I’m tough. I’ll play it by ear.
Auntie. Qiang Huo.
None
You’re back.
Jin…
None
Saint Girl, have you had your dinner?
Are there any leftovers?
None
Let me cook a bowl of egg noodles for you.
Take it easy.
None
You’re always reckless.
Did she forget?
None
Well, give it to me.
Thank you, Auntie.
None
You have been to Luoye Mountain
for more than one month.
None
What did you get?
I gained a lot.
None
I will sort it out in a few days
and lecture other girls about it.
None
How was everything going
in this month when l left?
None
Everything was good.
I feel relieved then.
None
Jin Mi, I didn’t tell them.
I don’t know
None
how the elders would punish you
if I told them.
None
I thought it over later.
What you said did make sense.
None
Anyway King Yi can’t live forever.
It’s better to give it to other people who need it.
None
I chose you other than ginseng for sure.
How nice you are, Qiang Huo. I know
None
you’re my best friend.
But you were so bold.
None
Don’t ever do it again.
I won’t.
None
Anyway
I don’t have any Millennial Ginseng to steal anymore.
None
By the way,
was the person you treated with the Millennial Ginseng
None
cured?
Yes.
None
But I met
a rare disease
None
when treating my first patient.
It’s said in the book that
the patient can be cured in three days,
None
but it took me one whole month.
My biggest impression this time is that
None
we can’t believe everything in the book.
Experience is the best teacher.
None
Let’s go.
A country cannot exist without a king.
None
Xu Feng is missing and may be dead.
We should hold a funeral at once.
None
Now Huaiwu is beset by enemies from within and without.
I have no choice.
None
Cousin must be alive.
I will look for him in Luoye Mountain with my men.
None
There are plenty more fish in the sea.
As my daughter,
None
you can certainly find a good husband.
Why are you so obsessive
None
about Xu Feng?
Daddy, you should understand my only dream
None
is to get married with him in my life.
Even death can’t part me from him.
None
I don't believe heaven is so cruel
to perish my only dream.
None
I must find Cousin.
You can’t hold a funeral now.
None
You…
Your Highness.
None
What’s the hurry?
Your Highness,
None
King Yi returned safely.
What?
None
King Yi did return safely?
Yes.
None
Where is he now?
He should have been back to his mansion now.
None
Who is that?
Why don’t you show up but hide covertly?
None
Show up.
Just stay away from her.
None
Hey, I advise you to mind your own business.
Get rid of him first.
None
Watch out.
Are you all right?
None
"Beiyuan Villa"
Your Highness, His Majesty is having a rest.
None
Let me get in to see him.
His Majesty said
None
no one is allowed to disturb him without his permission.
How dare you stop me?
None
Military orders cannot be disobeyed.
Please forgive me, Your Highness.
None
I won’t leave without seeing him today.
Qin Tong.
None
Yes.
Go to handle her.
None
Yes.
Get out of my way.
None
Your Highness, can I have a moment with you?
You’re so reliable.
None
I’m flattered.
How did you send her away?
None
Although His Majesty is safe and sound,
but he is exhausted and weak and needs some rest
None
after a long and tiring journey.
You shouldn’t bother him now.
None
Please come here tomorrow
and His Majesty will meet you for sure.
None
How could you make a decision for me?
I was wrong.
None
The message of my hunting
must have been divulged to Liangguo.
None
You doubt there is a mole in the palace?
Fine.
None
Since I need some rest today,
I won’t think about it.
None
Let’s discuss it tomorrow.
You can leave.
None
Yes.
Most of the wound has been recovered.
None
The poison must have worked.
Your Majesty, it’s not a trivial matter
None
if someone really divulged
the message of your hunting
None
to Liangguo.
Please allow me to investigate it.
None
I’ll find the mole as soon as possible.
Thank you, Duke Nanping.
None
Yes.
Your Majesty, it seems that you’re still weak?
None
The medical skill of the
imperial doctor isn’t good enough.
None
How about summoning Saint Girl
of Saint Doctors’ Family here
None
to examine you?
Saint Girl?
None
Jin Mi?
She must not be involved.
None
I feel much better.
You don’t have to go through all this trouble.
None
Your Majesty, you’re the foundation of Huaiwu.
You can never take it lightly.
None
Moreover, the mission of Saint Doctors’ Family
is to make sure the good health of you.
None
It’s proper
to summon Saint Girl here now.
None
Your Majesty, I think what
Duke Nanping said makes sense.
None
I hope
Your Majesty can summon
the Saint Girl here as soon as possible
None
to nurse your health.
I also agree.
None
Duke Nanping acts quickly.
He asked me for the imperial edict
None
and sent for Saint Girl
shortly after he advised to summon her.
None
Qin Tong, pick several of your trusted subordinates
to follow the men of Duke Nanping
None
and make sure the safety of Saint Girl.
I’ll protect Saint Girl?
None
I won’t feel relieved if you don’t go there in person.
I’m worried that
None
someone really wants to kill you.
Don’t worry.
I have a plan.
None
I’ll get prepared now.
Cousin, are you getting better?
None
Much better.
Yesterday I heard from Qin Tong that
None
you were still weak,
so I asked the senior pharmacist
in my mansion for advice
None
and chose the best materials
to stew a cup of decoction in person.
None
It can alleviate your weakness and tiredness
Thank you.
None
You know,
I worried much about you recently.
None
Leave the decoction.
I’m tired after discussing
official business in the court today.
None
I’m going to take a rest.
Someone, keep the decoction.
None
But…
When will you look back at
None
my love for you?
Taste some grapes for me.
None
It looks sweet.
So sour.
None
Liar.
You such a liar.
None
"Saint Girl Hall"
Hurry up.
None
"Saint Girl Hall"
What’s going on?
None
"Saint Girl Hall"
Look. Have a look. What’s going on?
None
"Saint Girl Hall"
What happened?
None
I don’t know.
What happened?
None
It isn’t the day to hold a memorial ceremony today.
Auntie looks serious.
None
I said nothing.
Did Auntie know
None
we flew a kite secretly yesterday?
I don’t know either.
None
Saint Girl, do you why we come to Saint Girl Hall?
I’m stupid. Please instruct me, Auntie.
None
Tell me where the ginseng is.
How come the ginseng is gone?
None
If people from the capital didn’t ask me about it,
the elders and I
None
wouldn’t check the pharmacy
and we wouldn’t find
None
the ginseng is gone.
The ginseng is kept by you.
None
How come it’s gone?
Well, er.
None
Oh, no.
I didn’t expect that I was caught so soon.
None
Saint Girl, where is the ginseng?
Auntie, Longevity Qiankun Elixir is prepared.
None
What?
But,
None
but I took it.
I was afraid that any mistake was made,
None
so I took it for King Yi
to have a test.
None
How, how could you
take such an important thing?
None
Auntie, I took the liberty to take it
without discussing with you and the elders
None
in advance. Please punish me.
Didn’t you know the ginseng
can’t be found within 1,000 years?
None
Since you weren’t totally sure,
how could you add the guiding drug easily?
None
Auntie, I was not very well the day before yesterday
and arbitrarily took away the medicine of Saint Girl.
None
I thought it was common medicine
and didn’t expect it is Longevity Qiankun Elixir.
None
You…
No, Auntie.
None
It has nothing to do with Qiang Huo.
She wanted to bear the blame for me.
None
It was done by me alone.
I’m willing to take the consequences.
None
No. It’s my fault.
No, Auntie.
None
It’s my fault. It’s my fault. It isn’t Qiang Huo’s fault.
You don’t have to protect me.
None
Auntie, it’s my fault.
Saint Girl. Auntie.
None
King Yi issued an imperial edict summoning Saint Girl.