"Ashes of Love"
"Episode 25"
Invite Saint Girl of Saint Doctors’ Family now.
Yes.
General Qin.
What’s wrong with His Majesty?
His Majesty is unwell.
Your Excellencies, please go back.
Minister, please wait.
Get out of the way!
-Your Majesty.
Minister Fu. Duke Nanping.
Do you have anything important to report?
Your Majesty, you feel unwell, so we are so worried.
I have been in a cold recently.
It’s a minor illness. Don’t worry.
Is there any urgent report from the border?
All the main forces of Liangguo withdrew.
Your Majesty, don’t worry.
Minister Fu is in command to deal with
military affairs and important things,
so you can rest easy, Your Majesty.
Other officials and I will also help him sincerely.
With you two,
I feel so contented.
Your Majesty, here comes Saint Girl.
Summon her.
Do you have anything else to say?
Your Majesty, please rest without worry.
-We’ll leave.
Minister, please wait.
His Majesty is unwell by accident.
Why am I in command to deal with
military affairs and important things?
Duke, I can’t
stand your groundless pretence up.
Minister.
Minister, don’t embarrass me.
His Majesty is unwell, so it’s reasonable for you
to deal with state affairs on behalf of him.
Minister, did I misread?
I saw His Majesty seemed to spit blood.
What do you think?
I also saw that.
In your opinion, His Majesty
suffers from some severe illness
rather than cold.
I am afraid that
His Majesty falls ill from overwork
and lots of hardships on earlier expedition wars.
Surely,
the condition also depends on
the diagnosis of Saint Girl.
His Majesty was in army for half a life.
In recent years, he has been
busy with government affairs
and had no time to marry consorts,
so he still has no son.
We keep submitting memorials,
but His Majesty ignored us.
Once His Majesty has bad health,
whom will he give the throne to?
Whom, indeed?
It’s a misfortune for the state and families.
The deceased emperor advocated imprisonment
and His Majesty’s blood relationships
were all killed.
Now,
even no one can be adopted by him.
Duke, please.
Minister, please.
Take care.
Go to arrange
so that princess can come here
to pay respects to His Majesty
and sound out his illness condition tomorrow.
Yes.
Today King Yi didn’t hold court due to illness.
Spread this piece of news
in secret.
Remember to keep it a secret from princess
before she comes
to prevent her from making a
wrong judgment due to care.
I see.
It’s his breath.
Mu Ci, I know it’s you.
Why haven’t you admitted you are Mu Ci?
Why haven’t you meet me since you save me?
You even took away the only gift you gave me.
Now that you want to draw a line with me
Well,
I’ll give my life right back to you now.
From then on,
we don’t owe each other.
You haven’t come out.
Well.
I know you care about me.
Even if you don’t want to take off your mask,
I also know you are Mu Ci.
You shouldn’t have gambled
with your life.
If not,
you wouldn’t have come out to see me.
It shows I won.
Go back now.
Those chasing to kill you
will come again after a failure.
Be careful of your own safety.
Mu Ci.
Return my brass strip to me before leaving.
Why haven’t you admitted you are Mu Ci?
Do you know how much I want to see you again?
That Mu Ci you mentioned
has been gone.
All people think you died,
but I don’t think so.
I know you must be alive
and you will come back to meet me.
It seems that we are different
in the definition of being alive.
What actually happened back then?
Why did you disappear
after there was Nether Fury in Wangchuan River?
Mu Ci, what actually happened back then?
-Demon Lord.
My Lord.
Demon Lord, Mu Ci
was accidentally hurt by Liu Ying 1,000 years ago.
King of Bian City thought he was alone and helpless,
so he took him back and brought him up in his mansion.
He has practiced magic
with two princes and Liu Ying since childhood,
showing no abnormity.
But Nether Fury appeared without reason today,
which is a bad omen.
He could solve it easily.
He has black pupils.
Only the pure bloodline of Spirit-Vanishing Family
can have this abnormity after growing up.
But I did
kill the whole Spirit-Vanishing Family back then.
Unexpectedly,
there is still a leftover evil of Spirit-Vanishing Family.
Back then, Spirit-Vanishing Family rebelled
to try to overthrow our Demon Realm.
Luckily, Your Majesty was wise and resolute,
so a disaster was avoided.
To leave no chance for their revival, we must kill him.
My Lord, I am not a different family.
Please let me out.
You aren’t from a different family?
It’s obvious to people of the whole Demon Realm that
you hurt Liu Ying by Wangchuan River.
Don’t quibble.
I hurt Princess Liu Ying?
So, how was she then?
My Lord,
we can’t take such an evil lightly.
We’d better seal him
and throw him into Yu Abyss right now.
I hurt Princess?
OK, I’ll leave it to you.
Remember not to make any trouble again.
Yes.
You don’t need to know what happened before.
Just remember there is no Mu Ci
in this world.
I know you’ve suffered a lot.
Mu Ci, go back to Demon Realm with me.
As usual, we can
practice martial arts and…
Mu Ci, don’t go.
Don’t leave me, OK?
As fast as wind.
As slow as the slowly spreading forest.
Attack like fire.
Defend like mountain.
Difficult to predict the movement when motionless.
Take action at lightening speed.
You’ve progressed.
Of course.
When you were out,
I learnt military strategies and tactics hard.
I heard from Qin Tong that
you had taken away
all the “Seven Military Classics” in my study.
I remember you didn’t like martial arts before.
I couldn’t understand them when I was young,
but I find I am deeply attracted by them
after several years.
The art of war is like the feeling of the world,
so we should be clear-sighted
at the situation and popular feeling.
As the saying goes, there are
different situations in deployment of army
like the water flows without a fixed shape.
Those with foresights will win.
No wonder you always read.
Fortunately, you are enlightened late,
or you, the General Feifeng of Huaiwu
might own my title God of War.
Don’t laugh at me, Cousin.
As a woman, I don’t dare to talk about
affairs of state defense and administration.
I just know little
under your influence.
It’s a pity that I am not a man,
or I can serve as a pawn and pacesetter
under your command.
Your Majesty, it’s time for you to take medicine.
Your Majesty, here are our respects.
Who are they?
Jin Mi of Saint Doctors’ Family.
Qiang Huo of Saint Doctors’ Family.
Princess, here are our respects.
May you great happiness.
Are you the famous female doctors
of Saint Doctors’ Family?
Your Highness, you flatter us.
Our family always lives in seclusion
from the earthly world,
so we aren’t famous at all.
Because of so,
there are many rumors about you in the human world.
I’ve long heard that Saint Doctors’ Family act secretly
and need to observe numerous rules.
You do impress me a lot today.
But why do you cover your faces with veils?
Covering face with veil is
a century-old tradition of our family.
The female doctor of our family
begins to wear veil since childhood.
We also wear veils when
presenting ourselves to His Majesty.
I am not a king.
How about letting me look at your face?
It seems that I have no qualification.
No. No.
We are ugly and afraid to scare you.
Your saying
even arouses my curiosity.
They have strict family rules, so don’t force them.
Saint Doctors’ Family is loyal to the royal family all the time.
Cousin, you may make a decree
to abolish their bad habit.
If all of them cover their faces with veils,
spies and assassins may sneak into the palace
to hurt you, Cousin.
Cousin.
Cousin, are you OK? Cousin.
Cousin. Cousin.
How is His Majesty?
On the way here,
I just heard His Majesty was unwell.
Seeing he brandished a sword vigorously,
I thought his illness was just a rumor.
It seems true now.
Your Highness,
His Majesty has kidney yang and blood failure,
so he is impotent.
He just coughs.
Why, why is he impotent?
Rome is not built in one day.
His Highness falls ill from
overwork throughout the year.
Now he is extremely weak.
Besides kidney yang and blood failure,
His Majesty also has five taxations
and seven damages,
so he often has prostration, coughs
and blood in phlegm.
At first glance,
it is due to lung meridian,
but virtually
kidney meridian.
Can he be curable?
As he is incurably ill, he approaches death.
But, please don’t worry, Your Highness.
I’ll treat His Majesty carefully.
Your Majesty.
Your Highness, Saint Girl of my family
has excellent medical skills,
so she’ll treat His Majesty with all her strength.
Depending on the situation,
His Majesty won’t wake up so soon.
Don’t be anxious here.
It’s not worth if you get ill due to tiredness.
How about going back for a rest first?
Once His Majesty comes round,
we’ll inform you at once.
I leave all that to you, Saint Girl.
Your Highness, don’t worry.
We’ll try our best.
Qiang Huo, see Her Highness out.
Yes.
Your Highness, please.
If His Majesty gets better,
ensure to inform me first.
OK. Please don’t worry, Your Highness.
She loves you so deeply.
How is my acting skill?
Duke Nanping asked someone to send you a letter,
right?
How, how did Your Majesty know?
Now, with domestic trouble and foreign invasion,
Huaiwu is beset by uncertain border
and unstable court situation.
In the midst of war, people worry about their safety,
not to mention a good and prosperous life.
But being obsessed with ambition,
someone wants to kill me
and usurp the throne in chaos
for his own power and desire.
But it’ll take a long time
to eliminate the traitor.
Its hardships, advantages and disadvantages
can’t be expressed in a few words.
I did have some doubts about you
when you came in the beginning.
I was afraid you were really
on the side of Duke Nanping.
But you haven’t written back to Duke Nanping,
so I know
you are on my side, right?
Saint Doctors’ Family pledges loyalty to King Yi.
As Saint Girl, I don’t dare to neglect my mission.
Then tell Duke Nanping
I’ve been incurably ill and approached death.
Why?
In this case, he’ll drop his guard
and show his original face.
I can counterattack when he is off guard.
So I need your full cooperation.
As for what kind of serious illness I have,
you need to think about it.
Your acting skill has actually
reached a high degree of excellence.
I am gladly convinced,
admire you from the bottom of my heart
and bow to you in worship.
Don’t fool me.
We face
such traitor officials like Duke Nanping and Minister Fu,
hard-boiled and slippery persons
who have been in office for decades.
If they are put on the stage,
all of them will become famous actors.
We should be full of spirit and energy.
Yes.
It’s all your fault.
You tell them I am a patient
with deficiency of the kidney
and can’t have sexual intercourse.
How can I face them later?
Well, is,
isn't this Your Majesty’s meaning?
What?
What’s this?
Qiang Huo can understand
and get you medicine by prescription.
Powder for the Seven Emotions Medicament can fully achieve
Your Majesty’s desired effect.
But with seven emotions,
people have different reactions due to external stimulation
and express them in lines, which is natural.
The medicine can reverse veins
and forcibly take away one’s feelings,
so one can take it for a long time.
If you must take it,
remember not to get too happy or sad.
You’d better take it with Golden Chamber Pill
to slow medicine resistance.
OK, you can arrange it.
The crafty and suspicious Duke Nanping
may not believe so easily,
so he’ll send Sui He
to sound out my condition in two or three days.
You cooperate with me
to act before Sui He by then.
Your Majesty,
are you tired of
scheming against them every day?
I am just a doctor rather than an actress.
I am unmarried,
but now you widely spread
I can’t have sexual intercourse,
breaking my reputation.
If I am alone
and childless later,
who will accompany me?
You?
Your, Your, Your Majesty, calm down.
After taking the Seven Emotions Medicament,
you can’t become emotional or angry.
I heard
people have seven emotions and
change their emotions with the environment change.
If the environment changes,
people’s emotions will be stimulated and changed.
Now only the secret behind the veil
can make my emotions fluctuant
and make me be lost in a reverie.
Both Sui He
and I
are curious about your look.
Your Majesty,
it’s said by Confucius:
“I’ve never seen anyone who
loves morality just like loving a beauty.”
Your Majesty, please be self-possessed.
And I look…
You look ugly and are disliked by all people?
I don’t care.
When we were in Luoye Mountain,
we stayed in the same room for over a month.
I know your character well.
I don’t see my lover,
so I am care-laden like entranced.
What can I do?
You’ve forgotten me.
I don’t dare.
When we stayed in the mountain,
you were so bold.
You found chances to have physical contact with me.
After treating me flippantly in the mountain,
you actually want to disown me
and be irresponsible for me.
Do you
have special love
for mountain bandit?
I am terrified as I am guilty.
I, I am very guilty and deserve death.
Don’t always talk about death.
I know you cherish your life.
No.
Though I cherish my life,
I pledge loyalty to Your Majesty more,
or I don’t help Your Majesty deal with Duke Nanping
without consideration of life and death.
I never want your loyalty.
Well,
many a day will come yet.
One day,
I will make you willingly remove the veil.
Your Majesty,
with the bounden duty
as a saint girl of Saint Doctors’ Family,
I need to observe both
Your Majesty’s orders and my family rules
and don’t dare to go off the rails.
I have no other merits
except loyalty.
I can’t give what Your Majesty wants.
Though we had a good time in the mountain,
it isn’t the life of Your Majesty
and me.
About the time in the mountain,
please just take it as a dream, Your Majesty.
I almost couldn’t control myself.
As the emperor of a state, so enchanting
that I was even trapped.
You came up with this dumb idea.
What dumb book is this?
The words of sages
featured by ideas without evil,
such as abstemious joy and sadness.
Unexpectedly, Saint Girl was scared away.
Your Majesty, the love between
man and woman is like march to war.
Besides fine weather, favorable geographical
and human conditions,
tactics and ideas are also important.
When the enemy advance, we retreat
and when the enemy retreat, we chase.
Your Majesty loves Saint Girl
who is dignified and stable,
so the ordinary positional warfare is infeasible.
You should adopt the city seizure tough warfare
of strengthening the defenses and clear the fields.
You are an expert.
Fellow officers and I
think about two things all our lives,
namely protecting our homes and defending our state
and carrying on the family line.
Good.
Go to fetch “Wuzi” for me.
I want that volume with notes I made in spring.
“Wuzi Art of War”?
It was borrowed away by Princess Nanping.
What about “Six Secret Teachings”?
Your Majesty, do you forget
all the Seven Military Classics
were borrowed away by Princess?
Hasn’t she finished reading them?
Go to get them back from her.
Your Majesty, do you forget
now you are unconscious due to illness?
So how can you make an order?
Yes.
Get them back some other day
when I cure
my kidney.
Leave.
So terrible.
Jin Mi is double-faced
and Xu Feng also irritates me.
He actually only listened to Jin Mi verbally.
Well, if it goes on like this,
when will they be together?
It worries me a lot.
This part was over.
You’re to blame. It’s all your fault.
You banished Jin Mi
to the hated Saint Doctors’ Family.
I think
you just envy at
her youth and beauty,
so you don’t want her to have a happy marriage
and arranged her
a fate that is doomed to loneliness.
Damn fox, how can you blame me?
You were there back then.
Recall carefully.
Who agreed to arrange her to Saint Doctors’ Family?
Who disallowed Jin Mi to experience
separation of lovers in mortal world?
It was your dear Second Nephew.
No one expected he would also
jump down to mortal world with her.
He hurt himself
by his own doing.
He deserves it.
Sui He.
Daddy.
What’s wrong?
Who makes you cry
so sadly?
Tell me.
Cousin.
His Majesty?
What did His Majesty do?
Cousin is…
Don’t panic. Don’t panic. Speak slowly.
Today I saw Cousin
coughed up a handful of blood
and passed out.
Saint Girl of Saint Doctors’ Family
diagnosed His Majesty.
What did she say?
She said Cousin
was impotent with kidney deficiency
and five taxations and seven damages.
He has been incurably ill.
Daddy, what can I do?
Find a way to save Cousin.
OK, don’t be afraid.
Don’t be afraid.
I’ll handle everything for you.
Fortunately, His Majesty’s father already passed away.
I’ll manage to cancel your engagement.
Daddy, what do you mean?
Don’t worry.
I won’t push you into the living hell.
You.
You want…
As you see,
a wedding gown and a mourning gown.
Since I was 12 years old,
I’ve preparing a wedding gown for myself every year.
Also when I was 12 years old,
I first saw Cousin
returned from battlefield with wounds
and knew another fate
was waiting for me.
Sui, how stupid you are!
Xu Feng crusaded everywhere,
so he won’t live long.
I know you’ve loved him passionately since childhood,
but we can’t
go against the heaven’s will.
As your father,
I won’t allow you to marry this autocrat.
It turns out that you think of him
in this way all the time.
You really disappoint me.
But I am afraid that I’ll also disappoint you.
I must marry Cousin this life.
Whether I live in widowhood
or can’t have any child later,
I won’t regret.
If I marry him, it’s my luck
and if not, it’s my fate.
Unless he dies,
no one
can separate us forcibly.
Qi Chong.
Your Highness, what can I do for you?
Go get Saint Girl.
I have something to discuss with her.
Yes.
What’s wrong with you?
I didn’t see you the whole afternoon.
Now you are back,
but you bend the brows.
Taste it now.
His Majesty just asked people
to send sweetmeats to us.
Having some sweet food,
you’ll become happy.
I just went to meet Duke Nanping.
Why did you meet him?
I was afraid that you would worry,
so I didn’t tell you.
But now…
Jin Mi, what actually happened?
I heard His Majesty’s illness condition
from my daughter.
You’ve done a good job.
My Lord, you flatter me.
In your opinion,
how long can King Yi live?
One year at most.
I haven’t told it to Her Highness,
or she may feel sad.
Leave her alone.
Today I meet you
to let you manage
to reduce King Yi’s longevity
into 10 days.
10 days?
Yes.
The plan changes.
I can’t wait that long.
It’ll be the Meeting of Commanding Officers
10 days later
when civil and military officials and
border defending generals of various places
will come.
I’ll depose Xu Feng by then.
You should
exactly make him
be killed by poison
on the spot that day.
Yes.
Does Duke Nanping think he is the living Hades
who can determine the death time of a person?
Lower your voice.
Sit down.
Moreover,
he holds the lives of more than one hundred people
in our family this time.
It’s worse than last time.
Now he has sent killers into the village.
They’ll act according to the news 10 days later.
We can’t let Auntie die.
I know.
But if King Yi dies,
more people will suffer.
Why?
Now there is a state of chaos.
People are destitute.
But as for the places under the rule of King Yi,
wars are pacified and people live and work in peace.
If he dies,
who can save the living in water and fire?
I believe him.
If he can calm down the country,
he’ll create a peaceful, tranquil and prosperous age
without war and famine.
It sounds reasonable.
It’s too nerve-racking.
We can’t await our doom
in this way at all.
How about seeking advice from Auntie?
I also think so.
This is a matter of great importance.
We need to discuss with our auntie carefully.