“Ashes of Love”
"Episode 13
Thanks for your favour, Fairy Jin Mi.
I like you, too.
How come you and the Night Immortal...
Do you know who is Jin Mi?
Do you know why Jin Mi can create flowers?
Do you know about the Liuzi Pond in my Qiwu Palace?
Do you know the name of the past Floral Immortal?
Do you know that Jin Mi is water by nature?
Do you know that the past Floral Immortal’s real body
is a piece of water lily?
Do you know
you, me, and Jin Mi
are half-siblings?
Oh my God.
How come I, a grape
have so many
birds and beasts relatives?
If this is true,
then the Heavenly Empress would be my stepmother.
So horrible!
It’s OK.
Even though we three are siblings,
the situation is not bad.
Fairy Jin Mi, tell me.
Besides me,
do you like Xu Feng?
Yes, I like him.
What about the Moon Immortal?
Of course.
What about Yan You?
Yes.
What about Liao Ting and Fei Xu, the servants of Qiwu Palace?
What about Chief Peony?
If Chief Peony
won’t be so hard to me in the future,
I will like her all the better.
Forget it. You are so heartless.
If you still want to be alive,
then go back to the Floral Realm with me.
No. I don’t want to.
I’m useless.
I didn’t expect that His Highness would be bewitched by Jin Mi to such a degree
that he ruined your birthday.
That sprite went to the banquet in disguise, so I don’t blame you.
But she dared
to show her real body in front of Heavenly Emperor and Highness who is in charge of water.
What’s her intention?
The Heaven Realm is a quiet place,
but the Rat Fairy even brought a rat to the banquet,
making such a mess.
Although it is unintentional, it is really absurd.
So funny.
The Snake Fairy went to the banquet with a sprite.
And the sprite was scared by the Rat Fairy.
I’m not sure.
I will check it out.
To say something improper,
His Highness and the Night Immortal
have unusual relationship with this girl.
If left unrestrained,
I’m afraid they will make the same mistake as the Heavenly Emperor
and Water immortal.
In addition, the Snake Fairy,Yan You, has always been infamous.
Aunty, don’t forget
why he was demoted thousands of years ago.
Is it possible
that another Zi Fen exists in the six realms?
I don’t allow
something that can bring disasters and chaos to the Heaven Realm to happen again.
Leave it. Go back and take some rest now.
Yes, aunty.
Your Majesty.
Go and check the information
about those lower-level fairies who came to the banquet today,
especially the twelve zodiac fairies.
Check it carefully.
I’m wondering
which sprite dared to ruin my birthday banquet.
Yes, Your Majesty.
How is Jin Mi?
She’s fine.
Besides, her magic power is stronger.
I cooked some soothing medicine for her.
Let her drink it and go to bed early.
This time Jin Mi showed her real body in the Heaven Realm.
I am afraid that her birth information will be uncovered.
It’s ridiculous that the Fire Immortal
thinks he is Jin Mi’s half brother,
closest relative.
He?
He doesn’t deserve it at all.
There is nothing wrong about making him misunderstand and give up the hope completely.
Don’t forget
how the past Floral Immortal died.
This is a deadly feud.
No matter what happens,
Jin Mi shouldn’t have any connection with the sons of Heavenly Empress and Heavenly Emperor
any more.
Do you know who is Jin Mi?
Do you know why Jin Mi can create flowers?
Do you know about the Liuzi Pond in my Qiwu Palace?
Do you know the name of the past Floral Immortal?
Do you know that Jin Mi is water by nature?
Do you know that the past Floral Immortal’s real body is a piece of water lily?
Do you know
you, me, and Jin Mi
are half-siblings?
What is the connection between Liuzi Pond and my ability to create flowers?
What is the relation between the past Floral Immortal’ s real body and name and me?
How come we three become half brothers and sister
in a blink of an eye?
The Heavenly Empress becomes my stepmother.
Phoenix’s thinking is really leaping.
The past Floral Immortal wanted Jin Mi to be a free and happy fairy
without getting involved in any worldly
romantic relationship.
We should definitely keep this secret
as long as possible.
What's more,
Jin Mi haven’t experienced her destined disaster.
So it is really improper for her to leave the Floral Realm.
From now on,
we take turns to spend the night on watch, staying in the courtyard.
Yes.
But now,
everyone has seen Jin Mi’s real body.
I am afraid that the Heavenly Emperor will come and ask for explanation.
How dare he!
If he dares to ask about this,
then let him go to the Floral Immortal’s Mausoleum and reason with the past Floral Immortal.
What a close call!
I can’t hear clearly what they were saying,
but I think it is something good for me.
Although it’s very boring to practice in Water Mirror,
it’s better than being taken and killed
by the God of Thunder and the Goddess of Lightening.
What do you think, Rou Rou?
So sleepy.
I have run away.
But he still catches me back in my dreams.
Why is Heavenly Emperor so stingy as his wife is?
I venture to take you
to this Fantasy Land.
I hope that you don’t mind.
Not to condemn me...
Your Majesty, you are too modest.
I didn’t expect that
I would actually meet Your Majesty in the dream.
This is Fantasy Land
a place where the Immortals travel and practice.
Occasionally the illusion appears in the Human Realm.
Human beings would call it “Mirage”,
thinking that it is formed .
by the breath of toads in the sea.
When I first heard this,
I couldn’t help but laugh,
thinking that human beings were ignorant.
Until 90,000 years ago,
when I traveled here at night
and saw her stepping on the water
with lotus following after her every step.
Removing the mist
that hid her face when she glanced back,
I started to know what is fantasy,
and what is mirage.
I’m Taiwei, from the Heaven Realm.
May I have your name?
Since she passed away,
there have been no flowers in the Heaven Realm.
I haven’t been here for a long time.
So alike.
Just now in the mist,
I nearly got the wrong person.
But when I look at you carefully,
I find nothing alike.
She didn’t like laughing.
During the 90,000 years when we knew each other,
I saw her laugh only ten times.
Her occasional laughing wouldn’t last long.
She is not as bright and sweet
as you.
If without me,
during these 90,000 years,
she would have laughed a lot,
and wouldn’t have ended her life in loneliness
like this.
The dead person has gone.
Please restrain your grief, Your Majesty.
There have been no plants in the Heaven Realm and this Fantasy Land
for over four thousand years.
I heard that you can create flowers.
You might as well plant some green lotus here.
Why did he suddenly mention planting flowers?
He’s really Phoenix’s father.
Even his thinking is so leaping, too.
According to Phoenix,
he seems to be my father, too.
So I should fulfill my filial duty.
OK.
Sure enough.
Please retrain your grief, Your Majesty.
I can only do this
to comfort you.
Do you know who I was talking about?
I’m still so young, and I have stayed in the Water Mirror for long time.
The people I know
are some
vegetables and fruits.
I really don’t know any reserved person
who only laughs once ten thousand years
like you talked about just now.
But as for those shallow ones who laugh ten times a day,
there are plenty of them.
Please don’t mind my lack of experiences.
I don’t know who you were talking about, Your Majesty.
The person I talked about just now
is the Floral Immortal Zi Fen.
You are more than four thousand years old.
Is it possible that you have never seen Zi Fen?
Never.
I didn’t expect that
she actually hated me so much
that she even didn’t want to see her child.
Your...Your Majesty.
You..you can’t say something that is not true.
This dream is too strange.
Why does the Heavenly Emperor
come to my dreams?
The past Floral Immortal is a piece of lotus.
And I am a grape.
How come she is my mother?
The father and the son’s thinking
are so leaping.
No, this is my dream.
It seems that my thinking is leaping.
It’s Phoenix’s fault.
In the daytime, he always talks about things that are not real.
I’m dreaming so deeply. It’s time to wake up.
It seems that it is not a common dream.
Forget it. Since I’m in dream now, I should enjoy it.
I don’t have many chances to meet the Heavenly Emperor.
It’s better to ask him for some magic power.
To have a dream of getting much magic power
is so worthwhile.
Your Majesty.
If you like to watch me plant flowers,
I can often plant flowers for you.
And it’s also OK if you assign me to be a gardener in the Heaven Realm.
But...
But..
What’s wrong?
If you have any difficulties, let me know.
My magic power is not strong.
Although I have practiced hard
I’m still an elf.
I know some tricks of planting flowers and grasses,
but I still need the power from the outside
to create them.
So you have seen my poor performance, Your Majesty.
Zi Fen must have sealed your spirit.
How about this?
I’ll give you some magic power.
And you go back and practice for 49 days.
Then your real body will show up.
How can I afford to the magic power you give me,
Your Majesty?
Good girl.
You don’t have to be so distant to me.
It is a matter of righteousness
that I give you some magic power.
Thank you so much, Your Majesty.
But your power is not strong,
so I can only give you five thousand years’ magic power.
Five thousand years.
Thank you so much, Your Majesty.
If I hadn’t make that mistake tens of thousands of years ago,
the Chiefs of Floral Realm wouldn’t have considered the Heaven Realm as enemy.
And we wouldn’t have had to see each other in dreams at night.
Sorry to make you feel wronged.
I don’t feel wronged.
Not at all.
You give me five thousand years of magic power in one night.
You don’t even feel wronged. Why should I feel wronged?
I hope this is not just a dream.
As for what I owe Suifen,
I will slowly make compensation for you.
But you should keep one thing in mind.
Go ahead, Your Majesty.
I will do whatever you ask me to do at all costs.
You should keep in mind
that you can’t have any romantic relationship
with Xu Feng and Run Yu.
Understand?
Don’t worry, Your Majesty.
It’s easy.
Are you thinking about the grape elf
who appeared at the birthday banquet of the Heavenly Empress?
That elf and she do have some resemblance.
For when I saw that elf
I keep thinking about Zi Fen.
In these years,
you never mentioned Zi Fen in front of me.
But I know,
in your heart
she has never left.
Linxiu,
it’s really unfair for you
to marry me.
I’m not blaming you.
In these years, we have respected each other like guests,
living a peaceful life. I’m already satisfied.
It’s just that seeing your heart still closed,
I feel sad for you.
Linxiu.
If you miss her,
then just go to see her.
OK.
All right.
It’s too late now.
Go to bed early.
You, too.
You took action first without my permission,
letting that sprite go back to the Floral Realm.
And then you come to report your guilt now.
Mother, please don’t be angry.
You, the Fire Immortal
are the noble son of the Heavenly Emperor.
Everyday so many people watch you.
But you make friends
with that bad-mannered sprite who even hasn’t entered the immortality.
And because of her,
you even argued with me in public.
How can I feel relieved?
Jin Mi has saved my life for many times.
And because her power is weak,
I have to help her.
Jin Mi is young and ignorant, knowing little about the manners and rules.
But she is not malicious.
Tell me.
Do you really just want to repay her?
Or you already have affection for her?
No.
Good.
Then promise me
that you will never see that sprite again.
Then I will forgive her.
Yesterday I promised Chief Peony
that I will not see Jin Mi again.
Mother, you can feel relieved now.
Relieved?
Only when you really become the Heavenly Emperor,
leading the Heaven Realm,
marrying Sui He and having kids
can I really feel relieved.
You’re thinking too much, Mother.
I have to go to the drill ground and train the soldiers.
I need to leave now.
If I hadn’t have thought much,
how can you enjoy the current status?
Your Highness, you just rested for a little while after the night patrol.
Why bother to go to Floral Realm in a hurry,
making yourself tired?
I heard that Chief Peony has always been strict with younger generations.
This time, I secretly took Jin Mi to the Human Realm without her permission,
and even nearly made a disaster in the Heaven Realm.
I am afraid that Chief Peony will not forgive Jin Mi easily.
I am going to the Floral Realm.
You don't have to follow me.
Yes, Your Highness.
Oops!
She will not forgive Jin Mi easily.
The Heavenly Empress have already borne grudge against you, Your Highness.
At this time, if you go there hastily,
I am afraid things will get worse.
And the problems will be more difficult to solve.
Xu Feng was so sure yesterday
that Jin Mi is Father’s daughter.
The way Father looked at Jin Mi yesterday
was really unusual.
I’m going to ask Father for help.
OK.
Then I’ll go to the Floral Realm to make a thorough inquiry.
Be careful.
I, Jin Mi, a fruit elf
pretended to be a descendant of the past Floral Immortal
and got five thousand years’ magic power from the Heavenly Emperor.
You are a great person and won’t care about the faults of the petty ones.
You won’t blame me, right?
I don't know what you like to eat.
If you need anything,
you can tell me in my dreams.
I will take good care of you
at all costs.
Here, I would like to express my thanks to you.
In fact, I should celebrate such a lucky thing
with everyone.
But I am not in the Heaven Realm,
so I can only invite Lord Puchi to celebrate this thing with me.
Heavenly...Heavenly Empress.
I could call Lord Puchi before with small part of my power.
I didn’t expect that I would be able to call Heavenly Empress
after my magic power gets much stronger.
Your Majesty.
Why are you here?
Before you die,
I would like to teach you some manners.
Your Majesty.
What are you doing?
What manner?
I don't care who you are.
And I don’t care what relationship you have
with Xu Feng and Runyu.
Just because of your face,
I would like to kill you thousands of times.
You and Zi Fen really have a bond.
You will die a worthy death here.
I don’t know what you mean.
How long ago?
It’s been half an hour.
Mother, please don’t be impulsive and angry.
If Father you are a bit late, I am afraid that Jin Mi will...
Jin Mi is my child.
If I go to stop Tuyao hastily,
she won’t let Jin Mi go easily.
How about this?
You pass on my order quickly.
Ask your Mother to come back, telling her that there are things to discuss
about rewarding fairies and forgiving the sins in the Heaven Realm
after her birthday.
Since Jin Mi is Father’s child,
she is also my sister.
Please don’t worry, Father.
I will try my best to protect her.
Mister Water Immortal.
Don't you know the law of superiority and inferiority ?
Why are you here to interfere with me
instead of going to making wind and rain?
I certainly know the law of superiority and inferiority.
But the past Floral Immortal and I are old friends.
Today, I’m here to show my worship.
But I didn’t expect that
this child was almost killed by someone.
I’m here to punish a little floral elf.
It’s none of your business.
Jin Mi is an elf of the Floral Realm.
Since it is in the Floral Realm,
only the Floral Immortal and Chief Peony have the right to decide who is guilty and deserves punishment.
Zi Fen has passed away.
In front of her tomb,
how can you bear to lay murderous hands
on such a low-level elf?
You said you knew the law of superiority and inferiority.
But actually,
you are here just for the sake of Zi Fen.
You do this,
just because this sprite
looks a little like Zi Fen, right?
In view of the public and personal concerns,
I can’t let you do this.
Do you think you can stop me?
Mother, I’ve been looking for you for long time.
Fish Fairy.
Mister Water Immortal.
Fish Fairy, please save me.
Mother.
I haven’t allowed you to stand up.
Mother,
I’m here just to perform Father’s order.
He asked you to go back to the Empyrean Heaven quickly
to discuss things about rewarding fairies and forgiving sins in the Heaven Realm.
Your Majesty, you are a motherly model in the Heaven Realm.
So you should assume your personal command in the Heaven Realm, minding your words and behaviors.
If you disturb the Chiefs of Floral Realm,
bringing the arguments to His Majesty,
I am afraid it will damage your good reputation
of virtue and kindheartedness.
Very good.
Night Immortal, you can do things independently now.
You are more and more powerful,
daring to conspire against me with others.
I don’t dare.
Mother,
please.
Mister Water Immortal. Fairy Jin Mi.
See you.
Thank you so much, Mister Water Immortal.
Fairy Jin Mi, are you here to accompany Zi Fen by her tomb?
It’s just a trivial thing.
Jin Mi...Jin Mi.
looking for peace among the blooming flowers;
leading a life of floating clouds and water.
These are two lines of poem
that hung in front of Zi Fen’s desk when she’s alive.
I copied these two lines of poem, mounted and hung them for her.
I didn’t know
Zi Fen still has a child left in the world.
Mister Water Immortal.
According to what you said,
am I really the child
of the past Floral Immortal and the Heavenly Emperor?
Lord Puchi
Jin Mi.
Can you improve your accuracy?
You will get my bone broken sooner or later.
I’m being so rude. Mister Water Immortal.
Yan You, are you here to play?
No, no, no.
I never go about in the hope of finding girls.
I trespass the Floral Realm,
just because Jin Mi called me.
Your magic power becomes stronger.
Is it you who called Mister Water Immortal?
When you call Yan You,
what spell do you use ?
My magic power is weak.
I just use the common call spell.
The real body of Yan You is a water snake.
Can you call water?
The Fire Immortal said that my body constitution is coldness-oriented.
So he let me practice some water-related magics.
I created hail stone twice.
But I have never tried to call water.
Then try it.
Me?
Now?
Fine.
Then I’m going to try it today
in front of Mister Water Immortal.
Call!
You still can't call water with your magic power.
I’ll try again.
Call!
Jin Mi, you are just a common elf.
Why parade your ability?
How about this?
Such a big cloud.
It’s so dark.
Jin Mi
Chief Peony.
Mister Water Immortal, what’s wrong with Jin Mi?
Look!
It’s snowing.
I can call snow.
I can call it.
Your Highness.
Why did Highness who is in charge of water go to the Floral Realm?
It seems that he went there to worship the past Floral Immortal.
The Heavenly Empress was going to kill Jin Mi
and destroy the past Floral Immortal’s Mausoleum.
I didn’t expect that Mister Water Immortal would arrive in time
and save Jin Mi’s life,
even at the cost of offending the Heavenly Empress.
Water Immortal has never cared about the worldly things.
But when he saw Jin Mi
his reactions were too unusual.
I’m going to the Floral Realm again.
If the Heavenly Empress attempts to hurt Jin Mi again, inform me quickly.
How is Jin Mi?
Is it because of too much lost of magic power?
That heavy snow was called by Jin Mi.
If Jin Mi is not water by nature,
how can she call Yan You?
What’s the real identity of Jin Mi?
If Jin Mi is just a common elf,
why are you and Chief Begonia
being so nervous?
I’m just a floral fairy of the Floral Realm.
Water Immortal, don’t you
know what you have done?
Do you need others to tell you the truth?
Jin Mi looks like Zi Fen so much,
but she said she was a grape.
I really can't figure out the reason for this.
Jin Mi has been taken care of by you since she was born.
Today, only the Chiefs of Floral Realm
can tell me the truth.
I said that Jin Mi’s tendency to be confused is born by nature.
It turns out that there is some reason for this.
Did you say...
Is Jin Mi really...
Don’t ask me, Water Immortal.
I can’t tell you everything.
We Chiefs swore in front of the Floral Immortal.
If we leak out anything about Jin Mi’s birth,
we will destroy our souls.
Please forgive me, Water Immortal.
The essential Qi in Jin Mi’s body is in disorder.
Did you give Jin Mi magic power?
This is the first time I privately met Jin Mi.
The magic power in Jin Mi’s body is so strong
and overwhelming.
With my ability,
I can't dissolve it.
For the sake of Jin Mi’s life,
we don’t have other choices .
How is Jin Mi?
The Yang Qi in Jin Mi body is very strong.
I don't know who
gave her so much Yang Qi,
which contradicts her Yin nature.
If I weren’t here today,
I am afraid that she would be in danger.
Thank you so much, Mister Water Immortal.
If something wrong happened to Jin Mi,
how
can we explain to the past Floral Immortal?
Jin Mi
turns out to be my child.