♫ Chasing wind, I set out afar ♫
♫ The road ahead lost, my voice unheard ♫
♫ I've tasted joy and sorrow ♫
♫ Laying low, I plan every move ♫
♫ With a mortal heart and lingering ties ♫
♫ I'm roaming far and wide ♫
♫ A twist of fate in desperate times ♫
♫ A bond that outlives the dust of life ♫
♫ Still chasing what immortality means ♫
♫ Even eternity flashes by in a blink ♫
♫ Don't mock my ordinary life ♫
♫ I fight alone as chaos shakes the world ♫
♫ Don't scorn my humble roots ♫
♫ Kind at heart, ruthless when I must be ♫
♫ Fate stirs with joy and grief beneath ♫
♫ I hold the tide between life and death ♫
♫ Faith carries me through endless dark ♫
♫ And I return with a heart refined ♫
♫ Forged by trial, I rise through three realms ♫
♫ Reborn in the wheel of fate ♫
You've exceeded your permission!
I came to bring Yan some medicine.
It is a secret concoction from my sect,
capable of preserving one's power
for a brief moment.
Would you like to try it, Lord Yan?
I was told you kept staring at a woman
from Yellow Maple Valley in the city.
You're mistaken.
I already have Yan.
I don't need another woman.
But I have need of that woman
from Yellow Maple Valley,
so I need to scour more information.
Worry not.
No one knows my identity.
In that case,
perhaps we can postpone the plan
against the common folks for the moment.
Lord Yan,
are you having a moment of compassion?
Impossible.
Those cultivators just arrived.
I don't want anything to happen to you
before the ceremony tomorrow.
All right then.
As you wish.
The plague is almost over.
- Make sure to take the medicine.
- Thanks, Miss Mo.
Here.
Thank you.
- Take this.
- Thanks.
Take the medicine on time.
Okay. Thank you.
Mister.
Miss Mo!
I have 20 gems here.
Like what you said previously,
I should have enough for two Moongazing Grass.
Unfortunately, Miss Mo,
many cultivators have arrived in this city.
Moongazing Grass has become a scarcity.
20 gems was the price from 3 months ago.
You know what?
I don't need the grass.
Can I buy some seeds from you?
That's a fool's errand.
The spiritual power is weak in the Lower City.
It's not conducive for cultivating herbs.
Miss Mo,
have you thought about moving to the upper level?
Thank you.
It's okay then.
Miss Mo. Hear me out.
Like I said, be my second wife
and you can have whatever herbs you want.
Miss Mo.
Miss Mo. Hear me out!
I am the biggest herb supplier in this stronghold.
You'll have a comfortable life,
even as my second wife!
Miss Mo. Listen to me.
A comfortable life awaits. Just come with me!
Li?
Miss Mo.
♫ The ripples disappear into the river ♫
♫ My robe is soaked under the drizzle ♫
Over here, Li.
♫ The current flows swiftly,
the mountains weigh heavily ♫
♫ The setting sun outlines the returning fleet ♫
♫ As I meander in the mortal world ♫
♫ The breeze brushes through the corridor ♫
♫ As the swallows whisper overhead ♫
♫ The setting sun graces the bamboo forest,
for whom do I harmonize? ♫
♫ Leaning against the rails,
water ripples below me ♫
♫ The wind whispers to the forest ♫
♫ I wander into the dream under the clear galaxy ♫
♫ This journey that spans across the universe ♫
♫ Feels both familiar and unfamiliar ♫
♫ Looking at the various faces of our world ♫
♫ Each word, each utterance ♫
♫ Carries the hopes of a lifetime ♫
♫ Let's make use of our present
to build a legacy ♫
♫ Reunion and departure, looking around... ♫
It's been many years.
And you are as reticent as ever, Miss Mo.
It's been a decade.
How have you been, Li?
♫ And the gentle drizzle... ♫
I'm doing great.
I didn't expect to run into you here.
How is your family?
They are gone.
Three years ago,
the Five-Color Sect found an affluent ally
and became powerful.
As you already know,
they have been trying to usurp my family's legacy.
My family was slaughtered in a night.
Only I survived.
To be frank, my family has expected that.
They just didn't know it would happen this soon.
And this brutally.
The Five-Color Sect.
What about Qu Hun?
Did he not protect you?
Several months before the tragedy,
he lost control and ran to the mountain.
I couldn't catch up to him.
It's fine,
Li.
It's history anyway.
I found my way here, and founded this apothecary.
Even though I'm all alone,
I'm content with my life.
The tea has gotten cold.
Li, drink this instead.
I just brewed it.
How did you cross that cultivator just now?
Li, no need to worry about me.
I can protect myself.
Okay.
Just let me know if you need my help.
Don't be shy.
I'm fine.
Li, stay here to rest up if you want.
I still need to retrieve some herbs.
Let me do it.
Take a break.
I can carry it.
People roam here in haste.
No one has the time to look up.
To me, this is such a relief.
Now I understand
why Han Li wishes to avoid attention.
Solitude feels good.
Why must I have the gift of enchantment?
A mortal can live freely.
Yet I always attract conflicts
even though I don't mean to hurt anyone.
I have no freedom.
I arrived here yesterday.
And I heard that there were
some mysteries in the Lower City.
Are you aware of them?
Mysteries?
Like the sudden death of some commoners
or rookie cultivators.
I did hear that some people disappeared
under mysterious circumstances at night.
But no one has found their bodies.
Miss, it is a great evening tonight.
Why are you sulking alone?
Relax.
We are not bad guys.
We just hate to see a frown on your face.
Miss, try this.
It makes me feel happy?
Have you not heard of this saying?
Liquor can drown your sorrow away.
We're not trying to make you drunk.
We just don't want to see you sulk.
And I know you're not bad guys.
I just can't bring myself
to drink the moon in this cup.
You worry for naught.
The moon will appear in all things that flow.
Just as all things that flow
will reflect the moon.
So long as your cup is filled,
I... The moon will always be in your hands.
Well said.
Thank you.
It's beautiful. Cheers.
- Cheers.
It burns.
That's it.
Again.
You can drink.
Okay. You can drink, miss.
You hold your cup.
Let me fill it.
Li, you must be a powerful cultivator now.
I only reached the Foundation Establishment Stage.
Well, just strong enough to protect myself.
Beautiful.
Look over there.
It's so beautiful.
So pretty.
Look there.
I am Dong Xuan Er of Yellow Maple Valley.
How may I address you?
I am Wu You Zi of Clear Void Sect.
I am Ba Chu Shui of Giant Sword Sect.
Are you here for the betrothal ceremony?
We're here to catch the bad guys.
But this doesn't matter.
Come. Drink up.
- Come.
- Yes, it doesn't matter.
- Thank you.
Great!
There's more.
Wow!
Bravo.
I've never seen him this happy before.
He found a new girl this soon in a foreign place.
Let's go down and check it out.
Well, we shall take our leave.
We'll be admiring the fireworks.
Enjoy the drink.
Thank you.
- Let's go.
♫ Shards of dreams inside a dream... ♫
Li, is it impossible to be a cultivator
without a spirit root?
♫ Years slipped by as I lingered on ♫
♫ Old scenes rise again ♫
♫ Too hard to forget, easier just to miss ♫
♫ They say the past fades like smoke ♫
♫ But looking back still stirs the ache ♫
♫ This noisy world, this lonely page ♫
♫ Swept away by time ♫
♫ Eyes once looked far now lost in the shift ♫
♫ Autumn winds stir, smoke curls once more ♫
♫ Like clouds on the edge of sky
returning to my eyes ♫
♫ Looking back from the mountaintop,
time lost its name ♫
♫ Was it yesterday or tomorrow? ♫
♫ The world has changed beyond recall ♫
♫ Time will fade ♫
♫ All the words ever spoken ♫
♫ Only this longing remains ♫
♫ Crossing centuries and days ♫
♫ In a fleeting moment ♫
♫ we call eternity ♫
You there.
Come.
You're hit by my enchantment.
Look at me. Look at me.
I am Dong Xuan Er of Yellow Maple Valley.
You are all enchanted.
Look at me. Look at me.
Oh, no. She's in danger.
Miss Mo, please go home first.
I still have things to do. I must go now.
Keep this.
If those cultivators give you trouble,
throw it at them.
These are the seeds of mystic herbs
and the pills good for mortals.
You can take them, or sell them after refining.
Don't sell them for too cheap.
They are good pills.
If anything, leave a message at the inn.
Will we meet again?
I'll see you off.
Go home.
Okay.
So beautiful.
My dear, just come with me.
I'll make you feel good.
I'm not your dear.
I'm Dong Xuan Er of Yellow Maple Valley.
I Know that.
You know me?
I know your father, mother,
grandmother, and grandfather.
All of them.
I can recite your family lineage.
Oh, I know now.
You're enchanted by me.
Yes.
I'm so enchanted by you.
Where does this guy come from?
Who are you?
Don't get in our way.
You want to play the hero?
Are you strong enough?
You two should fight.
I'll go with the winner.
Okay?
All right. Come on.
Fight.
Fight now. Fight.
What a weird technique.
Why won't he show his face?
Perhaps he doesn't want to draw attention.
Wow. That's amazing!
Who's there?
He fled.
You won.
I'll come with you!
You are all enchanted by me.
I am Dong Xuan Er of Yellow Maple Valley.
Can you resist my enchantment?
Oh, no.
If my master and mentors see her like this,
they'll hold me accountable.
I need to sort this out first.
Han, where am I?
Drink the medicine.
What medicine is this?
Stop staring at me.
Drink it.
Dong Xuan Er,
I told you to stop using your enchantment.
That man took advantage of you
and damaged your spirit.
You need a few days to fully recover.
We promised to stay out of each other's business.
Why are you following me?
Following you?
I'm following your kidnapper.
I've sensed his gaze on you
many times in the city.
He's following me?
Yes.
I have an ominous feeling.
Stay close to me tomorrow.
We'll go back as soon as the ceremony ends.
Obey my order for now.
Then, we stay out of each other's business.
This is not a negotiation.
Okay.
Where are you going, Han?
I mean, can you stay the night?
I will keep watch tonight.
I hope you won't tell my master
about what happened today.
I never intend to cross anyone.
Why is it my fault every time?
All right.
I know you don't mean to use your gift.
I won't tell anyone about today.
You promise?
I promise.
Han, I'm hungry.
Sleep.
But what about my tummy?
You don't feel hungry when you're asleep.
But I want to...
You're boring.
Han, is it cold over there?
Quit staring.
Where are you from?
I am Xuan Yue of Moonshadow Sect.
My sect has instructed me
to retrieve this month's gems.
Xuan.
They are our loyal patron.
No need to check. Go back to your work.
Follow me.
How come you're early, Xuan?
We're two days before the deadline.
My sect needs it urgently.
Can you
help us?
Oh, come on.
We always reserve the best for your sect.
Enjoy your tea first.
My friend, what has happened to the quarry?
I see many new faces.
Young Lady is getting married.
So we station more people here
for better security.
The groom is so fortunate then.
He will own the entire quarry.
He got lucky.
Which sect does the groom hail from?
He is fortunate enough to marry
the daughter of Lord Yan.
I heard he's a foreign cultivator.
A foreign cultivator?
From where?
What background?
Stop asking already.
This is for the higher-up.
We should just stay quiet.
Come. Have some tea.
The Mountain Barrier is hit?
Xuan, stay here.
I'll be back soon.
Ouch. Easy.
Tell me now.
Why mobilize so many people
for the betrothal ceremony tomorrow?
Ouch.
Xuan. Stop asking.
For old time's sake, listen to me.
Run.
I might not be able to return here again.
I need to carry out my plan soon.
Grandmaster.
Yes?
The Jiang Kingdom
and The Cheqi Kingdom are no more.
The whole royalty was eradicated.
The Ghost Spirit Sect did it.
Inform all elders to meet at Yellow Maple Valley
for a discussion.
And tell Xuan Yue
to report back about the Yue Kingdom's border.
Noted, Grandmaster.
Go now.
Is a war about to break out?
It's so crowded.
Han, Dong. Morning.
- Morning.
Did you two find anything last night?
Well... The fireworks were mesmerizing.
The liquor was intoxicating. Yes.
After the ceremony,
we'll return to what we came here for.
Exactly. Han, join us.
Sure. I'll join you.
- We do it together.
Do what together?
It's a secret.
Listen. We can't...
You said someone was following me last night.
Did you find him?
No.
But you must stay close to me.
Don't go anywhere.
Look, Han.
It's so festive in front.
Let's check it out.
How odd.
I sense something ominous.
It's majestic.
The grandeur!
Let's stand in the front row.
Stay behind me.
Where is Lord Yan?
I know, right?
It's a betrothal ceremony.
None of the elders is here.
Yan Ru Yan looks weird.
He was the person from last night.
Him?
Why would Lord Yan pick someone like him
to be his son-in-law?
Hush.
There's something off about this ceremony.
Follow me.
Welcome to the betrothal ceremony
between Yan and me.
The banquet begins now.
Wait.
My power is all gone.
Oh, no. My power has been suppressed.
The Wind Boat doesn't work here.
Han, my power has been suppressed.
My power has been suppressed too.
Run!
It's the Blood Spirit Spell
by the Ghost Spirit Sect.
Run! Run!
Yan and I received your gifts with thanks.
The so-called righteous seven sects
pride themselves with their generosity.
Then surrender your power
to save the future heiress of the Yan Clan.
At this critical juncture,
forgive me.
There is...
No turning back for my clan.
Lord Yan, these people are not dead.
They merely turn into power
and are fused with Yan.
They should thank me
for this honor.
No.
They should thank you,
Lord Yan.
We made a Truedeath Oath.
If you fail to save Yan,
I will make you pay.
Yan is my wife.
I want her back more than you do.
Yan is still unconscious.
Despite all this power,
she does not wake up.
My wife sure has a big appetite.
Be patient.
A few escaped just now.
I'll chase after them and feed them to Yan.
♫ Shards of dreams inside a dream ♫
♫ A pale moon falls into mirrored skies ♫
♫ Years slipped by as I lingered on ♫
♫ Old scenes rise again ♫
♫ Too hard to forget ♫
♫ Easier just to miss ♫
♫ They say the past fades like smoke ♫
♫ But looking back still stirs the ache ♫
♫ This noisy world, this lonely page ♫
♫ Swept away by time ♫
♫ Eyes once looked far ♫
♫ Now lost in the shift ♫
♫ Autumn winds stir ♫
♫ Smoke curls once more ♫
♫ Like clouds on the edge of sky ♫
♫ Returning to my eyes ♫
♫ Looking back from the mountaintop ♫
♫ Time lost its name ♫
♫ Was it yesterday ♫
♫ Or tomorrow? ♫
♫ The world has changed ♫
♫ Beyond recall ♫
♫ Time will fade ♫
♫ All the words ever spoken ♫
♫ Only this longing remains ♫
♫ Crossing centuries and days ♫
♫ In a fleeting moment ♫
♫ we call eternity ♫
♫ called eternity ♫