Of course, Mr. Zero.
Understood.
I apologize for keeping you waiting.
We are tying up
some especially pesky loose ends.
I believe you have a history
with one of them.
Princess Vivi of Alabasta?
Cobra's blue-haired brat.
I heard she went missing.
And Mr. Zero would like to ensure
she's never found.
Now, how can I help you?
Oh, I came to speak to the man in charge.
Not some secretary.
Delicious as she might be.
Unfortunately, Mr. Zero
is otherwise occupied.
This is an insult.
You disrespect my king.
A king currently
in exile from his own kingdom,
who requires the aid of my organization
to get it back.
Unless you'd prefer to keep sailing
around the Grand Line playing pirate?
I have been very generous
with my financial contributions
to Baroque Works.
But you tell your leader
there's no such thing as a free lunch.
I want
what I'm owed!
Sire, your blood pressure.
Funny you mentioned lunch.
The symbol of Drum Kingdom's royal family
is a woolly hippo, is it not?
An animal known
for its voracious appetite.
Mmm.
Well, rest assured,
we have no intention
of leaving you hungry.
Blackbeard has vacated Drum.
Mm-hmm.
Mr. Zero thinks
it's time you reclaim your birthright.
He feels a king
would make a valuable ally.
Hmm.
Is this…
A gift.
A token of gratitude
for your financial contributions.
What do you get for the king
who has everything?
A devil fruit!
What power does this one hold?
Well, that's the fun, isn't it?
Take a bite and find out.
Mmm!
Bon appétit.
Sanji?
What…
How…
You're okay. You're okay.
Do you want some food?
I made you, uh, some fresh consommé.
I ran out of chicken stock,
but it turns out that dinosaur
is a very versatile ingredient.
I'm not hungry.
Well…
you need to eat something.
- I've been trying, but--
- Sanji, I'm fine.
I just passed out at dinner last night.
I must've been more tired than I thought.
Nami, that was four days ago.
What?
You've been in and out since you fainted.
I've been here the whole time.
Uh…
It's probably just heatstroke. I…
No.
I think that…
I think that something happened
at Little Garden.
I don't know what, but…
but it's okay
because we're getting you help.
Okay.
Thank you…
for worrying about me.
I always worry about you.
Aren't you cold?
Could be warmer,
I guess.
You know,
everybody else has got a shirt on.
If you insist.
How's Nami doing?
She's asleep again,
but it's getting worse.
Her fever's still sky-high.
- We need to find a doctor.
- We don't even know where we are.
How are we gonna find a doctor?
What about Alabasta?
You have doctors there, don't you?
We could be days,
maybe weeks from Alabasta.
Nami doesn't have
that kind of time.
We have to try.
You wanna get home
as soon as possible, don't you?
I do need to get home as soon as possible.
Which is why we're gonna stop
at the first island we find
and get Nami help.
Then we make to Alabasta.
That's well said. Thank you, Vivi.
Exactly.
That is the fastest way.
Sounds like a plan.
So this is
the communications outpost?
Better to be discreet when the job
is intercepting and tracing calls.
Hope they have a shower.
What?
We could both use one.
All right, let's make this fast.
Get a comm snail and radio Marine fort.
Tell them we've been
up and down the Grand Line
and found no sign of Baroque Works.
Can't capture an agent alive
if we can't find one.
How do you think
Vice Admiral Garp's gonna take it?
Ah, we've indulged this wild goose chase
long enough.
- It's time to go after the Straw Hats.
- They could be anywhere by now.
This again? Do we need to get you a cane?
Captain?
Sword wounds.
Pirates.
Not just any pirates.
These wounds were made
by a skilled swordsman.
Straw Hats.
Why would the Straw Hats go out
of their way to attack a comms outpost?
Find the commander's office. Call it in.
What if you need backup?
I won't.
Luffy, we found an island!
Look at all the snow.
It's so white!
Drum Kingdom.
You recognize this place?
Lucky for us, it's a nation
renowned throughout the Grand Line
for its medical expertise.
Oh, that's great. There'll be
tons of doctors there, then, no?
Or snow monsters.
That possibility should be factored in!
When we arrive, it might be best
if we keep my identity a secret.
'Cause you're an assassin or a princess?
From what I've been told,
the people of Drum are welcoming and kind.
But there is some history.
The politics between Drum and Alabasta
are… tenuous.
What does that mean?
It means someone on the island
hates Vivi's guts.
Do you wanna tell us who?
Their king.
Wapol.
Royal conflict isn't the kind of problem
we need right now.
We have no other choice.
This is our only option to save Nami.
Then let's go find us a doctor.
The reverie will now come to order.
Welcome, fellow nobles.
I, Thalassa Lucas,
King of Ilisia,
call this reverie to order.
Before we begin, I would like to once
again extend our thanks to the Marines
for their protection during our travels
and these proceedings.
And where are the warlords of the sea?
Hmm?
Remind me again
why we give those criminals free rein
if they aren't around to protect us,
let alone our kingdoms.
Warlords exist as a deterrent
for other pirates.
An important check
to the power balance of the seas.
And how did that
work out for the fishmen?
Their queen was assassinated a while back,
and not even the fishmen warlord
could stop it.
If those among us wish to question
the efficacy of the warlords,
perhaps they should run for chairman
and put it on the docket.
Today, we have
a more pressing threat to address.
He is known only as Dragon.
Though his numbers are modest now,
his revolutionary army
grows more every day.
I believe there is no greater threat
to the World Government,
to our prosperity, to our stability,
than this man.
We must not ignore the danger…
…the danger that he…
Something else to add, King Wapol?
Me?
Always.
That's fine.
Rebellion schmabellion.
The people of Drum Kingdom are happy.
I provide them with food and water,
an army for their protection,
and the best medical care in the world.
And should any of my subjects
become ungrateful for my generosity,
then I can always take my gifts away.
May I have the floor?
The chair recognizes
King Cobra of Alabasta.
Revolutions are also
an expression of human emotion.
People whose voices are not heard
cannot truly be happy.
There was a time when one could hear
the people's laughter in your kingdom.
Well, someone's into old tales.
Drum once had a king
who listened to his people.
Well, I couldn't stand my father.
He hadn't the slightest clue
what it meant to rule.
And now I am king.
A king is but a man,
and a crown is just a hat.
It is the kingdom that endures.
I am the kingdom!
Politics is about power,
not feelings.
And I'd sooner hear wisdom
from one of your sandpit's giant ducks
than listen to another second
of your prattling on
about the laughter in the hills.
- Enough!
- Do you know what I do…
Enough!
- I'll tell you when it's enough!
- Order!
Here comes the heat.
Way to keep your eye on the ball, slugger.
What the hell are you?
Stepping up to the mound,
it's Miss Thursday.
- Baroque Works.
- You've heard of us.
Talk about an unforced error.
Guess not everyone's ready for the majors.
Enough baseball jokes.
Hit the bench.
Now she's got me doing it.
So much for taking one alive.
Where are we?
We're getting you help. Just stay with us.
What the hell was that?
The last warning shot
they'll ever get off.
Stop right there, pirates!
Turn back at once,
or face the consequences.
We saw your ship.
- You can't fool us.
- We have a sick crewmate who needs help!
Leave this country alone,
you lying pirates!
We need a doctor!
Vivi!
You assholes!
Stop! All of you!
Your impulsiveness
will not solve anything.
If you get us killed,
what will happen to Nami?
You are the captain. Think!
We are very sorry.
If we cannot enter your village,
please spare us a doctor out here.
Our friend is gravely ill.
Please help us.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong!
Please!
Help our friend.
That was very smart, Vivi.
Are you all right?
I'll be fine.
All of you, come with me.
Wow, here comes
the welcoming committee.
Is she gonna shoot us again?
Please forgive Maria.
We've all been
on edge.
Sorry, Dalton.
Sorry, pirates.
The villagers here
aren't soldiers.
They're civilians.
Prone to itchy trigger fingers.
But after what they've been through,
it's understandable.
Are you the king?
My name is Dalton,
captain of the Civilian Guard.
I don't understand.
What happened here? Where's King Wapol?
A pirate named Blackbeard
laid siege to our village.
He was a man
fueled by bloodshed and carnage.
When his Jolly Roger
showed up on the horizon,
the country was left defenseless.
We couldn't hold Blackbeard off.
Only endured
until he'd had his fill and left.
You're saying Wapol's forces
had no chance against Blackbeard's crew?
I'm saying the king and his soldiers
didn't even try.
Once Wapol saw Blackbeard's power…
he abandoned us all.
And he has the nerve
to call himself a king.
- Vivi.
- How could he do that to his people?
What about the doctors?
Hopefully one of them survived.
Wapol took all the doctors with him.
Great. So we've
wasted our time for nothing.
Except one.
Her name is Kureha.
The witch.
Did you just say witch?
She's taken over Drum Castle
at the top of the mountain.
She's the only one
who can help your friend.
Her medicine is dangerous. Unnatural.
I've seen her flying through the sky under
a full moon with the beast of the forest.
And there's a beast?
Mm-mm. Mm-mm.
- I knew it.
- I'm not scared of a witch.
Or a beast.
If she can save Nami,
then we have to get up there.
How do we get up there?
There was a gondola.
But Wapol destroyed it, trying
to protect his palace from Blackbeard.
You'll have to take the path
on the far side of the mountain. But…
you'll never make the trek by nightfall.
You can stay in the tavern until morning.
I'm sorry we don't have more to offer.
I hope your friend will make it
through the night.
I must get back to my watch.
Ha.
Ah. Not bad.
Not great, but not bad.
You have Kashu.
I haven't heard that. I prefer "style."
Your sword, you idiot.
Kashu.
It's one of the 50 Skillful Grade Swords.
You know, I never thought
to give it a name.
How about Walter?
It doesn't belong
in the hands of an assassin.
Oh.
Well, by all means, dear girl,
come and take it.
I think when I beat you,
I'll take your sword.
You will never touch that sword again.
Huh.
So…
…how did Baroque Works know
we were coming?
They didn't.
Communications room was trashed.
- They were looking for something.
- Like what?
Let's find out.
Luffy, we can't wait till morning.
What do you want to do, Luffy?
If we can't go around the mountain…
then we go straight up.
You want to climb it?
Nami can't make that.
None of us can make that.
Nami.
The only doctor here
lives on top of a mountain.
We're gonna have to climb it
to get to her.
I'll carry you on my back.
Are you okay with that?
It's going to be night soon.
It's impossible.
Death.
Certain and inevitable death.
I'm counting on you, Captain.
Leave everything to me.
Fine. I'm coming too.
Me too.
No, you've got to stay.
Vivi can't make the climb with her arm.
And Baroque Works is still out there
looking for us, so someone's gotta stay.
I'll stay too.
And get Zoro's back, just in case
the witch feeds you to the beast.
All right.
We'll come back after we save Nami.
Should hold.
My jacket should keep you extra warm.
Here we go.
What if this witch can't heal Nami?
We just have to believe.
I should have gone instead of the cook,
shouldn't I?
Sanji will be fine.
Are you even listening?
We should go up there now--
Zoro, do something else.
Like I'm doing something.
Stop asking questions
and hovering over me,
and do something
because this is not helping.
You could've asked nicely.
I'm gonna join Dalton on watch.
Good.
Now, Princess Vivi,
you were supposed to be
on your father's ship.
As far as he knows, I am.
Princess…
Igaram, I couldn't just stay
in my quarters. It's a reverie.
I wanted to see it with my own eyes.
Or at least hear it.
My father just gave
that King Wapol an earful--
Princess Vivi, you are next in line
for the throne of Alabasta.
But until that time, you are not permitted
to hear what happens inside that room.
No one is.
How am I supposed to learn how to lead
a kingdom if I'm stuck on a ship?
Hmm.
Perhaps I could arrange
for a tour of the grounds.
See how the World Government operations
work, and
I won't tell your father you snuck out.
As my royal guardian,
that seems like that would get you
in more trouble than me.
- You--
- Throw in ice cream and we have a deal.
Your first treaty.
I'm proud.
Now, stay here.
The audacity!
Does that fool
not know who he's dealing with?
A grave disrespect for sure, Your Majesty.
Out of my way, child!
Your Highness!
Oh my goodness!
You would dare strike
the Princess of Alabasta?
Oh no!
Oh, the Princess of Alabasta!
How unfortunate you are to be
the daughter of that worthless fool!
It's all right.
Sorry I bumped into you.
Let's go!
Get out of my way!
I'm sorry.
Your Highness,
you were magnificent today.
Never have I witnessed
such an act of bravery.
Princess Vivi, you averted
a great potential conflict.
Listen to me.
Watching you today,
I already know how you will lead Alabasta
when the time comes.
Come.
You're awful quiet over there.
I thought you weren't interested
in hearing worries.
Look, I'm nervous too.
But those guys will stop at nothing
to get Nami the help she needs.
It's not just about Nami.
This kingdom used to be prosperous.
They were on the cutting edge of medicine,
and now they have nothing.
All because of their king.
Vivi…
And… and Alabasta… I have been
away from home for so long.
How do I know
that things haven't gotten worse?
How do I know that what's happened here
hasn't happened to my home as well?
Vivi. You can't…
carry the weight of the world
on your shoulders alone.
You can't solve every problem by yourself.
I just…
I just want to do something.
I get it.
You could start
by handing me that wrench over there.
Look at that.
Doctor.
Luffy!
We're almost there!
Luffy…
Hold on, Nami.
Luffy!
Are you okay?
- No!
- Just get her to the top!
What a pretty castle.
Hey.
Save
my
friends.
Why is Baroque Works here?
Haven't you heard?
Our motto is mystery.
I have a motto too.
Tell me what I wanna know,
or I'll shove a baseball down your throat,
like I did your partner.
Go ahead.
I completed my mission.
My work here is done.
Sir, we need him alive.
We didn't get any information out of him.
Calm down.
He's just taking a nap.
Besides,
I think I know what they were after.
He won't talk.
But maybe this one will.
If we
can keep it alive long enough.
How is your friend?
Some of them took her
up the mountain to find the witch.
They couldn't wait until morning?
I don't know whether to marvel
at their perseverance
or shudder at their foolhardiness.
Yeah.
That's our captain.
Do you really think
this Blackbeard is coming back?
Hopefully, he's had his fill
and will not return.
But he isn't the only abomination
we're up against.
You're looking for your king. Wapol.
He is a cruel man
with an insatiable hunger.
And I know that he will try
to reclaim what once was his.
This… village…
is finally beginning
to recover from his reign.
And I hope we can build something new.
A peaceful nation.
And who's gonna lead this nation?
You?
No, I'm not.
My aim is not to lead these people.
Only to be a shield for them.
You don't always get a choice.
I'm more of a sword guy myself.
I could lend you mine,
should the need arise.
You're all right.
Hello?
Are you
hiding?
Of course! That's why you can't see me.
- You're peeking the wrong way.
- Shut up!
Are you… feeling better?
A little bit, yeah.
Are you the one
that's been taking care of me?
That'd be me.
I'm Kureha.
You can call me Doctorine.
And lucky for you, I am the last
and greatest physician on Drum Island.
Hmm.
100.76.
Fever's gone down a smidge, which means…
The antibodies are working!
Correct. Treatment's not over yet.
Patient still needs?
Further rounds of antibiotics
and more bed rest.
Hmm. Right again.
No, really, I'm feeling much better.
Thank you so much for your help,
but I need to get…
Only two ways
a patient leaves my care, girly.
Fully recovered or dead.
You're not going anywhere.
You need to rest. Doctorine says
you were bitten by a Kestia.
That's right.
Nasty little buggers.
An infectious tick whose bite
infects the victim with virulent bacteria.
Fever never goes below 104,
which eventually ravages the victim.
We are talking super infection.
Myocarditis. Arteritis. Encephalitis.
I get it. It's bad.
Kind of impressed
you managed to get bit by such a thing.
- Kestia are supposed to be long extinct.
- Mm-hmm.
So unless you were traipsing
through some steamy prehistoric jungle
with your skin exposed--
I was.
You're a strange one.
What about my friends?
A couple of cracked ribs on that one.
And…
and Luffy?
Guys! Guys!
A huge beast dragged us into this castle!
Then this old witch tried to cook me
in a soup and eat me!
Luffy, why are you yelling?
Sanji, we're about to be eaten!
We are not about to be eaten,
and she's not a witch.
I think.
- Nami?
- Nami, you're okay!
Nami, you're fine.
Are you better now?
You're all better now.
I gave her antibiotics.
I reset his ribs.
I put you in warm water
to prevent hypothermia.
Oh.
Okay.
Thanks, Grandma.
I'll bill you later.
And like she said, I'm not a witch.
I'm not old either.
I'll have you know,
I am not a day over 139.
Seriously?
Wow.
You're really old.
Okay, but, Nami, can I get you anything?
Actually, I could eat.
I feel like I haven't eaten in days.
- Because you haven't.
- Me too!
You have.
I'm a doctor, not a chef.
Lucky for you, I am.
Chopper, show him where the kitchen is.
Yes, Doctorine.
What are you?
What is that?!