=Pavilion Secrets=
(Adapted from "Pavilion Secrets"
by Huang Fanfan and Ji Wuyun)
=Episode 25=
Commander Zhou's letter?
He said there are
many injured soldiers in the army.
He'll meet me once he's settled them.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't protect
the soldiers completely.
Shen Lan is perceptive.
If there were no casualties in the army,
he would definitely become suspicious.
Then all our efforts would be in vain.
By the way,
how is he?
He suffered some superficial injuries.
To earn this glory,
he risked his life.
Rest assured?
General, it's me.
Come in.
General,
all the spies have been identified.
What should we do with them?
It's not the time to deal with them yet.
Just monitor the information
they're spreading.
Yes.
Let's not talk about that.
Madam Meng,
prepare a few appetizers in the kitchen.
These past few days,
you've barely eaten or drunk.
You need to eat on time.
I...
I have to go out with Madam Meng today.
I won't be eating at home.
Let's go.
You must have prayed for me, right?
As long as you're safe.
I knew it!
You're just harsh with your words.
When the knife flashed before my eyes,
do you know what I was thinking?
Don't say it anymore.
I was thinking
why I didn't hug you back then.
Stop it!
I was also thinking
if I survive this,
I'll definitely hug you tightly.
Look.
Shen Lan,
what do you really want?
I want to be with you,
as a proper husband and wife.
Please, I beg you.
Stop this, okay?
Liu Su.
Master.
What's this?
Letters from General.
So many.
What's General been busy with lately?
She doesn't allow me to say.
(Wang Long. Guo Yun. Du Haochuan.)
By the names, they should
all be from the Yun Family Army.
They're brothers
who've been through
thick and thin together.
It's only natural for her to miss them.
But,
for several days in a row,
she hasn't come to eat.
Are there so many injured soldiers?
And if there are injured soldiers,
she should visit them.
Why is she communicating
through letters?
Well,
why are you here?
What?
Not welcome?
No.
I'm just not feeling well,
so I want to rest early.
You don't like being kept in the dark,
but you're keeping secrets from me.
That's not fair, is it?
No.
Can I tell you about it later?
Okay.
Then you...
Can you explain this?
You read it?
No, I didn't read it.
I told you,
you're still you.
If you want to
visit the Yun Family Army,
you should go.
Why do you communicate like this?
I won't restrict you.
I know.
Then why do you still...
I just wanted to...
I just wanted to give you a gift!
That you're alive
is already the greatest gift
heaven has given me.
I don't want anything else.
Why not?
I don't need it.
You!
I want to use the armor plates
of the soldiers
to make you a suit of armor.
You said that you regretted
not protecting me.
You felt guilty.
But I just want to tell you
that I've been doing well these years.
The soldiers ate, slept,
and fought alongside me.
When you weren't here,
they fought by my side.
I wasn't alone.
You don't need
to feel guilty about the past.
Now I can protect myself.
And I can protect you too.
So...
But you don't want it.
Forget about it!
Who let you in?
I was wrong.
It's my fault.
I shouldn't have been
so presumptuous with the gift.
That's not true.
I'm sorry.
You made this?
It's a pity.
My sewing skills
aren't as good as yours.
Teach me, please.
Didn't you say you didn't want it?
Who said that?
I want it.
If you don't give it to me,
I won't leave.
Thank you.
I like this gift
a lot.
Your Highness, it's confirmed.
Song Huanbei
is the deposed Crown Prince, Shen Mo.
Now it all makes sense.
It's hard for him to gain my trust
by giving such a big gift
to the Yun Family Army.
Before, he wanted to join you,
probably to find out some secrets.
Should we eliminate him?
No.
He has a big use for us.
But if his identity...
I want it to be known!
Let the entire court hear
that the deposed Crown Prince
has returned.
Yes.
There's a needle sewn into this belt.
In case of need,
it can defend against enemies.
Don't worry.
When entering the court,
they'll search everyone,
so it's useless.
But what if?
Recently, rumors have been spreading
that you're the Crown Prince.
The deposed Crown Prince.
Is that the point?
These rumors
are obviously Shen Lan's doing.
He's always been determined
to ascend the throne.
And now, suddenly, there's another you.
I'm worried he might take action.
I'm not completely unprepared.
You have a plan?
Yes.
What plan?
You.
If anything happens to me,
you'll lead the Army to rescue me.
Stop joking.
Don't worry.
I'm going.
His Highness was delayed,
so you may proceed
to see His Majesty first.
Do I need to remove my armor?
No need.
(Wait a little longer.)
(In a few days,)
(you'll be my rightful wife.)
His Majesty...
You killed His Majesty.
You've killed two birds
with one stone, huh?
Guards!
Yes!
Song Huanbei
assassinated the Emperor.
Arrest him!
♪People easily drift apart,
and dreams easily shattered♪
♪Yet for you, I take it all in stride♪
♪Through wind and rain, mountains high,
and roads far♪
♪My feelings are like
a returning swallow♪
♪Twists and turns,
a thousand lives lived♪
♪Searching along the way,
and fearing loss and confusion♪
♪Only for the sake of lifelong
longing not too far♪
♪Awaiting your fulfillment♪
♪My green robes rustling♪
♪Your fleeting beauty,
graceful as a swan♪
♪Parting is difficult
to see or to leave♪
♪Lingering in this mortal world♪
♪Your fleeting glance back♪
♪Sets my heart's balance askew♪
♪Endless nights, lingering♪
♪Past days, countless and vast♪
♪The red thread entwined,
fate already sealed♪
♪Each at an end,
winding past distant mountains♪
♪Meeting again, brushing
away the snow of youth's hair♪
♪Only beauty remains♪
♪As the years pass,
what can we do against heaven's will?♪
♪Even with myriad charms,
looking back with lowered gaze♪
♪Waiting for you to unravel
my tangled worries and disheveled hair♪
♪Endless nights, lingering♪
♪Past days, countless and vast♪
♪The red thread entwined,
fate already sealed♪
♪Each at an end,
winding past distant mountains♪
♪Meeting again, brushing
away the snow of youth's hair♪
♪Only beauty remains♪