=Pavilion Secrets=
(Adapted from "Pavilion Secrets"
by Huang Fanfan and Ji Wuyun)
=Episode 20=
Congratulations, Master Song.
Happy wedding day!
General,
His Majesty has secretly
arranged your marriage to him.
Arranged marriage?
From now on,
you are my fiancée.
Master,
even though it's a new marriage,
you just got out of prison,
don't overindulge.
Are you tired?
Someone's there.
Why are you afraid?
We're truly married.
What are you talking about?
If they want to watch, let them watch.
Are you exhausted?
I prepared some appetizers for you.
Eat some too.
I need to hurry up,
and practice my swordplay.
It's almost evening.
It's time to rest.
I'm just an ordinary civilian now.
I need to find a way to make a living.
Or else,
I can't just sit here,
spending all my money.
As the head of the Thousand
Machines Pavilion, I can't support you?
Madam Meng said,
men can't be relied on.
That's right, but as your
senior brother, I'm your family.
My shoulder will always
be there for you to lean on.
Sometimes,
I also want to be your support.
General,
Imperial Consort Yun
sent something over.
What is it?
Send it back!
Tell her I don't want it.
Imperial Consort Yun said
you could refuse everything else,
but there's one thing you must accept.
(General's Mansion)
To celebrate General's new marriage,
Imperial Consort Yun has sent a gift.
I'm no longer a general.
Take it back.
She already anticipated
that you would say so.
Her Highness said
please accept this sachet.
She said,
she doesn't want you to hurt yourself
because you hate her.
(I don't need it anymore.)
Mo...
It hurts.
Let me go!
If you get rid of it,
you can live peacefully.
Let me go!
Yun Shu, behave yourself.
Actually, the reason you
were pardoned this time
was because Imperial Consort Yun knelt
before His Majesty for days and nights.
Imperial Consort Yun
didn't let them tell you.
Tomorrow,
go visit her.
(The Ancestral Tablet
of the Eldest Sister Yun Yin)
Auntie.
It can't be Shu'er.
Shu'er,
it's really you!
♪The mountain breeze, like smoke,
brings a chill to this setting sun♪
♪Your poetry, I cherish deep
within the winter's embrace♪
♪A pot of brew
holds memories that never fade♪
♪Tender raindrops mirror my thoughts
that linger and stray♪
♪A solitary sail gazes out
upon the spring river's flow♪
♪Even the flowers and the moon
seem to grieve♪
♪Your smiling face, slowly fading away♪
♪I can't forget♪
♪That arched bridge, curving gracefully♪
♪My window, permeated
with thoughts of you♪
♪This hometown♪
♪Where only moonlight still
sways and dances in the night♪
♪I've walked through ten miles
of crabapples♪
♪Watching the wind turn them gold♪
♪The verdant grass withers,
and the setting sun defeated♪
♪Waiting for you is my arrogance♪
♪Counting the endless roads
that stretch to the horizon's edge♪
♪I turn back
from ten miles of crabapples♪
♪A tale of sorrow♪
♪The west wind blows,
but no wild goose returns♪
♪Another year passes,
filled with melancholy♪
♪You're not far away♪