=Pavilion Secrets=
(Adapted from "Pavilion Secrets"
by Huang Fanfan and Ji Wuyun)
=Episode 21=
It can't be Shu'er.
Auntie.
Shu'er,
it's really you!
Auntie,
what's wrong with your head...?
I'm fine.
Are you okay?
Does Song Huanbei
treat you well?
Well,
he treats me extremely well.
Has Shen Lan caused you any trouble?
No.
After all, I'm his mother.
He wouldn't dare do anything to me.
Auntie...
You pleaded for me in the throne room.
I...
Silly girl.
Family members shouldn't be
so formal with each other.
My sister's death was because of me.
You're not wrong about that.
Back then,
when I learned
that Eunuch Zhang and Wang Kui
were coming to capture the Mo family,
I secretly met with them.
No need to care
about the rest of the Mo family.
Just rescue Yun Yin and Yun Shu for me.
I'll ensure you live a comfortable life
for the rest of your days.
Your Highness,
Yun Yin and Yun Shu
are both on our wanted list.
If we're missing two people...
Well...
We can't report back without them.
I've already considered that for you.
First, bring them
to the entrance of the valley.
I'll meet you there.
Then set fire to the mountain.
Destroy the evidence.
Naturally, no one will suspect you.
These deeds to the city properties
are just a down payment.
After the job is done,
there will be a generous reward.
But what I didn't expect was...
They took the money
but didn't do the job.
I waited and waited
at the entrance of the valley,
but neither you nor my sister showed up.
So I led my troops in.
Shu'er,
you know
what happened next.
(I'm guilty.)
(If I hadn't been so "clever",)
(my sister might still be alive.)
(Auntie,)
(don't be too hard on yourself.)
(It was a death trap that the Mo family)
(was framed back then.)
(No one could have saved my mother.)
(General's Mansion)
What?
You want to behave like a lady?
Aren't you already a lady?
Look at me.
Do I look like one?
When Huanbei and I are together,
we're look like homosexuality.
Did he really say that?
No.
I said it myself.
You don't look much like one.
Just teach me the basics
of walking, sitting
and standing.
(Getting married)
(can really change
a person's personality?)
Walk a few steps.
No lady walks like that.
Let me show you.
Walk a few steps
with this vase.
Walk.
If you drop this again,
you won't get dinner tonight.
Although my father
released Song Huanbei,
he's recently been intending
to let me oversee the country.
Right now,
the imperial edict is on its way.
Your Highness, you should be cautious.
I think,
His Majesty's move is somewhat unusual.
The throne
will be mine sooner or later.
Song Huanbei,
you're not even worthy to fight me.
♪People easily drift apart,
and dreams easily shattered♪
♪Yet for you, I take it all in stride♪
♪Through wind and rain, mountains high,
and roads far♪
♪My feelings are like
a returning swallow♪
♪Twists and turns,
a thousand lives lived♪
♪Searching along the way,
and fearing loss and confusion♪
♪Only for the sake of lifelong
longing not too far♪
♪Awaiting your fulfillment♪
♪My green robes rustling♪
♪Your fleeting beauty,
graceful as a swan♪
♪Parting is difficult
to see or to leave♪
♪Lingering in this mortal world♪
♪Your fleeting glance back♪
♪Sets my heart's balance askew♪
♪Endless nights, lingering♪
♪Past days, countless and vast♪
♪The red thread entwined,
fate already sealed♪
♪Each at an end,
winding past distant mountains♪
♪Meeting again, brushing
away the snow of youth's hair♪
♪Only beauty remains♪
♪As the years pass,
what can we do against heaven's will?♪
♪Even with myriad charms,
looking back with lowered gaze♪
♪Waiting for you to unravel
my tangled worries and disheveled hair♪
♪Endless nights, lingering♪
♪Past days, countless and vast♪
♪The red thread entwined,
fate already sealed♪
♪Each at an end,
winding past distant mountains♪
♪Meeting again, brushing
away the snow of youth's hair♪
♪Only beauty remains♪