♪I'm just a common man
under the sky♪
♪Among all living beings,
they speak of my recklessness♪
♪Above the sky, my heart yearns♪
♪The light that these hands cannot hide♪
♪The justice gavel strikes
and releases countless burdens♪
♪Looking back, it's the same old story♪
♪Time and space brought me
to another yellowed page♪
♪Curious about the greed in the world♪
♪I tore the sky's curtain apart♪
♪The powerful words♪
♪Spilled this golden soup♪
♪It is not very firm♪
♪Standing here♪
♪I set the rules that shackle me♪
♪Learn to cure♪
♪Eradicating the diseases of this land♪
♪I am just a common man♪
♪I wanted to take things step by step♪
♪Never want to be a confused fool♪
♪I am just a common man♪
♪Listening to the songs without dispute♪
♪Yet I always see the lonely souls♪
♪But I always rush ahead♪
♪Leaving my scribbles behind
for future generations to study♪
♪The light that these hands cannot hide♪
♪The justice gavel strikes
and releases countless burdens♪
♪Looking back, it's the same old story♪
♪Time and space brought me
to another yellowed page♪
♪Sunlight pierces through♪
♪One comes and goes as one pleases♪
♪My Go board holds both sides♪
♪When I set the game, learn to see♪
♪Don't be a sore loser♪
♪So many lies and deceits♪
♪I can see through every play♪
♪May I live and die
with the sun♪
=Guardians of the Dafeng=
=Episode 28=
It must've cost you a lot of money.
(As expected.)
(My future father-in-law is a Fighter
obsessed with martial arts.)
(He shouldn't be hard
to get along with.)
A hero deserves a treasured saber.
How can it be measured by money?
Thank you, Miss.
Why?
You lied to me!
Xu Qi'an, I won't trust you ever again!
Get out! Out!
Leave me alone!
I can't stay here anymore!
Not anymore!
My family betrayed me!
Get out!
Out!
What a nice saber!
You must be Miss Xu Lingyue.
Your brother is right.
You're gorgeous
and elegant.
You're flattering me, Simu.
After thinking,
I believe this is perfect for you.
Isn't it
the Whitening Cream from the Beauty Shop?
It brightens and nourishes
the skin fantastically.
Ms. Li gave me a jar.
It was really good.
I waited in line for days
but failed to get another one.
Miss Simu,
it's so sweet of you.
I pulled some strings to get it.
That's fine.
Such cream is designed for beauties like her.
I'll try it for you.
Thanks. It's so thoughtful of you.
(Unlike her mother, Miss Xu)
(seems more sophisticated.)
(That's good.)
(I can't wait to know more about her.)
Actually,
I have another gift for you.
Does it smell good?
This is the latest book of poems.
(Elegant Poems)
You may read it.
(Top Men of the Dafeng 101)
Thanks, Simu.
Who's this curious little girl?
I stopped by the Moon Resto on my way here
and picked up goodies for you.
Moon Resto!
Little one, thank Miss Wang first.
Thank you, Miss Pretty.
Eat up.
I came in haste, underprepared.
I apologize for the humble gifts.
No, no, no. They're too nice!
You're wonderful...
You must be thirsty coming all the way here.
I'm sorry for our humble abode
and poor treat.
- Please bear with it.
- Yes.
No, it's great.
You have
a beautiful house of class.
After seeing you,
I realized why Xinnian turned out talented,
kind, and pure.
That's also true.
Other things aside,
my son, Cijiu, has been
studying hard for 18 years.
He is a talent.
Once he passes the Spring Exam,
his... his future
will be limitless.
Xu Cijiu,
your 18 years of handwork are futile.
Your future
is ruined.
Now, you're a joke in the scholar circles.
How foolish!
How stupid!
Why did I believe a liar?
Or I wouldn't have ended up like this!
If fate hadn't let Xu Xinnian
be born...
Xu Qi'an, say something to comfort me.
Cijiu,
let it go.
Have some hot water.
Hot water?
How foolish!
How stupid!
You're a fool, Xu Xinnian!
Sorry,
Xinnian was humiliated earlier
because of me.
Don't blame yourself, Miss.
Cijiu's always been obedient,
well-behaved,
and calm.
He'd never cross the line
or cause others trouble.
- Right?
- Yes, that's true.
Are you sure he's fine?
Of course!
- Don't worry.
- He's fine.
No need to worry!
Don't worry!
Alright then.
If fate hadn't let Xu Xinnian
be born,
the Dafeng would still be
in the dark!
Cijiu,
enough is enough.
I'm tired. I need to sleep.
Are you hanging yourself for real?
Alright. Never mind.
I'm sorry. Get down now!
Leave me alone!
You can't die! Get down!
Let me die!
- Knock it off!
- Leave me alone!
Stop!
- Let me die!
- I'm sorry...
Xinnian is in his room.
(Bright and Sunny)
Xinnian!
Don't kill yourself, Xinnian...!
He's studying at this time.
Let's not interrupt him.
Come on.
Miss Simu came all the way here.
So what if he's studying?
He can continue later.
Is there dust in your eyes?
- Xin...
- Let me die!
He's been studious since childhood.
Yes, that's right.
"It's never too early to learn."
It's better to
let him focus on his study.
Yes, she's right.
I'd like to have a word with him.
What do you think
about this poem?
This line is beautiful.
Hello.
What's up?
- Nothing.
Xinnian is busy with his study.
Let's not
disturb him.
Sure.
Hold on.
I apologize for my father
for what happened earlier.
But I believe
with your talent,
one day,
you'll enter the Cabinet
and become a minister.
You'll go up in the world
and achieve your goals.
I see you're studying.
I won't disturb you.
I'll
come again another day.
Sure. No problem.
(Xinnian,)
(I'm sure)
(that after this,)
(you'll fall for me.)
♪Flowers in the yard♪
♪Bloom and wither♪
♪Time goes by♪
♪The wind blows through hair under the eave♪
Coward.
♪Where is the one taking a break from♪
♪Stars are outside the window♪
What is
this stone for?
"My heart is like a stone.
It can't be moved around."
♪Words said every day♪
I'm going to bed.
Your Highness,
how did it go?
Yang Youde said Father was working
and told me to go back.
As the ruler of the state,
he's always busy
with state affairs.
Father is mad at me
and avoiding me.
I just heard a joke from others.
Would you like to hear it for fun?
Got kicked out of the Personnel?
Yes. Many people saw it.
They said Xu Xinnian
covered his belly like a dead fish
and couldn't move for a long while.
How strange!
Xu Qi'an is gallant and smart.
How come his brother is so simple-minded?
How dare he, a student,
go to provoke
the Prime Minister who'll decide his career!
Your Highness,
you probably don't know
that he seems to admire
Prime Minister Wang's daughter.
That's why the Prime Minister fumed.
Xu Xinnian is
a top student at the Yunlu Academy.
He's young and talented.
Why was Wang Zhenwen mad?
So what if he's a top student?
There are plenty of them in the state.
Xu Xinnian is
of humble birth
without an official post or title.
He might be talented,
but
compared with Miss Wang,
he's a worthless nobody.
Is one's family background
really that important?
Of course.
People should be matched
for marriage in our state.
Miss Wang is the Prime Minister's daughter,
while Xu Xinnian is
a humble civilian.
Other than him,
even Mr. Xu, who's made great contributions,
doesn't deserve her.
Your Highness!
Your Highness, I didn't mean that.
I'm saying he's smart and resourceful.
He's more than qualified
to be her match.
Your Highness...!
I've never had anything so flavorful.
Was it made by a new Imperial Chef?
No.
It was seasoned
with chicken powder
to bring out the umami of the ingredients.
Besides,
the one who made such powder is...
Xu Qi'an?
Yes.
Mother,
he owns unmatched talent.
He can write poems
and solve cases.
He was in charge of retrieving tax silver
in Yunzhou.
Such a rare talent
is also my guest advisor.
Shouldn't you
reward him, Mother?
I know what you're thinking.
I'll advise your father to grant him
a title of nobility when the time's right.
Your father is
aware of his contributions.
He hasn't granted him a title
because he must've had other plans.
That's not up to us.
I'd appreciate it
if you'd put in a good word.
Thank you, Mother.
Let's eat.
Eat up.
(Xu Mansion)
What are these?
Wang Zhenwen was impeached by his rivals.
Lord Wei asked you
to send those letters
to the Personnel.
What...?
(Yao Lin of Revenue embezzled
thousands of liang of gold.)
If such scandals were...
I mean if such secret letters were leaked,
who knows how many officials
in town would be found guilty?
Looks like the official circles
will undergo great changes.
Few have access to such secret letters.
They wouldn't be leaked.
Hadn't Lord Wei given the order,
do you think
you'd be allowed to read them?
Will the Guardians help Prime Minister Wang?
This is important.
It's also a power struggle.
Why did Lord Wei choose me?
He said
it'd only be convincing if you sent them.
Here's the thing.
Everyone in the capital knows
Xu Xinnian was kicked out
of the Personnel for Wang Simu.
As his brother, you stood up
to bring them together.
You sneaked into the Guardians' archive
to steal the letters
and gave them to Wang Zhenwen
in order to
patch things up with him.
What a brilliant story Lord Wei made.
He should've been a scriptwriter.
Scriptwriter?
It's urgent.
I'm on it now.
Wait.
Are you going over like this?
Do you think it's easy
to sneak into the archive?
Hey,
what are you doing?
I knew it.
You'd fall into my hands someday.
What...?
How's he?
You didn't break him, did you?
No.
He dodged my whip.
He said he had a better story
to get it done more easily.
It goes like this.
You, Xu Xinnian, were kicked out
of the Cabinet because of Wang Simu.
In order to win over that girl,
you sneaked into your brother's room
to steal the letters
and gave them to Wang Zhenwen
to patch things up with him.
Remember,
let Miss Wang pass the letters.
That'll work better.
What a brilliant story you made.
If that's the case,
I'm on it now.
Hold on.
Are you going over like this?
- What...?
- Do you think it's easy
to steal the letters from your brother?
You're meticulous.
Choose one.
Which one
causes no pain?
No one.
The more the pain, the more the gain.
The more the pain,
the more the affection.
Relax.
I can control my strength.
I won't break your veins or bones.
This one it is.
It looks small.
Sure.
Good choice.
One strike will
leave six holes in you.
No.
They won't heal quickly.
This one.
It's not too sharp,
and it won't leave holes.
That's better.
It'll make your face swell.
No.
Simu is attracted
to my good looks the most.
Use this one then.
It's bigger,
but I can't take it. Just don't hit my face.
The hammer is the best!
One strike is enough.
It'll break your head and cause bleeding.
No, no, no!
Scholars can't be brain-damaged.
Use this one instead.
I won't make soup with it for Mother tonight.
We aren't poor.
We don't need it.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
- No second thoughts?
- No.
Let's do it.
Here I come!
Look, Miss.
Take this. Go ahead.
Xinnian.
Simu.
What happened to you?
Nothing.
I asked you out tonight
to bring something to you.
Please pass them to your father.
(Censor Yuan's relative
stole others' properties.)
(Yao Lin embezzled...)
These...
(Duke Cao took bribes.)
Where did you
get such secret letters?
I took them from my brother.
Your brother?
Isn't he Lord Wei's right-hand man?
Xinnian,
you...
Let me see.
Did he beat you up?
He didn't beat me.
I hit...
I fell.
Tripped and fell.
Does it hurt?
Not at all.
Simu...
Xinnian...
It hurts if you keep pressing it.
Sorry, Xinnian.
I went to the Judicial Review
and Censorate earlier
to make them drop the charges,
but
State Duke Cao got there first.
Minister Sun,
I contacted Crown Prince's other supporters.
After hearing the news,
they avoided me like the plague.
Prime Minister Wang,
how about we yield to His Majesty
on the delivery corvee?
That corvee does more harm than good!
I could yield,
but the people would suffer.
The worst situation is
I'll retire.
No, you can't, Prime Minister!
You cannot do that, Prime Minister!
Don't do that.
If you retire,
you'll play right into Duke Cao's hand.
It's not bad to step down now.
Quitting at the peak of my career is
better than ending up dishonorable.
Besides,
I can make a comeback later.
Gentlemen
should know when to quit to avoid harm.
But officials should be remonstrative!
As the Prime Minister,
if I didn't say it, no one else could.
Father,
I need to talk to you.
Miss Simu is
cultured and courteous.
It must be important,
or she wouldn't interrupt us.
Come in.
What is it?
These things
in my hand
can help Father and the rest of you out.
(Duke Cao took bribes.)
(Trod on a five-year-old child.)
With these letters,
we have a chance to turn things around.
Who gave you these letters?
The one who you kicked out of the Personnel.
He didn't hold a grudge
but paid a huge price to obtain
and send over these letters.
His brother is
Guardian Xu Qi'an.
(Self-disciplined and Pure)
She's grown up.
Yes.
When I saw her years back,
she was a little girl.
Thank you for remembering my daughter.
- Your Majesty...
- I heard
your wife was sick and bedridden.
She was feeling a bit unwell.
Thanks for your concern.
- Youde.
- Yes.
Have someone
send a Golden Pill from the Treasure Sect
to Prime Minister Wang's mansion.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, I...
Well,
let's chat another day.
Yes.
(Duke Cao...)
Walk him out.
Yes.
(Overreached himself by stealing
national funds and tributes.)
Your Majesty,
I'll take my leave.
This morning, in court,
His Majesty changed his mind.
He rejected Prime Minister Wang's resignation
and exonerated him.
My guess is
those secret letters
are about State Duke Cao.
He's Father's trusted follower
who's never joined any parties.
He only takes orders from Father,
so he's remained powerful all these years.
This time,
Wang Zhenwen must've found dirt on him,
forcing Father to compromise.
Whether the impeachment against Wang
is serious or not,
Father is sharp enough to tell.
That was to make an example of Wang
to warn others.
Prime Minister Wang
turned the tide overnight.
That was unexpected, though.
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty,
Wang Zhenwen...
How did he acquire those secret letters?
Wei Yuan.
Yes.
It must be him.
Youde.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I'm tired.
Help me to rest.
- Yes.
- Your Majesty,
Wei Yuan is colluding with court officials.
We must stop him.
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
Mind your own business.
Had Lord Wei interfered,
His Majesty wouldn't have done nothing.
Father knows him too well.
Lord Wei cares about the people.
His goal
isn't to rise in court.
His ambition
isn't to gain power.
I didn't believe the Guardians
could supervise officials.
Turns out, your people are really good.
We're simply serving the court.
Why did the Guardians
help me?
Grains are eight wen per jin.
(Grains are eight wen per jin.)
Brown rice, 12 wen per jin.
Rice, 18 wen per jin.
At this time two years ago,
paddy rice was only four wen per jin.
Brown rice was six wen per jin.
Lord Wei,
if you want to talk about prices,
go to my place.
We can discuss them all night.
This year,
prices have shockingly doubled.
The past few years have been eventful.
With war in the North
and droughts in the South,
the Treasury has almost been emptied.
Despite huge pressure from the Palace,
I didn't raise this year's farm tax.
But that didn't change anything.
In times of peace,
prices are low.
In times of chaos,
farmland is abandoned.
Roads are blocked.
Prices rise.
As powerful officials,
we're concerned about the people,
but
we can't imagine how hard their lives are.
There are people struggling in poverty
in the capital.
In this world,
how many civilians
would be ground like rice
but
suffer in silence?
You're benevolent and selfless.
I was narrow-minded.
Prime Minister Wang.
After you, Lord Wei.
I helped you
because I saw
that facing overwhelming pressure
and His Majesty's wrath,
you held on to your principles
and spoke for the people.
That's why
I'm entrusting this huge task to you.
Lord Wei,
what is it?
The Witcher's Sect is rampant in the North,
slaughtering civilians.
I'll
petition His Majesty
to attack that sect soon.
Then
I can only rely on you
to safeguard the court
and the Dafeng.
(...the people.)
Looking up,
one can face the heavens.
Look down,
one won't disappoint the people.
Sir,
Silver Gong Guardian,
Xu Qi'an, came to see you.
(Personnel)
Without permission,
the Guardians can't enter the Personnel.
You should leave.
Hold on.
I'm Xu Qi'an,
Xu Xinnian's elder brother
- Greetings.
- and a Silver Gong Guardian.
Silver Gong!
Lord Wei sent me here for investigation.
You... Did I not make myself clear?
I'll say it again.
The Personnel is off-limits.
Without His Majesty's edict, the Guardians
aren't allowed in.
Please leave.
Sir,
do us a favor
and let us in.
Do you a favor?
Alright.
Fine. Close the gate.
Hey...
My hand...
- Never mind.
- Let me go!
I have other plans.
You're too slow.
I've waited for a while.
It occurred to me
that I shouldn't have worn my uniform
to work with a civilian.
It wouldn't be of help.
What's Wang Zhenwen doing?
A drop in need shall be returned
with a spring in deed, no?
Look at that petty official.
As low-ranking as he is,
he's so bureaucratic.
By the way,
why did you stop me just now?
Had you let me go,
I would've turned that place upside down!
Calm down.
I've sent a message
to ask Miss Wang for help.
Really?
Fine.
I'm off.
Where are you going?
Let's talk.
About what?
If I need you, I'll send Su Su over.
Have you paid?
Sir,
put it on my tab.
Sure.
Hey, little boy.
Give me my pouch.
Your pouch? Can you prove it?
Finders keepers.
A gold sunflower seed is in it
with the character "Zhi".
Open it and look.
Give it back!
- Give it to me.
- What are you doing?
- Picking a fight?
- It's mine.
- Do you know me?
- Give it
- Don't push me.
- back.
- It's my pouch.
- It's not yours.
It's mine.
It's my pouch.
(Mu Nanzhi)
How did you know a gold sunflower seed
was in it with the character "Zhi"?
It's my pouch.
Of course I know.
Your pouch?
There's a character "Zhi",
but it's not on a gold sunflower seed.
(Pig.)
(It says "Pig".)
I knew it.
No wonder I was so unlucky
that I lost a pouch every time I hung out.
So all those pouches
were taken by you, pig!
(Looks like)
(she's that unlucky victim.)
Miss, he stole your pouch.
- I saw everything.
- Really?
You have to believe me.
He even beat me.
You little liar!
What's wrong?
Whose pouch is it?
I get it.
You two are
setting me up
in public in broad daylight.
You're partners in fraud, right?
Let's go to the authorities.
Are you coming?
No.
- Yes or no?
- I didn't say anything.
I saw nothing.
Stop it.
Your partner ran away.
Will you go with me?
I...
I... I'll let it slide this time.
But next time,
I'll make you pay!
I made it.
Here you go, 600 liang.
Thanks.
(Looking up, one can face the heavens...)
Your writing has further improved, Father.
It can literally be seen from the back.
How powerful.
You wrote,
"Looking up, one can face the heavens.
Looking down,
one won't disappoint the people."
But that's not how you've been acting lately.
What do you mean?
What's your point?
Let me be clear.
If you're here for that Guardian Xu,
don't bother
to say it.
Why?
Do you feel guilty?
Father,
you know
you owe the Xu Family.
If you keep avoiding them,
can you face the heavens?
Won't you disappoint them?
The Xu brothers
are in cahoots.
Mu,
you're a clever girl.
You weren't fooled
by their ruse of self-injury, were you?
You're right, Father.
I saw through
Xinnian's silly trick,
but I also saw
he went this far for me.
He was sincere.
Although he played a trick,
he made me happy.
I wouldn't mind.
Besides, he did so
to change your opinion on him.
To change my opinion,
he has to pass the Spring Exam first.
That won't happen soon.
Father, you haven't told me
why you refuse to help the Xu Family.
If you're so ungrateful,
won't others look down on the Wang Family?
The Personnel is off-limits.
Ever since I became
the Vice Minister there 14 years ago,
not one Guardian has been
allowed in the archive.
No exceptions since the Dafeng was founded.
Well,
they don't
have to go inside.
Y-Y-You...
Some chicken soup you made.
Alright, I'm full.
Take this.
This Healing Powder is fantastic
and extremely rare.
Father,
who is it for?
Your injured admirer, Xu.
Mr. Chu.
I'm late. My apologies.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
How did it go?
Don't get me started.
A geezer fooled us.
Good liquor!
This 30-year-old liquor
tastes rich and strong.
Let's set aside the troubles.
Why not
indulge in drinks?
- Cheers!
Here we go.
Ouch!
Bear with it.
Easy!
Just stop.
It's nothing serious.
I'm fine.
Nothing serious?
I only hit you once.
How come you were badly injured?
Who left all those scratches?
I hit myself a few more times.
But I was badly injured for nothing.
We didn't get to see Prime Minister Wang.
I made a bad plan.
Let me put more powder on you.
Don't bother.
I realized something yesterday.
With Prime Minister Wang's experience,
he must've seen through
our silly trick instantly.
I should go back to study.
That's the right path.
No need to be in a rush.
I am!
All those means of trickery you taught me
would only backfire.
Who knows when I can see Simu again?
Right now,
only if I pass the Spring Exam
and gain an official rank
will I be able to see her again.
Fine. Alright.
You should leave, Ningyan.
I don't want to see you again.
Wait, Cijiu,
I can explain it.
- Go away!
- Or I can spin it.
- Ningyan, Xinnian.
- No.
There you are.
I'm here to tell you
that Miss Wang came.
Mother is with her now.
Which Miss Wang?
Who else could it be?
Cijiu wrote all these
when he was a child.
(Idle fathers raise spoiled children.)
Look, frogs.
(Lazy teachers make wild students.)
His cursive style looks free and easy.
Even the characters he wrote in childhood
look adorable.
Yes, they are.
So adorable.
There's more.
Check this out.
At Cijiu's 100-day birthday,
we hired an artist to draw our family.
You're as young and beautiful
as before, Mrs. Xu.
Yes.
Look.
Cijiu was crying.
I was so worried. I didn't know why
until later.
You know why he cried?
He wet his pants!
Stop looking at it!
Xinnian.
Miss Wang.
Why are you so nervous?
She's our guest.
There's my sister-in-law.
- When did you come?
- Don't say that!
It's rude.
How offensive.
Here I am.
You know what?
Just now, he feared
he couldn't see you again
and decided to study even harder.
And now, there you are.
He's all shy and timid.
Xu Cijiu,
do scholars like you never mean what you say?
Don't listen to them.
Did they lie?
Not exactly.
Ningyan,
can we have a word
in private?
Sure.
My father said
the archive is off-limits.
Outsiders can't get in without permission.
But the rainy season has come.
It's humid.
All those files in the archive
can't get wet or moldy.
All of them
will be moved to the backyard
to be dried.
I've made arrangements.
My carriage will take you to the backyard.
Someone will wait for you there.
Thank you for your assistance.
You're a lucky man, Xinnian.
Xinnian,
let me check your face.
It's fine.
"It's fine."
Ningyan,
don't you have things to attend to?
Go ahead. Hurry up.
Yes, sure.
I'm going.
Aunt,
did you wash my Guardian uniform?
Where did you put it? I need it.
- I have to go.
- Help me find it.
How many times have I said
it was made of silver
and not washable?
Why did you wash it?
They've left.
(Xu Mansion)
Ningyan,
let me ask you something.
You were talking about
going somewhere off-limits.
Miss Wang's family
must be powerful, right?
You're so sharp, Aunt.
His father is a court official.
Is he
high-ranking?
He's fine.
How high is that?
- Take Uncle as an example.
- Sure.
He's an Imperial Guard
of...
the 7th Rank.
You know that.
I do. Go on.
Her father is above him...
by six ranks.
Is that clear?
Let's go, sir.
Make the horse go faster.
Does it hurt?
Such scratches
aren't worth mentioning.
Xinnian,
do you know who gave me this?
My father
gave me such powder made by the Palace.
He's
agreed to help your family in secret
and allowed me to see you.
You're so smart.
Do you know
what that means?
I'll study assiduously
to gain an official rank.
I won't let you and your father down.
Then...
Then I will...
I've put powder on it.
Don't touch it.
♪Chasing the south wind
through a quiet garden♪
♪Among all the worldly sights♪
Simu...
Xinnian...
♪How to express my longing poetically♪
♪I once read poems by Lu and Bai♪
♪But even Li Bai couldn't portrait you♪
♪I flipped through pages♪
♪Took all the words I could♪
♪Only to realize
that love is a mysterious fate♪
♪I am still just a disciple♪
♪Can't compare to true love♪
♪I'd use the rivers as ink♪
♪To write about my longing for you♪
♪If we meet but do not truly know each other♪
♪We'd better pretend that we'd never met♪
♪Every day, I hide my longing for you♪
♪How can I express my feelings to you♪
♪I want this bronze mirror to be magical♪
♪So that I can see Xi Shi and Wang Zhaojun♪
♪Alas, I can only see you among all beauties♪
♪Words may lack proof♪
♪But I've seen it; don't deny it♪
♪From now on, in this world♪
♪Nothing matters more to me♪
♪Mastering the 36 strategies♪
♪Unfolding the scroll, I write your name♪
♪The heavens bear witness for me♪
♪The mountains move for you♪
♪My heart is only for you
with no more exceptions♪
♪Thousands of words♪
♪For you, I can become Li Bai♪
♪Thousands of thoughts as the preface♪
♪Half a poem still depicts my feelings♪
♪Thousands of simple words make a poem♪
♪To express my devotion to you♪
♪All the scenes in this world♪
♪Are beautiful because of you♪
♪Clouds and stars♪
♪I study extensive classics♪
♪I wander with wind♪
♪Only your level stands out♪
♪Perfectly matched love and you♪
♪If I were to fly or move♪
♪In the smallest of dust♪
♪My dear, I'll do anything for you♪
♪Thousands of words♪
♪For you, I can become Li Bai♪
♪Thousands of thoughts as the preface♪
♪Half a poem still depicts my feelings♪
♪Thousands of simple words make a poem♪
♪To express my devotion to you♪
♪All the scenes in this world♪
♪Are beautiful because of you♪
♪If we meet but do not truly know each other♪
♪We'd better pretend that we'd never met♪
♪Every day, I hide my longing for you♪
♪How can I express my feelings to you♪
♪I want this bronze mirror to be magical♪
♪So that I can see Xi Shi and Wang Zhaojun♪
♪Alas, I can only see you among all beauties♪
♪Words may lack proof♪
♪But I've seen it; don't deny it♪
♪From now on, in this world♪
♪Nothing matters more to me♪
♪Mastering the 36 strategies♪
♪Unfolding the scroll, I write your name♪
♪The heavens bear witness for me♪
♪The mountains move for you♪
♪My heart is only for you
with no more exceptions♪
♪Thousands of words♪
♪For you, I can become Li Bai♪
♪Thousands of thoughts as the preface♪
♪Half a poem still depicts my feelings♪
♪Thousands of simple words make a poem♪
♪To express my devotion to you♪
♪All the scenes in this world♪
♪Are beautiful because of you♪
♪Clouds and stars♪
♪I study extensive classics♪
♪I wander with wind♪
♪Only your level stands out♪
♪Perfectly matched love and you♪
♪If I were to fly or move♪
♪In the smallest of dust♪
♪My dear, I'll do anything for you♪
♪Thousands of words♪
♪For you, I can become Li Bai♪
♪Thousands of thoughts as the preface♪
♪Half a poem still depicts my feelings♪
♪Thousands of simple words make a poem♪
♪To express my devotion to you♪
♪All the scenes in this world♪
♪Are beautiful because of you♪
♪Thousands of words♪
♪How to express my longing poetically♪
♪For you, I can become Li Bai♪
♪I once read poems♪
♪Thousands of words♪
♪But even Li Bai couldn't portrait you♪
♪All the scenes in this world♪
♪I'd use the rivers as ink♪
♪Are beautiful because of you♪
♪To write about my longing for you♪