♪I'm just a common man
under the sky♪
♪Among all living beings,
they speak of my recklessness♪
♪Above the sky, my heart yearns♪
♪The light that these hands cannot hide♪
♪The justice gavel strikes
and releases countless burdens♪
♪Looking back, it's the same old story♪
♪Time and space brought me
to another yellowed page♪
♪Curious about the greed in the world♪
♪I tore the sky's curtain apart♪
♪The powerful words♪
♪Spilled this golden soup♪
♪It is not very firm♪
♪Standing here♪
♪I set the rules that shackle me♪
♪Learn to cure♪
♪Eradicating the diseases of this land♪
♪I am just a common man♪
♪I wanted to take things step by step♪
♪Never want to be a confused fool♪
♪I am just a common man♪
♪Listening to the songs without dispute♪
♪Yet I always see the lonely souls♪
♪But I always rush ahead♪
♪Leaving my scribbles behind
for future generations to study♪
♪The light that these hands cannot hide♪
♪The justice gavel strikes
and releases countless burdens♪
♪Looking back, it's the same old story♪
♪Time and space brought me
to another yellowed page♪
♪Sunlight pierces through♪
♪One comes and goes as one pleases♪
♪My Go board holds both sides♪
♪When I set the game, learn to see♪
♪Don't be a sore loser♪
♪So many lies and deceits♪
♪I can see through every play♪
♪May I live and die
with the sun♪
=Guardians of the Dafeng=
=Episode 15=
Hurry up and think of a plan.
What are you looking at?
Your Highness, I have an idea
to make him swear loyalty to you
and never betray you.
However, this idea...
Hurry up and say it. Don't mystify it.
Take him as your kept man.
Take him as my kept man?
Exactly.
If you take him as your kept man,
Huaiqing will naturally stop
competing with you.
But you'll need
to sacrifice your reputation.
That doesn't matter.
My reputation is spread far and wide.
Losing a little is no big deal.
But
what does "kept man" mean?
You...
You don't know?
I've never heard of it.
Do you guys know?
What are you waiting for?
Start to eat.
I'll finish this dish and join you.
Is he
crazy?
Is he trying to poison me?
He won't poison you,
but surely he's gone crazy.
Coming.
Come on.
Scrambled eggs with tomatoes.
Let's see.
If there is any housework,
just let me know,
and I'll take care of it.
Otherwise, if I fall asleep,
all my efforts will be wasted.
The plaque at the entrance
needs polishing, coloring, and waxing.
Perfect, sis.
I'll do it now. You all eat.
Don't wait for me. I'll eat later.
Don't mind me.
Ningyan.
Are you about to break through?
How do you know, Uncle?
How wise of you.
So soon?
What's wrong? Aren't you happy?
Yes, I'm happy.
I'm really happy.
I've been alive for decades,
waiting for this day
when I shouldn't sleep.
Ningyan, I'm truly happy for you.
How did you cultivate yourself?
Can you teach me?
It's actually quite simple...
Ningyan!
Xu Qi'an!
I'll explain later. Coming!
Ningyan, where were you yesterday?
The chief asked about you.
I had something to do and left.
Why are you here?
Isn't today a rest day?
We have good news. Come here.
What good news?
Well...
Don't say we don't look out for you.
Let's go confiscate property.
Confiscate property?
Listen, the Taikang County Governor
got imprisoned, right?
His house should've been
confiscated long ago.
Because of Sangbo,
it was postponed for a few days.
How is confiscation good news?
I still have work to do.
(Xu Residence)
You haven't done it.
You don't know the rules.
Explain it to him.
During the confiscation,
the Recorders will inventory
valuable items in the front hall,
and record them.
The items will then be taken back.
But
the Recorders won't be
the ones who take them.
If the chief finds out about this,
it won't be good.
What are you thinking?
We're saying
we can take things
that no one wants, right?
The unrecorded scraps and junk.
There might be
something valuable among them.
What do you usually say?
Seeking...
Seeking
reasonable profit.
Exactly.
- Hurry up and change.
- Hurry.
Wait for me. I'll be quick.
Hurry up.
(Xu Residence)
Uncle, I won't be eating at home.
Hurry up.
- Hurry.
- It's here, right?
Yes.
Let's go. Hurry up.
Zhu, hurry up.
Bro,
has the Silver Gong leader arrived?
Breeze Hall?
You three are late.
Late?
Weren't they also late?
Bro.
Yes, we're late.
We're late.
Bro, don't hold it against us.
Let's not delay important matters.
(Zhu Chengzhu, Guardian,
7th Rank Fighter)
Draw your saber.
Don't act rashly.
You're tough, huh?
Stand straight to take a beating.
Go back.
Yes.
Watch carefully.
Learn from him.
Understood?
Very good.
Everyone, learn from him. Understood?
Understood?
- Yes.
Good.
My Lord, thanks for your teachings.
Mr. Song, are you okay?
Luckily, you didn't
draw your saber earlier.
Otherwise, you'd be done for.
I know.
Defying a superior is a grave offense.
His surname is Zhu.
He's the youngest Silver Gong
in our yamen.
His father is also a Zhu.
So what?
Aren't you also a Zhu?
Are you his father?
Gold Gong Zhu?
Yes, exactly.
He's not only the youngest Silver Gong
in our yamen
but also the most promising young man
in the capital of the Dafeng
before you showed up.
A few days ago, I went drinking
with one of his Copper Gongs.
He mentioned
that Silver Gong Zhu
dislikes our Breeze Hall.
He dislikes Yuchun.
And he especially dislikes you.
He's said more than once
that you're just a Copper Gong...
(Giving me trouble, huh?)
(Liu Mansion)
Good! Good!
What a jerk.
(Clear Skies)
Take it.
It's okay.
Take some for them.
What is it?
Who else is hiding things?
They all are.
You three.
Haven't you had enough beatings?
Put those things down.
(Impartial and Upright)
Stay here, all of you.
Don't go anywhere.
Clean up all this trash
on the ground.
If it's not clean,
I'll kill you.
Do you hear me?
Yes.
I can't hear it.
Yes!
(Impartial and Upright)
We still got something.
Ningyan,
I'm sorry.
I thought it would be a good thing.
But...
No.
It's me who dragged you into this.
Ningyan,
you touched your arm
several times.
Is the injury serious?
That jerk used his Qi force?
Ningyan, listen to me.
You can file a complaint
about this.
Go and tell the chief.
He'll stand up for you.
Forget it.
No need to trouble the chief.
I'll go find Lord Wei.
Let me go!
What's going on?
- Don't act rashly.
- Let go!
The document states this.
His family shall not suffer.
Let's get to work.
I don't want to!
- Please spare me. I beg you.
- Don't.
Ningyan.
- Please.
- Louder.
I beg you.
Here.
- Miss, go.
- Get lost.
Go.
Xu Qi'an.
- I...
- Come on.
Strike me.
I've remembered your name.
When I return,
I'll report you to Lord Wei.
Fine.
Just wait.
I'll go find the chief now.
I'll destroy you all.
Let me go.
Move aside.
You are really beasts.
One person per room. Rescue them.
Let go of me!
Zhu, let go!
If you dare touch her again,
I'll immediately report you to Lord Wei.
What an ignorant fool.
What's going on?
Let go of me!
What will you do to me?
Ningyan!
Don't act rashly.
You know the consequences.
Let her go,
or I'll take your life.
Did you hear that?
He said he'd take my life.
Alright then.
Let's see
how you'll take my life.
Help me!
Let go!
Die!
(Focus on one thing)
(to achieve greatness.)
My Lord!
- Ningyan.
- My Lord.
Ningyan, run.
You won't survive this. Just escape.
If I run,
what about my family?
What about you guys?
Is it worth it?
Is it worth risking your life
for a stranger?
It's not about worth.
Some things in life
are greater than life itself.
Surround them!
♪Heaven and earth gave birth to me♪
Copper Gong Xu Qi'an
assaulted a superior,
defying the law.
He is to be escorted by Breeze Hall
to the yamen for trial.
Guangxiao, I'll go
and report this to the chief.
Remember. Do not let
Silver Gong Zhu's men escort him.
Take care of him.
Move aside!
(Xu Qi'an)
Chief!
Yuchun!
Something's wrong!
Something huge!
Why are you so panicky?
Xu Qi'an almost killed Silver Gong Zhu.
Hurry and save him.
Guangxiao is escorting him
back to the yamen now.
Gold Gong Zhu will soon hear of it.
I fear Xu Qi'an won't even make it
to the yamen alive.
Hurry, Yuchun!
Chengzhu!
Is there still hope?
(Zhu Yang, Guardian, 4th Rank Fighter)
His Silver Gong shielded him
and kept his life.
Chengzhu.
Father is here.
Wake up.
Chengzhu!
What happened?
The saber force
entered his organs.
We need a sorcerer
from the Astronomical Bureau
to save him.
Where is the sorcerer?
Someone has gone to fetch them.
They'll be here soon.
Call them over.
If they don't arrive in time,
I'll have you die with my son!
Yes.
Son.
Father.
Chengzhu.
Xu
Qi
An!
Hurry up.
You are only safe in the yamen.
Gold Gong Zhu.
You're Xu Qi'an?
My Lord,
Xu Qi'an belongs to Breeze Hall.
Please allow me to bring him back.
Guangxiao!
You're the one
who injured my son.
Any last words?
I regret
not killing that scum.
Die!
How dare you touch someone
from Breeze Hall?
Guangxiao,
are you alright?
Chief, I...
I know.
Don't speak.
Yang Yan,
he almost killed my only son!
So what?
Are you sure you want to protect him?
Yes.
Stop.
Lord Wei has ordered
that Xu Qi'an be brought
back to the yamen,
where he will decide this.
Lord Wei,
Copper Gong Xu Qi'an injured
my son Zhu Chengzhu severely.
He's still teetering
on the brink of life and death.
Lord Wei,
please seek justice for me
and punish Xu Qi'an harshly.
Lord Wei,
Zhu Chengzhu tried to assault
the convicted official's family.
Xu Qi'an tried to stop him but failed,
and only then did he act out of anger.
Nonsense!
It's clear Xu Qi'an held
a personal grudge.
You have a disagreement.
Let's hear the testimonies.
Greetings, Lord Wei.
Tell Lord Wei everything.
Lord Wei,
Xu Qi'an was late for the assembly.
Silver Gong Zhu disciplined him.
Unexpectedly, he held a grudge.
During the confiscation,
Xu Qi'an noticed Silver Gong Zhu
behaving inappropriately
towards the convicted official's family,
so he used this as an excuse,
drew his saber, and attacked.
Lord Wei.
- I need to report.
During assembly,
we weren't late.
But Silver Gong Zhu
made things hard for us,
beating both Xu Qi'an and me.
During the confiscation,
he forced us to stay in the front hall,
forbidding us to enter
the courtyard.
We had no choice but to comply
until cries from the women
in the courtyard reached us.
Xu Qi'an, unable to endure it,
rushed to stop Silver Gong Zhu.
But instead of stopping, Silver Gong Zhu
dragged the woman into the courtyard,
intending to assault her in public.
It was to force Xu Qi'an to act.
Lord Wei,
these two have close personal ties
with Xu Qi'an,
so their testimonies
are inevitably biased
and unreliable.
Lord Wei,
there were other Copper Gongs present.
They can testify.
Speak truthfully,
and you will not be punished.
During assembly,
Xu Qi'an and the others were not late.
Silver Gong Zhu did drag the woman
into the courtyard,
intending to humiliate her before us.
His words were
full of provocation
towards Xu Qi'an.
Shut up!
Even so,
it should be handled by the yamen.
Since when can mere Copper Gongs
administer punishment?
Lord Wei,
Xu Qi'an defied his superior.
According to the Guardians' rules,
he should be cut in half.
Your son Zhu Chengzhu
ignored the law
and acted recklessly.
He is dismissed starting today
and will never be employed again.
Copper Gong Xu Qi'an,
for attacking a Silver Gong
and causing serious injury,
is guilty of a heinous crime.
He is to be imprisoned.
Seven days later,
he shall be cut in half
at the market gate.
- Lord Wei!
You may all leave.
Lord Wei.
Dedicating oneself to the people
without seeking personal gain.
Do you mean it?
Of course, I do.
♪The thoughts linger♪
♪Watching with a smile
and swaying sleeves♪
You're paid as a court official.
You live off the people's resources.
You can easily oppress
the common people,
but you can't fool the heavens.
♪A little warmth of me♪
I meant it too.
♪No need to cry to soothe me♪
♪I sigh alone, with my eyes lowered♪
♪The long dream came to a halt again♪
Someone,
carry out Lord Wei's orders.
Escort Xu Qi'an
to the prison
to await execution.
♪With you, what is there to fear♪
♪Let troubles come my way♪
♪With you, I'll find peace♪
♪Though this world is bitterly cold♪
♪I only wish for Xu's safety♪
♪Neither joy nor sorrow lingers♪
♪Flowers fall♪
♪Their fragrance fades♪
♪I pledge my life to you♪
♪To bloom brightly♪
Mr. Xu,
Ningyan injured a Silver Gong.
Lord Wei has decreed
he be cut in half.
Take care.
Chief, we've told his family.
Apologies.
We did all we could.
Do we have any colleagues left
who can help?
We've contacted everyone we could.
Except for the Gold Gongs.
But we can't reach them.
(Upright and Incorruptible;
Just and Impartial)
(Breeze Hall)
You two,
drink with me for a while.
Chief.
I know you've been hiding wine
and sneaking drinks while on duty.
(Just and Impartial)
I understand
Lord Wei has his difficulties.
Xu Qi'an did make a mistake.
That idiot.
He nearly killed someone with his saber.
And the victim was a Silver Gong.
I thought I was foolish,
but he's even worse.
If I'd known,
I wouldn't have recruited him.
It's maddening.
He deserved it.
He's indeed more talented than others.
But with such a commotion,
the entire yamen was watching.
Could Lord Wei show blatant favoritism?
What would happen to his authority?
Building a reputation takes years,
but destroying it only takes a moment.
If he showed favoritism
toward Xu Qi'an,
who'd trust Lord Wei afterward?
Now, it's settled.
One is dismissed,
and the other will be executed.
Justice served!
(Breeze Hall)
(Xu)
Ningyan.
Look at your bowl.
(Xu)
Even the pattern is unsymmetrical.
In the long days to come,
everyone in the yamen
will keep to the rules.
Xu Qi'an,
your death will not be for nothing.
It'll be worth it.
(Breeze Hall)
Candied hawthorn!
Are you blind?
(Wang Xiuhe,
wife of the Vice Minister of Rites)
Ms. Xiuhe.
Ms. Ru.
It's been a long time.
I almost didn't recognize you.
There have been
many family matters.
I've been too busy to visit.
Please forgive me.
Here are some pastries.
Please accept them.
(Moon Resto)
This is from Moon Resto.
It must've cost you a lot.
You never gift me anything.
What's the occasion today?
Why are you so generous?
It's because my nephew, Xu Qi'an,
accidentally injured a Silver Gong
and was sentenced to death
by Lord Wei.
So, I was hoping
to ask the Vice Minister
to intercede
and save
my nephew's life.
My husband
is the Vice Minister of Rites.
He does have
- influence in the court.
- Yes.
However, with his high position,
he can't help a condemned criminal
for no reason.
If political rivals get hold of this,
he'd suffer because of me.
You'd better take these back.
Let's go home.
(Xu Residence)
Dear.
What did Wang Xiuhe say?
She agreed to help.
Where's your bracelet?
I exchanged it for favors.
That was part of your dowry.
It's just a possession.
When Ningyan returns,
I'll deduct it
from his next month's salary.
How did the Bureau respond?
I met Song Qing.
He said
the Bureau couldn't interfere
in Guardians' matters.
The Imperial Guards also...
As his uncle, I've failed.
Now is not the time to despair.
Let's wait for Xinnian's return.
Perhaps...
Perhaps he has a solution.
I'm just a small Copper Gong.
My words are insignificant.
I don't have the right to choose.
You're paid as a court official.
You live off the people's resources.
You can easily oppress
the common people,
but you can't fool the heavens.
I meant it too.
The human minds are hard to read.
Judging hearts is like solving cases.
One must not
make hasty conclusions
based on temporary biases.
(Steadfast Enforcement)
Do you think I judged wrongly?
(Long and Arduous)
I dare not.
However, Xu Qi'an only acted
out of righteousness
because the Silver Gong
humiliated a woman.
I believe
this act
serves to deter immorality
within the yamen.
Lord Wei, please have mercy
and spare Copper Gong Xu's life.
(Devotion to Duty)
Lord Wei, please have mercy
and spare Copper Gong Xu's life.
Father,
please have mercy.
Xu Qi'an has quite the support.
It's only early morning,
but many have come for him.
All the Gold Gongs
have shown up,
except for Zhu.
Father,
one more won't make a difference.
please have mercy.
Do you think I judged wrongly as well?
Father, you're not wrong.
But neither
is Xu Qi'an.
Chief, don't be impulsive.
There must be another way, Chief.
Don't go there.
- Yuchun.
- There must be another way.
- Don't go there.
Chief.
Chief, think it through.
Wei Yuan!
Get out!
Chief.
Everyone, rise.
Li Yuchun, how dare you!
Chief.
You...
(Rule With Virtue)
Subordinate Li Yuchun.
Chief!
Calm down.
He's drunk.
He's not thinking straight,
so he's speaking nonsense.
- He's a lousy drinker.
- Get out.
Yuchun.
Get lost!
Subordinate Li Yuchun.
I joined the yamen in Yuanjing Year 20.
Since then, I have remained loyal
to my duties.
I swore to root out corrupt officials
and pledged allegiance to my country.
For 17 years,
I have worked tirelessly,
never derelict in duty,
never accepting bribes,
and never oppressing the innocent.
I believed
that my fervent dedication
would bring about a world of justice.
Yet,
in these 17 years,
I've witnessed countless colleagues
oppressing civilians and merchants.
During confiscations,
they always embezzle money
and defile the families
of convicted officials.
The line
must be drawn here!
♪Heaven and earth gave birth to me♪
♪With determination,
the wind can't sway the shadow♪
♪Errant thoughts
entangle the dark world♪
♪Out of fury, I wield my saber♪
♪To cut down injustice
and triumph over evil♪
♪Across eternity,
this realm feels like an endless night♪
♪Only my steadfast heart
remains unchanged♪
♪Stars and constellations
scattered like murky smoke♪
♪Yet my resolute will shines
through to dispel the peril♪
♪The tree longs for stillness,
but the wind will not cease♪
♪Darkness disintegrates before me♪
♪Entwined with injustices
again and again♪
♪Heaven and earth gave birth to me♪
♪With determination,
the wind can't sway the shadow♪
♪Errant thoughts
entangle the dark world♪
♪Out of fury, I wield my saber♪
♪To cut down injustice
and triumph over evil♪
♪Across eternity,
this realm feels like an endless night♪
♪Only my steadfast heart
remains unchanged♪
♪Stars and constellations
scattered like murky smoke♪
♪Yet my resolute will shines
through to dispel the peril♪
♪The tree longs for stillness,
but the wind will not cease♪
♪Darkness disintegrates before me♪
♪Entwined with injustices
again and again♪
♪Across eternity,
this realm feels like an endless night♪
♪Only my steadfast heart
remains unchanged♪
♪Stars and constellations
scattered like murky smoke♪
♪One's arrogance deserves execution♪
♪Slaughter all confusions♪
♪The moonlight illuminates the sky♪
♪Bringing justice back to the world♪
♪Demons and spirits♪
♪Born and perish as one♪
♪A resolve hangs high in my heart♪
♪Worlds apart,
yet sharing the same origin♪