[Roommates of Poongduck 304]
Yes, Baby. Just a minute.
What's going on?
Secretary Yun?
I guess your last night was pretty fine, Young Master.
What?
My shirt... Do you know where my shirt is?
F-Father...
You punk! Come here!
- Please, Father! Please calm down and listen to me!
- How dare you cause an issue again!
How many times was that?
Didn't I tell you to stop dating celebrities?
How many times did I tell you it's not good to be gossiped about by reporters?
Listen, Father. I didn't do anything, but they came to me─
You punk! How dare you talk back to me?
Don't you know what this woman does?
Of course, I know what she does. She's the actress Han Ju Ah.
Do you even think before doing something?
Out of all people, how can you date the one who does Jinseong Group's commercial?
She's the one who brings all the sales for them! What do you think the reporters will say about this?
Well...
[Han Ju Ah and Ji Ho Jun are in a serious relationship. Are they going to be official?]
[Han Ju Ah is dating the heir of the Geumnam Group. When will they get married?]
[Caught the secret date scene of Geumnam Group's Ji Ho Jun! What about his relationship with Ms. M in the past?]
[Geumnam Group's Ji Ho Jun is dating a rival company's model! Is this a reconciliation between the two companies?]
I guess they can say a lot.
- Secretary Yun.
- Yes, Sir.
- Which newspaper company was it?
- It was the Fact Patch, Sir.
The news got exactly two pages like this.
Oh, my head.
How long do I have to take care of this punk?
Raise your head.
Do you think you are living comfortably because you are great?
Yes, I think so.
Unlike you, I'm tall and have wide shoulders.
Also, my face looks wealthy and handsome.
It's written on my face that "I'm a chaebol."
So how am I not supposed to be popular?
No, Sir.
I will give you a final chance.
What? Final?
How can you say it so scarily?
Even the genie of the lamp makes three wishes come true.
Well, you are not the genie.
- There are two conditions.
- And there are even conditions.
First, give me all the credit cards you have right now, and then go out and live on your own for two years!
Wait!
Seriously, you bastard!
Secondly, I will appoint you as a team leader in the headquarters.
So make a profit out of there somehow.
Father, why are you doing this to me? You know that I'm not interested in business─
When you make a profit, I will bring back all the support for you.
- Secretary Yun!
- Yes, Sir.
Sell all of his cars in the garage!
Wait, not my cars!
Hello, Accounting Team. Please sell all the cars of Young Master now.
Sure. We need to sell them.
What are you waiting for?
I'm sorry? Oh...
- But, Father.
- What?
I will get paychecks when I'm working, right?
Seriously...
This is absolutely disgusting!
Even if I made it with my feet, it would be more delicious.
I don't have any money to see any of you right now.
By the way, I wonder how much I will get paid for that job.
[Secretary Yun]
Ajeossi!
Yes, Ho Jun!
So, where are you staying right now?
I don't know. Don't ask me about it.
This is just a temporary place to stay.
I will move into a hotel immediately when I get paid next month.
Right. It's not easy to find a place that fits our young master's taste.
What's wrong with my taste?
The water pressure from the shower has to be above a certain pressure.
It must meet your scalp with a specific feeling between pricking and refreshing.
Don't you remember your nanny went through a hard time with your bath times?
By the way, your face looks so much better.
I guess you are doing great since I'm not there.
No! I couldn't even sleep well because I was worried about you.
Isn't that a pillow mark on your face?
Did you finally have a good night's sleep?
Anyway, Ho Jun. This is the contract that says you'll be working as Geumnam Group's New Business Planning Team's team leader.
Sign here, and let's move your place to a hotel next month.
Don't change the subject. Give me a pen.
But how much am I getting paid? 400 million won? 500 million won?
Wait, this doesn't have the front page.
- What is it? Why are you not saying anything?
- What?
I'm saying this doesn't have the front page. I need to know how much I'm getting paid.
Why don't you sign here first?
It's right there. Right next to your butt.
Why are you acting as if you put it aside on purpose?
Ho Jun, wait.
- Give it to me.
- One second, please.
I said, give that to me!
What? The annual salary is 22 million won?
Minimum wage?
Ajeossi, are you kidding me?
What kind of team leader in conglomerates works on a minimum wage?
Ho Jun, so the thing is...
Ho Jun, wait! Please wait!
Let me go.
Ji Ho Jun! If I go like this, the chairman will kill me.
I don't care. That's not my problem!
Don't you ever think of seeing me again unless there's another zero behind the annual salary.
No! Wait, Ho Jun.
This is the contract and your team members' résumés, so please read it all and come to work!
- Let me go.
- No, Ho Jun!
I said, let me go!
Seriously, isn't the minimum wage too harsh?
They all look stifling.
What?
[Résumé]
[Seo Jae Yun]
Your portfolio was amazing.
Thank you so much. I just worked hard on what I had to do.
I guess something good happened to you.
Yes, such a great thing just happened to me!
Oh, we haven't ordered coffee yet. Let me get it for all of us.
I will come with you, Sir.
No, please have a seat.
- Oh, my goodness! What should we do, Jae Yun?
- Excuse me?
Jae Yun, after joining this company, I wanted to quit 14 times until now.
But I never actually handed in the resignation letter. Do you know why?
What's the reason?
Strangely, I couldn't hand it in, as if someone was pulling my hands.
But now I get it. It was all to meet Team Leader Ji, like destiny!
He's so handsome! Amazingly handsome!
Wow, it's really motivating me to work.
I will be back from the restroom.
Landlord!
You need to build up some lower body strength.
Why? Do you have something to say?
- What's going on?
- What about it?
I'm asking why the heck you are here.
I'm not "you" but "Team Leader."
Team...
Team Leader.
Since you called me Team Leader, I will answer your question.
I got the job. That's why I'm here.
I'm having a hard time wrapping my head around this situation.
So can you tell me in more detail? What happened?
Where should I start?
Did you already know that I was working here?
Since when? Did you already know when you were looking for the house?
No.
I figured it out about 12 hours ago.
I saw your résumé only yesterday.
Until then, I had no idea either.
Then are you saying this is a pure coincidence?
I think so.
Wait.
But if you figured it out about 12 hours ago, you should've told me beforehand!
This morning, yes! You could've told me this morning.
I told you so.
Landlord.
Where are you going?
I'm going out now, too. I will give you a ride.
Why are you staring at me? I said I will give you a ride.
Is he joking around with me? Seriously...
I was going to tell you at that time.
Anyway. Employee Seo Jae Yun, you were pretty good.
What are you talking about it?
Although you graduated from an online college,
you got hired by this conglomerate with a blind test, beating the top university graduates.
You didn't just get hired. You came in first place in the marketing division.
I don't feel like listening to that right now.
Why not?
Is it because of me, for getting the team leader position, even though I'm just your tenant?
I guess your face right now can be interpreted as, "I wanted to kick out this lousy tenant, but now I have a problem."
I saw something interesting in your résumé last night.
There is only one more full-time job transition screening left for you.
But that screening...
will be done by me in three months.
Are you threatening me right now?
Not at all.
I also have a reason why I need to get through this.
So, if you want to do it well together, don't play landlord on me.
Okay?
[How to Become the Best Marketer]
[Become Successful by Starting a Business]
[Trends in the Media Where Influencers Are Active]
[Overseas Influencers Marketing Cases]
[How to Make You Want to Buy, Marketing on Emotion]
[Online Marketing]
[Marketer's Work]
[Ho Cheol]
The person you are trying to reach is not available at the moment. Please leave a message after the beep─
What kind of neighborhood is this? It neither has capacity nor order.
It's driving me crazy.
Hello. I'm at the parking lot right now.
Oh.
Oh?
Just give me five minutes!
This is insane. What should I do?
Wow, I know this car is a limited edition with only ten in this country, isn't it?
Hey, hey! What are you doing?
- Did you move in here recently?
- Yes, why?
May I ask for your apartment number?
Oh, I live in unit 303. My business card is...
White Class?
May I ask your age? I'm 27.
I'm older than you.
Then can I call you Hyeongnim?
Hyeongnim, since we are neighbors now, let's get some drinks together.
I don't have any neighbor friends.
The drinks are on me.
Also, since I wasted your time unintentionally...
Hyeongnim, this is chocolate from overseas.
I don't give this to anybody.
Hyeongnim, but you are lucky.
Huh? This is...
It's my company's gift.
I'm working for a company with a tradition that has ten years of history.
It's a very beneficial company for your life, but I will tell you about it later.
Excuse me for a second. I got a call from a client.
Yes, to make your life better! This is Yu Seung Seok.
Oh, the jade mats? Yes, we do have it!
Hyeongnim, I will call you later.
You made a great decision, Sir!
I wasn't going to say this, but it's a great product for men.
Speak of the devil.
- Hello?
- Where are you?
Why do you ask about that?
Let's meet for a second.
Here's the 500,000 won.
I bet you know what this means.
- It's the exact amount.
- What are you doing?
You said the monthly rent is 300,000 won.
- Excuse me.
- I'm not "excuse me." Call me "Team Leader."
Team...
Yes, Team Leader.
I thought about it, but this doesn't seem right.
You have a talent for making me say the same thing over and over again.
- I definitely told you that I'm going to stay here.
- Are you kidding me?!
No, I'm very serious.
If you don't like it, then persuade me.
I mean, you'll probably know because you have enough experience with work life.
We work together the whole day, but does seeing each other again after work make sense to you?
I have to get off work and have a private life. Don't you think so?
What's wrong with my face? I'm very good-looking!
Have you ever seen someone like me out there? If so, bring them to me.
Not having a private life? That's the same for me.
Since it's like this, let's just─
So I'm saying, rent a place somewhere else!
There are plenty of houses. Please!
I said I don't want to.
Why? What's the reason?
I've already told you the reason multiple times.
So I'm giving you your money back.
Because you, no, I mean, Team Leader!
I trust your words entirely, and I am giving back your 500,000 won.
Or should I give you one million won? Was that what you wanted from the beginning?
Do I look like a piece of trash who's desperate for just a few bucks?
If it feels unfair to you, you should get a new job!
What? Get a new job?
How can you say that so carelessly about someone else's job?
With your logic, why are you clinging to this job when there are plenty of companies?
It ranks first in the average annual salary of South Korea.
It ranked 71st place in New York Times' "The World's Best Companies to Work for."
I can learn a lot from here, and it pays the best. This is the only place for me.
- To me, the Marketer─
- That's what I'm saying!
Why do you settle for the 71st place? Hop on a plane and go!
The remaining top 70 companies are waiting for you in Silicon Valley.
I will take good care of this house for you in the meantime.
I feel like I'm talking to a wall!
Wow, you just scream in front of the team leader when you are just a regular staff?
This is why I said it's a problem!
What about you?
You are a total squatter who doesn't leave when the landlord asks you to leave!
Are you going to come out like this? It's a total revolt.
Team Leader, you're abusing your power.
Is that so? Since we are on at it, shall I abuse my power to the extreme?
I told you that I must survive here no matter what.
This means even if you are my landlord, as long as I'm the team leader,
revolts can't happen in my team.
It also means I need to oppress your spirit like this.
Try your best to hang in there.
If you are still on my team after a month,
I will pass your full-time transition screening without any conditions.
What did you just say?
♫ Oh, look around, there is nothing easy in this world ♫
♫ Uh, but it seems that my heart is at ease ♫
♫ Sometimes I don't know why you act so edgy ♫
♫ And it's so strange that I still don't hate that ♫
We used to use this format in the Sales Team, so I...
Then why would the Business Management Team take their time to distribute the form to each department?
[Crazy bastard. Crazy bastard. Crazy bastard.]
[No Parking]
Who the heck put this on it?
You can only park one car per unit in this building.
What?
I'm not a person who puts pressure on people for something like this. Please don't think that way.
Of course, I know you're taking care of me.
Let's hit that, and the one who gets a higher score wins.
If I win, you leave the company.
And if you win, I leave this house.
[Roommates of Poongduck 304]