[Green Years - Ning Hengyu / Zhao Beier]
♫ The bicycle bell rings and takes me back to
the alley I saw in my dream ♫
♫  I invite the sunlight to traverse the morning
fog and breeze with me ♫
♫ Riding my bike, trying to catch up to the fleeting youth ♫
♫ The Forbidden City made from red walls and
encaustic tiles in my memory ♫
♫ Unlike the hustle and bustle of everyday life ♫
♫ It's quaint and peaceful ♫
♫ Throughout the ordinary and extraordinary four seasons  ♫
♫ Some words are just like seeds ♫
♫ Growing in our youth, changing our future ♫
♫ Who can understand the silence in our hearts? ♫
♫ We once thought our dreams were somewhere far away ♫
♫ We wanted to grow up as soon as possible ♫
♫ Some waited while some traveled ♫
♫ How far away is our future? ♫
♫ Now, each of us ♫
♫ Has gone through a lot ♫
♫ We have grown up ♫
♫ Finally confirming that love is faith ♫
♫ There's no need to wander anymore ♫
♫ The questions we asked back then ♫
♫ Have been answered gradually ♫
♫ Through the passing of time ♫
♫ Who had pursued their dreams and left no regrets behind? ♫
♫ Returning to this place in the end ♫
♫ Returning ♫
♫ To the place that I've always loved  ♫
♫ We once thought our dreams were somewhere far away ♫
♫ We wanted to grow up as soon as possible ♫
♫ Finally confirming that love is faith ♫
♫ There's no need to wander anymore ♫
[Memory of Encaustic Tile]
[Adapted from Beifeng Sanbaili's original novel "Memory of Encaustic Tile"]
[Episode 17]
[The Restless Sadness]
I like seeing you.
I'll visit you every day.
You have school.
If your grades go down, your mother will be mad at me.
I'll come after school. I can do my homework here.
It's better than being next to my mom.
Don't let your mother hear this.
Otherwise...
Is it hurting again?
Maybe you can take another half of the painkiller.
I'm fine.
Did the pain recede?
Zhang Qi.
Yes, Ms. Jin Ning.
You're the talkative one,
but you haven't said a word since you came in.
Is it too much to see me in my current state?
Don't say that.
I've always wanted a wife as pretty as you are.
When this kid uses all his wits on flattery,
he's indeed great at it.
Ms. Jin Ning, my mom is on a business trip in Hong Kong.
She's been to many major hospitals.
They have more treatment plans for your condition.
She wants to talk to you about it.
She can even transfer you there.
Don't make your mother worry.
Zhang Qi, do as I say.
Tell your mother to take care of herself.
Beijing has the greatest doctors.
- If they can't do it here, I don't...
- They can cure you.
They certainly can.
Yes, Ms. Jin Ning. You will get well.
My mom is waiting for you to take her abroad.
She won't go without you.
She doesn't know the language and the customs.
What if she gets lost?
Okay.
I have more free time now.
I can plan the trip.
Great. I'll tell my mom.
She'll be so excited that she can't fall asleep.
I bet she'll stare at the calendar.
Okay.
- Why are you here?
- Hand me the food.
It's time to eat, Mom.
Sunian, you came just in time.
Take the two of them out and grab some food.
Eating hospital meals has made you lose so much weight.
Listen to me.
Go get some decent food.
It's my treat.
- It's okay, Ms. Jin Ning.
- It's okay.
- Take it.
- Never mind, Dad. I have money.
Just take it.
Let's go.
Eat heartily.
Don't forget to finish your food, Mom.
Goodbye, Mr. Zheng and Ms. Jin Ning.
- Goodbye, Ms. Jin Ning.
- Goodbye.
You don't have to come here all the time.
Studies are your priority.
If you keep doing this, I'll quit.
What... What did we do?
Yeah, what did we do?
I am the same person.
I didn't change into a monster. Don't tiptoe around me.
Okay.
Who says you didn't change?
Look at your bangs. They are blocking your sight.
You look like Kakashi.
Ease up on the comics.
Sunian, what do you have in mind?
I'm fine with anything.
However, I need you to come with me first.
Where are we going?
We're buying you some snacks.
[The Cute Pet House]
This is the snack you mentioned?
What's wrong?
Did your master mistreat you?
Don't be so mean.
Did you sniff too much disinfectant and find enlightenment?
You're probably right.
When I have nothing to do, I talk a lot.
Fine. I'll talk less from now on.
I don't want to seem like I have nothing better to do.
Sunian.
This is the most expensive cat feed in this shop.
We'll take both.
You're buying a lot.
Can the cats even finish it?
We'll leave it there.
When the cats are full, they can finish it later.
Cats are not like dogs.
Why are you looking at me?
Sunian, I never thought you still cared about those cats.
It's my mom.
She keeps saying those kittens might be starving.
Sunian,
you are so kind to the cat.
Yeah. I've never had anything so expensive before.
When it's done, I'll feed you.
Kitty, eat all you want.
You can't stay healthy if you starve.
Sunian, aren't you feeding me?
We'll go get some mutton.
How about Pizza Hut?
I'm fine with Pizza Hut.
Can we have something else?
- What?
- Such as?
How about Ro Jia Mo?
[Corner Sundry Shop]
Welcome. It's been a while.
[MENU]
Ms. Deng.
Three Ro Jia Mo with both fatty and lean meat?
I'll have four. One is for my father.
Okay.
[Local Specialty, Economical and Tasty]
It's on the house.
That doesn't seem right.
Why? It's not like I can't afford it.
It's on the house.
Sunian,
I was upset for days after I heard what had happened.
- She is such a nice person... She...
- Ms. Deng.
You're giving us too much meat.
People might think it's not fair for them.
I do what I want.
They don't have to buy it if they don't like it.
Sunian, I've wanted to pay her a visit.
But I got busy lately and can't make the time.
It's okay, Ms. Deng.
She'll crave your food when she sees you.
That's easy.
I'll just make more for her.
Is there any food that she must avoid?
I'll make her some bone soup later.
It's very nutritious.
It's okay, Ms. Deng.
She doesn't have an appetite.
She can't eat anything.
She was all right, how did...
Sunian.
Trust me, kind people will have good karma.
Your mother will get well.
I believe it, too.
Here, Sunian, take it.
Give your mother my regards.
Let me know when she is available. I want to visit her.
Thank you, Ms. Deng.
Don't mention it.
We'll eat at my house.
Never mind.
My dad is alone at the hospital.
If I go there now, he can take a break.
I'll get going now.
[Ro Jia Mo]
Sunian...
Whenever you need any kind of help, let me know.
Yes. Me too.
Just stay healthy and well.
I'll be fine.
See you.
Sunian, wait!
Take this.
This is...
I prepared some tonics. Give them to your mother.
I can't make the time.
Here, take it.
Go on.
Thank you.
He keeps saying he's fine, but he's just pretending.
Sunian is smiling,
but when I see him smile,
I feel sad for him.
We must stay strong.
As he said, he feels full of energy when he sees me.
I agree with him.
I feel full of energy too when I see you.
That is why I must put this strong point to great use.
I can't help with Ms. Jin Ning's condition, but at least,
I can bring them joy.
Sometimes, you really impress me.
You are so optimistic about everything.
Dad.
Dad?
- You're here.
- What are you doing here?
Your mother chased me out.
She wants me to go home and rest.
This will warm your hands.
I understand.
Zhang Qi and Xue also told me to go home.
I don't want to go home either.
When I'm in that house,
I keep thinking...
how she used to be.
Dad, be honest with me.
Is Mom's condition...
deteriorating again?
The doctor told me...
I should transfer her to the intensive care unit.
What's the difference?
The difference...
Your mother's daily necessities
must strictly follow the doctor's instructions.
We can't be with her all the time.
We only have four hours every day to keep her company, it might not be enough for her!
So...
How long...
is she going to be in there?
Until...
Until she is cured.
Dad.
Can Mom...
really be cured?
Yes.
I told you...
to go home and rest well.
Hello, Ms. Jin Ning.
I wasn't expecting you.
Please come in.
Come.
Sit next to me.
Come closer.
Come on.
How did you...
get into this mess?
There goes the saying,
"No one knows the future for sure."
Ms. Jin Ning, I work at a supermarket nearby.
If you crave anything, ask Sunian to inform me.
I'll deliver them to you right away.
Okay.
I'm so glad you are so kind to me.
Ms. Jin Ning, you need to decide.
If not, I'll send you random items.
Don't waste your money.
I have everything I need here.
If you are sending gifts, send them to your family.
Make sure you and your mother eat well.
Ms. Jin Ning, I have matters to see to.
I should get going. You two carry on.
Mom, I'm going now.
He is such a nice kid.
You look well.
And you're the opposite.
I know.
What's so funny?
How can you still laugh at a time like this?
I'm already bedridden.
Whether I laugh or cry,
it won't make a difference.
I'm just clinging onto my life.
This is nice.
What's nice?
With you around,
I can finally be honest with someone.
Xin Jie,
do you know...
what I hate the most at this moment?
It's waking up.
When I wake up every day,
I have to face the frail being I've become.
Everyone I care about...
slowly becomes so drained and desperate...
because of me.
I don't know if I can...
compare my suffering to what you have been through,
but right now,
I am in a lot of pain.
If I could make you feel better,
- I...
- It pains me to see you like this!
I thought I hated you.
I wanted you to have the worst and most miserable life.
But when I learned you've been sick,
I couldn't sleep well at night.
I refused to believe what I heard.
Then, I felt this pain in my heart.
And then,
I began to hate myself.
Maybe all those thoughts I had about you
had become a reality.
Was it my fault?
It's because of my cursed mouth!
My cursed mouth!
- Maybe it...
- Senior... Senior!
Stop it.
This is more heart-wrenching than the most depressing TV drama.
Slowly.
Sit.
Sit down.
Senior.
Senior, thank you.
Thank you for visiting.
I went to the temple yesterday.
I prayed to Buddha
so all those thoughtsI had won't come true.
As long as you are well,
I'm willing to do anything.
No.
Go to the temple again.
Take back what you said.
You are now having a better life,
so is Wu Huan.
You must pray for yourself
and for Wu Huan.
Do not be concerned about me.
My life means nothing.
When I die,
Wu Huan will finally be free.
Senior!
Promise me that as long as life can go on,
you must never give up so easily.
You must stay strong and live
so that I can remember you and keep hating you.
It's the only thing that gives hope to my life, is that clear?
Sure. I'll do my best.
Mom, I need to have a word with you.
I want to visit Ms. Jin Ning every day.
Don't worry, it won't affect my studies.
I'll bring my books there.
Wait, you just said
you were scared.
I reflected on it.
Ms. Jin Ning needs me right now.
I cannot run away just because I am mentally weak.
I must face the problem bravely to solve it.
Am I right?
Our daughter has grown up.
She sounds like an adult.
Dad, I am already 17 years old.
I am an adult now.
I can't always let you protect me.
I must learn to face the problems myself.
Sure. I'll visit her with you.
You're coming too?
If my daughter knows about facing the problem, I must follow suit.
We should spend more time with her.
That should give Sunian and his father more time to rest.
Okay.
The three of us will visit her.
- Eat up.
- Okay.
Stop looking.
You're already pretty.
Keep it down.
I've been pretty my entire life.
When the end is near, I turned into this mess.
Don't be silly.
I'm even more hideous when the pain comes.
Stop it, or I'll get mad at you.
I don't care what the others see.
But I must at least be presentable
for my son.
Zheng.
Cover for me, will you?
When I look the most hideous,
I don't want my son to see me.
[Peking Union Medical College Hospital]
Jin Ning.
- What's the matter?
- It hurts.
- Is it hurting again?
- It hurts!
- How bad is it?
- Mom...
Sunian, call the doctor.
Is it very painful? Hang in there.
What is taking so long?
Hang in there. I'll hold it for you.
- It hurts!
- Doctor, it's suddenly hurting. It's very severe.
- I...
- Lay still.
How about this? The family can wait outside.
- But she... she is in great pain!
- Sir, please do as you are told.
She won't be afraid when I'm here.
We need your cooperation. Thank you.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Jin Ning, we are right outside. Don't be afraid.
[Ward 4]
Doctor, how is it?
She passed out.
This will only happen more often from now on.
I suggest you transfer her to the ICU as soon as possible.
It'll be easier for both of you.
When she's awake, you should discuss it with her.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
Sunian, perhaps you should go home and rest.
I'm fine.
We don't...
I can take care of her myself.
I want to keep her company.
Your mother told me...
she didn't want you to see her in pain.
She is too prideful.
Let's not make her feel embarrassed.
Please.
You're awake.
This is for you.
It's pretty.
I had a dream.
Really?
What do you see?
In my dream,
we were still young.
When we first met,
you were scratched by a cat.
I took you to the hospital for an injection on my bike.
On the way there,
people were making fun of you.
In hindsight, it was baffling.
That bike had a small backseat.
I could barely ride a straight line, how did you not fall off?
Back then... it was almost unbearable.
Tell me. How unbearable was it?
Back then, my hand was hurt.
I couldn't hold onto anything.
I wouldn't dare to hold your waist with my other hand.
I was sitting at the back, so I had to maintain the balance. Like so.
I felt like I was Zhu Bajie with his long rake.
(A major character of the novel "Journey to the West")
Zheng Jin.
I wish I could go back in time.
If I could,
I would hold onto you as soon as I saw you,
and tell you I was your wife.
I'd tell you to marry me.
I bet you'd be terrified.
But that wouldn't stop me from telling you.
I must tell you...
to cherish every second we spend together...
and never to waste any second...
because...
Because...
Because we have plenty of time to be with each other.
We would have so much time to spend with each other.
Actually, this is my fault.
Why should I blame you?
You took great care of yourself when you were young.
You did your check-ups regularly.
But after we got married, you kept everything to yourself.
And that eventually got you sick.
This is indeed your fault.
You spoiled me.
I got too lazy with everything.
I was too lazy to get a check-up.
Every morning,
the first thing I think when I wake up...
is what new way there is to spoil you.
I mean it.
I talked to the doctor.
Tomorrow, we're transferring you to the ICU.
No.
Jin Ning, trust me.
You need time to recover.
When you get well, you can leave this place.
I don't want to go there.
Zheng Jin,
I thought it through.
Everyone dies someday.
Listen to me.
The ICU costs too much money.
They charge several thousand just for a day there.
Sunian still needs the money in the future.
You are just extending my life with money.
It's meaningless.
You must live on.
You must live on and be well.
We agreed, there is still plenty of time.
I need to think of more ways to spoil you.
When you get well, take me on a ride on a bicycle.
I won't hold your waist. I'll spread my arms.
Sunian. Sunian!
Why are you sitting here alone?
I came out to buy breakfast.
It's already 11:00.
It's that late already?
I'll buy lunch, too.
Go on without me.
I'll go with you.
It's okay.
Go on.
My mother is such a nice person.
Why her?
Why is it her?
Why her of all people?
I've known Sunian for 17 years.
I've never seen him cry.
He never liked fighting,
nor is he easily frustrated.
The teachers have always taught him
that everything will have a bright side.
Those who don't know him well will think he is a cold person.
But in my heart, he's always so strong and capable.
He is Sunian who is capable of anything.
But he is having a breakdown in front of me.
His breakdowns are silent and unnoticeable.
I've never felt so sorry for him.
I wish I could become stronger right now
and become a shoulder he can rely on
so that when he's afraid,
I can give him strength.
[Textile Division]
Dongge?
Check this for me. Is it good enough?
You have silk wrapped around your hand.
Is something bothering you?
Is it about Jin Ning?
Yes.
I can't help myself.
How did it...
Has her condition improved?
She looks frailer with every passing day.
She is slowly...
losing her hair.
I made a hat for her.
I even added the embroidery of a lily on it.
But I'm not sure if she will wear it.
She certainly will.
Your craftsmanship is remarkable.
Not even the most beautiful hat is good enough for her.
After all, she had beautiful hair.
- Mr. Zheng! Mr. Zheng!
- This one must be reworked.
Mr. Shao, where is Mr. Zheng?
He's not here. What is it?
A British pocket watch for the exhibition has some issues.
The staff there only recognizes Mr. Zheng's craftsmanship.
They want him there to examine it.
Mr. Zheng is not available.
[Case file]
Will Mr. Shao do?
You are a master craftsman. Of course, you can do it.
But where is Mr. Zheng anyway?
There are so many watch exhibitions coming our way.
We need every worker we have.
If there is anything that needs Mr. Zheng, let me handle them instead.
That's too much work for you.
We'll do it one at a time.
Mr. Lu Xun once said this, "Time is like water in a sponge.
You can always get some by squeezing hard enough."
When is Mr. Zheng coming back?
His wife is sick.
Is his wife...
Let's go.
A modal verb with the present perfect continuous of a verb
indicates a guess about the past.
Take this sentence as an example.
"Your mother must have been looking for you."
Shao Xue,
please give an example.
Xue. Xue!
Shao Xue!
Give us a sentence with past tenses.
She was healthy.
Use the sentence on the blackboard.
Change it into past tense.
What were you doing just now?
You will be in your senior year soon.
You should pay more attention to your studies.
The same goes for the rest of you.
Pay attention during the classes.
Class dismissed.
I should have reminded you, but I didn't understand it either.
Sorry.
I should have paid more attention.
This isn't your fault.
["OLD SONG" - Featuring artist: Ma Di]
♫ As I traverse this path without minding it ♫
♫ My memory does all the hard work for me ♫
♫ All the memories are embedded deep within my heart ♫
♫ The past I've been hiding from year after year ♫
♫ Carved into the days long gone ♫
♫ Although simplicity is plain, its vibrancy has never faded ♫
♫ Those songs in the past ♫
♫ They had accompanied me through everything ♫
♫ Singing about the stubbornness of our youth ♫
♫ Using this song to boost our courage as we sing ♫
♫ Please don't cry because you have me ♫
♫ Until I saw the bustling city ♫
♫ Until I realized that it was once within my reach ♫
♫ I was this sober once but I still did the same thing ♫
♫ As days go by, I wish to forget ♫
♫ But unknowingly, I remember them again ♫
♫ I remember the deep feelings that were long gone ♫
♫ Within those simple days ♫
♫ Those songs in the past, they had accompanied me ♫
♫ As I regretted our parting during our youth ♫
♫ Using this song, this song belongs to us ♫
♫ Please don't cry again ♫
♫ And don't ask when I'll return ♫