♫ The bicycle bell rings and takes me back to
the alley I saw in my dream ♫
♫  I invite the sunlight to traverse the morning
fog and breeze with me ♫
♫ Riding my bike, trying to catch up to the fleeting youth ♫
♫ The Forbidden City made from red walls and
encaustic tiles in my memory ♫
♫ Unlike the hustle and bustle of everyday life ♫
♫ It's quaint and peaceful ♫
♫ Throughout the ordinary and extraordinary four seasons  ♫
♫ Some words are just like seeds ♫
♫ Growing in our youth, changing our future ♫
♫ Who can understand the silence in our hearts? ♫
♫ We once thought our dreams were somewhere far away ♫
♫ We wanted to grow up as soon as possible ♫
♫ Some waited while some traveled ♫
♫ How far away is our future? ♫
♫ Now, each of us ♫
♫ Has gone through a lot ♫
♫ We have grown up ♫
♫ Finally confirming that love is faith ♫
♫ There's no need to wander anymore ♫
♫ The questions we asked back then ♫
♫ Have been answered gradually ♫
♫ Through the passing of time ♫
♫ Who had pursued their dreams and left no regrets behind? ♫
♫ Returning to this place in the end ♫
♫ Returning ♫
♫ To the place that I've always loved  ♫
♫ We once thought our dreams were somewhere far away ♫
♫ We wanted to grow up as soon as possible ♫
♫ Finally confirming that love is faith ♫
♫ There's no need to wander anymore ♫
[Memory of Encaustic Tile]
[Adapted from Beifeng Sanbaili's original novel "Memory of Encaustic Tile"]
[Episode 34]
[With the Loved Ones Around, Rekindling the Memory of Encaustic Tile]
Mom.
Where did you put my Zhao Ling'er keychain?
Dad.
We will be moving out soon.
That house is big and luxurious.
If you're still around, you would have scolded me and said I was a spendthrift.
I won't listen to you this time.
[Forever in our Memories]
Since you were the one who left us behind.
Do you see?
Our son is very promising now.
If you were still around, you would be very proud.
Son, salute your father.
Do you still remember how he taught you?
Dad, are you not willing to move because of Mom?
Even if we moved to a new place,
Mom's possessions and photos are still there. Isn't it the same?
How can it be the same?
The old house is no more.
What else can I keep in my memories?
All of you won't be coming back.
The old house is no more.
What else can I keep in my memories?
Dad.
I wanted to tell you this later.
I've decided to come back and work here.
I've found a house in Beijing.
I'm just waiting for you to move there and stay with us.
I hope you won't find us too annoying.
Are you telling the truth?
Will your son lie to you?
In the future, no matter where you are, I'll be there with you.
Don't touch that.
Remove it after watching Shiyin's show at night.
Come on.
She was the one who opposed our daughter learning this.
Now, she is the one who wants to watch the show.
Didn't you oppose it as well?
You can just complain about me.
Mom, I'm going out for a while.
Why don't you leave after watching the show?
This is a rerun.
You have to watch it even if it's a rerun.
[Demolish]
Shiyin?
How's the progress?
I've packed most of everything.
Why are you here?
I was just passing by.
Where's your mother?
She is tidying up the new house.
How's it going between you and Tang Ya?
It's fine.
When's the wedding ceremony?
We won't be having a ceremony.
Just a simple banquet will do.
You need to treat her well.
Don't be so stingy.
What about you? Are you not going to find someone to take care of you?
There's no need.
I'm very independent now.
I can take care of myself.
That's great. That's great.
I've been staying here for 20 years.
I suddenly feel reluctant...
to move away from this place.
Although your old house is gone,
your friends will still remain.
[This place will be demolished soon. Dine here as soon as possible!]
It's just the two of you today?
Shiyin moved.
Zhang Qi went abroad, too.
Madam, are our dishes ready?
They'll be served soon. See what you'd like to eat.
Go and do your things.
Sunian, this place will be demolished soon.
Why do they still have so many customers?
I should call my mother here and let her experience this bustling atmosphere.
My mother has been touching walls in the house every day.
It's so scary.
There's not much change with my father.
He is just spacing out for a longer time.
If this goes on, I won't be in the mood to get married anymore.
No way.
They are two different things.
Look how scared you are.
Have you ordered?
Mr. Qian? Why are you helping here?
Are you surprised? This is my restaurant.
Your restaurant?
I've joined forces with Ms. Mei.
Where's your hair?
I have love now so I no longer wear a wig.
I actually started getting bald when I was 17 years old.
Enough talk about me. When will you two get married?
We haven't decided yet.
Aren't we preparing for the relocation?
Don't hesitate.
You can hold your wedding reception here.
Qian, hurry up!
I'm coming, Dear!
I'll give you a plate of lamb kidneys for free later.
Your wine.
Sunian,
why don't we organize our wedding at the alley?
We can even make our parents happy and let them keep some nice memories.
What do you think?
Sure. Anything you say.
In that case, we have to call and inform Shiyin and Zhang Qi.
Yes.
Zhang Qi.
Shiyin.
- We are getting married.
How is it?
Pretty, right?
Dear, your craftsmanship is incredible.
With this material and craftsmanship,
if it were being sold on the market,
it would be a six-figure price.
That's a must.
Unlike my wedding
where I only got a simple red uniform.
Since my daughter is getting married,
she must be pretty.
What do you mean by a simple uniform?
I wanted you to make a new dress but you wouldn't.
How expensive would that be?
Didn't we have to live our lives?
Fine. You are right. It's my fault again.
It's all my fault.
Don't touch it. You might scratch it.
Did you tell Xue about this dress?
No.
I want to give her a surprise.
You're keeping a secret?
Dad! Mom! I'm back.
- You're back?
- Mr. Shao. Ms. Yu.
Even the star is here.
Don't make fun of me.
I'm not making fun of you.
Both of us are watching that show of yours every day.
"Happiness First."
Shiyin, why are you free to come today?
I came here today to pick a wedding dress for Xue.
Pick a wedding dress?
Look.
This is a very amazing designer.
I'm close with him.
Can I even afford this?
There's no need to pay with my connections.
Don't worry. I'll deal with everything.
Think of it as your wedding gift.
That's very nice of you.
Mom, sit here. Let's pick one together.
I'm looking at it. I can see it from here.
Sure.
So pretty.
They are all Western dresses.
Western dresses are not as nice as Chinese dresses.
Aunt, Western dresses are better.
They are fashionable.
Chinese wedding dresses are so old-fashioned.
I don't like Chinese dresses, either.
It's better to wear Western dresses. Right?
Yes.
You can wear this.
I'll match a set of accessories for you.
Perfect.
Sunian will fall in love with you all over again.
There's no need. He loves me more than enough now.
Are you trying to provoke me?
Xue, your mother made you...
What did she make?
Mantou.
[*Chinese steamed bun without any filling]
I made some dough today and steamed a few mantou.
It was a successful attempt.
Just go out and buy them if you want to eat them.
It's tiring to make it yourself.
How can you compare the ones outside
with the ones your mother made?
Yes. They are different. My mother's food is the best.
Let's listen to Xue.
We'll buy the ones from outside.
We'll buy them.
- This is prettier.
- Yes.
Indeed. This is pretty.
Yes. This is pretty.
This is pretty, too.
They are all pretty.
Let's go to the shop and try it on in the afternoon.
Sure.
Hello, Mr. Zheng.
Hello.
Bi Lan. Zhang Qi's ex-girlfriend.
Ex-girlfriend?
Let's take a seat first.
Both of you are...
- Both of us are...
- Let me say it.
Although we were in a contractual relationship,
I got serious after that.
Zhang Qi broke up with me on the plane.
Also, he hid in the toilet after he broke up with me.
He refused to consult me.
The word "consult" is a bit...
Mr. Zheng, have you experienced
being laughed at by everyone on the plane?
No.
I hope you won't ever experience it in your life
because it will make you regret ever being born in this world.
Don't worry.
Both of us are friends now.
I've also realized that even though I have
a double doctorate in psychology and sociology,
I still can't avoid the fact that I'm being played by a jerk.
The word "jerk" is...
To show that I'm generous, I even flew here
and pretended to be his girlfriend.
Don't you have a seminar here?
Let me remind you.
I might regret my decision anytime.
You better be obedient.
Forgive me for bringing this up when we've just met.
Zhang Qi mentioned you to me.
I have a good impression of you.
In the future, if you have any psychological problems,
you can come to me anytime.
Are you purposely cursing him?
Why don't we make an order first?
Can I visit the kitchen?
I'm a bit of a clean freak.
I want to see if this place is hygienic.
Be my guest.
Where are you going?
Now you know how hard it's been for me, right?
Since you broke up with her, why did you bring her back?
How dare you say that?
You are getting married but I don't even have a partner.
My mother will nag me.
I'm going to the kitchen. I hope she doesn't argue with the chef.
You can order first.
It's been so long since I last visited you.
I'm sure you missed me.
[Ms. Jin Ning's Grave]
I bought you flowers.
Your favorite.
Do they smell nice?
I came here today
to say something important to you.
I'm sure you won't be happy
about the first thing.
We will be relocated soon.
We are moving to a new house.
Dongge and Shao are still living across from our house.
Tianbao and Zhang Ling aren't far away from us either.
We can visit them whenever we like.
As for the second thing,
you will be very happy to hear it.
Sunian is getting married.
Can you guess who the bride is?
It's Xue. Yes.
You guessed correctly. It's Xue.
Didn't you like Xue the most?
Both of them...
will get married tomorrow.
I saw both of them getting busy the last two days.
I thought of you especially when I saw Xue.
How nice would it be if you were around?
I've told myself.
I've been telling myself on the way
that today is a happy day and I can't cry.
I have to tell you something happy.
Don't cry.
I should be happy.
Our son is getting married.
When they have children in the future,
what names should we give them?
You are well-educated.
If you have a name in mind,
just tell me in my dream.
I brought this for you.
Wait for a while longer.
When I've seen our grandchildren,
I will go and accompany you.
I know you are lonely over there.
You are used to being taken care of.
♫ Carved into the days long gone ♫
♫ Although simplicity is plain, its vibrancy has never faded ♫
♫ Those songs in the past ♫
No. It's too slanted.
More towards this side.
It's covering the sides.
- Look at you.
- No.
Lin.
Come and take a look. Help me to take a look. Is it slanted?
- Sure.
- How is it?
Okay. That's good.
Just right.
Just right?
Seriously.
Put the lights over there.
Adjust the flowers over there.
Okay.
Siyuan, go back.
Your son is still young.
Qiaomu is there, don't worry.
Qiaomu specifically told me
to come and give you all a hand.
Have you decided on your son's name?
Yes. His name is Dou Yanxi.
My master named him.
Great name. Yanxi.
"True talents always shine through."
(From the Records of the Grand Historian)
Yes. That's it.
What a nice name.
Mr. Shao! Where do I put this flower?
Put it... Let me do it.
Go. Leave this place to me.
Sure.
Coming.
Come. Let's get to work, everyone.
I'm getting married.
I'm really getting married.
Dad, you're still awake?
My daughter is getting married tomorrow.
I'm here to see her.
What's wrong? Is something on your mind?
Suddenly, I feel afraid.
What's there to be afraid of?
I'm afraid both of us
will change after getting married.
Sunian might change.
I heard many people loved each other a lot
before they got married.
After that, they will argue every day and feel annoyed.
There will definitely be changes.
You will change. He will also change.
Both of you will go from lovers to family members.
It won't be as romantic as before.
However, both of you will face these changes calmly.
What about you and Mom?
What are the changes before and after you got married?
Your mother and I loved each other a lot before we got married.
After we got married,
it got more exciting.
How is it exciting?
She hits and scolds you every day.
Is that exciting to you?
Many things will happen when you're in a relationship.
My relationship with your mother is considered complicated.
Tell me.
Will Sunian and I become like you two
after I marry him?
Quarreling every day.
Will he find me annoying
just like how you feel annoyed by Mom?
I don't feel annoyed by your mother.
We might argue
but it won't do if I don't get to see her.
They say marriage is like a shelter.
I don't think so.
I think it's like a safety belt in a car.
Once you get in the car, it will tie you up.
But you'll realize if this person is reliable,
you'll feel safer when he ties you up tightly.
In the future, when all kinds of trouble hit you,
you will realize it's quite nice
to have this person with you.
I'm content if both of us
can be like you and my mom.
Don't even think about it.
Our relationship is one of a kind.
Look at that smug face of yours.
Is Mom asleep?
She's been busy all day. I asked her to rest early.
Xue.
Let me show you something.
What is it? Why are you being so mysterious?
[Bless]
Xue! Today is your wedding day!
Why aren't you up yet?
Mom, it's only 6:00 a.m.
Your wedding dress isn't here yet.
Call Shiyin and ask her what's going on.
Why should I call Shiyin?
I canceled the dress.
You canceled it? Are you not getting married?
What will you be wearing?
Why do you have to act on your whim?
Are you trying to make me anxious?
Mom, it's fine.
It's not like I don't have one already.
What are you wearing then?
I'm wearing this.
Thanks to Dad, I get to wear this dress made by the imperial weaver.
In the past,
this could only be worn by princesses.
Exactly.
Which designer has better craftsmanship than your mother?
No.
I think my dress
is not as pretty as the western dress.
Where's your confidence?
You're not acting like my wife.
Mom, you know which dress suits your daughter best.
Who else in this world understands me more than you?
I am wearing this dress.
You brat.
Here. Here, have some sweets.
Drink some water.
Thank you.
- Congratulations.
- Ms. Li. Ms. Liu.
- Sit down.
This is an auspicious event for all of us.
Indeed.
Do you need any more help?
No. There are so many people here.
Mr. Shao. Ms. Yu.
Shiyin, you're here.
Where's Xue?
She's in her room.
- Okay.
- Go.
- Hurry up. This way.
- Please come in.
Makeup artists.
Xue!
You're here?
It looks nice, right?
Today, I've invited
my personal makeup artist team.
What a big team.
My buddy is getting married. This is no joke.
You and Sunian will be tying the knot.
This is a once-in-a-lifetime event.
You need to be as pretty as an angel.
I'm just getting married
and not hosting a live broadcast.
You're making me so nervous.
What's there to be nervous about?
Later, there will also be a special guest.
Who is it?
A host from my channel will be your emcee.
What programs does he host?
Law programs.
Can a law program host be an emcee for the wedding?
Enough talk.
Come. Dress her up.
Where are you going? Your hair's not done yet. It's time to put on hair spray.
No. It's too greasy.
I'm telling you. Only others will make it greasy.
I'm not bluffing about my skills.
If I didn't study for a Ph.D. but hairdressing instead,
my net worth would be in the millions.
I advise you to change your career then.
Don't humiliate the academic world.
Enough. Just be content.
You may look better than me for just this day only.
Come. Lower your head.
Xue, this is perfect.
If I were a man, I'd marry you.
Xue.
Tang Ya.
- Shiyin.
- Tang Ya.
- Long time no see.
It's been a while.
Xue, you look so pretty today.
Thank you.
Where's Wu Huan?
He is helping Mr. Shao greet the guests.
I heard you two got married.
But we haven't had a ceremony yet.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I'm going out to help first.
I'll wait for your amazing appearance later.
Sure. See you later.
I thought both of you would start a fight.
It scared me.
Why should we fight?
I'm sincerely giving them my blessing.
Sit down. Don't think about nonsense.
I'm going to guard the door so they won't sneak in.
What's with the rush?
You'll be seeing her every day for the rest of your life.
It's fine not to see her now.
I have yet to see her in a wedding dress.
Groom.
- The groom is here.
- Thank you.
The groom.
- Open the door.
Wait for a while.
It's not that simple.
Open the door, I'm from the bride's family.
Say something nice first.
For example, who is this world's most beautiful woman?
Xue.
Not opening.
Of course, it's the world's most beautiful,
cutest, prettiest, and most generous Lin Shiyin's...
That's more like it.
Best friend, Shao Xue.
- Zhang Qi!
What are you doing?
Sunian, I saw the bride earlier than you.
Are you angry?
Zhang Qi, open the door.
What are you doing?
- Getting my revenge.
- What revenge?
Zheng Sunian stole my first love.
Do you think I should get my revenge?
Zhang Qi, just wait.
Sunian, I have something to say to Xue.
If you agree, knock once.
If you don't, knock twice.
Xue.
I liked you.
My affection for you was no less than Sunian's.
If I didn't give up in the past,
you might even be marrying me now.
But I want to ask you.
Have you ever...
fancied me...
even just a little?
Zhang Qi, I'm useless in this sense.
I've only fancied Sunian ever since I was little.
You are my best friend.
Our relationship is so firm.
I can't even imagine us not being buddies.
You are very important to me.
You are so important that I will rescue you first
if both you and Sunian fall into the water.
Sunian.
You hear that, Sunian?
Because Sunian can swim but you can't.
I'm good at swimming now. I don't need you to save me.
Come. Let me hug you.
Promise me. You need to be happy.
Where's Lin Shiyin?
She went to look for an ax.
Is she chopping the door or me?
She's chopping the door. I'm chopping you.
Treat her well.
Go in.
You don't say.
Xue.
♫ Missing you ♫
♫ No better place to go, Amour ♫
Sunian.
Do I look pretty?
♫ No better things to do, Amour ♫
Say something.
♫ Why don't you just find me at 3:00? ♫
This scene has appeared countless times in my dreams.
Are they the same?
♫ I love you, Lovely ♫
You were in a different outfit
and had a different expression.
They were all happy dreams.
♫ I love you, Lovely, my amour ♫
But...
no matter how happy a dream is,
♫ My beamish boy, ♫
it cannot be compared to you now.
♫ Missing you ♫
♫ Like Sunday misses sun and day ♫
♫ Want to hear the ring tone for me ♫
Friends, relatives, and neighbors.
Welcome to the clients,
Zheng Sunian and Shao Xue's wedding ceremony.
The deep and quiet alley...
Clients?
Is this emcee reliable?
- It's been hidden for years.
- He is Shiyin's friend.
He waited patiently to protect his love.
He searched everywhere but the person he searched for was unexpectedly...
Is this emcee at the wrong place?
- After more than 20 years...
- What do you mean?
What is he talking about?
It's not bad. It's quite funny.
All right. Let's look at the end of the red carpet.
♫ I love you, Lovely, amour ♫
♫ Never feel my life alone, ♫
♫ My beamish boy, ♫
♫ For me ♫
Mr. Shao.
You're still calling me that?
Dad.
How nice.
Sunian.
Today, I'm handing Xue over to you.
Life is hard,
cherish each other.
Dad.
Don't worry.
I won't worry.
You're so pretty, Xue!
Xue.
A long time ago,
Master told me...
to find a girl like a hibiscus flower.
I didn't understand at first.
Until I first saw you...
wearing a cheongsam and walking towards me...
Sunian.
I suddenly understood.
You are like the hibiscus that blooms in my life.
I always thought you needed my protection
so I worked hard to grow up.
But actually,
you have always been in front of me...
while guiding me forward.
The first step of growth is to reap what you sow.
No. I mean being independent.
Think about it. Doing it yourself. How exciting is it?
You've violated the three big taboos at once.
You are the person who brought me out of sadness
>when I was at my saddest and most helpless moment.
Don't keep your sadness inside.
Just let it all out.
I'll lend you my shoulder.
I also want to leave something to the world.
I hope what I left behind
can be seen by the people of the world after a hundred years.
No matter what you choose,
I will also be by your side and accompany you.
You were the one...
who gave me the courage...
to become my ideal self.
You accompanied me when I was growing up in the past.
Now, let me...
grow old with you for the rest of our lives.
All right?
Sunian.
Actually, I was quite scared
during the days before the wedding.
I was afraid...
that we would change after we got married.
I was afraid that you would change.
But when we were
holding our hands and walking toward here,
I suddenly didn't feel afraid anymore.
I know we will change.
We will only talk about our daily lives,
we will nitpick,
we will argue because of something minor.
We will get angry because of each other's changes.
But we will be together for such a long time.
I believe...
change will only bring our hearts closer.
In the past,
I didn't understand...
what was so nice about growing old hand in hand.
I always thought...
it would be so boring
to stay in one place with only one person
forever.
But I finally understand now.
Because even if I have the world's excitement,
it's not as good...
as you being by my side and accompanying me.
Thanks to our Channel Manager:
💘🗿pattycdc_143🔢📜
Thanks to our Chief Segmenter: 💘🗿bjohnsonwon🔢📜
Thanks to our Chief Editor: 💘🗿kakashiandme🔢📜
Thanks to our Segmenters Team: 💘🗿sabrinafair, karenperez, beckarooney_497, dircempires_312, addictedtobooks, nmelova, porkypine90_261, ma_xt_26🔢📜
Thanks to the 💘🗿Moderators of all Languages ​​🔢📜
Thanks to the Team Moderators:
💘🗿 ________________ 🔢📜
Thanks to Our Team:
💘🗿 ___________________________ 🔢📜
- Mom! Dad!
- Mr. Sun. Dad. Come here, hurry up!
Let's go.
Come.
Can I sit here?
- Sit down.
- Okay
Okay, look at the camera.
Three, two, one.
[Seven Years Later]
Dou Yanxi. Zheng Anning.
Why did both of you run around again?
It's fine, Miss. My father is working inside.
My father is also working inside.
You still can't run around as you wish. What if you get lost?
I'm taking all of you to visit the Restoration Department. All right?
- All right!
- Come.
Slowly.
Let's go.
[The End]
♫ As I traverse this path without minding it ♫
♫ My memory does all the hard work for me ♫
♫ All the memories are embedded deep within my heart ♫
♫ The past I've been hiding from year after year ♫
♫ Carved into the days long gone ♫
♫ Although simplicity is plain, its vibrancy has never faded ♫
♫ Those songs in the past ♫
♫ They had accompanied me through everything ♫
♫ Singing about the stubbornness of our youth ♫
♫ Using this song to boost our courage as we sing ♫
♫ Please don't cry because you have me ♫
♫ Until I saw the bustling city ♫
♫ Until I realized that it was once within my reach ♫
♫ I was this sober once but I still did the same thing ♫
♫ As days go by, I wish to forget ♫
♫ But unknowingly, I remember them again ♫
♫ I remember the deep feelings that were long gone ♫
♫ Within those simple days ♫
♫ Those songs in the past, they had accompanied me ♫
♫ As I regretted our parting during our youth ♫
♫ Using this song, this song belongs to us ♫
♫ Please don't cry again ♫
♫ And don't ask when I'll return ♫