♫ The bicycle bell rings and takes me back to
the alley I saw in my dream ♫
♫  I invite the sunlight to traverse the morning
fog and breeze with me ♫
♫ Riding my bike, trying to catch up to the fleeting youth ♫
♫ The Forbidden City made from red walls and
encaustic tiles in my memory ♫
♫ Unlike the hustle and bustle of everyday life ♫
♫ It's quaint and peaceful ♫
♫ Throughout the ordinary and extraordinary four seasons  ♫
♫ Some words are just like seeds ♫
♫ Growing in our youth, changing our future ♫
♫ Who can understand the silence in our hearts? ♫
♫ We once thought our dreams were somewhere far away ♫
♫ We wanted to grow up as soon as possible ♫
♫ Some waited while some traveled ♫
♫ How far away is our future? ♫
♫ Now, each of us ♫
♫ Has gone through a lot ♫
♫ We have grown up ♫
♫ Finally confirming that love is faith ♫
♫ There's no need to wander anymore ♫
♫ The questions we asked back then ♫
♫ Have been answered gradually ♫
♫ Through the passing of time ♫
♫ Who had pursued their dreams and left no regrets behind? ♫
♫ Returning to this place in the end ♫
♫ Returning ♫
♫ To the place that I've always loved  ♫
♫ We once thought our dreams were somewhere far away ♫
♫ We wanted to grow up as soon as possible ♫
♫ Finally confirming that love is faith ♫
♫ There's no need to wander anymore ♫
[Memory of Efncaustic Tile]
[Adapted from Beifeng Sanbaili's original novel "Memory of Encaustic Tile"]
[Episode 14]
[It's the Thought that Counts]
Order whatever you like. It's my treat today.
I only have a few bowls of mutton soup left.
Mutton soup is fine. It's been so long since I had it.
The smell is so tantalizing.
Give us four bowls of mutton soup then. One for takeaway.
One bowl is enough for me. You don't need to do any takeaway.
You're thinking too highly of yourself. It's for Qiaomu.
Siyuan, how's your relationship with Qiaomu going?
It's pretty good.
[Traditional taste, mutton soup,mixed mutton soup, clear soup, mutton]
Seems like Siyuan did the right thing by choosing to stay.
Back then, Siyuan did hesitate.
Thank you.
Back then,
I did hesitate.
Thank you.
It's because my university coursemates
were doing so well out there.
All of them were at the top. They did very well.
Some of them were academicians. Some of them were researchers.
Some of them were businessmen. Some of them got their Ph.D.
When I looked at myself, I was only tinkering with junk.
I thought I would never be successful. Right?
But after that, when I changed my perspective,
people in our industry have to be like this.
We have to be able to withstand loneliness and a poor life.
If not, you won't be able to get good at this trade.
Maybe I'm talking too much.
You guys might not be able to understand me.
But I'm sure you guys will understand me in the future.
Eat up. Finish it and go back to rest.
Here.
Be careful, it's hot.
I didn't expect Siyuan's inner thoughts to be that deep.
Siyuan possesses the craftsman's spirit.
The craftsman's spirit?
A true craftsman is willing to exchange their current moment for eternity.
Just like Mr. Sun and Mr. Luo, the expert craftsmen.
They have never fretted about the amount of money they earn.
What they truly cared about was the things they had done.
I respect them.
I wish to be someone like them.
Just like how I idolize Ms. Jin Ning.
Isn't this the most handsome guy in the universe
and Zhao Ling'er's boyfriend, Li Xiaoyao?
Do you guys still treat me as a friend?
Why didn't you guys invite me when you guys went to visit Mr. Sun?
It's because Wang Haoran pissed us off this morning.
We'll surely invite you next time.
How many times have you said that?
Since you guys are so busy,
I guess there's no need for us to gather in the future.
Did you need to resort to that?
Would you be happy if the two of us went out as a pair?
Don't be angry.
At most... At most, we'll apologize to you.
Sorry, Zhang Qi!
Sorry.
Don't do this again.
I will forgive you guys since I'm magnanimous.
Xue! Don't you know what time it is?
Must I shout for you before you will come back?
I'll return home first.
- Hurry up.
- Coming!
Playing is the only thing you know.
You two should return home as well. It's getting late.
By the way, how's Wu Huan today?
I consoled him on our way home. I sent him back.
After that, I went to find you guys, but I couldn't find you guys.
But today, Lin Shiyin was too much.
Huan's love for her was in vain.
If I were Wu Huan, I would surely never talk to her again.
If you truly like someone, you wouldn't leave her no matter what she does.
If so...
If so,
do you have someone you like?
What about you?
You should come up with your own answer before you ask someone else a question.
Sleep early.
I heard that.
- Hello?
- Ms. Yu, it's me.
Shiyin?
Can you ask Xue to pick up the phone?
I'll call her for you.
Xue.
Xue, you have a call.
Hello?
- Xue.
- Give me a moment.
Mom. Dad. Why don't you two go to sleep first?
Give me some privacy.
I'm watching TV. I cannot hear anything.
Wait.
- What are you doing? The show isn't finished yet.
- Do you know what time it is? Time to sleep.
I haven't finished that episode.
Look at the time. Time to sleep.
Xue, you should sleep early as well.
- Remember to turn off the lights.
- Okay.
Let's go. Hurry.
Hello?
Xue.
Are you still angry at me?
I'm not angry. I was just disappointed.
Disappointed?
What do you mean by disappointed?
Shiyin, I remember I told you
not to hurt people who are truly kind to you.
It's hard for me to accept the fact that you treated Wu Huan like that.
Xue, you may not know,
ever since the dance incident, I've been doubting myself.
And I finally met someone.
I finally met a group that could prove my superiority when I mingled with them.
But they were looking down on Wu Huan. I was just saying that.
What if one day they look down on me?
Why would someone look down on you?
I don't know why they look down on Wu Huan.
But Wu Huan told me that
on the first day you two became friends, everyone was laughing at him.
Only you... Only you were the only one who took his hand and finished the red carpet.
I always thought that this was a wonderful thing.
I don't know why you ended up like this.
I didn't change.
I have never treated him as my friend.
I took his hand back then because I wanted people to think that I was kind.
You have Zhang Qi and Zheng Sunian by your side.
You will never know how I feel.
What if Wu Huan was the one following you all day?
Would you still be as happy?
I hope what you are saying is all of that out of spite.
Because I believe that my friend, Lin Shiyin,
is a girl that is truly kind.
If you mean what you said just now,
let's stop being friends.
Wang Haoran was right.
You guys are together.
You guys don't take me seriously at all.
[Peking Union Medical College]
Mr. Sun, I'm sure you have learned your lesson. Right?
If you're hospitalized because of smoking again, I'll ignore you.
- Really?
- Really.
Don't scare me.
Mr. Sun, congratulations on being discharged.
- Mr. Luo.
- Hold this.
You are quite somebody.
You're only here when I'm being discharged?
You should consider yourself lucky that I'm here today.
When I was hospitalized,
I couldn't find someone to pick a fight with.
I do want to pick a fight with you.
But I'm afraid you'll die of anger if you lose to me.
We've been fighting for several decades.
- Have I ever lost to you?
- Fine.
Be honest with me.
Did you miss me when you were hospitalized?
Did you?
I'm asking you a question.
I'm asking you if you missed me.
- Did he miss me?
- He did. He missed you very much.
Wait up.
This Sun... You...
Listen up. Next time, you need to be careful when you smoke.
Did you hear me?
This part of your lung will be ruined because of your smoking habit.
[Teaching Building 1]
Why do you look so exhausted?
Did you stay up all night to do your revision?
Just forget it.
Now, I'm taking math tutoring on the one hand,
and practicing Spoken English on the other.
Both my physical and mental power have been depleted.
If this continues, I'll go crazy.
Why don't you discuss it with your mother?
Maybe you can skip the math tutoring for now.
I dare not do so.
It was hard for me to convince her to let me study overseas.
Now, I have to obey every instruction of her.
If so, is the path you take safe enough to travel back home?
Of course, it's safe.
You need to be more careful.
I heard that many students were mugged on their way home.
Why don't you find someone to pick you up?
What about Zhang Qi and Zheng Sunian?
One of them is in his senior year and the other one is in the competition class. Our schedules are different.
Besides, I'm a strong man.
No one dares to mug me.
Xue, you're truly the boldest girl
I have ever met.
Bold?
Is that even a compliment?
Definitely.
If so, I'll protect you from now on.
Fu Qiaomu. Fu Qiaomu!
Mr. Sun, I'll be out for a second.
Go ahead.
Mr. Tong.
Were you looking for me?
This bouquet is for you.
Don't misunderstand.
It's not from me.
There was a chap by the entrance. He told me to pass it to you.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Were you busy?
Qiaomu.
Ms. Yu. Moshui.
This bouquet is huge. It looks gorgeous.
Did your boyfriend give this to you?
No, he's not my boyfriend.
He's sending a bouquet like this when he's not your boyfriend?
You can have it if you like it.
I dare not accept this.
I'll make a move first.
Youngsters nowadays are really generous, huh?
It was a huge bouquet.
It must've been expensive.
Precisely. I'm sure it's not cheap.
That is a huge bouquet.
It's in the way.
I think it looks great.
What's so great about it?
They'll wilt when the weather gets cold.
Where are you going?
I'm going to water my flowers.
You want to water them with boiling water? They'll wilt even faster.
Look at how sour you look.
Even though you're so near to her,
you can't even win her heart.
Mr. Sun, it's not entirely my fault.
Look at that bouquet.
He's sending her a bouquet of roses without any reason.
I'm sure he's an indecent guy.
Who would do so without any reason? What are you saying?
You don't need a reason to make a girl happy.
- But...
- You're so dumb.
Mr. Sun, do you like roses as well?
Stop trying to be witty.
Get me the brush.
It's rare for you to be this hard-working.
So a student from the competition class has graced us with his presence. This is such an honor.
I guess so. Prepare a red carpet for me before I come next time.
What's the matter?
I'm here because I have a surprise for you.
What is it?
I won't spoil the surprise first.
Just look forward to it tonight.
Hurry up! If not, I'll dwell on it the entire day.
To put it precisely, my mother has a surprise for you.
She bought a new computer.
She's going to give you her old computer. Really?
Do you think I'm joking?
Zhang Qi, I love you so much!
What are you guys doing?
You were following me again.
This is the classroom.
I know you think he's not good enough for you.
But you should mind your behavior as well.
How could you say that?
I heard from your class teacher
that you've been on a roll lately.
You won several prizes in a row.
So you've heard about it?
You see, I guess I'm too exceptional.
I can't even keep a low profile even if I want to.
You should be more modest and prudent. Go back to your class.
Even though I've been working so hard,
I can't even get a smile from you.
This is heartbreaking.
Go back.
Xue, see you.
This brat...
Xue.
For last month's test,
the essay you wrote based on the theme of youth
was circulated within the Language Division.
- Really?
- Of course.
You used a great quote.
"Youth is the state
where we haven't achieved something we want.
It's the state of eagerness and longing.
It's the state which contains possibility."
Not many high school students have read the works of Yukio Mishima.
An amazing lady gave me the book.
She has plenty of them.
You have a unique view of youth.
I hope you can keep up the good work. Okay.
Go back now.
Dad? How come it's you?
What's wrong? Am I not welcomed?
Come. I bought them.
Xue.
Xue?
Why are you standing there?
Return to your room and finish your homework.
Just ignore me.
- Coming!
- Come and help us out!
- Hurry.
- Go and help my mother.
Ms. Zhang Lin, you're finally here.
This is a lot of metal junk.
This is so heavy.
What metal junk? This is the CPU.
Do you think I'm really outdated?
I surely know that this is a computer.
I used this to search for information when I was in the Restoration Department.
Really?
Dongge.
Dongge! Hurry!
- Zhang Ling, you're here?
- Ge.
This...
What's going on?
I bought a new computer.
I wasn't using this anyway.
That's why I thought of giving it to you.
But after I thought about it,
I'm sure you won't accept it if I tell you beforehand.
That's why I brought this here directly.
My dear, you mustn't sell it as junk.
It's a treasure. How could we sell it away? Ms. Zhang Ling.
I forgot to bring the mouse and keyboard. Let me go get it.
- Let me tag along.
- Okay.
Look at you.
You moved such a heavy thing all the way here.
Besides, this is very precious.
I can't accept this.
That's enough of you. I've been using it for quite some time.
It's not that valuable anymore.
It's not cheap either.
You should bring it to Zhongguancun.
Maybe you can sell this for 5,000 or 6,000 yuan.
You want me to bring this to Zhongguancun? It's too troublesome.
Just let your daughter use it for now.
You can buy a new one for her when she goes to university, all right?
Think about it.
Will she be able to get into a university when she has this?
She'll play with this every day. My goodness.
Listen up. This computer is quite old.
It's too slow for her to play games with it.
She can only use this to surf the Internet and search for information.
And many famous teachers have started to teach their students online.
In the future, online lessons will become more and more common.
This thing is actually capable of that?
Not bad. Not bad at all.
I was planning to register an account on QQ.
I wanted to chat with other people.
With whom?
What? Are you tired of chatting with me?
I... I was planning to create a QQ group.
You'll be the group leader.
[Who's the cutest person in our family?]
You're pretty fast.
Of course. I got a perfect score
for computer class when I was in junior high.
You're only good at learning nonsense like this.
What do you mean by nonsense?
You can give it a try if you think you're that good.
Fine.
- Get up.
- Come.
These are the hands of an expert embroiderer.
They're swift.
[Shao]
Seems she is typing with just one finger.
I'm just unfamiliar with the keyboard.
If I were familiar with it,
you won't be able to see them moving.
[Shao Xue]
[Shao Xue is naughty]
Morning.
- Morning.
- You're so early today.
It's from me.
I guessed so.
No one else would give me this kind of present.
I went to the flower market
and bought this especially for you.
The shop owner said this plant was easy to keep.
And it can live for a long time. Do you like it?
Be careful! It'll prick your fingers.
How about this? I'll find another spot for you.
Don't. I want to put it over here.
It can protect me.
- Morning.
- Morning
Qiaomu doesn't want this bouquet?
That's right. She said she'd leave it here.
This child.
She gave it away even though she just received it.
That means she's uninterested in that guy.
Honestly. I did see the guy.
He was waiting for Qiaomu in front of the entrance.
He looked pretty ordinary to me.
Yeah, I met him once.
He looked pretty awkward.
He was foppish.
Siyuan is better.
But Siyuan is not good at talking.
We need to give him a push when we have the chance.
If we let him do it alone, he'll surely ruin it.
What do you think?
Youngsters nowadays have their own ideas.
Our opinions don't matter to them.
You're right. It was different in our times.
We had to listen to our parents and the matchmaker.
The marriage was already over when we still had no idea about what had happened.
Pass that to me.
It's fine if other people talk about this.
But you? You don't have the right to say that.
Your legendary story is almost like the plot of a drama.
Why is it about me again?
In just a flash, he and I have been through so many years together.
It's pretty good.
What? Do you want him to buy you a bouquet as well?
He doesn't dare to do so.
He shouldn't waste our money like that.
Morning.
Dongge, I'll leave your breakfast here.
Whose bouquet is it?
Morning.
Dongge, your husband is really fortunate.
I'm the fortunate one.
Who's there?
Su-Sunian!
What's the matter?
I think someone is following me!
I don't think there's anyone there.
Maybe it's because I was too nervous.
Let's go.
Did you hurt your leg?
I sprained my ankle when I ran just now.
Come, have a seat.
Slowly.
It hurts.
I think there's a sprain. Let me carry you on my back.
No.
Why not?
We used to do this all the time when we were young.
I just finished my checkup.
I've gained three kilograms of weight.
Come.
Maybe the scale in our school is faulty.
Come, let me measure your weight.
I...
I think we should forget it.
The scale is pretty accurate.
I hate you.
Sunian, why were you here?
My class ended early today. I went to your house.
Ms. Yu said you hadn't finished your tutoring yet.
That's why I thought of picking you up.
Why were you looking for me?
Can't I look for you without reason?
You're a senior-year student now. I don't dare to waste your time.
But luckily, you were there.
If not, I think I'd have been on tenterhooks all the way home.
Are you still scared?
I feel much safer with you around.
Sunian, I think studying is exhausting.
Why aren't you exhausted from all the studying?
I do get exhausted as well.
Really?
That's the reason I came to look for you.
- You don't feel exhausted when you look for me?
- Yeah.
But why?
Because you have an energetic voice.
I feel energized when I listen to your voice.
[Residents Committee Activity Center]
When do you go to tutoring again?
You won't need to be scared when I'm keeping you company.
Xue?
I was looking for you two.
She fell asleep.
I heard that someone has been following you after school.
Why don't I go to work later? I can send you home first.
No, thanks. I'm afraid of nothing.
Zhang Qi!
Huanhuan, you can head back first.
What's with that expression? The emperor is right in front of you.
- Why were you looking for me, my son?
- How dare you to take advantage of me?
I heard from Sunian that someone has been following you after school.
This item is very effective.
When you pull it, the entire village will hear you.
It's that amazing?
But of course. When I'm around, no perverts will be able to do as they please.
If so, can you chase away the pervert right in front of me?
Do you know how far away the competition class is?
I came all the way to give you this buzzer, but you're not grateful to me at all.
Thank you very much.
Why don't I reward you with a silk banner after I chase away the pervert?
What will you write on top of it?
The friend of all maidens?
Sunian!
Why do you look so happy when you see him?
You should take a good look at yourself then.
Sunian, why are you here?
Sunian, I didn't expect you to have this kind of hobby.
Sunian, are you too stressed out lately? Did you not rest well?
You have to rest more often.
My mother told me to make this.
Is it for me?
I think this is the most girlish item among all the items Shao Xue has.
You don't need to turn it on during the day.
Okay. Thank you guys so much.
Tonight, I'll ready my blades.
I'll see who's daring enough to tail me.
I'll return to class first.
Thank you. Goodbye.
I'll go as well.
Today, let's talk about argumentative essays.
What are these?
These are the self-defense items given to me by Sunian and Zhang Qi.
What about this cat?
Zhang Qi said it was a buzzer.
How do you use this?
I don't know. Let me study it for a moment.
Shao Xue, what are you doing?
This!
What's going on?
This isn't mine!
Principal?
[Good at Guiding, Virtuous, Renowned for One's Virtue]
[Strive to Produce Great Students]
This is outrageous!
Principal, I didn't do it on purpose.
Principal, Shao Xue has always been an obedient child.
I can guarantee that this was purely an accident.
Where did you get the buzzer?
I bought it as a self-defense item.
Sorry, Principal. Principal, I know my fault now.
I was the one who gave her the buzzer. It has nothing to do with her.
Weren't you in the competition class?
Class is in session right now.
Your time is precious!
Why are you here to mess around?
What about her time then? Isn't her time precious?
I can't just let you wrong her.
What are you saying?
I'm speaking the truth.
I'm sorry, Principal. It's all my fault.
I will write a self-reflection report.
I will never commit the same mistake again.
Please forgive me this time.
Principal, this is her first offense.
Please forgive her.
Luckily, it didn't cause a huge mess.
Go back and write a self-reflection report.
Don't do this again.
Thank you, Principal. I will surely study hard to repay you and the school.
Thank you. Let's go.
It could've been resolved right after he told me off.
You almost made the situation worse.
I just wanted to defend you. Was I wrong?
I didn't say you were wrong.
But you need to change your temper somehow.
Lord Zhang Qi, it's all thanks to you. You tried to uphold justice for me.
If you didn't come in, I think he would've lectured me for another half an hour.
I think he'd lecture me for at least one hour.
Your buzzer was confiscated?
Forget it.
With an IQ like yours, I'm sure you didn't understand how to use it.
Yeah, you're the genius here.
You can return to the competition class then.
What will you do for tonight?
Do you dare to go back alone?
Do you need me to send you back?
No, thanks. I have the flashlight that Sunian had given to me.
What can you do with a flashlight?
Can you shine the pervert to death with it?
If I can't shine him to death, I'll whack him with the flashlight.
I'll make a move now. Don't worry.
Don't try anything funny!
I'm armed!
[Sunian is here]
Don't tell me it was you all along...
You scared me every time.
How about this? I'll make you a deal.
I'll treat you to some sausages.
But you're not allowed to scare me in the future.
Here you go.
Cheers. From now on, we're friends.
Good baby.
This? I'll give this to you next time.
See you.
[Sunian is here]
Hey.
I can actually summon the person itself with this?
What are you thinking?
[Fruits and vegetables, grains, oil, and non-staple food. Goods Sold Here]
Boss, get us the bill.
Sunian,
- Boss.
- why are you here at this time?
Don't you have night classes to attend?
I felt uncomfortable. I had applied for leave.
Uncomfortable? What's wrong?
I have a sore throat.
A sore throat?
Let me check.
Stop it.
If only I could summon you with this flashlight.
And it's best if I'm the only one who can see you.
That way, I won't need to worry about my exam.
What are you thinking?
Where did you get this?
[Sunian is here]
Have some pomelo.
Why is your name on top of it?
You must've been mistaken.
That's impossible.
Turn it on and show it to me.
Mom, the drama is going to start soon.
Fine then.
No girl will be happy about receiving
a gray and dull flashlight.
This isn't a gift.
If you can decorate it with some pink ribbons,
the result might be different.
Coincidentally, I have some pink ribbons with me.
I'm not using them anyway.
I wonder if someone else wants to use them.
Call me your lovely mother.
My lovely mother.
Good boy. Wait for me. I'll bring it here.
Where did you get it?
Since there are no crooks around,
you should throw it away.
It's mine now.
Don't worry. I'll repay you with another gift.
A gift?
I've already bought it online.
It was my first time shopping online. It means a lot to me.
What did you buy?
It's a secret. You'll know it by then.
[Taobao]
Have you finished your homework?
You should stop playing.
I was just checking the shipment date for the things I had bought.
You bought something online?
I'll show you something new next time.
So you just need to click on the things and someone will deliver them to our house?
I'm sure this is a scam.
You're too outdated.
There's a thing calledparcel delivery right now.
If you make an order online, they'll send the items to your doorstep after a few days.
They'll send the items to our doorstep after a few days?
Youngsters nowadays are into nonsense like this.
What if they don't send the items to you after you transfer the money to them?
Isn't that a scam?
Comrade Yu Dongge, we need to be courageous enough to accept new things.
Just read the newspaper with me.
Enough. Stop nagging.
Xue, let me warn you.
You mustn't upload our home address
and your ID card number onto the internet.
This is very risky. If the scammers have our home address, they will...
- Mom.
- Our house will...
- Have a seat.
You loved Cantonese songs, right? Let me play one for you.
How did you know?
Your drawer was filled with cassette tapes.
You couldn't bear to play them when I wanted to listen to them.
What are you saying?
I just couldn't play them after winding them up.
♫ I don't care if it's right or wrong ♫
♫ I won't allow you to live alone ♫
♫ Because I love you ♫
What?
We ran out of salt. We'll go and get some salt.
You can get them yourself.
♫ But I won't back down ♫
♫ I just want to hug you ♫
♫ And pass the times together ♫
Mr. Qian, get us two bottles of yogurt.
Sure.
I thought we were getting salt?
Have a seat.
Let your mother enjoy that song alone for a moment.
What's so special about that song that she has to listen to it alone?
When your mother was young, she listened to this song
whenever she was facing hardships.
It had accompanied her then.
Mom had actually faced hardships before?
I heard that my grandfather was a cab driver in Beijing.
They were pretty well-off.
She met you after that, right?
What kind of hardships did she face?
So there's a story behind it?
Tell me about it.
All the other children know about the stories of their parents.
I'm the only one in the dark. Tell me about it.
"OLD SONG" - Featuring artist: Ma Di
♫ As I traverse this path without minding it ♫
♫ My memory does all the hard work for me ♫
♫ All the memories are embedded deep within my heart ♫
♫ The past I've been hiding from year after year ♫
♫ Carved into the days long gone ♫
♫ Although simplicity is plain, its vibrancy has never faded ♫
♫ Those songs in the past ♫
♫ They had accompanied me through everything ♫
♫ Singing about the stubbornness of our youth ♫
♫ Using this song to boost our courage as we sing ♫
♫ Please don't cry because you have me ♫
♫ Until I saw the bustling city ♫
♫ Until I realized that it was once within my reach ♫
♫ I was this sober once but I still did the same thing ♫
♫ As days go by, I wish to forget ♫
♫ But unknowingly, I remember them again ♫
♫ I remember the deep feelings that were long gone ♫
♫ Within those simple days ♫
♫ Those songs in the past, they had accompanied me ♫
♫ As I regretted our parting during our youth ♫
♫ Using this song, this song belongs to us ♫
♫ Please don't cry again ♫
♫ And don't ask when I'll return ♫