♫ The bicycle bell rings and takes me back to
the alley I saw in my dream ♫
♫  I invite the sunlight to traverse the morning
fog and breeze with me ♫
♫ Riding my bike, trying to catch up to the fleeting youth ♫
♫ The Forbidden City made from red walls and
encaustic tiles in my memory ♫
♫ Unlike the hustle and bustle of everyday life ♫
♫ It's quaint and peaceful ♫
♫ Throughout the ordinary and extraordinary four seasons  ♫
♫ Some words are just like seeds ♫
♫ Growing in our youth, changing our future ♫
♫ Who can understand the silence in our hearts? ♫
♫ We once thought our dreams were somewhere far away ♫
♫ We wanted to grow up as soon as possible ♫
♫ Some waited while some traveled ♫
♫ How far away is our future? ♫
♫ Now, each of us ♫
♫ Has gone through a lot ♫
♫ We have grown up ♫
♫ Finally confirming that love is faith ♫
♫ There's no need to wander anymore ♫
♫ The questions we asked back then ♫
♫ Have been answered gradually ♫
♫ Through the passing of time ♫
♫ Who had pursued their dreams and left no regrets behind? ♫
♫ Returning to this place in the end ♫
♫ Returning ♫
♫ To the place that I've always loved  ♫
♫ We once thought our dreams were somewhere far away ♫
♫ We wanted to grow up as soon as possible ♫
♫ Finally confirming that love is faith ♫
♫ There's no need to wander anymore ♫
[Memory of Encaustic Tile]
[Adapted from Beifeng Sanbaili's original novel "Memory of Encaustic Tile"]
[Episode 20]
[Never Lost in Youth]
Let's have instant-boiled mutton tomorrow by the alley. My treat!
You're treating all of us?
- Oh, right.
- Instant-boiled mutton.
Invite everyone in the Restoration Division, too.
We haven't seen them in a while. A reunion is long overdue.
All right. Let's go.
Stop hiding here.
Have they all gone home?
Your neighbors are all happy for you.
Don't treat them as your enemy. Let's go.
My misery is the fuel of their happiness.
Oh, my Little Lord. Act nice and friendly for me tomorrow.
- See you, Ms. Zhang Ling.
- Come.
- See you.
- Bye.
Having a genius son isn't all good and dandy.
Blame your own genes. Don't be jealous.
Did she not inherit another half of her genes from you?
I feel sorry for our baby girl.
Your baby girl is here, you know.
Xue, you don't need to be a genius.
It's troublesome. And expensive, too.
You need to treat everyone to instant-boiled mutton.
[Liuli Restaurant, In Celebration of Zhang Qi's Admission to USTC]
[The Pride of the Alley]
Congratulations, Zhang Qi.
Thank you. Please go inside.
Zhang Qi. Congratulations! You've done so well.
I knew you were a smart kid since you were little.
You didn't say that when you complained to Zhang Ling.
Mischievous kids are the brightest.
Go inside, please.
- Go inside.
- Sure.
- Congratulations, Zhang Qi.
- Congratulations.
- Go in, please.
- Okay.
Why don't you go in?
My mother asked me to stay here to greet the customers.
Cheer up! Today is your big day, Zhang Qi.
Congratulations, Pride of the Alley.
Spare me, please.
Since last night, I have been pestered by several madams.
They asked me to tutor their children.
One even brought her son to my home
and asked me if her son looked like math material.
I told her with that kind of mentality, her son most probably will fail math.
Then, I took a beating from my mother.
Now, I just think being ordinary is the best thing ever.
When you say that, you sound as irritating
as those rich people who rant about their wanting to lead a normal life.
Just go inside.
Let's go in, Sunian.
Work properly!
Order whatever you want.
Not bad, Zhang Qi.
You were recommended for admission to USTC.
- Congratulations.
- Please go in.
- Congratulations, Zhang Qi.
- Thanks.
[Private Event Today]
Six lamb slices and six beef slices, please.
All right.
Now that all of you are here, allow me to say something.
Okay.
Everyone here is my relative and my neighbor.
All of you came here to celebrate my son's minor achievement.
For that, I feel grateful.
All these years, you have taken good care of me.
If you need my help in the future, just ask away.
A toast to everyone.
Eat and drink to your heart's content.
- Okay!
- Thanks.
- Come.
- Cheers.
- Congratulations.
Come!
Sit down. There's no need to stand up.
What's the matter, Qiaomu?
Are you upset?
Me?
Why don't you ask him?
How is it going, kids?
Are you enjoying the food?
I am.
I'm exhausted. Everything tastes bland.
Fine, Zhang Qi. Don't eat then.
Save food for others.
Siyuan. Qiaomu.
Why didn't you two eat anything?
You don't like it?
- No, that's not it.
- No, it's good.
Siyuan, I heard that Qiaomu found you a job.
How is it?
Not good.
I like this place. I don't want to go anywhere else.
The youth nowadays have such a different mindset.
Siyuan, you have the education and the qualification.
You can work in any big company.
It will be better than doing a dead-end job. Don't you think?
- Zhang Qi, take care of our guests.
- Come, eat.
- Eat more.
- Enjoy yourselves.
Indeed. I asked for so many favors and finally found him a job.
And he turned it down just like that.
Master and Sirs, I still have work to do so I have to leave now.
Leave after the meal.
No, thanks. I can grab something on the way.
We just put the meat in the pot.
Zhang Qi, I'll treat you another day.
It's okay, Siyuan. Go back to your work.
Qiaomu, I'll boil the meat for you.
Where were you? What took you so long?
I went shopping, Mom.
Dig in then.
What were you doing?
I am taking broadcasting classes in secret.
Why in secret?
I want to major in broadcasting but my parents don't want me to.
Keep it between us for now.
Congratulations, Zhang Qi.
It's no big deal.
Qiaomu, I saw Siyuan when I was coming in.
Why did he leave so soon?
Because he can.
Zhang Qi, I'll be leaving too.
Go ahead, Qiaomu. I'll be fine.
Master, I'll be going now.
What happened to Qiaomu?
She's having a squabble with Siyuan.
Go keep her company.
Save some for me.
I will.
I should go check on her, too.
Just the three of us now.
Why did everyone leave when I'd just arrived?
No one likes you, perhaps.
Qiaomu, don't be sad.
Siyuan was a bit harsh today.
He brought me to his classmate reunion.
His classmates are now either businessmen or technical experts.
He was clearly upset that day.
So I wondered if he was envious of them or had some other thoughts.
His degree is pretty good.
He can get a pretty high starting salary if he works for a big company.
So I asked around to see if there was a job vacancy.
I finally found him a tech job,
but he just decided that he wouldn't take it.
Siyuan is a traditional man.
If it was you who found him the job, he would feel too ashamed to take it.
I asked Master.
He said that Siyuan was struggling to get by.
I was doing this for him.
I know. Whatever you do, Qiaomu,
it's for Siyuan's own good.
I guess I'm too meddlesome.
Look at the mess now.
I pissed off everyone.
Why are you all here?
Master, why are you out here?
Just to get some air.
It's more like you miss your cigarette and you are not allowed to smoke inside.
Come. Let's all go to my place for some tea.
Thanks, Master.
Tell me then.
What do you like about Siyuan?
I don't know.
Not knowing is right.
If you can list out the reasons about why you like him,
then it's just business, not love.
You found him a job out of kindness.
But do you know what he truly desires?
I'll let you in on a secret.
Before you came here,
Siyuan was pondering about whether he should stay or not.
He couldn't make up his mind.
But the day he met you,
he suddenly came to a decision.
I know about that!
He thought to himself,
if the girl he likes wants to stay here,
then he has no reason to leave.
After Siyuan decided to stay,
he faced a lot of pressure.
His parents didn't want him to stay.
They wanted him to find a better job and earn more money
so that he could live a comfortable life in Beijing.
But after considering everything,
he still thought that all those things
didn't hold a candle to the metal scraps in his hands.
That's what he's like; very stubborn.
That's what you like about him, right?
Master, why did I fall in love with an idiot?
When I was young, I was an idiot too.
This is my late wife.
You have never mentioned her.
She passed away long ago.
It was so long ago
that I don't feel like mentioning it.
My late wife
never had one good day with me.
There was this auction house who came to me.
They offered me a high salary to be their antique appraiser.
Back then, my son wanted to study abroad.
We were trying to find the funds.
I was in a dilemma and I didn't know what to do.
So I came back and asked my wife.
She told me
to do what I valued the most.
And so I thought hard.
What exactly was it that I valued the most?
If I became their antique appraiser,
I would earn a lot of money
but that would be the ceiling of my pursuit.
If I stayed in the restoration workshop,
I could still leave something for this world.
I thought that had more value.
So I stayed.
Qiaomu, are you still mad at Siyuan?
Yes.
He stayed here for you.
Why are you still mad at him?
I'm mad because he kept everything to himself.
You didn't have your lunch. Why don't you grab a bite at my place?
I'm good. You two have fun.
I'll go back now.
Have a safe trip.
- See you.
- Bye
I didn't know Mr. Sun was part of such an amazing story
when he was young.
Xue.
I want to visit a place.
Where?
I am Aisin-Gioro Shaoxue!
(Aisin-Gioro: family name of the Manchu emperors)
Sunian, why did you want to come here all of a sudden?
I had to drag you here all the time.
I just want to have a look.
We've been here so many times.
What else is there to look at?
Did you hear what Mr. Sun said?
Which part?
He said many things.
He said he wanted to leave something for this world.
Have you thought about what you want to leave for this world?
Something... tasty or fun!
I want to leave something for this world, too.
I hope what I leave
will still be admired by many after a century.
Just like the Forbidden City.
I don't get it.
I can't explain either.
I just want to be like Mr. Sun
and have no regret when I talk about the choices I made...
when I become an old man.
I know what you want.
It's the saying, "I regret nothing for I did not squander my life away,
I'm ashamed of nothing for I did not toil blindly in vain."
So what's your choice?
It's okay. Take your time.
No matter what you pick, I'll be by your side.
You'll be leaving soon.
Who told you that?
I'm staying.
You're studying abroad.
I wasn't chosen.
Impossible.
You scored so well in IELTS.
I failed the interview.
But it's fine because I don't feel like studying abroad anymore.
My parents are also very happy to hear that.
They say I should stay if I want to.
No, there must be another solution.
What's up?
Do you really want me to leave?
Of course not. But you...
It's more than enough already.
I'll stay and just cling to you.
What are you doing?
I'm making a wish.
The wish I made was to see you smile.
You should make a wish, too. Your wish will come true here.
Come. We'll do it together.
I wish I could find something I want to do.
And I wish everything around me
can remain the same.
It's almost noon now and she's still not here.
That's unacceptable.
Be mad at her all you want now.
You might not be able to anymore.
What do you mean, Master?
Qiaomu is really upset this time.
She might have left already.
Master, you're saying
that Qiaomu doesn't work here anymore?
If you don't apologize,
even I can't save you.
I...
Master, I'll take a day off.
Mr. Sun, didn't Qiaomu take a day off for her school?
This young man is too slow.
I'm giving him a nudge.
[Kou Siyuan]
That's all for today's lecture.
Class is dismissed.
Who are you looking for, mister?
F-Fu Qiaomu!
Fu Qiaomu! Fu Qiaomu.
Why are you looking for me?
Why did you quit?
Quit what?
You're still lying to me?
What lie? Are you crazy?
- Are you leaving with that man?
- Who?
The one who drives a Mercedes-Benz.
She is the one who drives a Mercedes-Benz.
It's her.
Who said only men could drive a Mercedes-Benz?
You owe her an apology, too.
I asked her to find you a job and you turned it down just like that.
What?
I thought you thought I was too poor so you found me a new job.
I didn't say that.
I just thought you wanted a better job.
I did.
But after you came, that thought disappeared.
How does my presence have anything to do with whether you want to change your job or not?
It has everything to do with it.
If I change my job, I have to leave.
How far can you go anyway?
I have to leave the Restoration Department.
And if I do that, how can I still be together with you?
Even if you leave the Restoration Department, we can still be together!
Are you dumb?
If I leave the Restoration Department, we can't even meet up.
How can we be together like that?
Are you dumb, too?
I can't take this anymore.
She already confessed to you
and you're still taking everything literally.
Dude, how did you survive this far with that level of emotional intelligence?
- Exactly.
- Dump him!
- Don't stay with him.
- Dump him.
Fu Qiaomu!
I know I'm not good with words.
I suck at communicating
and I don't know how to impress a girl.
Before now, I didn't even know what loving someone felt like.
But after I met you,
I think loving someone
means I want to be with her every day.
I like you.
I want to be with you every day.
Can I?
Say yes!
- Kiss!
[Chinese Arts History and the Pinnacle of Chinese Arts]
Mr. Luo.
You can do so many other things for this weekend.
Why come here?
I...
I'm here to look at the tree.
That tree is growing quite nicely
but you have seen it for many years already.
You're not sick of it yet?
I'll show you something you're supposed to look at.
This is your mother's final drawing.
Although it is incomplete,
I can tell it's a masterpiece.
She started decisively
but ended her touches on a melancholic note.
The upper one is the original work.
The original author must have hidden
many feelings in his heart.
It's hard to replicate what he was feeling.
But the one who tried imitating the original painting
had this generous sentiment that rivaled that of the author.
Before your mother left, she told me
she couldn't let go of this painting.
Strictly speaking,
this cultural relic is but a Xuan paper.
(For Chinese calligraphy and drawing)
It has no life.
But when you pour your soul into it,
it bears a part of you.
If the relic is there, the people will be too.
Humans are bound to leave this world sooner or later.
If you can leave something for this world,
then your life is not wasted.
You're just 18 years old.
If you're sad, you can just cry.
Cry it out, make a big fuss,
cry some more, and then it's over.
You move on and live.
Live for yourself...
and for your mother.
Mr. Luo.
I want to be like my mother.
I want to finish...
this incomplete painting of hers.
[Teachers' Office]
Dad, what did the teachers say?
They said you shouldn't switch to arts.
They asked me to talk to you.
Can you tell me what's on your mind?
Why did you suddenly change your mind?
I want to join the Restoration Division
and replicate old paintings.
Don't force yourself...
because of...
because of anyone else.
I'm not forcing myself.
I really want to do it.
Dad, I want to be like you.
I want...
to leave something...
for this ever-changing world.
I get it.
I'll support whatever you want to do.
Let's go. PE class is now.
You can go first. I'll catch you later.
Go back to your seat.
Your PE teacher is busy right now.
This class is now a math class.
Math class again?
Quit complaining.
Both of you, bring back those who ran to the field.
The lesson will begin in five minutes.
Those who are late will have to answer questions in front of the blackboard.
Xue, why doesn't Shiyin attend the classes anymore?
She's occupied.
What happened to Lin Shiyin?
Nothing.
Xue, do you know what Wu Huan likes?
Why? Do you want to give him a present?
No!
I was just curious.
Shao Xue, someone's looking for you.
Zhang Qi?
No. Hotter than Zhang Qi.
Sunian!
Sunian.
Slow down. I won't run away.
What are you staring at?
You have been eating well. You look better, too.
Xue,
I need to tell you something.
Go ahead.
I want to switch to arts.
I want to apply to the Academy of Fine Arts.
Qiaomu's school?
What do you want to learn?
Drawing. After I graduate,
I'll replicate old paintings.
Did the teachers agree to it?
No, but I must insist.
But can you still change your major now?
Those who pick arts started drawing in Grade 10.
- You don't have faith in me?
- Of course, I do.
I just don't have faith in the taste of those people.
Sunian, will you work in the Restoration Department then?
I want to finish...
my mother's incomplete drawing.
- What are you doing?
- I'm cheering you up.
Sunian, just do what you want to do.
You'll succeed.
Time for class!
Go back to your classroom for your class.
I should head back now.
Bye, Sunian.
Bye!
Look at the color of this patch.
It's too new.
When it comes to color,
try learning it from Moshui.
She's very sensitive to it.
Why is Moshui absent again?
She took a day off.
She did?
She didn't tell me.
Dongge. Come with me.
I need to tell you something.
Keep looking for it.
Look for a darker color.
Okay.
Hurry.
Hurry up.
What's the hurry?
What happened?
Shiyin is making me worried sick!
She was doing just fine in school
but she decided to quit school all of a sudden.
She quit school?
She took some broadcasting classes behind our back.
And she even played truancy to attend some specialized courses.
Her father found out.
Before I could reprimand her, she delivered a speech.
She said, "My dear father and mother,
I am an extraordinary girl.
I have a dream and my dream is to be an excellent host.
I hope both of you can support my dream."
Stop laughing.
She's raising my blood pressure. Seriously!
All right.
Why would she want to be a host?
She must have seen how glamorous
the hosts are on the TV and wants to be one herself.
Tell her how hard it is to get into that kind of school.
One in a hundred odds!
I told her everything. I even got mad at her.
And she gave me an ultimatum.
She said if I wouldn't support her dream, she would quit school.
Quit school?
I'm out of wits so I came to you.
- Calm down.
- Dongge,
can you tell this to Xue?
Let Xue talk to her.
Perhaps she'll listen to Xue.
Okay.
But I still think asking one kid to discourage another kid
will yield no result.
I'm doomed.
Relax.
- Calm down.
- What should I do?
In my opinion, as a parent,
we are our child's gatekeepers when it comes to important matters.
You're right.
You know what?
I'll talk to Xue.
If Xue won't do it,
I will talk to Shiyin myself.
My dear Dongge.
Having your help in this critical moment.
Don't you worry.
No, thanks.
If I talk to Shiyin, we won't even be friends anymore.
Aren't you good friends with Shiyin?
You will let her walk the wrong path like this?
What wrong path?
Broadcasting and hosting is a good major. It suits Shiyin.
Fine.
I knew you would take her side.
So unreliable.
How irritating.
It's okay if you won't help me
but I'm telling you right now.
Sit for the National College Entrance Examination properly.
Do not think about other irrelevant things.
What got into her?
Did something tick her off?
She is worried about Ms. Ji Lan and Ms. Kang.
What happened to Ms. Kang?
She's been absent for two days.
Should I check on her?
That might work.
You can visit Ms. Kang
so that your mother won't have a lot on her plate.
You can reduce her burden, too.
Reducing my mother's burden is my duty and my calling.
Why are you shouting?
I'm not deaf.
Come back early.
Go.
I'll go then.
See you, Mom!
Are you new here?
I'm Li Yuan. I've been studying in this atelier for three years.
I know this place inside out.
Come to me if you have any questions.
How old are you?
18.
So young. You're about to graduate soon.
Where are you applying?
Academy of Fine Arts.
Here comes another one.
How long have you been drawing?
I just started.
When's the entrance exam?
This year.
My friend. You were drunk last night, weren't you?
I've been applying to it for three years.
You have no prior knowledge and you want to get into the Academy of Fine Arts after a few months of learning?
I learned some rudimentary tricks.
Really? From who?
My mother.
My mother taught me how to sing too,
but you don't see me applying to a conservatoire.
What does your mother do?
She replicated old paintings.
Not bad. Replicating old paintings.
Where? Under a bridge?
In the Restoration Department.
Then she has...
Your mother, has she met Sir Luo Huaijin?
Mr. Luo is my mother's master.
My friend, can you put in good words for me?
Can we draw first?
Go ahead.
My friend, can you put in good words for...
Continue, please.
Ms. Kang.
Ms. Kang, are you here?
Xue?
Ms. Kang, I'm here to pay you a visit.
If you're busy, I can go back.
You came in time. Come in.
Ms. Kang, are you expecting someone?
Sit.
Why are you staring at me?
You look different now.
How do I look normally then?
You look beautiful.
But today, even more so.
What a sweet-talker.
Your mother sent you here, didn't she?
No. No. I came here of my own volition.
But my mother is a tad worried about you.
I'm glad you came here instead.
Because I don't feel the need to hide anything from you.
Try this.
Is this Suzhou cuisine?
Sweet and sour. It's delicious.
I haven't made it in a long time.
My culinary skill isn't as good as before.
Ms. Kang, drink moderately.
Alcohol is not good for your health.
It isn't, but it can help me
forget unhappy memories.
Ms. Kang, is today an important day?
You cooked so many delicious dishes.
"OLD SONG" - Featuring artist: Ma Di
♫ As I traverse this path without minding it ♫
♫ My memory does all the hard work for me ♫
♫ All the memories are embedded deep within my heart ♫
♫ The past I've been hiding from year after year ♫
♫ Carved into the days long gone ♫
♫ Although simplicity is plain, its vibrancy has never faded ♫
♫ Those songs in the past ♫
♫ They had accompanied me through everything ♫
♫ Singing about the stubbornness of our youth ♫
♫ Using this song to boost our courage as we sing ♫
♫ Please don't cry because you have me ♫
♫ Until I saw the bustling city ♫
♫ Until I realized that it was once within my reach ♫
♫ I was this sober once but I still did the same thing ♫
♫ As days go by, I wish to forget ♫
♫ But unknowingly, I remember them again ♫
♫ I remember the deep feelings that were long gone ♫
♫ Within those simple days ♫
♫ Those songs in the past, they had accompanied me ♫
♫ As I regretted our parting during our youth ♫
♫ Please don't cry again ♫
♫ And don't ask when I'll return ♫