"Green Years" - Ning Hengyu / Zhao Beier
♫ The bicycle bell rings and takes me back to
the alley I saw in my dream ♫
♫  I invite the sunlight to traverse the morning
fog and breeze with me ♫
♫ Riding my bike, trying to catch up to the fleeting youth ♫
♫ The Forbidden City made from red walls and
encaustic tiles in my memory ♫
♫ Unlike the hustle and bustle of everyday life ♫
♫ It's quaint and peaceful ♫
♫ Throughout the ordinary and extraordinary four seasons  ♫
♫ Some words are just like seeds ♫
♫ Growing in our youth, changing our future ♫
♫ Who can understand the silence in our hearts? ♫
♫ We once thought our dreams were somewhere far away ♫
♫ We wanted to grow up as soon as possible ♫
♫ Some waited while some traveled ♫
♫ How far away is our future? ♫
♫ Now, each of us ♫
♫ Has gone through a lot ♫
♫ We have grown up ♫
♫ Finally confirming that love is faith ♫
♫ There's no need to wander anymore ♫
♫ The questions we asked back then ♫
♫ Have been answered gradually ♫
♫ Through the passing of time ♫
♫ Who had pursued their dreams and left no regrets behind? ♫
♫ Returning to this place in the end ♫
♫ Returning ♫
♫ To the place that I've always loved  ♫
♫ We once thought our dreams were somewhere far away ♫
♫ We wanted to grow up as soon as possible ♫
♫ Finally confirming that love is faith ♫
♫ There's no need to wander anymore ♫
[Memory of Encaustic Tile]
[Adapted from Beifeng Sanbaili's original novel "Memory of Encaustic Tile"]
[Episode 11]
[A Gift from the Prince]
Once upon a time, a beautiful princess fell seriously ill.
Two warriors who love the princess embarked on a journey
to find a cure for the princess's illness.
They are going to find the legendary jasmine flower that can bring people back to life.
The outfit is a nice touch.
[Mr. Chen, Ms. Miao, Ms. Zhao]
They finally came to the place where the jasmine grew.
But they both wanted to be the princess's one and only.
So they wanted to have a final showdown with each other.
You!
What?
You don't deserve her!
I...
Why don't I deserve her?
Because I said so!
The actors phoned in their performances.
What's with the actors? Just a bunch of amateurs.
You can take over. I'm leaving.
Come back here!
You got the line wrong.
I forgot my next line. Just continue.
While the two princes were arguing, the dragon guarding the jasmine
came down from the sky
and spewed blazing flames.
The two princes buried the hatchet
and worked together to defeat the dragon.
They worked together to defeat the dragon!
But a warrior tragically died.
You shouldn't be dead. I'm the one who should die.
- I thought I was the one who died?
- It's me.
Why are you both on the floor?
One of you has to get up.
One of you has to get up! Just one!
The warrior returned with the jasmine flowers
and presented it to the princess.
Princess? Princess?
What an ordinary-looking princess.
She's totally not worth dying for.
That's right.
Return home and present it to the princess.
Princess.
The princess was terribly saddened
when she heard that a warrior had died for her
as it suddenly dawned on her that the dead warrior
was the love of her life.
So the princess decided to revive the warrior with her singing.
Sing.
It's your turn.
One, two, three, go.
Is this princess a mute? Why isn't she talking?
- Get off the stage!
Why is she running away?
She left without saying a word.
What kind of stage play is this?
Pull the curtains!
These kids aren't up for it.
They should just focus on studying. This isn't for them.
Pull the curtains!
I haven't gotten inside yet!
Tang Ya.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Where are Xue and the others?
They went to talk to the teachers.
It's all my fault.
I suffered from stage fright again.
I've let you guys down.
You are still better than Zhang Qi and Sunian.
They didn't even remember their lines.
What's the point of me remembering the lines?
I couldn't even utter a word out.
I watched you rehearse.
Just perform like you normally did, and you'd do great.
I was too nervous being on the stage.
I ruined it all for you guys.
I know you don't want to hurt my feelings.
Maybe I should just quit?
Don't say that.
Tang Ya, trust me. Give it another try.
We've got your back.
I'm afraid I might let you down.
Tang Ya.
Actually, I myself am not a confident person.
But I'm trying to overcome it.
You're way better than me.
So don't doubt yourself. Okay?
All right. Enough crying.
Let's go and find Xue.
Come on.
Come on!
Let's go.
Ms. Miao, we didn't have time to rehearse properly.
Could you give us another chance to try it out?
Hear me out.
Zheng Sunian. The top Grade 12 student.
Zhang Qi. You're from the competition class, right?
Both of you are doing great in your studies.
So just focus on your studies.
Don't bother taking part in anything else.
Give us another chance.
Just one more chance.
Coming up next is the drama troupe's performance.
Why don't we watch other stage plays first?
You can come back to me again after that.
Ms. Miao.
Off you go now.
Five, six, seven, eight. Move.
One, two, down.
[Dance in youth's rhythm, let brilliance bloom]
Three, four, five, six, seven, eight, slow down.
Two, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
All right. That's all for today's practice.
Thank you.
Lin Shiyin.
Stay.
[Dance Room]
What are you looking at?
Shiyin is in there.
You must be exhausted.
It's been hard on you.
I just realized that you have no talent at all.
But it's good that you are willing to work hard for it.
Sir, am I really that bad?
What do you want to hear, the truth or something else?
I always thought I was pretty good.
People tend to have the wrong impression
and think they're different from others.
But the truth is...
there's only one way for the untalented to improve themselves.
- What is it?
- Be obedient.
- But I...
- It upset me when you questioned me earlier.
You know what? I was the one who chose you from an ocean of crowds.
You should know that you don't have what it takes to be the main dancer.
I discovered you and guided you.
That's how you became the focus.
But you challenged me in public.
Was that right of you?
I'm sorry, sir.
I forgive you.
Here.
Right now, look at yourself.
Keep dancing.
Dance until there are no more flaws.
All right?
I believe in you.
Seriously?
See? Xue doesn't buy that.
Juliet.
You're the beautiful sun, my soul mate, and my love.
Your eyes shine so brightly in space
that the birds sing their song as they mistakenly
think the night is over.
How wonderful your posture is?
How I wish I was a glove on your hand
so I could kiss your fragrant hand.
Why are you here?
I just happened to be passing by.
School's over. Stop practicing.
That teacher was wrong. Don't believe his words.
What do you know? He's an artist.
I think he is an incompetent guy.
He gets his sense of presence by hurting others.
Don't you say that!
Shiyin, don't trust him.
You're not what he said you were.
Well, I believe him.
Stay out of my business!
I admit that my performance was kind of exaggerated.
But that's my understanding of the character, Aotian.
I admit that I kind of forgot my lines.
But a good actor never has to stick to the screenplay.
Maybe I could go...
talk to Ms. Miao and tell her to give us another chance?
No need for that.
If that's the case,
let's eat something nice to cool down.
Unreliable.
Not only is Zhang Qi unreliable, but you as well, Sunian!
Why am I unreliable?
Just keep your mouth shut.
Had I known, I wouldn't have asked you to perform.
It would have been better if I'd spent 10 yuan to get the sundry shop's owner
- to perform instead of you two!
- Well, 10 yuan isn't enough.
I asked him to play my dad once. His acting was terrible.
I don't want to talk to you! Move!
It's just a cultural performance.
Does she have to be so mad?
Shao Xue.
Hi. I'm Wang Haoran.
The Little Li Flying Dagger?
What?
Nothing, I know who you are.
Sure enough. All the girls in this school know me.
I think it's a shame that your stage play didn't go as planned.
Right? I thought the same, too!
- The actors didn't put any effort into it.
- I thought the same, too!
- I'm thinking of giving you a chance.
- I thought...
What?
As the president of the Drama Club,
I'd like to invite you to join the club.
I don't think that's necessary.
Don't feel unworthy of it.
If I think you can, you can.
Xue.
Isn't this the warrior who wanted to die so badly?
Isn't this Romeo?
- Why are you here?
- Xue.
Pizza Hut just launched a new flavor. Let's try it out.
I'm not going.
Come on, Xue.
We can discuss the acting.
What's going on?
Just a lunatic.
Sorry, I'm late.
I just sent Shiyin home.
It's okay. There's not a lot of stock today.
It's fine. I'll take care of the rest. You can take a break.
It's all right.
I have nothing to do anyway.
Wu Huan!
Here. The packaging was damaged, and it fell out.
It looks just like you. You can have it.
- Thank you, sir.
- Don't mention it.
Do you like it? You can take it.
No. It's a gift for you.
Why would a guy want this?
You can have it.
Can't you see that you're unwanted here?
I don't think so.
Who invited you here?
If I don't come, she's not going to come either.
Where does your confidence come from?
Anywhere.
Aren't you eating?
I'm trying to keep fit.
Why are you here then?
I've come to experience the taste of junk to know how healthy I am.
Junk.
But seeing how much you enjoyed it, I feel like taking a bite too.
Buy it yourself.
It's just one piece. Do you have to do this?
It's not too late for you to leave now.
But that's not what Xue wants.
Who are you to call her Xue?
I'm already feeling annoyed, and you won't give me a break.
Enjoy yourselves.
Sit down!
Your hostility towards me is pretty obvious.
No hostility. We just don't want to be friends with you.
But that's not what Shao Xue thinks.
You're overthinking it.
Interesting.
Sunian, you wanted to see me?
Sunian!
Sunian, how did you find this place?
Sunian, I was afraid you'd make fun of me.
I got everything! Don't worry. Let's go home!
Sunian.
Sunian, you're so lame.
As expected of my lead actor.
Sunian can always think of some wonderful ideas.
You'll always be the Sunian that I know.
Sunian!
- Dad.
- Your milk.
Dad.
Back then, how did you know?
Know what?
How do you know...
if you like women?
- I...
- Zheng, come and help me out!
Coming!
This woman.
This woman...
This woman is your mom.
She...
Right.
Yes.
I'm feeling a little sleepy.
Rest earlier, Dad.
I think if you like someone,
that feeling lasts for a lifetime.
Zheng, what are you doing? Hurry up!
Ms. Miao. Zhang Qi has friends.
I'm his friend.
Failure is the mother of success. Don't you know that?
I'll buy you noodles. How about that?
How do I look?
Why are you laughing?
Why are you here?
Nonsense! Can't I come back to my own house?
Didn't you say you were working overtime and wouldn't come home tonight?
Says who?
You're blushing. Is there a little secret?
- Are you dating someone?
- No.
Tell me. Is she pretty?
- Just go home and sleep!
- Go home and sleep?
What are you talking about? This is our home.
Where else should I go, you punk?
You have a little secret.
Get to bed now.
[Teachers' Office]
Morning.
Good morning.
Xue, I'm sorry about yesterday.
It was my fault. I had stage fright.
It's not your fault. You didn't do it on purpose.
[A Pocket New English-Chinese Dictionary]
But those two screwed it up on purpose.
Given their performances, there was no way we'd pass.
They... perhaps, it's because they hardly know me.
Why don't I ask Ms. Miao to make you the lead actress and give us another chance to perform?
It'll surely be great.
Shao Xue, someone's looking for you.
I'll talk to you later.
What's up?
I went to see Ms. Miao yesterday.
She's willing to give us another chance.
How's that possible?
You don't believe me?
What did you do?
I had a sincere conversation with her.
Ms. Miao.
Yes?
I have a favor to ask of you.
What are you doing?
For real?
The talented are generally bold.
Our parents dedicated great efforts to making this sword and outfit.
Please take their efforts into consideration
and give us another chance.
Sunian, you're awesome!
We've been given another chance now.
But there's something you need to know.
- How to teach you two?
- Of course not.
It's Tang Ya's stage fright.
Let's make you the lead actress. That's way safer.
Sunian, have you forgotten why I wanted to direct a play?
You dream to be a director.
That was the case at first.
But right now, I want to help Tang Ya find her confidence
- and let her know how great she is.
- Understood.
- Understood
- Will you help us?
I'll do my best.
Sunian, you're the best.
I'll get back to class.
Bye.
[Dancing Classroom, Qiming High School]
Five, six, seven, eight. Move.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Two, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Three, two, three, up.
Now we're at the climax of the show.
Princess Jasmine finally found the most amazing jasmine flowers.
But she decides to use the jasmine flowers to revive her dead lover
and chooses to die.
Director, I have some questions.
Ask away.
I don't know which one of them is the lead actor.
[Dream Sets Sail]
Let me think.
Sit down, all of you.
Actually, at first, I wanted him to be the lead actor. He will be the villain.
Both of them would fight for you and both would get severely injured.
But I thought it was too bloody.
So I added romance to the story so that both of them
would be madly in love with you.
The problem lies in this part of them being "madly in love".
What problem?
I can't even sense their love for the princess.
So I don't understand the reasoning behind the princess's sacrifice.
That's because they didn't get their lines right.
Zhang Qi, hurry up! Say the lines.
She's my princess. I won't let you take her away.
Done. It's your turn.
That's impossible. The princess is my everything. Her voice makes me believe that all difficulties shall pass.
The look in her eyes makes me believe that all good things will last forever.
I'm at peace with the world. But if you want to take her away, I'm going to risk it all and fight you to the bitter end.
Sunian, can you put some emotions into it?
We're acting, not reading in the morning.
Even that has more emotions than you.
Hurry. Practice!
If you can't get it right, none of you can go home.
Does that mean the dragon isn't needed anymore?
Your part is easy. You may leave first.
Thank you, Director.
Zhang Qi, hurry! Again!
I won't let you take her away.
She's my princess.
Five, six, seven, eight. Move.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Two, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Three, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Two, two, three...
- Shiyin, how are you?
- Shiyin.
- Are you all right?
- Let me take a look.
I think she sprained her ankle. Take her to the infirmary.
Why are you...
[Infirmary, Qiming High School]
You need to be more careful in the future.
Hi, your medicine is ready.
Okay. Coming.
Shiyin.
Are you okay? Does it hurt?
I've heard what happened. That teacher is too much!
Good thing Wu Huan was there. Wu Huan is awesome.
Xue.
What did the doctor say?
The doctor said it's nothing serious, but she won't be able to dance for a while.
Shiyin, if you can't dance, so be it.
It's not worth dancing for a teacher like that.
I'm fine. I'll get going now.
Walk with her.
Shao Xue.
What do you want this time?
I still want to invite you to join the Drama Club and be a part of "Juliet."
I have my own show.
Are you sure you want to do this with them?
I think a good actress like you needs a better partner.
They don't deserve you.
Wang Haoran, don't talk bad about my friends.
I'll take on anyone who does that.
They don't even know how to act.
Who are you talking about?
I'm only asking her to join the Drama Club.
Why would she want to join your lousy club?
- Are you sure you won't give it another thought?
- No.
All right then.
I wish you all the best.
Let's go.
How did your rehearsal go?
- Not bad.
- Perfect.
Don't screw up. Don't lose to that Romeo guy.
- Don't worry.
- Come on. Let's go home.
We're off the clock. Let's go.
What's wrong?
The performance is tomorrow.
I'm a little nervous.
But you did great when we were rehearsing.
But once I get on the stage, I'll start having stage fright.
I dare not face the audience,
and I'm afraid I'll be a drag to you guys.
The audience?
How about this?
Don't treat the audience as people.
That's not what I meant.
I'm saying...
You can treat the audience as boxes.
This warehouse is the stage.
This is Xue.
This is Sunian.
This is Zhang Qi.
Also...
This.
This is me.
Give it a try in front of them.
Why don't I step outside?
Keep it up.
♪ What a beautiful jasmine. What a beautiful jasmine ♪
♪ Buds and blooms are here and there ♪
♪ Pure and fragrant all do declare ♪
What's the matter?
- Happy Birthday.
That's so nice of you!
This is your birthday breakfast.
This is your birthday present.
There's a present? What is it?
Your dad and I scrimped and saved
[Math Tuition Class]
and tightened our belts to sign you up for the best math class.
From now on, you'll go there every Tuesday, Thursday, and Saturday to study math.
Here's your birthday breakfast.
Remember to eat it.
Eat more. This is the only meal for today.
Your mom and I have restoration work to do at the Restoration Department.
Get your own lunch.
- Once again, happy birthday to you.
- Hurry.
- We're running late.
- Bye.
- We have to go now.
- Hurry up.
What kind of birthday present is this?
I don't want this!
I'm standing right here. Didn't you see me?
What is it?
Happy Birthday.
Thank you.
It's your birthday.
Why do you look so gloomy?
My mom signed me up for a math tutoring class as a birthday present.
There are gifts from the others.
What if someone gives you something that you love?
You're right.
But it's not going to be you.
Why?
Because you've never given anyone a birthday present.
What if I have changed?
Sunian.
Let's go.
[Qiming High School 10th Anniversary Cultural Performance]
Principal. Mr. Liu. You're here.
Here. Have a seat.
- Shiyin, how's your injury?
- Much better.
Right, Shiyin, how is your leg?
I'm good now.
We're going backstage for rehearsal.
- We'll get on the stage now.
- Okay.
- See you.
All the best.
Come on, guys.
How's your leg?
If not, you can play a rock in our play.
What are you talking about?
Shiyin, are you all right?
It's the dance team's loss to not have you with them.
Just take a seat and rest. Cheer for us.
- We'll go on the stage now.
- Okay.
Hurry up, Sunian.
Take a seat.
Shiyin.
Take a seat over here.
Wu Huan, we need to stand by now.
Okay.
Shiyin, sit here.
We'll come to you after the performance.
Next, please enjoy the stage play of costume, martial arts,
romance, love, and comedy,
Princess Jasmine.
Once upon a time, a beautiful princess fell seriously ill.
Two warriors who love the princess embarked on a journey
to find a cure for the princess's illness.
They are going to find the legendary jasmine flower
that can bring people back to life.
The outfit and props are so cool. Are those real swords?
That should cost a lot.
Our school's drama club is rich, isn't it?
This isn't a performance by the drama club.
They finally came to the place where the jasmine grew.
That guy in white is so handsome.
But they both wanted to be the princess's one and only.
I won't let you take this bunch of jasmine flowers.
Principal, these are the students from our class.
Not bad. Pretty good.
That depends on whether you have what it takes to stop me.
So they wanted to have a final showdown with each other.
While the two princes were arguing, the dragon guarding the jasmine
came down from the sky
and spewed blazing flames.
Take that!
The two princes buried the hatchet
and worked together to defeat the dragon.
This time, their performance is a lot better than the previous one.
- Right?
- Awesome.
The one in the purple outfit is also good-looking.
They are both my best friends.
The warrior returned with the jasmine flowers
and presented them to the princess.
The princess was terribly saddened
when she heard that a warrior had died for her.
It suddenly dawned on her that the dead warrior
was the love of her life.
So the princess decided to revive the warrior with her singing.
What's wrong? Why is there no sound?
What's going on?
There seems to be a problem with the speakers.
It's taken care of.
You can treat the audience as boxes.
This is me.
Sing to them.
♪ What a beautiful jasmine. What a beautiful jasmine ♪
♪ Buds and blooms are here and there ♪
♪ Pure and fragrant all do declare ♪
♪ Let me gather some with tender care ♪
♪ Sweetness for all to share ♪
♪ Jasmine fair, oh jasmine fair ♪
- Bravo!
- Nice!
- Not bad.
What a beautiful singing voice!
- Awesome!
- Bravo!
Awesome!
How satisfying.
Today is just perfect. Tang Ya did really well.
Like the two of us didn't?
Yes, everyone did a great job.
You've passed your place. You don't have to walk me back. Go home.
I'll get going then.
- Bye!
We'll go now.
Xue.
"OLD SONG" - Featuring artist: Ma Di
♫ As I traverse this path without minding it ♫
♫ My memory does all the hard work for me ♫
♫ All the memories are embedded deep within my heart ♫
♫ The past I've been hiding from year after year ♫
♫ Carved into the days long gone ♫
♫ Although simplicity is plain, its vibrancy has never faded ♫
♫ Those songs in the past ♫
♫ They had accompanied me through everything ♫
♫ Singing about the stubbornness of our youth ♫
♫ Using this song to boost our courage as we sing ♫
♫ Please don't cry because you have me ♫
♫ Until I saw the bustling city ♫
♫ Until I realized that it was once within my reach ♫
♫ I was this sober once but I still did the same thing ♫
♫ As days go by, I wish to forget ♫
♫ But unknowingly, I remember them again ♫
♫ I remember the deep feelings that were long gone ♫
♫ Within those simple days ♫
♫ Those songs in the past, they had accompanied me ♫
♫ As I regretted our parting during our youth ♫
♫ Using this song, this song belongs to us ♫
♫ Please don't cry again ♫
♫ And don't ask when I'll return ♫