♫ The bicycle bell rings and takes me back to
the alley I saw in my dream ♫
♫  I invite the sunlight to traverse the morning
fog and breeze with me ♫
♫ Riding my bike, trying to catch up to the fleeting youth ♫
♫ The Forbidden City made from red walls and
encaustic tiles in my memory ♫
♫ Unlike the hustle and bustle of everyday life ♫
♫ It's quaint and peaceful ♫
♫ Throughout the ordinary and extraordinary four seasons  ♫
♫ Some words are just like seeds ♫
♫ Growing in our youth, changing our future ♫
♫ Who can understand the silence in our hearts? ♫
♫ We once thought our dreams were somewhere far away ♫
♫ We wanted to grow up as soon as possible ♫
♫ Some waited while some traveled ♫
♫ How far away is our future? ♫
♫ Now, each of us ♫
♫ Has gone through a lot ♫
♫ We have grown up ♫
♫ Finally confirming that love is faith ♫
♫ There's no need to wander anymore ♫
♫ The questions we asked back then ♫
♫ Have been answered gradually ♫
♫ Through the passing of time ♫
♫ Who had pursued their dreams and left no regrets behind? ♫
♫ Returning to this place in the end ♫
♫ Returning ♫
♫ To the place that I've always loved  ♫
♫ We once thought our dreams were somewhere far away ♫
♫ We wanted to grow up as soon as possible ♫
♫ Finally confirming that love is faith ♫
♫ There's no need to wander anymore ♫
[Memory of Encaustic Tile]
[Adapted from Beifeng Sanbaili's original novel "Memory of Encaustic Tile"]
[Episode 33]
[Until You Won't Let Go of Me]
Sunian didn't want you to pass on another great opportunity because of him.
That's why he decided to break up with you.
He was very upset, too.
He only attended those blind dates
because he didn't want to upset his dad.
Even though it was him
who proposed to break up,
it was I who decided to leave.
We never talked to each other
even once when I was abroad.
I came back here of my own volition, too.
Now that he's leading a stable life,
I don't want to intrude.
Also, maybe he doesn't love me anymore.
That, you'll need to ask him yourself.
Don't worry about us.
All right. Take care of yourself
for the next few days then.
Where are you going?
I'll be on a business trip.
I have to go now.
Think about what to do with Sunian.
See you.
Bye, Xue.
Hello?
- Hey, Sunian.
- I gave everything you sent to me to our neighbors already.
They all love it.
Sunian, Xue is in a pickle now
but she won't let me tell you.
What happened?
She's gone back to China already.
Mo Hai swindled money from the company and pushed Xue to be the scapegoat.
Her visa application is now on hold
and her bank account is frozen now.
Has everything been resolved then?
You don't know the worst yet.
She fainted due to anxiety.
And when she was hospitalized, she found out she was sick.
I was shocked when I saw her.
Her face was pale and her breathing was weak.
She's back in China for surgery.
Give me the address.
Okay. Will do.
Hello?
What did you forget again?
Xue's voice?
Hello?
How are you?
What kind of surgery? What kind of sickness?
I'm fine.
You're still lying to me.
I'm not.
I'm fine. Go back.
If I go back now, who can take care of you?
I can take good care of myself. Just go.
You have been scammed and you're now very sick.
How is that taking good care of yourself?
I said I can.
Who are you to meddle in my business?
Because I'm your Sunian.
Wasn't Sunian here just now?
Xue is sick?
When did Xue come back?
Ask them.
Do your parents know you're back?
No.
You haven't been home for many years...
and yet you hid your return from them.
Have you considered their feelings?
My parents will just scold me...
if they see the way I am now.
I'm scared of going back home.
Let them scold you.
I will comfort you.
Sunian.
How have you been...
all these years?
It's been great living alone abroad.
I cooked alone.
I watched movies alone.
I shopped alone.
I went to the doctor alone.
I...
I won't let you be alone anymore.
Then why...
did you let me leave alone?
Because you wanted to explore the world.
Now that you have seen it,
listened to it, and experienced it,
I won't...
let go of you anymore.
Sunian.
I have missed you so much.
When I was alone abroad,
I missed you every day.
I hoped that you would be by my side every day.
When I was gone,
did you miss me?
Or did you forget about me?
♫ Look up to the starry sky ♫
♫ Floating in space ♫
♫ When I miss you ♫
♫ There's a strong surge of courage in my heart ♫
♫ I'll love you till the end ♫
♫ Even if time gets lost ♫
♫ And there's no ending ♫
♫ The thought of you makes my dream soothing ♫
Who said you could kiss me?
♫ They've watched us go through ♫
Because you kissed me first.
Xue!
Pick up the phone!
Hello.
Mom.
I'm glad you still called me that.
When did you come back? What happened to you?
What kind of sickness?
And you...
You said Sunian and you...
Sunian, he...
What did you do to Sunian?
Come back now at once to explain everything!
What's going on?
Mom, why did you call me?
I did not call you. You called us.
Xue, you called us.
Right, Old Zheng? Calm down.
Xue, you phoned us.
Mr. Zheng, you're there too?
Yes. Well, the three of us are here.
This has really taken us by...
Well... I...
So... you know what, Xue?
I have an old apartment outside, currently occupied by tenants.
Sunian has a fixed income every month.
Not a lot but he doesn't really care about this extra rental income.
[Home]
You know what? From this month onward,
I'll ask Sunian to transfer the rental income to you.
Dad, no need to help.
I can handle it.
He hung up.
This is a bit...
You should go.
Where to?
To where you live.
- You just had your surgery. Who's going to take care of you?
- I can take care of myself. Just leave.
The doctor said I could turn somersaults now.
This is not my fault.
So, bye.
Wait.
[Double Good Fortune]
Sunian.
Zheng Sunian.
Yunsheng.
Why are you here?
Nothing, just for a drink.
Well... maybe another day?
I'm busy today.
You're hiding someone.
Let me take a look.
It's Xue.
Xue? You two...
Not bad, buddy.
You haven't had meat for a few years and when you finally do, it's a meat extravaganza.
She's back at last.
All right. I'll leave you two alone.
The beer is to improve the mood.
Don't overexert yourself.
Just leave.
[Ten unanswered calls from Ms. Yu]
[Eleven unanswered calls from Dad]
Sunian, don't leave!
What's the matter?
Can I have a hug?
I'm here. There, there.
What did you dream of?
I dreamed that...
I dreamed that you made good food for me.
Your dream is coming true then.
So many dishes!
Sunian, did you cook all of them yourself?
Yes.
They look so familiar.
Aren't they from the recipes you gave me?
Yes.
Did you use my recipes when you were abroad?
No, I was too busy with work.
I didn't have time to cook for myself.
I will cook for you every day, then.
Hello?
Lin Shiyin, you still have the gall to call me?
Come on.
I have to check if you're sleeping alone or with someone today.
With someone.
Where are you? When will you be back?
My stuff is still in your place.
I'm so busy that I don't have time to go back home.
What should I do then? My clothes are in your place.
How am I supposed to get clean clothes?
Ask your Sunian to help you.
I'm losing the signal. I'll hang up now. Bye.
Hello?
- She hung up.
- I'll help you.
Let's go shopping tomorrow.
All right.
Now, eat.
What's the matter?
You must have cooked for another girl before.
Do you think I'm like that?
So you never considered dating another girl when I was abroad?
Never.
What if I didn't come back? What would you have done?
Then I'd wait...
until you come back.
Sunian.
♫ Missing you ♫
♫ No better place to go, Amour ♫
♫ I even want to hear the birds say, "Miss me." ♫
♫ Missing you ♫
♫ No better things to do, Amour ♫
♫ Why don't you just find me at 3:00? ♫
♫ The sweetest hour starts from the time... we meet ♫
Why did you stop?
♫ I love you, Lovely ♫
♫ You're the smell made for me ♫
♫ I love you, cherie amour ♫
Wait!
Confess your love to me like a knight.
♫ I love you, Lovely, my amour ♫
I'm afraid I can't pull that off.
But I play a very mean dragon.
No!
It's early in the morning.
Why are you hugging the phone?
Hugging it won't make it ring.
I'm not hugging it.
I'm cleaning it. It's easier this way.
You know...
When did Sunian become this unreliable?
He still hasn't returned my call.
A long-awaited reunion calls forth a wonderful time.
No one is free to return your call.
If they won't return my call,
pick up my call then.
But they didn't. What are they doing?
What do they think they are doing?
You already know the answer.
Don't pretend as if you haven't been through this.
Fine.
I won't wait for the call.
I won't clean it either.
You missed.
Got you.
You hit my kidney!
Xue?
Sunian, it's time for breakfast.
Breakfast.
What?
You thought I left?
All right. I'm here. I'm not leaving.
Not bad.
It looks good.
I like it.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Would you like to try some other ones?
No, thanks.
I'll pack all these up then.
All?
This mister here has paid.
I didn't say I wanted them. Why did you pay already?
You look great in them so I bought them all.
You bought them just because I look good in them?
Fine. Don't regret your decision.
Come.
I want this, too.
Take my card.
Enough. Enough.
Why? I'm not taking back my word.
I regret it.
All right? I regret it.
You're en route to buying everything in this mall.
I think you still need a handbag.
I was used to living a frugal life when I was abroad.
I'm not used to this shopping spree.
I'm just trying to make up for not pampering you all these years.
Then... use another method.
Which method?
Help me return all these items.
Don't stand still.
We still need the money for our future.
Come.
Hurry up.
I...
Aisin-Gioro Shaoxue is back again!
You're not making a wish this time?
I'm not because my wish has come true.
Sunian, make your wish.
What did you wish for?
If I tell you, it won't come true.
Tell me. If it doesn't come true,
I'll give you another wish.
I wish...
that I could hold your hand...
like this forever.
Is that all?
Permission granted.
What do you mean?
If you want to hold my hand forever, then do it.
You won't leave anymore?
Sunian,
you became a dummy.
I made the decision to stay
when I came back here.
From now on, I'll stay by your side.
I won't go anywhere anymore.
You can never shoo me away now.
Put it down.
I'm not good enough for that.
What are you on about, Mom?
I would wash your feet if you asked me to,
let alone serving you tea.
How long has it been?
It's been a week...
since I learned about...
this affair.
No, five days.
And only one phone call in these five days.
And you refused to come back.
What now? Am I still your mother?
Mom, I had to prepare myself mentally for this.
Did you hear that?
She had to prepare herself mentally just to come home?
Mom, I just came back and I'm jobless.
If our neighbors know about this, you'll be embarrassed
So almost immediately, I found a decent job.
Insurance covered and good pay, too.
Only when everything is settled
can I come back to see you
and make you feel proud of me.
Don't you agree?
It sounds all fine and dandy.
Settled, you said?
Where?
You aren't even engaged to Sunian
and you're now living with him.
I already feel ashamed mentioning it.
I'll move back here today.
Ms. Yu, I think...
What are you trying to say?
I think...
Xue and I should get engaged first
and once that's done, we can move on to something else.
Sunian is right.
Look how resourceful Sunian is.
We need to talk to Old Zheng.
We need to pick a date for their wedding.
Right, the date.
We have to book the hotel, too. It's the hardest one to book. At least a six-month waiting period.
Not to mention the wedding dress and the wedding photos.
Also, the invitation.
Oh, you...
We have to start now. Zheng...
Old Zheng! Old Zheng!
[Shao Xue's Itinerary]
"Friendly reminder.
Have dinner at your parents' place at least six times per week.
Failure to do so will incur dire consequences."
My mother went overboard.
I'm an adult.
She can't tell me what to do as if I'm a kid.
That's because you didn't go back to see them
so Ms. Yu is now forcing you to spend more time with her.
And whose fault is that?
Do what she wants now.
Once we're married, we can do whatever we want.
You're setting up a trap again
to force me to marry you.
You slept with me.
You're now responsible for me.
Zheng Sunian.
Stop acting like you're the damsel in distress.
Pack my luggage for me.
My mom wants me to move back tonight.
But don't you have to go to Suzhou for your training program?
Tell your mother that you'll move back later.
I haven't told my mom about that yet.
It's a serious business and you haven't told her?
She'll explode when she knows about it.
I asked my dad to handle it.
Whether she'll explode or not will be his problem.
Come out now!
How can you just hide in someone else's home?
I won't come out.
Stop making a scene here.
A scene? How can I not make a scene?
You let my daughter leave when she just came back.
Come out now!
I didn't ask her to leave.
Her job needs her. Her job needs her.
I'm just the messenger.
Don't shoot the messenger, they say.
You could have told me earlier!
If you told me, I would figure out a way to make her stay.
Come out now! We'll settle this back home.
No.
I will stay with Old Zheng.
You should head back
and think why no one wants to stay with you.
Dongge. Dongge.
Say that again. Again!
You can't boss me around.
You don't want to stay with me, is that right?
Then don't come back.
Don't ever come back!
Stay with them!
Spend your life in there!
But... Be rational, please.
Don't you regret what you said.
From now on, I'll stay with Old Zheng.
Don't stop me.
If you didn't stop me, I would...
Let me see you off.
No need. It's too troublesome.
I'll call you once I get to the hotel.
Send me a message when you're in the cab.
Another one when you arrive, too.
Text me the car plate, too.
In case you get an unlicensed cab driver.
All right. I lived alone abroad for many years.
I can take care of myself.
Don't worry.
See you then.
Why are you looking at me like this?
I'll just be gone for a few days.
I'll go now then.
Hello?
Xue, you have to think about me.
Every day.
Xue.
Ms. Kang.
Ms. Kang, it's been a while.
Indeed.
I haven't seen you ever since you went abroad.
You're more beautiful now.
Have a seat.
Ms. Kang, how did you know that I was in Suzhou?
Your mother called me
and told me you were on a business trip to Suzhou.
She was worried so she asked me to come to see you.
Ms. Kang, have you gotten used to the work here?
Weren't you doing just fine in the Restoration Department?
After wandering for many years, home is still the best.
How are your parents? Are they doing well?
Yes, though they keep asking me to get married.
It's about time, too.
But my persuasion will never be effective
since I, myself, got married when I was almost 40.
Who is this lucky man? How is he?
He's a nice man.
We were introduced to each other by our mutual friend.
He's a history teacher.
When we're together,
I find out that he's a kind and gentle person.
That's why we decided to tie the knot.
It takes a fine gentleman to impress you, Ms. Kang.
Stop exaggerating.
Enough about me.
What about you? Have you found a companion?
Is he Sunian?
How do you know?
You are slow.
I had seen it coming miles ahead.
You have no idea the love Sunian has in his eyes
when he looks at you.
And did you notice that Sunian is very similar to his father?
Both of them are the quiet, inexpressive type.
But they share something in common.
Their stubbornness.
Being with someone like this is a blessing.
Their world is pure.
One life, one goal.
One life, one partner.
When they find their true love, they are not giving her away.
Both of you will definitely be happy together.
Look how long-winded I am. Let's eat and catch up.
Try this fish.
Sunian, you don't have to pick me up anymore.
It's quite tiresome.
I want to see you.
I don't want to wait one second longer.
Then whenever I'm on a business trip,
you'll come with me.
Sure.
I'll go wherever you go.
I won't let you leave me.
You'll get bored of me eventually.
We'll see.
[Liuli Hutong Residents' Committee]
Sunian.
I need to tell you something.
Marry me.
♫ The wind whispers ♫
♫ Reminding me of the starry sky ♫
♫ Would you do the same? ♫
You always steal my thunder.
♫ To cherish a certain moment ♫
♫ I wish to silently protect ♫
♫ Every detail and everything we desired ♫
♫ If we reverse time and space ♫
Did you release it too early?
Impossible.
I just heard the two of them moving.
♫ Look up to the starry sky ♫
♫ Floating in space ♫
It's us in all of these drawings.
The past us.
The present us.
♫ I'll love you till the end ♫
And the future us.
♫ And there's no ending ♫
♫ The thought of you makes my dream soothing ♫
♫ Time can not be reversed ♫
Xue.
My life is very simple...
but because of you,
I can experience every joy life has to offer.
I am never someone who smiles a lot.
But after you came to this world, you kept making me smile.
When I drew them, I realized...
you were there in all of my...
joyous moments.
I hope you will also be there for the rest of my life.
♫ I'll love you till the end  ♫
Xue, will you marry me?
♫ And there's no ending ♫
♫ The thought of you makes my dream soothing ♫
Yes.
♫ Forgive every star for being lonely ♫
♫ They've watched us go through ♫
♫ The rugged paths of life ♫
♫ And the future we hoped for ♫
♫ Can still last forever ♫
You said yes.
There's a no return policy.
I don't want to return you anyway.
♫ My vision gets blurry ♫
♫ When I miss you ♫
When we mention this in the future,
we'll say I'm the one who proposed first, all right?
♫ Let me discover the beam of light ♫
Okay.
♫ Down the farthest road ♫
♫ Quietly illuminates the deepest part of the heart ♫
Our effort was not in vain.
They are finally tying the knot.
We did everything we could.
What about your contract girlfriend?
It's terminating soon.
Dad. Mom.
- Madams and Misters.
- Dad.
All of you are here.
We're just chatting here.
Oh, my. The love is in the air.
When is the wedding?
We're all waiting for the good news.
Indeed.
Is my mother all right?
I didn't piss her off.
It's just...
that this place will be torn down soon.
Your mom feels a bit nostalgic, having lived here for many years.
It's okay.
I know.
All of us spent half our lives here.
It breaks my heart...
that we have to move.
I know, right?
So after I finish work,
I won't be able to hang out
with all of you whenever I want to like I can now.
Ms. Li, no need to help me.
You haven't packed your belongings either.
[Demolition]
No hurry. Let me help you carry all of them first.
You know, we lived in this alley
for a good portion of our lives.
And now, we have to part ways.
Right?
Do visit me often.
Don't worry. I'll find you when I'm free.
I'll miss you dearly if I can't hang out with you.
- Ms. Li. Ms. Liu.
- Xue.
- You're back.
- You're moving this early?
I have many belongings and my children are busy with their work.
So I plan to pack everything first.
You guys haven't moved yet?
We haven't even started packing.
Really?
Hurry up then.
Do continue.
I'll go back first.
Bye, Ms. Li and Ms. Liu.
See you.
Dad.
Xue.
Is Mom okay?
She doesn't want to leave this place.
On my way here,
I saw others moving their belongings about.
When are we moving?
Your mom said we would stay until the very last day.
Is my mother going to be a holdout?
No.
Your mom just wants to stay until the very last day
and bid this alley farewell.
Do you think Mom is spiraling?
She has been for a while.
♫ As I traverse this path without minding it ♫
♫ My memory does all the hard work for me ♫
♫ All the memories are embedded deep within my heart ♫
♫ The past I've been hiding from year after year ♫
♫ Carved into the days long gone ♫
♫ Although simplicity is plain, its vibrancy has never faded ♫
♫ Those songs in the past ♫
♫ They had accompanied me through everything ♫
♫ Singing about the stubbornness of our youth ♫
♫ Using this song to boost our courage as we sing ♫
♫ Please don't cry because you have me ♫
♫ Until I saw the bustling city ♫
♫ Until I realized that it was once within my reach ♫
♫ I was this sober once but I still did the same thing ♫
♫ As days go by, I wish to forget ♫
♫ But unknowingly, I remember them again ♫
♫ I remember the deep feelings that were long gone ♫
♫ Within those simple days ♫
♫ Those songs in the past, they had accompanied me ♫
♫ As I regretted our parting during our youth ♫
♫ Using this song, this song belongs to us ♫
♫ Please don't cry again ♫
♫ And don't ask when I'll return ♫