Of course I'm not here
as the auditee's rep.
But if
you're here as my boyfriend,
you're way over the line.
This is my job.
I can handle it.
Hello?
Safe.
Okay.
Just wait for me at the gas station.
Miao Jing...
And
if you ever
pull another stunt
without telling me again,
I'm really not coming home.
Are you coming home?
You told me
to go to a colleague's.
Forget I said that.
I got something to do.
What?
Picking up a colleague.
Cen Ye?
Get out.
Three hundred.
Been waiting long?
Grab two bottles of water.
Sir, how much?
Three hundred.
Sir.
Sir!
Your tank's almost full.
Did you just fill up?
Never mind. Just top it off.
Okay.
Hi.
Ring up number 3 and 4 together.
Number 3's done. Three hundred.
Number 4 will be a moment.
Mr. Chen?
You've got business out here too?
I'll give you a ride back later.
I'll
hitch a ride with Ms. Miao.
She's taking me back.
What,
you bought a car before you even
have a license?
Yeah, it's been a while. A bit rusty.
Mr. Chen, you're getting heated?
You head back first.
Shall we go?
Thanks for the gas.
I'll treat you to a meal.
I'll keep Mr. Cen for a quick work chat.
Ms. Miao, you've learned to bite back?
What?
Nothing.
Just never knew
you had this side to you.
Makes me a little jealous.
What are you laughing at?
You're reminiscing with me.
It's hard for me to know
how to respond properly.
I'm your subordinate after all.
I need to think
before I speak to my boss.
It's after work now.
Not your boss reminiscing with you.
Do you guys
all think office romance
is exciting
and attractive to girls?
You're pretty worked up.
Investigation didn't go well today?
Haoyun's fleet
swapped plates
before crossing the border.
Tao Jiang was there too.
Tao Jiang was there?
Yeah.
But I was too far.
I didn't get a clear shot.
That fleet wasn't
the one Haoyun registered.
If I hand this
over to Hongshen,
We're still missing
some data to back it up.
They're careful.
Guess we'll have to smoke them out.
But
we've got the bait ready.
You mean Ding Lei?
But means putting you in a tough spot.
When Chen Yi finds out,
it won't be just a few threats
that settle it.
You're not asking what he said to me?
I can guess.
Mr. Cen,
I'm a simple man. I don't get
your way of working.
Professionally, I've got nothing to say.
But personally,
if you ever put Miao Jing
in harm's way again
for your career or some plan,
I'll make sure you regret it.
Hello.
Here's your ID.
Please keep it safe.
Okay.
Thanks.
Let me see your ID.
Hi.
I need to file a report.
Hello.
Truck scrape?
Was the other driver
not in the vehicle when it happened?
It was out in the middle of nowhere.
I didn't dare wait around.
So I took a photo
of the plate.
This one.
Could you see if you can
contact the owner?
I'd like to file an insurance claim.
Sure. One moment.
Please write this down.
The owner's contact info is...
Hello?
What is it?
You both
did two runs yesterday, right?
Yes.
- Mr. Tao.
Have a seat.
Mr. Tao, here's the schedule.
Where's Bai?
I said no one's late
for the meeting.
Bai's truck
got scraped.
He went to the traffic police station.
Scraped?
Yeah.
How's there a scrape now of all times?
Which plate?
His own truck.
Call Bai.
Keep calling till he picks up.
Meeting's cancelled today!
Why's it cancelled all of a sudden?
Meeting's off?
Who told you to come?
I came on my own.
Bai doesn't know you.
I'll tell him
everything's taken care of.
You leave now.
Whose number did you leave as the reporter?
Chen Yi, do you even know
what you're doing?
If you want to
keep working your case,
then leave.
Mr. Chen.
Mr. Chen?
Sorry.
Mr. Chen!
Bai.
Mr. Chen.
Um,
Mr. Tao's asking
which mediation room we're in.
That way. Number three.
Okay.
Let's go.
Hello.
Mr. Tao.
Where's the person who filed the report?
Just a regular accident.
They already paid up
and left.
What good is money?
Do you know
how many eyes
are on us right now?
That plate's only been used a few times.
And it just happens to
get scraped
in the middle of nowhere?
Well...
Trucks
all have blind spots.
It's normal
we didn't notice.
Bai,
this isn't about a scrape.
Someone's digging into us.
Where's Chen Yi?
Where is he?
Mr-Mr. Chen was just...
Someone was indeed behind this.
The audit team
is onto us now.
What do you mean?
The one who filed the report
is Ding Lei, the head of Mingtong's
audit team.
His warehouse in the old district
was caught by Cen Ye for freight fraud.
To throw Mingtong off his trail,
Ding Lei
set his sights
on Bai's truck.
Passing the buck.
Pretty clever.
If he keeps digging,
Cen Ye won't have time for him anymore.
We'll be toast
even if we survive.
I'll go tell
Mr. Zhang about this.
You go remind him
to keep his mouth shut.
Come in.
You wanted to see me, Mr. Chen?
Sit.
I hear Mr. Cen
has been on a roll
in your team lately?
I've got
resources and connections.
Truth is,
I just lack opportunities.
He won't be above me forever.
Really?
But I think
he's about to bring you down.
What do you mean?
Just intercepted this package
from Cen Ye.
See for yourself.
How did he get all this?
You left a mess
and Cen Ye found dirt on you.
What's the point of getting mad now?
I'm telling you,
if I hadn't stopped it,
this letter would've been mailed out.
Then not just you,
but Haoyun would be screwed too.
No way.
Absolutely not.
Haoyun's waiting for
that final payment from Hongshen.
Isn't Cen Ye afraid of
tanking this whole IPO?
What are you thinking?
Still don't get it?
Either way,
you and Mr. Wang go down.
Hongshen and I foot the bill.
Mr. Chen,
since you managed to
intercept this letter,
you've already got a plan,
right?
If this
gets exposed,
nobody wins.
This matter
dies in this room.
Hongshen can't find out.
You resign now.
I'll handle Mr. Wang.
Resign?
If you don't want your reputation ruined,
get the hell out.
Didn't expect you to have such guts.
When you asked me for the courier slip,
you didn't say it was for this.
But the problem's solved.
Right?
You're hiding things from both sides.
Zhang Bin
won't be that easy to fool.
Mr. Zhang.
He's here.
Alright. Send him in.
Mr. Zhang.
You wanted to see me?
You know,
raising fish isn't all that
different from raising people.
Most people never realize
they've been living
their whole lives in a
fish bowl
that's just a little bigger.
Take Ding Lei for example.
During the audit,
he grabbed all he could.
But in the end,
a few words from you
scared him
into giving it all back.
Ding Lei used to be a good lapdog.
But
he can't stay now.
He was trying to squeeze Haoyun
for some cash.
But once the plate-switching
got found out, he wanted out.
Didn't dare take the money anymore.
So
being too cowardly
means you can't get anything big done.
Don't worry.
I've got dirt
on him and Mr. Wang.
Even if he leaves, he won't run his mouth.
Everything you said
checks out.
But there's one thing
I don't get.
That plate was registered
under Bai's name.
Port truck.
Nothing to do
with you.
Why did you stick your neck out?
Zhai Fengmao fooled me once.
I'm not letting anyone
fool me again.
That's why Zhai Fengmao's dead?
That's why.
Since you know how to handle
the audit team,
don't bother with anyone else.
You're fully in charge of this.
And then?
Then you swap positions
with Tao Jiang.
All port trucks
will be under your control.
Yi,
I didn't bring you to Haoyun
just to work
in the freight department.
Yi,
think bigger
and give it your all,
then you can play in the big leagues.
Zhai Fengmao is dead.
But let me remind you,
no one
can just cut ties
with the past.
What are you doing here?
After you got called away,
I've been waiting for you to come home.
Forget it.
Got sweat on it. Kinda dirty.
Let's go home.
Chen Yi.
Why are you always like this?
What?
Never mind.
Let's go upstairs.
Wenjie.
It's been a while since I visited you.
The other day,
Chen Yi bought a new bedding set.
Floral print.
I know
you wouldn't like them.
But
it was a sweet gesture.
Miao Jing's back too.
She
is completely different now.
Girls really do change when they grow up.
But
she's still as sensible as ever.
She still remembers my favorite tea
and what you liked best.
This rice cake
is from her.
Try some.
The kids
are all grown up now.
They have their own minds.
I can't budge them on some things.
If you were here,
maybe they'd listen to you.
I wish you were here.
Come in.
Qian.
Still not giving up?
Just take a look.
How did you
get gray hair already?
People get old.
I just want to sort this out
before I'm too old
to work.
Alright. I see.
Go back and wait.
I'll file a report to the higher-ups.
Qian.
I'm pretty confident this time.
I know
what's on your mind.
I'll report it up.
You know this case
inside out.
If a task force gets formed,
be ready to
get seconded there.
Understood.
I'm off.
You should've taken that spot
in the Criminal Investigation Unit
back then.
Investigating there would've been easier
than at the station.
Any regrets?
No regrets.
My home's right here.
Where else would I go?
I'm off.
Miao Jing, you got any hair gel?
Styling spray.
I'll head over first.
See you in a bit.
Can you help me...?
Birthday.
October 16th.
ID number.
197...
Not 197.
1016.
She's a
Libra.
Blood type AB.
Met on
February 16th, 2009.
Favorite...
Why bounce your leg?
Getting married and still acting all hood.
Don't get my clothes dirty.
I'm nervous, man.
Look, I'm sweating already.
You know what, Yi?
He was just mumbling
to himself over there.
Going on about anniversaries
and Qiao's ID
and phone number.
That's the wedding quiz
I looked up online
last night.
Tell you what,
if I'd put this much effort
into the college entrance exam,
one of us three
would've made it to university.
Yeah right.
You wouldn't even know
where to write your name
on the paper.
Get away.
Look at us.
Who
looks like
the studious one?
I'm a little scared.
What if they ask something
really heartfelt,
like what promises
I can make?
I'm not good with words.
You guys know that.
Say too much
and I might promise the moon.
But you can't live on
empty promises after marriage.
Yi, what do you think?
You'll face wedding door games too.
Consider this your practice run.
You guys over there!
Alright.
Let's head up for the bridal pickup.
Let's go!
Go!
Don't be nervous.
- I...
- Come on!
I'm going.
Go!
Let's move.
- Go!
- Come on!
Wrong way.
Here. This way.
Go!
Come on!
Go for it!
- Here we go.
- Go!
Coming.
Coming!
Which one's the alcohol?
If it's not enough,
I'll grab more.
Forget that for now. Let's first...
Come on.
Up so early.
Have some candy, sweetie.
No. Stop bothering me.
Alright.
- Seriously.
- Don't bother her.
I'll
take care of her for you.
- Gorgeous.
- Need to make it
- Too easy for him.
- harder.
Add a little more to this side.
Exactly.
What would I do without you?
So pretty.
Love it.
Close your eyes.
So beautiful, right?
Someone's knocking.
Is that him?
Li Qiao, your friend is here.
Come in.
Miao Jing?
Qiao.
You made it!
Happy wedding day.
Thank you.
Sit down.
Continue.
Ya, can you help entertain her?
Sure.
Have some candy.
Wishing you sweetness.
Thanks.
Here.
Want some water?
Come on. Sit here.
Yeah.
Look at my baby here.
Look at the photos my baby took.
- So pretty.
- What's wrong?
Nothing. Just happy.
Let's make the games harder,
- shall we?
- So pretty.
Yeah, yeah.
Who cooks after marriage?
Who cleans?
The groom's here!
He's here!
What do we do?
Block the door!
Don't be nervous.
- Hide the shoes!
- Don't be nervous.
Block the door!
What do we do?
Hurry!
What do I do?
Where do I hide?
Just look pretty.
Just focus on looking pretty.
Okay, okay.
- Don't be nervous.
- Alright.
Don't be nervous.
Okay.
Coming!
Don't push.
Why block the door?
Show us something.
Well,
here you go.
Enough red packets?
Enough?
That's barely any.
Not enough for everyone!
- Not enough!
- Right?
There are more.
Give us more.
- Enough?
- Not enough!
- Be generous!
- Take them all.
Take them all.
That's all.
Open the door!
Enough?
Handing them out!
What's this?
Hold on.
A wedding pickup needs a trap like this?
What is this, Yi?
Can't let you
marry my girl that easily!
That's right.
This is called the Fate Web.
You need to
crawl through this.
Dodge all the wrong people,
overcome every obstacle,
and tie the knot together.
Are you kidding me?
I've got bad legs.
How am I supposed to do this?
It's not hard at all!
Very easy!
Yi, you're nimble.
Can you do it for me?
Why's it always me?
Yi, come on!
Come on, Yi!
- Yi!
- I'm begging you.
Let the best man...
Who can I pair with?
You can pair with...
Look,
Miao Jing's already
in with them.
You guys send her out.
She and Yi are a good match.
Just play along.
Yeah, Miao Jing.
Miao Jing!
Come on!
Play along.
Go for it.
Help Bo out.
Yi! Yi.
Come on, Yi.
Go.
Come on.
Everybody agrees, right?
- Yes!
- Then
listen to my cue.
Here.
Go!
Come on!
Alright.
You owe me a private dinner.
Okay. A private dinner.
No problem. Come on.
Ready?
Listen for my cue.
Three, two, one.
Go!
Her question.
When do I feel that spark the most?
Can't let you hear that. Seriously.
Okay. Pass!
Ah, you're blushing.
Hold on.
Okay. Last question!
But before you
answer this,
let's find someone
to give you a little inspiration.
How about our handsome best man?
Yi!
Two private dinners.
- Two private dinners for you.
- Here we go!
What's the most sincere promise
you can make to her?
As long as she's
safe
and happy,
nothing else matters.
Good!
Great!
So cheesy!
What a generic answer.
What? What do you mean, generic?
I... I actually thought the same.
I think the best man
went easy on the groom on purpose
to save his face!
No, no.
Exactly!
So half-hearted.
Definitely!
Exactly!
Stop!
When the groom answers,
say it louder!
So the bride can hear!
Right?
Let the bride hear it clearly!
Louder!
Qiao!
I... I...
I...
I said
I'd buy you a big house
and give you a good life.
I won't lie to you.
We...
We... We'll build a good life together.
I... I love you!
Great!
Is that enough?
Yes.
Good enough.
Good.
Let's go.
Wait.
What's wrong now?
Didn't we go over everything yesterday?
The MC's here.
We need to go pick him up.
Go pick up the MC.
I need to go over things with him.
We're here.
Qiao, look who's here.
Sweetie!
Come on.
Qiao.
Good girl.
I missed you guys.
You look so pretty.
Auntie.
Thank you.
Come here, sweetie.
Yeah.
Come over here.
This is from him.
Thank you.
Wishing you a beautiful family soon.
What should you say to Auntie?
Have some candy.
Thanks. Here.
Go wish Auntie a happy wedding.
Happy wedding day, Auntie.
Good girl.
Come sit over here.
Have some water.
Okay.
Thank you.
This is from your uncle and me.
Thanks.
Your sister's too busy with work.
Can't make it.
Who were you even talking to
with that third question?
Whoever
wants to claim it.
Have some candy.
Alright.
This is Bo's wedding.
You're here playing the big romantic?
What do you mean?
You're not even thinking
about a future together?
Oh no.
Bo!
Listen.
What happened?
Take your time.
Qiao's friend, Hong,
just called.
She said
she can't make it.
Hong?
That's the bridesmaid, right?
Yes!
We need someone
to fill in as bridesmaid.
The bridesmaid can't make it...
Then I...
What's that girl's height and weight?
Height...
About...
About her size.
Similar build.
About this tall.
Miao Jing,
can you help out
and fill in?
How about I do it?
I've never been a bridesmaid before.
Alright.
We're short on time.
Let's go.
Okay.
Well, run through
the process with me again.
Hurry up.
Yeah.
First, the groom comes out.
Then...
It's like...
- See you in a bit.
- Congratulations.
Thank you.
- Thanks.
- Bo!
Great-aunt.
Great-aunt, you're here.
Alright then...
You've grown so big.
Of course.
Alright. Let me take you
to meet
my mother-in-law.
Let's go.
Come. I'll take you.
I'll take you. Let's go.
Dear family
and friends,
welcome to
the wedding
of Mr. Wang Bo
and Ms. Li Qiao.
Right now,
I believe the couple
is ready to
begin their forever together.
Everyone here, let's give them
a round of applause!
Let's welcome
the newlyweds!
Right now,
in front of all their
family and friends,
our newlyweds
have taken
center stage.
Bridesmaid, please hold
the bouquet for a moment.
And
to our newlyweds,
please turn and face each other.
Groom,
do you
take this woman
to be your wife?
To love her, protect her,
and spend your life with her?
Do you?
I do!
Great!
Wonderful!
Do you take him to be your husband?
To love him, protect him,
and spend your life with him?
Do
you?
I do!
Thank you.
Once again, congratulations to you both!
Wonderful!
I declare!
Groom,
you may kiss the bride!
Three, two, one!
Congratulations.
Congratulations to this lucky guest.
Tell everyone whether you're
a friend of the groom
or the bride,
and give them your wishes.
Bo said during the pickup
that they'd build a good life together.
His promises for the future
are made for two.
So I hope
through the highs and lows of life,
you will always walk hand in hand,
forever and always.
Wonderful!
Miao Jing, nice!
Alright.
Thank you.
The pool hall
never felt this empty before.
Bo said
you gave him fifty thousand
when he bought his place.
I'm
a single man.
I don't need much money.
Yi,
I haven't touched a single dime of
the pool hall dividends you gave me.
I just lent it to Bo.
You'll be
Bo's kids' number one godfather.
And I'll be number two.
I know how you are.
You always do things quietly.
But we remember
all the good you do.
Don't keep things
bottled up.
Just tell us anytime.
Alright, Yi.
I just want to imagine
that one day,
Bo and Li Qiao
would be with their kids,
you
would be with
your future wife
and your kids,
and
all of us
would be out
on a big grassy field.
No one else. Just us.
We'd go camping.
No worries.
Just relaxing.
It's been hectic lately.
Thanks for all the overtime.
Got any plans this weekend?
I'll take everyone to the beach for two days.
You pick the spot.
The company
covers everything.
For real?
Jing?
No need.
My team's expenses are covered by Mingtong.
Where to?
Let's go to Puri Island in Jinguo.
It's a rare team outing.
We've got to go abroad.
Right, Jing?
I'm down.
It's pretty fun there.
What do you think?
What's wrong, Mr. Chen?
Let's go to Sannan Island.
Too much hassle with visas
for all of us.
Works for me.
Whatever the boss says.
We're lucky to even go.
Alright.
Beats being stuck here
crunching numbers.
- Absolutely.
- Right.
Alright. No problem.
Should we get some essentials?
Should we?
Yeah.
Can we expense it?
- Go ask about it.
- No way.
Sunscreen.
Need to pack sunscreen and stuff.
Right.