Gross.
Take the dishes out.
Dinner's ready.
Okay.
Come on, Yi.
Bo,
you looked awfully serious
in those pre-wedding photos.
Don't look.
That's not me.
Is the soup ready?
Here you go.
Coming.
Gosh, it's super hot.
Here.
Careful.
Down it goes.
You two just sit there and watch?
It's burning hot.
Feel it?
- Qiao,
- You're such a pain.
beat him.
Don't go easy on him.
You're asking for it.
You're
always egging Qiao
how to boss me around.
When are you gonna get a girlfriend
to do the same to you?
I...
I'll just
leave it to fate.
If the right one shows up, I'm in.
If not, this is fine too.
Makes sense.
Come on.
Help yourselves.
The soup is amazing.
I simmered it all morning.
Try this.
The veggies are good too.
Spill it.
What's going on with you and Miao Jing?
I have
no idea what she's thinking now.
That's easy.
Here's the trick.
When girls say no,
they actually mean yes.
When they say they're fine,
it means they're mad.
Just do the opposite of what they say.
Nonsense.
Absolutely nonsense.
How can you do the opposite?
Just take their word for it.
Are you married?
No.
Then who in this room
has the most experience?
You do.
You silly thing.
Take the dishes back.
Kick them out.
Just shut up and eat.
What if
she says "it depends"
and tells me to figure it out myself?
That's
tougher.
But I think
it depends on
the specific situation.
Maybe try
a different approach?
Like
act cute around her?
Get lost.
Stop giving him bad ideas.
You always dodge problems
this exact same way
instead of facing your mistakes.
That's why I
wanted to move out before.
Yi,
I think first
you need to figure out
what the real problem
is between you two.
Dating and marriage
are two different things.
Dating's all about romance.
You can overlook
small conflicts
for you don't think too far ahead.
But marriage
is different.
You can't just brush things off.
Exactly.
Listen to her.
She's right.
A relationship
needs equal effort.
If one person
keeps giving
while the other only takes,
the balance will eventually fall apart.
So
what should I do?
I'm just sharing some general ideas.
You'll have to
figure out the rest yourself.
Maybe
start with
small things.
Call her at night
and say things like "I miss you,"
"are you tired?",
and "you've done a good job."
What do you think?
Why are you laughing?
No, no, no.
She has a good point.
You really are a love expert.
Let's toast to Qiao.
To Qiao.
Alright, let's eat.
Are you praising me?
Of course we are.
We really are.
Isn't that nice?
[Start with]
[small things.]
[Call her at night]
[and say things]
[like "I miss you,"]
["are you tired?",]
[and "you've done a good job."]
[Hello?]
Are you off work?
What happened to your voice?
Nothing.
Just breathed in some cold air.
Have you eaten?
I have a dinner with a client later.
What about you?
[I ate at Bo's place,]
[but I didn't eat much.]
I'll head
home soon.
[What?]
You can't eat when I'm not around?
What's so funny?
I miss you.
I miss you too.
Well,
hearing you say that,
I've suddenly got an appetite.
I'll eat a bit more later.
Go grab something too.
And wait for me,
okay?
Bye.
[Miao Jing Coming Home]
Hello?
[Hello? Chen,]
[it's me, Ma Yang.]
It's late.
What's going on?
Yu and I are
at the hospital.
Jing's mom
fainted at the hotel just now.
Which hospital?
We're at
Vineton First People's Hospital.
[I'm on my way.]
Hello, Yu.
I just called Chen.
He said he'll be here soon.
Right.
I can only wait for him to
come and fill out the forms.
He's on the way.
Alright.
Okay.
Ma Yang.
Chen.
Where is Ms. Wei?
She's still in the ER.
She hasn't come out yet.
Yu is with her.
How is she now?
How did she suddenly pass out?
I'm not sure either.
All I've got
is her ID card.
There's a lot of info I don't know,
so I've been waiting for you.
Sorry to trouble you two.
It's okay.
Have you contacted Miao Jing?
I called her,
but she didn't answer.
She's probably busy.
She's been
overwhelmed with work these days.
Don't tell her yet.
I'll handle things here.
Okay.
Yu.
You're here.
How long has she been in there?
Over half an hour.
The doctor still hasn't come out.
Where's Wei Mingzhen's family?
Doctor, how is she?
After emergency treatment,
the patient is out
of immediate danger.
But we've found
that the cancer cells
have already spread
to her lungs and liver.
She's at Stage IV breast cancer.
How could this happen?
How much time does she have left?
That depends on
the treatment plan
and how well she recovers.
If her condition improves,
chemotherapy may be an option.
If not, we can only
focus on conservative treatment.
And
judging by her current condition,
she likely knew about it for a while.
Please be prepared
for the worst.
Okay.
Shouldn't we tell Jing
about something
this serious?
I just don't know
if she can break away from work now.
I'll take care of it.
You have had a long day.
Go home and get some rest.
It's fine.
Let's head out then.
We'll go now.
By the way,
please don't
mention this
at the company.
Just pretend you don't know.
Okay
Bye.
Let's go.
The patient will wake up from
anesthesia in about half an hour.
Given the severity of her condition,
please stay with her at all times.
Do not leave her unattended.
What's Jing gonna do?
She's still away on a business trip,
and now her mom...
Who could've
seen this coming?
Good thing she's got a brother,
though they're not blood-related.
But...
Yu,
is Ms. Wei
his stepmother?
I don't know.
Jing rarely talks
about her family.
But she did tell me
that she came to Vineton
with her mom when she was little.
If Chen Yi really is her brother,
then it's probably true.
No wonder Chen told me
not to talk about it.
He's really considerate.
For someone who isn't related by blood,
he's gone far for her.
- Let's take a taxi home.
- Yeah, sure.
Let's go.
Jing is away on a business trip.
Don't talk yet.
I need to ask you something.
Just nod if I'm right.
You came back this time
to ask Jing for money?
If you don't want money,
are you expecting her to take care of you?
I called her.
She'll be back tonight.
I don't need your help.
Don't worry.
I'm not doing this for you.
How is she?
The doctor said it's her breast.
I'll go ask for
more details with you.
Let's go.
You can go home first.
I'll stay here tonight.
I'll stay with you.
And I'll find a caregiver tomorrow,
so you can get some rest.
Don't worry.
I'm here.
I'm fine.
I'll be discharged in a few days.
I'll find you a caregiver tomorrow.
I have to work and won't
have time to come by during the day.
No need.
Either you listen to me,
or you're on your own.
[Hello, Yi.]
[You asked me to have Gordo]
[look into Wei Mingzhen before.]
[They just got back to me.]
[They found out]
[she remarried in Rocford.]
[Her new husband had a son,]
[and his family seemed]
[pretty well-off.]
Come in.
Hello,
I'm Wei Mingzhen's family.
She's in Bed 18.
What's your relation with her?
I'm her daughter.
Sounds like
she's been doing alright these years.
So why did she come back?
[Not necessarily.]
[The guy]
[has a son,]
who should be in middle school now.
My friend in Rocford
sells insurance.
[He found]
[an inquiry record]
[from Wei Mingzhen]
[for a cancer insurance plan.]
[But it was pretty expensive,]
[and nothing came of it.]
Late-stage cancer?
I thought she only needed a few days
of observation.
Let me walk you through
her condition first.
She is currently at
Stage IV breast cancer.
That means it's terminal.
The cancer has already spread to her bones,
skull, liver, lungs,
pleura, and other areas.
In other words,
it has metastasized.
Her vital organs
are also
beginning to fail.
At this stage,
treatment focuses on
relieving her pain
and extending her life.
This is her pathology report.
You can take a look.
The results show
that she had received
medication treatment before,
but it appears she
hasn't continued treatment
for the past year.
That's why
the cancer spread so rapidly
and her condition deteriorated so quickly.
[I heard she was hospitalized]
[for quite a while.]
[The guy couldn't afford to support]
[both a sick wife and a kid,]
[so they split up.]
Okay. I got it.
Get some sleep.
This afternoon her condition was critical.
With
no immediate family
present,
we performed
emergency treatment
according to protocol.
You have no objection, correct?
Alright.
These are the informed consent form
and surgical consent form.
You need to sign them.
How much time does she have left?
It's not looking good.
Given her current condition,
at most one month.
Is there anything we can do?
There are
two options.
One is chemotherapy alone.
The other is
chemotherapy
with targeted drugs.
But
that treatment would be
very costly.
Honestly,
considering her current condition,
the outcomes of both options
may not be very different.
Either way,
be prepared for what's ahead.
Think it over,
and let me know which
treatment plan you choose,
okay?
One yuan.
Don't start smoking.
It's bad for your lungs.
I brought the blanket up,
and she's asleep now.
Tomorrow, I'll move her to a private room
and go home to grab
some clean clothes for her.
I'll go back to hand over my work
and take a few days off.
I've decided.
I'm gonna get her treated.
Alright, alright.
I'm not tired.
Don't worry.
Is my baby home from school?
Let me talk to her.
Sweetheart,
have you missed Grandma?
I've missed you so much.
Did your teacher praise you today?
Good girl.
I will
bring you
a pink barbie doll later.
Okay, okay.
Bye.
See you soon.
No.
Wait.
Just call me
if you need anything.
I'll get it for you.
You need some water?
Here. Take a sip.
Drink slowly.
Careful.
You're this sick
and your daughter
hasn't even come to see you?
She's at work.
They really need her there.
No matter how busy she is,
she should
look after you when you're sick.
What good is it if she doesn't care?
She'll be here soon.
Besides, I'm fine.
She's so busy with work.
Is she dating anyone?
You may
not be worried now,
but when you
see others become
grandparents,
you'll start worrying.
So noisy.
You mean the TV is too loud?
I'll turn it off.
Have some more.
Come on.
Here.
Good. You need to eat more.
Mei,
you can go home.
I'll stay with her.
She didn't eat much.
Try to get her to eat a little more.
Call me
if you need anything.
Okay.
What are you doing here?
I took some time off.
I'll stay with you for a couple of days.
Why did you take time off?
Go back to work.
Making money matters more.
In your eyes,
money will always come first.
A woman has nothing
if she doesn't have money.
What's wrong?
Does it hurt?
Move up a bit.
Here.
Easy, easy.
Lying all day feels awful.
I wanna go down and take a walk.
Dr. Cui said you can't walk around yet.
The doctor said
you can still
go outside in a wheelchair for some air.
Mom!
Doctor, please save her!
Mom, please hold on!
Don't leave me!
Looks like
they're fighting death.
After I die,
will you burn joss paper for me?
How much do you want?
The more, the better.
With it,
many things can be taken care of.
Take this money
and buy joss paper for me.
No need to burn a lot every year.
Just don't forget.
Let's go back and sleep.
Miao Jing.
She's missing.
Stay calm. I'll have the nurse check the cameras.
Let's go look for her.
Excuse me,
have you seen the patient
from Bed 18?
No.
Okay. Thanks.
Come on. Let's go back.
I don't wanna be
some pathetic, failed,
and haggard woman.
Even if it's my last moment,
I wanna
look beautiful.
Don't say such foolish things.
Even if I have to die,
I don't wanna die
in that tiny bed,
looking miserable and helpless,
like an old rag.
What's wrong?
Jing,
I promise you
I'll be
a better mom
from now on.
You lazy bum!
Gosh,
hurry up!
Cooking takes forever.
I'm starving.
Are you trying to kill me,
lazy bum?
What did you say?
Get out.
Get over here.
Come here.
That's how you talk to your cousin?
Watch your mouth.
What are you doing?
What am I doing?
Why are you hitting my son?
Didn't you hear how he was talking?
Get lost.
Go inside and do your homework.
Move,
you brat.
How is the meal still not ready?
It's been ages.
You're useless
at everything.
Mingzhen,
- Sis.
- what brings you here?
I came back to see you.
Where is Jing?
She's
inside.
Has Jing been good?
She's a good girl.
Don't worry. She's doing just fine.
Actually, I came back
this time to take Jing home.
She's been staying
with you for so long,
and I hate to keep bothering you.
Alright.
Oh,
these are
for you and your husband.
You really didn't have to
bring anything.
Let me get you some water.
Jing,
I'm here to pick you up.
I'm taking you home.
Of course.
We're
gonna be together every day.
I'll take you
to the amusement park.
We'll ride the roller coaster,
set off fireworks,
and eat hamburgers. Sound good?
Okay.
Whatever you want to do,
we'll do it together.
Anything other kids have,
you'll have too.
Here.
The morgue charges by the day.
Please arrange the funeral soon.
One of you, come handle the paperwork.
I'll go handle it.
Wait here for me.
I'll be back soon.