Hello.
Half or full portion
of white cut chicken?
Full, please.
Got it.
And we'll also have
the typhoon shelter fried crab.
- Okay.
- And the steamed fish.
Sure thing.
Here you go.
Anything else you want?
That's enough.
No point wasting food.
Okay.
Oh right,
when you and Ding Lei
went to get the confirmations,
did you pull the list?
I've already done it.
It's in my office drawer.
Haoyun's financial accounts
are all with local banks.
Check out
the local policies later.
After all,
those little details
are easy to tamper with.
Okay.
Excuse me.
All your dishes are served.
Enjoy.
This spread's plenty for us.
This is good.
Sweet,
your favorite.
You two are so close?
I never heard
Miao Jing mention you.
Does your company
require staff
to report family info on hiring?
No, not really.
No surprise
she never brought me up
to you.
Workplace lines don't call for that.
But besides work,
we used to date.
She's quite reserved.
If we didn't work
at the same firm,
we'd lose touch completely,
like her last ex.
There was someone before him?
I remember it was her college classmate.
They met on the swim team.
We just weren't compatible.
Even her first love ended that bitterly.
I guess I only get to see her
thanks to our jobs.
First love?
I doubt it.
Let's eat.
It'll get cold.
Help yourself, my treat.
Check, table 28 please.
Someone left a card
for your table.
The guy with glasses.
That's my card.
Just swipe it.
She's in the restroom.
You're our guest.
Guests should be treated.
I said I'd treat her anyway.
No way the guest foots the bill.
Want another table
to sort this out?
What did you say?
Your total is
458 RMB.
Just swipe the card, okay?
Thanks.
Let's drive you back.
No need.
My ride's almost here.
Safe trip.
See you tomorrow.
What are you laughing at?
I thought you'd ignore me
till you got home.
I wasn't ignoring you.
You don't like Cen Ye.
I barely know him.
No strong feelings either way.
I thought
you'd want to hear
about my past with him.
But you think
prying about exes
is tacky
and petty.
So all you can do
is toss and turn alone,
your mind tangled
in endless
chaotic thoughts.
And...
A top grad from Jiaohai University,
yet messes up idioms.
Get huffy from embarrassment?
I'm annoyed he knows more about
your life these past years than I do.
Well, he's an ex anyway.
Tell me about
your exes.
I'm curious.
What?
Nothing much to tell.
I wanna know everything.
When did you meet them,
how many have there been,
and what do they do?
I met them ages ago.
What?
Go on, tell me.
Come on in.
I'll tell you.
Look at all the dust.
Why always pick plain ones like this?
At least get something brighter.
You wouldn't understand.
Which one goes where?
Give me a hand.
Your sister used to
have two pots of daisies
on her desk.
She loved that kind of color.
Put that down.
Start with this one.
Okay.
Almost done.
Have some water.
How's business lately?
Not bad.
Not many kids,
but more adults in the classes.
Teaching adults
is easier than kids anyway.
Besides,
you're still a kid yourself.
You don't have the patience for them.
Heard
you've been
hanging around Zhang Bin a lot lately.
Liu Binbo.
You know him?
Heard of him.
He's from Gangcheng.
Zhang Bin's been meeting with him
to strike a big deal.
What, exactly?
Probably import and export business.
Zhang Bin and I
only play pool together occasionally.
He wouldn't
talk business with me.
Leave this photo
with us.
Our police officers
will keep an eye on Zhang Bin.
Stay out of this.
I'm just a regular citizen.
What could I even do?
Yi.
Just a heads-up.
Don't gamble your future
on the past.
It's not worth it.
If we could let go that easily,
then why
did you bring me here today?
Bo's moving tomorrow.
I'm heading over to help them out.
I'm off.
Yi.
Spare key's on the shoe cabinet.
Take it with you.
My princess.
Check out our new place.
It's spacious.
This side
faces
south.
What do you think?
Check out the kitchen.
Here?
Yeah.
Cookware's all ready.
Everything's set.
You've thought of everything.
- Check out the room.
- There?
Kids' room.
Right.
Bathroom's big too.
Bedroom?
Our bedroom.
Like it?
Yeah.
I love it.
Babe.
Believe me.
I'll give you a lifetime of happiness.
Kang'an.
Thank you for giving me
such a warm home.
Moving house
Careful.
ages you five years in one go.
That's what you get for not working out.
Go clean the bedroom.
Come on.
Can't I at least get a sip of water?
My legs are killing me.
Thanks for all the hassle, Yi.
No trouble, anything else to carry up?
I'll grab it all at once.
Appreciate it.
We need to worry about
their future life.
- Which way?
- Moving?
It's here?
This is the place?
Yeah.
Nice young man.
Mom, Dad.
You came?
Mr. and Mrs. Li.
You're here.
You should've told me.
I'd have picked you up.
What's all this?
We moved to
a bigger place.
More comfortable.
And
better decor too,
Qiao will love living here.
Right.
Let's go.
Our Qiao isn't staying here.
She's coming home with me.
Mrs. Li.
- Mrs. Li.
- Mom.
Li Qiao and I
plan to get married.
Married?
You don't even
have a proper house ready.
She won't marry you.
You expect Qiao
to live in a dump like this?
Look at this place.
It is
a pigsty.
Who gave you permission
to get married?
Let's go.
Go.
Boss.
Boss, you buying a place?
The quarterly dividends
are in.
With some extra from elsewhere,
should cover a down payment.
Who's this?
Nice to meet you.
I work at the pool hall,
came to help Bo move.
Chen Yi, come on in.
Come inside.
Yeah, boss.
What did you just call him?
Boss?
Isn't he just the front desk guy
at the pool hall?
Bo didn't tell you?
He took over the hall this quarter.
He probably wanted to wait
till the dividends came in
before telling you.
Right.
Now that the money's here,
we can buy the place.
Qiao and I
plan to buy this place.
Yeah.
He only got the confidence to tell you
once he had money.
Right?
No way.
Boss.
Rocky was just talking about
the classes next month.
Why don't you take them
to check out the hall?
Sure.
Sir, madam,
if you've got time later
we could
head over to the hall for a look.
Yeah.
The hall's really nice.
It is all fixed up nice.
This place is just a mess.
You're such a silly girl.
Let's go see the hall.
The hall's really great.
Let's go.
Is it far?
Not at all.
I'm not going if I have to
climb that high again there.
I'll carry you down.
How can you buy a place like this?
No lift at all.
What'll you do when you're older?
Look at other flats.
You hear me?
Sir, Madam.
He'll carry mom.
I'll carry you.
Easy, easy.
Watch your step.
Easy.
Sir, Madam.
This is
our pool hall.
Boss, Madam.
Get back to your work.
Keep teaching the lessons.
Sir, it's called Diagonal.
Our main business
is billiards coaching.
It's not full of
random rowdy folks
like you might imagine.
All our coaches
are professional instructors
who only run
formal classes.
Boss, Madam.
Back to your duties.
Keep at it.
Bo, look at this.
Coach Wang.
Why does it still say Coach Wang here?
Can't you sort this simple thing out
as an employee?
Go deal with it yourself.
I'm with guests here.
You should get back to your work.
It's fine, really.
I'm not busy at all.
Sir, Madam.
I never
put on airs
as the boss.
I get along with all staff
just like old friends.
But when trouble pops up,
I know how to take charge
and lead properly.
Wait, the real boss is Yi...
Yi.
Sir, Madam.
Bo's office is upstairs.
Want to check it out?
Yeah, I've got an office
on the second floor.
Yeah.
There's a second floor?
This way.
- Pretty big.
- Come on up.
Yeah.
Sir, Madam.
Watch the stairs.
Okay.
What's going on, Yi?
This is one of our offices.
Here.
This is my office.
Yeah.
You secretly
started a business
and didn't even
brag to us?
Just keeping my big plans low-key.
Yeah.
Not bad.
Having an office like this
is good.
Solid wood, huh?
Looks brand new.
But your desk's totally empty.
Do you just sit here
staring at photos all day?
Not really.
I barely stay
in this office.
I'm out front most days
meeting with
tons of clients.
So this desk's brand new,
as you can see.
I haven't had time to fill it up.
Mrs. Li, have some water.
Honey.
Bo's at work.
Don't bother him.
Okay.
Let's go then.
Alright.
We're off.
Mr. and Mrs. Li.
About the marriage...
Does it even need asking?
Yes.
Great.
Now that you're a boss,
dress
a bit more maturely from now on.
It's fine.
- You're still young.
- Let me see you out.
Wait for me.
Not bad.
Take care, sir.
How big is this venue?
Not huge, but we're...
How much per hour?
20 yuan.
- Bye, sir.
- 20 yuan.
Four tables.
Bye.
Forty's a fair price.
Twenty...
- Mrs. Li.
- 80 yuan.
- Let me drive you home.
- One hour...
- If it operates
- No need.
a full eight hours a day,
- that's
- Say goodbye
- 960 yuan daily.
- to him.
Thirty days times 960
equals 28,800 yuan,
subtract half of that for costs...
Alright, go.
Goodbye.
Bro.
You're the best.
You're the best, seriously.
You nearly spilled it.
But you pulled it off alright.
You pulled it off.
Come over for dinner at my place.
My treat.
Come on.
Let's go.
This is the official account book.
Covers equipment and all revenue.
We have digital copies too,
but keep this hard copy safe.
The tax registration certificate.
File taxes accurately at the tax bureau.
Wait, wait, Yi.
Weren't we just putting on a show?
Just listen and remember all this.
Here's the business license
and the health permit.
You came with me
when we got these.
The industry and commerce office.
Right.
Don't forget to pay the insurance.
This...
Never mind.
I'll make you a checklist later.
About
Rocky's dividends.
Pay him in full as usual.
You know he's simple-minded.
Keep an eye on him.
This is the bank card.
And this is the safe key.
Inside the safe are
contracts
and documents.
Don't ever lose track of them.
Yi.
I borrowed
the money from you.
And I'm just managing the hall for you.
Don't just ditch it.
Alright.
Treat it as a loan from me then.
You've always wanted
a stable life with Li Qiao, right?
What I said earlier
wasn't a joke.
Nor just lip service to her parents.
The pool hall doesn't
attract sketchy crowds anymore.
You spend way more time here
than I ever do.
You get along great
with all coaches and staff.
You're better suited to run it than I am.
Come on.
It's not like I'm leaving forever.
I'll stop by whenever I'm in town.
Otherwise I'd have
nowhere to go.
So where are you going this time?
Yi.
Give me a straight answer.
Don't worry.
It's a good place.
Quit staring at me like that.
I'm not staring.
Creepy.
Creepy?
I'm getting married in a couple days.
You're gonna be my best man
and drive the wedding limo.
Sure.
Can you also host the ceremony?
Save me the cost of hiring an emcee.
Emcee?
Sign it.
It's no death warrant.
Stamping my fingerprint?
Go ahead.
Stop sighing.
The audited party's
current asset figures
are far too vague.
We can't draft audit work papers
without clear supporting evidence.
We hope you can
provide
a reasonable solution.
We've sent over all the inventory records
from recent years,
and cooperated fully
every time you asked for materials.
But I can't guarantee
there aren't gaps in the files.
Besides that,
our audit team
found several
shipment records
during inventory count
that don't match the data on file.
Destination unknown.
What do you think, Mr. Wang?
Young lady.
You're new around here, right?
With all those warehouses,
all those fleets,
do you
have any idea how much cargo
we ship out every single day?
Setting aside
whether your accusation
is just groundless nitpicking,
even if this discrepancy really exists,
it's most likely
a clerical oversight.
It proves nothing.
Watch your wording.
Payments for those outbound shipments
are completely unaccounted for.
We have reasonable grounds to suspect
that your company staff
may have embezzled corporate funds.
You sure lack
professional expertise
yet have wild imaginations.
Sir.
Supervisor Cen and Manager Wang
are in a meeting.
It's fine.
I'll just check them out.
Such narrow-minded thinking.
I can get someone out for you.
I'm coming in.
What department are you from?
Can't you knock first?
Hello, everyone.
I'm Chen Yi, the new hire.
Mr. Zhang said
I'm taking over
Mingtong from now on.
A pleasure to meet you.
Audit meeting, huh?
Perfect.
I'll sit in and learn the process.
What's this about?
Why are you looking at me?
Carry on.
Gotta go through the motions, right?
I'm Cen Ye, head of
Mingtong audit team,
Miao Jing, Deputy lead.
Keep going.
Go ahead.
Besides the warehouse discrepancies,
we also uncovered multiple
high-value contracts at your firm
that lack rigorous approval workflows.
Many were not processed strictly
in line with internal company policies.
Do you have any plans
to review and upgrade
your internal control framework?
She speaks clearly and logically.
Pretty sharp, isn't she?
Mr. Wang, earlier
you said she lacked experience,
are you just jealous of her?
Please don't
interrupt the meeting.
Additionally,
from your 2010
financial statements,
we observed that your company's
accounts receivable turnover ratio
has declined year over year.
And several receivables have
remained outstanding for extended periods.
Have you
implemented any measures
to strengthen collection efforts
and receivables management?
These are my three
core questions.
Xiao Yu will cover the rest.
The auditee may provide
unified responses
once all audit inquiries conclude.
Wait, is the audit process
this cumbersome?
A simple spreadsheet would do.
With all this back-and-forth,
you could've drafted two reports already.
Mr. Chen. You haven't
officially taken over yet, have you?
At least for today,
M .Wang
is still in charge.
You have no authority
to interrupt our session.
Which just proves
your whole process prioritizes
form over practicality.
My official authority took effect
the day I joined Haoyun.
If you have objections,
feel free
to escalate them to your superiors.
Then let's not waste
any more time here.
We'll adjourn for today.
Once you've sorted out
your internal issues,
we'll talk again.
Chen...
Sir.
I'm the HR manager.
Let me take you
to your office first.
Just tell me where it is.
I'll go check out the audit team.
It's next to the freight department's
office area, your office is
right next to Mr. Wang's.
Sir, it's this way.
He said he's a manager,
but which business segment
he's in charge of?
Even if he's just a figurehead,
Mr. Zhang
handpicked him himself.
Sorry about earlier.
I bought you some drinks.
Milk tea and coffee.
It's fine.
But you just barged into
the meeting room,
it gave me a heart attack.
Ms. Miao.
I'd like to ask you something.
Milk tea.
Coffee.
Isn't he the guy
who picks Jing up every day?
He charged straight into
the meeting room without a word.
He's the new project manager.
Starting today,
he's replacing
that Wang guy
as our contact.
We're already acquainted,
so future coordination
should be a breeze.
He's way easier on the eyes
than Manager Wang.
Even with that terrible combo?
Suit, floral shirt and sneakers.
You wouldn't get it.
It's trendy dandy style.
Well, I don't get it.
Handsome men are thorny roses,
he looks really hard to get along with.
How's my outfit?
Come closer.
When you were at Company Kuang,
you used to wear suits too.
You had less money back then,
yet dressed far more meticulously.
Peaked lapels always paired with striped ties.
But now you show up
in sneakers.
I was younger back then.
I had to dress mature
to command respect from others.
I don't need to do that anymore.
You used to
try to look polished,
but now you
dress down on purpose.
Why?
Afraid Haoyun will rub off on you?
If that's the case,
why wade into this mess?
Can't I just get an honest job?
I'll give you one more chance
to tell me the real reason.
I just wanted to surprise you.
This sure is a surprise.
You look very professional today.
Do I look good?
You've buttoned your shirt up too high.
On purpose.
Undo it.
What?
You've been in there
for half an hour already.
I thought you passed out.
Let me dry your hair.
After you left today,
that Ding Lei in our group
was complaining nonstop.
He said you embarrassed him
in front of everyone,
Haoyun really
doesn't take our audit team
seriously.
And you joined Haoyun
right at this critical moment,
does that mean you don't
respect me either?
I'd never dare.
Zhang Bin came to the pool hall
to see you dozens of times,
so why did you agree to this job now?
Didn't you say he
looks good in a suit?
I just wanted you to see
I look just as good too.
Or what if you leave me for him?
When did I ever say
he looks good in suits?
I hadn't even named anyone,
yet you knew straight away.
Seems like you two are pretty close.
Don't deflect.
Are you plotting something?
Your nose is bleeding.
Too long in the shower.
Got too much internal heat.
Go see a doctor?
No need.
I'll grab some herbal tea downstairs.
Take this and wait for your number.
What to eat?
This is the place I saw.
- I heard it's
- This one?
really good.
So many people.
Shall we eat here then?
Sure.
We've got Qixi discounts.
Come check out our Qixi set menus.
Hi, table for two.
Two.
- Yeah.
- You need to take a number.
How long's the wait?
It's quite busy right now,
roughly an hour.
Alright then.
You still wanna eat here?
Yeah.
Shall we
- go get in line?
- Sure.
Let's take a look
at the menu.
Here's the menu.
What do you want?
Braised pork rice?
Qixi set menu.
Maybe we should
get this couple's set.
It's 40% off.
Way better value than ordering à la carte.
The couple's set?
Doesn't feel right for us.
I never pegged you, Ma Yang,
you're usually so easygoing,
didn't expect you
to care about that.
No, I...
I get it.
Scrambling for discounts
sounds cheap, I won't deny that.
But still,
you're the one I asked out today.
I'd never let anyone else
find out about this.
If Miao Jing were a guy,
I wouldn't have
bothered you.
Qixi discount.
Let's just get this.
Hey, isn't that Jing?
Who?
Jing.
It is her.
Okay.
Wait, let me get your change.
Jing.
Okay.
I knew it was you.
Just you?
I just saw a guy over there who looked
a lot like that new guy from Haoyun.
What are you two doing together?
We're just grabbing dinner.
Over there.
Having a meal.
Right, Jing.
Did you know
Ma Yang saw Mr. Cen
up to something when he
worked overtime last night?
What?
Mr. Cen was asking about a bag.
Aren't you curious?
Don't interrupt.
I'm getting to the good part.
He was asking a sales associate about
the new women's bag that just came out.
Guess who it's for?
His mom?
Isn't her birthday coming up?
You've been broken up for over a year,
and you still remember
his mom's birthday?
Why'd you buy
two cups of herbal tea?
Who's the other one for?
I've got internal heat,
one cup might not cut it.
You two should go get your food now.
I hear they're calling numbers.
No rush, it's fine.
I'm in a hurry to get home.
Okay.
We're off.
Bye, Jing.
- Let's go.
- Wait a second.
I swear that guy back there
looked exactly like...
It's true.
Not drinking it?
I'm not helping you if you bleed again.
You ran off the second you saw them.
Scared of being seen together?
I just didn't wanna put you on the spot.
Sounds like you're looking out for me.
If it's true, you shouldn't have
joined Haoyun at all.
Are you hiding some tricky scheme
up your sleeve?
Not at all.
Chen Yi,
promise me
you won't pull those petty stunts
that push me away like you used to.
Don't leave me behind again,
okay?
Then you promise me too,
no more dangerous stuff.
You hear me?
Here, eat.
Before it gets cold.
What's wrong?
Is there something on my face?
No.
Then what are you looking at?
Just looking.
You really do look great in a suit.
Can't take my eyes off you.
We're at the office building now.
So?
You said it yourself.
You wore a suit to my workplace
so I'd only have eyes
for you.
So here I am,
staring at you properly.