Hold still.
Looking sharp.
Feels like
we're heading to the altar.
Jittery?
About time.
Does it still hurt?
Shall we?
Court is now in session.
In 2005,
Zhai Fengmao trafficked me
out of the country.
A year later,
he sold me to
Kao in Jinguo.
I was forced into smuggling.
With police help,
I made it back home
in 2008.
I started college
in 2005,
losing contact with
my only family.
I came back
to Vineton in 2011
as an auditor.
That's when I
found evidence
of Zhang Bin's crimes.
As an auditor
for Mingtong,
I present this evidence
under professional guidelines.
I swear that my testimony
is the truth.
The court has reached a verdict.
Please rise!
Having reviewed the evidence
and the public indictment,
this court rules that
defendants
Zhang Bin
and Tao Jiang
bypassed
customs controls
to
smuggle
germanium,
a highly
restricted
rare earth
metal.
This is a severe criminal offense
with devastating social impact.
They
violated
the penal code
and
must
face justice.
Zhang Bin
directed
and controlled
the entire operation
as the
lead offender.
Tao Jiang
acted
as his accomplice,
handling the
logistics.
Weighing
the facts
and the sheer damage
done
to
our community,
this court
sentences you
as
follows:
Defendant
Zhang Bin,
for
smuggling,
arson,
and
attempted murder,
you will serve a term
of
life imprisonment
and
forfeit all civil rights
for the rest of your natural life.
Defendant
Tao Jiang,
for
smuggling,
you are
sentenced
to eight years
in prison.
Finally, with regard to
the 2005 arson that
resulted in the death of a civil servant
and the fraudulent schemes involving Kuang Corp,
the defendant,
Zhai Fengmao,
is now in custody.
For these
heinous crimes,
this court sentences you
to life imprisonment,
with the permanent deprivation of all civil rights.
This concludes the sentencing.
This court is adjourned.
I still have a few days off.
Finish up this to-do list.
Once we're done,
let's invite
the gang over
for dinner.
You're selling off my whole life.
What's in it for me?
You get to be with me.
Duh.
Where are we running off to?
To the ends
of the earth!
Babe,
you're officially responsible
for me now.
It's a promise.
We're a package.
Deal?
Hang this up.
Without the pole.
I'm too short, you idiot!
Just jump for it.
Oh, sure. Watch me fly.
Are these chopped or butchered?
He's useless.
Classic.
Put this here.
Dude,
just step away, please...
Not good?
It's totally fine...
Hey,
look...
Stop, sweetie...
Don't suck on it.
Where are
the clippers?
Hey,
don't scratch it.
In the
pink bin.
Just stay still.
Can you grab it?
Yeah, hold still,
OK...
Sweet!
There you go.
Hey, Zhou.
We're making hot pot tonight.
Join us.
[Nah,]
[you kids have fun.]
An old head
will ruin the vibe.
Hey, Mr. Zhou.
Here for the pickup.
Got it.
Just a sec.
What are you guys up to next?
Reopening
the pool club.
[Thanks, sweetie.]
I've got no real skills, man.
Always just
followed your lead.
Plus, the kids are itching
to get back to practice.
Yeah.
The walls need work.
We've delayed it forever.
We've been hitting
Home Depot
to get
the right plaster.
Total headache.
He can pitch in
before we go.
Since when do you do manual labor?
I can patch walls like a boss.
Back when she was in school,
I did every odd job in town.
So...
your flight
is
already set?
Leaving on Saturday.
No airport drama, alright?
Keep it easy for me.
Man,
you were
barely home.
Now you're taking off
again.
I'll be back
for New Year's.
Yeah, but...
sh*t, man.
I don't know
how to say it.
We go way back,
you know?
You're like my brother.
Don't get all sappy.
I just hate seeing you go.
You'll be fine.
They're leaving us behind.
F*cking cold-blooded, right?
C'mon, let's toast.
I'm in!
Toasting to the move!
Cheers,
everyone!
What about you?
Oh,
nothing new.
My salon is solid.
I might
get some extra hands.
I really wanna be with my boy.
But nothing's set
in stone.
Yo,
we got a classic line-up!
You guys ready?
What?
Hey,
to beat the blues,
I'm gonna sing
for you guys.
OK,
listen up.
Stop staring...
Keep eating.
Pretend
I'm some
street busker.
♪Should old acquaintance...♪
♪Be forgot...♪
♪And never...♪
♪And never brought to mind?♪
♪And days of auld lang syne!♪
♪For auld lang syne, my dear!♪
Come on! Drink up!
Pretty good, huh?
You killed it, babe!
Bottoms up!
Hi, beautiful.
I have some great news.
Zhang Bin got the book
thrown at him.
Zhai is locked up for good.
It's finally over.
I know the kids
came by.
Honestly,
we couldn't do it without them.
Yi is
a grown man now,
but he still acts
like a kid.
Thank God Jing's got his back.
She's the real deal now.
Top of her class,
audit manager,
highest degree
out of all of us.
They should be
flying out now.
Moving to the big city.
Good for them.
God bless'em.
You can finally rest, my love.
So you go to work,
and I do what?
Housework and cooking?
Sounds perfect.
Major deja vu.
Like what?
Years ago,
at the bus station.
I had you on the back of my bike.
We rode for
what felt like forever.
You
fell asleep against my back.
Feels like a lifetime ago...
I know.
Hey, look.
The sunset is beautiful.
Well, well.
Miao Jing.
Cen Ye got
kicked out again, huh?
Guess he couldn't
handle the heat.
It's called business travel.
You can tag along
if you want.
I don't lick boots.
Everyone knows
he screwed up.
He killed
the Haoyun audit,
and Hongshen lost their minds.
He's done for.
You talk a lot for a loser.
Be glad Monica
saved your job.
You took bribes from Haoyun
and got yourself demoted...
Yet you're
still talking trash.
Jing!
Need a hand?
What?
Packing up your desk?
Serves you right!
Your sugar daddy's is gone,
you're
outta the game.
She got her own office.
You didn't know?
A private office?
No f*cking way!
Yes f*cking way.
Because
I actually
do my job
and mitigate risks.
For your information,
Haoyun is a criminal syndicate.
Cen Ye is
working with
the police now.
That's why HQ
and the client
are keeping this quiet.
The official announcement
will be
on the portal soon.
Oh, and about my new title?
Check your inbox.
Junior,
move aside.
Tell
the new guys
dinner is on
the new manager.
Let's mingle!
On it, boss!
Woohoo!
She actually got it!
Told you.
She is the queen!
Never doubt me.
Hell yeah!
Awesome!
She crushed it!
Party tonight!
Yay!
What's the plan?
Let's go crazy!
Where we going?
Shall we...
Hot pot!
This looks so good.
Tastes even better.
The pies are here!
Let's get a toast going
for the queen!
Congrats, girl!
We're so proud of you!
Love you guys!
Let's go!
Congrats on the raise!
Bottoms up!
Cheers!
I knew she'd get the raise.
I'm gonna eat my weight
in pizza!
Oh, absolutely!
I'm Ma Yang.
On Cen Ye's team.
Looking forward to working
with you all.
Cheers!
Come on!
Drink up!
Help yourselves, please.
Thank god,
I was starving.
Take some.
This is incredible.
You gotta try this one.
Cool.
Hey, babe.
[Where you at?]
Eating with the crew at Sino Bistro.
Don't wait up for dinner.
I'm in the neighborhood.
I'll come
get you.
We're on the main floor.
Wanna join us?
Sure.
So~ Coming back
with a hot plus-one, huh?
A 6'3'' total stud!
Girl knows how to shop.
[OK.]
Babe!
Oh, dang!
That's him!
That's her guy? So hot.
What a looker!
Am I crashing
the party?
No,
not at all!
Make room for him!
Come on, here!
Please!
Hey,
get some forks here!
Hey, guys.
Name's Chen Yi.
Her guy.
Hey, you staying here
for long?
For good.
I'm hers now.
We're gonna get beers, man.
Aw... so sweet!
C'mon,
dig in!
Gracias!
Come on.
That lamb is heavenly.
C'mon, eat!
Here.
So, when is the big day?
Excuse me?
Seriously?
[Water, please.]
Come on!
You two are head over heels.
Where's the ring?
Hey,
stop grilling them.
Just
stuff your face
already!
Hey...
meh...
Have some warm tea for your cramps.
Hey,
you better
lock her down.
Guys at the office
are lining up for her.
Can't blame'em. She's a keeper.
True that.
What are we missing?
Pasta?
Ooh, grab this too?
I need more food.
That portion was a joke.
You should've
said so then.
88 for broccoli?
That's
a total rip-off!
My trophy husband, everyone!
I gave you cash
weeks ago,
and you never asked for more.
Babe,
inflation is real,
You're my sugar mama now.
Gotta watch
the dimes.
C'mon, housewife.
When we getting that car?
Cruising in the cold
sucks.
We barely unpacked.
Chill,
we'll get it later.
Going stir-crazy yet?
Nah, I'm good.
No job,
no crew.
You're like
a caged animal.
Wanna feel how wild I am?
Seriously,
though.
This town
is new to you.
Quit babying me, alright?
Listen to this.
I'm listening.
I actually
went to see you after
I got back home.
When I was in college?
Why didn't you say hi?
You were playing badminton.
You literally
glowed, babe.
And I
was a total wreck.
Hitchhiked for days.
Smelled like hot garbage.
I didn't want to spook you.
Survival changes you.
You grow up,
you learn.
I was
used to
the dark.
I thought my shadow
would only ruin you.
But seeing you again...
it woke me up.
I wanted to push you out,
but I was starving for you.
Now?
I'm your shadow.
Wherever you step, I'm there.
Babe...
I didn't care
if you looked down on me.
But...
you are my home.
The only place
I fit.
I want your life
to shine.
If being
consumed
by you,
day and night...
if that's what love is...
then...
I love you way more!
On a scale of 1 to 10?
It's a solid 12.
Just one
tiny note?
Hard pass.
Tell me it's amazing.
Use insulated boxes, babe!
It's cold!
Here, your masterpiece.
Hey, babe.
I'm working out with Xiao Yu.
See you in a bit.
Love you.
Seriously?
You guys
are inseparable.
So, did he pop the question?
Question?
To marry him!
I'm not nagging,
but you guys
need to make it official.
I know.
We're just settling in.
One step at a time.
I get it.
But
you're
out of the woods
already.
It's all uphill from here.
From your lips to god's ears!
Let's go!
Alright.
Need a lift?
Sup, Jing.
My ride is here.
See
ya!
Later!
You're late.
No, I'm not!
I've been here
for a while.
What's for dinner?
I'm dying for hot pot!
Hot pot
it is, then.
Hey, stop piling it on!
I haven't been starved, OK?
You've had
a brutal couple of months.
Sold
your ride and
the rest of your sh*t.
We've got
extra savings
if
you're short.
Keep your damn card.
I'm good.
Go have fun
with your sweetheart.
Stop
worrying about me.
Hard to
have fun with
a permanent chaperone!
Screw you!
I didn't
ask to
cock-block you guys.
I'm here
to source inventory.
Yeah, right.
What inventory?
You haven't left my side.
It's kind of creepy.
Nah,
he's full of sh*t.
Hey,
have your fun,
boys.
But
I need a favor soon.
So... did you ask her
the "big question?"
Big question?
Is that a requirement?
School him, Rocky.
Hell if I know.
Never put a ring on anyone.
Look, man...
Some girls
dream of
a flash mob proposal.
Others are happy with
a calendar invite.
You gotta know
your target audience.
Hold on...
you
lost me.
Explain
like I'm five.
Not your business, kid.
Go find a chick first.
Then
I'll tutor you
privately.
Go to hell.
Cheers to my wedded bliss,
boys!
"DOGGED..."
What the hell
is that?
"D-O-G."
Duh.
No sh*t,
Shakespeare.
But
what's the
"G-E-D"
for?
Doesn't "-ed" mean
"turned into"
something?
So... "dog-ified?"
I actually
named it
in your honor.
Doggy style?
Dog-like?
Just... dirty dogs.
Dirty dogs?
Hey, that's an insult!
He's playing us!
Hey,
the place is
still a bit raw.
Needs some work.
Yo,
we'll handle it.
Relax.
It's in your hands.
We're on it!
Alright!
I knew
- Let's get to work!
- I could count on you.
When it's ready,
Thanks.
Jing's gonna
love this place!
Hot! Hot!
Set it here.
Here.
Like the soup?
Home, sweet home...
Hey, babe.
I'm dead.
Let me pamper my boss.
Dig your fingers in.
It's not porn!
Gotcha! Ha!
Pork chops?
New recipe?
Is this for me?
For myself.
And?
Tu Li!
Great.
I'll call Cen Ye.
Double date?
I'm still learning.
Hold me...
Can't sleep...
Rest on my arm.
Doesn't work...
You gotta work.
Want some sleeping pills?
Screw sleep.
Sun's coming up.
So calm.
No blushing anymore?
I was a clueless kid
with no taste in women.
No taste?
So who did you find later?
What?
It's just surreal.
It feels like
we won the lottery.
Like we stole this life.
And overnight,
we became adults.
Now we can stay up all night,
and no one
can stop us.
If we're not sleeping... what's the plan?
Hey,
hear me out.
I planned to
take you somewhere
beautiful
and romantic,
to make this special.
But honestly?
I came back
for you.
That's all that matters.
I just want us to be together.
Nobody else
but you.
Babe,
I love you.
And I want your love...
all of it.
Don't shut me out again.
Tell me to stay.
I don't want to be alone anymore.
I want a safe haven
with you.
Will you be my home?
Hey, you didn't answer my question.
Back in '08,
after I saw you at college,
I thought that was the end of us.
I thought my story
was over,
and that
was enough.
Then
I returned to Vineton
and just wasted away.
But three years later,
you saved me.
I am the luckiest man alive.
To survive
all that hell,
just to
have you in my arms.
Babe,
I love you!
[Wow, look at that!]
Thank you
for guiding me home.
for being my light!