♪During the dark night♪
♪A guiding light♪
♪Just like you♪
♪Makes life turn bright♪
♪Breaking free from darkness♪
♪You gave me strength♪
♪Running for truth♪
♪I find my path♪
♪Drawing on the hope♪
♪That you render me♪
♪In this long journey♪
♪I run on lightly♪
=Reborn=
(Adapted from the serialized work "Reborn"
by Qiang Yu)
I tricked you, silly.
You're so despicable.
Wait, how was I supposed
to know you'd risk your life
for that file?
Good thing I saved your life.
Let's just call it even now.
Just wait until I find the evidence.
Tsk.
Sheng.
I heard all about your heroic act
at the swimming pool.
Stop picking on Qiao Qingyu.
She has been through a lot.
Give it to me.
Are you the one who told them?
Told them what?
Are you the one who told
them about Qiao Beiyu?
=Episode 3=
(The Clues in Nanqiao Village)
(Pharmacy, Service Center)
Your test results look fine.
It's natural for girls to care
about their appearance,
but you shouldn't diet recklessly.
I'll prescribe you something
to strengthen your digestion,
but you need to exercise more too.
Honestly, you're not even fat.
Doctor, I want to ask something.
Was there a patient named Qiao Beiyu
who died from an appendectomy
at this hospital?
We can't disclose a
patient's private information.
What's your relation to her anyway?
She's my sister.
Oh.
You'll need to ask
the attending physician.
He'd know more.
But in over 20 years
of our hospital's history,
no one has ever died from appendicitis.
(Dermatology Treatment Room)
(Consultation in progress)
(Cherish life, prevent AIDS)
I'm here to...
What you're here for
has nothing to do with me.
You're here to see your dad, right?
None of your business.
You could actually get
Qiao Beiyu's medical records.
I can't.
Please.
I told you, I can't.
You could find out the truth,
but you won't tell me.
So you can keep
spreading lies, is that it?
You're overthinking it.
Medical records are private.
Besides, my dad and I don't get along.
Doctor, I'm begging you.
Please save our Qianqian.
She's only 28.
We don't want to give
up on her just like this.
Doctor, please.
Please save her.
Please calm down.
Given the patient's condition,
we have to hold a meeting
before we can give you any answers.
Please stay calm, alright?
Please save her, okay?
Please? I'll kneel and beg.
Please don't.
Please help her.
We'll hold a meeting right away.
Please wait here.
Doctor...
Doctor, please help her.
Please.
We're begging you, doctor.
Please get up first.
Please.
We will do everything in our power
if treatment is possible.
Please get up first.
Get up and talk. Come.
Don't worry.
I've transferred your
allowance to your card.
This is the subject
stream selection form.
Sign it.
(High school subject stream
selection form - Ming Sheng)
Why did you change my selection?
Science suits you better.
My career plan for you is
to follow my path,
to become a doctor.
I want to pursue arts.
You won first prize in the
National Biology Competition.
Do you know why
I entered that biology competition?
Why I fought so desperately
to win first place?
I wanted to prove to you
that I wasn't incapable.
I just hate it.
I hate studying medicine.
I hate you.
I don't want you controlling my life!
You went through all that trouble,
even at the cost of your future,
just to spite me?
Son,
that's not capability,
that's immaturity.
This form requires parental consent.
This is my decision.
Your decision means forcing your will
onto others, right?
You never consider others' feelings.
Just like when you drove my mom away,
when you pulled the plug
on grandpa's ventilator,
it was the same, wasn't it?
Just because you wear a white coat,
you think you can control
other people's lives?
You're not a doctor.
You're a murderer!
Shut up.
That girl who died last year,
Qiao Beiyu, you remember her, don't you?
Can you really say
what happened to her had
nothing to do with you?
I will never study medicine.
I refuse to become
a horrible person like you.
We'll be busy tonight.
We got an order from
the nearby construction site.
They have over 100 workers.
Don't wait for us at dinner.
Just make something simple at home,
fry some eggs.
There's milk in the fridge.
Your health comes first.
I'm going out now.
This detergent's still good.
If we dilute it,
it'll last another week.
Qingyu.
What are you doing?
By the way,
wake Jinyu up.
Hang the clothes out.
I don't care if you're a boy or girl.
When I call your name,
will you answer me?
Qiao Qingyu!
What is wrong with you?
You're no fun.
I went to People's Hospital yesterday.
Were you not feeling well?
You went to investigate Beiyu's case?
I spoke to several doctors and nurses.
They all said the hospital
had zero appendicitis deaths
in recent years.
Does that mean
Mom, Dad, and Jinrui were lying?
I don't know.
But I just
saw that the drawer in Mom
and Dad's room has a lock on it.
We've never locked any
drawers in our house before.
They racked up tens of thousands
of yuan in debt treating Qiao Beiyu.
Then we moved and added more debt.
With our financial situation,
even burglars would pity us.
A lock does seem unnecessary.
Unless there's something they're hiding.
If we could open that drawer,
we might find medical records,
hospital receipts
something that has to do
with Beiyu's condition.
I think you should drop it.
That lock isn't to keep out thieves,
it's specifically to keep us out.
And you still want to go poking around?
Aren't you afraid Mom
will skin you alive?
Besides,
even if they are hiding something,
adults must have their reasons.
What if
Qiao Beiyu really died
of that kind of illness?
Some truths
are better left unknown.
So we should
avoid truth
just because it might hurt?
Isn't that just lying to ourselves?
I can't out-debate you, honor student.
But still, I really think
we should drop it.
She's gone.
(A life lived in lies is true tragedy.)
(The most painful truth)
(is better than the sweetest lie.)
This is our last exam before
(Class 5 Year 11)
the National Day holiday break.
I expect everyone to perform
to the best of your abilities.
Double-check your answer sheets
and scratch paper.
Let me emphasize again,
never underestimate monthly exams.
Treat every practice test
as seriously as the actual
college entrance exam.
We must continuously improve ourselves,
hone our skills, understood?
Now, pass the papers back.
Stay focused and careful.
Read the questions thoroughly first,
only start answering after
you've fully understood them.
(When we were little,
everyone used to say,)
("Just grow up faster.)
(Everything will be better
when you're older".)
♪I saw hope outside♪
(Seventeen, no looking back)
(But why is it that the older we get,)
(the more confusion
and troubles we face?)
♪You spoke words I couldn't comprehend♪
(Seventeen.)
(I don't want to be seen
as just a kid anymore.)
(Even if it's heavy, even if it hurts,
I want to find my own strength.)
♪You lit a lamp♪
♪I saw the light♪
(This reckless, passionate seventeen...)
♪As you walked away♪
(I believe)
(as long as I follow
the truth in my heart)
(and stay true to myself.)
(No hardship can stop me.)
(Seventeen,)
(the path may still
be thorny and rough,)
(but I know)
(hope and light await ahead.)
Easy there, dad.
It's completely soaked.
Yes.
Let's see.
Dad, Mom.
You're back.
Dad, Mom,
we're back.
Easy there.
Say hi.
Hi, Grandpa, Grandma, Uncle.
Hi.
This year's rains have been frequent.
Yes. Good thing Jinrui reminded us.
He checks the weather forecast every day
and he warned us in advance.
He told us to move into
Haisheng's apartment building.
Who knows what state
we'd be in otherwise.
Mom, just put that down.
See.
We'll put them away later.
Just leave it.
Mom, just leave it to us.
Here.
It's okay, just leave it.
We got it.
Just take a break.
Qing...
You've gotten taller and thinner.
Other girls in your age look
bright and full of life.
Why do you look so pale?
Fanghao,
you shouldn't spend all day
obsessing over business and money.
Take better care
of your children.
Mom, she's been taking
good care of them.
Now that you're back,
I'll take Mom and Dad home.
Sure, sure.
Go home and rest, Mom and Dad.
We'll clean up the place.
Walk Grandma out.
Okay.
Bye.
Careful, it's slippery.
Okay.
Haisheng.
I bought our parents something.
Go home now.
Lusheng.
Your family will have to
make do in the old house
for these next few days.
Here, take it.
I don't think I should, Grandma.
Don't let your sister see it.
Okay.
Put it away.
Thanks, Mom.
Let me walk you out.
Okay.
Don't tell me you're going
to keep playing detective here.
We get flooded every year
during the rainy season.
This old house is deteriorating.
Look over there,
the wood's rotted.
I was thinking,
after we finish cleaning up,
maybe we should renovate this old house.
What do you think?
At least then Mom and Dad
could live more comfortably.
Sure. Renovate if you've got the money.
Well, about the money,
we young folks can
just tighten our belts a little.
Surely we can scrape together something.
Sure.
However much you can scrape,
you go right ahead.
Come on.
I'm just trying
to talk it over with you here.
I didn't say no, did I?
Didn't I already say okay?
Your family's affairs
always come first anyway.
We finally get a National Day break,
would've been nice
if the kids could rest at home,
catch up on studies,
get some proper rest.
But no, we had to come back here.
What's even the point?
Alright.
Just adding to the mess.
Okay, okay.
Let's just clean up the place.
(Dream Catcher)
Check this out!
You're disturbing me! Who is it?
Let me introduce you,
Shunyun's prettiest girl,
Qiao Beiyu.
Oh, the gorgeous girl who
passed away from illness, right?
If you hadn't told me,
I wouldn't have known that
the new transfer student in our class,
Qiao Qingyu, is her younger sister.
I just found out too.
Hey, are we still playing or not?
Yes, yes.
Just taking a little gossip break.
We can do both.
I heard
that Qiao Beiyu,
despite looking all cold
and unapproachable,
could get
really passionate
if a guy treats her nicely.
Wow, you know her that well?
Don't tell me you had a thing for her.
No, I just heard it from Hei.
You know who he is, right?
My sworn brother.
He said he used to date Qiao Beiyu.
Hei is your sworn brother?
Since when?
Is that really the point?
The point is Qiao Beiyu.
Think about it,
if Qiao Beiyu was
Shunyun's prettiest girl,
her younger sister must be the
second prettiest girl, right?
Since they both look alike,
maybe their personalities
are similar too?
Maybe Qiao Qingyu is also...
Your hoop is over there.
It slipped.
I have to go.
You guys carry on.
What has gotten over him?
(I'm not the one who told
people about your sister.)
(Want to know who told them?)
(Have you finished your homework?)
Sheng.
Why are you leaving?
Who are you texting?
None of your business.
I was just asking.
"Protecting the environment
starts with me.
Give nearby trash a proper home."
So what, want me to
find a home for you?
Hold up.
You were definitely
texting a girl just now.
Why are you always up
in everyone's business?
Mind your own business.
Come on, let's go eat.
Let's go.
Thanks, ma'am.
By the way,
don't forget to add extra
chili to my sister's portion.
Got it.
Madam Xuehua,
there's something I'd like to ask you.
Go ahead, what is it?
It's about Qiao Beiyu.
People called her a "temptress jinx",
but I always thought she
was just tragically beautiful.
She was sent off to the countryside
at such young age.
(And your parents)
(visited her only once
every few months.)
(Your grandparents,)
(well, they were old.)
(They didn't have the energy
to really take care of her.)
(She grew up in this village)
(like a wild child.)
(But you know what's strange?)
(Even though no one cared for her,)
(that girl only got more
and more beautiful.)
(She danced beautifully too.)
(She was very talented.)
(I heard that a dance academy)
(from Beining scouted her.)
(But for some reason,)
(she ended up going to
Huanzhou Art School instead.)
(I heard it's just a vocational college.
What a pity.)
Qingyu, look.
(To Qingyu)
(You hardly ever)
(came back to Nanqiao Village
when you were little.)
(But your sister
really missed you a lot.)
(Whenever she had something
nice, she always saved it for you.)
(To Qingyu)
Qingyu, Jinyu, come out.
Throw out that feather lamp,
and all that other useless junk too.
Mom, even the floor lamp?
It's still in good shape.
Just needs a new bulb.
Just throw it out.
But that was Beiyu's favorite.
I remember
that it was a gift from Jinrui.
Didn't you hear me?
It's all useless stuff.
Looks nice, but serves no purpose.
This place floods
year after year.
We should've tossed everything long ago.
This old house wasn't so bad to live in.
If I hadn't lost that job
at the power station back then,
we could've stayed here together.
Life wouldn't have been this exhausting.
Running a noodle shop
while raising kids,
and Bei wouldn't have
ended up separated from us.
I remember when we were little,
every time we came
back to Nanqiao Village,
she'd always save the best food and toys
for us.
If
Qiao Beiyu had stayed with us,
if she'd stayed in Shunyun
with Mom and Dad,
how different would her life have been?
Grandma and Grandpa always said
that Mom and Dad's two hands
couldn't support the three of us.
So
they left her behind in Nanqiao Village.
If the one left behind
had been you or me,
would Qiao Beiyu have had a better life?
(Certificate: To Qiao Beiyu
Your competition essay)
(First Prize in the 7th "Sunshine
Essay Collection" Writing Competition)
Fanghao.
Look at this.
Remember that year you promised Bei
if she won the writing competition,
we'd take her to Wumu Mountain?
Then during National Day,
we were too busy.
We couldn't go.
When I called to tell her
that we couldn't go,
she said
it was okay
because she didn't win anyway.
(Certificate: To Qiao Beiyu
Your competition essay)
(7th "Sunshine Essay Collection")
Turns out she did win.
She just never told us.
What were we thinking back then?
Why didn't we try harder?
We already had Yu at the time.
If we'd just persisted a little more,
maybe Dad would've agreed
to let Bei come home with us.
Then none of what came
after would've happened.
Somehow, without noticing,
Qiao Beiyu became
a complete and utter sinner.
Mom flies into a rage
at the mere mention of her.
Dad just shakes his head and sighs.
I hated her too.
I hated how she always stood out,
how she made me seem like the obedient,
boring one with no opinions of my own.
But it's also true
that she'd take punishments for you
and secretly save candy for me.
Alright,
enough with the emotional monologue.
The dead can't come back.
Beiyu is gone.
This chapter is closed.
Mr. Sun,
I'll submit
the subject selection form
this afternoon.
I couldn't get it sign earlier
because my dad was away
on a business trip.
Don't worry,
I'll get it to you
before your training ends.
Okay.
Let me see.
Hey, check mine out.
Why is there English on it?
Your dad's the hospital director, right?
Figured the signature
should be more fancy.
You're absurd.
Sign here.
(High school subject stream
selection form)
How's this?
Hmm.
Good?
Decent, I guess.
Way better than yours.
Just look at what you wrote.
At least this one is in Chinese.
Sun is easy to fool,
but good luck explaining this
to your dad.
No worries.
My dad doesn't care about me.
Even if he did, he couldn't control me.
Alright.
The whole class has turned theirs in,
you're the only one left.
Hand it in before break ends.
Hmm.
You went through all that trouble,
even at the cost of your future,
just to spite me?
That's not capability,
that's immaturity.
(High school subject stream
selection form)
Jiangsheng.
Lusheng.
You're home.
Fanghao.
Haisheng said you were back.
When did you arrive?
Early morning.
We took the first train here.
You're just in time.
Get ready for dinner.
One more soup coming right up.
Dinner's ready.
After such a long trip,
you shouldn't have cooked for us.
Nonsense.
Take a seat.
Sit, Wenqiu.
Uncle Jiangsheng, Aunt Wenqiu.
The soup's ready.
Bei?
Bei!
No, she's not Bei.
Wenqiu.
Aunt Wenqiu.
Wenqiu,
let go of her.
This is Qingyu, not Beiyu.
You're back.
Wenqiu, let her go.
I've missed you so much, Bei.
Let go.
Bei...
Aunt Wenqiu.
Look at the flowers.
Let go first.
Aunt Wenqiu.
You're crushing them.
The flowers...
Bei.
Let's eat first.
Come on.
You guys eat without us.
We'll just eat in our room.
Come on, let's have dinner.
Let's go.
Are you okay?
Come.
Bei...
You can pick some
more flowers for her later.
So,
Fanghao, Lusheng,
Wenqiu has episodes sometimes.
I hope she didn't scare Qingyu.
No, she's fine.
Keep drinking.
Qin still seems
a little...
Ever since we lost our child,
she hasn't been the same.
She suffered a mental breakdown.
We've seen a lot of doctors,
they all say it's psychological.
There's no real cure.
You've really had a tough time.
Slow down now.
I'm glad you're back.
We used to dream of a simple life,
getting married, having a kid,
and living peacefully.
Wenqiu always loved children.
But now, in her condition,
she can't have any.
She can't be without me.
I've accepted that.
I can't be without her either.
Jiangsheng,
every family has its struggles.
Life goes on,
it gets better with time.
You're lucky.
You have Qing and Yu,
they'll grow up soon.
But speaking of which,
Qing's grown so fast.
When she walked in,
I didn't recognize her.
I thought she was her sister.
Don't be ridiculous.
Enjoy your drinking.
Lusheng,
I didn't mean it like that.
But girls harder to manage when older.
You'd better keep close watch.
Jiangsheng...
Let's drink.
I...
Drink.
Before Beiyu left
for Huanzhou Art School,
she'd been living here at the old house.
She was really close with Aunt Qin.
After living together all those years,
they must've bonded deeply.
No wonder she mistook you for Beiyu.
When Aunt Qin hugged me earlier,
she held me so tightly.
She couldn't even
say a word for a while.
She's not mentally well.
Don't take it seriously.
But she was genuine.
I think she really cared about Beiyu.
It's a shame that Beiyu...
A shame, but not surprising.
Everyone else speaks ill
of Qiao Beiyu,
turns out Aunt Qin was
the only one who stuck by her.
What do you think
really happened to Qiao Beiyu
that made Aunt Qin
care for her so desperately?
Sheng.
Sheng!
I live at the head of the Yangtze River,
you live at its tail.
I'm in the science track,
you're in the arts.
We're like two parallel lines,
never to cross paths again.
Just thinking about it
fills me with unbearable sorrow.
I can't pull myself out of it.
Drama queen.
Sheng,
even though you've chosen arts,
we're still friends.
Let's grab dinner tonight,
consider it a farewell feast.
I've thought it over.
I'll take science after all.
What?
You changed your mind?
Judging by your reactions,
you don't seem too thrilled.
Worried I'll steal your spotlight?
No,
we're just confused.
Weren't you rebelling against your dad?
Why the sudden change of heart?
This is my decision.
It has nothing to do with him.
Warm up first, man!
(Literature)
(Qiao Beiyu)
(Love is the most radiant element here,
yet also the fuse of catastrophe.)
Qingyu?
Ma Mingkai.
I'm back
to visit my grandparents.
It's been
a long time since
we last saw each other, huh?
By the way,
I wrote you a letter a while back.
Why didn't you ever write me back?
I never received any letters.
Must've gone to the wrong address.
People don't really
write letters these days.
Good thing
you weren't ignoring me
on purpose.
So what did you write?
Nothing special really.
Qingyu,
how about we go study
in the library together
tomorrow morning?
You're good at your studies.
There are a few questions
I could use your help with.
Ma Mingkai,
thank you.
For what?
Thank you for still being
willing to hang out with me.
Actually,
I've heard the rumors.
But Beiyu is Beiyu, and you're you.
You shouldn't be held accountable
for her actions.
Besides,
the Qingyu I know
is an exemplary student,
never steps out of line.
Obedient and proper.
"Obedient and proper"?
I just mean
you're not the same as your sister.
I have something to do today.
I have to go.
See you tomorrow then.
(Medical Records Release
Authorization Form)
(What if)
(Qiao Beiyu really died
of that kind of illness?)
(Such truth is better left unknown.)
Nice shot!
I give up.
I can't beat you.
I'm done. Let's go.
Come on, let's go home.
We'll play again next time. Bye.
Next time then.
Washboard.
(Qiao Qingyu:
You stole the letters Ma Mingkai sent me.)
(I asked the class monitor.)
(You were the one in
charge of picking up)
(everyone's mail from
the mailroom last month.)
(Ming Sheng:
Wasn't me. Don't accuse the wrong person.)
(Medical Records
Release Authorization Form)
(Qiao Qingyu: Then do me a favor.)
(I want my sister's medical records.)
(I've filled out the release form.)
(Ming Sheng:
Best I can do is get you copies.)
(If I manage to get it,
how are you going to thank me?)
(Qiao Qingyu:
What do you want?)
Sheng.
Those arched eyebrows,
those smiling lips,
they're sending a very clear signal.
He's possessed.
(I, Qiao Qingyu, as a family
member of Qiao Beiyu,)
(request Huanzhou People's Hospital
to provide complete medical records)
(including all emergency
visits and inpatient admissions.)
Madam Xiuzhen?
Hi, Qing. You've grown tall.
My uncle
and my parents went out.
They're not back yet.
It's fine.
Your uncle asked me to check on Qin.
How is she?
She looks alright for now.
But I'm just a clinic health
worker at the village infirmary.
I'm not qualified to diagnose this.
Your uncle asked me to come by
just for peace of mind.
Make sure she doesn't have
another episode and wander off.
Remind your uncle that
he needs to keep a close eye on her.
She can't take another shock.
Madam Xiuzhen,
you're a health worker
at the village clinic?
That's right.
Over 20 years now.
Every illness in this village,
I usually know about it.
Then do you know about Qiao Beiyu?
Beiyu, huh...
Of course I heard the rumors.
Everyone was talking.
But whether she really
had that kind of illness,
I don't know.
One thing though,
I remember very clearly.
♪Maybe♪
♪The more I care,
the more I tread carefully♪
♪Counting the distance between us♪
♪Just one step away from reaching♪
♪The future♪
♪Time will unveil this mystery♪
♪Waiting is a silent promise♪
♪But one that never expires♪
♪Turns out, all my thoughts♪
♪Spell your name♪
♪The one and only stubbornness
in my heart♪
♪From the very first glance♪
♪I started painting
what our future would look like♪
♪That's when the dream began
to feel real♪
♪Turns out♪
♪Your heart had a place for me too♪
♪Cradling the same story we both knew♪
♪Thankfully, we were naïve enough♪
♪And brave just in time♪
♪To make sure our moments
weren't lost to time♪