♪During the dark night♪
♪A guiding light♪
♪Just like you♪
♪Makes life turn bright♪
♪Breaking free from darkness♪
♪You gave me strength♪
♪Running for truth♪
♪I find my path♪
♪Drawing on the hope♪
♪That you render me♪
♪In this long journey♪
♪I run on lightly♪
=Reborn=
(Adapted from the serialized work "Reborn"
by Qiang Yu)
(2007, Shunyun County, Nanqiao Village)
(Shunyun to Huanzhou)
♪That village in the back of beyond♪
♪That little village♪
(Shunyun to Huanzhou)
♪My dearest mother's hair
has turned white♪
♪Those unforgettable days of old♪
Do you want some?
♪I can't forget♪
♪How many kisses Mother has given me♪
♪How many were there?♪
♪She kisses away my tears♪
♪And warms my little heart♪
Hello?
Hello, I'm the landlady.
Hello, ma'am.
Yes.
Well, the property management fee...
Wait.
Didn't we already pay 80,000
for the transfer fee in full?
Why is there a property fee now?
Ma'am,
we're just running a small business.
I'm so sorry, mister. Sorry.
Please cut us some slack.
We clean the place ourselves every day.
We don't need management service.
Don't read on the bus.
Yes, I want!
I'll pay! I'll pay!
Good. When?
By the end of the year. Is that okay?
Hello?
I'll pay!
Sir, drive carefully.
I spilled my water.
(When we were little, everyone said,)
("Hurry up and grow up.)
(Things get better when you're older.")
(But why,)
(the older I get,)
(Huanzhou)
(the more confused I've become?)
=Episode 1=
(Beiyu's Younger Sister)
(Qiao's Handmade Noodle House)
Grand opening!
(Tripe 4 yuan)
(Oyster 5 yuan)
(Intestines 5 yuan)
(Beef Noodles)
Hello, feel free to try
Qiao's Handmade Noodle House.
(Blessing)
Hello, we're Qiao's
Handmade Noodle House.
Come try Qiao's Handmade Noodle House.
Fair price and generous portions.
Exactly.
Hello, come try
Qiao's Handmade Noodle House.
We just opened. Welcome.
Fair price and generous portions.
You...
No.
Hello, feel free to try
Qiao's Handmade Noodle House.
It doesn't look like a proper opening.
There are only two firecrackers.
Do people even know what we're doing?
When we opened in our hometown,
you at least prepared flower baskets.
Now, you didn't prepare anything.
And everything's in a mess.
I don't get it.
Why do you have to choose today?
Didn't I explain to you?
We picked this date.
Today is a good day
to start the business.
Fine, I guess so.
This tiny little shop
actually costs 80,000
for the transfer fee.
Aside from that,
there's also a property management fee.
I've never heard of it.
You know what?
I bought green veggies this morning.
It costs 0.4 yuan more per jin.
I bought it in our hometown
for less than 0.4 yuan per jin.
Why didn't you mention
we could sell a few more yuan
for each bowl of noodles?
Who do we sell the noodles to?
There's no one around.
What happened?
Mom.
Did you get hurt?
Don't move.
Pieces for peace. Everything goes well.
Well.
You two go hand out flyers.
I'll clean up here.
All right. Go on.
Be careful.
I'll do it. Give it to me.
Where's Jinyu?
Outside.
Nice shot! Yes!
This boy.
You just run off
without telling anymore.
Can't you be more like your sister
and help out?
We've got so much to deal with
at the shop.
I haven't paid the money yet.
Ma'am,
today's the first day
of our noodle house.
We haven't made any profits yet.
How about this?
I'll bring you a bowl of noodles.
Is that your shop?
Yes.
No worries.
We're neighbors.
We'll pay you back tomorrow.
It's all right.
Flyers.
Ah, yes. Flyers.
He's naughty.
How many children do you have?
Two.
She's the eldest one, right?
One boy, one girl. That's good.
You'll have a comfortable life
in the future.
I'm blessed.
All the best for your new business.
Thank you.
Thank you, ma'am.
Please come by often.
Sure.
We will.
Go in.
How blessed.
You splashed dirty water into my bowl.
I didn't.
The cloth is dry.
I saw you splash it.
Which eye saw that?
What did you just say?
Do you have no manners?
Fanghao.
I'll teach you some manners.
Say that again.
What has happened?
Let me see.
Don't go.
You're a service person.
What's with your attitude?
He said I'm blind.
Sorry.
What's wrong with this brat?
Please calm down.
You're his mom?
He said I'm blind.
Please sit down. Calm down.
Well.
Put that down.
Why are you so careless?
He was using a cloth
and splashed dirty water
into my noodles.
Please sit down. Calm down.
I'll prepare a new bowl of noodles
right away.
Such a big temper.
Here's a new bowl of noodles for you.
I'm too pissed to eat anything else.
(Qiao's Handmade Noodle House)
Why is the tire flat?
Bummer.
I didn't even touch her.
That's enough.
We're new in town
and don't know anyone here.
We'll always end up on the downside.
Are you okay?
Well, I'll give you a day off.
Go and rest.
Go.
I thought it'd be a good start
if we were nice.
She has a bad temper.
Had you stepped out earlier,
his hand wouldn't have been burned.
There's no one I can rely on
in this family.
Order, please.
Coming.
Isn't it inappropriate
for a man
to meddle in a catfight?
Let me.
Qingyu, you're always the sweetheart.
The most sensible child.
Sir, an extra egg, please.
Coming.
I'll do it.
Hey, don't.
Be careful.
Look at this.
I bought it at the morning market.
"May everything go well."
Not bad, right?
That's a good blessing.
But
you've brought
too many useless things here.
Look at these.
Everything I brought here is useful.
They are worth a million, you know?
We have to be careful with our spending.
There'll be plenty to spend on later.
Mom,
I don't want to share a room
with Qingyu.
Sleep on the streets, then.
Exactly.
Mom, where's my gaming console?
All you do is play.
I don't like this place.
Why did we have to move here?
Why do you think?
It's all because of you two.
This place has
a better learning environment.
(Classmate Record,
Shunyun No. 1 High School, Qiao Qingyu)
Have you straightened everything up?
Mom.
How do you fold this blanket?
What are you even capable of?
Let me see.
Find the corner.
Look at your sister.
She's sensible and good at studies.
Huanzhou High School accepted her
right after they saw
her academic transcript.
And look at you.
It's so hard for you
to get admitted to a sports school.
Yes, right.
Qingyu excels in everything.
Then why did you give birth to me?
That was a mistake?
How could you say that?
Mom,
hurry and rest up.
We'll take care of this ourselves.
Did you hear that?
Do it yourself.
You're sensible and intelligent,
but so what?
Look at me. I'm free and easy.
Qingyu, I did you a favor just now.
You should treat me to a good meal.
In your dreams.
Is this how you repay your life savior?
Dad and Mom are already stressed enough.
You want me to be like you
and irritate them again?
Yes, you're sensible,
but they've never given you any rewards.
On the contrary,
I've been slouching every day.
They care more about me.
Dad and Mom pay
the least attention to you.
To be frank,
you're kind of invisible.
Back in Shunyun,
many people thought
I only had one sister,
and it wasn't you.
You're asking for another beating?
I'm telling the truth.
All right, all right.
You're my only sister.
You're my sister forever.
Is that okay?
Talk to the hand.
(Classmate Record,
Shunyun No. 1 High School, Qiao Qingyu)
(Ma Mingkai: Qiao Qingyu, it's a regret
I didn't get to say goodbye.)
(May you always carry a smile,
hope, and love with you.)
Qingyu,
it's only the first day of the business,
and my hand almost got burned off.
Is Huanzhou really as great as Mom says?
Qingyu.
What?
It's not easy to run a business
in a big city.
Mom said this.
Why do you always believe
whatever she says?
I know
you don't want to come to Huanzhou.
You were doing so well
in your old school
and might've been recommended
for university admission.
Now that you've come to Huanzhou,
your situation has been overturned.
I doubt you're fine with that.
There are more opportunities
in Huanzhou High School.
Perhaps I might
get into a better university
in the future.
Besides, since we've come
to a new place,
a new environment,
things will happen for us.
The nerve of you!
Stand still. Don't run!
Get out of my way.
You're not getting away.
What are you doing?
Run as you want.
Keep running.
Don't move.
Take out your wallet.
I don't have it with me.
Where's your money?
Money.
(Ma Mingkai, I hope
this letter finds you well.)
(Everything's fine here in Huanzhou.)
(Right now, I'm writing this)
(under a banyan tree by the river.)
(Shunyun and Huanzhou are
only a hundred miles apart)
(but they're so much different.)
(You wrote in the classmate record)
(that you regretted
not saying a proper goodbye to me.)
(Perhaps separation is part of life.)
(But as written in novels,)
("No matter how far we are apart,)
(we're still under the same sky.)
(No matter where we are,)
(we don't feel lonely.")
(I hope you study hard)
(and pass NCEE with flying colors.)
[*National College Entrance Examination]
(Hopefully, we get into
the same university.)
(To Ma Mingkai, From Qiao Qingyu)
Eh?
You took my leave.
Get out of my way.
This isn't yours.
This tree is mine.
Bayan tree
(Ficus altissima Blume)
belongs to
Huanzhou Municipal Forest and Parks Bureau.
When I say it's mine, it's mine.
On your letter here,
It writes Qiao Qingyu.
This name sounds familiar.
If you like it, you can have it.
I can always write another.
You've got guts.
Do you know who I am?
You don't know me, anyway.
I know you.
Beiyu's
younger sister.
Are you?
Two, two, three, four,
five, six, seven.
Qiao Qingyu, let's go.
(Ms. Ma's General Store)
Wang rented out his rooftop unit.
He got it rented?
Then how come ours hasn't?
You're not putting in any effort.
Tell me about it.
Hands off. Mom hasn't had her meat yet.
I'm not eating.
I eat it every day in the shop.
One of you is always bouncing around,
and the other one's worn out studying.
Qingyu,
study harder.
This isn't like Shunyun.
You used to be in the top ten there,
but you're only
slightly above average here,
right?
You might not stand out.
People say students at your new school
are ace students.
They all strive hard to study.
I've given up on him.
He's never the study type.
If you can get a diploma certificate,
that's the best I could ask for.
So I'm counting on you
to make our family proud, right?
You're home.
Yeah.
Have you eaten?
I have.
There weren't any customers
before eight.
I was waiting, but no one came.
So I had dinner there.
Don't be impatient.
We take time to build our business.
We just opened, after all.
I brought your meds.
Take them on time.
All right.
Don't let your injuries act up again.
I know.
(Painkillers)
(Adolescent Sexual Health
Education Textbook)
Qingyu,
you're a grown-up girl.
As a girl at school,
you need to be careful
with what you do and say.
Stay away from
those who don't study well
or troublemakers.
Your safety comes first.
If it were just your dad and me,
we could live anywhere.
We went through all the hassle
just for the sake of you two.
We want to give you a better environment
in which you can focus on your studies.
What's wrong with you?
You can't even handle
such a simple thing.
Let me see.
Is it deep?
Why keep them?
Those were her last pair of shoes.
The last keepsake from her.
She looked so beautiful dancing on stage
in those shoes.
Everyone in Shunyun
knows Qiao Beiyu.
Mom said
once we moved to Huanzhou,
there was no such person
in the family anymore.
There you go again, "Mom said".
I just thought
she was our sister.
She is not.
Tch.
What's with that scoff?
Whatever you truly think,
you only repeat everything Mom says.
Qiao Jinyu!
Well,
I mean,
you're the first child,
and I'm the second child.
Anyway, not many people here know us.
You don't know me, anyway.
I know you.
Beiyu's
younger sister.
(Isn't this Beiyu's younger sister?)
(Stay, sister.)
(Oh, nice.)
(- You're pretty.
- I don't know you.)
(But we know you.)
Where are you going, sister?
Hey, don't go.
Go away.
(Huanzhou High School)
(School Compound Floor Map)
Meixi, wait for me.
Where did you go for the holidays?
My dad took me to Hong Kong, China,
for a concert.
Lucky you.
I wish I could go to a concert too.
A demerit point isn't that bad.
Once or twice is fine.
The real issue is his dad.
His dad's such a pain.
(Commendation Notice)
Why do you think
Sun picked us two
to post Sheng's demerit notice?
(Demerit Notice for Ming Sheng)
He knows we're tight.
This is a warning for us.
Ming Sheng?
Why aren't you in your uniform?
Newcomer?
Sun mentioned
we're getting a transfer student today.
That's not you, is it?
I'm Qiao Qingyu. Just transferred
into Class 5, Year 11.
So it is you.
What a fate.
Let me introduce myself. I'm Ye Zilin.
Chen Hao.
Nice to meet you.
Our class is cleaning the natatorium
this morning.
How about this?
We'll take you there now.
You don't have to go to the classroom.
Yeah. No one's in the classroom now.
The natatorium is over there.
Let's go.
Come.
Come. Let's go.
This way.
Over here.
Who arranged for our class
to clean the natatorium this early?
Stop complaining.
Consider it as an exercise.
Qingyu,
see those coiled lane lines?
Go and fix them.
Isn't that your job?
Let the newcomer have a chance.
Here. Take this.
It's almost time for study hall.
Why hasn't anyone shown up yet?
Don't tell me we're cleaning
this whole place by ourselves.
Tell me about it.
This bunch doesn't contribute
to the class at all.
Hey.
Why did she fall into the pool?
Help her!
Who's that in the pool?
Save her!
Grab this.
Was it you, Ye Zilin?
Not me.
I didn't know how she fell in.
Was it you?
I didn't see anything.
Who's that?
(Class 5 Grade 2, Senior High)
Enough. Quiet.
Let me see who's eager to speak up.
Qiao Qingyu just transferred here
from Shunyun No. 1 High School.
Although there was
an accident at the start,
I believe in the days to come,
Qingyu will definitely feel
the fiery passion
of our class.
What's wrong with you guys?
Do you want to take home
a few more papers
to fuel your passion?
All right.
Qiao Qingyu,
you'll sit next to Jiang Nian.
If you have any questions, ask Liu Jia.
She's the class monitor.
All right. Turn to
the third section of the second chapter.
Thank you for lending me your uniform.
You're welcome.
My mom's also from Shunyun.
So we're kind of from the same hometown.
How come she fell into the pool?
Who's in the water?
What are you standing here for?
Save her!
Grab this.
Who's that?
Hurry up.
Here are some tips for you.
Keep your distance from them.
The two of them
are infamous slackers in our year.
Ye Zilin, a transient student.
No matter how poorly he scores on NCEE,
he'll inherit his family's shoe factory.
Chen Hao is a sports student.
A long jumper.
He's already pre-admitted to
Huanzhou Sport University.
They may be terrible in their studies,
but they're best
when it comes to pranks.
As for Ming Sheng...
Beiyu's younger sister.
You've got the wrong person.
(Proper ways to protect yourself
from harassment)
When sexual harassment or assaults
happen,
dealing with it wisely and bravely
can help stop it.
Never be weak or helpless.
For example, shout for help,
distract the perpetrator,
or signal those nearby.
These are the correct ways
to deal with the situation.
As for high schoolers like you,
especially girls,
where does harassment
most commonly happen?
The new student,
please stand up and answer.
Page 43, third section.
(Adolescent Sexual Health
Education Textbook)
(Biology, Qiao Qingyu)
Qiao Qingyu,
where does harassment commonly happen?
Ma'am, I know why
she can't answer your question.
Qiao Qingyu,
why is it all blacked out?
Were you highlighting the main points?
I can't read them.
Ye, what's wrong with you?
You shouldn't touch girls' things
without asking.
You're disrespecting her.
Ma'am.
I'm so sorry.
That being said, Qiao Qingyu,
you're too upright.
Are you from ancient times?
Please behave.
For a long time,
a lack of knowledge
about reproductive health
has made it a sensitive topic
in society.
I hope that through this class,
reproductive health
can become as common a topic
as eating or sleeping.
Why are you still up?
My slippers.
Are you not feeling well?
Hurry and go to sleep.
You have to go to school early tomorrow.
Did you do something to my textbook?
Hmm.
What's wrong?
Did you argue with someone at school?
Was the food at the canteen terrible?
You can cancel the school meal tomorrow.
Your dad and I will prepare it for you.
Take it with you to school.
It's not about food.
Having trouble adjusting to
the new school?
Don't worry.
Try to make some new friends.
Right?
You'll get used to it over time.
What's this?
These are useless stuff.
It's not tested in NCEE.
You're not reading this nonsense.
This is a school textbook.
I don't care about others,
but you're not reading
this nonsense.
It's part of the curriculum.
Qiao Qingyu, how old are you?
You're 17.
Why does a 17-year-old girl
need to read such nonsense?
You didn't teach Qiao Beiyu back then,
that's why she ended up like that.
She ended up that way
because she read nonsense
like this.
Talk nicely.
You...
Didn't we agree
not to bring this up again
after moving to Huanzhou?
It's late now.
You're disturbing my sleep.
Right. They have to go
to school tomorrow.
Go to sleep.
You have to go to school tomorrow.
Get rest early.
All right. Back to bed.
Don't be mad. She didn't mean it.
I did.
Qiao Qingyu.
Qiao Qingyu!
Why are you walking so fast?
We're classmates.
We'll be seeing a lot of each other.
What exactly do you want?
How are you going to compensate me?
Bite me back,
and then we're even.
If it were someone else,
the consequence would be different.
If it weren't for your decent grades,
I wouldn't even bother talking to you.
My hand hurts. I can't do my homework.
You do it for me.
I just transferred here
and have a lot to catch up on.
I don't have time to do your homework.
You don't have time?
Don't you want to know
how your sister died?
Go!
(Physics, Ming Sheng)
(If you can't finish this week's
homework, don't come to class.)
(You don't have time?)
(Don't you want to know)
(how your sister died?)
(Liao Xiuzhen, Fifth-Generation Madam
of the Chen Family in Jingchuan)
(Funeral)
(Shunyun)
Isn't that Qiao?
Heard she died of AIDS.
AIDS?
Yeah.
She died at a very young age.
What a pity.
Let's eat here.
(Qiao's Handmade Noodle House)
Be careful.
(To let)
Higher.
Once we leave here,
we can say goodbye to the past
and start over.
(Qiao's Handmade Noodle House
To let)
Have you done your homework?
Hmm.
Are you adjusting well to school?
Quite well.
Are you keeping up with the syllabus?
Hmm.
People say
kids at your school
aren't just doing
what's in the textbook.
They're also doing extra
or even more advanced questions.
You need to push yourself hard.
If not, the gap between you and them
will grow bigger,
and you won't be able to
catch up with them.
By the way,
Aunt Qin is sick again.
Go to the bank this Sunday
to send 500 yuan
to Uncle Jiangsheng.
What's Aunt Qin sick with?
They say she has a mental problem.
Her condition has been unstable
over these years.
Uncle Jiangshen
has been taking her for treatments,
but there's no improvement.
What's wrong with me?
I keep calling her Aunt Qin like you.
I can't change it.
What about Qiao Beiyu then?
Dad and you never talked about it.
What?
It was appendicitis.
I told you before.
She had complications after surgery.
But everyone says she had AIDS.
What... What AIDS?
Who told you that?
Nonsense! These are simply rumors!
If it's nonsense,
why didn't you argue with them?
How?
How am I supposed to talk back
to that many people?
You kid is so ignorant.
Words can kill, you know?
But if we don't make it clear,
we keep getting bullied
and get dragged down by it
no matter where we go.
Who bullied you?
We've already moved to a new place.
She's gone.
Everything's over.
No, it's not over.
What do you want, then?
♪Maybe♪
♪The more I care,
the more I tread carefully♪
♪Counting the distance between us♪
♪Just one step away from reaching♪
♪The future♪
♪Time will unveil this mystery♪
♪Waiting is a silent promise♪
♪But one that never expires♪
♪Turns out, all my thoughts♪
♪Spell your name♪
♪The one and only stubbornness
in my heart♪
♪From the very first glance♪
♪I started painting
what our future would look like♪
♪That's when the dream began
to feel real♪
♪Turns out♪
♪Your heart had a place for me too♪
♪Cradling the same story we both knew♪
♪Thankfully, we were naïve enough♪
♪And brave just in time♪
♪To make sure our moments
weren't lost to time♪