♪If you can see me♪
♪Holding myself back for you♪
♪The past rides the wind into the horizon♪
♪Taking our beginning into oblivion♪
♪In the dim light♪
♪You and I stare at each other♪
♪Our fate turns into an illusion♪
♪Who feels more hopeless now?♪
♪So, I will just sit by your side♪
=Passionate Love=
=Episode 18=
(I Don't Want Anything To Happen To You)
Please enjoy the meal, everyone.
These are Songhe Restaurant's
signature dishes.
- Enjoy, enjoy.
- Come, enjoy this.
This way.
Xunchu,
why are you here?
Xunchu.
Major General Duan, you're here.
I heard Mr. Chu is hosting Mr. Song
here today.
As it happens, I got my hands
on a bottle of excellent red wine today.
So, I brought this here
for everyone to try.
Xunchu,
you are too considerate.
Come.
Mr. Song, Mr. Chu, everyone,
this toast is for you.
Good, good.
- Cheers, Major General.
- Cheers.
This is good wine.
(Songhe Restaurant)
Thank you for the dinner, Mr. Chu.
And also for your wine, Xunchu.
Thanks to your protection over the years,
the chamber of commerce's new business
will depend on you.
Oh, yes.
This is a gift
from me for Miss Song.
It's a necklace of the latest design.
I hope Miss Song will like it.
Good, good.
Mr. Chu, you're too kind.
Xunchu,
shall we go for an outing tomorrow?
We can invite Song...
No, I meant Xunrui.
Wanzhen.
This child is a handful.
Chu,
since you follow me,
that means you're under me now.
Don't disappoint me.
Of course.
Uncle Song, it's getting late.
Wanzhen, you should go home
with Uncle Song.
Wanzhen, be good.
Come home with me.
Fine.
Mr. Chu,
I shall treat you next time.
Sure.
- Goodbye.
- See you.
Watch your step.
What's going on?
Sir, the road is closed for repairs.
Please take another route.
Get down.
Lin Wenyu,
are you trying to get yourself killed?
Why are you here?
Should I sit by
while you bring me trouble?
Come out.
- I found...
- Useless fools.
Daddy.
Investigate this now.
Yes, Master.
What do we do?
Weren't you quite gutsy just now?
Why are you afraid now?
This is too high.
Stop talking.
Jump down, I'll catch you.
What's wrong, Xunchu?
Had enough?
I'll deal with you when we get back.
- Do you know how dangerous that was?
- Just take a look at these.
Song Zhenyuan had the police
watched you all these years.
Ten years ago,
they closed the case
by saying my father killed the Commander.
Looks like they've been
colluding all along.
I don't want anything to happen to you.
If they had found you tonight,
you wouldn't make it back alive.
I'm sorry
for acting on my own without telling you.
Song Zhenyuan must have
kept me alive all these years
to get hold of the Duan family vault's
location from me.
Song Huaining
must also be a spy he planted by my side.
Oh, look.
What are you doing?
You'll pay for this.
Let me go. Let me go.
Director Wang.
How does it feel
to be the chief of police
all these years?
Duan Xunchu,
how dare you kidnap me?
Let me go.
Let me go right now.
Ten years ago, you were in charge of
investigating the Duan family's murder.
Tell me.
Was it really Su Mu
who leaked my father's whereabouts?
Director Wang,
I heard your son just came of age.
I'll tell you everything.
Please don't hurt my family.
Su Mu didn't leak
Commander Duan's whereabouts.
It was Song Zhenyuan.
Song Zhenyuan?
Song Zhenyuan wanted to get
the Duan family's wealth and power.
When Commander Duan was in the army,
he had many guards to protect him.
Song Zhenyuan never
had a chance to kill him.
So he had been spying on Commander Duan.
On New Year's Eve,
Commander Duan came home
with just a few guards.
When Song Zhenyuan got the tip-off,
he immediately led his men
to murder the Duan family.
- He didn't think you would escape.
- Keep going.
When Song Zhenyuan knew you escaped,
he searched for you.
He wanted to know the location
of the Duan family vault from you.
Later, he found out
you joined the military academy,
so he sent his adopted son
to your side.
He never expected to fail
to locate the vault after so many years.
Su Mu found out
that Song Zhenyuan wanted
to kill Commander Duan.
He died protecting Commander Duan.
After the murder,
Song Zhenyuan wanted
to take over the Duan family's army,
so he bribed the police department
to close the case
and pin it all on Su Mu.
Duan Xunchu.
Major General Duan.
I told you everything.
Please spare me.
Spare me.
Keep interrogating.
Make him spill every single detail.
Major General Duan.
Spare my son.
- Major General.
- Adjutant Sun.
What is the recent status
of Song Zhenyuan's military strength?
He has been guarding Feng City
with his troops for years.
He is famous.
Moreover, the troops under Commander Duan
are now mostly under his command.
Major General,
I'm afraid it is difficult
to gain their trust if you step up now.
And...
And, what?
And he has been colluding with the police.
We cannot act without proper planning.
- What is the progress with Wang?
- We're still interrogating him.
Keep torturing him
until he tells everything
about his collusion with Song Zhenyuan.
Yes, Major General.
I have something to tell you.
Huaining seems suspicious.
What did you find?
A few days ago,
he asked me about Adjutant Sun.
I believe he is still
under Song Zhenyuan's influence.
That's the reason I found an excuse
to go to the Song mansion with him.
Young Master,
we tracked the Major General's men
to an abandoned temple.
They seem to be digging for something.
Come, let's go take a look.
Yes.
♪Looking deep into her heart♪
♪Looking at each other
under the moonlight in secret♪
♪This reunion came unexpectedly♪
♪Your face is unforgettable♪
♪In the time that passed us by♪
♪My love turned into a lie♪
♪I bury thousands of words
behind an icy facade♪
♪Our shadows locked in an embrace♪
♪Finally find a home♪
♪Never fear the eternity♪