♪If you can see me♪
♪Holding myself back for you♪
♪The past rides the wind into the horizon♪
♪Taking our beginning into oblivion♪
♪In the dim light♪
♪You and I stare at each other♪
♪Our fate turns into an illusion♪
♪Who feels more hopeless now?♪
♪So, I will just sit by your side♪
=Passionate Love=
=Episode 3=
(Isn't Everything Thanks To You?)
You told Adjutant Su
about the Commander's return on the phone.
The Duan family got massacred
on the same night.
And I saw you
opened the door to the enemies.
Hello.
Father.
Today is the New Year's Eve.
When are you coming home?
Even Commander Duan has come home.
Xunchu,
I did open the door
but I didn't know who it was.
I only heard footsteps
and then I got knocked unconscious.
I really didn't know anything.
Xunchu,
you must believe me.
Xunchu.
Throw her out.
Miss,
you're back.
what's wrong?
Did Duan Xunchu bully you?
I'm fine.
Miss,
I had a hard time
searching for you years ago.
We hid our identities and came back
to Feng City and find the truth
to prove Master's innocence.
Duan Xunchu gives you trouble
as soon as he came back.
No.
I will go and explain it to him.
He hates me deeply now.
He won't believe me.
It's only after I've found the evidence
and know the truth,
can I clear my father's name.
(Yaren Medical Hall)
By the order of the Major General,
Yaren Medical Hall is to be sealed.
Everyone, get out.
Get out, get out.
Wait.
Why?
It's the Major General's order.
- Move out of the way.
- You cannot do this.
- Miss.
- What are you doing?
(Feng City Military Office Sealed)
Without the Major General's permission,
Yaren Medical Hall is not allowed
to open for business.
Make anymore trouble
and you'll all be arrested.
You...
Miss,
this is too much.
I don't know either.
I'm still waiting for my salary.
Yes.
Stop the car.
Why did we stop?
Xunchu,
didn't you promise
to stroll around with me?
If I kneel and beg for forgiveness
from the Duan family,
will you spare Yaren Medical Hall
and my employees?
Xunchu,
who is she? What a downer.
Just a schemer.
Take a look in a mirror, will you?
The Major General has just returned
and you want to flirt with him?
In that case,
I will play a game with you.
If you made me happy,
I'll put in a good word for you.
Xunchu,
we haven't seen each other for years.
You promised to stroll around
with me today.
You won't go back on your words, right?
Adjutant Sun,
find me a rope.
I want to test this lady's legs.
Tie her to the back.
Since you foolishly
ruined my plan,
I'll have you taste the consequences.
Are you sure?
As long as
you'll spare Yaren Medical Hall.
Start driving.
Major General?
If you don't get out now,
you'll die.
Do you understand?
What do you mean?
I leaked the Commander's whereabouts.
Su Wenyue,
do you know what you're saying?
I never suspected you.
Did you know
that my entire family is dead
because their whereabouts were leaked?
♪Every time the waves rolled in♪
♪You stared endlessly at them♪
♪I missed the time
when the sun reflected the past♪
♪What is left to love?♪
♪I thought you were an angel♪
♪My guardian angel♪
♪You have seen all of me♪
What's wrong, Adjustant Sun?
A person can walk faster than the car.
Go faster.
♪You finally escaped reality♪
♪I could hear all the people♪
♪Cheered for you♪
♪I hid in the cape after the rain♪
♪So I couldn't hear your turmoil♪
♪I spread my arms for one last embrace♪
♪But you escaped between the gaps♪
♪I watched the seasons change♪
♪I thought we will have time♪
♪But I couldn't endure the storms♪
♪You made my heart panic♪
♪No matter how absurd,
I learned to value♪
♪My own worth♪
♪I could hear all the people♪
♪Cheered for you♪
♪I hid in the cape after the rain♪
♪So I couldn't hear your turmoil♪
♪I spread my arms for one last embrace♪
♪But you escaped between the gaps♪
♪I watched the seasons change♪
♪I thought we will have time♪
♪But I couldn't endure the storms♪
♪You made my heart panic♪
Go faster.
♪My own worth♪
Stop the car.
Wanzhen, go home.
Su Wenyue,
admit it.
Tell me
and I'll let you go.
Su Wenyue.
What's wrong?
Don't touch me.
I won't believe in your fake acts again.
I wasn't as dumb as I used to be.
Major General,
what's wrong?
Let me check on him.
Don't touch him.
Stay away from him.
He looks terrible.
Let me check on him.
You won't move?
Do you want him to die?
♪Looking deep into her heart♪
♪Looking at each other
under the moonlight in secret♪
♪This reunion came unexpectedly♪
♪Your face is unforgettable♪
♪In the time that passed us by♪
♪My love turned into a lie♪
♪I bury thousands of words
behind an icy facade♪
♪Our shadows locked in an embrace♪
♪Finally find a home♪
♪Never fear the eternity♪