Are you going to work today?
Yes. It’s almost time to go.
Can I go with you?
I would be so worried about you if you came.
I beg.
You don’t want me to become crazy, do you?
This is FueangNakhon’s secret.
Was it the Power of Love
that brings us together.
He’s just having a bad singing,
why they hate him like he commits a crime.
Free tasting.
Please take it.
Please stop, Namsom.
Enough.
Please don’t ruin my life again.
Are you done here?
Let’s find somewhere to talk.
How does Namsom work?
Good. She’s beautiful, talented, patient.
What's up, Namsom?
Please help me say thank you to Krom.
Was it about him suggesting you work with his friend?
You must take good care of him.
Sure.
Here’s the Dry fish with watermelon from mom.
This clip is not for Yayee.
It is for you, Krom.
I love you.
Now… I’m going to kiss you.
I kissed my darling.
Wait. When did I become yours?
Since… now.
“Beauty lies in lover’s eyes.”
I realized its meaning
just now.
Love makes the world brighter.
My every minute is worth more than ever.
The air that I breathe
doesn't feel the same.
Everything seems to be different
because of him.
Hello, what’s up?
Hello. Where’s my clip?
I’m busy. I’ll send you later.
Not later! Send it now!
Did I tell Namsom to wait
when she needed help?
All right! You're annoying.
Now!
Got it!
Let me see.
This clip isn’t for Yayee.
It is for you, Krom.
Don’t stop recording.
I want you to keep it as a reminder.
If there’s a day that we fight each other
or if I did something terrible to you,
please use this clip to warn me.
Namsom asked me to thank you
for what you did to her.
The more I stayed with you, the more it ensured me that
I did it right by letting my heart
rules my head.
From now on, I’ll give you my everything.
I’ll take care of you
and I could be anything you want me to be.
I love you.
Now… I’m going to kiss you.
You can continue recording or stop it.
I don't mind.
Krom! Get your ass here!
Krom!
I’m coming.
What the heck!
You should tell me first!
I called you hundreds of times, and you didn’t answer my chat!
I’ve been working!
I love you, Krom.
Where did you get this?
Didn’t you tell me to tell no one?
Who spilled the beans now?
I knew you guys kept something from me.
But I’d never imagine that you’re dating with Fueng!
Are you going to tell the world?
Spit it out. Tell me everything.
Come on! Hurry!
You haven’t told her yet?
No. You should explain her yourself.
I don’t know if I should tell her all.
Whoa! Just tell me everything!
Aren’t we friend?
Alright. Get in to my house.
Can you open the door?
Of course!
Sit!
Did he crush on you since before you were back?
So, he got a Zendaya account because of you.
No. He’s already had his account
since before he knew me.
So romantic.
Well, then…
Did you guys make it out?
See? Everyone is keen to know
how yummy he is.
You’re brats!
So what? Did you?
Not yet.
What are you waiting for?
Waiting for him to start, okay?
What about that kiss in the clip?
Did he kiss you?
No.
No kiss?
No way we didn’t kiss!
I wish I were you, Krom!
Krom. Hey, Krom.
Who’s that? He sounds likes Fueang.
It’s Fueang. He’s my neighbor.
Your neighbor! Since when?
It’s been a while.
Oy! You jerk!
What else are you hiding?
Krom. Where’re you?
Hey, Thoo. Go hide!
Just act normal.
Don’t tell him that we’re here.
I want to see him when he’s crazy in love.
No way. You’ll record us.
No, I won’t do that.
There! Behind the bar.
- My bag!
- Behind the bar.
Whoa! Hurry!
Aw, Fueang.
I miss you, darling.
He said no record.
He's so cute.
I need a kiss to charge my battery.
Please don't break up with my friend!
I promise.
Ay!! He's so handsome! Look!
Let’s go out for dinner at 7 p.m.
I’ll take you to a good place.
Everyone is keen to know
how yummy he is.
Calm down, Krom. That's ridiculous.
Should I go with him?
Or shouldn't I?
Let's do it.
Hey! Where are my pants?
Aw, Fueang.
Why are you dressing like this?
You said you’ll take me for dinner.
I thought you’d drive your car there.
I wanted to take you
where they have delicious food.
Snacking and strolling.
We’d got stuck in traffic with the car.
I see.
It's alright. There's no need to change it.
Come here.
Okay.
Here. Let me help you.
Stay still.
Is it too tight?
No.
Let’s go.
Are you hungry?
Yes.
I know many secret places with excellent food.
Okay.
Don’t get full so soon. Okay?
Um.
Let’s go.
You should tell me that you’re coming.
It was lucky that this space was empty.
Would you close this Zone for me, please?
Sure. Take your time.
This is our signature dish.
Have a wonderful meal.
Thank you.
I hope you’re not too full.
Their soybean curd is the best.
I don’t want you to miss it.
I won't.
Hmm! So tasty!
Very nice view.
The owner is Madam Aoi's friend.
She likes to take us here late at night.
It’s private.
Wait. Why do you laugh?
Is my humming that terrible?
No.
It's just your singing in that event
still stuck in my head.
Was it the Power of Love
that brings us together.
It’s amazing that I can love you.
Hey. Are you teasing me?
If you don’t like to sing,
why didn’t you refuse it?
It’s because of Madam Aoi and Sand.
They always accepted the singing events.
They said
I don’t need to sing well,
My fans will still understand me.
Even that, it was still embarrassing though.
I sang out of tune in every key.
Don’t you have the freedom to choose your job?
Honestly, not much.
But I must admit that
Madam Aoi always got me good ones.
Every job she chose either paid well
or was helpful in terms of connections.
Unsafe Cosmetics,
Dangerous face cream,
or diet pills,
they’ll never get close to me.
Very well care about consumers.
No.
All she concerns about is my image.
She said those products
will ruin my reputation.
She’ll choose only jobs that enhance my image.
But I wonder why she likes to accept singing jobs.
If I could sing like before,
Madam Aoi will force me to sing every month.
Were you a good singer earlier?
I’m not bragging.
You may not know that
I was my school's singing champion before.
Then what happened?
Fueang.
You can talk to me anything.
Listen.
I want to be the one that you can tell everything.
I actually liked to sing before.
Fueang.
Dad.
What’re you doing? Why didn’t you go home?
I’ve done my homework and reading.
Don’t let me see you do this nonsense again.
Give me that guitar.
Let go of it.
Don’t let me see you do this nonsense again.
Since that day
I’ve never had any confidence to sing again.
His face and the voice of my friend’s laughing
always showed up in my head.
Fueang.
Are you consoling me?
So cute.
Well… I’m really fine now.
If you were fine, as you said
you wouldn’t lack of confidence when you sang.
Fueang. You must forgive your dad.
Forgive but not forget.
I know it is hard.
But, you must understand that
he meant well to you even if his actions hurt you.
Sometimes he might forget that
you also has your own life.
Once you're ready to forgive your dad,
the knot in your heart would be untied, too.
Those negative thoughts that are in your mind will disappear
and you’ll come back to sing as well as before.
I didn’t just say it.
Simon often sent me and my colleagues
to train with psychologist.
He said if you want to create positive energies,
you must have positive thinking, too.
Otherwise, it’d be fake.
I will try.
You can do it.
Well, let’s continue eating. Here.
Hmm.
My Turn.
Lin Lan.
Fei Lin.
Cut!
Okay. Change the scene.
Fueang. Kor.
Go say hi to Mr. Lee.
Okay.
No.
What?
You should take care of me
not bring me issues.
Do you want a punch?
Just do what I said.
It’s Madam Aoi’s order.
Nope.
I’m already tired from that fighting scene.
I don’t even know that guy at all.
Uh! Is he sitting next to Madam Aoi?
Yes. Mr. Lee.
He’s the owner of many products.
I can’t remember the brand.
However,
he’s the main sponsor of this movie.
That’s why she wants you guys to greet him.
If you get chances to be his brand’s presenter,
it’ll top up your career path.
Sand.
Very good.
Such a fast move.
Press there.
He’s very good at it.
Well, let’s go.
You can change your costume, Fueang.
Please wait here, Kor.
I’ll call the make-up artist for you.
Vinegar.
Fueang.
Hmm?
Do you still use the same passcode for this phone?
The same one.
Why?
Oh. It’s about the trainer, Golf.
Someone I know wants to have his contact.
- I transferred you the amount I borrowed you yesterday.
- So, he wants to train with Golf?
My mom is fine.
Can I check from your phone?
Yes. His number should be there.
How was it? Did you find it?
Hello.
Hello?
Here is your favorite.
Chinese sausage. Eat a lot.
I burnt it a bit for you.
You burnt it?
Yes. Eat more.
But it’s not healthy. Too burnt.
But it'll be tastier.
Did Fueang busy recently?
It’s been a while since his last coming.
Sure.
He’s been shooting the night scenes.
Don’t you have to go take care of him anymore?
I don’t have to.
He’s afraid that I’d be too exhausted.
Um Hmm. That’s lovely.
He really concerns about my son.
Aw. Are you full?
Um.
Baby, please wash your dish, too.
What’s wrong with him?
He still needs more time to think about you and Fueang.
Think?
Think about what?
Well. Need I say more?
Hmm.
You already knew it!
Oh ho! It is so obvious.
I also knew that, previously,
he often came by our house
just to listen to your story.
I told your dad before.
But he said I imagined it myself.
Until you came back
and your dad saw you both were so close.
Not to mention that Fueang's eyes always show he's crazy in love with you.
Your dad now admits that I’m right.
Okay.
Just give him sometimes.
He’ll get over it.
Alright.
But if he doesn’t,
I’ll deal with him for you.
You’re all grew up.
You can take care of yourself.
You never cause us any problems.
That’s more than we ask for.
I love you so much.
I knew.
But are you sure
that he doesn’t have someone else?
You just said he’s crazy in love with me.
It doesn’t mean that
he can’t feel the same way with others.
He’s very lovely and he’s also an actor.
Everyone wants to get close to him.
How can you be so sure that he’s faithful?
I must ask you this
because I don’t want you to feel sorry about it later.
Hmm?
Um. I’m confident about him.
There is no one else.
Fueang.
It’s alright.
Fueang. Did you wake up?
Is he still sleeping?
Fueang.
Didn’t you ask me to go to the gym?
Are you coming for Fueang?
Who’s that?
Aw, Krom!
I didn’t know that you had a guest.
Ah… I…
Excuse me.
Krom.
Mom!
Honey.
Krom.
Fueang…
He really has someone else.
Oh, honey.
I should trust you.
It’s alright, honey. Don't cry.
Krom.
Are you alright?
I’m alright.
This is Roen.
Charoenkrung. My brother.
Your brother.
Oh. You’re Kromtha.
I’m his brother. We’re siblings.
Ah! Siblings.
You guys look so similar.
Uh. I’ll wait for you outside.
Sorry for interrupting.
His brother.
Krom, you fool!
Thanks for the ride.
I'm leaving.
He’s pretty cute though.
He really is.
Are you serious about this one?
Of course.
At first, it was only like, but now I love him.
but now I love him.
I’m happy with you.
Fight for your love.
I wish you luck!
Thanks.
What were you arguing with Mom last night?
Do you want me to talk to her?
It’s alright.
I only hope she’ll understand that
May asked me to divorce
because she’s having someone else,
not because I’m gay.
That’s what I need.
Well. You’d better go.
Bye. See you later.
She came so fast.
Because you were waiting for me.
I drove here at my full speed.
Didn’t I tell you don’t drive too fast?
I'm kidding.
Roen had an urgent,
so I had to rush him home.
What’s going on?
You look worried.
When I first saw Roen in your room,
my heart fell to the ground.
Now I am so sure
that I really like you so much.
That’s all good.
Then why do you look sad?
My mom.
She worried that you might have someone else.
Wait. Did she know about us?
Um.
She knew.
She also knew you came to my house
to seek my stories.
Really?
She kept acting all along.
Isn’t she good?
Yes. She’s an outstanding actress.
I should suggest her to Madam Aoi.
Only my mom?
Both of you!
Don’t worry.
I won’t have anyone else but Navy.
Navy?
Aw! I heard your colleagues call you that.
I want to call you Navy, too.
It’s cute.
But I don’t want you to call me that.
Aw. What do you want me to call you?
I prefer you to call me
“Darling.”
Alright.
Navy?
My darling.
Don't be paranoid.
One more?
Hello.
Hello?
I’ll block you if you don’t speak.
Namsom, I…
It's you!
Someone is calling you, Krom.
What’s up, Fueang?
Can you come to see me?
Krom?
Okay.
Who’s that?
I’m leaving, Kung.
I asked who’s that?
My friend.
I'm going.
Good luck.
Please put away my shirt.
Bye Bye.
You look weird.
Fueang.
Fueang?
Fuang.
What are you doing?
I want you to know that,
from now on, I can’t live without you.
I don’t know why, but your smile
hypnotized me into a trance.
That was my feelings when we first met.
Whenever I feel sad, I look into your eyes.
You console me and boost me up.
I can feel that and it’s so warm.
Maybe it was destiny
that put us together.
You’re another part of my life.
You’re always beside me.
I won’t ask anything for me.
Just holding our hearts together.
It’s paradise. Our moments are beautiful.
We belong to each other.
Because all my life is you.
Finally, you can do it.
I could find my way to sing,
all because of ...
...you.
Thank you.
Navy?
You’re another part of my life.
You’re always beside me.
I won’t ask anything for me.
Just holding our hearts together.
It’s paradise. Our moments are beautiful.
We belong to each other.
Because all my life is you.
I'm proud of you, darling.
You’re another part of my life.
You’re always beside me.
I won’t ask anything for me.
Just holding our hearts together.
It’s paradise. Our moments are beautiful.
We belong to each other.
Because all my life is you.
is you.
How is it?
Having Fueang as your wife.
You jerk!
Does he have a lover?
Hmm?
I have to shoot many love scenes with him.
I don’t want to make his lover get angry.
Don’t worry. His lover will understand.
Fueang. I love you.