What! Fueang likes you?
I overheard it from his friend.
He likes him.
Really?
Um.
His friend might imagine it himself.
If he didn’t think about me that way,
so why did he do that?
He might be a Casanova.
You can go home.
I have to work.
He has changed.
He kept hiding from me.
What had he done to you
to make you hide from him?
I didn’t hind from him.
Don’t forget to explain it to Sand.
Explain?
Krom has a lover!
What!
Why do you have to be crazy if I had a lover?
Because I like you.
Since the first time I saw your photo.
Please keep pretending you didn’t know it.
Please do the same.
Does this mean you like me too?
I told you.
Please keep pretending too.
They were watching us.
I’m afraid there’ll be rumors.
Isn’t it good to have rumors with me?
It’s not like that.
I’m very new in this business
and I prefer people to focus on my work.
So…
I’m thinking, why don’t we…
find somewhere more private.
What do you want to do?
Whatever you want.
Stop!
Sand!
Why did you hit us?
What’s wrong with you?
Stop it!
- Go!
- Why?
Well… wait for me here.
Where are you going?
I want to talk to some jerk. See you later.
Thank you for letting me know, Fueang.
Otherwise, he would get her already.
Eh! Or she would get him?
Fueang!
Did you tell her?
Don’t think that I don’t know
that you tried to manipulate Sand
about Krom’s lover.
That’s it. I’m going to bed.
Have fun.
Alright, Fueang!
You started it!
Wait for my turn.
Do you want to know Fueang’s secret?
Fueang’s secret?
You’re betraying me again.
I did it
because I love you.
If you love me as you said, tell them the truth
that we are dating.
Alright.
Kor makes Fueang’s body burn
like a vocano that is ready to erupt.
He won’t stop giving a sweet revenge
to his beloved wife
to pay back for the guilt he had committed
and suddenly,
he brings his dearest wife
to their heaven,
where no others exist.
So overwhelming!
Right. Next episode?
- Yes!
- Good! Good!
- Here you go.
- Hey!
If I had to listen another word,
I’d rather go.
Bye.
Hah! Don’t you hold me up?
The next episode is fire. Look!
Such a masterpiece!
Sorry for my late.
Fueang posted a picture on the Zendaya.
It was super chaotic.
Why are you standing? Sit down.
We’d better go somewhere else.
They’ve been crazy for those guys since.
What’s going on?
It’s FuengKor’s fans.
They edited your photo with Kor and put in their fiction.
You’re also in it.
Do you want more?
Yeah, good.
Look.
Hey! Who shot this?
Aw! How am I supposed to know?
#TheFirstWifeFace
Look at Fueng’s face. So jealous.
Kor must be punished badly.
Didn’t those fans aware that there’s nothing between these two?
They know.
But they’re still happy even in their dream
or their imagination.
Imagination?
Really?
Well, let me see.
Hmm. What else do you have?
Which kind of fictions?
Drama, Erotic, or Period?
Huh? They have a Period fiction?
Anything can happen in a fiction’s world.
Oh! Oh! Oh! There is one.
You’re portrayed as a convent student.
Fueang and Kor,
they came to sing at the school as K-pop artists.
Then, they took you to Saladaeng brothel.
Saladaeng brothel?
Where is that?
Kor’s condo.
It locates at Saladaeng.
He always took his girls there.
That’s why they call Saladaeng brothel.
You knew that Kor is such a wolf.
What makes you guys imagine things with him and Fueang?
Those girls are just his flavor of the week.
His real love is only for Fueang.
That’s right!
Eat the chickens.
Hold on. Show me those fictions.
Come on.
They are so good!
Well, you read them for me.
Are you going home?
Yes. How about you?
Me too.
Do you want a ride?
Super!
See you later.
- Bye Bye. See you.
- Goodbye.
Drive safe.
- Thanks.
- Be careful.
Well, Krom.
I have a thought to write a story about you and Fueang.
Isn’t it good?
Well.
What is the plot?
I imagine you
as a young hermit
Hmm?
who assumes that the prince has a crush on him.
So, he confessed his love to the prince.
The prince is so furious.
He hits your head very hard.
What do you think?
I’m afraid
that your plot
is out-dated.
out-dated?
The prince already confessed that he loves the young hermit.
Is it true?
Um.
What did he say to you?
Did you guys have sex?
Is that the only thing you have in your head?
Why?
But Kor said to me that
he has Fueng’s secret to tell me.
And this secret
will make me stop loving him.
Secret?
What secret?
I have no idea.
Start your day with a good meal
before seeing your special one.
Please do the same.
Hey! Wait!
Does this mean you like me too?
I didn’t know that you can cook.
I can cook, but never have time doing it.
So, I had to rely on others.
How about the sauce?
What does it taste like?
Any comments?
Aw! You haven't ate it yet?
I brought one for me and one for you.
But you...
Aw! You should've told me.
I already ate all of them.
That’s alright. Seeing you smiled while eating
made me already full of happiness.
Now I know what the sauce tastes like.
Did I startle you?
You attacked me again.
Get used to it.
I’ll wash this dish.
Hey, stop. Let me do it.
There’s no water.
The tab is broken.
My father wants to fix it but hasn’t done it yet.
Do you have some tools? I’ll fix it.
Can you do that?
Yes. When I was with my parent,
I was a regular technician at the house.
Go get the tools.
Alright.
He can cook.
He's romantic.
He's good at fixing things.
Why is he so perfect?
It won’t take long.
Alright.
Get ready. I’ll pick you up.
Where are we going?
To see Fueang’s secret.
He is with me.
What is he doing?
Fixing the tab.
Ask him about his today’s job.
He won’t allow you to go with him.
It works now.
Are you tired? You’re sweating.
This?
The water was splashing me.
Good job. I’ll ask my mother to cook you a nice meal.
There’s no need. I got my reward.
Uh. Are you going to work today?
Yes. It’s almost time to go.
Can I go with you?
Well.. I…
I really need a high concentration on this job
and I would be so worried about you if you came.
What kind of job that needs such a high concentration?
Well, it’s a showcase. The general one.
There’s a ton of client data
that I need to memorize.
How was it? Did you ask him?
I asked him.
He doesn’t want me to go with him.
You must prepare yourself.
He's not likely a good person.
Is that so?
Um. Go see it yourself.
Are you alright?
Well, can’t I just be happy?
Look at that good weather.
Wait here. Let me get change.
Namtarn.
When will you finish your class?
Ah.. You didn’t forget about our date, right?
Good. At 4 p.m.
Don’t miss it.
Okay. See you.
I have another date with Amp at that time.
Amp. It's me.
About our appointment at 4 p.m.
I’m afraid that I have an acting class at that time.
It’s because of Madam Aoi. She says I need an urgent class.
Can we...
Can we shift it to 8 p.m. instead?
Okay, right?
Good.
I’ll take you to a good restaurant.
I don’t understand.
Why are his fans so crazy about him?
If a guy like him said,
I wouldn’t be able to handle Fueang’s secret.
Could it be possible that it is worse than Kor’s bad habits?
Let’s go.
What happens?
Whose car is this?
I don’t know.
Whose car is this?!
Is this yours?
Huh? How could someone parked a car like this?
Are they blind?
Is this yours?
How about you? Huh!
You dipshit! How did they get the license?
How am I going to get in? Like this?
Who's going to responsible for it?
Ah.
Please don’t. It’s not good.
I beg you, Sand.
You don’t want me to become crazy, do you?
Hello, guys. How’s it going?
I heard some of you have been here
since before the store opened.
Now, the waiting is over.
Our FuangNakhon has arrived.
Is there anyone here who wants to see him?
Where are you taking me to?
You’ll see it.
- Give me louder please.
- Hurry! It's almost time.
Oh Ho! He must be very impressed.
Please welcome, FueangNakhon!
Hi, Fueang.
Hi.
You look so smart.
Our Handsome guy.
What are those shoes?
Well, he always wears these shoes
whenever he lacks of confidence.
He said people will put their focus on them instead of him.
Sand doesn’t like him to wear them
because of the color.
Right. So outstanding.
How do you feel
as a new presenter
of Moomee?
I’m very glad.
It is such an honor
to receive this opportunity.
As you guys may know.
Before I accepted to be the presenter,
I always ensure that those products
must be good as they claimed.
Did you hear that?
Beside of the new product’s opening,
he also prepares his special show
to surprise all of you.
Am I right, Fueang?
Am I right?
Yes.
Oops. He’s very considerate of his fans.
Get ready.
Ready?
Ready for what?
This is FueangNakhon’s secret.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Let’s watch the performance from FueangNakhon.
And this secret
will make me stop loving him.
I really need a high concentration on this job
And…
I would be so worried about you if you came.
You must prepare yourself.
He's not likely a good person.
I beg you.
or I would go crazy.
There was no one for me.
Where were you?
There was no place for me.
My mind is drifting far and far away.
And at the end,
I found you.
I don’t care about any others.
Don’t off the beat.
One. Two. Three. Four.
Is it the Power of Love
that brings us together.
- มหัศจรรย์ ฉันได้รักเธอ
- คนอะไร ร้องเพลงเหมือนไม่เคยรู้จักดนตรีมาก่อน
wherever it leads me to
you’ll always be my destiny.
As they say,
nothing is perfect in this world.
The people I respect the most
are these fans.
They knew that he had a desperate singing skill
but they still tried their best to sing along.
Please remember one thing. I love you.
I beg everybody here.
Please don’t hire me to sing again
I feel sorry for my audiences.
That’s alright.
- That’s alright.
- You’re awesome.
You’re Amazing, Fueang!
That’s Kor!
He came to support his wife.
You!
You didn’t tell me you’d come.
Wait until tonight. I’ll beat you hard.
Big scream to FueangNakhon!
Again please.
Oh ho! Such a massive screaming!
It must be because of his angelic voice.
Before we go,
do you have anything to say?
Yes.
Well.
Please support Moomee Cushion.
The green cartridge Cushion.
Compatible with every generation. Cover every scratch.
Wow! Don’t forget to get one, everybody.
I guarantee its best quality.
Now.
I’ll let Fueang go rest.
Thank you very much.
Please cheer for him.
I thought he had a scarier secret.
I was frightened.
He started this war.
Fueang.
He told Sand about me and Mim.
In fairness,
that was my payback time.
After this event,
he knew his anti-fans
would spread many nasty comments on social media.
That won’t concern him.
But you,
the guy who he likes would make him embarrassed.
You said anti-fans.
Um. Look. Check the social media.
Is that called singing?
His pretty face helps him.
Your singing is like a signal to evacuate.
You sing like a goat trying to imitate Mariah Carey.
He’d be serving a life sentence for his singing.
I didn’t know the cat could sing.
- He’s just having a bad singing,
- Your singing sounds like a GPS lost in a tunnel.
- not committing a crime.
That’s why he only uses Zendaya.
How could you guys stand it?
What else can we do?
We don’t have time to reply to all of those hated comments.
No one does that.
I can’t believe
I could hear it from the guy
who likes to scold the press.
At least I still got a scene on the media for scolding the press,
but replying to those toxic fans
is wasted of time.
I prefer to spend my quality time
with something good or things that make me happy.
Especially, having our own brothel. It’s very good.
It is undeniable things
that come together with our career.
Imagine if you were a doctor.
You wouldn’t want your patients to die while you're on duty.
But that is inevitable.
You still need to face it.
It is the same as being an actor.
Keeping our personal issues private
or avoiding negative comments
is almost impossible.
It comes as a package with our career.
Eventually… we only have to live with it.
Right.
What’s going on?
Free tasting.
Please take it.
You can take it.
Aw!
Where are you going?
Hey.
Kor.
It’s Kor.
Namsom, I…
Please stop, Namsom.
You always ran away from me.
Well…
Please talk to me.
Don’t go.
Please.
I beg you.
Enough.
Please don’t ruin my life again.
Okay.
I’ll leave you now.
Namsom?
So familiar.
Rumor! A new rising star actor is dating Namsom, the famous transgender model.
Transgender woman.
Very pretty.
Where is Kor?
Okay.
I’ll wait you here.
Alright.
Are you meeting someone?
Hello, Fueang.
How are you doing?
I told you. You can’t run away from him.
You found each other again eventually.
Uh. This is Krom.
The one I told you about.
She is Namsom.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
When the hashtag to ban your idol was on viral
I just knew that
he wouldn’t be only an ordinary staff.
Are you done here?
Let’s find somewhere to sit.
I’d rather not. Someone will notice us.
I don’t want to cause you and Kor more trouble.
I better go.
Wouldn’t kor be mad if he knew about this?
Fueang.
Hmm?
You’ve been contacting with her all these times, haven’t you?
So that I can ask about her living
If she needs anything.
Didn’t you afraid he’d notice when you called her?
I recorded her as this name.
Vinegar.
Yes. A guy like Kor
won’t care about things like this.
Fueang.
Hmm?
He’s always been loving her, hasn’t he?
Did you notice it?
Well.
His actions clearly showed when he was with her.
Yes. He has.
I think she’s the only one
that he truly loves.
No matter what gender she is, he still loves her.
Alright.
The famous actor “K” was found, taking the new actress to his condo.
Excuse me. One Blue Hawaii, please.
Hello.
Yes. I’m Namsom.
Hello. What's up, Namsom?
Please help me say thank you to Krom.
Was it that he suggested you work with his friend?
I knew it since when he asked for your number from me.
He wasn’t only suggesting,
but also guaranteed me to his friend.
Really? How was it?
Yayee admitted that she didn’t like me as first
because she’s Kor’s fan.
But, Krom reassured her that
he would pay for my wage
if I disappointed her.
Without his help,
I definitely wouldn't have gotten this job.
You must take good care of him.
Alright.
Passionate between his beloved wife
and the young Japanese man
increases the heat which is confined
and never be released,
like a waterlogging waits to be drained.
His suffering eventually turned him
into a zombie. Eating people alive.
In the end, he was caught and killed.
His body was then displayed in the hospital
at the center of Bangkok.
Young hermit’s fiction is out of the world.
What’s the writer’s name?
Young hermit.
Young hermit!
Thoo! Is it you?
I always know that I have a gift.
Whatever!
Yayee. How does Namsom work?
Um. Good.
She’s beautiful, talented, patient, hardworking and never complains.
Unlike the rumors.
What rumors?
It was a few years ago.
They said she dated with Kor.
The transgender community
were not accepted by society at that time.
People assumed that
She was a gold digger who wanted to be famous
from dating Kor.
Someone created news that Namsom had problems at work.
No responsibility. So, no one dared to hire her.
She’s worked hard to support her mother since her dad died.
As well as pay for her tuition fees.
Those people who created those fake news
without knowing anything about her
They should know that they ruined a person's life
She is pitiful.
Yes. She really is.
But, wait.
How did you know her?
I knew her through my friend.
Gee! As someone who just got back,
you’re so good at making friends.
Ouch! That’s hurt!
Hey. Hey. What are you two hiding from me?
Nothing! Why will we do that?
There is no secret among us.
Right?
Yeah. Nothing at all.
Don't let me find out.
Krom, what about your promise?
You said you’d give me something in return
if I gave her a job.
Oh. I won’t forget.
Very good.
We're all here. Such a pity that you can't come.
Please take care Fueang for me.
Jong, these are my fans.
Take it.
I'm counting on you.
Cheers.
Whoa, Jay!
What are you wearing?
Oh. I followed your advice.
Just be casual.
Can you teach me how to take good pictures?
Look at you.
Is it good?
It's too casual.
Fueang. Here’s the Dry fish with watermelon from mom.
Wow. Look so good.
I wanted to eat it.
Let me feed you.
You look strange today.
Um Hmm. Yummy!
It’s good, right?
Very fresh.
Are you tired today?
Not likely. Is something wrong?
Can I take your video?
video?
What video?
Just a general one.
It is for yayee.
Oh, Yayee. I remember her.
She’s crazy about you.
Would you help me, please?
Now?
With this dress?
She still likes you badly no matter what you wear.
Well, alright.
Okay.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Okay.
Cut!
Hello, Yayee.
Thank you for your support.
I hope your product will be the best-selling.
If I didn't get a face cream contract
I’d do the product review for you.
How about
if I take you to a nice restaurant instead?
Let me know when. See you.
Bye bye.
She’d be all screaming after watching this clip.
Krom.
Can I have another take?
This’s already good.
Come on. Let do one more.
Alright.
Okay.
Ready?
This clip is not for Yayee.
It is for you, Krom.
Don’t stop recording it.
I want you to keep it as a record.
If there’s a day that we fight each other
or if I did something terrible to you,
please uses this clip to warn me.
Namsom asked me to say thank you to you.
What you did, assures me that
I did the right thing
by letting my heart rule my head.
From now on, I’ll give you my everything.
I’ll take care of you
and I could be anything you want me to be.
I love you.
Now… I’m going to kiss you.
You can continue recording or stop it.
Whatever you like.
I’d better stop. It might be leaked.
So what? I don’t care.
I kissed my darling.
Wait.
When did I become yours?
Since… now.
Are you okay?
Okay.
Are you…
sure about this?
I always want this since the day I met you.
So…
Okay.
You're shaking.
I miss my baby.
Can you boost me with a kiss?
If I could sing like before,
Madam Aoi will force me to sing in every event.
Have you ever sung better than this?
You may not know.
I was my school singing champion.
He’s cute.
I liked you before but now I love you.