TRUE TO LOVE
ALL CHARACTERS, EVENTS, LOCATIONS, AND
INCIDENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS.
Yes.
I've been trying to reach you
since yesterday.
You just woke up?
Yes.
You know today's
an important event, right?
You have to do well.
Everybody worked hard on it.
Huh? On what?
On what? Hey!
Tonight is the Golden Night party.
Don't tell me you forgot.
No.
I just woke up,
so I wasn't thinking clearly.
Okay. See you later.
'Cause you're garbage!
You're stinky, disgusting garbage!
The garbage is being loaded.
That's right, I'm garbage too.
You are toxic waste
that can't even be recycled.
You really stink.
I'm garbage myself.
-Good morning.
-Hello, Sang-jin.
What is this?
What happened?
Sang-jin. Despite its great intention,
we reached an agreement
it has many inconveniences.
Right, Sang-jin.
We need to focus on work,
but the open plan is too distracting.
And it felt weird
facing each other without the partitions.
You know how awkward it is to make
eye contact while yawning?
It's not been long since
the partitions were removed.
How inconvenient could it have been?
How'd you find time to reach an agreement?
When you adapt to changes,
you go through a transition period.
U-ri?
You agree? Was it uncomfortable?
No, I really, really loved it.
Without the partitions,
it was easier to ask questions.
It was easier to catch up
with how everything was going.
Right, U-ri?
Hey, that's the benefit I was hoping for
when I got rid of all those with our U-ri
covered in sweat,
but you put it all back up.
And when the CEO suggests something,
you are supposed
to be supportive sometimes.
It's like, "You can say your piece,
I'll go my way."
Go where? You got so many places to go?
When I was your age,
I was unconditionally obedient,
did whatever I was told
without a question.
You are having it all too easy now.
This is like heaven, you know that?
Have the CEO's office. I'll sit here.
You should work comfortably
in the CEO's office.
I'll go work. Get some rest here.
If you're hungry,
eat or whatever you want.
I'm off. Just lie down.
I'll be standing up.
VP, I need to talk to you.
Why am I so out of breath?
Sit down. Why are you up?
Your legs must be tired.
He meant well, right?
Sit, sit.
He meant well.
"Our U-ri."
You were like a condescending geezer.
Those who hold a grudge
for something they made the person do.
Exactly like that.
"When I was your age,
I was unconditionally obedient."
That was so off-putting.
Seriously?
You wanted me to remind you
when you act like one.
That's why I'm telling you.
Okay, I'm a condescending geezer.
That's me. So what?
I thought you didn't know.
Seriously...
By the way,
we need to take it as a "no," right?
When you have a blind date,
no call for three days is a "no."
Look at how many days it has been.
"An offer you can't refuse"?
What is this? Spam mail?
That's how confident I feel
about the contract.
But that's not the point.
She told me to send a contract
as if she'd sign it right away.
She doesn't check emails.
She's unreachable.
Goodness.
You can't get a hold of her?
She ignores my texts,
her phone was off
when I called after email.
And she hasn't called me back.
She's straight up ghosting me.
She must have her own reasons.
Wait a little longer.
What is it?
Hey, you know something, right?
You followed her to give her phone back.
Did something happen that day?
Like what?
Bo-ra, Bo-ra...
Wipe your lips first.
You saw everything, right?
Any signs of backstabbing
or...
-Did you do anything wrong?
-I didn't.
We switched the phones and I came back.
For now, it is a "no."
But is it because
she's testing the waters?
Or is it because she already signed
with another company?
I need to know to plan my next step.
I'm getting a headache.
Seriously. Yeon Bo-ra.
It's a "no" either way.
Let's move on and try something else.
No.
It's been a while
I felt challenged like this.
I will get her signature no matter what.
Let's go.
Go where?
It's tonight.
Champagnes are provided by the sponsor.
-Make this straight.
-Okay.
Did you check the cue sheet?
Yes, all checked.
We're checking up on Deborah.
You look so gorgeous today.
I thought there was an actress in here.
Right back at you.
Anna Wintour would be intimidated by you.
You look really stylish.
Give it to me.
I heard you got proposed to.
Congrats on your engagement.
Congratulations.
Of course, marriage is a crazy thing.
But, it won't hurt
to do a crazy thing once in your life.
It calls for a celebration.
I appreciate it.
Oscar de Rang wants to do
a wedding dress shoot with you.
Among the dresses you try in the shoot
they'll sponsor the one you like.
You know, Oscar de Rang, right?
-I'm so jealous!
-Awesome.
Really?
I'll be really honored.
How did I land this?
I was talking with the PR manager,
who turned out to be your fan.
So I mentioned that you...
Was I not supposed to mention it
before the announcement?
No, I don't mind that at all.
Right?
Once this issue is out,
everybody will know anyway.
Now, before the party begins,
shall we have a toast?
Sounds good.
It's time to go.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Good luck, Bo-ra.
-I'll look forward to it.
-Thanks.
You can do it.
Did you eat anything?
Did you take some medicine
after eating something?
Did you get any sleep?
Yu-jeong, can't you
just say, "nice dress"?
You look nice.
Good luck.
Our concept today is classy best friends.
Let's look mannerly
and politely offer champagne.
You know what I mean?
You do know why we are here
and who invited us?
I do.
What are you doing? Let's go.
-She smiled at me.
-Who?
Looks like you forgot the dress code
as you were busy looking stunning.
I see no champagne gold.
I do have champagne gold.
I missed that, since you are so gorgeous.
Behind you.
Long time no see, Su-hyeok.
People are staring at us to see
how the divorced couple say hi.
Smile and say hi.
It's been a while. Have you been well?
Thanks for inviting us.
Well...
You think it was me who invited you?
Anyway, you took the trouble
to come all the way here. Thank you.
No problem.
You look well. You look really pretty.
Don't.
Yes, ma'am.
Deborah, please standby.
-Okay.
Golden Night, a party for Gold Misses.
Tonight, we have a guest speaker
who'll give the Gold Misses tips
on how to win in a relationship.
The dating expert that is winning
in her own relationship!
She is Korea's first and top dating coach.
Please welcome to the stage Deborah.
Music, cue!
Deborah, please standby.
Okay.
EP 04
CRAZIER THAN JOKER
At that moment,
I felt a strong urge to tell those
who believed that Santa
will come on Christmas
if they are nice and don't cry...
that Santa Claus does not exist.
Deborah?
As long as I am worthy,
as long as my mojo is still present,
nothing will go wrong with my love life.
Even if that's not the case,
it's okay to break up or be alone.
And someday, I'll be recognized by someone
and love less and be loved more.
He'll eventually
get down on one knee with a ring
and we will have a happy ending.
I ought to tell
those who have this belief,
there is no such thing as Santa
nor happy endings.
JU-WAN
Your call has been forwarded to voicemail
and will be charged after the beep.
JU-WAN
After all, promises get broken,
love changes, and men leave.
A woman is a woman's worst enemy,
a woman you know at that.
I have to tell the truth.
I ought to.
A party for Gold Misses...
Welcome to Golden Night,
ladies and gentlemen.
By the way,
what's the point of being a Gold Miss?
It's no match for a Diamond Miss.
Why don't we be honest here?
Wearing a ring on a ring finger
on the left hand,
having a diamond ring there
means there's nothing to worry about
even if you go broke or lose your job.
It also means you're free from
guy problems or the pain of breakups.
Still, we haven't been able to do that
and are still called "Gold Miss."
We are losers.
We need to admit our failure first, right?
What?
Is this not what you were
expecting to hear?
Then what is it that
you wanted me to tell you?
It's okay to be alone?
You're so okay with being alone,
you wear high heels,
holding your head up high
curving guys with lots of attitude.
Then why do you highlight things
in my books, read my column,
cry and lose sleep over a guy all the time
and send me your stories seeking advice?
"Is this flirting?"
"Is it just me?"
"Does he even love me?"
You're okay being alone? As if.
You're scared and lonely 'cause
you think you might end up alone forever.
If not, why don't you extend your lease
no longer than a year?
You can't have a haircut as you like,
you reluctantly attend all the weddings,
you can't cut ties with friends.
Why do you keep holding off big decisions?
'Cause he will show up one day
and put a diamond ring on your finger?
Are you waiting for that?
Gold Miss, my foot.
Until we get married,
we just live an incomplete life.
An incomplete life
awaiting a complete life!
What else?
What else do you want to know?
How to hit on a guy?
When you think it's too late,
it's already too late.
You should have found a guy
when you were younger.
All the decent guys
are already taken by younger ones.
We got nothing.
So if an unattractive,
ugly, old guy likes you,
just date him.
Go date him.
-What's she doing?
-Or...
Or...
get plastic surgery, facial fillers,
or shave down some bone.
Do something.
Now!
Shall we talk about men?
Men.
All men are...
bastards!
Sorry, I'm really sorry.
Let me try again.
Deborah says!
Men are bastards!
What is she saying?
Get her off stage!
Why do you call men bastards? Why?
At first, they follow you around
like a little puppy,
but when another girl is nice to them,
they smooch that girl, those bastards.
-Did I cross the line?
-Turn off the microphone.
-Turn it off.
-There.
Guess what they call us
if they feel unheard!
They call us bitches. Bitches!
Don't just stand there. Go do something.
Come on, do something.
Even a pro dog trainer
can't fix those bastards.
Put on some music! Louder!
Bastards.
The most terrible bastard was...
Music, cue!
Everybody is leaving. Do something!
Louder!
I thought my life was a tragedy,
but it was a comedy.
I wish someone would come
and take me to anywhere but here.
I wish I could become smaller than an ant
and be carried outside.
Put me down, please.
Don't follow me.
It's my second time seeing that back.
Yes, Yu-jeong.
It's near the back door.
Yes.
-Hello.
-We're terribly sorry.
-We'll take the...
-Yes, sir...
Oh, that was...
The incident was something
we failed to expect.
Once again,
we apologize for the inconvenience.
We're sorry.
I'm going nuts.
You're here, ma'am.
You look like Meryl Streep today.
Yes, I think I'm going to be the devil.
Gather around, everyone.
Come along.
So what's the status?
We're jammed with complaints,
not only from the guests
but also the sponsors and advertisers.
Fortunately, no one said
they'll pull back their ads.
Just not yet.
These days, even a small incident
instantly leads to a boycott.
What kind of advertiser would put an ad
in a magazine
with column of a controversial figure?
I just checked.
The next issue has already been printed.
Deborah.
How can she screw me over?
I let her jump on the bandwagon,
but she repays me by ruining everything?
Why did she do that?
Let me hear the reason.
Why are you all looking at me?
What do you mean? You're her best friend.
Is it because she was drunk?
Or has she gone insane
preparing for the wedding?
Are you sure she was drunk?
She wasn't high?
How would I know?
There are various kinds
of friendship between women.
You know, it could be
just shallow and superficial.
We aren't close enough
to pour our hearts out to each other.
What the fuck...
Good morning.
Don't put anyone through.
Call the security manager stat.
Sir.
Amp up the number of security guards,
if needed,
to prevent outsiders from entering. Okay?
And remember this photo.
This person.
-Call right away if you see her, okay?
-Yes, sir.
Even I feel hurt.
-This isn't the end.
-Really?
Who do you think it is?
-Vice president?
-It is. It's Su-hyeok.
So manly.
A knight in shining armor.
-So cool.
-And handsome.
Amazing!
A flasher's big picture
to show her panties?
Not impressive.
She's a parasite obsessed with a man.
The video is going viral,
the Internet is flooded with articles,
and the intensity
and speed of the hate comments...
Even a traitor
wouldn't be criticized this much.
And it's so cruel.
Even if she did something wrong,
how can they bash one person this hard?
Like what they say
in the comments isn't crass.
She makes a living
by using her celebrity status.
It's the price for fame.
That's not fair.
She works hard too.
Why are her tax
and exchange rates different?
Rightfully so.
'Cause she touched an extremely
sensitive issue in Korea.
Hey, why did you jump on the stage
all of a sudden?
'Cause a person collapsed.
She didn't collapse, she just fell.
And when you see a woman fall,
it's good manners to pretend
you didn't notice.
It's super embarrassing.
So what now?
-What?
-Deborah's book.
What are you going to do?
As for that...
we need to keep an eye on things for now.
How can she come back from this?
It's safe to say she's finished now.
If Deborah calls you, don't answer it.
It'll only make things awkward
for each other, right?
Jeez.
It's not like I said something wrong.
Did I do something wrong?
INFLUENCER DEBORAH
UNDER FIRE FOR FOUL LANGUAGE
UNDER THE INFLUENCE IN PUBLIC
HURLING OFFENSIVE REMARKS AT THE GUESTS
THAT WERE AS INFAMOUS AS POLITICAL BRAWLS
DREADFUL DEBORAH SAYS
SAYING MEN ARE BASTARDS AND MOOCHERS
PROVOKING OUTRAGE AMONG MEN
Saying there's no Santa
came at a bigger price than I thought.
ALL SPINSTERS THERE
GOT A DAGGER IN THEM.
OTHERS' LOVE STORIES
WAS HER MONEY-SPINNER.
Who is it?
It's me.
Hey.
How is she doing?
I don't know.
She won't come out of the room.
You still hungover?
Get up already.
Hey. Come on.
Did you see the articles?
In the morning.
They say I hate men
and I hate women as well.
I was thinking what kind of person I am
if I hate both men and women.
What could it be? A public enemy.
It's not the time for this.
It's really serious.
Signing a petition?
Look how far it got in just half a day.
This is blowing out of proportion.
At this rate...
When you say one word wrong
you get buried in no time these days.
And you didn't say just one word.
I should have dragged you
off the stage yesterday.
I should have knocked you
in the head and made you pass out.
I shouldn't have let you say all that.
Yes, you should have.
Hey.
New articles keep coming up in real time.
MOM'S CHICKEN F&amp;B'S FULL STATEMENT
What is it?
What?
In this situation?
-What?
-How can he do this in this situation?
He didn't even call you, right?
Our company and Deborah
are connected by a model contract.
We confirm that our company
has nothing to do with her.
As a way to take responsibility
for the incident,
we inform that we decided
to terminate the contract
with Deborah effective today.
The company probably decided
to dodge the bullet.
But who caused all this mess?
Whatever, now you have to do something.
First off, post an apology right away.
If you don't do it now,
you'll be dragged to do it later.
What should I write?
"My boyfriend cheated on me
and even dumped me."
"I was drunk, out of it,
and made a scene."
Should I say that and ask them
to go easy on me?
Or to curse at him with me?
You can say that. That's a fact. Why not?
At least people will feel sympathetic.
Let's focus on you.
We have to prevent this
from getting worse.
Hello, this is Deborah.
I am deeply sorry
for my inappropriate and insensitive words
under the influence at the event.
I would like
to sincerely apologize to those
who were offended by my remarks.
I recently came to part with my boyfriend
whom I had dated for quite a long time.
As a dating coach,
I've indirectly experienced
countless relationships and breakups.
But when I went through it myself,
I had a dreadful time
going through the breakup
and was hardly able
to control my emotions.
Though I was physically
and emotionally drained,
I could not cancel the event.
As a result of pushing through it,
I ended up getting on the stage drunk,
and saying awful things
that were inexcusable.
Unlike some people suspected,
drugs nor alcohol abuse were involved.
From the incident,
I completely realized how emotional,
vulnerable, and irresponsible
I am as a person.
I take full responsibility for my actions,
so I will stop all the activities
planned for the future
to take the time to reflect on who I am
and how I can become more mature
in the future.
Thank you for taking
the time to read this.
Sincerely, Deborah.
I actually had a slight hope
as I was making the confession
that maybe this can
act as mitigating factors.
However, reality hit...
and there's nothing like Santa
in this world.
CLASS ACTION FOR DEFAMATION...
CONFESSION ON HER BREAKUP!
HAND-WRITTEN APOLOGY
REASON FOR BREAKUP?
ALCOHOL? DRUG? NETIZENS' COLD RESPONSE!
A woman in her thirties,
self-pity party after being dumped.
She made such a fuss all the time.
Long story short.
She got dumped, drunk, humiliated herself.
She has so many excuses.
A woman who loses control of her emotions
sickens me as a woman myself.
She's crazy like Joker.
Deborah's ex-boyfriend
is the real winner in the relationship.
She's a real "K-ex-girlfriend."
Are those who unlike the comments
Deborah's friends?
She's a dating coach,
but she got dumped. How pathetic.
I saw that coming
as she was being a know-it-all.
A total smarty pants.
If she thinks about
what she's said so far,
she'd cringe really hard.
Deborah the Liar, isn't this a lie too?
Will she turn on the waterworks now?
ACCOUNT PRIVACY
ACCOUNT SWITCHED TO PRIVATE ACCOUNT
I went from a crazy and horrible bitch,
to a pathetic and a little weird bitch.
I also got nicknames like Pet Peeve,
Deborah the Liar, and Korean Joker.
A complete failure.
A complete downfall, indeed.
God never gives us
more than we can handle.
Isn't that amazing?
I must be a really remarkable bitch.
You overestimated me!
You see, I can't handle this much.
Hey.
You're drunk.
I'll bring more.
We're out of beers.
I'm good.
Then we can drink wine.
Wine.
PLEASE ALWAYS SPEAK TO ME NICELY
Nicely? How?
It's all ruined!
You want to hear nice words?
You did wrong,
but you don't want to be blamed?
You think someone will comfort you?
Get it together.
In this cold, harsh world,
no one is on your side!
People waited on your downfall.
People are gloating
'cause you became miserable.
Let's put her to bed.
Let's go to bed. Come on.
-Put it down.
-It's not the time for nice words.
All right.
-Seriously...
-Give it.
Yu-jeong, I'm really...
I'm sorry, Yu-jeong.
I'm sorry.
Thank you, I mean it.
Bo-mi. My Bo-mi.
Bo-mi, I'm really sorry.
I love you.
Next item.
"If you're not sincere, don't come near."
"If you're meant to pass me by,
please just pass me by."
"To deal with more heartbreaks...
tteokbokki is too spicy."
This is written in Korean, right?
I don't get it. What is it?
It's an excerpt from
a famous writer on social media.
The concept is a book you read at
3:00 a.m. while having a beer by yourself.
These kind of sentimental books
are in high demand these days.
On top of sentimental illustrations,
if we add some calligraphy,
it can be a sentimental illustrated essay,
which can draw readers' attention.
How does it sound?
Well...
Not bad.
An expensive book cover,
pretty illustrations and calligraphy,
comforting sentiments.
Shoving everything that could work
into one book to make money,
that superficial goal is clearly noticed.
It'd be a relief
if it sells well at least.
You could have just said
it's a bad idea, Su-hyeok.
No, it's not bad.
The thing is,
planning what's hot now is pointless.
We should take the initiative.
We can't be an imitator,
albeit third-rate.
Let's just say
this proposal was a bad one.
No, what I meant was...
Okay, then. Let's move on.
So not this one. What's next?
That's it?
That's really it?
Right.
It had to be this.
This was the best option.
You said no, why are you so hung up on it?
It's better to be hung up on work
than on a girl like someone.
Where's this coming from?
You mean me?
Do you still stare
at Yu-ri's profile photo?
Didn't I always tell you?
I know.
Women are half of the world population.
I have no objection to that.
Really?
Then how about tonight?
Let's go on a double date
with the models we met at the party.
You said you got over her.
It's not because I'm not over her.
How can I meet someone else
right after a breakup?
It's not good manners to my ex.
You got it wrong.
It's good manners to forget
someone who left you.
I'm so sick and tired of it.
You said you got over her.
Are you a stalker or what?
You got something wrong too.
It's true that women
are half of the world.
But there's only one Yu-ri.
Hey, why is Yu-ri only one?
There's Sung Yu-ri, Lee Yu-ri,
-Yu-ri in Girls' Generation.
-Stop joking.
Sang-jin.
If I call her now, she'd be asleep, right?
Yes, with another man, maybe.
Seriously...
She's not that kind of woman.
Hey, what's that kind?
You guys broke up.
She said that she'd meet someone else.
You didn't stop her. And?
I'm trying to win her back now.
It's too late.
How can you win her back now?
She's probably waiting to hear from me.
The song was played again today.
The song she chose
when she told me she likes me.
So what you mean is
she picked the song in the radio show
to send a message that
she's not over you yet?
Like some kind of spy code?
You're so seriously deluded
that I don't know what to say.
I'm telling you this
because it seems like you'll call her.
I'm sure she has a new boyfriend.
If you'll call her, just know that.
What are you talking about?
Who told you that?
And how do you know?
What is it?
Huh?
Look.
Count. One, two, three, four
five, six, seven.
Look at these fingers in the back.
It's a man's hand around her shoulder.
Don't you know where this is?
It's in Gangneung, where we went
to catch squid.
It's the hottest café there.
And two cups of coffee.
On top of that. Here.
"Heart fluttering."
Okay, forget about everything.
Look at her face.
Her makeup and facial expressions,
all point to her having a boyfriend.
Hold on.
How can these be a man's fingers?
Look carefully. It's a man's fingers.
No. Forget it.
You're talking nonsense.
Okay. All right then.
Yu-ri has seven fingers. Happy?
Hello?
What is it?
A messenger voice call. I answered.
Who's Sang-jin?
Sang-jin?
Hello?
Yu-ri.
I meant to call a different Yu-ri.
So you called the wrong number.
Yeah.
You know, Yu-ri.
I know so many people with the same name.
You haven't changed. I'm doing well.
Okay. Glad to hear that.
How's the publishing business going?
It's going well. Sure.
So sorry to bother you at night.
Good night, and be happy.
I told you.
It's good manners to forget
someone who left you.
Look at her.
She's got great manners, dude.
Sir, I'm sorry,
but please go to Yongsan Forest Town.
Thank you.
When do we meet again?
I'll come again tomorrow.
Really? Okay.
You got something in your hair.
Thanks.
-Call me when you get home.
-Okay.
Head inside.
-Hang on.
-Get home safe.
-You too.
-I'm really going.
-Okay.
-Bye.
Bye.
So how's your sister doing?
Does she eat well?
Yes, she does.
So Mom, don't worry about her.
And visit later on, okay?
She's so carefree.
How can she eat anything
in this situation?
After she got drunk, talked rubbish,
and made such a big scene.
I'm so embarrassed
that I can't hold my head up.
Why's she not getting married
all of a sudden?
There's no one like Ju-wan for her.
Why is she so fickle-minded...
I wouldn't know.
She's driving me crazy.
Hang up.
Where are you going?
Just to get some fresh air.
You want me to go with you?
Why?
Are you worried about me?
I'm such a bad sister, making you worried.
I'm okay now. Don't you worry.
-Okay.
-See you later.
Don't be too late.
Watch out for cars.
Come home early.
Okay.
That makes me more worried.
The sky didn't fall in,
and everything on earth was there.
The world was the same as yesterday.
The only thing that has changed is me.
Every day, you smile at me
Every night, you call me
Trying to be someone else
Who you want
Though it's hard...
ONE DAY, 2 YEARS AGO
You're listening.
I picked this song for you.
You like it, right?
But to me, ballad songs
all sound the same.
The lyrics are nice.
It's something I want to tell you.
What do you want to say?
That I will be waiting for you here
till you come to me,
unless you tell me not to...
Don't.
What?
You don't need to.
Stop waiting for me.
From now on, I will do that.
What's wrong?
Yu-ri, what's wrong? Get up.
You scared me.
Were you scared? I'm sorry.
-Did I scare you a lot?
-Yeah.
All right, I'm sorry.
I was super cool back then.
What the...
Why is she crying like that?
She thinks there's no one outside?
TRUE TO LOVE
You know what always happens
to the key witness, right?
-Why are you crying?
-Smile.
They die. Are you trying to
warn me or something?
-By the way, why do you hate me so much?
-I don't hate you.
I thought we'd be different from
other married couples,
but after getting married,
I realized that we're not any different.
Did my boobs get smaller?
"Dating coach Deborah
failed in her relationship?"
So you can't write books about love?
What would they want to hear about love?
Just be satisfied with seeing my panties.
Why can't you just let it go?
You can't get over disappointment
or your ex.
How can I make you stop?
I hate you. I hate you like crazy.
Let's not see each other again.
Even if you see me crying, falling,
or even hit by a car, just pass me by.
Sure. I will.