TRUE TO LOVE
ALL CHARACTERS, EVENTS, LOCATIONS, AND
INCIDENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS.
-Hello?
-What's wrong with your voice?
Were you crying?
No.
The thing is...
We've really met before
at the wedding.
Now you believe me.
Why did you call me?
Well...
So...
When you feel down or bored at night,
so when you need a free hug,
you can call me anytime.
Have a good night.
I said we're like Mulder and Scully.
He said we're like
DiCaprio and Kate Winslet.
How about a drink at my place?
One thing is clear.
Like Mulder and Scully did,
I don't want to ask him to
donate his sperm to have a baby.
What is that?
Like DiCaprio and Kate Winslet,
I don't want him to escort me
when I marry another man.
Instead, I want to march down the aisle
with him arm-in-arm.
And I had hopes
of falling in love with someone
who, perhaps,
would love me for the way I am.
I had hopes that something like a drama
might happen to me.
PNB PRODUCER JUNG-EUN
You know what?
I want to start over.
In this restructuring process,
the main focus is...
Tune in for Date at Noon today!
I'm back with a new segment.
I'm coming back with "True to Love."
Would you support my new start?
DATE AT NOON
Seriously?
Hello?
I'm going on the air in a bit.
What do I do? I'm so nervous.
Give me some pep talk.
Pray for me so I won't make mistakes.
Oh, right, you're going on the air today.
Don't worry. You'll do great.
You're a genius after all.
No way, did you forget?
You twisted my arm to do this.
Now you hang me out to dry.
Unbelievable.
You sound fine. There's no need to worry.
That's the spirit! You can do it!
-Bo-ra, you're on the air in five minutes.
-Five minutes.
There are flowers for you.
Flowers?
I can do this.
Okay, coming.
Who is it from?
Who is your number one fan?
-Is this for me?
-Yes.
ROOTING FOR YOUR NEW START
FROM DEBORAH'S NO. 1 FAN
He pretended like he forgot.
Where's Yu-ri?
You haven't heard? She quit her job.
Her husband will work abroad,
so she's going with him.
-I'm going in.
-You got this!
Romantic relationships, is it really hard?
You can't be true and sincere
in a romantic relationship?
If you still find love difficult,
tune in for True to Love.
So very nice to
hear her voice again, right?
For us who still find love life difficult,
she came back to Date at Noon.
Formerly known as a dating coach, and now?
I'm not sure how to introduce her now.
Why don't you introduce yourself?
Hi, everyone.
Formerly known as
a dating coach, currently...
I returned as a breakup icon, I'm Deborah.
So good to be back!
Bo-ra, Bo-ra, Deborah!
You have no idea how much I missed you.
Thank you.
Deborah, I'm so glad you're back.
Our listeners have been
really concerned about you
while you were away.
How do you feel to be back?
Could you share with us?
Sure.
They say that you learn from pain.
I didn't believe it, since it seemed like
all there was left was pain.
But I'm sure I learned something
through my breakup.
I was able to discover
parts of myself that I hadn't known.
Of course, it is very difficult
to face parts of myself
that aren't my favorites.
But I realized I needed to
learn to embrace it as myself.
I can therefore say without reservation
that I have grown through love.
When I was struggling,
someone told me this,
"I got dumped, too."
"But consider it as a common cold."
"It's going to be okay soon."
I didn't know at the time,
but in hindsight,
having someone in the same boat
who empathized with me,
and hearing those words
was a huge help to me.
So in the hope of giving
that kind of consolation to someone else,
I mustered the courage
to come back to the show like this.
Come to think of it,
I haven't thanked that person yet.
I'd like to take this chance
to tell the person
that it felt so warm
and I'm very grateful.
Also, if you're currently hurting
because of a breakup,
I want to tell you this.
I've been there.
A breakup, like the common cold,
is not a big deal.
This too shall pass.
You will get well soon.
You can take time to
process those painful feelings.
Right now, messages
of support and congratulations
-are flooding in.
-Right.
First off, 8854.
"What a pleasant surprise
to hear this sweet voice."
"Deborah, I've been waiting
so long to hear your voice."
Thank you, 8854.
And this is from 0501,
"You got over the cold, right?"
"Deborah, let's not be sick again."
Let us all stay healthy, everyone.
And from 9737.
"I can't believe
you became a breakup icon."
"Still, thank you for coming back."
Thank you for waiting for me.
Okay.
There's someone who sent us a short story.
From one of our listeners
with phone number ending 6958.
"Hi, I'm a longtime fan of Deborah."
"Like Deborah,
I recently broke up with my girlfriend."
It's a male listener.
"I had a difficult time
after breaking up with my girlfriend."
"Until we broke up,
I did not know how much I love her
and how much she means to me."
"So I'm going to be courageous
and start over."
"I need your support, Deborah."
-That was the story.
-Right.
We will have a live phone call
with this listener right now.
Why don't you answer the phone, Deborah?
Hello, listener 6958.
Hello, Deborah.
It's so good to hear your voice again.
Hello?
Okay, well...
Listener 6958.
You said you want to
get back together with your ex-girlfriend.
Did you tell her your feelings then?
No.
I'm on my way to tell her now.
No, don't come...
I mean, don't go.
Because...
you don't know how she feels now.
She might have moved on already. So...
That might be the case.
Still,
there should be a way to win her over.
I believe you can give me some answer.
No.
There is no answer.
There cannot be an answer,
don't you think?
Like you can't turn back time. So...
What you can turn back right now
is your car that you're driving.
I know I can't get everything
back to normal.
That was so painful,
so I looked back at
the time we spent together.
When we were so happy together
and loving each other so dearly.
That is something that does not change.
I decided to have faith in that time.
I assume that Deborah
is speaking out of concern for you.
Because telling an ex
your feelings in a rush
is not likely
to work in your favor, right?
Are you still going to push for it?
There's this quote.
"When something is important enough,
even if the odds are not in your favor,
you do it."
That's right. Elon Musk said that.
I cannot calculate
the timing or probability.
Because I realized
what is really important.
I won't give up easily.
-It's him, right?
-I think so.
He quoted Elon Musk.
Has he lost his mind?
What's going on?
If your ex-girlfriend
finds out how sincere you are,
I'm confident that she will
surely change her mind.
I think letting her hear this could help.
-Right?
-Well, maybe.
We wish you the best of luck.
Last but not least, this listener
asked Deborah for some words of support.
Why don't you wish him luck?
Okay.
I wish you good luck.
Now, after a song,
we'll be back with more stories.
You still look tense.
Yes, a little...
That's okay. Take it easy.
Go crazy.
What is all this about out of the blue?
Bo-ra, let's...
start over.
I want to get back together with you.
I could have turned him down right away.
No, I could have avoided him
in the first place.
But how can I explain this moment
when I cannot do that?
The gravity that held our relationship
was already long gone.
But there remains the force of momentum.
I can't stop right away after running.
I can't stop right away after loving.
EP 13
IT'S ALL ABOUT TIMING, TAKE COURAGE FIRST
Did you like the flowers?
Yeah...
Is this from you?
Of course.
Who is Deborah's number one fan
besides me?
I special-ordered pretty purple flowers.
Of course, the prettiest purple
is light purple, Yeon Bo-ra.
As it's the same as your name.
Ju-wan.
What you told me...
I kept thinking about it.
You asked me if I wanted to
be the good guy until the end.
You're right.
I always wanted to look like the good guy
and be a good person.
Because I wanted to be
the perfect boyfriend for you.
I acted like I was a decent person.
Even though I knew I wasn't.
Back then, I was just venting my anger.
Don't let it bother you.
No.
It was hard to apologize.
It was scary to own up to my faults.
So I avoided it.
I'm nothing special.
I'm just a selfish and insecure person.
I felt like I shouldn't be
such a person in front of you.
I pretended like I wasn't.
I tried not to show it.
Maybe I was tired of that.
We all are.
No one is perfect after all.
You were.
You were a perfect woman for me at least.
That's because...
I pretended like I was as well.
I told you that you don't know me well.
Right.
I thought I knew you well.
But these days,
you look like a different person.
I guess I didn't know you.
That's why
I want you to give me a chance
to get to know you better.
I need to know at least
what kind of woman I loved
and broke up with.
By the way, are you sure?
They're seeing each other?
But they barely talk to each other.
That's just a cover.
They suddenly became awkward,
not even saying hi.
That's more suspicious.
Yeah, I showed you the note.
"With love."
They even have pet names for each other.
They watched a movie alone.
Hello, thanks for calling
Jinlee Publishing.
Right, Chun-woo said
he saw them having coffee alone that day.
I'm not surprised.
She got hired through connections.
They had coffee and lunch alone.
It was obvious.
Thank you.
-U-ri.
-Yes?
-Are you going to Sang-jin's office?
-Yes, do you need anything?
No, never mind.
Did you hear that?
The designer called
and wanted your confirmation
on the revised draft
and wanted you to send
emails to this address.
-Okay, thank you.
-Sure.
Sang-jin.
Hey.
You didn't hear the broadcast
since you were outside, right?
I was worried about hate comments.
But the reactions are great.
Now, we don't need to worry
about publicity.
That Deborah. "Deborah, breakup icon."
She straight up went head-on into it.
She's good.
That's great.
You know what's more amazing?
I've got quite a hunch
in the dating department.
I'm quite extraordinary.
She had a live phone call
with a listener who's called 6958.
From the story, I came to think
that there was something going on here.
So I looked it up.
The last digits of
Deborah's phone number is also 6958.
Deborah's ex-boyfriend
wants to get back together.
He said that on a live radio show.
If this goes well,
it's perfect for book publicity later.
Perfect storytelling marketing.
That's just an assumption.
And if he confesses his love,
is it guaranteed to work?
It wasn't just a confession of love.
A wholehearted confession
of a man who has surrendered to love.
It was almost like a drama.
The male lead regrets,
comes to his senses,
confesses his love on a live show
and they get back together.
It's so romantic.
What kind of woman
wouldn't be swayed by that?
It even made my heart flutter.
So when is your meeting with Deborah?
What?
Oh, tomorrow.
Tomorrow.
Then we'll find out everything tomorrow.
Get a bouquet of flowers tomorrow
before the meeting.
I should have sent one
on behalf of the company.
I was so swamped that it slipped my mind.
Come on, man.
When I'm busy,
you should have sent her one already.
You're so clueless...
What did I do wrong?
We can give her one tomorrow.
Not even a call.
-Yes.
-Did you get home all right?
You must be tired.
Why don't we have lunch tomorrow?
As friends. Lunch wouldn't hurt.
I'm afraid I can't. I have work.
You're making an excuse
to reject me, aren't you?
I'm not used to this, so I'm confused.
I am rejecting your offer,
but I really have work.
All right, then let's have
dinner together.
If you're going to reject this too,
do it in person.
Bye.
Excuse me.
-I'd like to order.
-Bo-ra.
Have French toast
with strawberries on top.
Get another one for me along with yours.
Get another one for me, too.
Get them one.
Look at the way you do business here.
Fine, you two can enjoy that.
And I'll have two Americanos, please.
Why two?
You have company today?
-Hello.
-Hi.
Did you listen to the broadcast yesterday?
I guess you couldn't because of work.
It would have been nice if you did.
I did.
You thanked someone.
It was touching.
If it was touching, you should have
let me know that you'd heard it.
I waited.
Then did you hear that part, too?
The live phone call?
Yes.
So did you talk with him?
He came to the broadcasting station,
so we briefly talked.
So...
I talked with him all right.
Welcome...
Bo-mi.
I heard you work here.
How have you been? It's been a while.
-What's up?
-Hey.
Come on.
You won't even talk to me?
You've become more beautiful, Bo-mi.
Why didn't you call me?
I missed you.
You've become prettier
since I saw you last.
How can you be so pretty?
Gifts from my ex-boyfriend.
Selling at a real bargain.
You said you're selling this
at a bargain after a breakup.
Come on, say something to me.
I can't stand this pathetic bullshit.
If you broke up, that's it.
Being desperate and clingy.
Shame on you!
What's the matter?
You'd better give up.
It's too late.
Nothing's going to change anyway.
Who are you, and why are you saying this?
Forget it. Stop. It's okay.
Don't you get it?
I'm the current boyfriend
of your ex-girlfriend
whom you can't possibly get over!
No way. You must be joking.
No, Jin-ho. Don't.
That's not it. Okay?
Jealous much?
Bo-mi is perfectly happy with me.
So can you just get lost?
Stop it.
He's my sister's ex-boyfriend.
What?
All right, seems like
it's time to be upfront about it.
I know you're all wondering
what is happening.
Here's the thing.
I've been going out with him.
Happy now?
I'm sorry for keeping you in the dark.
It was hard to keep it a secret.
Now that we're open about it,
it's a load off my chest.
We'll be a good couple.
I look forward to your support.
Sure.
Jin-woo, give me a coffee.
-Iced?
-Yes.
Why didn't you tell me
you had a meeting here?
I said I'd pick you up.
What...
What are you doing now?
I'm here to see you. Jin-woo as well.
Hello.
We did shake hands before.
We haven't been properly introduced.
I'm Noh Ju-wan.
I'm Lee Su-hyeok.
You didn't grab my hand tightly today.
I heard from Bo-ra
that you became close through work.
When I heard what you said that day,
I thought you were dating.
I was really on guard.
It was just a wrong impression.
It was just you being
passionate about your work.
I reserved a restaurant for our dinner.
You'll be surprised if you know where.
It's the place where we used to go.
You wanted to sit on the terrace
when it's nice outside.
We were in the middle of a conversation.
You need to talk more about work.
I'll let you two talk first.
I need to call someone anyway.
You should go.
I'm busy right now.
-What?
-I said go.
Okay. Got it.
I'll talk with Jin-woo.
Let's go when you're done.
Why did you come?
What do you mean? Shouldn't I come here?
So,
are you trying to get back with Bo-ra?
Well...
You look busy.
By the way, do you always
do your work in this manner?
What manner is that?
I understand that it's common in Korea
to mix business with pleasure.
But that usually leads to
unnecessary waste of emotions
as well as avoidable mistakes.
You're not getting to the point yet.
You're really beating around the bush.
I'm getting there.
Do you...
have feelings for Bo-ra?
I don't think I need to
answer that question.
Right?
Does an ex-boyfriend
have the right to do this?
I don't have the right for the moment.
If you heard the broadcast,
you must be aware.
I will get back together with Bo-ra.
That is why I asked you.
Fortunately, you didn't
give me any answer.
If you said you had feelings for her,
I was going to tell you not to.
I was going to beg or persuade you.
Don't look at me like I'm a loser.
If I can start over with her,
I'm willing to become a bigger loser.
See? I was going to keep you in check
and make you give her up.
But now I'm just begging you
to stop swaying her.
So you acknowledge that she's been swayed?
You know already.
When someone goes through a breakup
they can be swayed for a bit
by someone who comforted them.
But taking advantage of that vulnerability
is clearly not fair play.
When we get back together
and get married as we planned,
Bo-ra...
will have a hard time because of the fact
that she was swayed for a moment.
I know that so well.
That's why I'm telling you this.
First of all, I'm so sorry.
I know it could be very misleading.
Please let me explain.
I didn't get back with him at all.
He just wanted to be friends.
And...
I didn't plan to meet him here...
No, there's no need.
What?
You don't need to explain
everything to me.
I wasn't going to pry into
your love life, that's your privacy.
I was just wondering
if there needs to be any changes
to what we discussed
during the meeting last time.
I was just asking for your confirmation.
I see...
Now it seems like
we do need to make some changes.
Let's wrap up the meeting today.
I...
I'm afraid I'm interrupting your date.
Let's talk in the meeting.
This is for you on behalf of our company,
though it's a day late.
I congratulate you on starting over.
Your radio show and relationship.
Are you done?
Take care.
We have a lot of time left
till our dinner reservation.
What should we do?
Do we have enough time for a movie?
-What are you doing? It's so childish.
-What?
You really don't know?
I was having a meeting.
How could you interrupt that?
Well, I just...
Since I'm acquainted with him,
I didn't want to act like a stranger,
so I said hi.
-It made you uncomfortable.
-I know you did that on purpose
to mislead him about our relationship.
What's there to mislead?
You said he's just a close colleague.
Isn't he?
Or... do you have feelings for him?
What?
If you can't answer, never mind.
He couldn't answer
the same question either.
If you can't too,
there's nothing to worry about, right?
Fine.
Let me reject you in person.
I can't have dinner with you.
Bye.
I swallowed my pride,
and I'm making an effort.
But why now?
You said you hated me.
You were sick and tired of me.
Now that it's over, you feel sad?
Are you jealous I'd see someone else?
Fine. I hated it.
Now that it's over, I can't move on.
The thought of you with someone else
is driving me crazy!
Bo-ra.
Listen to me.
I love you.
But what I can't possibly stand right now
is the fact that you're swayed
by a guy who doesn't even like you.
We should have just
gotten married back then.
What on earth are you talking about?
Like you said, I don't know you well,
but I do know one thing.
You're not emotional enough
to be swayed by a guy
who gives you such little assurance.
Am I wrong?
It's true, Bo-ra.
If you do this, we can't even be friends.
I didn't want that in the first place.
How can we be friends?
Should I say it again?
I love you.
How can we possibly become friends?
Hey.
How did it go with Deborah?
Do they seem to be back together?
Yeah.
That's amazing.
All right. This is more like it!
Do you hear that sound?
The sound of printing
1st, 2nd, 3rd editions, right?
What's with all this?
Aren't we supposed to go for
an open ending, not a reunion?
Things are different now.
I didn't like an open ending
from the beginning.
Nothing beats a happy ending.
You call this a happy ending?
An ending like that?
Is it all a happy ending
if the book sells well?
That's not what I meant.
It's what the writer wanted.
What did she want the most from day one?
She wanted to get her ex back.
Also, how many couples do not
go through a breakup before marriage?
They must have learned something from it.
And they get back together stronger
after staying apart.
Indeed, it is a happy ending.
So we have to change
the publishing plan for Deborah's book?
You heard him.
I made all the marketing plans
with the current concept.
Then what was that meeting for
in the first place?
There's nothing we can do.
It is what it is.
He insisted that he's not a geezer.
But why is he acting like one?
By the way, U-ri.
What do you think?
Pardon? About what?
Why do you even ask?
She should be on her boyfriend's side.
What? Boyfriend?
U-ri. We all know about you two.
You're dating him, right?
You could just tell us.
What's the big deal?
Me and Sang-jin?
Yes.
No.
Come on. I wasn't going to
bring it up, but to be honest,
you got hired by pulling strings.
Everyone here knows that.
That's true.
No, what I mean is...
By the way, are you okay with it?
You know Sang-jin got divorced.
It should be okay.
He's from a very wealthy family.
A building owner.
A born-with-a-silver-spoon president.
U-ri, you must've watched too many dramas.
Or is it more like Cinderella?
It's nothing like that.
It's a misunderstanding.
I won't force you to answer,
but U-ri, please make one thing clear.
You won't become full-time
before Hyun-seok, right?
How would I know that?
No way. Is it all arranged already?
Then, is it all right to do this?
Shouldn't we get on her good side?
It's really nothing like that.
It's not.
In that case,
is Sang-jin hitting on you
using the job
or your full-time employment?
No.
-Sounds true.
-You can tell us if that's the case.
Do tell us. It's really okay.
No.
That's what the employees said?
And U-ri couldn't say a thing?
Sang-jin.
You know you always say that
you do what can be criticized for,
but never do what you'd be ashamed of.
It's not that, right?
You didn't do something
you'd be ashamed of, right?
Right.
If they hear
the president kept hitting on her,
they wouldn't blame the female employee
for flirting with him anymore.
Okay, let's go with that.
Where is that coming from?
How is that a solution?
What should I do then?
She just started her career.
Should I let her take all the heat?
Let's call it a day.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
You see...
There's something I need to tell you.
It was just me.
I had a crush on Mr. Sang-jin.
I got dumped even before saying
how I feel about him.
I don't think that is wrong.
Because you don't need to be qualified
to like someone.
But now I come to think
that I'm probably not qualified.
Also, I didn't know Sang-jin was rich.
I really had no idea.
Though I think that'd make no difference
to the way I feel about him.
That is not why I had feelings for him.
Other than that,
there were so many things
I liked about him.
As for myself,
I prefer books to dramas.
That's why I got a job at this company.
My favorite books are
Anne of Green Gables, Daddy-Long-Legs,
not Cinderella.
Let me keep this short.
I need to straighten something out
as vice president.
At Jinlee Publishing,
as you know, we've hired office assistance
and management support positions
year-round.
That said, in the process of hiring U-ri,
there were no
procedural issues whatsoever.
As for switching to full-time,
the decision will be made
solely upon performance reviews.
In addition, office gossip
and unsubstantiated hearsay
about your co-worker
is clearly workplace bullying.
Last but not least,
as for confessions and apologies,
when you think it's late, it's too late.
That's all.
Enjoy the rest of your day, everyone.
See you tomorrow.
-See you tomorrow.
-Bye.
Let's go, Sang-jin.
He does all the cool stuff.
Bye.
U-ri.
Sorry. I'm so sorry
that I can't find the right words.
I thought you were dating.
We were upset
since we thought you lied to us.
It's just how we felt.
Anyway, there's no excuse for it.
We were so wrong.
It's about time for me
to get a chance to be full-time.
I was over-sensitive. I'm so sorry.
You don't need to accept my apology now.
No, apology accepted.
I'm sorry, and thank you.
Shall we have a beer together?
-It's on me.
-No, we got a company card.
-Let's go together, U-ri.
-I'll pack my stuff then.
You have a stomachache?
Isn't it indigestion?
I don't know.
It kind of feels like indigestion.
Maybe I ate too much today.
Right.
You had French toast,
waffles, strawberries and a lot of cakes.
You could win an eating competition.
SANITARY PADS
What should we buy?
Cola? Sparkling water?
Or digestive medicine?
Where's a pregnancy test?
We have three minutes to think.
Let's think what we should do
if it's two lines.
What do you mean? Of course we...
Not of course.
Whether to give birth or not,
whether to raise a baby by myself
or together, we should make a choice.
I made my decision.
Let's get married.
Don't be impulsive. Think.
I will think about it, too.
You do the thinking. I'm done.
I want to marry you anyway.
If it's sooner,
it's all the better for me.
Because we'd be able to
be together longer.
I can't believe I'm becoming a daddy.
I feel like I'm on top of the world.
I mean it.
Awesome!
What's wrong?
You hesitated.
You hesitated. You just did.
No, I'm really thrilled.
I feel like I could fly now.
When you are extremely happy,
you could go numb all of a sudden.
I mean it!
Believe me.
So did you make a decision?
I don't know.
I shouldn't have a belly bump
in my wedding dress.
I'm so happy!
Are you hungry again?
Yes.
But I'm not the one who's hungry.
I shouldn't let our baby feel hungry.
Wait up.
Honey, guess what...
No.
Why are you saying no?
You don't know what.
Whatever it is, it's a no.
Well, the thing is,
you know Sang-cheol, he...
I said no!
You didn't even hear me out.
Can't let me finish my sentence?
I'm saying no to a caravan.
What, Sang-cheol told you
to buy it from him?
-That it's a steal?
-Yes.
Do you know why?
Because his wife
told him she'll divorce him
if he doesn't sell it,
because she's had enough.
If you bring it here,
do you think I'd say nothing?
You're unbelievable.
Games, cameras, figurines, golf,
fishing, and now it's camping?
-Well, still...
-No.
-I said no.
It's a no-no.
Okay, I won't. Enough.
No to everything...
You heard me.
Where's my phone?
Out of the way. Aren't you sitting on it?
I don't know. Look carefully.
Is it downstairs?
-Call me!
-Okay.
Found it!
Yu-jeong.
So you've been
letting Jin-ho stay downstairs all along?
You could have told me so, why...
Why?
Why couldn't you tell me?
He needed to crash for a short time
till he got a place.
So I just didn't tell you.
-Right?
-Yes.
But finding a place is taking
longer than I thought.
Lead the way.
-To where?
-You know where.
-But...
-Lead the way.
-Privacy...
-Hurry up.
What is this?
Oh, my gosh...
What is all this?
I don't know.
What is all this? I have no clue.
Jin-ho. It's all yours, right?
Yes.
Seriously, cut it out.
When are you going to stop lying?
What else did you lie about?
You could just say you two are dating.
Is there more that I don't know about?
Did you hide a girl in here?
Bo-mi.
-What is it?
-Are you okay?
You must be scared.
Is our baby okay?
It's okay.
Are you pregnant?
I can't believe this.
BO-RA
No.
Don't pick it up. Please. I'm begging you.
Let go.
No. She's really going to kill me.
This isn't right. Let go.
Let go.
Don't tell her, or I will throw this.
I can really throw it. I will.
No!
Honey, put down your phone.
It's really expensive.
Please, Yu-jeong.
-I'm going to throw it.
-No!
All right.
I'll talk to her briefly and hang up.
So that she won't call again.
Sounds good?
Then give me the phone
and talk on the speakerphone.
Give it.
Hey.
Hey, I shouldn't be asking a married woman
to come out this late at night, right?
Why? You need a drink?
Bo-ra. Hurry here! Bo-mi's pregnant!
What did she say?
"Bo-ra, hurry here."
"Bo-mi's fragrant?"
What did she say?
So...
you're saying...
she's pregnant?
Come on out.
No, I won't go.
If not, what are you going to do here?
Come with me.
Bo-ra...
-Come.
-What's the matter with you?
Why are you acting like
I did something wrong?
You...
Hey, go and talk to her at home.
You should go with her.
Hey.
Stay here.
Hey...
How shocking.
What was all that?
Why are you following me up?
Go play downstairs like you do.
Come on.
You want me to go?
I just played video games
and watched soccer sometimes.
I'm sorry.
Did I complain?
Why do you lie to me?
You keep lying to me.
What lie?
All right.
I'll stop everything. That'll do, right?
"That'll do"?
How am I supposed to believe you now?
If you needed alone time so badly
that you had to lie,
why did you even marry me?
Right, because I asked you to.
You didn't even propose to me.
You married me
just because I asked you, right?
That's why you're doing this.
Until when are you going to
talk about the proposal?
Do you love me?
Do you even love me?
You said you won't believe me.
That's right.
I can't believe you anymore. I won't.
Because you've lost my trust.
Where's the man that I wanted to marry?
The man who put his phone in a waterproof
pack not to miss my call while showering.
The man who let the last bus leave
and stayed all night together
and was still sad to say bye.
The man who used to do a video call
24 hours 'cause you missed me
when I was studying abroad.
That's the man I married.
But now, you're just...
You're just a selfish,
emotionally detached guy.
Hey. Yang Jin-woo.
You've really changed.
Are you aware of that?
Yes, so have you.
-What?
-You think you haven't changed?
You always complain about whatever I say.
You hate whatever I do.
You say no to everything.
That is why I can't say anything.
Why would I? You won't listen anyway.
Did I? When? About what?
Am I wrong? "Stop playing games."
"Biking is dangerous."
Fishing? You hate everything!
"Golf? A guy like you?"
"Don't you dare invest in stocks."
"I'll divorce you
if you buy cryptocurrency."
Then what can I ever do?
All I should do is work?
Work, home, work, home,
no time for myself?
I need alone time.
Just a little bit of alone time,
I just need a little bit.
What did I do so wrong?
Then what about us?
What? What about us?
Do we ever spend time together?
Jin-woo.
In the morning, we are in a rush
and busy all day at work.
In the evening, after dinner and
cleaning up, we just pass out.
But you complain
you don't have alone time for yourself.
You're not bothered about
not having time with me?
I guess you aren't. I am.
If you put it that way...
Well, we will be together
for the rest of our lives, so...
Is that so?
That's what you think.
So you lie to me
'cause I'd give you an earful,
you don't do it with me
'cause you could some other time.
We'll be together for life,
so you can put off spending time with me.
I'm your lowest priority.
I see that's what you think.
By the way,
who said we'll be together for life?
What's that supposed to mean?
I just wonder
if living together for life like this
is really meaningful.
That crossed my mind.
How can you...
I'll sleep somewhere else. Okay?
Let me crash here tonight.
I'm sorry, Jin-woo. It's all my fault.
You should have told me.
You lied and made things get out of hand.
Turn off the light.
-Good night.
-You, too.
Hello, Ms. Yeon.
-Hi, U-ri.
-Let me take you to the conference room.
Mr. Han. Ms. Yeon is here.
Okay.
U-ri.
Yes?
Well... Are you all right?
Pardon? Why?
No, I was just...
I was worried about you.
Did you talk it out with your co-workers?
I hope you don't feel
uncomfortable around me.
They apologized to me
and we cleared up the misunderstandings.
And I'm all right.
I owe you an apology.
I shouldn't have made you uncomfortable
by expressing my feelings.
But you don't have to worry about it.
It will never happen again.
I got over you now.
And I'm cool.
Well, then.
Let's start the meeting in ten minutes.
I have something
to discuss with her first.
-Okay.
When can I expect to receive a draft?
By now, I need a specific timeline.
But you won't share your draft,
it's hard to get things moving.
I only have the ending part left.
I need some time to mull over it.
So you aren't sure about the deadline.
Is that what you mean?
Yes.
When a writer can't decide an ending,
in most of the cases,
it's because the ending doesn't
seem convincing to readers.
If it's not convincing to yourself,
how are you supposed to
convince the readers?
You got out of a beat-up car,
but you bother to repair and
get back in it, such a happy ending...
It is not a very convincing ending.
It is easy to criticize destructively.
How should I change the ending?
I got out of the beat-up car,
and get hit by an even more beat-up car?
Or I sold a beat-up car
and got a Mercedes.
Turns out it was salvaged?
I got totally screwed? Fooled? Scammed?
It's way better than that.
"An even more beat-up car"?
"Salvaged car"?
Why? You thought you were a Mercedes?
So, you'll show only the left side
of your face which you like,
eat naengmyeon that you don't like,
acting like you love it,
acting like you're happy
to become a princess of "Chicken Land,"
is that the ending you really want?
You called yourself genius.
You apparently aren't.
You said you follow your instincts.
You're dishonest,
not just with others, but with yourself.
Or you don't know what you want.
Do you want to say I'm pathetic?
Do you want to insult me
by saying I'm shallow?
But do you know what's really pathetic?
When I heard someone didn't hate me,
I thought, "Does it mean he likes me?"
Having that self-delusion,
not knowing that was just false hope.
Who are you talking about?
When you were good to me,
you were just being kind and nice.
When you gave me a hug, it was a free hug.
When you kissed me, it was... a mistake?
When you expressed your feelings about me,
it was an act. Right?
Who is the dishonest one here?
Was I the only one in that kiss?
Didn't we agree that
it was mutual and simultaneous?
And who said it was a mistake first?
Then why did you
invite me over to your place?
Don't you know what that implies?
You were feeling me out
to see if I'd say yes.
I didn't feel you out!
If not, what was it then?
You won't swallow your pride.
You can't do what embarrasses you.
Not in a million years.
You know what?
I don't have a clue
what's in that incredible heart of yours,
but if you can't verbalize your feelings,
don't show them in the first place.
Because it only makes
the one who's misled a fool.
TRUE TO LOVE
Didn't I tell you I won't do it?
I said I wasn't up for Deborah
from the start.
Hello? Is this "Kiddo?"
-What?
-Don't get back with him.
You won't remember anything anyway,
'cause you're drunk.
Because you love him, you marry him,
you're pregnant, so you have a baby,
you'll just live like that?
You think I'm pathetic, right?
Jin-ho doesn't.
He says I can do it.
Jin-ho, don't tell him I'm here.
Don't you need to go bring Yu-jeong?
I should figure out what to say
after I say I'm sorry.
If I don't get it right at once,
it gets really serious.
I'm sorry I'm always late.
Besides an apology,
don't you have anything to tell me?
I like you a lot, Su-hyeok.
And do you know what it's like now?
Everything is a mess.
Still, you have nothing to tell me?
Thanks for keeping your promise
that you'd let me dump you first.
Bo-ra.
Will you marry me?