[rain pattering]
[video games beeping]
[Mikami] Excuse me.
Did the girl who's always playing
that game show up today?
- I haven't seen her yet today.
- Thank you.
Tominaga always comes here?
This is the only place I could think of.
[players laugh]
- The girl was messed up.
- Was she drunk?
Sure, she was even in her school uniform.
[both laugh]
[rain pattering]
[suspenseful music playing]
You managed to send an SOS.
You did great.
[sighs]
[Tominaga sobs]
Um, my place is nearby.
Let's go there for now.
Tominaga, think you can make it?
Okay, ready, one, two... All right.
[laughing] All three of us
are wearing my clothes...
That's pretty hilarious.
[Tominaga mumbles]
Huh?
Sorry.
[Mikami] If you want to talk, I'll listen.
And if you don't you don't have to.
If it's better to wait, then I'll wait.
You already...
know, don't you, Okami?
I kind of suspected it.
This is about your precious family.
MR. MIKAMI'S CLASSROOM
I knew that your younger brother
has a disability.
He has a congenital condition
with his spine and can't walk.
He also has a mild learning disability.
I also heard your parents
are completely devoted to his care.
What concerned me
was that, despite those circumstances
you were always killing time
at the game arcade.
And yet...
Seeing how positive you always were
I convinced myself that nothing was wrong.
Is Detective Okami's deduction
right, Tominaga?
My brother...
he gets unstable when I'm around.
He has this rule
that he goes into his room
at 8:00 p.m. every night.
So I made sure to come home
after that time.
That's tough.
I still remember...
Ryu-chan...
That's my brother's name.
I remember the day he stopped liking me.
You know those relatives
who mean well but always...
say the wrong things?
One of them told him...
"Your sister's going to
Tokyo University, right?"
[exhales deeply]
"She should've given half
her brains to you, Ryu-chan."
Are you serious?
I got so mad and yelled
"That's not funny!"
But ever since then...
[sniffles]
Ryu-chan hasn't been the same.
Can I ask what happened today?
Lately, Ryu-chan's been really agitated.
I got a call from my mom
saying she couldn't
calm him down by herself.
So, I rushed home.
When I go there,
he really was out of control.
Without thinking, I said...
[sniffles]
"That's enough! Cut it out!"
When I saw Ryu-chan's palm
covered in blood
I thought
"Maybe the only thing
I can do is not be here."
That's what crossed my mind.
[emotional music playing]
[Mikami] I see.
[Tominaga sniffles]
- Thanks for calling me.
- [sobs]
It meant a lot.
[Tominaga] Huh...
Sounds silly, doesn't it?
But having a student
rely on my like that...
makes me really happy.
[knocking on the door]
We're in the middle of something
right now!
[woman] Come on! Open up!
Sorry.
- [gasps]
- You must be starving.
Here, warm yourself up
with something hot.
Thank you.
It's nothing. If anything,
you're the one working late.
Say, Tominaga-chan,
why don't you stay over tonight?
- Huh?
- Tomorrow's Saturday anyway.
I figured I might be meddling, but...
I already called your mom.
Wow, Mom for the win!
She told me a little bit
about what's going on.
So if you're okay with it...
Thank you.
[chuckles] All right then, it's settled!
Here, have some udon!
Most things are manageable
if you eat udon.
[chuckles]
- Thank you for the food!
- Go ahead, enjoy.
Take your time.
Thank you.
[Tokura] I've been worried
this whole time.
For these past four years
I kept thinking something might happen.
[Kanzaki] Tokura...
told me everything.
He hacked into the school system
to get the test questions.
And he got caught.
[thunder rumbles]
It was during a time
when I was struggling mentally
and was completely unable
to keep up with my studies.
So I panicked, and that's why...
Please tell me.
What really happened?
I desperately negotiated
with the school
so Tokura wouldn't be punished.
That's all.
I should've properly
faced the consequences.
But...
there must've been some strings attached.
It's way too suspicious
that he didn't face any consequences.
He had always been a dedicated student.
He was pushed to the edge
because the school failed
to look after his mental well-being.
In other words,
it was my fault, wasn't it?
When you put it like that...
So a deal really was made, wasn't it?
And the real reason
why you left the school...
It wasn't an affair.
It was sexual assault.
[Tokura] I looked up to you.
You always put your students first...
and put yourself last.
But maybe, Ms. Saejima...
there are some things
you shouldn't put off, right?
By protecting me...
you threw everything off balance.
Because of that
your daughter got hurt.
She ended up doing something terrible.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I was...
helping the school cover up...
its wrongdoing.
Wrongdoing?
Rintoku had been accepting
students through illegitimate admissions.
Don't tell me...
Did Mr. Tsutsui find out
and start blackmailing you?
Yes.
Do you have any kind of proof?
No, I don't.
Tokura...
I should be the one apologizing.
I was going in circles all on my own.
I hurt people.
I hurt you.
I hurt my daughter too.
Um...
I will never forget.
I'll never forget that you protected me
with everything you had.
I'll remember it for the rest of my life.
[uplifting music playing]
[footsteps receding]
[sniffles]
[sniffles, exhales deeply]
TO YUZURU MAYAMA
[Tsugimoto] If you think
about slope with tangent
you can solve it easily, right?
[Kanzaki] I see.
You don't have to force it
into the cosine rule.
[Tominaga] Wait! My synapses are firing!
Oh, and now the brain cells
are connecting with a bang!
What is this? It's like
"Good morning, new world!"
I might be having a good morning too.
- [Tominaga] Yeah!
- [all laugh]
[Tsugimoto] Let's move on
to the next question.
- Try solving this as a challenge.
- [Tominaga] Oh, sounds good!
Hold up. This might not be
a good morning for me.
This is from Mai-chan.
- Here.
- What's this?
[both laugh]
It's adorable. Thanks.
Mai-chan really wanted to come.
- Yeah, I know.
- You really are loved.
I'm not sure about that.
She's mad at me
because I'm useless when it counts.
Tsubuki...
what are you going to do
after the surgery?
Huh? What do you mean?
Are you coming back
to the Ministry of Education?
I can't really think about that right now.
Personally...
Of course, I want you to come back.
Now, with that in mind,
I want you hear me out.
If you're going to quit, now's the time.
That's ridiculous.
Tsubuki...
you're the second one, you know.
[Tsubuki] Yeah, I know.
He collapsed, which lead
to a mental breakdown.
And in the end, he took his own life.
[inhales deeply]
[Makino] I saw the signs.
But having Mikami point it out me...
my pride got the best of me.
[tense music playing]
You're afraid and worried, aren't you?
Yeah.
I'm so scared that I can't sleep.
If you do come back,
I'll support you with everything I've got.
And if you change careers,
I'll help you in any way I can.
Thank you.
But are you...
really in a position
to be worrying about me?
Makino-san, you're looking
pretty terrible right now.
[both chuckle]
I'm fine, really.
[chuckles]
See?
[laughs softly]
[Mazakazu] That looks good.
When you were little and asked for cake,
your mom never let you have any.
- Yeah, it's delicious.
- Yeah.
I was able to talk to Tokui-san.
I heard that the chairman and Tokui-san
were high school classmates.
But he didn't donate,
which seemed suspicious.
Actually, Tokui-san was involved
as an external auditor
when the prep school
was first established.
Really?
Yeah, and even back then, there were
rumors about under-the-table money
so he pulled out.
Tokui-san said maybe Kodai-san
is the kind of person who
ends up deceiving even himself
while spouting his ideals.
Chairman Kodai had this way
of making everyone he meets
believe he is a wonderful educator.
Even I was one of them.
Mom used to worry...
because you were frail and a picky eater.
She would say, "If I let her eat cake,
she won't eat dinner."
Mom was also the one
who connected you to Tokui-san.
Really?
I'm sure your feelings got through to her.
Tominaga...
[in high-pitched voice]
Tominaga, are you okay?
[chuckles] What are you talking about?
Okami's got to be up to something
if he called us out here, right?
Mmm.
I felt better after eating the udon.
So, I'm all good.
Got it.
[Mikami] Sorry you had to come
all the way out here.
- No worries.
- Shall we go?
[Mikami] Mom.
Kota, you came?
I want you to meet some people.
These are my students,
Tominaga and Tsugimoto.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
Mom, can we talk outside for a bit?
Would you mind listening too?
I think it's time I finally deal
with something I've been...
putting off for far too long.
Will you stay with me while I face it?
This place is one
of my mother's favorite places.
[wheelchair brake clanks]
Hey, Mom.
I'm Takashi.
Do you understand?
Takashi.
What are you saying?
You're Kota.
Kota...
he died...
twenty-two years ago.
If it was what you needed, Mom...
if it made you feel better...
I was okay with being Kota.
But...
that was a lie.
Every time...
you called me Kota...
it felt like I couldn't breathe.
[voice breaks]
[inhales deeply] That's how much it hurt.
I knew I had to face it.
That's what I thought.
I am...
Takashi Mikami.
Kota Mikami died.
I'm the one who killed him.
It's not your fault, Mom.
Kota...
my big brother...
made that choice himself.
No.
It was all my fault.
Mom.
I...
I've always lived as if I were living
for both Kota and myself.
It's always...
been that way.
And it always will.
Takashi?
That's right.
I'm Takashi.
[gentle piano music plays]
[sniffles]
[Tominaga] I'm going
to talk with Ryu-chan.
[Mikami] But...
Yes?
...I think probably...
the next time...
I see my mom...
she'll act like nothing happened...
and just call me Kota again.
Your brother...
might not respond
the way you hope he will either.
You understand that, right?
I do.
I know that his feelings
and his words don't always match.
I understand that.
If even we struggle with that...
then it's probably much harder
for Ryu-chan.
But...
today...
I just want to say,
"I love you, Ryu-chan."
[sniffles] I adore him
I love him so much.
But I've never been able to say it.
And that's...
what hurt the most.
[stirring orchestral music playing]
If the next time...
you see her...
she were to call you Kota again...
you'd still be glad you told her,
wouldn't you, Okami?
I would.
Mmm!
[sniffles]
- What the heck, Jigen?
- [both chuckle]
- What the heck, Okami?
- [Mikami laughs].
- I'm good.
- Here you go, Okami.
[music swells]
[Tsugimoto] You know,
it's kind of amazing.
What's this about?
If I'm going to be a prosecutor
I need to learn more
about how different people live.
You'll make a great legal professional.
[chuckles] Huh?
If you don't know love,
it's a job you probably can't do
one that you shouldn't do.
Whoa, you suddenly dumped
a lot of pressure on me.
- I can walk alone from here.
- Oh, okay.
- Good luck.
- I'll do my best.
[chuckles]
[male student 1] Miyazawa, Fuyuki,
did you pass the AO exam?
- [male student 2] Yeah, kind of.
- [male student 3] What about you?
[male student 4] I've changed gears
and am focusing on the Common Test now.
[male student 1] So you didn't pass?
Did something happen?
Wakui's too popular.
I haven't gotten my turn yet.
Guess I have no choice.
You'll have to help me, Okami.
That's no way to ask for help.
Then be as nice as Wakui.
Jeez. So what don't you get?
The inverse image method...
- I've mostly recovered.
- That's good.
Oh, Ms. Koreeda.
Do you also teach classical Chinese?
I do! In fact, I'd be happy to.
Okay, everyone lost in classical Chinese,
gather round Ms. Koreeda!
- Yes!
- Let's go. Let's do it.
- Wanna try something else?
- Yeah.
- Good morning, Tominaga!
- Good morning!
How did it go?
It was pretty emotional.
Oh wow, that's great.
[chuckles]
[Mikami] For the specified X and Y pair
check if a T exists
that meets the condition.
- Good job.
- What?
- Congrats!
- Yay!
The attitude of agreeing
with one's lord...
Wait, hey, listen.
Pointing out mistakes
and correcting them...
- Your handwriting sucks.
- Huh?
- Write properly.
- My handwriting?
Begin.
[paper rustles]
- [school bell chimes]
- Stop.
[Kanzaki] Okami.
Tomorrow, Yuzuru
is meeting with Ms. Saejima.
Are you going to be there?
Yes.
I see.
Let's do a post-test review, Kanzaki!
Uh, okay.
Excuse me.
[male student] Come on.
Thanks to you, I was able
to nail the essay questions.
- [Kanzaki] That's good.
- [chuckles]
[Kodai] About the other day...
I'd like for you
to take over for Mizohata.
and help make Rintoku
an even better school.
Thank you.
I'd like you to meet
with Nakaoka next time.
Of course.
When that time comes,
there's something I'd like to ask of you.
Yes.
I'll be in touch.
- [cell phone buzzes]
- [suspenseful music playing]
Hello, Tsukada speaking.
I spoke with Mikami.
And what did he say?
- [Kodai] He accepted the offer.
- [door beeps]
So you're choosing Mikami.
[Kodai] Yes. Regarding Secretary Azuma,
we hope he'll handle the damage control.
I also got word from Nakaoka
that Makino's no good.
Because of his jealousy
toward Mikami-kun
he's turning into Mizohata. [chuckles]
Anyone without a vision
for education needs to step aside.
Talk to you soon.
[breathes deeply]
[Mikami] It's just as I thought.
If they want to revise
the national budget estimates
they need to act now.
He is trying to win me over.
- It'll get soggy.
- Huh?
[slurping]
If you let ramen this good go soggy...
you'll get bad luck.
I believe Mr. Mizohata
will come around.
When I joined,
he was passionate about education.
But somewhere along the way,
he changed.
Many people have become victims
of Chairman Kodai's ideal of education.
Like baboons.
Baboons pretend to kindly warn
the gazelles of an approaching lion
then once the gazelles
let their guard down
the baboons eat their babies.
Well, to Chairman Kodai, his ideal
of education probably isn't a lie.
After all, there really
is a lion out there.
Yeah, that's true.
And thinking it's better
than being eaten by the lion
he eats the gazelle's children himself.
- Good, isn't it?
- What?
This ramen.
OFF HALF DAY
Makino-san, are you leaving for the day?
Yeah, Tsubuki is having surgery today
and his wife's been in labor
since yesterday.
You're taking half a day off for that?
That's right, I'm taking
half a day off for that.
[door opens]
[footsteps approaching]
[door closes]
Listen...
What is it?
I didn't want to forget
what I wanted to say so I wrote it down.
[paper rustles]
First...
I won't see you anymore.
[Kanzaki] What?
[Mayama] Second...
Mom...
please forget about me.
Third...
I'm the one who killed...
Yusuke Shibutani.
Yuzuru...
[Mayama] Fourth...
it's not your fault.
- Yuzuru, stop.
- Fifth...
I'm really...
sorry.
- Yuzuru, listen...
- [paper rustles]
That's everything.
[Kanzaki] Yuzuru...
I understand.
I really do, but...
This is between me and my mother.
[Kanzaki] Yuzuru, listen.
[melancholy music playing]
Everyone here...
carries some kind of guilt.
A guilt that can't be shared
with anyone else.
That guilt doesn't go away.
Because no matter what we do
Yusuke Shibutani isn't coming back.
But...
I know...
how much it means
for Ms. Saejima to be here.
I...
do know that.
[melancholic music continues]
[Saejima] I understand
what you're trying to say.
I think I understand.
You want to take responsibility
on your own.
Kanzaki-kun and...
Mr. Mikami...
they taught you that, didn't they?
[music swells]
And yet, I thought
if I just sacrificed myself
that would be enough.
I left you all alone.
I told myself it was all for you.
That it was all for my students.
But I never stopped to see
that setting that kind of example...
as a mother and as a teacher
was the worst thing
I could have done.
And I...
pushed you to the edge.
I'll think carefully about what you said.
But please, just one more time...
I want to talk with you.
- [male student 1] Wow...
- [male student 2] What is it?
[male student 3] The results from
the mock exam the other day are out.
[male student 1] Class 3-2
had an unbelievable jump.
[male student 2] Whoa, you're right.
That's amazing.
- [male student 1] It's wild, right?
- [male student 3] Even geography went up.
[male student 1] That's awesome.
[indistinct chatter]
Mr. Mikami, everyone said
their rankings improved.
It looks like your head's
still on your shoulders.
Yeah, I came back from the guillotine.
[students laugh]
All right! Let's get started!
[all laugh]
All right, let's do this!
- Let's give it a shot.
- Yeah.
[indistinct chatter]
This is amazing.
They're talking about studying, right?
Yeah.
- Should we start with math?
- Can we?
I didn't know something
like this was possible.
[male student] Geography?
What about geography?
Geography went up by, let's see...
seven points.
- [indistinct chatter]
- [airy music plays]
Right.
[dramatic music playing]
[Saejima] Thanks again for the other day.
Don't mention it.
If you hadn't been there,
I might've just left there
pretending to be a reasonable adult again.
When you're my age,
even if you want to change
it's not easy.
It's hard for people to change, period.
It's not about age.
Yeah, you're right.
This is the first time you reached out.
Um...
Here.
Huh? What's this?
Aren't you going to look
at what's on here?
Yeah, but Okami said to wait.
They should be here soon.
Huh? Someone's coming?
I don't know who it is either.
[knocking]
[door opens]
Yamato Takeru is here.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
He said you'd know.
What's that about?
Huh?
What?
Wait, seriously?!
Let me introduce you.
This is my colleague
from the Ministry of Education
Kyosuke Makino.
Also known as Yamato Takeru.
Nice to meet you. I'm Makino.
What's going on?
Makino and I are colleagues
and while I've been investigating Rintoku
Makino has been tracking
any movements within the ministry.
So you've been working together
from the start?
Pretty much.
I thought we promised no more secrets?
This really is the last one.
Ugh, you bureaucrats are so irritating!
You must be Tominaga.
Yeah, is there a problem?
I heard you gave Okami
a piece of your mind.
Which means you're the landlord,
right, Jigen?
And you must be Kanzaki.
Nice to meet you.
So much for privacy, huh?
I've been looking forward
to meeting you all.
Let's look at the data.
She gave it all to me,
including the reason...
it couldn't be shared before.
This is?
It's the data I took. All of it.
But you said there wasn't any proof.
There was a reason
I couldn't bring it out.
[suspenseful music playing]
Itsuki Tokura wasn't the only one
you were protecting.
Giving this to you will place
a heavy burden on your shoulders.
But I've chosen to trust you.
I see.
- Hey, Lupin. Let's do this.
- [computer beeps]
- [Lupin in English] Gotcha!
- [in Japanese] The names on this list...
They're probably the reason
she couldn't release it.
[gunfire effect echoes]
So these are the students
who were fraudulently admitted?
There aren't as many as I expected.
Even if it's the top school
in the prefecture, this isn't Tokyo
so it's probably about right.
Huh?
Sis, dinner's ready.
[tense music playing]
Coming.
[Tominaga] Chigira?
[door closes]
PREVIEW OF THE FINAL EPISODE
We can finally expose
the full scope of Rintoku's corruption.
[man 1]
Here's Yamato Takeru's assignment.
Photos, audio data, witnesses...
All of it is there.
[man 2] All the dots have been connected.
[Koreeda] The school took the freedom
away from you.
- [man 3] I am involved too.
- [man 4] It's finally starting.
[man 5] It's a fight for the survival
of Japan's education.
[Mikami] This year was way more difficult
than I ever imagined.
But every time, you all came up
with solutions that defied belief.
[woman] Our students
are leaving this school now.
Congratulations on your graduation.