Coming here to lecture me at this hour?
You hungry?
Starving.
You have one of these too?
What a coincidence.
Mine is white,
and yours is black.
Where'd you get it?
Hei Yan.
I just found out you were the one
who talked Mike into dropping Ko Shasha.
It was just a suggestion.
Are you out of your mind?
Replacing your own labelmate
just to back someone from another agency?
Like I said,
I choose my rivals.
I only shine when the competition is tough.
I didn't want to miss the chance.
Let me tell you,
if you ever go behind my back
to make decisions like that again,
you'd better watch yourself.
You chose your own manager,
and you signed the contract yourself.
You've still got a year and a half.
Just tough it out.
You're so unguarded.
Subconscious reactions don't
change, no matter how long it's been.
Did you also forget
that you once called someone negative
and insecure?