I know.
Don't miss me too much, okay?
Don't worry.
Okay.
Love you.
Bye.
This feels like...
a scene from a music video.
Two people meeting by chance...
after years of being apart.
I heard your voice just now...
and thought I was hearing things.
I thought you'd settled abroad.
What brings you back so suddenly?
I'm back...
...to see you.
Quite the nostalgia trip.
We haven't been in touch for years.
I never expected to run into you here.
I can't tell...
if this is a surprise...
or a total shock.
It's not like I didn't try to reach out.
Save the excuses.
We were friends, after all.
You didn't even tell me you got married.
I'm not married.
"Don't miss me too much"...
...and "Love you"?
Chen Tian-you,
I didn't think you'd still...
talk to people like that.
That was an old lady...
who looked after me overseas.
A local there.
She was always on my case...
about learning to say "I love you."
That's nice.
But what about you?
Are you married?
Has life been treating you well?
Do you have kids?
I'm not married either.
Back then,
you just up and left.
You left me for someone else,
and then went radio silent.
So why didn't you marry him?
He just wasn't the one.
We broke up a long time ago.
I'm still waiting.
Have you found him yet?
I have.
Then don't keep him waiting too long.
I've got a meeting to get to.
Let's catch up soon.