It's not enough.
Still not enough.
Fine, you're impossible.
You're so high-maintenance.
I'm the "Little Prince" of the Bais.
I'm supposed to be difficult.
You really don't regret being with me?
People will say...
you're just after my family's money.
And then,
they'll dig into your past
and say you're a social climber.
Or worse,
fans will come after you
for ruining my reputation.
Will you regret it?
I wouldn't...
dare.
Is it that you don't dare,
or that you just won't?
This necklace...
Why does it look so familiar?
Stop hanging every necklace
you find around my neck.
I'm not a pet, you know.
True.
Even a pet would be more grateful.
How am I ungrateful?
You designed this. Forgot?
I did?
Wow, I'm talented.
After the entrance exams,
you asked what I wanted,
so I had you draw a wing for me.
Why did I only draw one wing?
Because the other one is yours.
That way,
I'll never be able to leave you.
Was I really
that calculating back then?
But tell me,
back then,
did you actually like me?
You already know.
I want to hear you say it.
If you had confessed
to me back then,
I wonder if I would've said yes.
But at that point,
we hadn't even met in person.
If you like someone,
just
go for it.