Blimey!
Oh my goodness!
Cheers, mates! We are BTS TS!
Welcome to B TS WORLD TOUR
LOVE YOURSELF, SPEAK YOURSELF here
in London,
Wembley Stadium!
My name is RM.
Nice to meet you guys.
What's up, Wembley!
Make some noise!
I'm your hope!
You're my hope!
-I'm -
- hope!
Thank you.
Hi, guys!
Hi, London!
Nice to meet you. My name is V.
Let's have fun tonight.
Hi, guys!
I'm SUGAR.
Nice to meet you guys.
Hello, my name is Jin.
UK!
Hi, guys! My name is Jung Kook.
Nice to meet you guys!
Wembley!
Make some noise!
Hi, I'm Jilin.
We're finally having
a stadium tour here in Wembley!
Hey, Wembley!
Can you hear me?
In this big stadium
with ARMY,
it feels like a dream!
A dream!
Hey, guys!
Look at this!
The Wembley Stadium!
You made this, ARMY.
We purple you.
Thank you so much for your support
and the love on our new album
"MAP OF THE SOUL: PERSONA"!
It's all because of you, ARMY.
You're our wings!
It feels like we're flying here.
London, thank you!
Is you ready to fly with us, ARMY?
Is you ready?
Okay, let's spread your wings.
Let's get it!
Let's fly!
Sing with us!
Put your hands up to the sky!
Put your hands in the air!
Everybody, let's clap!
Put your hands to the sky!
If you're ready to fly!
If you're feeling the vibe!
Yo, ]
Let's do it.
Everybody, sing with us.
Okay, Wembley.
Are you guys having fun?
Come on, UK.
Show me how's your voice.
Show me how you speak your voice!
Yo, ]
Let's get it.
Everybody, make some noise!
Make some noise!
Welcome, Wembley!
Sing with us!
I want more.
Louder!
Thank you, Wembley!
Let's go!
That's right!
Thank you!
Sing it!
We love you!
Is you ready for the big "Love"?
You know what you gotta say! Say!
Let's go, left side!
Okay, right side!
At the front!
Hey, left side!
Right side!
Okay, at the Bar!
I just want to spread this.
I just want to give you this.
Wembley, make some noise!
(Watch on www.kisskh.la or www.kisskh.co to support Admin)
Wow!
- Surprise!
- Beautiful!
- Wow, beautiful!
- Beautiful scene!
Surprise!
Wembley, how was it?
You like it?
Hey, ARMY!
You know what? Some of the B TS members
came from Hogwarts.
Hogwarts!
Hogwarts?
J, come on!
Okay, I'm ready.
Stupefy!
J!
Not that one!
We shall show ARMY a better one.
A better one?
Let's get it.
You ready, Jilin?
I'm ready.
Let's go!
Lu mos Lu mos!
Whoa, Jilin!
Very nice!
I've got another spell.
Another spell?
I want it.
I'm ready.
ARMY, are you ready?
Okay.
Firestorm!
One more time.
So cool!
Harry Potter!
Shut up!
Shut up, Malfoy!
- Okay, guys.
- Shut up!
- I'm Harry Potter!
The last spell.
This spell will make you
happy and fun, ARMY.
- Okay.
- Let's go, V!
You ready?
Purple Love!
ARMY magic!
Professor?
- Yes.
- The spell works!
Satisfied.
You did it.
Okay.
Professor SUGAR?
You got something to say?
ARMY, are you ready
to have more fun?
No, no, no.
Have more fun?
One more time!
Make some noise!
- Let's get it! Let's go!
- Let's get it! Go get it!
Let's go!
ARMY, make some noise!
We won't keep it down.
Okay.
Everybody, sing along to this song.
We are "IDOL"!
Go get it!
Make some noise!
This is the last song for tonight.
Let's drop it.