This series is created for entertainment purposes only.
Characters, places and events in this story are all fictional.
It's not related or referring to any event or any individual's behaviour.
Please use your viewing judgment.
♫ Just you coming here makes my heart melt ♫
♫ It melts, melts that I want to swallow you whole ♫
♫ You didn't come with anyone else, right? ♫
♫ What do you like? ♫
♫ Tell me and I'll find some or you ♫
♫ I’m not rich like others ♫
♫ I don't have what others do ♫
♫ I just wanna say that a guy
like me only have true love ♫
♫ I will never abandon you ♫
♫ Nor make you sit in sadness ♫
♫ Even though I’m not handsome,
my heart is sincere ♫
♫ I will give all my heart to you ♫
♫ In my life right now, I only have you ♫
♫ please don’t leave me aside
and pulverize my heart ♫
Let's hurry up.
How are you?
P'....
I'm sorry.
It's all right
It's not your fault.
I've very
serious about it all the time.
Why does it
have to be this way?
What did Dad say?
Dad didn't say anything.
Don't think too much.
Dad will come visit tomorrow.
Seriously...
I think it's a coincidence.
We don't even know who hit him.
I think it was an accident.
I don't think so.
What are you guys talking about?
IG, do you know this guy?
Ai'Kui and I...
went to investigate...
and Ai'Choi,
a scallion chicken rice seller...
is the perpetrator.
Dad.
The police caught the
guy who hit-and-run Ruk.
The rider confessed
that he was hired by...
Tunwa.
Tunwa?
Tunwa probably on the run now.
That damn Tunwa.
How could you this to my son?!
Sawasdee krub, Uncle.
Why are you here?
Please let me visit him.
Give IG a chance, Dad.
At least, IG?
is better than Tunwa.
Please, Uncle.
Yeah, go ahead.
Thank you.
In that case...
please excuse me
to go to the police station.
Are you OK?
I can't play soccer anymore.
Listen to me.
No matter how you feel...
you may feel sad...
you may feel angry.
Maybe you feel
the world is unfair to you.
I want you to know...
I will be by your side forever.
Don't be afraid.
I am here.
I will not leave you.
I will be here.
Ruk.
Sawasdee krub, Uncle.
IG...
have a sit and talk to me.
IG.
If I directly from Ruk,
he probably won't tell me.
I'm gonna ask you straight.
What is your relationship with Ruk?
We..
We are dating
At first..
I thought...
if I hear a response like this...
I would be very mad.
But no.
When I hear this kind of response...
I feel so much relieved.
Relieved?
Yes.
You and Ruk...
love each other...
it makes me feel happy.
Most importantly...
it makes Ruk, my son...
smile.
I'm old now.
and I still have many things to learn.
Look at Tunwa, for example.
I trusted and known him for 10 years.
and he can still do this thing to me.
This is what called know from
the outside but not on the inside.
I have to stop judging people from outside.
IG.
For all these while...
I'm so sorry...
for not trying to understand you two.
There are no,
certainty in this world.
Especially love.
Thank you so much to you..
for my beloved son.
Don't mention it.
I promise...
I will forever take care of Ruk.
You can trust me on this.
Thank you.
When I'm free, I will go and apologize
to your grandmother and your mother.
Kao, thank you
for meeting me today.
At first, I didn't want to come. However, after
hearing your voice, it doesn't sound OK.
I'm sorry about
what happened that day.
Sorry for shouting at you like that.
I didn't mean it.
I also...
want to apologize to you, Kim.
With everything that happened...
it's obvious.
you and Kao...
looks very suitable.
More than I was
when I was dating Fangkao.
Honestly...
I should be the
one apologizing to you.
I took away your girlfriend...
and...
troubling you.
To be honest, whatever
I do didn't feel right.
You really did wrong.
You took away my girlfriend.
But...
honestly...
Fangkao and I doesn't
love each other anymore.
It's good that it end this way.
Stop worrying about it.
If I find out that
you have someone else...
you'll be sorry.
Rest assured.
I only love Fangkao here.
I love her for so long too.
Wait.
Since when did you change
from her boyfriend to her father?
Yeah, she is my ex-girlfriend.
My girlfriend.
Dad had to hurry
because of his elections matter.
And I have to back to teach at school.
Can you stay on your own?
Yes.
Don't think too much. It's in the past.
Take care of yourself.
OK?
Sawasdee krub, Mr. Tunwa.
You've been disappearing.
Where are you going?
It's time to pay your monthly debt.
I'm not gonna let you go.
I got it!
Stand still.
Let's go.
Cheers!
IG, we never thought that...
you could make the reputation of our
Chatreemit school to be once again famous.
Because I have a good teacher.
If you put your mind
into it, you can do it.
A man from a famous school...
was beaten up by his creditor
and was rushed to the hospital.
The police accused him of fraud.
This is news about P'Tunwa.
In the end, someone
committed got his punishment.
But that's how it should be...
for a guy like him.
Next time, we have to be
more "stick" to our work.
Focus! (seutid)
You're such a...
P'IG.
This semester break,
we're going to Nong Saeng again.
We're going to do merits.
Really?
Let's go then.
We'll let IG sing...
and you guys
will dance the votive.
I probably won't go
back this semester break.
Why?
I have to record
a song with Thaithep.
You're not
going to sing at Saengsin?
I've signed the contract and may
have to stay here for a long time.
I may not return
to the village at all.
Relax, it's not like we can't
dance with IG not coming.
Ai'Ruk can handle the venue.
You guys just have to get
ready with the appropriate attire.
I'll do the recording and
"chare" it with you guys.
It's "share"!
Yes, yes. Share it is.
This semester break, I'll...
Hello, what's up?
Hello, Ruk.
It's so happen that the province
club increase their selection number.
And they want you to go for
the selection after your legs recover.
Really?!
Will you return to
the village for semester break?ป
Well, um...
Sure, sure.
See you later.
Who called? Looks like a good news.
My brother called and told me...
that the Country Province Football Association
asked me to participate in their selection.
- Damn
- Is that true?
Yes!
Let's cheers.
Then that means, you will come
and help us with the merits thing.
Yeah.
I think this semester
break will be special.
I think so too.
Have you made your decision...
about moving out of Saengsin?
If you got selected by the association...
that means you...
will have to stay at Saengsin forever.
Probably.
I live in Bangkok.
You live in Nong Saeng.
It's such a sky
apart relationship here.
You talk like it's
life and death apart.
We just leave for a
while to pursue our dreams
For us to meet again.
You promised me, didn't you?
That we won't
leave each other again.
P'Ruk.
Do you really have to go
I can't breathe.
Don't you pity me?
I have to go.
Look.
Looks so pathetic.
You mean me?
I mean me!
Let me go.
I really have to go.
Take good care of yourself...
and focus on your studies.
Understand, troublemaker?
Good.
LINE text me if you miss me.
I'm gonna go now.
Stop crying.
It's not like I'm gonna die.
Thank you.
Sawasdee kha, my name is
Khet from Thaithep recording company.
Yes.
Do you any agent yet?
Not yet.
Are you interested in making
music with our company?
Yes, I am.
I'm very interested.
♪ Are you really single
and not just being lonely? ♪
♪ Not just because you had a fight with her ♪
♪ So you came to tell about your loneliness ♪
♪ Are you really single or pretending....♪
You sing it wrong.
How can it not be right?
It's wrong for real.
I told you, you always argue.
You think that you're teacher,
you do everything right?
Yes.
Everything.
But not because I'm a teacher.
What then?
Because I'm your boyfriend.
You suddenly became deaf?
You treat the fact of
being frank as if it's a big deal.
Don't be so loud.
You'll wake up the forest
guardian and the mountain guardian.
So annoying,
it's stinks of sweetness here.
Grateen, Grandma wants
you to come. The host is here.
Let's go.
I'll go now.
It's quite good to have love.
P'.
Ruk.
When did you arrive?
Just now.
Really?
See you later, I'm leaving.
Wait.
Are you...
still mad at me about that day?
If you know...
that I was the one who sent the photo
of you and IG kissing to Uncle Yingyod...
will you still
want to talk to me?
I'm sorry.
I was hoping for it
too much on my own.
Didn't think
what I was holding.
It's alright.
It's in the past now.
Just let it be in the past.
We can start anew.
Really?
Yes.
Thank you.
P', what are you doing?
I was talking to Ruk.
What talking?
I clearly saw you hug him.
You are a woman.
Holding a guy 3 to 5 times
like this, is that appropriate?
What's his problem?
Or are you two in
some kind of relationship?
Ai'Tong, are you crazy?
Me and P'Noinae
is not in a relationship.
Yes, true.
Just a hug,
that's normal. Nothing...
Stop talking!
If you really are not in relationship...
then...
can I have your number, P'Noinae?
Something suspicious?
Not here.
If no then...
can you give me your number?
What's his problem?
Give it to him.
Please.
Can you give N'Tong your number?
If you don't give it,
you're suspicious.
I'm happy for you.
Good luck, Brother in love.
Since there's no one here now...
how will you go home?
No nee to be a busybody.
Let's go for a stroll.
I thought you weren't coming back.
At first, I didn't think about coming.
But I don't know why...
I can't get rid of
my longing to this place.
I probably can't control my feelings...
like you once told me.
IG.
Thank you so much...
for not leaving me.
Thank you too.
What is this?
What are you doing?
Wait.
What are you gonna
do wearing that life vest?
For playing golf perharps.
Move, we're gonna
jump into the water.
Shit.
Katty.
What is it, P'?
You're not going into the water?
No, I'm afraid of fried fish.
Fish bite!
The fish at your house is good for frying.
It's the same thing.
Yeah, yeah.
What are you guys doing?
We're watching our friends swimming.
Come up! Come up!
- Come up, come up!
- Come up quick!
- Tong, come up quick!
-Hurry!
P', what's there in the water?
There are leeches!
Shit!
Come up!
Why didn't you tell
them there are leech in there!
I forgot!
Come up!
♫ Just you coming here makes my heart melt ♫
♫ It melts, melts that I want to swallow you whole ♫
♫ You didn't come with anyone else, right? ♫
♫ What do you like? ♫
♫ Tell me and I'll find some or you ♫
♫ I’m not rich like others ♫
♫ I don't have what others do ♫
♫ I just wanna say that a guy
like me only have true love ♫
♫ I will never abandon you ♫
♫ Nor make you sit in sadness ♫
♫ Even though I’m not handsome,
my heart is sincere ♫
♫ I will give all my heart to you ♫
♫ In my life right now, I only have you ♫
♫ please don’t leave me aside
and pulverize my heart ♫
♫ I met you when I didn't have anything left ♫
♫ Will you accept me on the
day I don't have anything left? ♫
♫ The economy is bad,
my house is in troublesome ♫
♫ There is famine, not enough money to spend ♫
♫ Are you looking at me from
the outside or the inside? ♫
♫ Please look at my heart,
look at me from the inside ♫
♫ Even though I'm not handsome,
my heart is sincere ♫
♫ I will give all my heart to you ♫
♫ In my life right now,
I only have you ♫
♫ Please don't leave me
aside and pulverize my heart ♫
♫ Just by walking here it's
enough knowing that you look ♫
♫You look, look and look at
me until my eyes stares like hers ♫
♫ I'm not here with anyone ♫
♫ I came alone and only want to have fun ♫
♫ Just walk in here to forget
about the person who left me ♫
♫ I’m not rich like others ♫
♫ I don't have what others do ♫
♫ I just wanna say that a guy
like me only have true love ♫
♫ I will never abandon you ♫
♫ Nor make you sit in sadness ♫
♫ Even though I’m not handsome,
my heart is sincere ♫
♫ I will give all my heart to you ♫
♫ In my life right now, I only have you ♫
♫ please don’t leave me aside
and pulverize my heart ♫
♫ I met you when I didn't have anything left ♫
♫ Will you accept me on the day
I don't have anything left? ♫
♫ The economy is bad, my house is in troublesome ♫
♫ There is famine, not enough money to spend ♫
♫ Are you looking at me
from the outside or the inside? ♫
♫ Please look at my heart,
look at me from the inside ♫
♫ Even though I'm not handsome,
my heart is sincere ♫
♫ I will give all my heart to you ♫
♫ In my life right now, I only have you ♫
♫ Please don't leave me aside
and pulverize my heart ♫
♫ Even though I'm not handsome,
my heart is sincere ♫
♫ I will give all my heart to you ♫
♫ In my life right now, I only have you ♫
♫ Please don't leave me
aside and pulverize my heart ♫
♫ Just you coming here makes my heart melt ♫
♫ It melts, melts that I want to swallow you whole ♫
♫ You didn't come with anyone else, right? ♫
♫ What do you like? ♫
♫ Tell me and I'll find some or you ♫
♫ I’m not rich like others ♫
♫ I don't have what others do ♫
♫ I just wanna say that a guy
like me only have true love ♫
♫ I will never abandon you ♫
♫ Nor make you sit in sadness ♫
♫ Even though I’m not handsome,
my heart is sincere ♫
♫ I will give all my heart to you ♫