This series is created for entertainment purposes only.
Characters, places and events in this story are all fictional.
It's not related or referring to any event or any individual's behaviour.
Please use your viewing judgment.
♫ Just you coming here makes my heart melt ♫
♫ It melts, melts that I want to swallow you whole ♫
♫ You didn't come with anyone else, right? ♫
♫ What do you like? ♫
♫ Tell me and I'll find some or you ♫
♫ I’m not rich like others ♫
♫ I don't have what others do ♫
♫ I just wanna say that a guy
like me only have true love ♫
♫ I will never abandon you ♫
♫ Nor make you sit in sadness ♫
♫ Even though I’m not handsome,
my heart is sincere ♫
♫ I will give all my heart to you ♫
♫ In my life right now, I only have you ♫
♫ please don’t leave me aside
and pulverize my heart ♫
Sawasdee krub, my name is Ruk.
I'm from the village called Bang Nong Saen.
I got a scholarship to become the
football player at Chatreemit School.
This is the first time in my life I come to Bangkok.
In this city, my life change unexpectedly.
Especially...
my love story.
Hello.
What’s up, dude.
Have you reach Bangkok?
Yes, I have.
Have you become a city boy now?
That's exaggerating.
I'm only gonna be here for awhile.
I'll come back and see you
again during the semester break.
So, since you'll be there for quite a while...
you won't be able to speak Isaan again.
Someone who live in the Northern
region can't speak Isaan now, Ai'Pek?
Well, because you're studying in the city.
Where are you now?
I'm at the Victory Monument.
But I don't know which bus to take.
There are 500 buses routes.
Think about it.
Yeah, just, try to search carefully.
Take care of yourself.
I know how to go there now.
P', do you know where is Chatreemft School?
Of course.
How much»?
They're all the same price.
Come, hop on first.
For your safety,
I’ll lend you a helmet.
Splendid.
H’ow much, P'?
200 baht.
It wasn't even a 5 minutes ride.
You have a lot of
luggage and they're heavy.
My tires are almost bursting.
Come now.
P'....
I only have 50 baht.
Can you just accept this much?
You don't have any cash?
I have QR code.
It will solve all your cash problems.
Pay now.
Sriphichat Samphachot.
Yes.
Done.
Thank you.
Good thing we have code scan now.
Just go, P'.
[ Invitation for Jaturamitr Samakkee Football Competition ]
Do you think the
"God Guys" will come today?
Of course, today is the club opening day.
When will they come?
Calm down.
So handsome.
Who is he?
I think opening a new club is a good idea.
How so?
Look, all the girls are sexy.
Hey, Nong!
Nong?
Can you see me?
Where is he?
Nong?
Can't you hear me calling you?
Where is he?
Nong, I saw a ghost.
It can split itself into two.
You mean them?
Relax.
This Natee and Nathan.
They're twins.
Sawasdee krub.
- I'm Natee.
- I'm Nathan.
This is insane!
When I was calling you,
didn't you hear me?!
We were wearing earphones.
Your(P') name is Ruk, right?
Yes, yes.
You look better than in the picture.
My name is Chaiya.
Are you from Northern Thai too?
Yes, I'm a northerner.
You heard me talking in Isaan language.
Most students here are from Isaan.
They can speak Isaan language.
What's wrong with your voice, Chaiya?
It's like a girl's voice.
I don't know either.
It's like that since I was born.
Are you on the football team too?
Yes.
Do you like football?
On the contrary, I like the football player.
You're into guys?
That depends on the guy...
whether he wants me to like him or not.
Is this how you welcome your freshman?
I'm kidding. Later you can go
to play football with Natee and Nathan.
Yeah, yeah. Go.
Tee, Taan, go play football.
Hello, hello. 1, 2, 3, test.
Sawasdee to all Chatree students.
I'm Kaengsom, the usual awesome guy.
The newly appointed broadcasting station master.
I'm here to give report.
Our radio station has been
broadcasting for a week now.
We also that we have a
football competition coming...
that's jointly held
with 3 other schools.
Also, various clubs are
recruiting new members this evening.
Let's listen to who they are.
The Cheerleading Club,
lead by our very cool captain.
P'Mes from M. 6(12th grade).
Let me tell you, his achievement this year is
absolutely superior to the previous captain.
As for those who likes to
dance and and twist their bodies...
can come for an audition
with our dance team captain.
P'Katty, M. 5(11th grade).
Let me tell you,
he is very handsome.
He's very skillful in difficult movement.
And for those who like music,
we have that too.
Come to our music club.
Led by P'Tong from M. 5.
Lastly is the undisputed and is essential
to our previous Samakkee event.
And that is our own football team.
The captain is the extremely handsome
P'Kui, the sweet-eyed goalkeeper.
The shaker of every girl's heart.
And the best one is P'IG.
Alright, which one do you want to be with?
Hurry and sign up.
See you at the event.
[ School Building ]
Alright, Sawasdee to all.
Sorry.
What club are you in?
Football.
Have a seat.
As we all know, we are going to be hosting the
Jaturamitr Samakkee Football Competition this year.
This year, the organizing committee
wants to hold better football activities.
For that, we need to reduce the
budget for the other clubs...
and use it for the football team activities.
I'm Pogmes, the captain of
the 22th Cheerleading Club.
Our cheerleading club has a long history here.
So, for the sake of inheriting,
innovating and encouragement...
I think...
Stop the nonsense, straight to the point.
I think you can
reduce other club's budget.
All our training tools and cheer stand...
they are all our cohesion.
If our budget is reduced,
I fear it will damage our reputation.
I agree.
The cheerleading image is
like the spirit of our school.
Aside from the school's reputation,
we're also the face of the school.
If you need a good school's reputation...
you can't reduce the
budget of the music club.
Because we can also
improve the school's reputation.
What sound do you want?
Drums, cymbals,
finger cymbals, saxophone?
We can play all of it.
Ai'Tong, what are you talking about?
The director wants to improve cheu siang(reputation),
not just siang(sound). Are you stupid?
Ai'Katty, why did you insult me?!
You want some?!
Guys, guys!
Can you not butt in, P'?!
I'm your senior!
Stay out of this.
Go, go.
OK.
Continue.
Stop, stop, stop!
I said stop!
OK, I understand that every club is important.
But I've decided..
This is all your fault, Ai'Tong. You idiot.
How's that, P'?!
It's because you were
fighting that the budget was cut!
Serve you right!
You better stop that.
Sorry.
Why don't you guys
find your own budget?
I saw the senior before us
asked for their seniors for help.
Oh yeah.
Then why didn't you
stop us from fighting?
I didn't have time!
- There were plenty of time. Didn't you see? We were hitting nonstop.
- You guys were fighting fiercely!
If I stop you, would you listen?!
Enough!
It has been decided!
But one thing's bothering me.
That new guy, who is he?
His name's Ruk, the school brought him here.
Today is his first day.
He's the one who caused our
budget to be cut off, right?
He'll answer to me, I'm telling you.
Let's get him.
Are you looking for trouble again?
Do you want some too?
Sorry.
Pass it.
Nicely done.
Take it.
Run.
Run, run.
Hurry up, hurry up!
Everyone, we have a new
friend from the Northern region.
His name is Ruk.
He will play in our team.
Take care of your new friend.
Ruk, this is Kim. The team's captain.
Kim, please take care of your friend.
Yes, Coach.
Are you really gonna wear that shoes?
This is all I have.
I'll give you one tomorrow.
What size do you wear?
42.
We're the same size.
I'm Kui, the goalkeeper.
I'm...
Ruk, I know.
I already got introduced
about you 3 to 4 times today.
Chaiya.
- Natee.
- Yes.
Nathan.
- Kim.
- Yes.
Salabpao.
Kanoon.
Champ.
- Kui.
- Present.
IG.
Why the fuck are you laughing?
IG?!
What kind of name is "IG"?
Let's just say there is.
IG?!
As usual, he skipped.
Again? Is he gonna graduate like this?
Come, let's train.
Yes.
There really is someone named IG?
Ai'Ruk, you're great.
Damn, how did you do that?
Can you do it one more time?
Damn.
Ai'Ruk.
If you wanna show off...
go back to your hometown for that.
Understand?
This is break time, P'.
I was just kicking the ball.
Ai'Kui.
If IG doesn't want to train...
just let him out of the team.
I don't want to be dragged
down by him, understand?
Ai'Kui.
Is it hurt?
Yes.
P', can you give this to P'Kui?
From whom should I tell him?
It's Noon, also tell
him to call me sometimes.
Sure thing.
Thank you.
IG, come back to practice!
What's wrong with you?
Will you be able
to graduate like this?
- I'm not going!
- IG!
I said I'm not going.
- Let's go.
- No!
Let me go!
IG!
What is Kui doing?
What's his deal?
- IG, let's go
- I'm not going
What's wrong with you?
Will you be able
to graduate like this?
That's my problem.
Get back to practice.
Ai'Kui, let me go
- I'm not going.
- Ai'Kui, what's going on?
- Help me grab him, he's heavy.
- Let me go!
Who the hell are you?
- Hold him!
- Let me go!
Fuck, it's blood!
Kui, I won't go to training with
my face wounded like this.
Who the hell are you?
Was that big guy named IG?
Yes.
Did he name himself that?
What kind of name is IG?
Actually, his name
should be Ai'Chol(prick).
No.
His mothe
r often goes abroad.
"I" is from his first name...
and "G" is from his last name.
A girl name Noon
ask me to give this to you.
Which Noon?
Whatever, thank you.
As we close to the football competition, there will
always be a lot of girls giving things like this.
Are you with that
so called god gang, right?
The God Guys.
We're close and we
go anywhere together.
Suddenly there are so
many people following us.
No wonder so many
girls come to watch football.
That can't be help...
because I'm handsome.
Let's go train.
Damn, you so full of yourself.
Really handsome you are.
Here you are.
I've been looking for you.
Hey...
P'Ruk...
did you hit P'IG until his head bleeds?
I got it from P'IG's Angel's Gang.
They said that you hit
P'IG until he bleed profusely.
Bleed profusely?
Are they crazy?
That's exaggerating.
The wound is the size of a cat nail.
Plus, I was just grabbing his bag.
They made it sounds like I killed someone.
That means you still
have no clue who P'IG really is.
Come here.
I'll tell you.
P'IG real name is Intat Gorsaengsin
His mother's name is Kaewdtah.
She is a single mother. She's very beautiful.
She also let P'IG to stop studied for 2 years...
just for him to go in search for himself.
Did he found it?
I don't know, probably he didn't.
Otherwise, he wouldn't come back to school.
Also, during his time out of school, he became a youtuber.
Having a style like rich people...
to which people like are us won't get to reach.
Let's just say that he's very famous.
Is that so?
That's how it is.
So, you should not get involve with him.
Don't blame me for not warning you.
I'm worried.
About P'IG?
I mean you!
Damn, taking advantages now?
I'll kick you until
you fly over there.
IG...
My way, my way.
Give it some.
That's cool.
Ai'Kaengsom, how can
you do this stuff? So cool.
This is normal for me.
I tried so many times but can't do it.
What about me? Was it cool?
You are.
IG.
Is that Fangkao?
The one who's having
her photo taken, right?
He's right, P'.
Go for it, P'.
So?
What are you gonna do?
Then I'm gonna go see her.
See you.
Go for her, P'.
See you later.
He's so manly.
Look, he's in a hurry.
So quick.
He's full of confidence.
Did you get it?
This is so beautiful.
That's right.
Smile a lot.
Snap it.
- Very beautiful.
- 1, 2, 3.
Fangkao.
P'IG, is there anything I can do for you?
I'm going home now.
What about you?
Wanna ride home?
No need.
Fangkao will go home with me.
What did you say?
She's with you?
Yes.
What is this, Kao?
Well, Fangkao is...
I'm Kim's girlfriend.
What?!
You broke up with me...
because I'm a football player...
and I'm in 12th grade.
You said...
you and I didn't
have time to be together.
What about Kim then?
How is he different from me?
He and I are in the same team!
I don't mean any bad intention.
I think you should
focus on your studies.
Then you can graduate
normally like other people.
That's all the reason to it?
Why Kao?!
What did I do wrong?
You didn't do anything wrong.
I just don't love you anymore.
The girl already said it clearly.
What more do you want?
Stay out of this!
You're only an outsider!
The hell is wrong with you?
What the hell?
IG, you bastard!
What the hell?!
- What the hell?!
- Try me!
Come on then!
You jerk!
Come on!
P'IG, slowly.
P', slowly.
Calm down!
I can take all 4 of you!
No need for them,
I alone is enough!
- Come on then.
- Come on!
Let him come.
"6 month anniversary."
What is the meaning of this?
You were dating two guys at once?
We just broke up two months ago!
Let's go.
IG!
- Take it easy, P'!
You bastard!
Come on!
Come on, bastard!
Ai'Tong, get out of here!
I'll make you pay.
P', we should go.
Let's go.
I don't mean any bad intention.
I think you should focus on your studies.
Then you can graduate
normally like other people.
"6 month anniversary."
What is the meaning of this?
You were dating two guys at once?
We just broke up two months ago!
All women sucks!
Take it easy, P'.
Bro, just come down, man.
I think lately...
our luck is down the drain.
Had a girl but got dump!
We didn't even do
anything for the football event!
I'm fucking sick of this!
I know now...
how we can find something fun to do.
Do what?
You'll know. I'll tell you.
Why are you bringing me here?
Why does it has to be here?
Are they all asleep?
Why are we here?
Ai'Tong, Ai'Kaengsom.
What's the deal?
Why are you doing it slowly?
Because we have the solution.
We came here in secret.
You came here in secret...
but playing with something big?
Yeah.
So what's the solution
are you talking about?
No need for slow motion!
I have my own way!
Be quiet, P'. We're here in secret.
You've been doing that several times now.
What the hell are you doing?!
Sorry! Sorry!
- Let me go!
- Hold him!
Hurry up.
Who the hell are you?
Dude.
It's really missing.
If someone found out...
we're all in trouble.
Yes.
I looked everywhere,
I didn't find it.
IG.
What do you want?
I'm Ruk.
I'm sorry for causing you
to hit your head the other day.
That's all right.
You seems stressful.
Did you do something?
Huh? No.
This is yours, right?
No.
Mine's at home.
I don't know whose bag is that.
Really?
Then the IPad and
the camera in this bag...
can be thrown away, right?
Don't be rash.
So it's yours then?
No.
Isn't it expensive?
Can you afford to pay for that?
I don't know where the owner is.
Last night, something happened
in the athlete residence building.
I saw this on the ground...
so I took it.
It's yours.
It's not mine.
No idea to whom it belongs to.
The firecrackers were very loud.
The owner might be
panicked and dropped it.
Really?!
How do you know about firecrackers?
I didn't say that someone
sets off firecrackers last night.
You did it, didn't you?
No.
If you're not telling me the truth...
I'll throw this for real.
You will confess to the coach...
or else watch this camera and IPad...
drop to the ground.
Don't do it.
One...
- two!!!
- Yes, yes!
Me and my friends did it, I'm sorry.
We were just playing, didn't expect the
firecrackers would light up for real.
That wasn't too difficult, isn't it?
I'm not going
to see the coach with you.
You're such an idiot!
You think you can
threaten me that way?
Such a noob.
Whether I
can threaten you or not...
you'll know soon enough.
- two!!!
- Yes, yes!
Me and my friends did it...
This kind of behavior
can get you expel, IG.
Endure and
study for just a little while.
Can't you study
and graduate nicely?
I said I didn't do it.
The whose bag is this?
If you didn't do it,
then who did?
Just admit it.
If you did it...
just admit it.
This is really waste of time, IG.
Yes.
I did it.
You can expel me
right now if you want.
A guy like me...
attend school that way.
Sawasdee krub.
Sorry I'm late. I just
watched the security footage.
IG didn't do it.
I also know who did it.
IG.
IG!
What do you want?
I'm sorry...
for misjudging you.
Me and Coach know
now that you're innocent.
That's all right.
Good that you understand now.
However...
everything...
has a price to pay.
What does that mean?
There.
Behind you.
Good luck.
Noob.
Why are you here?
You did something mean to our IG?
We can talk about this.
What did you do?
Calm down.
Please don't.
IG!!!
♫ Even though I'm not handsome, my heart is sincere ♫
♫ I will give all my heart to you ♫
♫ In my life right now, I only have you ♫
♫ Please don't leave me aside and pulverize my heart ♫
♫ I met you when I didn't have anything left ♫
♫ Will you accept me on the day I don't have anything left? ♫
♫ The economy is bad, my house is in troublesome ♫
♫ There is famine, not enough money to spend ♫
♫ Are you looking at me from the outside or the inside? ♫
♫ Please look at my heart, look at me from the inside ♫
♫ Even though I'm not handsome, my heart is sincere ♫
♫ I will give all my heart to you ♫
♫ In my life right now, I only have you ♫
♫ Please don't leave me aside and pulverize my heart ♫