This series is created for entertainment purposes only.
Characters, places and events in this story are all fictional.
It's not related or referring to any event or any individual's behaviour.
Please use your viewing judgment.
♫ Just you coming here makes my heart melt ♫
♫ It melts, melts that I want to swallow you whole ♫
♫ You didn't come with anyone else, right? ♫
♫ What do you like? ♫
♫ Tell me and I'll find some or you ♫
♫ I’m not rich like others ♫
♫ I don't have what others do ♫
♫ I just wanna say that a guy
like me only have true love ♫
♫ I will never abandon you ♫
♫ Nor make you sit in sadness ♫
♫ Even though I’m not handsome,
my heart is sincere ♫
♫ I will give all my heart to you ♫
♫ In my life right now, I only have you ♫
♫ please don’t leave me aside
and pulverize my heart ♫
How are you feeling?
Mr. Superhero.
You're lucky, Kui.
Good that you're not
wounded more severe than this.
This little injury won't kill me.
Such a big talker.
Khun Kui...
are you're all right?
My friend here is crying river.
It's not like Ai'Kui is dead or anything.
Th... Thank you so much.
It was my fault.
I wasn't taking care of myself.
It's not really your fault.
Are you nuts?
He's crying
Move.
Don't get in my way.
Anyway, I have to thank you.
If there's anything you need my help with...
you can let me know.
Are you OK?
If you're really feeling guilty, then...
can you give me a massage?
Of course.
Thank you so much, Khun Kui.
If there's anything you need my help with...
you can let me know.
Hello Nae.
Do you want me to pick you up?
Yes, come and pick me up.
Sure, sure.
No need.
I'll give you a ride home.
Alright.
Your father's calling.
Hello, Dad.
Where are you?
At Grandma Yoi's house.
I've asked P'Tunwa to pick you up.
Hurry back.
Dad, Dad!
Dad!
Ruk, then I'l...
I'll go home by myself.
Take care of Kui.
I'm going home now, Petch.
Ai'Kui, I'm leaving.
See you.
Are you hurt?
No, just tickle.
Keep massaging.
Kui...
-What?
- Get out.
Get... Get out!
Is there something wrong?
Nothing.
Too much dust.
Should I get some water?
That won't be necessary.
Keep massaging.
Are you sure you don't
want a glass of water?
That's alright.
How do you know I'm here?
Your father told me.
S0....
Have you been back from Bangkok long?
Some time already.
I brought your friends here for photoshoot.
The God Guys Gang.
Such a small world.
Never thought of seeing them here.
By the way...
I heard that you...
pretend to date IG, is that true?
So why did you come home together?
He's Grandma Yoi's grandson.
The owner of Saengsin car parade.
What a coincidence.
If IG's fanclub know that he's Isaan...
they'll be all confused
like rooster lose its eye.
IG...
doesn't want anyone to know that he's
He's obsessed with his image.
You sure knows a lot about IG.
P'....
me and him are not real boyfriends.
Can you promise me...
that you won't tell this to my father?
You don't have to worry.
I won't tell anyone about this.
Thank you so much.
If I don't have you,
I might not be able to survive.
Come, I think we should go home now...
or your father will be worried.
Sure, P'. Let's go.
Here.
Thanks.
Lately, you haven't
mention much about Fangkao.
Or your method of pretending t
o be Ruk's boyfriend works?
I guess so.
Mes.
I think I'm gonna stop being a youtuber.
What do you think?
You're just all talk.
If you don't do it,
what else are you going to do?
I just don't feel like doing
anything for the time being.
I don't even want to
talk about going to school.
But I don't know what to do.
You're feeling too
overwork or you're bored of it?
It's actually a good thing
because you've tried many things.
But I don't see you stick to any of them.
Are you really going to
keep changing things like this?
It's not the right thing for me.
Not right...
or you can't hold on to it?
You always refuses to persist like this.
How can you really
be interested in something?
Hello, Mom.
Aunty.
Where is that Bangkok football player?
Who do you mean?
That guy...
Move!
All the gangs are here.
Not you.
Then who?!
That Yingyod's son!
If you're looking for Yingyod's son...
then go look for him at Yingyod's house!
Why are you here?!
I don't care.
Your son is that guy's friend!
Whatever you do, you have
to be responsible for it together.
What do you want?!
What?!
Hold on!
What are you gonna do to my son?!
Why are you interfering?
He's my son!
Hey, wait, wait!
Finally, here you are!
What are you gonna do?
Why?!
I think you should calm down.
Otherwise, things will get worsen.
Who are you...
dare you preach us?
Your friend caused
my friend to get arrested!
Are you sure...
that my brothers started this?
If you ask people
who're present at the scene...
maybe...
the person who should be in jail...
might not be just your friend.
I think we should end this here.
Do you know...
trespassing into
someone else' house like this...
it violated article 364 of the Criminal Law.
You can get imprison for 1 year...
or a fine of 20,000 baht.
Or both imprisonment and fine.
Do you wanna try?
Come on, do you wanna try?
Do you want that?
What?
If you don't leave, I'll shoot!
She has a gun.
I'll let you go for now.
Next time, you'll be sorry.
Remember!
You're awesome.
What's up, Mr. Lawyer?
The future lawyer is here.
Mom.
- Mom.
- What is it?
Stand here, Mom.
Ai'Ruk, how are you here?
Ai'Kui told me about this.
I called him.
I got you a watermelon.
Thank you for visiting me.
What makes you think
of giving me a watermelon?
It's sweet.
You should try it.
Is it as sweet as the
one who gave it to me?
Have a sit.
Is there anything?
Are you usually
a less talkative person?
Well, no.
But, I don't know what to talk about.
What's wrong, Kui?
My arm and my wound hurts.
It's sore all over.
I'm thirsty too.
Can you feed me?
Sure, sure.
What are you doing?
It's all messy now.
Sorry.
Wipe it for me.
It's messy.
Be gentle.
Sorry.
Wipe here.
Of course.
Here.
Are you alright?
Why are your heart beating so fast?
Do you have a heart disease?
No.
I'm gonna go home now.
Dude.
Do you want to go see
the boys photoshoot today?
Who is this?
IG.
Is Ruk there?
He's not here.
He went to the
market and forgot his phone.
Is there anything you want?
Never mind.
Please tell him to
call me when he get back.
Yeah, yeah.
Dad
Did anyone called me?
No.
That's good pictures.
Very beautiful.
This one looks handsome.
- So handsome.
- True.
Mes, Katty.
How's it going?
P'IG.
You guys dressed up handsomely.
Of course, it's a cowboy costume, right?
- Shit.
- A cowboy.
Those pictures are nice.
Sawasdee krub.
Sawasdee ja.
N'IG!
You're so handsome in person!
So cute.
Thank you.
I'm gonna take some photos at the back.
Yeah, OK.
Say goodbye to my viewers.
Bye, see you.
So cute.
I think we should do more.
Let's go.
Tunwa, the price that we discussed...
does it include IG's promotion fee?
N'IG only came here with his friends.
The price that I
charged you in the beginning...
doesn't include N'IG.
If we include N'IG, I think...
the price might be higher.
That's unfortunate.
But he seems to be very
passionate about photo shooting.
Yes.
Do you want tell him that
he's not allow to take videos here?
No, no.
He can do it.
Because N'IG is a
very hot person right now.
He has a lot of followers.
It's a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
In that case, can you
talk to him for me about his fee?
See how much he wants.
Absolutely.
In that case,
you wait here for a moment.
Don't worry, I'll take care of it.
Very good.
Sawasdee to all IG-an.
This is IG, your usual great guy.
Today, I'm taking you guys to a horse farm.
No need to tell you that
because I'm standing in front of a horse.
Where did you get your hair done?
Which barbershop, can you tell me?
Your hair style...
IG.
It's...
What are your relationship with Ruk?
What?
I ask, what is your realtionship with Ruk?
Why?
Whatever I am to him...
has nothing to do with you.
Don't tell me you guys are dating.
But Ruk himself told me...
that you're not dating for real.
Do you even have rights to question me?
Even if there's
something between me and Ruk...
it has nothing to do with you.
The person he doesn't love...
has no right to be jealous.
I almost forgot.
The clip that you've taken...
Sis wants to ask you to help her promote.
How much your price is, just tell me.
But...
don't think about charging the price too high.
It's free, I'm rich.
OK, deal.
Since you're already here,
when you done recording...
help me to give the horse a bath.
Sis, I've talked with N'IG.
IG offers his price at 100,000.
100,000?!
That's it?
If you don't mind...
about those money for the kids...
you can give it to me.
Because we're already close.
Of course.
The money is no issue.
I'll transfer it.
Alright, Sis.
Thank you so much
for taking care of the kids.
Yes.
I'll give you a signal...
and you'll execute it, Tong.
Consider it done, P'.
He won't scold us, right?
The hell he will.
His very gentlemen, unlike you, Ai'Rang...
you're petty.
If we fail...
it will be over.
Are you ready, Kaengsom?
I'm ready since I was born.
Call P'Tunwa.
It will be done.
Kaengsom.
Sawasdee krub, P'Tunwa.
What is it? I'm busy.
Umm, here he is, everyone.
Our great hero who
sponsor our cheer event this time.
- Without him...
- Is that a live broadcast?
Yes, P'
No, no. Don't do it.
Wait, don't rush.
- No, no need for this.
- P', it will only take a while.
Why do you want to go back?
Let's ride a horse, have you ever ride one?
I have to leave now.
Just for a moment.
Drop it, drop it!
P'Tunwa!
Shit!
Shit.
Ai'Kaengsom, what the hell?
What the fuck are you playing?!
I said don't record it!
Put your phone away!
Shit, what now?
He is so scary.
Shit.
Shit, what the hell?
Oh shit.
What now?
You said he won't get mad.
I think I'm gonna wet my pants.
That yourdon't call angry?
It's all your fault, Ai'Tong. Damn.
I missed.
Look at my hair here!
Yes, I've bought it. It's the
beautiful mango you want to eat.
I bought it, I'm on my way home now.
See you soon, Dad, OK.
Petch.
Do you have anything to eat today?
I bought this.
Looks appetizing.
Thank you.
What are you guys doing here?
Nothing.
I was just on my way home.
Where's Ai'Ruk?
He's at home.
He's inviting P'Tunwa
for dinner at his house.
I'm planning to join.
I'll come too.
Sure thing.
Wait, you can't go.
Why?
Who's gonna feed me the mango?
Stop!
You guys settle
about your mangoes here.
You'll be coming with me.
- So, so...
- Hurry, I'm hungry.
He...
Grateen, what are you playing?
Someone might see us.
People might see us hugging...
but they don't know what it means.
Keep it down.
When will I get to call you
my boyfriend out loud?
We have to always hide whenever we go.
It's not the moment yet.
If it's not now, then when?!
♪ Go to eat alone and travel with no companion ♪
♪ Someone who has a girl and
not single will never understand ♪
♪ I have a smartphone but
can't use to express love ♪
♪ It's just expensive and I'm
really bored and lonely ♪
♪ I'm counting days out loud, don't
want to turn on my Facebook ♪
♪ Everywhere in it are couple photos,
it makes me more lonely ♪
♪ Someone loveless is seen
by the sky with no word ♪
♪ Who thinks as I do saying hat
evening to morning are quiet ♪
♪ Please appear before me ♪
♪ If you are the right person for me ♪
♪ Where are you now? ♪
♪ Cupid, please tell me ♪
♪ If we keep hiding from each other,
will we be fast enough to meet? ♪
♪ I want to have a couple ♪
♪ Holding hands while going for a shabu ♪
♪ Go anywhere in a couple shirt ♪
♪ Tell her so she'll know ♪
♪ If she's lonely too,
can you nudge and tell her? ♪
♪ To post it on the wall saying,
Hey, hey, what's up? ♪
♪ If that's the case then
I can meet up with her ♪
♪ I am so single ♪
♪ Please appear before me ♪
♪ If are the right person for me ♪
♪ Where are you now? ♪
♪ Cupid, please tell me ♪
♪ If we keep hiding from each other,
will we be fast enough to meet? ♪
♪ Even if cold winds blows to me,
the chambers of my heart are sitll empty ♪
♪ Please slow down and be a my partner? ♪
♪ I will take care of you in every possible way ♪
♪ I will kiss your cheeks every morning and night ♪
♪ I'll do the homework every day
before bed until you're satisfied ♪
♪ Do you wanna eat, I'll cook for you ♪
♪ Wanna fee your cat or
dog just order me to do it. ♪
♪ If you're displeased.
I'm willing to give my heart to you ♪
♪ I don't know when God
will send someone to me ♪
♪ Don't torture me further,
I can't take it anymore ♪
♪ I understand that
being single is unbearable ♪
♪ Look at those people who are a couple ♪
♪ I sympathize with single people, damn! ♪
♪ Holding hands while going for a shabu ♪
♪ Go anywhere in a couple shirt ♪
♪ Tell her so she'll know ♪
♪ If she's lonely too,
can you nudge and tell her? ♪
♪ To post it on the wall saying,
Hey, hey, what's up? ♪
♪ I want to have a partner ♪
♪ Holding hands while going for a shabu ♪
♪ Go anywhere in a couple shirt ♪
♪ Tell her so she'll know ♪
♪ If she's lonely too,
can you nudge and tell her? ♪
♪ To post it on the wall  ♪
♪ Oh my oh my ♪
♪ I want to have a partner ♪
♪ Holding hands while going for a shabu ♪
♪ Go anywhere in a couple shirt ♪
♪ Tell her so she'll know ♪
♪ If she's lonely too,
can you nudge and tell her? ♪
♪ To post it on the wall saying,
Hey, hey, what's up? ♪
♪ If thats's the case them I can meet up with her ♪
♪ I am so single ♪
You two!
Noinae!
How are you here?
My house is here.
Why are you two here?
I saw it earlier.
You two...
were kissing each other.
Kissing like that, aren't you
afraid you might get a thunder strike?
Please don't tell this to anyone.
If my father knows,
we'll be dead for sure.
But...
No buts, Noinae.
Don't you pity us?
But...
Please, don't tell anyone!
Don't tell anyone.
I've already known
about this for a long time!
You guys weren't slick enough,
should go to school again.
Always got caught.
Ever since that story about the haunted pond.
Do you think I'm afraid of ghost?
You're going on a date at that place, right?
I'm sorry that I'm not afraid of ghost.
So I saw the secret truth
of you two since last year.
Does anyone else knows aside from you?
Ruk.
Ruk know...
but he doesn't want
you to know that he knows.
Come now, don't be stressful.
What a relived.
I won't tell anyone.
I've been keeping this secret for a year now.
But, next time...
be more careful.
If so happen that someone
who's not me saw you...
it'll be a disaster.
Nukrop.
Don't kiss Grateen too often.
He might get pregnant.
Don't be ridiculous.
Nukrop, switch places with Ruk,
I can't see clearly.
How's that be any different?
I don't know.
Nukrop, you...
come and sit next to me.
Sit next to me.
I can't see very clear.
You sit over there.
My eyes are not very good.
Then let's dig in.
Yes, go ahead.
Ruk, get the chicken.
Yes.
Give it to Tunwa.
Very good.
Tunwa, next time bring
your father along to see us.
Lately, it's not very
convenient for him because...
there's been too much work at the factory.
He's a big time boss. No free times.
Especially now, that he live in a
different district, it's hard to contact.
Whenever he's free, bring him along.
Do you remember,
Ruk when he was a kid...
crying to watch football everyday.
Remember?
In his 8th grade, he cried
wanting to watch football at your house
That was during his 9th grade, Uncle.
Grade 9?
Grade 8 or 9, he was so small back then.
Dad.
You're a funny guy, Uncle.
How's your study now? Hard?
I will graduate in another 2 years, but...
I want to graduate in 3 and a half years time.
There's work and there's study.
It's been rough.
Awesome.
Graduate in 3 and a half years time.
Work and study at the same time.
You're great.
Ruk, remember to take
him as an example. Understand?
He's great.
It's good to work while studying.
I almost don't have enough time.
Right now, I'm doing a Youtube business.
What Youtube?
Youtube channel.
Youtube...
it's just you taking video then spread it out.
That's so simple!
You wanna talk about something
like that? That's just too simple.
All you need for
Youtube is just taking video.
Yeah, that's true, IG.
So, when did you study?
Unless you already stop studying.
I didn't study before.
I stop school for 2 years,
but now I came back to school.
I'm in grade 12 now.
I'm allocating my times as best I can.
Grade 12, grade 12...
Nukrop, you don't have to
stress about your study anymore.
You can just graduate in another 5 years.
Because...
that guy will graduate much slower than you.
- Dad.
You should be like this guys,
he'll graduate in 3 and half years time.
He's great.
See, be like Tunwa.
December(Tunwa), January,
February and April!
He's very good.
Eat.
Of course he is.
Studying and working and graduate
in 3 and half years. Awesome!
Eat, eat.
That's how you do it.
Come, let's eat.
Eat up.
I'm sorry.
I have to go home now.
My grandma and mom will be worried.
Yeah, yeah. Hurry, hurry.
Go to your grandmother.
So your mother and
grandmother will feel ease. Go, go.
Thank you for today.
Hurry to her, your grandmother
might be coughing sick.
Ruk!
Have some manners. We have guest, sit.
Hey, close the door!
Dad!
The door was opened,
when people leave, they have to close it.
That's normal.
Eat, eat.
Very delicious.
The papaya salad is good.
Yes.
I heard that you bring students from
Ruk's school here for photoshoot.
Yes, well...
I was looking for a sponsor
for them for their cheer event.
You look for sponsor,
that means you got some commission.
How much? Can you tell me?
I did it for them for free.
Do it for free?! That's awesome.
As for the money...
I let the boys handle all of it themselves.
You're even generous, to boot!
I don't want to get involve in that matter.
This is a good example.
Can I have a consult?
If I want to build a temple...
can you help me find some funding?
Where do you want to build this temple?
At Manchester.
You're funny.
Awesome.
I'm gonna build a temple.
Take him as an example.
Ruk, take him as an example.
He's good in his work.
Very good.
Fuck you, Tunwa.
Will Ai'Mes knows?
Where's my phone?
Hello, Mes.
Hello.
Can I ask you something?
Where did you get
P'Tunwa's contact number?
We asked from Ai'Kaengsom.
I don't know where he got it.
I'm just curious.
Why?
Ai'Kaengsom already asleep.
I'll ask him for you tomorrow.
Um, OK.
If I'm OK, why would I go home?
Mom, if we don't implement
changes, we'll die for sure.
As you can see clearly from the account...
there's only expenses
and our income insufficient.
Why need changes?
The antique is doing good enough.
Grateen's song is very famous and it sells.
But there's only Grateen's song here!
Are we going to make a
living with this song all the time?
Yes.
Why are you interfering with my business?
It's my band!
If it's going to die, it'll die with me.
That's what you always said.
Mom, Grandma.
If there's any problem,
just let it die with me.
You're not listening, Mom.
Enough, Kaewtah. Don't interfere,
I'm having a headache.
I want to-go-to bed.
Mom
You're not talking to me,
so how is this going to settle?
It's finished, I'm-outta here.
I'm gonna head to bed.
IG, go to.bed.
You never listen as always.
Kaewtah
You talk too much that I got a headache.
Mom.
I'm looking for a reason, talk to me.
I better go to bed.
What's going on?
♫ Just you coming here makes my heart melt ♫
♫ It melts, melts that I want to swallow you whole ♫
♫ You didn't come with anyone else, right? ♫
♫ What do you like? ♫
♫ Tell me and I'll find some or you ♫
♫ I’m not rich like others ♫
♫ I don't have what others do ♫
♫ I just wanna say that a guy
like me only have true love ♫
♫ I will never abandon you ♫
♫ Nor make you sit in sadness ♫
♫ Even though I’m not handsome,
my heart is sincere ♫
♫ I will give all my heart to you ♫
♫ In my life right now, I only have you ♫
♫ please don’t leave me aside
and pulverize my heart ♫
♫ I met you when I didn't have anything left ♫
♫ Will you accept me on the
day I don't have anything left? ♫
♫ The economy is bad, my house is in troublesome ♫
♫ There is famine, not enough money to spend ♫
♫ Are you looking at me
from the outside or the inside? ♫