This series is created for entertainment purposes only.
Characters, places and events in this story are all fictional.
It's not related or referring to any event or any individual's behaviour.
Please use your viewing judgment.
♫ Just you coming here makes my heart melt ♫
♫ It melts, melts that I want to swallow you whole ♫
♫ You didn't come with anyone else, right? ♫
♫ What do you like? ♫
♫ Tell me and I'll find some or you ♫
♫ I’m not rich like others ♫
♫ I don't have what others do ♫
♫ I just wanna say that a guy
like me only have true love ♫
♫ I will never abandon you ♫
♫ Nor make you sit in sadness ♫
♫ Even though I’m not handsome,
my heart is sincere ♫
♫ I will give all my heart to you ♫
♫ In my life right now, I only have you ♫
♫ please don’t leave me aside
and pulverize my heart ♫
Hello P'.
Where?
I'll go to you
Ruk!
What is it?
What is this?
Are you going to sleep?
It's 4 AM.
Why are you here so late?
Is there something wrong?
Your face...
looks not OK.
Nothing's wrong.
I'm just afraid that one
day you will forget about me.
But in truth...
I'm more afraid that
everyone will forget about me.
Who will for get about you?
Man of mm friends...
appreciate you.
What if I'm not the person that you know?
Do you still want to talk to me?
Why are you acting like this?
If I'm not competent...
not a nice person...
or rich like other people says...
Will you still want to be with me?
Just about that...
if it spread out...
I'll call my dad...
I like you.
What did you say?
I like you for a long time now.
I like you since
the first time we met.
At first...
I thought
you're not into guys.
Until...
You were dating IG.
I don't like all men.
IG is a special case.
If my dad knows....
that I'm dating a huy...
he must have hated me so much.
What if it's not IG?
You father loves me so much.
I think...
we can date.
But I don't like you that way.
I only think of you as an older...
Ruk!
Don't interfere!
Ruk...
why did you do this to me?!
Remember this!
- IG
- Ruk.
It's not like what you think!
♪ If love can easily be removed ♪
♪ Like files in a memory card ♪
♪ I would have completely forgotten
the pain when I'm almost suffocated ♪
♪ I still remember everything on
that day when you took her with you ♪
♪ I fell down and crying on the floor ♪
♪ I want to stand and
watch while you leave ♪
♪ But I'm unable to, as I
still remember those pains ♪
♪ It passed the dangerous point ♪
♪ Am I still alive? ♪
♪ I don't have you with
me it's like I only have a body ♪
♪ But has no life in it ♪
♪ Maybe a merit can keep my life go on ♪
♪ I'm struggling to survive ♪
♪ It's dangerous ♪
♪ If love can easily be removed ♪
♪ Like files in a memory card ♪
♪ I would have completely forgotten
the pain when I'm almost suffocated ♪
♪ I want to stand and
watch while you leave ♪
♪ But I'm unable to, as
I still remember those pains ♪
♪ It passed the dangerous point ♪
♪ Am I still alive? ♪
♪ I don't have you with me
it's like I only have a body ♪
♪ But has no life in it ♪
♪ Maybe a merit can
keep my life go on ♪
♪ I'm struggling to survive ♪
♪ It's dangerous ♪
♪ I want to stand and
watch while you leave ♪
♪ But I'm unable to,
as I still remember those pains ♪
♪ It passed the dangerous point ♪
♪ Am I still alive? ♪
♪ I don't have you with me
it's like I only have a body ♪
♪ But has no life in it ♪
♪ Maybe a merit can keep my life go on ♪
♪ I'm struggling to survive ♪
♪ It's dangerous ♪
If I'm not good enough,
be straight with me.
Don't date two people at once!
What the fuck are you doing?
P', haven't you seen
IG's uploaded status?
Why are you so over-the-top
when just reading his status?
It must have a little feeling into it.
IG called and told me...
he accidently saw
Ai'Ruk kissing P'Tunwa.
Kissed P'Tunwa?
Oh, man. How could he do that?
Also, P'Tunwa is really like a ghost.
If he wants to come out, he come out.
When he disappeared,
it's fucking hard to find him.
So, how's P'IG holding up now?
IG...
is still in the acceptance stage.
How?
When our bodies...
face heartbreaking situation...
it will produce a
type of stress hormones.
You, you...
Why do you have an orgasm?
As far as our brains...
it will stop producing happy hormones.
Including dopamine...
and endorphin.
So that grief comes in five stages.
One, accepting the truth.
Second, anger.
Third, coaxing the other party.
Fourth, depression.
So Ai'Ruk and IG...
has been in a conflict for a while.
Ever since they
came back from Nong Saeng.
So I think, he should
be in the fifth stage.
That is to brace
himself and acceptance.
Then back to normal.
Wait, wait!
Hold on.
Do you-want some mint?
Just a minute.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
I'm your senior, you motherfucker!
I'm sorry.
I have a plan.
What plan?
I think we need to do a presentation...
of us doing research at Nong Saeng.
The teacher should see how difficult it is...
for us to get the money,
P', you're very wise.
You really deserves to
be the star of our school.
I think this event...
we will surely succeed.
Why are you unhappy?
Sawasdee krub,
o our beloved principal.
to our beloved principal.
I am the cheerleader
representative of Chatreemit.
We went to Nong Saeng Village
A small village in the northern region.
While there, we had the support of
one particular kind-hearted elder.
We, with all our heart
and strength, did our best.
So we're able to make...
20,249 baht.
So we would like to ask you, Mr. Principal
to help us fill our budget to 100,000 baht.
To support us making our
cheerleading activities this year...
the best we can.
ОК.
Turn on the light.
No way.
I've already made my decision.
And it is final.
I don't agree
with this project anyway.
Jaturamitr Samakkee event...
it comes and goes.
Especially for you, Mes.
You're in 12th grade now.
Use your time to study.
Prepare for your exam.
You should make good
use of your current time.
We have money!
We will have enough, I mean.
It's time for me
to show my killer skills!
You won't expect this for sure,
I'd tell you that.
You won't be able to guess it.
What is wrong with you?
IG!
Can't you see that?!
Pass the ball, IG!
What the hell!
What the hell are you doing?!
Shit!
Gui, why didn't you guard the goal?!
IG, why didn't you pass it to Ruk?!
IG! Pass over!
IG!
How can you not see it?!
Move, let me do it.
Why did you snatch the ball from me?!
What are you playing, IG?!
What are you playing at?
Shit, what the fuck are you doing?!
Don't tell IG that we
were insulting him just now.
OK, OK, sit down.
IG did good.
- It's good.
- It's alright.
How are you? Tired?
A little.
Tired?
Let me buy you
some sweet drinks for you.
Sweet drinks.
I want to drink too.
- It reeks of love in here.
- Fangkao.
No need.
No big deal, I'll buy it.
It'll only take a sec.
Wait a moment, OK.
She's buying him a drink.
Reeks of love in here.
I'm thirsty.
Why are you guys so busybody?
What the hell are you playing?!
- Ai'Ruk, calm down.
- What the fuck?
I told you to pass it to me,
why didn't you?!
I didn't hear you!
How can you not hear it, IG?!
Hey, take it easy!
Don't bring your personal
issue into the game, IG!
That's my business!
Really? Your business?
Yes!
IG!
Calm down.
Let me go!
Ai'Ruk.
What's wrong with you?
Look at your friend there.
Calm down, calm down.
You're home, big boy?
Mom, Sawasdee kha.
When did you arrived?
Just a moment ago.
By the way, Fangkao...
Me and Fangkao are dating again.
You're together again?
That's good.
Ruk was kissing another guy?!
Is that true?!
It's true, Mom.
So...
So what next?
I broke up with him.
You really did?
If I didn't...
how can I bring
Fangkao home with me?
Did you really broke up?
Mom...
Are you deceiving yourself?
You brat.
I raised you, how can I not know...
when my son is really happy...
and when you're lying to yourself?
For us to meet the right person...
it's difficult.
And when we did...
we need to treat them properly.
Fooling other people... you can.
But lying to your own heart...
Think about it.
I'm worried.
Krub.
Very beautiful.
Everything is beautiful.
Beautiful.
Everything from the food and
the person are all beautiful.
Look, my dressing is very beautiful.
Beautiful dress that's
suitable for the Isaan lady.
The food also looks good.
Mom.
What are you wearing?
Today is the Cultural Day.
Cultural?
Yes.
It's our family's cultural day.
Who created this?
Grandma, of course.
Come now, here.
Let's tie this.
It's the Northearn region culture day,
so we need to appear as one a little.
Handsome.
Very handsome.
The mother's beautiful, the
son will definitely handsome.
We have to fit in with the culture.
Have a sit, what do you think?
The food looks so delicious.
I've prepared some traditional.
Wait, we'll eat together.
Wait until I unwrap these.
ОК.
Fangkao has been
calling so many times.
Really?
She didn't call your phone?
Let me check.
She did.
I didn't checked my phone.
Let me take care of it.
- Let me do it.- Wait.
Come, let's eat.
There's a phone call.
Sawasdee kha, my name is Khet
from Thai Tape recording company.
Yes.
I saw a clip of you and your
friends' music performance.
No need to smile like that.
People might accuse
me of having no decency.
Won't want to let
you walk home naked.
Thank you.
Wash, yourself.
Come son.
What's on you mind?
I want to thank you...
to be nice with Grateen.
I'm not that of a heartless person.
Just be nice with my son...
then I'll love them all.
As for what happened earlier...
why did the kid
threw eggs at Grateen?
He saw me...
Just be honest with me.
He saw me and Grateen...
He saw me and Grateen... kissing.
But I understand.
People doesn't understand
this kind of thing easily.
True.
I will try to make
the student's parents...
accept me.
Most importantly...
I will make you accept Grateen too.
It's alright son.
Just do whatever you want.
I just want you to be...
a good person in the society, OK?
Don't create any trouble for anyone.
Love and take care of each other.
Thank you.
Who's coming?
Go see who's coming.
Yes Dad.
Thank you so much.
I don't know who
to depend on anymore.
When I get my salary this month...
I'll immediately pay you back.
It's alright.
We're friends.
We should help one another.
It's no bi deal at all.
So...
when Tunwa came
back did you get to see him?
He won't dare to face me.
Why?
It's because of the state I'm in.
Because of his debt...
that I have to constantly moving
from one lace to another.
To the point that I
don't know where to go.
ย He's been gambling ever
since he entered the university.
He spent all the money.
Even the car and the house...
he sold them all.
I forbid him but he never listen.
When his mother got ill,
we had no money for treatment.
When she died...
he came back to me.
So now...
where is he staying?
He's staying in Bangkok.
I heard that he's been cheating
on people's money to pay his debt.
I think...
you (P'Roong) should report this, so...
you won't have to be responsible for it.
You have a son too right?
Who has the stomach
to do that to their sons?
Ruk...
how are you now?
Cheat?
P'Tunwa?
Yes.
I was confused like a
chicken with damaged eyes.
I was pondering day and evening.
Right now...
I can't sleep all day.
At first, I wanted to this a secret.
But I remembered that our
friends came here with him right?
Yes.
The God Guys Gang.
That's the name?
Yeah, them.
If he also cheats on kids...
then he's an asshole.
So is he still bothering you now?
Worse than mosquitoes.
He kissed me.
Kissed?!
He did that too?
So what did you do about it now?
At that time I was shocked.
But what's more shocking is...
IG found out.
He probably hates me now.
He won't be angry at
you if he knows the truth.
When will I get the
chance to talk to him?
He avoids me when he sees me.
When I look for him he runs away.
I don't know what to do.
Grateen told me...
"Slow and stead
will dominate the world".
Seriously...
that applies to you.
This formula doesn't work on IG.
Dude...
I'm back to ether with Grateen now.
Really?
It's not just a normal back together.
Dad is talking nicely with Grateen now.
I think...
he can't accept it 100%.
He probably doesn't
want to see us suffer.
we're still young.
Follow your heart
I believe that one day...
Dad will understand us.
I'm gonna hang up now.
But before that can
I take a screenshot?
I miss my brother.
Yeah, yeah.
Make a proper face.
OK.
See you.
Sure, sure.
Thank you.
See you.
Sawasdee ja, kids.
Sis Suang?!
You kids are all look radiant.
How's your cheer training?
What was the event again?
Jaturamitr Samakkee.
That's right.
When you finish with it,
please show it to me.
How can we finish it?
Because the money...
is only enough for tutoring.
Tutoring?
Yeah, that's what I said.
What is this?
I gave you 200,000,
is that still not enough?
You're a middle school
students, don't overspend it.
200,000?
How dare you say that?
Cheater!
We only got 20,000
120,000!
What?!
I gave Tunwa 200,000!
Here, I have prove.
Here, look at the transaction slip.
See?
Shit!
That means you've been
deceived by Tunwa.
He told me to transfer it
to him and he'll pass it to you.
So is there anything
we can do about this?
Can you help us?
In that case...
regarding Tunwa...
I'll use my contacts to
get him out and handle this.
As for you guys...
no need to interfere.
I'll handle him myself!
I'm sorry for misunderstands you.
- We're sorry too.
- We're really sorry.
Fuck.
P'...
since Sis promised us,
should-we-get back to our cheer activities?
Yeah, that's right.
I got goosebumps,
I think this time...
we will definitely succeed.
It'd be awesome.
Amen to that.
Sa-thu.
Wait, wait.
Don't get to happy about it yet.
If Sis Suang able to catch P'Tunwa...
does that means...
we can get the money?
Think about it.
If Sis Suang able to catch P'Tunwa...
she'd be wanting him to pay her back.
So...
I think it would be too late.
We'd definitely won't be able
to catch up with the football event.
I think the best way is,
we'll go ask him ourselves.
Oh, P'...
Let me tell you,
to get in contact with P'Tunwa...
is extremely difficult.
Lately...
we called, he didn't answer.
We LINE text him...
he didn't reply.
He's a fucking ghost.
Exactly.
I know where to find P'Tunwa.
Kaengsom.
What are you looking at?
I'm looking at our future.
This will help us
get back the 200,000.
Ai'Tong.
Let's go.
I can't take it anymore.
He's out of it.
P', wait for me!
What you guys up to?
You're acting like kids.
We're looking for your
brother's classmates book.
It's here.
Here.
What are you doing?
Be quiet.
P'Kaengliang?
'What are you doing in
Mom's room, Ai'Kaengsom?
We want to find P'Tunwa's address.
He's in the same class as you.
What for?
We're having some
problem with P'Tunwa.
You got tricked by him, didn't you?
How do you know?
Any senior knows about this.
But most senior from
his class all praised him.
That's your senior.
Ai'Tunwa...
after graduating, he broke
contact with all of his friends.
If when we can contact
him is when he is in trouble.
But he's good person.
Well-behaved.
He won't tricked us.
He will target you people.
By the way...
how did you get to know him?
You again?
The book that you're holding...
is the class that were ages ago.
You guys can go home now.
I'll help you find it.
I'll let Kaengsom pass it to you.
Alright, P'.
Thank you, P.
I knew that he's an asshole.
P'...
It's P'Tunwa's address.
Shall we go and burst in?
Take it easy.
If he's carrying a gun...
someone might die on this.
Careless.
I'm just hot-blooded youth, P'.
P'...
are you doing another party?
What party?
There.
See?
Shit.
I know now...
how to find Ai'Tunwa.
There.
♫ Just by walking here it's
enough knowing that you look ♫
♫ You look, loo and look at
me until my eyes stares like hers ♫
♫ I'm not here with anyone ♫
♫ I came alone and only want to have fun ♫
♫ Just walk in here to forget
about the person who left me ♫
♫ I’m not rich like others ♫
♫ I don't have what others do ♫
♫ I just wanna say that a guy
like me only have true love ♫
♫ I will never abandon you ♫
♫ Nor make you sit in sadness ♫
♫ Even though I’m not handsome,
my heart is sincere ♫
♫ I will give all my heart to you ♫
♫ In my life right now, I only have you ♫
♫ please don’t leave me aside
and pulverize my heart ♫
♫ I met you when I didn't have anything left ♫
♫ Will you accept me on the
day I don't have anything left? ♫