[10 days ago]
[Congratulations on your 70th Birthday Party]
Your mother's tastes are still the same.
No, she is more obsessed with
defi than bulk lately.
Defi?
Definition.
Definition of muscle tone?
Never mind, just give her the gift.
- You think she'll like it?
- Nothing is good enough for my Mom.
Still. What do you want me to say?
Just give her the gift already.
It's my money, after all.
Anyway, what is it?
Don't you think that's a bit small?
Something she can use
when she signs the contract.
A fountain pen.
With her initial.
Studded with diamonds.
Made in Germany.
- Excuse me.
- Hi.
Happy 70th birthday.
- Oh.
- I got this gift for you.
- You can use it when you sign.
- Did they come?
You're here.
Here, have some food.
What about my money?
Do you think she'd be as generous with me
if I took my shirt off?
- But you don't have the body for it.
- So?
Alright, I get it.
Let's step outside and talk.
Mrs. Jeon!
What's wrong with you? Why are you calling her?
What do you mean?
I have to ask her for the money you owe.
Her only son-in-law might lose his organ
because of the private loans.
I told you to wait a little while.
You should mind your manners.
My manner? Yes, manner.
Wait for a sec. It hurts.
Fine, fine.
You have one week.
Tell your mother-in-law, you idiot.
Or I'll do it for you.
[Real Capital &amp; Global Partners]
[Regarding Su Jong's Debt]
Now you can say
your final goodbye to the deceased.
Now, please excuse us.
Hey, what are you doing?
Hey, didn't you say
you'd be at the funeral all night?
Oh, I came to get something.
Sure, go ahead.
Isn't that your wife?
What happened? Why is she here?
I kidnapped her.
Excuse me?
What does that mean?
Like I said, I kidnapped her.
How much did you lose?
Is that important?
You got money?
Are you out of your mind?
What have you done?
It's not too late, so just take her home.
I'll call a cab. Okay?
If someone finds out,
just tell them you rescued her.
Are you crazy?
Rescue her? Do I look like Tom Cruise?
Listen to me.
I'm being serious here.
This is my last chance.
You are not making any sense.
We can't let people
walking all over us anymore.
I'll let you in.
500 million won.
No, it's not right.
I'll contact Gyun's friend and find a way out.
Su Jong.
Su Jong!
It's not what you think.
I'm just getting my money in advance.
I will inherit it anyway.
As long as I get paid, no one gets hurt.
There's no need to feel guilty.
- Hey.
- So annoying.
Hey, give it back.
- No.
- Give me my phone. Come on, give it back.
I said give my phone back.
I said no, I said no. I said no!
Hey, let it go!
Come on!
Hey, are you okay?
What the hell?
Why did you take my phone...
Here, take it.
Suit yourself.
Have fun living with all that debt.
That's not very nice.
Look what you did, you asshole.
I'm bleeding!
Let's stop the bleeding and get it disinfected.
This is so annoying.
I'll take care of everything else, okay?
You just need to look after
my wife in the freezer. Just two days.
Two days...
You need to...
inject...
this syringe three times a day.
But is she going to be okay?
Hey.
It's safe.
She's my wife, after all.
Have you decided?
It's really safe, right?
I can't believe I'm actually doing this.
You're freezing.
I am sorry.
[Dad, where are you?]
[I'm in the building, but you are not around.]
Hey.
What's going on?
It's too dusty in there.
[Mom's not doing well.]
Yes, right.
Let's go home.
[Mom, please eat some.]
[Dad brought your favorite porridge]
[from Buam-dong.]
Da Rae.
I can see that.
Do you have anything to say?
I am sorry.
That's it?
I'll try to do better.
I am not talking about that.
Something is off with you lately.
You and Gyun were like brothers.
But you didn't shed
a single tear at the funeral.
And you were preoccupied with something else.
Even after the cremation, you just disappeared.
How could you do that?
Aren't you sad at all?
Gyun is...
Gyun is dead.
I know you're worried about the building.
But what is the most important thing?
It's family.
You should be there for us.
Be there when we need you.
You look terrible.
Let's get you changed.
Thank you.
You must be a trendsetter
if you're looking around here.
You know this cafe?
- It's the hottest spot in the area.
- Hello, there.
Hello, sir!
Let's look at the vacant room
on the second floor and then the basement.
- Do you want to use a refrigerated warehouse?
- Yes, I want to see.
Let's order some boiled pork
and tofu kimchi for you.
This place hasn't changed.
Gyun loved this place.
I know.
He really loved boiled pork here.
The building owner isn't answering the phone.
Let's check the second floor.
What happened to the money for
Da Rae's school in abroad?
I had to use it for something else,
but I'll get it back soon.
[You went too far this time, Dad.]
I'm sorry, darling. I will make it up to you.
Trust me.
From now on, tell me everything.
I want to help.
Of course.
[Hee Ju, Real Estate,
Someone wants to see the basement.]
Who is it?
It's the realtor lady.
- That woman with leggings?
- Yes.
I don't like her.
Why? She could be helpful.
Honey.
I need to use the bathroom.
- Here we are.
- Yes.
Take a look at the rooftop too.
It's great, isn't it?
I liked the vacant room,
and this space is great too.
If you're interested, I can put in a good word
with the owner to help you get settled.
Please leave a message...
God damn it.
This area will grow even more
once it's redeveloped.
It's scheduled for redevelopment?
- Not this building.
- Good to hear.
Is the refrigerated storage in the basement?
Sure, just give me a second.
[Missed Call]
[Su Jong, Se Yoon Building owner]
The phone number
you have dialed is not available...
Would you like to see the basement
while you are here?
Sure.
Taxi!
What the hell is wrong with him?
Excuse me, my phone battery died.
Can I make a quick phone call?
Please? Just one call.
I'll give you 1000 won, please?
Taxi!
- What are you doing? I called this cab.
- What?
What the...
Unbelievable.
- Hi.
- Hi!
- Are you going down to see the basement?
- Yes.
Is that storage even working?
Why? It seemed fine.
I stored coffee beans there
but he asked me to take them out
to fix the storage.
Would you like to go check it now?
- You got the key?
- Of course.
Sure, I will go then.
Anyway, I've been calling him.
He was looking far ahead...
and set up this refrigerated storage.
He thought it would be helpful
to tenants one day.
You're pretty lucky, aren't you?
Doesn't it feel a little spooky, though?
Right?
Okay, let's see.
Is it this one?
I think I hear something.
What are you talking about?
You're being ridiculous.
I can really hear something. Right?
Maybe.
I hear nothing.
Come on.
Oh, it's this one.
Wait, wait, stop!
Oh my god!
You can't go in there.
You startled me!
You can't go in there without my permission.
You could get electrocuted.
Sorry, but you didn't answer the phone.
A water leak caused the short circuit.
Step aside.
Really?
- Seriously, you could have gotten hurt.
- Oh, that was the sound.
I have to get it fixed.
[Phyeongbuk Restaurant]
[Is he constipated or something?]
I'll check the bathroom.
- Is it you?
- Pardon?
Who is asking?
The phone number you have dialed
is not available...
Please leave a message after the tone.
You could've told me that earlier.
Sorry for not letting you know sooner.
So what's the deal with that storage?
The pipe burst, and it's completely flooded.
That's why I mentioned the electric shock.
That kind of thing actually never happens.
That's right.
But I can get it fixed easily
so don't worry about it.
Then let's check out the basement
some other time.
How's the refrigerated system working?
It works great with no issues.
If you sign the contract,
I'll handle the rest perfectly.
- He's a really good person, you can trust him.
- That's right.
He got this cafe tenant
with really good deals too.
Sure, please excuse me for a second.
This is the right place for you. He's...
- What's going on?
- Are you done?
How's my wife?
She's fine. I got her a blanket.
Oh, I forgot.
The syringe.
Hey.
Where is the syringe?
Take it out. Come on.
Where is it?
Huh?
[Refrigerated storage
Authorized Personnel Only]
God damn it.
This is ridiculous.
She's really strong.
You should've taken care of that.
Are you Okay?
When are you taking her back?
- When the time comes.
- Hey!
By the way,
there's something else you need to do.
What is it?
[If you want to save your wife,
get three billion won ready. I'll only talk to you.]
- I need to talk to them.
- Excuse me?
Why do you look so surprised?
They said they would only communicate with me.
You expect me to just
hand over three billion won?
That's not how deals work.
A deal?
- Your daughter is kidnapped...
- Then...
it's the...
biggest deal ever.
Do you know what is most important in a deal?
Seed money?
It's about your attitude.
If you let people think you're a doormat,
then that's what you become.
Can't you get that through your thick skull?
That sounds dangerous.
I'm done talking.
It's easy.
All you need to do is make the call and act.
- What acting?
- Pretend to be the kidnapper.
Call her tomorrow morning...
And tell her to meet me at 10pm
at the parking lot of Bukwang Sky Road.
This is not what we discussed.
You said you'll be here with money.
Things have changed, buddy. Is that so hard?
Just pretend you're in a movie.
What if she catches me?
She's a 70-year-old woman.
And this is a burner phone
so don't make any other calls on it.
[You are unbelievable...]
We've finished
all the administrative steps here.
What about the others
who are still holding out?
It's nearly done.
I sent the certificate of content proof
and it will be auctioned off soon.
What about the court?
We'll hire the appraiser
who got the order to match the amount.
Alright, next.
The Hanmaeum Building will take a bit longer.
She's from around here
and she won't listen to anything.
That old lady.
She's related to that old man, right?
So, when will you get it done?
I told you to secure
all the buildings scheduled
for redevelopment,
but you're not getting it done.
There was an accident recently
- and you told me to lie low.
- An accident?
You killed a cop.
Do you know how hard
it was to clean up your mess?
- There's a reason...
- A reason?
Are you trying to blame this on me?
Well...
Well?
I told you to finish the job, no matter what.
But no one can find out about Real Capital.
Don't you remember?
I do. I am sorry, sir.
Did you hear the news from headquarters?
What news?
Singapore.
They are getting all the focus now.
Singapore?
Don't you know what that means?
We're all screwed.
If this redevelopment gets delayed any longer
we are both finished.
Get it done.
Fast.
Fast and clean.
And do it legally this time.
Yes, sir.
What did he say?
Should I go ahead with the plan?
Hold on a second. He wants me to go easy.
This isn't the first time
we've killed someone here.
So, should I dig up the body
I buried in the basement?
No, that will look like an accident,
so don't worry.
Yes, ma'am.
Is there anything else?
Oh, we were supposed to have dinner together.
I've kidnapped your daughter.
No, that's not it.
I kidnapped your... Wait, who is that?
You're Ki Su Jong, aren't you?
[Real Capital &amp; Global Partners
Request for Repayment]
So 12% of one billion won is 120 million won?
What is going on?
Yeah, I can handle this.
Hi.
This is Jeon Yang Ja.
Put it on speakerphone.
Is anyone there?
Yes, nice to meet you.
Where's my daughter?
Where's your son-in-law?
Stop messing around and let me talk to her.
If you pay me, your daughter will come home
without a scratch.
Do you actually have my daughter?
Who kidnaps people like this nowadays?
You shouldn't yell at him like that.
Yi Gyeong! Sweetheart!
- Yi Gyeong!
- Take that off!
- Please don't touch her.
- Yi Gyeong!
Please, don't touch her.
Yi Gyeong...
[Unknown Number]
Hello.
Get three billion won ready.
Tonight at 10pm, Bukwang Sky Road parking lot.
See you there.
Tonight? Wait a second.
Listen to me.
He sounds like a professional.
He sounds like he knows what he's doing.
He said three billion won, right?
Yes, ma'am.
What if we put one billion in cash on top
and fill the rest with newspaper?
Sorry, what?
That's what they do in the movies.
If I put 10,000 won bills on top
it'll be hard for him to check.
That won't work.
We need to call the police.
If we make him angry...
it could put her life in danger...
Her safety has to come first.
[Divorce lawyer, Hwang Min Jeong]
It's always the same story.
Excuse me?
I stopped by just in case.
I'm not going to get a divorce anytime soon.
That's what you're thinking, isn't it?
Well...
That's how it starts.
You're a housekeeper?
- Yes.
- Any children?
She's going to college.
So you'll need money, then.
Excuse me?
You need to find out
how much can you get before the divorce.
Try not to let your feelings get in the way.
Identifying assets is the most important thing
and it helps if your husband is at fault.
Se Yoon Buliding...
[52 Sejeong-ro, Yongdaemun District, Seoul]
Se Yoon Buliding.
[Official land price KRW 2.4 billion
Debt 1.2 billion, Bank loan 1 billion Won]
There's nothing left but debt.
[I am a woman in my late 40s
who stopped working...]
[If you are in that situation, your
competitiveness in the job market is low...]
[What now? I am fighting against a world
worse than my cheating husband.]
You mean if the spouse is at fault?
It could be something like having an affair.
Hey, you did a great job.
Now all we have to do is meet her
and make the exchange
I'll bring the money, so you bring Yi Gyeong.
So don't call me from now on.
She might come along.
Then I guess I should bring that mask.
You're right.
- That's true.
- Yes.
She knows you, so don't say anything
when you're there.
Got it?
So you park your car over there...
- Give me 1.5 billion won.
- What?
Give me 1.5 billion won.
I think I've earned it.
[Seoul Yongdaemun Police Station]
Hey.
I found a video of Gyun's accident.
Want to see it?
Yeah? Where did you get it?
A delivery bike's black box caught it.
It's pretty far away and hard to see, but...
Hold on.
Look at this guy.
Zoom in on him.
Isn't that Gyun's brother-in-law?
It looks like him...
but there's no way.
- What are you all doing?
- Sir.
I was looking at the video of Gyun's accident
and found something.
- This guy right here...
- Look.
I know you're upset,
but it's just a hit-and-run.
The driver was already wanted.
Also about Jeong Chang Su, and Real Capital
Gyun was investigating...
I told you to drop it, remember?
But the circumstances are...
You can't go after a foreign company
without a good reason.
If you want to investigate
bring me some real evidence.
- Like Jeong Chang Su's body, for god's sake.
- Sir.
Forget about that...
We got a case so get ready to move.
Sir? What case all of a sudden?
Good, you guys all come with me.
Bo Ram, you too!
Where are we going? Sir, can you tell us?
Come on!
- Mr. Min, you are here.
- Hello.
Hey, put a wire on him.
Hi, could you take off your jacket?
Your jacket.
- Sure, here you go.
- I'll take that.
It's for your safety, so please bear with it.
There is a power button here. Press it
and turn it off when you go to the bathroom.
You must turn it on when we get there.
Would you put this in your ear?
Try not to be too nervous.
- Hwal Seong.
- Yes.
Just work with them.
Okay.
- Thanks for helping us out.
- No problem.
Why did you call the police?
I told you already...
You want me to just hand over
three billion won? Please.
Things could get really messy
if the police get involved.
Let the professionals take care of this.
Let's get going.
You all go ahead and wait. Ju Ran, Bo Ram,
and I will follow Mr. Min, alright?
Yes, sir.
Look.
Please make sure this gets done.
God, you really need to be more careful.
Things aren't like they used to be.
I can come with you, can't I?
You want to come too?
I can ride with you.
Oh, that's not really safe, though.
This is about my money and my daughter.
I will be in the car, so don't worry.
Yes, ma'am.
Don't worry. We'll be with you.
I need to use the bathroom.
The cops are onto us. Just stay on foot.
[T C A O U J S F]
We need to leave now to get there on time.
Okay, I'm coming out now.
God.
Sir.
Hey, Dong Gi.
Why didn't you ask me to help you?
- I didn't want to bother you.
- Come on.
Why is it so heavy?
There were a few things left.
Your brother-in-law's stuff?
Yeah, there's still a lot of stuff in there.
I need to clear it out soon.
Okay, come on.
You couldn't have possibly carried this alone.
This isn't working.
You pull, and I'll push from behind.
I'm exhausted.
Support the bottom.
- Okay, this is good, right here.
- Here?
Yes, thank you so much.
I am good now. Thank you.
I was wondering...
since...
I helped you move this
can you help me with something?
Help you with what?
Moving that plant over there.
- Sure.
- Right now.
- Yes.
- Okay.
My Mom saw this when she
went to Vietnam 22 years ago.
Back then, it was just a small seedling.
No, let's put this over there.
Anyway, she bought this seedling.
Oh my, good.
So after caring for it for 20 years...
She gave it to me when I opened this cafe.
She told me to let it grow naturally,
just like this.
What do you think?
Isn't it great with this cafe?
Yes, it looks fantastic.
- I should get going.
- You know what?
What?
The toilet is clogged again.
Then I should fix it for you.
When are you going to fix it?
I'll fix it this weekend, okay? Take care.
You need help?
No, I'm good.
He bought a car without telling me?
Please follow that car.
Go ahead, we'll follow behind you.
Where is he going?
Mr. Min, where are you going?
Sorry, my stomach is upset.
Sir, Mr. Min needs to use the bathroom.
Please go on ahead.
Got it, make it quick.
I'll take it out for a Moment.
Sorry about this.
Hey, what are you doing?
Is there a pay phone here?
What is a pay phone?
It's something you put coins in to make a call.
Why don't you use your cell phone?
- Let me borrow your phone.
- Excuse me?
Shit.
Damn it, it almost got me.
Please stop here.
Is that it?
Hey, when are Detective Ko and Mr. Min coming?
- Suspect is here.
- They will be here soon.
Tell them to hurry up.
That's it.
- That's the one.
- Pardon?
I should put this on.
Damn it, I can't see anything.
Why aren't you answering your phone, Su Jong?
Looks like he's not answering.
Can I have my phone back?
I need to send a text.
- What?
- Open the text panel.
- What text?
- Here, I don't have much time. Come on.
Hurry up.
Here.
What is this? What kind of key pad is this?
You enter the text.
Come on.
What do you want to say?
- The cops are onto you. Run.
- Excuse me?
No, it's nothing like that. Come on.
I think I might be running late.
Yes.
Well...
I'm trying to catch a kidnapper.
Yes, sure.
5,400 won, please.
Can I have a receipt?
Thank you.
- Have a good night.
- You too.
I can't see anything.
God damn it.
Why is he running so late?
Drive slowly towards the parking lot.
We'll be right behind you, so don't worry.
Sir, it's Bo Ram. We're here now.
- Will everything be alright?
- Don't worry.
Detective Ko, tell Mr. Min to just act normal.
Just try to relax and be yourself.
Come on.
What is he saying?
We have a suspect in sight.
- What? What the hell are you saying?
- Cops!
Stop messing around.
You got your money, right?
Put the money in the car
and give me back my wife.
- Why are you talking to me like...
- Stop it!
Stop talking! I don't want to hear it.
Where is my wife?
- Are you acting too?
- Where is my wife?
- Is your mother-in-law here?
- Come on! My wife!
My wife! Where is she?
- You crazy bastard.
- Where is she?
She's in the trunk.
Yi Gyeong, honey, come on.
Get ready to move in.
Secure all locations and stay ready.
Hey.
Hey, you can't get out of the car yet.
You have to catch him now.
What if he just runs off with my money?
What the hell is this?
You!
Come on!
I am so sorry!
Catch him!
Get him!
Open the door! Come on!
You are surrounded! Open the door!
Have you seen his face?
What happened to your hand?
It looks suspicious.
Do you understand what happened?
Your daughter was kidnapped...
- What is this?
- It's my backpack.
So what's in it?
Three billion won.
He took three billion won as ransom for you.
This is nice.
So, is this the criminal you saw last night?
You are under arrest
for robbery and kidnapping.
Let go! Get off of me!