(Connection)
(All characters, organizations,
and events in this drama are fictitious.)
Is Yoon Ho home?
(Jae Gyeong goes to Yoon Ho's house)
Do you remember our visit
to Lee Myung Guk's place?
Molotov cocktails were thrown in.
And Yoon Ho was the one who threw them.
Why would he?
Whoever left Lee's body there...
must have told Yoon Ho...
that the man he killed and buried...
was dug back up and placed at home.
Yoon Ho showed up at that house
to get rid of Lee Myung Guk's body.
Captain Jang, we'll get Jeong Yoon Ho.
You stay there.
Did the other detectives go to get him?
(He misses Yoon Ho because of the interference of Si Jung)
Run away.
Get out of there.
Detectives are on the way.
You can't get caught!
- Yoon Jin.
- Yes?
What character do you think this is?
The character for "pil"
that means necessary...
is used in the name, "Pilo-dong."
I think this is referring
to Jeong Sang Eui.
Youngryun Cold Storage.
I checked on the way.
Keumhyung Pharmaceutical owns
Youngryun Cold Storage.
There was nothing there when we went.
Most of them, I already knew about.
But one of them is weird.
(Ji Yeon came soon after)
Which one?
There was a pension insurance
that Jun Seo got 11 years ago.
And an old lady in her 60s in Boryeong
has been receiving the pension.
Yoon Jin!
(When Joo Song was celebrating Yoon Jin's birthday)
Happy birthday
(Ji Yeon is flustered when she finds out Yoon Jin's birthday)
Is today your birthday?
(The password that Ji Yeon and Joon Seo used together)
What is that?
It's just the one I've been using
for a long time.
Should we use that from now on?
(The password that Ji Yeon and Joon Seo used together)
(It was Yoon Jin's birthday)
What is this text about?
(When Yoon Jin found out the password, she called Tae Jin out)
I'll put in the password myself.
Once you transfer half of the
money to the account I want,
I'll return all these pictures and recordings back to you.
(Yoon Jin enters the password in exchange for half of the money)
Oh Yoon Jin!
(Taejin angered, attacked Yoon Jin)
Die!
(Joo Song appeared just in time to save Yoon Jin)
The guy came.
Please head over right away.
(The shop owner calls Jae Gyeong)
(Following Yoon's henchman, entering the old shopping district)
(Chang Soo was passing by in front of Jae Gyeong)
Kim Chang Soo.
What are you doing here?
(Jae Gyeong was flustered by Chang Soo's apperance)
(A gunshot was heard)
(They came to the scene immediately)
(Jae Gyeong finds out the secret room where he was drugged.)
(Questioning CEO Yoon)
Do you know Park Jun Seo?
Did Park Tae Jin put you up to it?
(She died)
Hey. Did you get me addicted?
I'll gather the evidence,
and return to the station first
with CEO Yoon's man outside.
If you keep the fact
that you saw me last time...
a secret until you die,
I'll let you get out after a short stint.
What's wrong with detectives these days?
One's a druggie,
- and...
- Shut your mouth!
(Eventually, Chang Soo jumps into the river with the intention to kill Gi Sung)
(Jae Gyeong arrived at the scene)
Chang Soo!
It was my mistake.
I thought it would be okay
to transport him alone.
(Feeling a bit suspicious)
(Investigating the scene)
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
Did anyone touch the window
by the driver's seat?
(Chang Soo had opened the driver's window)
No, we just got it out of the water.
Does that mean he went in the water
with the window open?
In this weather?
Did Chang Soo...
(Call history: Gong Jin Wook)
(Gong Jin Wook)
Hello?
Doctor, it's me.
What is it?
Well...
Today,
I killed CEO Yoon.
What?
So for a while,
you won't be able to sell in Korea.
I doubt you can find someone else.
For a while,
no one will be willing to sell.
I'll go to China.
I have connections there.
So...
Keep supplying me.
In return...
I need you to get me on a boat to China.
Mr. Gong.
I'm not asking for a free ride.
I'll send you two items
via subway courier very soon.
I'm sending them believing
they'll be of some value to you.
That's...
all I have right now.
Put the items in the back seat.
The money's in the envelope.
Okay.
This much?
(Connection)
(Episode 11)
They didn't get access to the account?
It looked like it.
Will Tae Jin be okay?
I don't know
where I got the guts to do that.
Yoon Jin was in so much danger.
How did she figure out the password?
At your place, when Ji Yeon
was throwing up in your toilet.
Yoon Jin got into Ji Yeon's phone.
That's why as soon as
Ji Yeon left my place,
she met with Tae Jin...
and asked him about Jun Seo and Yoon Jin?
She must be in all sorts of shock.
What did the doctor say?
She might be like that for a while
and we should watch her.
Does she need to be admitted?
No.
Oh Yoon Jin!
Die!
Don't you think you should see a doctor?
This CCTV video.
Delete it.
What?
Delete everything.
Delete it?
Okay, sure.
Two, three.
Four.
Eight.
Open up.
Chew.
Does it taste okay?
Good for you.
Here. Open wide.
It's okay.
It was too big.
You can't open your mouth wide.
I should give you very little.
You're doing this
because you're embarrassed,
but I have lots of questions,
so let's quit.
If you don't stand at the count of three,
I'll pull out your chair.
One, two...
What is it?
Do you need to pee?
Shall we go to the toilet?
What?
- Joo Song.
- Yes?
Next time,
add some kkakdugi sauce to my soup.
You kept feeding me bland broth...
and plain rice with nothing else.
Are you okay, Yoon Jin?
Can't you tell?
I only slightly sprained my neck.
Hey, was that an act? Darn you!
I was so worried about you!
I was embarrassed.
That's why.
- Sorry.
- Joo Song told me everything else.
What's the password for?
It can't be for a bank account.
It seemed to be
some kind of cryptocurrency.
Was it Thailand?
Did you check the site?
Yes.
They were weirdly funny.
The password is eight digits.
Tae Jin chose the first four,
and Jun Seo chose the last four.
They clearly didn't trust each other.
Does that mean
Tae Jin didn't kill Jun Seo?
He wouldn't have been so rash...
if he didn't have the password.
Tae Jin would've thought
he could get the code from Ji Yeon.
But what now?
There are zero clues
as to what the password is.
They only have one try left.
That money.
It's possible Jun Seo and Tae Jin
made it from selling drugs.
Were you going to...
make a deal with Tae Jin knowing that?
I know, right?
I'm remorseful, okay?
I'll let you scold me,
but will you let me at least finish...
my food?
Thanks. I was starving.
Someone called "Doctor" appears...
in the Lemon Mulberry investigation.
The manufacturer.
Do you remember Lee Myung Guk's logs?
He met Jeong Sang Eui
regularly at a lab...
in Pilo-dong and did something.
What they made then...
was Lemon Mulberry?
At first, they'll have made
small batches just for Jong Soo.
Then...
Lee Myung Guk manufactured it,
Jun Seo delivered it,
and Jong Soo took it?
I can follow that far.
But...
where does Tae Jin come in
when he's not in this picture?
Manufactures, delivers, and takes.
It's a simple picture
and Tae Jin's not in it.
Jun Seo was the courier.
Why did he switch roles
and start a drug business with Tae Jin?
Hey, that's sharp.
Thanks.
Because of who and what he is,
Tae Jin would've planned it
so he was never at the forefront.
He'd have used Jun Seo.
And Jun Seo who felt uneasy about it...
would've thought
he should have at least...
the last four digits of the code
to keep Tae Jin in check.
What about now that Jun Seo is dead?
Without Jun Seo,
who's delivering Jong Soo's supply,
and who's running
the Lemon Mulberry business...
Tae Jin used to?
Hey.
(Xinopharm)
Good job.
Thanks.
(Jang Jae Gyeong)
What brings you here at this hour?
I had something to ask you.
I met Oh Yoon Jin last night.
Why do you think...
I met with her?
I'm not sure.
Did you know?
Yoon Jin also knew...
the password.
Was it right?
Was it...
really the password?
Tae Jin.
Tae Jin!
(Jeong Sang Eui)
- What is it?
- Can you talk right now?
Go ahead. What is it?
Well, something big happened...
- Something big?
- Yes.
CEO Yoon, the person
who Gong Jin Wook did business with...
You idiot!
Don't you ever listen to what I say?
I told you not to talk about
this stuff over the phone, didn't I?
Oh, right. Sorry.
Sang Eui.
How much longer will you act
like such a dumb fool?
Hey, I'm sorry. It was so urgent that I...
Hey, then where should we meet?
Should I come to you?
Tomorrow at 4 p.m.
Come to Myeongeul Garden.
You remember
the place we had dinner last time?
Oh, okay.
(Tuesday, March 7)
(Yigu Group Han Sung Hoon)
Hey, how did it go?
For real?
Okay, got it. Good work.
What was it?
Did the board approve?
Yigu Group...
is giving us 500 million dollars.
You scared me.
We're all set, you punk!
We're set.
Now, as soon as Mayor Joo In Sang
signs off on it,
this will all be ours, Chi Hyun.
Of course.
I'm sure Joo In Sang won't have
any reasons to oppose this.
Good work.
Seriously.
Gosh!
(Prosecution Service)
Is that so?
That's good news.
Congratulations.
Of course, I should be there too.
See you later.
Bye.
Have a seat.
What brings you all the way here?
You didn't even call.
I thought you wouldn't show up
if you were called in as a testifier.
What?
That's your number, right?
So?
This is a list of calls
Jeong Yoon Ho made...
from a payphone the night before last.
Why do you think Yoon Ho called you?
What do you think?
Park Tae Jin.
I'm asking because I'm curious too.
A friend from high school
who's wanted for murder...
called in the middle of the night
from a payphone.
What do you think we talked about?
It's obvious.
"On what grounds was I named
a murder suspect?"
"Couldn't you help me out somehow?"
So?
I told him to turn himself in.
Don't you think
you would've done the same?
Let me know right away
if Yoon Ho calls you again.
Don't make me find out first
and come looking for you.
- All right.
- Also,
what happened last night?
You nearly killed Yoon Jin.
You already deleted the CCTV footage
from the Internet cafe.
Did you kill Jun Seo?
I'm a prosecutor.
This kind of shock method...
might work on guys like
Jeong Sang Eui or Oh Chi Hyun.
But you must know
that it doesn't work for me.
You heard...
that we were there that night.
You must be confused.
You must be so sure that one of us
did that to Jun Seo,
but Jun Seo had to fall
when we were all inside the elevator.
You can't prove a direct murder, right?
You must've had to
use your brain a bit for this one.
But it's too bad...
that Jun Seo left without telling you
the password.
Judging by the scale
of the Lemon Mulberry business,
it must be worth
at least ten million dollars.
It must be such a waste.
Right?
Are you the Doctor?
Did you drag me into this?
"Drag you in?"
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Lemon Mulberry and what? The Doctor?
What is all that about?
That's right.
You'd have to say that you don't know.
I might be recording our conversation
right now.
I'm warning you.
Judging by my gut feeling,
I think I'm nearly there.
I think I could catch you
if I just reach my hand out.
From now on,
when you make your next move,
be extra careful.
At this rate,
you'll get caught by me.
(Chairman, Won Chang Ho)
Come in.
(Keumhyung Group)
Have you heard?
It's 500 million dollars.
I was hoping for 200 or 300 million...
at the most.
Doesn't 500 million dollars mean...
Yigu Group believes in this project?
I just spoke to Chairman Han on the phone.
He has high hopes for this project.
He looks forward to it.
I see.
We only need the business approval
from the city now.
When are you seeing Mayor Joo?
We're meeting for lunch tomorrow.
The situation is different
from the last time,
so I'll make sure to bring good news.
As you should.
What is it?
How are things between you
and Tae Jin these days?
Good. Why do you ask?
Tae Jin told me...
he'd like to join...
the Pilo-dong project as an investor.
Pardon?
Oh, that?
He mentioned it briefly before.
He must know a few people
who have money around him.
He must be talking about them.
I already checked.
How much longer will you rely on Tae Jin?
You should've figured this out already
and have it sorted out.
I told him not to get any ideas
and to remain a prosecutor,
but he already had his head in the clouds.
Act oblivious for a while.
Just quietly put a man on him.
Okay.
Should I give you two some privacy?
Yes. Thank you.
(Fragrant Express,
Number 1 in customer satisfaction!)
Did you capture all of them?
Yes, all thanks to you.
Unfortunately,
except for the main culprit,
we caught everyone else.
I see.
Okay.
If you have something to say,
please go ahead.
Have you ever smuggled anyone out?
Yes, when I was young.
- To where?
- China.
You have the contacts
of other smugglers, right?
We lost contact a long time ago.
It was ages ago.
I'm sure you can easily find out
if you ask someone.
Hey.
Even if in this line of work,
people change jobs often.
The guys I used to know...
are either behind bars or dead now.
Just look into it.
One should live a clean life
from the beginning.
It's so hard...
when you try to switch over.
That's exactly my point.
You scare me.
- Young Eun.
- Mom!
How did you manage to come?
I thought the police wouldn't let you out.
I sneaked out.
I went to see Dad.
Mom!
He's well.
What if they catch you on your way back?
I waited for you
so we could go in together.
It'll be okay
if I go back with my daughter.
Is anyone there?
No.
Great. Let's go.
What should we have for dinner?
I don't know.
Ms. Kang Si Jung.
Where have you been?
I went to meet my daughter.
Can't you tell?
We'll have to take you in.
Thanks for your hard work today.
Hey, you have no excuse to be tired.
Of course, I'm tired.
I worked hard to earn money today.
I can't understand it either.
I don't know why he used my birthdate
as the password.
We only dated briefly in high school...
You can barely call that dating
these days.
If I had been in your position,
I would've felt offended too.
I understand, but...
You're right. I was offended.
But I thought about it
upon returning home,
and they were all excuses I had made up
for myself.
To be honest,
the seven years of our married life...
Our dear Yoon Hee...
was sick ever since she was born,
but we were happy then.
Then Yoon Hee passed away.
I was lonely,
and Tae Jin approached me.
I was tempted for a while...
but believed it would soon pass.
It somehow turned this way.
Before Jun Seo died,
did he know...
about you and Tae Jin?
Yes.
(February 13, 2024)
Are you still up?
Why did you wait up?
I'm going to bed.
Ji Yeon.
When did it begin?
What?
Did it happen...
before Yoon Hee left?
Or after?
Does that matter?
I'm sorry.
I don't think it matters.
When was that?
About ten days before my husband died.
Tae Jin came to me this morning...
and realized that the password I had
was the same as yours.
He then turned around and left.
I had to part ways with Yoon Hee
and then Jun Seo.
I was scared
of having Tae Jin leave me too.
I wondered how he would act...
once I told him the password.
I was afraid he'd leave me.
I wasn't sure how I'd survive
in this world alone.
Yes.
So this was where I ended up.
It's what I rightfully deserve.
That was the thought in my head.
(Anhyeon Police Station)
Captain.
Kang Si Jung's most recent call
reached somewhere in Inju-dong.
The other person used a burner phone.
Can you track the location of that number?
Yes, it's possible.
Do you want me to go in instead?
I'll do it.
Is Yoon Ho well?
You went to Inju-dong this morning.
Is Yoon Ho there?
Si Jung.
Yoon Ho is in a dangerous state.
We don't know who he'll harm next.
We must get him to turn himself in.
Jong Soo, Tae Jin, and Chi Hyun.
They're not interested in helping him.
If you have hopes
that they'll help out, you're mistaken.
Even right now,
the only one who can save Yoon Ho...
is you.
He didn't even ask.
If the kids and I were doing okay.
If any of us had been scared.
Or how I'd found him.
He didn't ask any of that.
All he said was...
"Have you heard from Chi Hyun?"
"Why haven't you done anything?"
"You should've gone
to Jong Soo or Tae Jin."
"What were you doing at home?"
That's all he said.
I got upset...
and asked if he wasn't worried
about me or the kids.
He told me not to worry
because Tae Jin and Jong Soo...
wouldn't ditch him this time.
The moron.
Would they have let it come to this
if they were going to help?
Do you know whose fault it was...
when Yoon Ho first went away for murder?
That was on Won Jong Soo too.
I went to him so many times...
and begged for his help.
I pleaded to him.
Only Chi Hyun and Jun Seo
visited him in prison.
Can you...
bring Yoon Ho in...
so he doesn't get hurt?
Can you give me your word?
Pine Motel in Inju-dong.
Pilo-dong murder suspect Jeong Yoon Ho.
He's hiding at Pine Motel in Inju-dong.
Send backup.
Your kids are home alone, right?
I'll get someone to drive you.
(Jeonghaejang Motel)
He checked out two hours ago.
What about his phone signal?
It's still in the neighborhood.
He'll have gone to another motel.
Send his description...
- to the patrol units.
- Okay.
We'll visit nearby motels.
- Get to it.
- I'll go this way.
This suspect's in the neighborhood,
so be on the lookout.
Hello, it's the police.
We won't enter the room.
We just want a peek.
Excuse us.
Excuse us. Sorry.
(A1 Motel)
Sang Eui. Come on in.
Hey, Sang Eui.
You're in a coat?
Looking good.
Something great happened today,
so I called my friends
who suffered with me for a drink.
Sang Eui you were always researching,
manufacturing, and now delivering too.
- You were busy, right?
- Yes.
Take a seat.
I didn't say you could sit.
Sang Eui.
Did you meet with Jae Gyeong?
Yes.
I knew it.
You told Jae Gyeong...
we were all there...
the night Jun Seo died?
Yes, but I just...
It's okay. You did great.
But you should watch what you say now.
Because of what you said,
Jae Gyeong came to me and strutted about.
Right. Sorry.
From now on, can you lot watch out...
so I don't have to put up with that again?
Especially you.
From now on,
if Jae Gyeong says something,
talk right back at him.
Why worry when I'm behind you?
- Right?
- Yes.
Oh, Prosecutor Park. Welcome.
Our hidden mastermind.
Prosecutor Park Tae Jin.
You did well planning all this.
I'm sorry to be a party pooper.
When will you meet Mayor Joo?
You are a party pooper.
That name is banned in my house,
you know.
I'm meeting him for lunch tomorrow
with Vice President Han.
It won't be like last time.
I hope so.
Let's have a toast.
To the great success...
of the Pilo-dong venture!
- Cheers.
Since I pooped on the party,
I'd like to speak with the group.
Hey, Sang Eui. Wait outside.
Okay.
(New recording)
What's this about?
I met Jeong Yoon Ho yesterday.
- Yesterday?
- Yes.
We met in a quiet place,
and I gave him some cash.
I told him to lie low
until things quietened down.
Jang Jae Gyeong came to see me yesterday.
He got all excited, I see.
He came to see me today.
What did he say?
The obvious.
So what about Jeong Yoon Ho?
The police are pretty sure...
he's guilty of murdering
Lee Myung Guk and the mill owner.
They have a car and CCTV tapes
that prove it was him.
Here's the problem.
Why he killed Lee Myung Guk,
where the body was kept frozen,
and why he killed the mill owner
and burned the CCTV server.
If the police keep digging,
eventually...
it'll lead to you.
What's the conclusion?
What do you want to do?
Jeong Yoon Ho.
He's too much of a risk.
Then what?
Do you really want to kill him?
Park Tae Jin.
Do you have a better idea?
I'm getting tired, to be honest.
We'd barely make it
even if we worked as a team,
but you lot keep messing up.
If something goes wrong,
you ask me to clean up after you.
Guys. What more can I do for you?
Hey. That's not right.
What did we come this far for?
It was so we'd all do well.
- But Yoon Ho...
- Hey.
You have no excuses.
Why did you kill Lee Myung Guk?
- Hey, that was...
- Don't use Jeong Yoon Ho as an excuse.
Did you ever consult with us...
that you were being threatened
by Lee Myung Guk?
You just make trouble first
without thinking,
and now what?
Are you asking us to understand
since you did it for a friend?
Oh Chi Hyun.
How many times is this already?
Did you perhaps...
use this chance
to do something to Lee Myung Guk...
because you had something rotten
to cover up?
What? "Something rotten?"
I mean,
who knows if you smuggled
Jong Soo's pills?
Hey, what are you doing?
Say that again. What?
Hey, Oh Chi Hyun!
If we dawdle, we're all done for.
If the police find him before we do,
we're all done for!
- Jong Soo.
- Jong Soo, this isn't right.
What's not right?
If we keep doing this,
we're all done for!
Won Jong Soo.
Let's think about this a little more.
- Jong Soo!
- "Jong Soo!" Give it a rest!
What do you want me to do?
You always bring me one choice
and ask me to choose.
Hey, if you come up with the answers
and ask me to decide,
isn't that an order?
That's always your problem.
Just hang on a little longer.
See what the police are up to.
If we really get backed into a corner,
let's decide then.
Darn it.
(You have one new voicemail.
Press the Call button to listen.)
(Dialing, Restricted number)
The police are pretty sure...
he's guilty of murdering
Lee Myung Guk and the mill owner.
Why he killed Lee Myung Guk,
where the body was kept frozen,
and why he killed the mill owner
and burned the CCTV server.
If the police keep digging,
eventually...
it'll lead to you.
Jeong Yoon Ho.
He's too much of a risk.
Do you have a better idea?
(You have a new message.
Would you like to check?)
The proof that
Park Tae Jin killed Jun Seo...
is with that woman
who lives at Jun Seo's place.
Yes, this is Oh Soo Hyun.
Is that so? Which direction is it?
Past Namho-dong, towards the new town?
We just got a ping from
Jeong Yoon Ho's phone again.
He's moving past Namho-dong
and headed towards the new town.
Let's hurry.
Hello?
It's me.
Hey, Jeong Yoon Ho.
Where are you right now?
Were you there too
when Park Tae Jin suggested killing me?
What?
You were there too, right?
Don't act dumb, you punk.
It sounded like he was talking to you.
How do you know about that?
Was Jong Soo there too?
No.
Jong Soo would've fallen
for Park Tae Jin again.
Hey, Yoon Ho.
Darn it. You traitors.
Hey, are you really my friend?
Are you really my friend?
It was all Park Tae Jin!
What?
Park Tae Jin planned everything,
you dumb punks!
I caught Park Tae Jin getting together...
with Jun Seo's wife. So, that's...
That's why he's trying to kill me.
Do you even know?
Gosh, you utter fools.
You were played by Park Tae Jin
your whole life,
but you don't even know a thing, do you?
Hey, Yoon Ho. First of all, calm down.
Where are you right now?
Tell me that first.
I'll be right there.
Why? So you can come and kill me?
Forget it, punk. Crazy jerk.
Yoon Ho.
I'm going to reveal everything.
Okay?
The fact that Park Tae Jin
killed our Jun Seo...
I'll reveal all of it,
even if I have to kill
that wench to do so.
Hey, Yoon Ho.
- Jeong Yoon Ho.
- Hey, Oh Chi Hyun.
Please deliver this message
to Mr. Park Tae Jin.
I won't go down easily this time.
We'll all die together.
Or we'll all live together. Got it?
Jeong Yoon Ho!
Why do you keep calling my name?
Yes.
The signal stopped
near Oeseong-dong just now.
I've just sent you
the exact location via text.
Oeseong-dong.
Nain Apartment in Oeseong-dong. Hurry!
What?
What brings you by at this hour?
Hey, Ji Yeon.
I have something to say to you
about Jun Seo.
One moment.
(Detective Jang Jae Gyeong)
Hello.
My gosh. Let's go.
What did you want to tell me
about Jun Seo?
Do you miss Jun Seo?
Pardon?
I miss Jun Seo.
I married Si Jung.
And Si Jung had a baby.
Our Young Eun.
But I hadn't found a job.
Then,
Jun Seo talked to Jong Soo,
and he got me a job
at one of Keumhyung's subcontractors.
But the CEO there...
was talking smack about Jong Soo one day.
I kept listening...
but couldn't stand it anymore.
I had had a few drinks,
and I hit him in anger.
But...
that man died.
What...
It's late tonight. If you come back...
Then, I got out of jail.
It felt as though the guys
were keeping their distance from me.
Even then, Jun Seo looked out for me.
He found me a job at the taxi company.
Looking back,
Jun Seo was different from the other guys.
I think...
he was a good friend...
to me.
Oh, I see.
So... I understand what you mean,
but you should get going...
So why did you do it?
Why would you leave
a nice guy like Jun Seo...
and do that with Tae Jin?
You killed Jun Seo with Tae Jin,
didn't you?
No.
I know you did.
I heard the evidence that shows
you killed Jun Seo with Tae Jin...
is here.
Where is it?
What do you mean?
Tae Jin is trying
to put all the blame on me...
and is planning to kill me.
Ji Yeon.
I can't just sit and watch.
Hand it over.
- I'll take the stairs.
- Okay.
Choi Ji Yeon.
Choi Ji Yeon!
Thank you for your time.
- What is it at this hour?
- Park Tae Jin.
- You know Jun Seo's passcode, right?
- What?
Hurry up and tell me.
Ji Yeon is in danger.
What's the door's passcode?
It's 9-1-9-1.
Ms. Choi Ji Yeon.
She's still breathing.
Call an ambulance right away!
I'm calling from Oeseong-dong's
Nain Apartment, Unit 503.
There's a patient here. Please hurry.
Jeong Yoon Ho escaped
via the emergency stairs.
Request support
from the nearby patrol unit.
I don't need it. I can do this.
Captain, do you remember the guy
who had drugs on him...
out of the men we arrested yesterday?
- Lee Jung Hoon.
- What about him?
He says he bought his drugs
from a guy named Kim Dae Sung,
and Kim Dae Sung...
is already under examination
by the Narcotics Unit.
So I wonder if we should ask them
to cooperate with us...
Hey.
- Go and get this guy.
- Pardon?
The Narcotics Unit always steals
our cases.
We can't just sit and watch.
Let's dig into this guy, Kim Dae Sung.
We'll find all the connections from him
from the ground up. Got it?
Take your grills out.
Take them out.
Chew with your real teeth.
What a joke.
Here. Have this too.
Enjoy your meal.
Eat slowly.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
By the way,
that captain of the Narcotics Unit...
is really something.
Who? Jang Jae Gyeong?
Yes...
Can't you read the room?
Keep your mouth shut and eat.
Punk.
What is it? Tell me?
What's so great about him?
That thing is really strong,
so it's not easy for an ordinary person
to stay sober with that drug.
And?
Drug?
What drug?
The day I was arrested,
Geun Ho drugged that detective...
with the new drug, Lemon Mulberry.
Geun Ho did it to check
if he was a detective or not.
He took in the full dose.
If you're not a druggie
and it's your first time,
most people faint.
But he threw me on the floor right away.
I totally respect him for that.
Hey, tell us more.
(Ambulance)
Are you getting a signal?
I think the phone is turned off.
We're searching the area
with the patrol unit.
Why did Jeong Yoon Ho come here?
Is there a reason for him
to kill Park Jun Seo's wife?
Do you have a hunch?
I also can't understand it.
The scene looked strange too.
He turned the place upside down
as if he was searching for something.
Also, if he really had wanted to kill her,
he could've done it in a flash
like the mill owner.
Aside from her head wound,
we didn't find anything else.
All the knives were untouched too.
Maybe he heard the siren...
and couldn't finish her off
before fleeing.
Maybe he staged it
like a robbery on purpose.
Which hospital is that ambulance heading?
To Anhyun University Hospital. Why?
I will drop by the hospital...
and check on the victim
before I head back.
Let me know if you find
Jeong Yoon Ho's whereabouts.
I will.
Captain. Do you want a ride?
I'm okay.
Ms. Oh!
- Hello.
- Why are you so busy these days?
You're never home.
I have a lot of work these days.
- Is everything well?
- Of course.
Here.
- What is this?
- You left your coat with me, remember?
The black one.
This was in the inner pocket.
(From Anhyun University Hospital,
Park Eun Young, To Park Jun Seo)
- Sorry for the long wait.
- Not at all.
(Dear Ma'am and Sir,)
Thank you.
Ms. Choi Ji Yeon's guardian?
Yes?
(Emergency Medical Center)
We ran through all emergency tests...
and aside from her head contusion,
she has a light concussion.
It's not life-threatening, is it?
No. But we'll run a few other tests
just in case.
We have an empty room,
so we'll move her there.
It'd be best to keep her here
until tomorrow.
I understand.
You look pale. Are you all right?
Your eyes are red.
I'm fine.
I'm just tired.
I see.
How is she doing?
Is it life-threatening?
Did you put him up to it?
Did you order him to kill Choi Ji Yeon?
Are you out of your mind?
What is it that you want?
How far do you have to go?
Which one of us do you need dead
for you to be happy?
What?
Did you sell drugs with Jun Seo?
You made Lee Myung Guk make drugs
in Youngryun Cold Storage.
But when he stopped listening,
you killed him,
and then you killed Park Jun Seo.
You ordered Jeong Yoon Ho
to kill the owner of the mill.
But that wasn't enough.
Now you're trying to kill the woman
you're having an affair with.
Do you call yourself human?
What nonsense are you spewing?
Why?
Why me? Why did you drag me into it?
What?
What are you trying to get from it?
You punk!
Darn it.
How dare you hit me?
What's wrong with you?
Are you on something?
Why would I kill Choi Ji Yeon?
Why would I kill Lee Myung Guk
or Park Jun Seo?
For what?
Hey. Stop deluding yourself.
Do you think I had an affair with her...
because of the password?
She doesn't even have a clue!
Hey.
Look at me straight in the eyes.
You accuse me of distributing drugs.
Do you have any proof?
Can you back anything you said?
Darn you.
You don't know anything.
If you dare touch me again,
I'll make sure the police let you go.
Try me again if you dare.
You're no game for me.
You almost choked me to death,
remember?
You only care about yourself, don't you?
Jang Jae Gyeong, are you all right?
(Connection)
He must have caused trouble.
Exactly.
(Jang Jae Gyeong,
forced to transfer schools)
(Science Lab 2)
Jang Jae Gyeong kept his back on us,
so I had him get transferred.
What about Jun Seo?
What should we do with him?
But Jun Seo chose...
our side.
Hey.
If my father hadn't threatened his dad...
to turn Jun Seo's mind around,
would he have chosen us?
I doubt it.
He should've never hung out
with Jae Gyeong, Yoon Jin, and Joo Song.
It was his fault. Don't you agree?
Jae Gyeong must know what happened...
at Kyung Tae's house...
because Jun Seo told him.
Jun Seo is the root cause of this problem.
Still...
- He's the class president.
- Enough with the class president!
The class president was the one
who ruined everything, Yoon Ho!
I think we should still accept him
as our friend.
I think he regrets it.
Let's do that, Jong Soo.
What do you think, Tae Jin?
Let's wrap it up
with having Jae Gyeong transfer.
There's no reason to blow this up.
He's right.
Let's do that.
Fine.
We'll let Jun Seo back in the group.
Is that enough?
Jun Seo and Yoon Jin...
They're still dating.
Then what can we do?
We'll have to make him end it on his own.
Come to Audiophile's club room right now.
I have to tell you something
about Jun Seo.
Hey, Park Jun Seo!
What are you doing?
Leave.
- Jun Seo.
- I said, leave.
Go!
Go! I said, go!
Don't ever call my name...
or talk to me.
Jun Seo.
Hey! Park Jun Seo!
(Jeong Sang Eui)
(Connection)
I want my share
of what we earned up to now.
Park Jun Seo.
I'm telling you we should stop!
Is it true? Did you fool around
with Jun Seo's wife?
Did you really kill Park Jun Seo?
I'm Park Tae Jin. I'm the Doctor.
You're sticking right beside Jae Gyeong
and telling him everything.
It's not me.
Don't lie.
You were a drug dealer.
How can you plan and construct
the future of Keumhyung Group?
Chairman.
It sounds like a job for you to wrap up.
Jong Soo...
Jae Gyeong!
Jang Jae Gyeong!
Wake up.
Drug...
What have I done to you
for you to drug me?
Stop smiling and answer me!
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)