(All characters, organizations,
and events in this drama are fictitious.)
Do those pills no longer work now?
Tell me if you need more. I'll get them.
Even eight pills can't get
the job done now.
Eight?
Hey.
You can't take more than five at a time.
It'll ruin your liver.
I know.
How did you know to come here?
I was wondering
which punks were fighting at a hospital,
and it was you two.
Didn't you come here
after hearing Choi Ji Yeon's news?
"Choi Ji Yeon?"
Jeong Yoon Ho went to see Choi Ji Yeon.
And?
She's badly hurt,
but it's not life-threatening.
They need to run some more tests.
What's wrong with Yoon Ho?
Is he really the Yoon Ho we used to know?
Hey, this won't do.
Take a taxi and go home. Okay?
Get some sleep first.
I came here...
to see the doctor
who treated Jun Seo's daughter.
He's in emergency surgery,
and I can only see him in the morning.
I'll call if something happens to Ji Yeon.
I doubt Yoon Ho would show up here.
(Connection)
(Episode 12)
Hey.
We just parted ways.
Why did you call me over here again?
I'm meeting Mayor Joo tomorrow.
Do you think Yoon Ho was arrested?
Did you have Tae Jin tailed as I asked?
Yes.
Why am I back here?
What did Yoon Ho do now?
Jeong Yoon Ho.
He tried and failed
to kill Jun Seo's widow and fled.
Who tried to kill whom?
I don't know why, but he's out of control.
He won't take my calls.
This is why I said
we should deal with him quickly.
It's out of my hands now.
Are you blaming me
for what Yoon Ho's doing?
You think killing a friend is a joke?
How many times must I say
it's over if we miss the chance?
You should've been decisive
when it was required.
What will you do now?
If we let Yoon Ho loose,
he'll be caught in two days.
The darn lunatic.
This is such an important time for me.
Yoon Ho called me.
What? When?
About two hours ago.
The conversation we had earlier.
He sounded as if he'd heard a recording.
A recording?
From here?
You said you set something up
to block listening devices.
You told me to turn it off
because you hated the high-frequency buzz.
So what?
What did Yoon Ho say?
He said he knew we'd kill him...
and that he wouldn't go easily, but...
He said something weird.
That it was all you.
That you're manipulating us all.
What?
You lost your mind
because you're cornered.
Hey, you.
Is it true? Did you fool around
with Jun Seo's wife?
What?
Wait. You did what with whom?
What Yoon Ho said was true.
So you wanted him dead to cover it up?
Is that...
worth killing for just to cover up?
Yes, it's true.
I slept with Jun Seo's wife. So what?
Hey, you crazy...
What are you saying?
Did you really kill Park Jun Seo?
Hello?
Jong Soo, it's Yoon Ho.
Speak.
Jong Soo.
Help me out.
I need you...
to step up now.
What do you mean by that?
I felt really let down this time.
Park Tae Jin.
He's a really nasty punk.
Do you know he's trying to kill me?
What for?
To hide the fact
he slept with Jun Seo's wife?
You know about that?
Yes.
Those two got rid of Jun Seo.
I went to his place to find proof.
I haven't found it yet.
The police happened to rush in.
So what?
I need you...
to scare Tae Jin.
Tell him that you know everything.
Say you know he killed Jun Seo,
and he needs to help me out.
Oh, yes. Oh Chi Hyun.
Don't tell him.
I think he's in on it with Tae Jin.
Really?
Yes, Jong Soo.
You can do anything. You're...
You're the future
Keumhyung Group chairman.
What can't you do?
What if I can't do that?
What happens then?
Then I'll be left with no choice.
I'll have to tell the world
you got Lee Myung Guk...
to make you a drug,
and when he blackmailed you,
you got me to kill him.
When did I ask you to kill Lee Myung Guk?
Jong Soo.
Don't do this to a friend.
I can tell what you want...
from the look in your eyes.
If we'd let Lee Myung Guk live,
he'd have dragged us down, you idiot.
Yoon Ho.
Can't you just go into hiding?
Do you have to do this?
I'm 40 years old, you know.
Where can I go to live in hiding?
What about Si Jung? And our kids?
I bought land...
because of the Pilo-dong business.
We're in this together!
Have you forgotten our students' creed?
"Be a helping hand to a friend!"
Where are you?
I got the point. Let's talk in person.
Shall we?
Yes, let's do that.
Text me a place.
I'll come over right away.
I'll be in touch. Keep your phone on.
Okay. Get back to me soon.
The police...
What he said.
How much of that is true?
I told you just now.
I did sleep with Jun Seo's wife.
That's it.
What?
Do you really think I killed Jun Seo?
If you guys actually suspect me,
I'd be so disappointed.
I'd accept the ridicule...
for sleeping with a friend's wife.
But don't you know me too little
if you'd think I'd kill Jun Seo...
over something like that?
Would I give it all up...
and betray you guys for a woman?
That's nothing.
If it's not that,
why didn't you look into
Jun Seo's death yourself?
I think I would have.
Do you...
still think he killed himself?
There is a possibility he was murdered.
But why would I bother?
Jae Gyeong came to see you all.
He's doing all the hard work
to claim the insurance money.
Won Jong Soo.
Making Jun Seo work for you
for 20 years wasn't enough,
so you made him deliver drugs too.
Didn't you use the 5,000 dollars...
his daughter needed
for treatment to crush him?
I bet Jun Seo called you and said this.
"The drugs made
at Youngryun Cold Storage,"
"the fact that
you get a delivery every week,"
"and that you can't go three days
without a dose."
"I'll tell the whole world."
That's why you came
to the construction site that night.
Jong Soo.
You honestly wanted Jun Seo dead.
Wasn't it you?
Shut your mouth.
Or...
was it you?
What?
Did it bother you to kill a friend?
So you got someone else to do it?
What nonsense is that?
Lee Myung Guk's murder...
Jun Seo said he'd tell the police.
That's why you came
to the construction site.
You said so yourself.
Are you denying that now?
You...
weren't even that close to Jun Seo.
What about you?
What were you doing there?
What did Jun Seo say to make you show up?
This is it.
What?
This is what Jun Seo wanted
when he left...
the insurance money
to Jae Gyeong and Yoon Jin.
He wanted us to fight, doubt,
threaten each other, and curse.
Guys.
All three of us...
had good enough reason
to want Jun Seo dead.
But so what?
What are you going to do?
What?
What do you want to do by fighting...
about figuring out who killed Jun Seo?
Get your acts together, you idiots.
The urgent matter on our hands isn't
Park Jun Seo, who's already dead,
but Jeong Yoon Ho.
Got it?
Where should I tell him to come to?
You should decide
wherever is convenient for you.
It seems like something
you'll have to take care of.
Jong Soo.
Chi Hyun!
What are you doing right now?
Hey, don't do this. Chi Hyun.
Hey, it was Park Tae Jin.
It was all his doing!
- Go quietly.
- Hey!
It was all Park Tae Jin's doing!
That's enough.
Chi Hyun, we can't do this between us.
We can't do this between us!
I know.
That's why I told you to stay down.
Why do you always do things
that no one asked you to do?
I was trying to do what was right!
I wanted to do a good job.
You know, I had to do something.
That way, Jong Soo would take
one more look at me.
Save me. Please?
Save me! Chi Hyun.
Chi Hyun, what about Si Jung?
Hey, if I die, your nieces...
What about Young Eun and Young Ji?
Hey, what will you do about...
- Young Eun and Young Ji?
- Be quiet.
Turn your head.
You idiot!
Do you think
those guys consider you a friend?
They don't!
Those guys only call you...
whenever they need you, you idiot.
Hey, Chi Hyun.
You know,
I wanted to be like you.
They don't ask me to do anything.
They don't ask me to do anything!
If I worked hard,
I could get to visit
the place you gather in Pilo-dong...
and just hang out...
- You fool.
- With you guys!
Like back in the day, I wanted to...
Chi Hyun. I wanted to do that.
Chi Hyun, no!
Hello.
Is Dr. Park Eun Young finished
with surgery?
I was here yesterday.
Dr. Park.
(Ultrasound room)
In the letters,
it said that
Yoon Hee could've been treated in the US.
What was that about?
The medicine used
for Yoon Hee's condition...
was rather expensive
and not covered by insurance.
And it was only effective enough
to stop her symptoms from worsening.
But then,
I was contacted about wanting to use
a newly developed drug in the US.
But why didn't they go?
It was because of the costs.
How much would it have been?
It was 500,000 dollars.
Yoon Hee's dad told me that
he would come up with the money somehow...
and for me not to lose
that chance for her.
But Yoon Hee...
didn't wait for us.
You...
died here today.
Don't ever show up around us again.
Don't think of seeing
Si Jung or the kids either.
You and me...
Our friendship ends here.
The students' creed!
One!
"Be someone who performs one's duty!"
Two!
"Be true to one's goal!"
Three!
"Be..."
"a helping hand to a friend!"
All right.
Here we go.
(Anhyun Stream)
Hey, Detective Kim.
Is your arm okay?
Yes, it's fine.
That's good.
The Unit Chief...
got called to the Chief's office
again this morning.
She must've had an earful.
- You're here.
- Yes, ma'am.
What did the doctor say?
I have a sprained wrist.
I have to watch out for a few days.
It's good it wasn't worse.
I'm sorry to cause you concern.
Forget it.
You see all sorts of things
when working as a cop.
Thanks to you, I almost got smacked
by the Chief of Police at this age,
but what can I do?
It's all because I lack virtue.
Where is the Captain?
He hasn't come in yet.
He won't answer his phone either.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
(Park Jun Seo)
What's the passcode?
- Zero.
- Yes?
- Five.
- Five?
Zero, two.
Jae Gyeong.
Jang Jae Gyeong.
Jae Gyeong!
Jae Gyeong, come to your senses.
Jang Jae Gyeong!
Jae Gyeong.
Come to your senses!
Oh, no.
Jae Gyeong. Darn it.
Drink some water.
Jae Gyeong!
Wake up. Please, wake up.
Drug...
Get rid of it...
Okay.
There was
a Lemon Mulberry pill here, right?
There was no other way.
What will you do
if that situation happens again?
Will you take it again?
Yes.
Hey, Straw. What is it?
Okay.
All right, I got it.
Send me the details via text.
Okay, I got it.
Samsol Port in Hwaseong, Gyeonggi-do.
Jangju Port in Dangjin, Chungcheongnam-do.
Manpyeong Port in Seosan,
Chungcheongnam-do.
According to Straw,
at 4:00 a.m. two days from now,
people will be smuggled in
through one of these three ports.
They're far from each other,
so it'll be difficult to cover them
at the same time.
This must mean it's difficult
for Straw to get info now.
We had one of our men show interest...
in smuggling out as a new attempt,
but these guys must be extra cautious.
Ask the Coast Guard
for their cooperation...
and get some internal support as well...
to try and cover all three ports.
- Yes, ma'am.
What happened?
What are you doing here?
Don't tell me...
How many hours did I sleep?
Maybe two hours?
What time is it now?
It's 2:30 p.m.
In front of Manyang Ferry...
at Manpyeong Port, two days from now.
At 4:00 a.m.
Hey, where are you?
Is everything okay?
Unit Chief.
Did you receive any information
from Straw?
I did.
But he gave me the names of three ports.
We don't know which one.
Is Manpyeong Port one of them?
Yes, it is. How did you know?
That's the place.
Two days from now at 4:00 a.m.
All right, we'll check.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I know very well how hard you're trying
to hold out,
but I didn't know what else to do.
It's okay.
I'm sure you were torn in the moment.
What you decided on...
was probably in my best interest.
How's Jun Seo's wife?
Well... She's okay.
She seems to have a lot of regrets.
All she did was cry.
Right.
I'll forward you the address
of that grandma in Boryeong...
in a text.
You remember, don't you?
She's the one getting the pension
from the plan Jun Seo signed up.
Yes.
When do you want to go to Boryeong?
I think I have to head out for now.
Okay.
Are you going back to the station?
No.
I'm going to go see Jeong Sang Eui.
Sang Eui?
Park Tae Jin is a prosecutor,
and he's very cautious.
It won't be easy to investigate him.
It might be a good idea to use Sang Eui
to get to Tae Jin.
Do you want to come along?
What's gotten into you?
Well, it's not so easy to drive either.
All right.
See me at Myeongeul Garden tomorrow
at 4:00 p.m.
Hello?
We found you a boat.
It departs...
from Manpyeong Port
at 4:00 a.m. in two days.
Thank you.
If you leave, you won't be able to return.
Aren't you curious about me?
Pardon?
I'm Park Tae Jin.
Don't you remember me
from early last year?
Come on, we've met.
Prosecutor Park Tae Jin of Anhyun District
Public Prosecutor's Office.
(1 year ago in January 2023)
Mr. Gong Jin Wook.
You ran
an adult entertainment establishment...
two years ago
and were sentenced to six months.
You're back with the same charges.
What is this?
Take a look.
It's our second time making a deal
through a flash drive, isn't it?
Didn't I help you get indicted then?
Thanks for the pictures in the drive.
Among your secret customers,
there are many individuals
who act strong and mighty.
Are you really...
Prosecutor Park Tae Jin?
That's right.
I'm the Doctor.
Jin Wook.
Didn't you ever wonder why
you were picked as the Doctor's dealer?
You never sold drugs before...
and didn't have the knack for it either.
People like CEO Yoon who had
a lot of experience in the field seemed...
too difficult to handle.
It was somewhat too dangerous
for me to deal...
with CEO Yoon directly.
That was why I needed someone
with a brain...
who was also loyal and strong.
That was why I scouted you.
It was more fun than running
an adult establishment, right?
Why are you telling me this?
I told you. I'm telling you
because you won't be able to return.
What? What is it?
Will you report me to the police?
But who's going to believe you
if you tell them I made and sold drugs?
No...
That was not what I meant.
I'm just confused by it all.
I'm sure.
Anyway, take care.
Go to the dock at Manpyeong Port
and find Manyang Ferry...
at 4:00 a.m. two days from now.
Someone will show up.
Okay, Prosecutor. As for the drugs...
Thanks for all you've done.
- It's Jeong Sang Eui.
- What?
- Turn the car around.
- Okay.
I'll wait outside.
Hey.
Yoon Ho...
Did he leave without a word?
Why does that matter now?
If a bioindustrial complex is built,
Anhyun will turn
into an organic future-oriented city...
that is a blend of industrial
and residential.
I'm sure you saw my proposal,
but we already have the funds secured
for this project.
I don't have any questions.
However,
you made things look like
you're doing the city a great service.
What you're saying is that...
you'll build us
a biotechnology complex...
if we give you the rights
to develop a Pilo-dong plot...
three times that size
into a private sector residential area.
Why would Yigu Group get involved...
when they don't care for the city?
They're in it for the profit.
Let's do it.
Okay.
Thank you.
- Let's make it work.
- Thank you.
- Good job.
- Well done.
Didn't I tell you it would go well?
- Hey, look.
- Drive on.
Okay.
(Myeongeul Garden)
Turn and park here.
(Main building)
Wait here.
- What?
- The next room is occupied.
Let's go outside behind the rooms.
Hey. It's Park Tae Jin.
Why are they meeting up?
The Lemon Mulberry business.
Is Jeong Sang Eui
the one who replaced Jun Seo?
This door's closed,
so it'll be hard to listen in.
What's that?
Now do you know why my bag's so huge?
Do you always carry this stuff around?
Listen.
Is there something in China?
Yes, apparently.
Forget that.
Yesterday, when we all met at Pilo-dong.
Do you remember
I told you to wait outside?
Yes.
Did you record our conversation?
- No.
- You didn't?
Then...
how did Yoon Ho know what we said?
Chi Hyun said...
it sounded like
Yoon Ho had heard a recording.
There's no way...
we'd record our chat for Yoon Ho to hear.
Right?
Are you saying you suspect me?
Someone told me...
to remember my place and act accordingly.
Sang Eui. Not all friends are equal.
Do you think you'd be in our group
if Jun Seo hadn't made you...
class secretary out of pity?
You always got beaten up,
you could never speak up,
and you were so slow to catch on.
That's what you were like.
You wouldn't have survived school...
if Jun Seo hadn't coddled you.
Do you think things have changed?
What will you do now?
Jun Seo is gone.
You should appease me,
but you're sticking
right beside Jae Gyeong...
and telling him everything.
And now you're causing a rift
between me and Yoon Ho?
Hey.
It's not me.
Don't lie.
You made the burner phone I gave Yoon Ho.
We're the only two
who can contact him with it.
Sang Eui.
Do you have something against me?
I have zero feelings for you.
While the others bullied you,
I did nothing at all.
So why would you do this to me?
Do you also think I killed Jun Seo?
And this is you avenging him?
Jun Seo said...
he'd only do it until
he'd made 500,000 dollars.
He said he'd quit
selling Lemon Mulberry once he had...
enough money to take Yoon Hee to the US,
but he couldn't.
Whose fault is that?
You're recording this, aren't you?
- What?
- Let's see it.
Give me your phone.
You cheeky thing.
Darn it.
Tae Jin.
Hey.
Tae Jin. I...
- You dirtbag.
- Sorry.
You'd record me?
Hey. Get up.
Stand up.
Sit down.
Park Jun Seo.
I didn't kill him, okay?
I don't know what you want to find out
by doing all this stupid stuff,
but if you do something like this again,
I'll make you pay dearly.
This is the last time I warn you verbally.
Sang Eui.
If we...
do our own thing well like we used to,
nothing will happen.
Okay?
Okay.
Let's eat.
I want to finish the meal.
What's this?
Have a look, and you'll remember.
Are you the Doctor?
What do you mean?
Did you make the Lemon Mulberry?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You and Lee Myung Guk.
You met often at Pilo-dong
outside work hours.
Youngryun Cold Storage.
That's the factory, right?
Did Lee Myung Guk make the drugs first...
and then you took over?
Darn it. Wait.
Jeong Sang Eui.
Jun Seo...
You said he wanted to take Yoon Hee
to the US to fix her...
and was going to make Lemon Mulberry
only until he had 500,000 dollars.
But he failed because of Tae Jin...
because he didn't share
his four digits to the password...
and Jun Seo couldn't withdraw the profits.
Aren't I right?
You two.
One is an officer,
and the other is a reporter,
But you act pretty much the same.
- What?
- You must be so frustrated.
Do you have a suspicion
but no actual proof? Is that it?
What are you doing?
Fasten your seat belt if you want to know.
It's fine.
Hold your breath.
Don't inhale the cold air.
Lemon Mulberry is made here?
Yes.
What about Jong Soo?
Does he also know that you made
and sold Lemon Mulberry?
What would Jong Soo get into
the drug business for?
He can just take them
when he's having fun.
As you said,
Mr. Lee Myung Guk found
the drug's component.
And Jong Soo is still taking...
the drug that was
first developed from that.
But...
I made the Lemon Mulberry.
I mean, I did use Mr. Lee's recipe a bit.
So, why did you bring us here,
and why are you telling us this?
I was the one who got you hooked
on Lemon Mulberries.
Hey, Jeong Sang Eui.
Why?
Because I don't like you.
- Hey!
- Jae Gyeong!
- Hey, Jang Jae Gyeong!
- Why?
Let go.
(Keumhyung Group)
You worked hard.
I was so worried
whether you'd be able to do well.
But I underestimated my own son.
Mayor Joo In Sang just called.
He said he was persuaded by you.
Yes, Father.
Now, that seat...
is yours.
Don't be anxious anymore,
and be confident.
I've known...
that you've felt a sense of inferiority
compared to Tae Jin for a while.
Now, you don't have to feel that way.
Tae Jin, or whoever it may be,
has existed for you.
Those guys can be replaced by anyone,
but not you.
You're Won Chang Ho's son.
This position...
isn't something someone can have
just because they covet it.
Come here.
Sit here.
Slt.
Now,
once the licensing issue is
finally confirmed,
let's get you some treatment.
Pardon?
The future chairman of Keumhyung Group...
can't rely on drugs for too long.
Yes, Father.
I'll hold onto this seat...
for just a little longer for you.
I want to rest now too.
So, hurry up with getting treated
and come back.
Yes.
I will, Father.
Prosecutor Park.
Congratulations on your new position.
- Pardon?
- Didn't you see?
The personnel appointment was just posted.
(Personnel Appointments, Park Tae Jin,
Ministry of Justice, Prosecution Bureau)
(Prosecutor Park Tae Jin)
Is there something like...
an antidote for Lemon Mulberry?
No.
Jae Gyeong. Stop.
I know you're angry. I do,
but what will you do to him now?
Were you also the one...
who kept sending packages
of drugs to Jae Gyeong?
- Yes.
- And what about 1882?
I thought only you and Jun Seo
knew about that, Jae Gyeong.
So, how did you find that out?
Twenty years ago,
I got beaten up by someone,
and Jun Seo told me
that it was an SOS signal.
He said to call Jae Gyeong
when things were urgent.
What did I ever do to you?
What did I do to you
that you got me addicted to drugs?
Stop smirking and answer me!
When we were in 12th grade...
before Jun Seo started hanging out
with you guys,
I was the only true friend Jun Seo had,
and he was the same to me.
But after hanging out with you guys
for a while,
he didn't even care about me.
Like that,
you guys took Jun Seo away from me.
So, I really hated you guys.
Hey, what are you talking about?
Who took what away from you?
We were all classmates.
Just hear me out.
It's not that long of a story.
Then, Chae Kyung Tae died,
and you transferred to another school,
Jae Gyeong.
Jun Seo.
And you, Yoon Jin,
split up with Jun Seo...
as the Audiophile clubroom got smashed.
For 20 years after that,
Jun Seo and I got along well.
We even got along well...
when Won Jong Soo, Park Tae Jin,
Oh Chi Hyun, and Jeong Yoon Ho...
(Xinopharm)
ordered Jun Seo around,
used him, and looked down on him.
Good work.
We were just fine.
But these guys were taking things too far.
Delivering drugs wasn't enough.
Park Tae Jin even made Jun Seo
sell drugs too.
Let's stop now. I can't do this anymore.
Why are you doing this
when we've come this far?
If we just keep going,
you'll fix Yoon Hee's illness for sure...
and even live without worrying
about money your whole life.
Hey, so trust me, and let's keep going
for a few more months.
Whatever.
Let's stop now.
Pay me what I've made so far.
Park Jun Seo!
I said we should stop, you punk!
He even played around with Jun Seo's wife.
So what?
Darn it.
What does that have to do with
you getting me addicted?
Sure, as you said, after I transferred,
I didn't even talk to Jun Seo once.
So why would you do that to me?
You're the worst of them all!
Jun Seo went to see you ten times.
I told him not to.
I told him getting your forgiveness
was meaningless,
but he still went.
He went to see you
because he wanted your forgiveness.
Hey.
He even begged for your forgiveness...
the day before he died,
and what did you say?
- Sang Eui.
- You're not any better!
Did you listen to Jun Seo?
Did you?
He wasn't like himself,
but did you ask him why?
That fool.
He signed up for insurance...
thinking you two would be the ones
to dig the truth behind it...
if he ever died.
I was the one
who stuck around for 20 years,
so why you two?
Why?
Why were you two the most important
in his heart instead of me?
So?
Was that why you hired CEO Yoon
the night Jun Seo died...
to abduct me and get me addicted
to Lemon Mulberry...
before leaving me at exit 3-4
of Anhyun City Hall Station?
So that I would try
to investigate this case?
Jun Seo...
was so happy to hear
about your special promotion.
I thought,
"Sure, Jae Gyeong is so great,"
"he'll be able to avenge Jun Seo."
(From Doctor, 1882)
(Sending, Sent)
But I had no idea that great detective...
would lose to Gong Jin Wook
right off the bat.
He even took your gun.
So,
I meant for you to arrest Gong Jin Wook
and then find CEO Yoon through him.
Then, you'd find me, the Doctor,
and then Park Tae Jin.
That was my plan.
But it got off on the wrong foot
with Gong Jin Wook.
Then,
how did you know
about the security camera at the mill?
I told you. I didn't know about it.
So how much
of this are you responsible for?
Lee Myung Guk's corpse.
"Lee Myung Guk's corpse?"
Did you put it back in his home?
By yourself?
- With No Gyu Min.
- "No Gyu Min?"
No Gyu Min...
is the taxi driver who drove Jun Seo
to the construction site, isn't it?
Yes.
What does he have to do with this case?
Ask him yourself.
I'm sure you'll meet him soon.
What?
Manpyeong Port at 4:00 a.m.,
two days from now.
You can make a stop
in Boryeong before then.
Who's in Boryeong?
That grandma who is receiving the pension?
Go and ask yourself.
Why did you bring Lee Myung Guk's corpse
back to that house?
To make Jeong Yoon Ho take my bait.
Jang Jae Gyeong...
That would allow you
to arrest Jeong Yoon Ho,
followed by Oh Chi Hyun and Won Jong Soo.
I thought you'd figure out
who killed Jun Seo through it.
But Jae Gyeong, you're unpredictable.
You keep losing people.
Do you find this fun?
I'm sure you had fun.
You must've had fun manipulating me...
after getting me addicted to drugs.
You said you did this
because we were bad and you hated us.
Then what about you?
How are you any better?
You were around Jun Seo for 20 years,
but what have you done?
He was suffering
under Won Jong Soo and Park Tae Jin,
but what did you do for him?
That's why I'm helping him now
by using you.
I'm helping Jun Seo get his revenge now.
Are you serious?
You're out of your mind.
Fine.
Let's see if you can speak that proudly
at the station too.
Park Tae Jin.
Are you sure you can arrest him?
Do you have
a single piece of evidence that proves...
Park Tae Jin killed Jun Seo
or that he sold drugs?
How are you so sure he killed Jun Seo?
Can't you see?
All clues are pointing to it.
Park Tae Jin stopped them
from going up to the ninth floor.
He was also the one who checked the body.
He did the postmortem examination...
and pushed to omit the autopsy
until the very end.
But you have no evidence.
He made sure to cut off any connection
between him and Jun Seo.
They never spoke about drugs on the phone,
and he handed over Gong Jin Wook
for Jun Seo to deal with.
This is the deal with the case.
Even if you dig further,
all you'll get is that I made the drugs...
and that Jun Seo sold them.
And?
What do you have?
Do you have proof
that Tae Jin killed Jun Seo?
I can help Park Tae Jin make
a mistake at least.
Hey.
Jang Jae Gyeong.
I won't run away.
I schemed everything.
I'll accept the punishment I deserve.
Arrest me!
But, not now.
You can't prove anything
if you arrest me now.
So please wait until then. Okay?
This was why I brought you here today!
I'll make sure that happens!
That's how...
That's how I'll get my revenge.
Yoon Jin. Jae Gyeong.
I regret what I did.
I'm so sorry...
I made the drugs, Jae Gyeong.
Please give me a chance.
If you give me some time,
I'll get Park Tae Jin for you.
Jang Jae Gyeong!
Let's go home.
Send some gifts
to Mayor Joo In Sang's house.
Nice oysters from Tongyeong would be good.
- Make sure to add a thank-you card.
- Okay.
The chairman's leaving right now.
It'll only take a moment. Is he inside?
(Chairman's Office)
You can come along.
I know what you want to say...
but just follow my orders.
I don't like it.
I don't like being a prosecutor.
I never liked being one.
I don't want to live a single day
as a prosecutor.
Despite that,
I kept my place...
just as you wished.
I wanted to become a businessman.
I thought that suited me better.
I've been serving you from a young age,
and I know Jong Soo well.
I believe I know what's best
for Keumhyung Group's future.
That's why I would like to work...
as a part of the company.
Same with the Pilo-dong project.
I planned, polished, and edited it.
That was why...
it got to where it is.
Please have my transfer appointment...
to Gwacheon's
Prosecution Bureau withdrawn.
Also, please allow me...
to see to the end of this project.
If you would do that for me,
I'll make sure to build the future
of Keumhyung Group you...
- and Jong Soo dream of.
- How?
How are you going to do that?
- Well...
- You were a drug dealer.
How can you plan and construct
the future of Keumhyung Group?
Chairman.
The biggest risk this project has
isn't Joo In Sang or Jong Soo.
It's you.
When I first heard you were selling drugs,
I thought it would be temporary.
Why?
Because you're someone
who believes you're smart.
Didn't we talk enough
at the soup place last time?
I hoped you would've got my message.
But what is this now?
Our company's fate depends
on the Pilo-dong project.
Yet you want
to bring in those filthy hands...
you used to sell drugs with?
How do you...
No, let me ask this first.
Why did you work with Park Jun Seo...
behind Jong Soo's back to make money?
Are you repaying my kindness with hatred?
Do you really not know?
Fine.
You're right.
I worked with Jun Seo to sell drugs...
so I could secure investment funds.
Is that so wrong?
You forced companies
to go out of business...
59:59,400... > 01:00:02,570
and bought them for next to nothing
to make the Keumhyung Group today.
In the process,
you made eight people commit suicide.
Tell me.
Can you say
that the money you earned this way...
is truly cleaner than the money I earned
from selling drugs?
Would adding some of my money taint...
the company more than it already is?
All you merely had were ten cows.
Your family couldn't even afford
to feed them.
I took their only son...
and poured my money into him
to turn him into a human.
But what is this?
What a work of art you've become.
Is Sang Eui telling the truth?
Is it okay to leave him like this?
If I arrest him now,
I'll be able to prove that he made drugs
and that Jun Seo sold them.
Park Tae Jin, that jerk.
What can we do to make him confess?
The case will face limits
if left as a narcotics case.
I won't be able to uncover
who sits above Park Jun Seo.
It'll only support their case
that Jun Seo committed suicide.
That selling drugs led him
to kill himself?
So what can we do?
Sang Eui is psychotic.
Are we going to trust him and wait?
He drugged you for his revenge.
He's out of his mind.
Tell Sang Eui to bring me some new drugs.
I don't want the usual stuff
on a day like today.
Come on, what's with the face?
Today will be the last.
I'm going to the US next month
to get treatment.
Don't be so shocked.
Anyway, that's the plan.
Let me just enjoy it tonight.
All right.
Tell him to hurry.
Hey, Sang Eui.
Can you bring some drugs
to the Lorraine Hotel?
Would 30 minutes be enough?
Okay.
(I spotted Jeong Sang Eui leaving
with a man and a woman after...)
(Park Sang Jin, Secretary's Office)
(Anhyeon Police Station)
Captain Jang.
We found...
Jeong Yoon Ho.
Where?
(Connection)
I can't read him anymore.
It's not for sure yet.
What's going on?
Did you sell drugs behind my back?
This is why hierarchy is important!
That money! No one can get it out.
Park Tae Jin is finally on the move.
We'll seize
and search Youngryun Cold Storage.
Let's head inside.
I was asked to pass this over...
if you two ever came.
What's on it?
Gong Jin Wook.
It wasn't your first time
meeting CEO Yoon, was it?
What's wrong with all of you?
Take a good look at what you've done.