STRONG GIRL NAM-SOON
EPISODE 13
SAVE THE SEA HARES
I made a vow after my older brother died…
that I would never let someone I love
die on my watch again.
But when I lost my team leader
in such an unexpected way…
it broke my heart.
"Why did this happen to me again?"
It felt like it was my fault.
And I hated myself
for being unable to prevent his death.
It wasn't your fault.
Out of everyone I've met,
you are the sweetest,
most competent,
and greatest police officer I know.
Not to mention,
you're the most amazing guy I know.
I'm glad I have you.
You…
mean…
a great deal to me.
You also
mean…
a great deal to me.
I love you.
I love you too.
GEUMJU TV NEWS
She isn't picking up.
How many times do we need to call her?
MS. JUNG
I SUDDENLY DON'T FEEL WELL
AND WON'T BE ABLE TO HOST TODAY
That's sudden.
Mr. Kim, you'll present the news alone.
Let's begin.
Is everything all right?
IT'S NO BIG DEAL,
IT MUST'VE BEEN SOMETHING I ATE
CEO HWANG GEUM-JU
Hey, Nam-soon.
Mom, are you done shooting?
We just wrapped up.
Once it's edited,
I'll send the final version to you
and Inspector Kang as well.
Mom…
Don't send it in the middle of the night.
He's exhausted,
and I don't want to interrupt his sleep.
Sure.
I'll let him sleep…
Sleep?
He's next to you and exhausted?
My daughter,
you did it.
Mom, what are you talking about?
It's not like that.
It's not?
Are you saying nothing's happening?
Whatever.
You're embarrassing me, Mom.
All right, fine.
Anyway,
I hope your stay with him
will be fruitful.
I have high expectations,
so don't you let me down, my dear.
Stop it.
The night is very long.
I'll take it that you catch my drift.
Then…
He's handsome even with his eyes closed.
IT'S A DRUG TESTING KIT
Hello?
It'll be wise to take the test fast.
You…
have been drugged.
It wasn't CTA4885 though.
You'd better follow my orders.
The new psychoactive substance, CTA4885,
has been discovered
at the logistics company Doogo.
Ryu Si-o, the CEO of Doogo,
formed close ties
with those in politics and finance
such as Director Jung Dae-cheol
of TBO Network,
Hwang Tae-jun, presiding judge
of the Seoul Western District Court,
Commissioner General An Byeong-ho,
as well as
Deputy Chief Prosecutor Moon Seong-u
to secure the distribution chain.
Such a networkaided him
in the expansion of his drug business.
The drug CTA4885
that Doogo's CEO Ryu Si-o
went to such lengths
to keep hidden in plain sight
is this
right here.
To the naked eye, it looks like
the filling of a puffer jacket.
However, take a look at what happens
when I pour water on it.
CTA4885 DISGUISED AS PUFFER JACKET FILLING
It becomes a drug.
Get me the PR and legal teams.
We need to respond with legal action.
Yes, sir.
Paint it as sensationalist fake news.
Spin it into something
that nobody would believe.
Yes, sir.
And find all articles related to Doogo.
Of course.
Wait.
You know the warehouse part-timer
who passed away a while ago?
The late Hong Jeong-ho?
Meet with his family.
I don't want someone
having leverage over us.
It wouldn't be a bad idea
to give them some condolence money.
Yes, sir.
Hillary, things are a mess at the office.
Some media outlet reported
that our exported puffer jackets
have drugs in them.
It's blowing up online!
Nice.
It's going as planned.
SUPER STRENGTH AND SEVERE THIRST
NEW DRUG CTA4885
GEUMJU TV
I'M A FORMER EMPLOYEE OF HERITAGE…
No way.
…I HEARD MANY OF THE MEMBERS
CAME TO THE CLUB TO DO DRUGS
Life is tough, right?
Hang in there.
The police will patrol soon,
so find a place to sleep indoors.
Your face will freeze off.
You…
Thank you!
Stay hopeful.
Anything can happen in life.
You little punk!
Are you kidding me?
You took a puffer jacket
that was obtained without a warrant
and handed it to some
pirate news station of all places!
And you call yourself a cop?
Are you out of your mind?
You of all people know
that it speaks the truth.
Request a correction notice
from Geumju TV or whatever it's called!
Are you furious with me
because I crossed the line
as a police officer
or because I did my job too damn well?
Why the hell…
are you going down a slippery slope
with a drug dealer?
You.
Do you think such insubordination
will go unpunished?
Sir,
speaking as your fellow alumnus,
do you know how many of your juniors
looked up to you
and dreamed of becoming like you?
I was one of them.
Go ahead and take
disciplinary action against me.
But I…
will get to the bottom of this case
no matter what.
Also,
if I have to quit, I'll do it myself.
Come with me, Tsetseg.
-Where?
-I have to meet some people.
Those who straddle the line
between friend and foe.
I'd rather stay back.
The team has a lot on their plate today
-including writing an official response.
-All right then.
You bastards.
We have been caught in Ryu Si-o's trap.
According to Geumju TV,
Doogo directly manufactured
and distributed the drugs.
-Is that true?
-Yes, I think so.
I think a Russian mafia group is involved.
Then…
what can we do about this?
We must set the record straight.
Mr. Jung,
provide countermeasures.
"A private news channel planting delusions
in its viewers during a rough time."
Release a press kit with that angle.
I'll take care of the rest.
Mr. Ryu,
is it true though?
Were those drugs?
That no longer matters now.
Whether you live or die
is the issue at hand.
I'm sure you saw the news,
but our conversations were wiretapped.
So they all know who you are
and of your involvement.
They also have you
receiving bribes on tape.
Prosecutor Moon,
dig up dirt on Hwang Geum-ju.
I'm sure you'll find something.
Hwang Geum-ju has a daughter.
Her name is Gang Nam-soon.
She lost her in Mongolia
and then found her.
Her story was covered,
but the links to
all of those news articles are now gone.
I'm sure your network has relevant files
and materials in the archive.
Dig up any information on that daughter.
The strong girl
Gang Nam-soon.
Mom,
it's Tsetseg.
Have you been well?
Mom.
Dad.
I miss you.
Mom, Dad.
I'm doing well.
Mom…
-Mr. Kwon.
-Yes?
"All puffer jackets
are inspected in advance."
"The drug allegations are preposterous."
-Add that to the statement.
-Yes, sir.
And the camera?
Come here and film Ms. Baek working.
-All right.
-Will my face be shown?
That's right.
Don't be nervous and be yourself, okay?
Also,
take photos in a way
that makes us look natural.
Relax, everyone.
Ready? Action!
-Hillary.
-Yes?
What are you doing?
Ms. Baby Face,
can you spare me a flash drive?
Thanks, Ms. Baby Face.
You got it, right?
Let's change it up.
Take photos on this side.
Move the camera further inside.
Point the camera this way.
All right, here we go.
Cue.
COPYING FILE
Hey.
Hey, where are you off to?
Where are you going?
Why you…
Mr. Ryu has arrived.
Hi, Si-o. How did it go?
I was waiting for you.
BEOM
All right. I'll be there.
Tsetseg.
I'm going to put all my trust in you.
Can I…
fully trust you?
You can trust me, Si-o.
You were curious about the lab, right?
Come on. I'll give you a tour.
All right.
Wait for me downstairs.
Gan I-sik, I'm sending you a package.
Yes.
I copied everything on his secret phone.
But everything's in Russian.
They must be texts
he exchanged with Pavel.
There are also recordings.
I'll send it your way,
so have it analyzed.
I'll be heading to Doogo's research lab.
Okay. Bye.
They've all gathered.
I should head over there myself.
They all speak different languages
and need a translator.
Take Kyle with you.
I have Tsetseg by my side.
Yes, sir.
Si-o!
-Have a good one.
-Thanks.
Are there any local numbers?
No, there aren't. Hold on.
Hang on.
That's not it.
The grandmother.
Her son.
Her ex-husband.
Do I have to choose one?
One at a time.
Take them to the brink of death.
Start with the easiest one.
We'll start with her.
Hee-sik.
010-0737-2221.
This is the only local number.
The others are phone numbers in Russia.
He called that number a lot too.
This is Kang Hee-sik of the DIU.
I'm sending you a phone number.
Please get me an ID
and their immigration records.
Thanks.
The phone's owner is
a woman who flew in from Russia
in August 2021.
MS. HWANG GEUM-JU
I have one of Ryu Si-o's bosses.
Nam-soon went to
Doogo's research lab to meet her.
It's been a while.
Hi, I'm Hillary.
She has a unique background,
so please don't mind her casual language.
I'll step outside
and let you two talk, Si-o.
No, you can stay.
It's all right.
Actually, I was hoping
to use the restroom.
Who is she to you
that you brought her here?
She's one of my people.
One of your people?
The next broadcast
will be about the attempt on my life,
the death of Hairtail,
and Madam Kim
attacking me at the hospital.
The viewers have been eating up
what we have to say.
Inspector Kang, just get me what you have
on how Hairtail's killer
faked the ID of a lawyer.
But you were hit with a broadcasting ban.
Are you sure about this?
I'm already facing all sorts of reprimands
and legal restrictions.
We're barred from airing our show.
But outlaws should be handled
outside the law,
and crime should be fought with crime.
I have information
on Doogo's research lab.
As the distributor said,
sea hares are there.
They bring them in from Busan Port.
I believe they're being imported
from the Philippines.
Payments are made
through the Bank of the Philippines.
Sea hare blood.
It's used to make the antidote.
Pavel only sold the drugs.
I'm the one who researched sea hares.
The antidote business
belongs to me.
That could lead
to your demise.
I don't want that.
So what should I do?
Should I follow your example?
If I offered an eye as an apology…
perhaps they would forgive me.
Binbin.
You know where he is, right?
Is he alive at least?
In your case,
it won't end with just one eye.
Maybe.
But I currently have both eyes,
so I have a wide field of view.
No one…
can tell me what to do.
Hwang Geum-ju has Opulentia on her side.
Take all the drugs you want.
You still won't be able to
achieve anything on your own.
I have the power…
to do as I please,
whatever that may be.
The drug controls the human brain.
It stimulates your hormones
to realize your deepest desires
and drives your body to the extreme,
though it'll lead to death.
Without your help,
we would've gotten nowhere.
The law is powerless
when evil forces combine their strength.
I hardly did much.
First, let's track
how the sea hare is imported.
Try to find out when the next shipment
will arrive in Busan Port.
There wasn't any information
on his secret phone.
Ryu Si-o hasn't been
sharing that with Pavel.
He's been keeping it to himself?
Jun-hee.
Mr. Gang won't be at the café
for the time being.
He's been grounded for his safety.
Geum-ju takes after her father
and does the craziest things.
She bought a broadcasting station
to present the strangest news.
Does she think she's a spy?
Who is she, James Bond?
This whole project has me baffled.
Unbelievable.
Daughters take after their fathers.
My daughter takes after me too.
That's why she's innocent and sweet.
I can't believe you said that
with your own mouth.
You cheeky thing.
But I must say it's the truth.
What's with that heated gaze?
It could melt my face.
Your name may mean "in the middle,"
but there's nothing moderate about you,
my dear Joong-gan.
What is it,
my Jun-hee?
I don't think
I'll be able to take you home today.
Why not?
There's something important
I must do today.
And what would that be?
I'll tell you some other time.
So I should go home alone?
But it's too scary to go alone.
I must say
it does worry me too.
You're like a kid by the water.
Don't stop by anywhere else
and go straight home, got it?
Got it.
I'm scared.
I…
have shown you everything.
By the way,
who was that woman?
Someone who monitors me.
Why is she doing that?
Because I'm not trusted.
The lab you saw today…
is my dream
and what I'm betting my life on.
It opened up the chance for me
to rise above them.
Who do you mean by "them"?
Very…
bad people.
Bad as in how?
Like the mafia or something?
That's right.
What?
Good night.
Okay. Bye.
Go.
Shoo.
You dirtbag.
-Hello?
-Did he drop you off?
Yeah, I know you were watching.
The sea hare that you got on video today.
We need to know
when the next batch will be imported.
It arrives through Busan.
How am I supposed to find that out?
I'll get right on it. Bye.
Hello?
Where are you, Ms. Baby Face?
What do you think?
I'm still at the office.
Things are crazy.
The company has never been
in such chaos before.
Where on earth are you anyway?
I was just about to head in
and lend you a hand.
I'll be right there.
What can I get you? Dumplings?
Hello?
It's Ryu Si-o.
You weren't drugged with CTA4885.
What you inhaled was an aerosolized drug.
One that shows up on a hair strand test.
And you…
left behind many strands of hair
in the taxi.
Your younger sister
is studying in Shanghai.
I'm sure you know that moving drugs
is a capital crime in China.
Your sister will soon
receive a batch as well.
I'm sure
you want to save her.
Go live as soon as
you get to work tomorrow.
Say that you delivered lies
under Hwang Geum-ju's orders.
Say you're coming clean because
you couldn't deceive the public anymore.
Otherwise,
the Chinese government will execute
your sister on drug charges.
No…
Yun-jeong.
Please pick up.
MISSED CALLS
DIRECTOR JUNG DAE-CHEOL
I see you called, Mr. Jung.
It's about Ms. Hwang's daughter.
The brawl at the Han River ger
was covered by reporters,
but it never made the news
due to a gag order.
There must be related footage.
The employee
managing the archive resigned,
but I reached out.
Find her no matter what.
Find that woman's daughter.
Find Gang Nam-soon.
There's a young man in Gangnam
who owns a tarot café.
His mom paid that money.
The fact she could pay
a billion won in cash
tells me she's loaded.
She paid a billion won
for the antidote?
She offered such a large amount in cash…
that I lost my mind for a second.
You took me in
when I had nothing going for me.
What I did wasn't right.
So I came to my senses and came back.
I'm sorry. It won't happen again.
Marie,
you said that Hairtail was arrested.
Will we be all right?
We'll have to shut down the club.
-Why?
-Hairtail…
is dead.
I can't believe there's only one left.
Unbelievable.
When did you read my mind?
Ta-da.
How did you know I liked this?
I have loads of work to do,
but I don't have the energy for it.
Girl, I can't even take
a coffee break when I want to.
All right, Ms. Baby Face.
It's nice and sweet.
-Ms. Baby Face.
-Yes?
If controversies and a bad rap
continue to follow the company,
won't our trade business also flop?
I don't know about domestic sales,
but overseas trade will be fine.
Are you worried you'll get fired?
Don't worry.
This team will never downsize.
I really don't want to get fired.
By the way,
which countries do we import goods from?
The Philippines and Taiwan.
-What are the items?
-Sea hares.
Why would anyone want those?
Why would I care?
Hillary, here you go.
I hear they come through Busan Port.
When, exactly?
Every month on the 25th.
It's when sea hares come through customs
at Busan Port.
Mom, I'm being discharged.
Is there herbal tonic at home?
I can't even lift a finger.
Send me a driver, Mom.
What do you mean
you'll have to toughen me up?
I'm not a kid anymore.
I've reached male menopause.
Mom…
Hello?
I mean, who is it?
Please watch your step.
Dad.
Hey.
My poor son.
Taking care of me
landed you in the hospital.
That's not it, Dad.
This isn't because I had to nurse you.
Geum-dong,
I'm sorry.
Goodness.
No, Dad.
Don't be like that.
-It hurts.
-Does it hurt?
Dad, that also hurts.
Right. Goodness.
Start the car.
How did you get in?
Quit yapping
-and drive.
-How did you get in?
-How is that important?
-It is to me.
I got myself a fully loaded car.
It shouldn't be broken into this easily.
Shut up, you old hag.
-What did he just say?
-Shut up.
Take a left at the intersection.
Who are you boys?
I'm just curious.
Who are you?
Tell me. Who sent you boys?
You can at least tell me that.
Just shut up and get in, you old hag.
Hurry up.
Why is the world full of scumbags?
Annoying pests.
Guns in Korea? For crying out loud.
I guess I should be armed myself.
What the hell is Geum-ju up to anyway?
I feel terrible for Nam-in and Bong-go.
Where am I?
Who am I?
-Chamma.
-Yes?
Can you run a trace on this?
This is where the antidote is made.
Got it.
I'll get the coordinates.
This might take some time.
Did your wife get you this?
My wife?
Why you…
But where are the other two?
They were summoned
by the commissioner general.
Hey, Nam-in.
What's up, Nam-soon?
Mom grounded me,
so I've been staying home.
So I've been having
fried chicken every day.
Marinated fried chicken,
soy sauce fried chicken,
and plain fried chicken.
Are you home alone?
Come on over and join me.
Okay, I'll be there.
Keep the doors locked until I arrive.
Sure. Hurry on over.
Got it.
GEUMJU HOSPITAL
Did the patient Hwang Guk-jong
have his stitches removed?
Who are you?
Hold on.
I'm
Gil Joong-gan's…
boyfriend.
Oh, her friend.
No, not just her friend.
I'm her boyfriend.
Her boyfriend?
That's an odd thing to say.
We…
enjoyed hangover soup together.
You know what that means.
Hangover soup is eaten at breakfast.
We've spent the night together.
Wait, so you two slept together?
Of course.
I…
am in love with Gil Joong-gan.
She is my lady.
You damn sleazebag!
So much for being a gentleman.
Would you rather have a crushed skull
instead of a busted tailbone?
Watch your language. A damn sleazebag?
Do I have to knock your teeth
into your throat
for you to shut up?
How old are you, you jerk?
I'm old enough, you twerp!
-Hey!
-Gosh, I'm sorry.
-My tailbone.
-Goodness.
-Why, you cowardly punk!
-Let go of me!
Let go.
What have you been up to these days?
I was attacked by armed men today.
I'm down with you
trying to uphold justice,
but at least give me a heads-up.
Don't always count on the fact
that I'm strong.
Hang up for now.
Just shut it and hang up.
Yes, Jun-hee?
Joong-gan, I'm outside your house.
Really?
Just a second.
Ma'am, get the door!
Just a moment, Jun-hee.
Right, of course.
Jun-hee.
Joong-gan,
everything has been settled.
Now,
we can love each other
to our heart's content!
Jun-hee.
Joong-gan.
Jun-hee, my bratty daughter…
I mean, no one's home at the moment.
How about
we watch Netflix and chill?
I'd love that.
Likewise.
Unbelievable.
I'm going to kill them both.
Damn it.
Dad, please be rational.
You're only making it harder on me.
Geum-dong, we're going home.
I bet you didn't know.
I haven't been home
since I landed in Korea.
Let me go by the house first.
Didn't you hear your doctor?
You need absolute rest.
That's not necessary--
Goodness.
How did my life turn out like this?
Why was I even born?
Why would you say such a thing?
Haven't you…
lived far too long to say that?
Jeez.
What are you up to, Tsetseg?
"I'm having fried chicken."
Is it your boyfriend?
As if.
I quite like your boyfriend.
My boyfriend?
The cop.
He's been wishing me luck
ever since I left the hospital
and has been calling me.
He asked how I was doing
and thanked me for staying strong.
-Did Gan I-sik really do that?
-Yes.
He even suggested we ride bikes together.
I like the guy.
I wonder what Grandma's going to do
about Grandpa and Barista Seo.
What are you talking about?
I guess you haven't heard.
Grandma's seeing someone,
but Grandpa showed up after ten years.
My gosh.
So they're in a love triangle
like the ones you see in K-dramas?
Yes, a passionate love triangle.
Gosh, it's a mess.
Wait.
Shouldn't Dad be out by now?
He said he was in the projection room.
That's odd.
Jeez.
TSETSEG
Sir,
it's about the late Hong Jeong-ho,
the part-timer from Logistics Team 3.
I went by to see his family.
According to his younger brother,
they're already receiving financial aid.
Really?
And the benefactor
is Gang Nam-soon.
Bring his brother to me
right this instant.
Damn it.
For crying out loud.
There will be a disciplinary hearing.
We expected that.
Our Drug Investigation Unit
will be disbanded.
We've been removed from our duties
pending the outcome.
They took us off the case.
We also expected that.
Commissioner General An wants
to deal with us before he's replaced.
Those rotten bastards.
Sir,
I have the video you requested.
SUPER-STRONG WOMAN REVEALED TO BE
HWANG GEUM-JU'S DAUGHTER
GER INCIDENT AT HAN RIVER PARK,
ART ACADEMY FIRE
GEUMJU TV NEWS
You're here.
Ms. Jung,
I don't think Geumju TV can be launched.
Because we were barred from airing,
she's countering
with a spontaneous live broadcast.
If this leads to Ms. Hwang's arrest…
Are you all right?
Okay, let us begin.
CEO RYU SI-O
Welcome.
I heard someone
was supporting you financially.
Is that person's name
Gang Nam-soon?
That's right.
Then you must know
Gang Nam-soon's contact information.
Yes.
You would also know her face.
DIRECTOR JUNG DAE-CHEOL
Yes?
I have the video, Mr. Ryu.
It's a large file,
so I'll send it via email.
Send me a screenshot of her face
right now.
-Is he not picking up?
-No.
Where did he go?
Dad?
I'm…
-quitting.
-Don't be ridiculous.
After the hard work we did?
You can't quit
an hour after putting me to work.
This is the time to be resilient.
It's wrong to stop working on this case.
I wasn't talking about the case.
KANG HEE-SIK
I'm quitting the police force.
What?
What the…
Remember what
the senior superintendent said?
He told us to wait.
I'm done waiting.
I'd rather become
the Sherlock Holmes of our time.
Sherlock?
Does that mean Ryu Si-o is Lupin?
I call dibs on Watson.
I'll be Detective Conan from Closed Case.
Here.
What the hell?
Where did that money come from?
I never thought I'd spend it this way.
Handle outlaws outside the law,
and fight crime with crime.
I'd like to recruit you all.
Do you know what this cash implies?
No tax. Nothing will be deducted.
Babe, I love you.
I love you so much.
Here's to a farewell and welcome party!
How about pork belly with soju?
No, make it plum wine.
No, black raspberry wine!
-Black raspberry wine!
Come on, let's go fatten our bellies.
You have more than enough money.
It should be mixed.
Take one each.
-All right.
-Here we go.
Cheers.
So is this day one
of our private investigation agency?
Yes.
First, I need to find us an office space.
Let's…
work out of a ger.
We can ask his wife to build us one.
-Seriously?
-Hey.
She's not the same person
she was back then.
She's above building gers now, you know?
We'll build it ourselves.
It won't take us four that long.
We're not in our twenties like you.
Exactly.
It's the middle of winter.
We'll freeze to death.
-Exactly.
-You know,
all the heroes born in turbulent times
were fueled by their grit.
-Grit, my foot.
-Let's go.
We're off to our new hideout.
-Just like that?
-Where is it?
Mom!
My gosh.
What do you think you're doing, Mom?!
Mister,
how dare you come here?
How could you break my dad's heart
when he's on the mend
and enjoy a steamy movie with my mom?
Let go of him, you insolent brat.
I didn't get you those pricy herbal tonics
just so you can manhandle him
and yell at me.
You don't care about Dad at all!
It's inhumane, Mom.
Leave.
-Leave already!
-Geum-dong.
How could you both do this…
GEUMJU TV NEWS
Hello, everyone.
GANG NAM-SOON
010-0392-4876
TSETSEG
DIRECTOR JUNG DAE-CHEOL
That's her. She's Gang Nam-soon.
Leave.
STRONG GIRL NAM-SOON
I don't distribute drugs.
Hwang Geum-ju. She is the axis of evil.
There's something
you need to do right away.
Joong-gan!
How dare you go after my man?
Bring it!
So who the hell are you really?
I think I'll be of use to you.
So how can I be of service?
I get it now.
I finally understand
why Pavel executes traitors.
Tsetseg is Gang Nam-soon.
Everyone in my family nearly died.
I need you to do this.
The entire nation is in uproar.
The DIU at Ganghan Police Precinct
has been reinstated.