STRONG GIRL NAM-SOON
Nam-soon?
Mom?
Come here.
Come on.
Nam-soon!
Nam-soon.
Nam-soon?
Mom.
Nam-soon.
Mom…
I'll do it.
To me,
you're still…
only six years old.
Mom.
Yes.
I'm your mom.
Do you remember me?
I don't remember,
but I can feel it.
I can tell you're my mom.
Don't cry.
I grew up perfectly fine and healthy.
The last memory I have of you
was when you were five,
so to me,
you'll start off by being six.
Aren't I too big
to be considered that age?
I have all my teeth and my feet are huge.
How is your Korean this good?
I studied it.
My mom and dad in Mongolia
even paid for classes.
I couldn't be more grateful
to those who raised you.
Let's bring them here immediately.
No.
Mom and Dad need to stay in Mongolia.
They're busy around this time of year
shearing sheep.
No.
I must return the favor.
Then…
can you build them a ger?
A ger?
As in a tent?
They can have one for leisure purposes.
I'll construct
a building for them as well.
FOR LEASE
They can run a rental property business.
The money they earn
will provide a cushy life
after retirement.
"Rental property"?
I know what that is.
I saw it on a lot of K-dramas.
From here on out,
I will teach you
how Korean capitalism works.
-"Capitalism"?
-Anyway,
you remember your home address, don't you?
Gers don't have addresses.
You lived at a place
that doesn't even have an address?
-Yeah.
-A house without an address?
Gang Bong-go, you damn bastard!
"Gang Bong-go, you damn bastard"?
No, don't pick that up.
Don't listen to me swear.
What good would blocking my ears do
when I already heard it?
It's all right.
I'm good at swearing anyway.
I learned a lot from movies.
"Fuck off, asshole."
No, please don't say that.
The swearing I picked up
from your grandmother
has been etched on my insides.
I don't want to pass that on as my legacy.
Got it. I won't learn any new swear words.
Anyway,
I will return the kindness
to all the people
who helped you these past 20 years,
so write down all of their names for me.
Professor Choi's lectures
are just the same as they were last year.
No effort was put in at all.
This is bad.
At this rate,
he could get fired after the evaluations.
-I'm worried.
-Is it someone you know?
Hardly.
I snuck in after hearing
he was an expert on macroeconomics,
but it was a waste of time.
With that kind of approach
to microeconomics,
he'd never understand macroeconomics.
You're right.
You have far more experience
in a wide range of economic activities.
What would a professor know?
That's the issue.
What good does it do
to sit at a desk and study…
Are you hungry?
I'm craving something spicy today.
Why don't we splurge on a meal today?
The bibimbap served in the cafeteria here
is topped with huge fertilized eggs.
Let's just grab a meal in Haengdang-dong.
You'll end up a vagrant
if you keep wasting money like that.
There's no need to put it that way.
-That's not what I meant.
-This is an announcement.
Han River Metro Trump Square
Super-Duper Tower residents
-Mr. Ji Hyun-soo and Ms. No,
-That's you.
-please report to the campus back gate.
-Should we go?
Allow me to repeat.
I am Gang Nam-soon's mother.
-I see.
-Hello.
Did we perhaps do something wrong?
It's 200 million won each in cash.
I suggest you take care of
urgent business with it.
Buy yourselves some clothes
and eat proper meals.
You'll stay at the Geumju Hotel tonight.
It's a hotel I own,
so do not decline.
Mr. Choi will drive you there
in the evening.
We'll solve your problems one by one,
starting with a place to stay.
Please call me directly
should any issues pop up.
The fact that you were
part of Nam-soon's journey…
of coming back to me…
puts me in your debt.
Anyway,
please be in touch.
This is insane.
Two hundred million won?
It's real!
I don't think
it's the day for bibimbap, babe.
Today isn't the day
for something spicy either.
First, hold onto the money.
Let's head for the subway lockers.
-Hurry!
-The lockers?
No, just leave that.
Goodness!
You're here, my child!
My precious darling.
Look at the fine lady you've become.
You took after me and not your mom.
Look how beautiful you are.
You sweet little thing.
Nam-soon.
I heard you came across a fire today
and saved people at the scene.
Your mom told me.
Look at all the dirt on your face.
Let's go and get you
cleaned up in the bathroom.
Wait.
Ms. Jung, can you buy
some new clothes for Nam-soon?
-Yes, ma'am.
-Okay, let's go.
I'll scrub your back for you.
It reacts to water and dissolves.
After a certain period,
the water evaporates
and leaves white powder behind.
This thing is dangerous.
I'm sure this mask…
Just a second.
Hello?
This is Hwang Geum-ju.
Hello.
Did you meet up with Nam-soon?
Yes, thanks to you.
She's with me as we speak.
I see. I'm glad to hear that.
Thank you.
Ms. Gang's luggage is in my possession.
I'll stop by your place
to pick it up myself.
Allow me to bring it over.
No.
It's only polite that I come.
All right.
This isn't drugs. I bet it's just dust.
Sir, no!
This is more potent than fentanyl.
Rinse your mouth!
-Hurry!
-What's the matter?
I think I already swallowed it.
What are you, a child?
How can the leader of a drug task force
just try an unknown substance like that?
I just thought
it couldn't possibly be drugs.
You weren't born yesterday.
Nam…
Nam-soon.
Of course.
No wonder…
It was you all along.
We met…
at the photo studio.
Dad?
Yes, I'm your dad.
It's Dad, Nam-soon.
Dad, I'm sorry.
I let go of your hand, didn't I?
No, don't say that.
I'm the one who should apologize.
I'm so sorry.
Nam-soon!
This is Nam-in.
Your younger twin brother.
I have a twin?
Underneath all that fat
is a boy who looks just like you.
Nam-in.
It's good to see you.
Nam-soon.
I missed you so much.
I prayed for you every day.
That must be why
we were able to meet again.
It's weird, you know.
When I met Hwa-ja,
I could tell she wasn't my sister.
But I knew you were my sister
the second we met.
Speaking of which,
where is she?
LEE MYUNG-HEE WANTED FOR FRAUD
REWARD UP TO 5 MILLION WON
GANGHAN POLICE PRECINCT
These are the transactions
linked to Baldy's crypto wallet.
All his transactions,
the amount, and time are recorded.
We must piece together
which wallet he traded with
and at what time, down to the second.
Let's work with the Cyber Bureau.
I'll put in a request.
They turned us down
as they're busy with pornography cases.
The five of us can't possibly
go through all this data.
Exactly.
We can't do all of this alone.
As Homo sapiens,
we should use our wits.
I'm heading downstairs for a bit.
What now?
Chief.
I'd like to propose an M&A.
-What are you talking about?
-An M&A.
-I look forward to our partnership.
-As do I.
A round of applause!
The precinct and the DIU
will help each other out
-and cooperate as needed.
-One, two, three.
It's a win-win!
Mom.
I felt so guilty
for failing to protect you
despite having super strength.
It's okay. I'm just as powerful.
That's why I grew up
to be strong and healthy.
Nam-soon.
The women in our family
are born with super strength.
However,
that strength
should only be used for good.
If you use it for something bad,
you'll lose your power.
The fact that you're still this strong…
means you've led an honest life.
I couldn't be more grateful for that.
And that's how I'll continue to live.
Of course you will.
I'll always stay by your side
and help you stay that way.
My sweet daughter.
It's late, so get some sleep.
You too, Mom.
Mom.
It's me, Tsetseg.
How are you?
Mom,
I found my birth parents
and my younger twin brother here.
How's Dad?
Can you put him on?
Dad,
don't worry about me.
I'm doing well.
Mom.
Dad.
I miss you both.
But I think there's something
I must do in Korea.
It seems there's a place
I could put my strength to good use.
Got it, Dad.
My son is too weak
and has trouble getting up.
He spends his days
lying on the sofa or in bed.
He's like a 40-year-old zombie
who smells like soap.
Can you please help him?
What are your symptoms?
It's as if
a strong gravitational force
is constantly pulling me
toward the ground.
I can't seem to get on my feet.
When I do,
my body aches all over
and I'm exhausted.
It's why I always lie down.
Let me examine you.
He lacks energy.
He's off-balance,
which explains the weak energy flow.
That and his arrhythmia
is why his vitals are weak.
I'll pay as much as you need,
so please just help my son
walk on his own two feet.
Velvet antler, bear bile, chaff flower,
virginsbower, gold-and-silver honeysuckle.
Add everything good for him,
including organic goji berries.
Get him whatever Qin Shi Huang ate.
No, I don't want a life
like Qin Shi Huang's.
He had an exhausting life.
It's already too late for you.
Even if you start building today
and continue until you die,
you won't be able to build
a fraction of the Great Wall of China.
In any case,
just add everything good for the body.
Blindly adding in ingredients
isn't the solution.
I'll brew a tonic
that is just right for him.
How about you, ma'am?
Shall I take a look?
Well…
Your pulse…
I've never felt a pulse
quite like this before.
It runs in the family.
The women are strong, but the men are…
Are you married?
-No.
-No?
I have a class to teach
at the association today,
so take a taxi home.
Mom, I'm completely exhausted.
Here.
Taxi!
-Taxi…
-A grown man…
I can't believe his mom is carrying him
in this hot weather.
What are you looking at?
He's not a spoiled brat,
and I'm no pushover.
He's too weak,
and this isn't a big deal for me.
Taxi, get over here!
Mom, please don't yell.
My ears hurt. You're killing me.
Really?
Your ears aren't well either?
They aren't. I'm exhausted.
Get over here!
Today's a special day.
My granddaughter has returned.
-Congratulations!
Thanks.
So today,
I will butcher a whole cow
for you to watch.
-Thank you!
At ease, people.
We're not like chefs.
Butchers don't try to establish
a hierarchy over each other.
Do you know why?
Because doing so
could lead to murder
if one loses their temper.
Knives…
can disjoin, dissect, and dismember
all organisms on this earth.
All right.
Blood, flesh, and bone.
Breaking up bones with a machine
just isn't the same as doing it…
with your hands.
A soup made with bones
broken up with your hands
tastes ten times more refreshing.
That's how my daughter, Hwang Geum-ju,
became a billionaire.
Her wealth comes from the success
of her seonji soup restaurant.
Right?
This gold magic wand
was my present for your fifth birthday.
You wanted one of your own
after watching Cardcaptor Carrie,
and your mom had it made for you.
I see.
These are the dishes
you enjoyed the most when you were five.
Let's eat.
It's so good.
Nam-soon.
Does this jog your memory?
-Yes.
-You loved cotton candy, remember?
You loved sausages as well.
I remember
how you even stole
my cotton candy from me.
Did I do that? I'm sorry, Nam-in.
No, it's fine.
You still let me have all the meat
since you didn't like it.
I wonder why I can't remember anything.
I feel bad about it.
It runs in the family.
You ladies are only built for strength,
not your brains.
That must be why you're not so bright.
Shut it, Bong-go.
Today's a good day,
so I'll let that one slide, Mr. Gang.
How about a family photo?
I'd love to hang a large one up
proudly at the studio
to show off my daughter.
Grandma should be in it too.
As well as your sickly uncle.
-Though he's been in bed for three days.
-Then,
let's take one by ourselves first.
Here we go. Smile, everyone.
One, two, three.
EPISODE 4
REUNION
Elegantly.
Like…
a swan.
Wow, nice shot.
My swings are on point
whenever I practice here.
Don't you agree, Nam-gil?
Of course, ma'am.
Hello?
Where's your boss?
We're at the indoor driving range.
Seriously?
Is she practicing
how to hold back her strength?
Yes, something like that.
Today is bone soup day,
so have Managing Director Nam
at Geumju Hotel pick the bones up.
Yes, ma'am.
-Nam-gil.
-Yes?
Forward any calls
from Opulentia right away.
I requested information
regarding drugs, you see.
Drugs? What about them
are you curious about?
Who the major distributor is in Korea.
Opulentia had better not
take my money and blow me off.
Goodness.
They're not blowing you off, ma'am.
Opulentia just sent you a reply.
Is that so?
"There are drugs stashed at Doogo."
Doogo?
Doogo.
Us new money should see each other around.
It's been a while.
Directors and investors,
it's good to see you.
As you know,
Doogo has strived to be the first
to actualize coin-based transactions
by issuing Doogocoin.
Its trading will soon begin officially.
Just like our name "Doogo,"
we do it ourselves.
We do whatever our consumers want
and go wherever
they want us to be. "Doogo."
Per the memorandum of understanding
that Doogo signed
to establish Asia's
largest logistics center next year,
we will need at least 3,000 Doogo Men
in the second half of the year.
Doogo will lead the industry
in employment growth
by an overwhelming margin.
Not only will we hire men,
but we will also hire Doogo Women.
Who says…
that deliveries…
must only be made by men?
Make sure to cross-check
the time of purchase
with the time of sale,
as well as the price.
If you cut corners,
we'll be here all night.
Jeez, my eyes.
There was an assault at the protest
against the Hyeonu Party by the Han River.
Why are you two getting up?
We agreed on a partnership, remember?
-We should help.
-What he said.
Ms. Hwang,
should we publish an article
on how you found your real daughter?
No, don't.
Things almost went crazy
with stories about her and the fire.
I made them take down everything
on social media and online newspapers.
I was actually sent photos
taken at the scene.
She leaped to the fourth floor
to save the kids.
I don't want to stress her out
with anything right now.
All the articles so far were to
let the world know I was looking for her.
Now, I must shield her from the spotlight.
Stop all articles from being published.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Mr. Kim.
It's time to move on to a new story.
Recently, Ms. Park died
after taking drugs.
Drugs are no longer
somebody else's business.
It's become ours.
Do a deep dive
into the drug use in Gangnam
and report on its severity.
Your face is on wanted posters
all over the city.
-How do you expect to survive now?
-I need to earn money.
Get me a fake ID.
That'll be 400,000 won.
Here's a million.
I got 150 million won
just by selling two of her watches.
Between the prize money I won
and selling the clothes and bags
I got from the family…
Well, I'm loaded.
There won't be any left
after paying the boys
and picking up their medical bills.
All the more reason for me to earn money.
A job will keep me hidden.
It's not like I can lay low forever.
Name, An Eun-ji.
She died three years ago.
It won't be a problem
since no one's looking for her.
Even if I died…
I doubt anyone would look for me.
DOOGO HIRING FEMALE DELIVERY STAFF
Why are they looking
to hire female delivery staff?
It's imperative for the firm's reputation.
It'll help Doogo look more global
and at its prime.
Of course.
There's one other reason.
Even among women,
there can be someone strong.
I saw her myself.
A woman who was unbelievably strong.
I want to confirm
if what I saw actually happened.
METHAMPHETAMINE
1 KG
He inadvertently became
a human test subject.
But he rinsed his mouth right away.
How is this possible?
What do we do about him?
I have a bad feeling about this.
-Hello?
-Gan I-sik, it's me.
Hey. I heard you met your mom.
I'm happy for you.
Remember the photo studio you sent me to
for my passport photo?
-The photographer's my dad.
-Really?
Who knew such a fateful encounter
could actually happen?
Thanks to you, I found my mom and dad.
Thanks, Gan I-sik.
How long are you going
to keep calling me that?
Words have power.
I might actually
end up with a liver transplant.
That will never happen
because I'll protect you.
Hee-sik, do you want to go out for a meal?
Okay.
Let's go for a meal.
Think about what you want to have.
I'll be in touch.
All right.
What's with you?
Why's your heart pounding over this?
Kang Hee-sik!
-Cheers.
It's good.
Thank you so much, Nam-soon.
-It's nothing.
-My life has taught me
that you never know…
what the future may bring.
It's what makes it fun.
If we hadn't
barged into Nam-soon's ger that day,
this miracle wouldn't have happened.
Gosh, I'm tearing up.
I've always been curious.
How did you two become vagrants?
Let's save that story for some other time.
Okay.
What will you do
with the money my mom gave you?
I lost everything through cryptocurrency
but it's what will get me back on my feet.
Cryptocurrency?
Is that how you lost all your money?
Nam-soon, let's do that job.
The assistant director
called me in person.
Do you have to work when you have money?
What motivates people isn't money
but dreams.
Let's go.
Off we go.
Have fun then.
I'm going to have a spa day at the hotel.
Okay.
What role did he offer you?
Sol.
Isn't this a period drama?
Why does Tarzan appear?
Is Tarzan from Joseon?
It has a modern twist.
Hong Gil-dong of Joseon
travels back in time
and lives as Tarzan.
The story sucks.
They say you can't judge a show
until it airs,
but this one is crystal clear.
It'll flop.
I can't believe writers get paid for this.
I told you, no audio!
You're a body double. Be quiet.
Was that too loud?
Hello?
Why is that beanpole going overboard?
Why is the body double
trying to do the audio?
I said he was too skinny
and we needed someone different.
Do we look the same size to you?
Hey.
He's doing a much better job than you.
Don't you agree?
What are you yapping about?
-I can do way better.
-Show us.
Go ahead.
See?
You're terrible.
Isn't he way better at it?
Think about it. He's even better looking.
Have him be the lead.
Hey, what's your Myers-Briggs?
Don't. She'll kill you.
Han River Vagrant, you're the best!
Hey, why don't you head over there and…
…practice that some more.
You just wait and see.
Come on.
Is this how you waste production costs?
The male lead is uglier and a worse actor
than the extra who only gets paid
100,000 won a day,
but he gets 200 million won per episode.
Is this how capitalism works in Korea?
Tighten your core
and give it your all.
MS. OH
Hello?
Hey, Mom.
Today?
Is she already here?
Hello, I'm Hwang Geum-ju,
Nam-soon's mom.
Hello. Come on in.
Then…
This is all of Ms. Gang's luggage.
Right. Thank you.
Inspector Kang.
-Yes?
-I don't know
how I can express my gratitude.
Tell me what you want.
What I want?
Everyone has a shortage of something.
Tell me what it is you need.
I'll fill that void.
-There's nothing.
-As if.
It's not "as if."
I really don't need anything.
As if.
Give it some thought.
There must be something.
I'm investigating a drug case.
I'd like to catch
the mastermind behind it.
How's that for an answer?
You sure are an impressive detective.
Hardly.
Even after staying up two nights,
we still haven't caught a glimpse of them.
Don't take this the wrong way.
I know you don't need this,
but doing this will put me at ease.
Is this money?
Yes.
I do love money,
but I can't accept what I don't deserve.
I'm someone
who loves showing off my money.
It motivates me to earn more.
I even thought about giving all that I own
to the one who brought my daughter home.
It's why you absolutely deserve this.
I'm afraid I can't take it.
Please do.
No, I can't take this money.
Gosh, my feet hurt.
Hee-sik…
Is this why you became a cop?
You decided to enter the force
knowing that the job was tough
and didn't pay much.
I don't care how desperate you are.
You sought out a sugar mama around my age?
-You brat!
-A sugar mama?
Mom, what are you saying?
It's not like that!
Yeah, right!
Let go.
Let go!
Ma'am.
It's not what you think.
A sugar mama?
Is that what you think
of your remarkable son?
Do I seem like someone
who'd be a sugar mama to a younger man?
Then who are you?
I'm sure we'll cross paths again.
Until then…
There will be a next time?
My gosh.
What on earth?
-My gosh.
-Ma'am, you forgot…
It's money, isn't it?
A check?
How many zeros are there?
A nine-figure check?
THERE ARE DRUGS AT DOOGO
100% CERTAIN
I'm investigating a drug case.
I'd like to catch
the mastermind behind it.
Even after staying up two nights,
we still haven't caught a glimpse of them.
There are drugs
at the logistics company Doogo,
Inspector Kang.
Mister, move over. I need some water.
Hey, mister.
This is Team 2 of Ganghan Police Precinct.
This is Inspector Kang at DIU.
He's dead?
A mask?
DOOGO MASKS
Baldy's dead.
Yes, I heard.
That drug sure is potent.
I only licked what was smaller
than a grain of salt,
but I've been out of it all day.
Sir,
I think I have to go undercover.
Where?
DOOGO MASKS
ONLY AVAILABLE TO PREMIUM MEMBERS
I don't like wearing
these kinds of clothes.
Please do it for Ms. Hwang…
I mean, please do it for your mother.
Imagine how much
she wanted to dress you up.
A day didn't go by
without her thinking about you.
Got it.
Then I'll wear this.
Ms. Yeon, get my daughter
a pendant from Bulga**
and a bracelet from Tiffa**.
Of course, Ms. Hwang.
Darling,
what kind of fun will you have today?
Wouldn't it be good to go to school?
You should study.
You'll be inheriting
everything I have in the end.
To do so, you must study about the world.
You must understand capitalism.
Korean capitalism is no fun.
It's because you don't know it well yet.
Once you do, you'll find it really fun.
I never liked studying.
You truly are just like me.
I never get why people
take pills for insomnia
when all you need is to read a book.
When I came here,
I only thought about meeting you and Dad.
But now that I've met you,
I don't know what I'm supposed to do.
Of course you do.
You can live happily ever after with me.
And meet your father from time to time.
What brings you the most joy?
You know,
I find the greatest joy
in helping other people.
I want to be of help to someone.
That's how I am as well.
Hey.
Got it. I'll take a taxi.
Right. Sure thing.
Who was that?
Gan I-sik.
He's this handsome guy.
As in the detective
who brought us together?
Yeah, him.
Is it a date?
A date?
No, we're just having a meal.
Then it's a date.
No, it's not.
We're just having a meal together.
I'll head out for my meal with Hee-sik.
All right.
You're so pretty.
You really look like
you're from Gangnam now.
I mean you look pretty.
Thanks. Let's order something good.
Is this the taste of capitalism?
Yes, and this is why people earn money.
To buy tasty meals for their loved ones.
By the way,
I won't be at the precinct for a while.
Why not?
I'll be going undercover.
What's that?
In other words,
I'll be getting a job somewhere
under a false identity.
Where exactly?
Somewhere that could have drugs.
I received a tip,
and the follow-up proved it was solid.
I want to check it out.
I'll join you.
Don't be ridiculous.
It's too dangerous.
I'll help you.
I'm strong, remember?
Use it to your advantage.
Right.
The company is hiring
female delivery staff too.
Do you really want in?
If you're doing it,
it must be for a good cause.
Your name is Hee-sik.
In Mongolian, it means "benevolent."
I think hanging around you
will make me a better person
and help people along the way.
-Are you all right?
-I'm good.
All right, thank you.
Keep up the good work.
Ms. An Eun-ji.
Ms. An!
Yes.
Check the list of goods
that must be delivered today.
You're liable should any go missing,
so always confirm the amount.
All right.
Hello?
Two new recruits?
Mr. Kim Jun-seok.
-That's right.
-And the young lady is…
-Tsetseg?
-Yeah.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Kim, you've been
out of a job for three years.
And the lady…
is from Mongolia.
I'm Korean, but I grew up in Mongolia.
Sir.
I have a work visa, so I can get a job.
You can read, right?
Of course.
Doogo, the hope
for the unemployed and immigrants.
That's how people will see the company.
All right.
I'll bring you on this month as interns
and see how you do.
Pull your weight or get packing.
Sweet.
Yes, sir.
We'll do our best. Thank you, sir.
Hey, I found it.
You found it?
It's Dericoin.
Luckily for us,
Baldy wrote his password on his phone.
I was able to trace the money he received,
but the wallet it came from
was already empty.
The owner must have cashed it in.
Then there's no way to trace it.
When will we have Baldy's autopsy report?
Tomorrow, sir.
Someone left him a mask.
That's as good as a suicide pill.
The mask wasn't anywhere,
including in the prison washroom.
Why do you keep chugging down water?
Beats me.
I can't quench my thirst.
The herbal tonic's too bitter.
It's unbearable.
Drink up for now.
Wait.
I should get some to Nam-in.
It's hot.
I don't think we've met.
Right.
I'm Seo Jun-hee, the new barista here.
May I take your order?
I didn't come here for coffee.
My grandson's the owner.
Goodness. Really?
It's a pleasure to meet you.
How did Nam-in
manage to hire a gentleman this dandy?
By the way,
this is the bone soup I made this morning.
Please have some when you're peckish.
Gosh, I'm honored.
Thank you.
Would you like some coffee?
I'd love that.
Let's chug a hot cup of Americano…
Let's drink some coffee.
You and me.
Together.
It's not like you have
other customers to serve.
Shall we?
The aroma of the coffee…
The aftertaste…
Thank you.
How long have you been a barista?
I worked at a securities firm
for 30 years.
After retirement,
I studied coffee as a hobby
and somehow ended up
entering competitions.
Your missus…
I mean, your wife must be delighted.
She passed away
five years ago.
You poor thing.
I'm also…
without a partner.
Did he pass away?
No.
He moved on.
He ran off, you see.
He left ten years ago
saying he wanted to find himself,
but I haven't heard from him since.
It's safe to assume he's dead.
I see.
The aroma…
is exquisite.
Slowly.
Right there. Okay, good.
Put them down.
Good!
All right. Today,
you'll begin your work
by transferring these to the truck.
You'll be partnering up like cops.
I feel bad for you
since you'll be doing
most of the work yourself.
Hey, you!
Hey, mister!
Were you talking to me?
Yeah.
It's nothing, sir. Please ignore that.
Will we be done for the day
once we deliver all of these?
That's right,
but why are you talking down to me?
You talked down to me first.
Why are you allowed and not me?
What? Why you little…
Hey!
DOOGO SPRING WATER
Hey, mister.
Get me that red plastic slab.
-We'll move the crates on it.
-Sure.
Got it, ma'am.
How on earth is she this strong?
Get out of the way
-or help with the load.
-What the…
Let's wrap this up quickly
and get inside the warehouse at night.
You said you had drugs to find.
By the way,
should you let people know
how strong you are?
What can I do?
Besides, it's nothing to be ashamed of.
It's not,
but it'll be bothersome
if you attract too much attention.
I don't care.
Anyway, I'll handle all the heavy lifting
and you handle the odds and ends.
Got it, Gan I-sik?
-Got it.
-Okay.
Where on earth did you
pick up on words like that?
But are you going
to keep calling me Gan I-sik?
In Korean movies,
I heard people call each other like this.
"Hey, brother!"
What?
We have the same surname.
Hey, brother!
Listen up.
Drive at this speed for two minutes
and then pull over.
Why? What is it?
Do it.
Why? Who is she?
The Airdnd scammer.
What the hell?
Give me back my money.
-What money?
-Do you know her, babe?
No, I don't…
Oh, right.
The Mongolian.
That's right. I'm from Mongolia.
Airdnd.
You listed a house for sale as your place
and took off with my money.
You're the worst.
How can you be out on the street
after scamming tourists?
Babe, she's completely crazy.
-Let me talk to her. Wait for me there.
-Sure.
Tell me about it.
The investigation was pretty sloppy
since I only targeted tourists.
My case was terminated.
I suggest you study more about Korea.
This isn't a country that locks people up
for stealing chump change.
Chump change?
What will tourists think of Korea
after running into people like you?
They'll believe
it's a country full of scammers.
I almost did myself.
You were rude even from the get-go.
The way you speak
really gets on my nerves.
Nam-soon, wait.
You can't hit her.
I don't hit women.
Give me back my money.
Give back the money
you stole from others too.
Then I'll forgive you.
Hey, even a prosecutor let me go.
So who are you to forgive me or not?
It's up to you to get your money back.
Is that so?
I hate Korea's so-called capitalism.
I hate its law as well.
How can they let that scammer
see the light of day?
Scammers are the worst.
I'm going to change
how things work in this country.
Start the car.
Got it.
SPECIAL THANKS TO JEON SOO-KYEONG
STRONG GIRL NAM-SOON
-You let her steal from you?
-I wanted to prevent that.
Do you still have feelings for each other?
-As if!
I checked with the manager in charge.
-There's an extraordinarily strong girl.
-There you are.
He launders money for the one percent.
I'll cut right to the chase.
I hear you're a master
at handling black money.
I'm obsessed with it.
I looked into Ryu Si-o.
Something's not right.
Tell him to abort the operation.
You can't lead a normal life.
Let's save the world.
I'll look into it alone today.
Gang Nam-soon is at Doogo.
I'm going to kill them all.