=The Secret of the Lost Pearl=
=Episode 15=
(Fiction. Do not imitate.)
Captain, the road ahead has collapsed.
Pass the word down.
- Move on foot.
- Yes.
No matter what,
not a single relic
can leave Xuanyi County.
Search carefully.
- Don't miss any corner.
- Move.
- Yes.
Hurry.
Ms. He, you really saved us this time.
If you had not stolen the box,
we'd all have died in there.
Wait.
What are you doing?
What did I tell you?
Is this how
you looked after her?
She almost got her head blown off.
Why?
Because she was trying to save you.
To save you, Lu almost died.
Something about that.
Calm down.
Let me say something fair.
If Chubby had not put the bomb there,
we'd still be chased by Huang Long.
Why didn't you negotiate
with Huang Long?
Why send a woman to do it?
Are you even being reasonable?
- You...
- Stop!
You want to fight?
Chen Youxi.
- Calm down.
- Chen Youxi.
Chen Youxi.
- What are you doing?
- Lu is a coward.
He nearly lost his life
trying to save you.
Say something about that.
You only value Ms. He,
but the two of us can die, right?
Get lost.
- Stop.
- Don't pull me.
Say that again if you dare.
Calm down.
- Why do this?
- Calm down.
I am perfectly fine.
You're really not hurt?
I'm fine.
How about you?
You just fell. Are you okay?
- You...
- It was great.
We had a lovely conversation.
Miss Bai, I've been meaning to ask you.
What is inside that box
that made your group fall apart?
I already asked her.
She said she doesn't know.
I was asking her.
Just like Chen Youxi said,
I don't know
what is inside the box.
Do you think
I'd believe that?
We talked about this too.
Huang believes that was the true hall.
The box was placed inside the coffin
with an eyeball pattern on it.
He thinks it is exactly
what their boss wants.
I said it already.
I am asking Miss Bai.
I have already told Chen Youxi
everything I know.
If you still have questions,
you can ask him.
Why does this sound like jealousy?
If I had known,
I'd have fallen with Bai Lingling.
Chen Youxi could stay with Ms. He,
and we wouldn't be fighting.
Dream on.
Fine.
Since you refuse to say anything,
there is no reason for us
to keep traveling together.
Why not split up here
and go our separate ways?
How would we split?
There is only one passage.
Do we go first while she follows,
or does she go first
and we wait for five minutes?
Do you think that is feasible?
Chen Youxi,
she is a risk.
Why insist on traveling with her?
What kind of risk could she be?
She is alone; there are four of us.
What's there to worry about?
Why insist on going with her?
She has information about the curse.
Fine.
Very good.
So, you mean
no matter what happens,
you will bring her along?
For now, yes.
Fine.
Then you take her with you.
I will go alone.
No.
I still have to handle this.
Go after her.
Why?
Where did that fighting spirit go?
Wasn't it all because of her?
Now, you just let her go?
Come on.
I give up on you.
I can kill a wild wolf
with my bare hands,
yet I can't make
the woman I love happy.
That is a movie line.
How many times have I said
that woman can't be trusted?
But you insist on believing her.
I've said it countless times.
Besides,
this is a team effort.
Not a solo mission.
Help.
Help!
Chubby.
Chubby!
Chubby, where are you hurt?
- Chen.
- Where are you hurt?
Ms. He is not here yet.
Listen to me.
Ms. He?
What do you mean?
In a moment, follow my lead emotionally.
Don't improvise, got it?
Are you crazy?
If you are fine, get up.
About Bai Lingling,
what do you plan to do?
What about Bai Lingling?
What nonsense are you saying?
Fool, what is in your head?
Don't you know
why Ms. He is angry?
Quick.
Your hand.
Chen,
this is as far as I can go with you.
From here on...
What is wrong?
Ms. He.
What happened?
I picked up a stone.
Maybe I was too hungry.
I could not resist and licked it.
I think I have been poisoned.
Poisoned?
Are you insane?
Why would you lick a stone?
It tastes like chocolate.
If you don't believe me, smell it.
My heart is beating too fast.
I can't breathe now.
Chubby, what is wrong?
Wrong spot.
Here. The heart.
The heart.
- Here?
- The heart.
Ms. He,
with my dying breath,
I entrust him to you.
I don't ask
that you two grow old together.
I only hope that right now,
you can put aside your conflict.
Right?
Join hands and have children soon.
That might be a little early.
First, get out of this tomb together.
Lift the curse on Chen.
Then have children.
What are you doing?
The Indians have a method.
If someone is poisoned,
just let some blood out.
How much?
Not much. Two gallons.
- Two what?
- Come on.
Just half a tank.
No.
Chen has a way to save me.
I believe in TCM.
A way.
A way. TCM.
You...
Fool, could you say something?
What a silent fool.
What did I just tell you?
Follow my lead emotionally.
And you said nothing.
Are you two bored or what?
Three-year-old kids?
Chubby forced me into this.
Chen,
that is unfair of you.
You were forced?
Then why did I do all this?
Chubby meant well.
Of course.
I even used a stone as an excuse
to put on such a big performance.
Ms. He.
So...
Well...
Did you already
figure it out earlier?
If you were really about to die,
would Chen Youxi still sit there,
listening to such a long final speech?
You are so stupid.
Besides,
do you know what this stone is?
Just licking it could poison you?
But this stone is quite magical.
It really smells like chocolate.
This should be Wenxiang Jade.
It's said to be an imperial treasure,
also called Jinxiang Jade.
In Prince Gong's Mansion,
there is a treasury vault.
There is one piece inside.
So, this counts as a treasure?
It was discovered
in ancient tombs before.
It first appeared
during the Qin and Han dynasties.
I heard it is a kind
of chocolate-scented fossil.
The drier the environment,
the stronger the fragrance.
After friction,
the scent becomes even stronger.
You two have said so much.
I only want to ask:
Is this stone a burial item?
This is just a raw stone.
There are no signs of human carving.
It's not a burial item.
Then why would it appear here?
Look.
I walked all the way here
and did not take
or touch anything.
This stone
is not a burial item anyway.
I want to keep it as a souvenir.
It is also for the two of you.
If you argue again in the future,
I will put this between you
and let you smell it.
Once you smell...
Well.
I will keep it for now.
Come to me if you need it.
Chen.
There are so many mechanisms here.
You can't act alone anymore.
I don't want to walk with you.
I think acting alone is great.
Why?
Because of Bai Lingling?
Yes.
I just feel she has another agenda.
Even if she does,
she doesn't even have a helper now.
What could she do?
Then why keep a ticking time bomb
by your side?
We can't just let her die.
What does her death have to do with you?
You two,
stop arguing, alright?
Ms. He,
if you really don't trust Bai Lingling,
why don't we
just ask her directly?
Do you think she'd tell the truth?
Who am I?
Just leave it to me.
Let's go.
What was that sound?
We took you in
out of kindness, you know.
Just follow us honestly.
Why do you keep annoying Ms. He?
She is the one who is jealous.
Not my business.
Not your business?
A few words from you
caused their fight.
One bad ladle ruins
the whole pot of soup.
Don't move.
Let go of me.
What are you doing?
I am doing this for your good.
Listen.
Answer
all my questions.
If you refuse to tell the truth,
I will tie you up right here
and let you fend for yourself.
Chen Youxi,
is this how you treat a friend?
We are not friends.
Earlier, you told Huang Long
that anyone could die
except Chen Youxi and Ms. He.
What did you mean?
If Chen Youxi died,
how could I move forward?
What about Ms. He?
If she died,
would Chen Youxi still help me?
That still doesn't make sense.
If Chubby and I died,
he'd also fight you to the death.
Are you sure?
She is really infuriating.
Sowing discord.
You are still arrogant
even while tied up.
Enough, Bai Lingling.
Stop being vague.
Just tell us directly
what you need Chen Youxi and me
to help you with.
You already know
why I need Chen Youxi.
As for you,
you are knowledgeable
and highly accomplished in semiotics.
According to my research,
that eyeball symbol
has some connection with semiotics.
Once we find the real main hall,
bringing you along
might help us solve
the mystery of the curse.
I think that long speech just now
made a lot of sense.
Do you even have a stance?
Well.
If you are still not reassured,
you can keep me tied up.
If you still want to break the curse
and continue moving forward,
there will be a time when you need me.
How about this?
I will keep an eye on her.
Alright then.
Sorry about this, Miss Bai.
Move.
Chen,
I really want to know
how the two of you got up here.
We fell into the Bagua chamber
and got trapped in the Qian chamber.
How did you manage it?
Power and wealth fade away
with time.
Only wisdom and knowledge
can endure forever.
These tomb builders, back then,
were seen as craftsmen,
laborers,
the lowest class,
unworthy of high society.
Yet every mechanism I encountered
in this tomb shows their mastery
of astronomy,
Feng Shui,
numerology,
physics,
mechanics, and more.
If they lived today,
they would be scientists,
architects,
and astronomers.
Their value far exceeds
that of the imperial nobles
who enslaved them.
They are the ones
who truly deserve
to be remembered in history.
If what you say is true,
then this tomb
has several floors.
With all the slopes and stairs,
it's hard to say
what the exact structure is.
But that last mechanism was interesting.
Most mechanisms
are built to stop tomb raiders.
Yet the last one
not only had a solution,
but it felt like it was communicating
with Chen.
An emotional resonance is
just my personal feeling.
But for the tomb builder
to express himself
through mechanism design
in such a grand tomb
is truly unheard of.
What are you doing? Do you want to die?
Help.
Police station. Call the police.
What?
Call the police.
♪A tiny ark sails;
the sky opens its eyes♪
♪Stillness in motion,
the earth plays its chord♪
♪A leaf falls;
we cross through time and space♪
♪In a blink, all things rest
upon our hands♪
♪La la♪
♪No line divides the border♪
♪Nothing limits your performance♪
♪Everything shows perfect harmony♪
♪Love circles the sky,
the earth, and our faith♪
♪Hey hey hey♪
♪Hey hey♪
♪Step into the galaxy of colors♪
♪Stars connect our hearts as one♪
♪No difference between you and me♪
♪No lead or side role on this stage♪
♪A perfect life is something we share♪
♪Love declares across the sky and earth♪
♪Huo la yi ya, huo la yi ya♪
♪Time and space go beyond all bounds♪
♪This is our world♪
♪Shining lives bring the change♪
♪In a blink, to forever♪