=The Secret of the Lost Pearl=
=Episode 20=
(Fiction. Do not imitate.)
How's Lu?
Lu,
are you okay?
What is this place?
Have we already left the tomb?
Are we out of danger?
You're overthinking, Lu.
Look.
That big eyeball is still staring at us.
What is that?
Fireflies?
Yeah, I think so.
I was looking at them for a while.
How come these fireflies
form an eyeball shape?
If this were just a cave,
we should have exited the tomb
and entered the mountain.
But it seems
this eyeball pattern hides a secret.
Anyway,
we've walked here for so long.
We've finally pieced together
this tomb's information
like a puzzle.
Since this eyeball pattern
is related to the curse on Chen Youxi,
let's keep moving.
Maybe
when we piece together
the truth,
the curse can be lifted.
Brilliant.
Brilliant, Ms. He.
Chen,
she's worried sick for you.
Say something.
Say a few words.
- Ms. He...
- I'm going to scout out.
Chen Youxi, what's wrong with you?
Why so silent?
She even played
The Phoenix Seeks a Mate.
Tell her what you think.
Enough.
What attitude is that?
Stop.
Judge for yourself.
How could Chen do that?
Right, when Lu woke up,
I saw Bai Lingling
take something out of her bag
secretively.
I'll be extra careful.
Look.
The fireflies twinkling here.
Pretty romantic, right?
Did you know
that across the ocean in Ireland,
there's a place
called the Waitomo Cave?
That's New Zealand.
You've been there?
Well.
Tell me.
Is it fun there?
Are there fireflies?
Would you understand if I told you?
As long as you speak Chinese,
I can understand every word.
Wait a moment.
Even if I don't understand,
you can teach me.
You need to be kind.
Shameless.
The Phoenix Seeks a Mate
you mentioned...
There's a lotus lamp here.
The color is quite unique.
Lotus lamp?
Let's go see.
Fire!
Lu?
Oh, no.
My legs are burning.
What happened?
Come help me!
Lu!
Come put out the fire!
Put out the fire!
Lu.
- Lu.
- Hurry!
Let me see.
Does it hurt?
Don't touch me.
It's all burnt off.
Good for you,
burning yourself while warming up.
What do you mean?
Am I that stupid?
Then what happened?
I don't know.
It just started burning.
Where were you just now?
Just a moment ago,
I went to find a place to pee.
I wandered around
and went there.
Then, I smelled something fragrant.
I wondered who was roasting.
And I caught fire.
That's crazy.
It's white phosphorus.
White phosphorus?
Where did it come from?
The glowing on the cave ceiling
isn't fireflies;
it's fluorite.
The white phosphorus
was applied to the fluorite.
When we made fire,
the cave temperature rose,
and the phosphorus fell on you.
Luckily, you noticed it.
If the fire kept burning,
the temperature rising,
everything would fall,
and it could've set us all on fire.
Chen, we can't stay here.
Let's go.
Go where?
I just saw
a light deep in the cave.
Light? What light?
Is it there?
Yes.
What?
Tell me.
Am I the only one
who finds this place creepy?
You find
everything creepy.
No, I have a sixth sense.
Trust me.
Slow down.
Take it easy.
I'm fine.
My sixth sense tells me
this place is different
from the others.
How?
The previous tunnels
and chambers
were cold.
But this place...
Is it warm?
You must've peed.
I'm telling you serious things.
Smell it.
What smell?
A wild animal stench,
like the lion and tiger area
in the zoo.
- Stop your nonsense.
- Really.
You're so good at making up stories.
When you get back,
don't mess with your antiques.
Set up a storytelling stall
on the bridge.
I'll give you 0.5 yuan
every day to boost your business.
What do you think?
What is this thing?
What is this?
Is that necessary?
It's just a big bat.
Bat?
What a creepy place.
Princess Xian'an,
Xiangmu,
Princess of Yan State,
daughter of Li Kuo,
Emperor Dezong of Tang.
I know this.
Back then,
The Huihu helped the Tang
quell the An-Shi Rebellion.
The Tang owed them a favor.
The Huihu sent emissaries
to request a marriage alliance.
Li Kuo initially refused.
He couldn't give up on his daughter.
Later, Prime Minister Li Mi
brought officials
to pressure the emperor,
forcing him to agree
to this marriage alliance.
Soldiers escorted Princess Xian'an
to the Huihu.
So, this tomb's owner
is Li Kuo's eldest daughter,
Princess Xian'an.
That doesn't seem right.
Historical records say
Princess Xian'an died in the Huihu
and never returned home.
Many historical truths
can't be recorded.
Right?
You can say that,
but that doesn't make sense.
Princess Xian'an married
into the Huihu.
She belonged to them.
She was the Khatun,
the Khan's wife.
That was a prestigious position.
After death,
she'd have been buried properly
and carefully protected.
How could she
be sent back to the Tang secretively?
Sorry.
Besides,
doing that is risky.
Who could be so determined
and capable
to bring her back?
Where's Chubby?
Chubby! Chubby!
What are you doing?
Chubby, run!
Run, Chubby!
Run!
Go!
(Xiangmu, Princess Xian'an)
- Lu.
- Sit.
Sit here.
I was scared.
Oh, my. That was close.
Lu,
why were you lying still just now?
I haven't enjoyed enough of my life,
and you almost got me killed.
My legs were weak.
Chubby,
luckily, you pulled me.
You saved my life.
Next life, I'll be a girl
and marry you.
Stop being gross.
Just stay put.
What exactly is that?
A spider?
A Ghost-Face Spider.
What?
A spider with a human-face pattern
on its body.
It's huge.
How did it grow so big?
It was born in the Tang dynasty.
Not surprising.
The Tang dynasty...
Still alive now?
Where's Bai Lingling?
Sorry.
That girl...
Chubby, Chubby!
Chen Youxi, I'll go too.
You stay and take care of Lu.
Be careful.
Those two are too daring.
Risking their lives for a girl.
Ms. He,
you should have stopped them.
Don't you have better things to do?
Well, Ms. He.
I didn't mean that.
Youxi is a good comrade.
But Li Ke is no good.
You can tell by that girl's eyes
that she's trouble.
Introduce a good girl to Li Ke,
so he doesn't pick badly.
She got hurt.
You're too disobedient,
leaving the team on your own.
Do you know how dangerous that is?
Sit here.
Does it hurt?
What happened?
Shutong, check her.
Leave us alone.
This jerk.
My little cannon
didn't kill it.
I noticed this giant spider
only walks
to that stone tablet
and then retreats.
It seems true.
You must hate it that I'm not hurt.
I don't care about that.
But let me tell you:
If you act alone again,
I won't let them save you.
I didn't ask them;
they just have kind hearts.
Bai Lingling, listen to me.
I know what you're thinking.
If you want to keep
the luminous pearl for yourself,
I advise you to give up.
Don't forget.
I'm here on a mission.
If my boss wants that pearl,
I will take it.
Fine.
Then let's see
if you can do that.
♪A tiny ark sails;
the sky opens its eyes♪
♪Stillness in motion,
the earth plays its chord♪
♪A leaf falls;
we cross through time and space♪
♪In a blink, all things rest
upon our hands♪
♪La la♪
♪No line divides the border♪
♪Nothing limits your performance♪
♪Everything shows perfect harmony♪
♪Love circles the sky,
the earth, and our faith♪
♪Hey hey hey♪
♪Hey hey♪
♪Step into the galaxy of colors♪
♪Stars connect our hearts as one♪
♪No difference between you and me♪
♪No lead or side role on this stage♪
♪A perfect life is something we share♪
♪Love declares across the sky and earth♪
♪Huo la yi ya, huo la yi ya♪
♪Time and space go beyond all bounds♪
♪This is our world♪
♪Shining lives bring the change♪
♪In a blink, to forever♪