The earth is full of laughter
This bloody and sad blood is full of bow and arrow
The old and new heartache is suffering alone in the old
This sentence is a life of a knife
The abyss is full of hard to embroider, nowhere to escape
This bloody and sad blood is full of bow and arrow
Eat the heart and make a mess, break through the ten thousand and ten thousand
A lifetime of love will never forget this morning
The Long Ballad
Episode 1
Father
I am going to die
You are also rebels, always
Father
Father, father, how are you, father
Yan, you go quickly
I beg you, let my father go, let us go
Yan, don't beg him
Father, father
These rebels, what's the use of them
No, no
Father
Father, father
Father, mother
Don't worry, I will not let them go
General Li has been a hero for his whole life
He is loyal to the country
After returning to the old Li, he should have a good life
Who knows, he will be a hero in the future
General Li, you are a hero
You are a hero
General Nie circled the party
Pissed off, loyal to the country
For me, he did this for a reason
This is retribution.
General Li,
the state's important affairs
are not as small as you.
You're so excited.
Is there anything between you and him?
Everyone knows that General Li is loyal to the family.
You are so vicious and hurt.
Could it be that the case of the destruction of the family is related to you?
Where did you get the idea?
Get out of here!
I think you look so ugly in black.
You must be separated from your family.
There must be bloodshed in the pool.
The whole family will be dead within three days.
You're talking nonsense.
Do you know who I am?
You're the young master of the Ghost Valley.
You should know it.
The Ghost Valley.
I'm waiting for you.
You're really a man of your word.
Why don't you have a banquet in the city today
and take a break?
First, you'll get rid of the disaster.
Second,
you'll have more ghosts.
You found it yourself.
Young Master,
the little monkey is missing.
I won't let you down today.
Let's go.
Five,
six,
seven,
eight,
nine.
Who is it?
Why are you so blind?
Young Master,
you're really a man of your word.
You believe such nonsense?
He likes to have fun.
It must be at the banquet.
Let's go.
Welcome to the wedding party.
Tonight is the wedding night.
Everyone is having fun.
Young Master.
Young Master, are you having fun?
Are you having fun?
Young Master, please.
Why are you all so excited?
This way, please.
Young Master.
Are you here to find...
Behind you.
Young Master.
Why are you so handsome?
Young Master, don't be shy.
Who are you looking for?
Come in.
Young Master.
If it's really you,
I must take you to the tomb
and bury you in the ground.
Young Master.
Everything is well arranged.
Did you find the thief?
No.
Come on.
Let's go.
The auspicious time has come.
Young Master.
Let's go.
The bride is about to come out.
I don't know what to do.
I think you're dark and dark.
You're full of shame.
You must have a family separation.
There must be bloodshed in ten steps.
In three days,
all the clans will be dead.
That's what I said.
You can't live on your own.
I'm afraid of everything.
I'm so worried.
I want to believe you once.
The bride is coming.
Do you want to see how beautiful she is?
I know.
Action.
Four.
Who is it?
Someone is killed.
Zhu Fei is killed.
Good night.
Beauty.
The bright night is beautiful today.
I want to say goodbye to you.
We're even now.
From now on,
as long as you want,
I will love you with all my heart.
Don't cry.
Why are you crying?
I'll untie you.
Untie you, will you?
If I didn't want to keep our clan safe,
I wouldn't have had to take you back for the wedding.
It's all that bastard's fault.
Forget it. I don't care.
If you don't want to,
when I get the disaster,
I'll give you a gift
and send you back.
Stop crying.
How come it's you?
You're a scoundrel.
You'll be killed
when I catch you.
You're a scoundrel.
Where are you going?
He's not a human.
I have to find a way
to find out the truth as soon as possible.
You're the one who's waiting.
Do you want to see
if you have the talent of blood?
You...
Tell me.
Who are you?
You're making fun of me.
Why are you doing this?
If you don't tell me,
I'll kill you
one by one.
Kill you?
Come closer.
You want to play, right?
I'll play enough with you today.
The three swords of the sword
are exactly the same as the black man's.
Could it be
that they
are really capable of fighting with me alone?
You're despicable.
You're shameless.
What did you say?
You're despicable.
You're shameless.
You're shameless!
I love him.
You're shameless.
You're shameless!
I'm...
What did you say?
I won't let you go.
You're so self-righteous.
Young Master.
My head.
I'm afraid you're crazy.
Let's go.
If you dare to enter the Ghost Valley,
you'll be dead.
Shi Tou.
Throw him into the back mountain to feed the wolves.
Remember.
Don't alert the Master.
Yes, Young Master.
I'll make a fool of my innocence.
Who will be the one to be blamed if the law is broken?
I've been through ups and downs in my youth.
But I've fallen in love with you.
We've been through ups and downs together.
That's our destiny to live and die
Snow falls on a Qing Shan mountain
Zabdご ва 깏та
membership is over
Leave the earth and love is short
Never letting lie don't reason with the machines