How ridiculous the world is
This bloody sadness is full of blood
You are suffering and suffering alone
This sentence is not over yet
The abyss is full of difficulties and there is nowhere to escape
This bloody sadness is full of blood
Eat the heart and act as a cold and rush to the end
A life full of difficulties and there is nowhere to escape
The Abyss of Love
Episode 16
A'Xi, come here
Madam
Come here
You caught me
It's my turn to catch you
A'Xi, where are you?
I'm going to catch you
Who is going to save me?
I don't want to die
A'Xi
This old woman, Jiang Wei
I don't understand
What's going on with you?
A'Xi, I didn't expect you to play with me
You are so good
I like it
Madam
Is it interesting to play with it?
You are cute
A'Xi, I'm going to catch you
A'Xi, I caught you
A'Xi
Am I good?
In the past, Yang Guifei bathed in Huaqing Lake
Today, you and I are in the Baihua Lake to take a break
It's really moving
A'Xi
I can't wait
It smells good
Madam, you are not in the mood today
I'm sleepy after drinking
I'm going to sleep
The past is gone
Why?
I'm not in the mood
A'Xi
What's the relationship between my father and Wan Qinghong?
Why are you so stupid?
I'm asking you
Is Xiao Hao here?
He should be
What do you mean he should be?
Did you find Xiao He?
Is Xiao Hao here?
If he is, we should go
This place is really not a place for people to stay
I almost got carried away by that old woman
This place is extraordinary
As I inferred
Xiao He should be safe
This place is like a ghost valley
It's hard to get in and out
Besides, with Wan Qinghong's martial arts
Even if you and I work together
It's hard to fight against it
As long as Xiao He is fine
Why did you come to such a ghost place?
I think this place is not compatible with me
I came here from the mountain
It's a
In my opinion, that lady is quite lucky
You don't have a bad mouth, do you?
What kind of lady is she?
She's almost my mother's age
This kind of woman must keep a distance
And you have to promise me one thing
What?
You know it
Anyway, if you dare to say a word
I'll make you die
Threaten me?
In my opinion
We should get Wan Qinghong first
I'll fall to death if I can't do anything
Xiao He
I brought you something
Come and have a look
This is the chicken soup I made for you
Try it
Xiao He
I didn't mean to leave you here
I just want to see you
I just
Madam
What's wrong with you?
Do you know?
You really look like my daughter
You look like my daughter
You look like her
Even the bracelet you're wearing
Is exactly like my daughter's
I picked this bracelet up from the woods when I was a child
Did she misunderstand me as her daughter?
What about your daughter?
Madam
Don't be sad
I have no parents since I was a child
Maybe
I'm your daughter
Come here, your highness
I don't know what this old woman is up to
I'll put it in her wine
A Xi
Today
Today I'll let you try the most fun game here
Go
Old rules
The loser
The loser will be the one who makes the flower fertilizer
Are you ready?
The game is about to start
The first round of the game, start!
You're so stupid
The second round of the game, start!
It's you
Then I
will treat you to grapes
Continue, continue
I'm done, I'm done
You little naughty
You're going to die
I'll find a way to let them live
Continue, start!
A Xi, Jian Wei
You two are so kind
But in this world
Not all kindness
will have good rewards
King of the Deceased, spare my life, I dare not
Looking at you
so cute
I'll give you a little punishment
Then
beat you to death
Great, great
I'm tired today
A Xi, Jian Wei
You drink with me
Coming, coming
King of the Deceased, spare my life, I dare not
What are you still doing here
Get out of here
Yes
Madam
Madam, why are you so extreme
Yes, madam
You, you're playing too crazy
You scared me
Young people nowadays
really learned to
fish for fame
Why are they
fooled by you
People are not grass
Madam, you are too cruel
I'm cruel
So what
In this world
we are all weak
Not to mention
In this Baihua Villa
I'm the only one who can talk
You two
Don't think
you can
You can tell me
to die
You
You poisoned my wine
No
Madam, you're drunk
Say
Where is the antidote
No antidote
You let her go
She gave me the antidote
Don't
Don't give her the antidote
Give it to me
Okay, I'll give it to you
Didn't you say you didn't want to give it to her
You'll die if I don't give it to her
This isn't the antidote
You're
despicable
You almost killed Xiao Ye
How can you not use any tricks
She's poisoned
She won't last long
I think we should go find Xiao He first
Madam, please
Xiao He
Why are you here
Madam, I just saw
dead people
in the garden
I'm scared
Xiao He, be good
Don't be afraid, it's not clean here
I'll send you back to your room
Today, for my daughter's sake
I'll spare you
Go
Madam, what's wrong with you
Are you okay?
Madam
Madam, what's wrong with you