The King of Blaze
Episode 16
It's just a doll of Madam Ban!
How dare you lie to Madam Ban!
How dare you poison Madam Ban!
My head!
It hurts!
Madam.
Madam, are you alright?
Don't be mad.
They are all good people.
What did you say?
They are good people?
You mean,
I'm a bad person?
Mother.
What are you laughing at?
Little Walnut.
Are you alright?
Mother.
I didn't mean to do that.
It's all my fault.
No!
It's all their fault.
It's all their fault!
I must kill them.
I must kill them!
Mother.
Don't be mad.
You are drunk.
It's alright.
You are very drunk.
Let me help you to rest.
的
Qin Wei!
It's me.
You scared me.
I almost died in your hands
instead of that crazy woman.
Who told you to get so close?
I just wanted to...
Forget it.
I don't want to fight with you.
You scared me.
I've never been to such a place.
I said this place is not suitable for me.
Who are you?
You scared me.
I can become the master of this place.
I'm the one you love the most.
We all have to die.
I'm going to steal the Queen for you.
If you want it, go get it.
Here you go.
Help.
Brother.
I want you to die.
Help.
Brother.
Let go.
Little boy.
Brother Jingfei, how are you?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Little boy.
Be clear.
If you're late, you won't see me.
Forget it.
Why are you here?
Did she do anything to you?
Brother, I'm fine.
Madam Wan thinks I'm her daughter.
She's nice to me.
Her daughter?
You?
We can't stay here for long.
Let's talk on the way.
Let's get out of here.
Let's go. Hurry.
Stop.
Come back.
I'm going to kill you.
Queen.
I want to be the queen.
You wanna be the queen?
You want to be the queen?
No.
I still wanna try.
I'm still can't take it any more.
You'reJust being stubborn.
我赢定了.
I won't let you fall again,
Where are we going?
Mother, don't hurt them.
Madam, we didn't mean to offend you.
We were afraid that Xiao He would disappear.
We were so worried.
Please forgive us and let us go.
That means
you planned the meeting
in the Ninth Building.
A'xi,
is that right?
Yes.
We can't find
your mother's silver nest.
That's why we did it.
What did you say?
Say it again!
I'll say it.
Mother!
Mother,
please don't hurt them.
Xiao He, get up.
I want to stay with you.
Xiao He.
Mother, please forgive them.
Please.
Mother.
Fine.
I can let them go.
Really?
Don't worry.
I haven't finished yet.
You bitch!
Why are you talking nonsense?
You want to settle the score?
You're so good at driving.
I haven't settled the score yet.
Let her finish first.
As long as you kill someone for me,
bring his body back
and make him a bandit for me,
I'll let Xiao He go with you.
Kill someone?
Who?
Li Pu.
Li Pu?
General of the Guardian, Li Pu?
Isn't he dead?
What did you say?
He's dead?
When?
You don't know?
He's already dead.
Last year, on the New Year's Eve,
General Li was killed.
No one survived.
Impossible.
You're lying to me.
He promised me
he would come back to me.
You must be lying to me.
Without my consent,
how could he die?
How could he die?
You must be lying to me.
Without my consent,
he can't die.
How could he die?
Humph.
After a long time,
you're the old friend of that bastard.
What a pity.
He didn't come to you.
Nonsense.
He promised to come back to me.
I've been against him for so many years.
He's been poisoned.
For so many years.
Why are you trying to provoke him?
Who told him to be with that bastard?
Liar.
You...
Identify his body.
Identify his next life.
Out of copulation.
Gorgeous dresses.
Where will it go?
Your sleeve has been knitted.
Zihua Grass.
How could this happen?
Back to the palace.
The half-moon is here.
How could this happen?
Take Zihua Grass.
Back to the palace.
The half-moon is here.
Mother.
What are you doing?
Mother, are you okay?
Xiao He Tao.
I am. I am.
Mother, don't scare me.
I am scared.
Xiao He Tao.
My daughter.
No.
You are not.
My daughter.
What are you doing?
You are Shi Xin Feng.
Shi Xin Feng?
My daughter.
Why don't we kill her?
Xiao Ye, I will kill her now.
My daughter.
Mother.
Listen to me.
I don't want you to end up like me.
So you can't fall in love with anyone.
Otherwise, you will be hurt.
Do you know?
I really hope
you can grow up healthy
and happy.
Do you hear me?
Calm down, mother.
I will kill her.
Come on.
My poor wife.
Where is my little sister?
If you don't tell me now,
I will burn your house.
Take the flowers and put them back.
I will be a nun.
I will be a king.
Where is my sister?
You crazy woman.
I am not crazy.
In this world,
everyone is pursuing fame and fortune.
Everyone is pursuing their own ambitions.
Which one of you is not crazy?
Cut the crap.
Where did you hide her?
You want her?
Fine.
If you want to know where she is,
kill her.
Jiawei.
Are you really going to listen to her?
I am not going to listen to her.
Xianfang.
Do it.
But
after I die,
you must take her back safely.
So touching.
Then let's die together.
No.