Eternal Love of Dream
Episode 32
Try this.
Here.
Your Highness.
Your Majesty.
To see the fun,
you've used every trick up your sleeve.
It's the most interesting thing
since the creation of the universe, anyway.
I just need to give up a bit of my cultivation.
Now that you can do that,
why can't I?
Take a seat.
Am...
Am I in a dream?
Why did Lian Song
come to Fanyin Valley with Li?
Am I still sleeping?
It's really a dream.
It doesn't hurt at all.
Are you enjoying pinching me?
Your clothes have creased. Let me smooth it.
Princess Jiuge.
I came here
to take an elixir
refined by the Supreme Venerable Lord to Dong Hua,
but Li couldn't pull himself together
since he lost his cousin
who was playing with him,
so I took him here to cheer him up.
It happens that you're hosting a dinner party,
so we're here without invitation.
No worries.
It's my honor.
I was worried that Dong Hua would suffer
if I came here late,
but it seems he's...
I don't need it at this moment,
but I may need it in the future.
I knew you wouldn't be that polite.
Master.
I told you
not to touch Longevity Vine.
Do you still remember that?
I'm just afraid
you're not used to food prepared by Princess Jiuge.
So I cooked some soup
and took it to you.
I'm also afraid you're not used to
lotus seed soup without Longevity Vine in it.
It's okay.
I just touched a little.
Don't worry about me.
I...
I'll go see if the dishes have been prepared.
I'll go with you.
Me too. Me too.
Just stay here. Don't make trouble.
One more for you.
And you, stop making trouble.
Forget about it.
You're picky. You don't like this.
Here you are.
I'll follow you while eating.
I want to go out for fun with you.
I can eat the cakes while doing that.
Ji Heng didn't cook soup for you,
but she did for Dong Hua.
You're envious and sad, right?
What to do?
I just made mung bean cakes, red bean cakes
and plum pudding
against unexpected needs.
Besides, in plum pudding
I put ginger powder which you don't like.
Fine. Just go with me.
Why didn't you make something I like to eat?
Did you forget what I like?
I remember.
It's plum sorbet.
I'll ask them to get you some of that.
I've heard chefs here are good at cooking.
Let's see if it's to your taste.
Okay.
Let them take some here.
And I like salty food these days.
Don't put liquorice. Put in some salt.
If it's not good,
go back to the old way.
Maybe I can also try egg-yolk puff.
Okay.
I'll make some salty food for you.
Master, the soup spilled.
Princess Jiuge,
I've heard that you're good at cooking.
Among cakes and pastries,
I like red bean and mung bean cakes best.
I wonder if I have a chance
to taste some cakes made by you.
Sure.
I'll wait for you outside.
Okay.
Master,
let me get you more soup.
You know well about what he likes.
Do you want to try the cakes?
But I'm not good at making cakes.
I'm best at cooking fish.
You tasted it, right?
Do you still want to have cakes?
But they've been given out.
How about this?
Li still has some.
Ask him if he wants to share with you.
Grandpa Lian has six cakes.
I have only four.
Grandpa Lian should share with him.
I won't.
Besides, I'm a kid.
My mom said
I should eat more to grow taller.
It seems
Princess Jiuge knows better about Yan Chiwu's taste
and doesn't know much about yours.
These cakes happen to be to my taste,
but I wonder if they're to yours.
Why do you bother to get mad
because of some cakes
you're not sure if you like?
We've been friends for years.
Do you have to do that?
Xiaojiu, are you leaving or not?
If they fail to make cakes for me in time,
you'll have to do that for me.
Who is it?
Who dares to attack me?
Sorry.
It slipped from my hand.
It slipped so far.
The soup made by Ji Heng.
It's good!
What a waste of my money.
Why are they all unhappy?
The banquet is wasted.
You used so much of your magic arts to enter the valley
just to have a dinner?
And you came back immediately after that?
Don't worry.
With His Majesty in Fanyin Valley,
there is nothing to worry about.
I've underestimated
your interest in gossiping.
I thought you'd go to ask Lord Cheng Yu,
but unexpectedly, you entered the valley directly.
I won't bother Cheng Yu
because of another man's issue.
She only needs to
worry about me.
I'm convinced.
You hate her,
but you're not her match.
You love him,
but you can do nothing about it.
Who are you?
Where on earth are you?
Who on earth are you?
You're deep in love with Emperor Dong Hua, right?
How did you know that?
It doesn't matter how I knew that
or who I am.
You just need to tell me
if you want to get him.
What do you mean?
You fell in love with him before you knew it,
but pitifully,
there is another woman.
You hate it,
but you can do nothing about it.
You tried to win his love,
but he didn't pay any attention
to how you felt.
What on earth do you want to do?
Do you dare to change the status quo
and try again to win?
But as you said,
no matter what I did,
he wouldn't care about me.
What if I have an idea?
I've figured out a way
to make them be suspicious of each other.
Suspicious?
If they don't trust each other,
you'll have a chance to get close to him.
Tell me
what your idea is.
It's simple.
To get pimpon fruit.
Pimpon fruit.
Trust me.
For you,
it'll be easy.
Ji Heng,
what's up?
Shall I take you back to your room?
I'm okay.
Yan,
can you do me a favor?
Just go ahead.
No matter what you want me to do,
I'll try my best.
Yan,
why are you here?
Do you want to eat something?
What's up?
Xiaojiu, I...
I'm sorry.
What are you sorry for?
I plan to join the tournament
to get pimpon fruit.
Why?
I want to get pimpon fruit
to help Ji Heng get better.
Did she ask you to do that?
No.
I insisted on it.
She's in poor health.
I've heard pimpon fruit can help to improve cultivation,
so I want to win it.
I thought you're a true man.
You value lover over friend.
I...
I also feel like I've betrayed you,
but trust me.
If I win by chance,
I'll share the fruit with you.
Alright.
If I win,
I'll also share it with you
so that you can save your love.
You're not mad at me?
You're a good friend.
Trust me. I'm bound to win.
How about you withdrawing from the tournament?
I'll share the fruit with you after I win.
Don't bother.
I'll be your tutor this time.
Come on in.
Yan,
why are you smiling like a fool?
Ji Heng asked me for a favor.
She asked me instead of others.
What do you think it means?
What does it mean?
It means you're a good servant.
Come on.
You know nothing about it.
Mind your own business.
I see. Yan.
You're driving me away when my help is not required.
I must go.
I'll try my best to get it for Ji Heng.
Get what?
She wants pimpon fruit.
I'll win it for her.
Pimpon fruit?
Come on.
Do you also want it?
I just promised to Xiaojiu I'd share it with her.
If you want it too,
I'm afraid it's not enough for us.
Does she want pimpon fruit
because Xiaojiu wants it?
Don't say that.
She needs pimpon fruit to recover
from Qiushui Cold Toxin.
Before you came to Fanyin Valley,
her excuse for staying with
master was she's in poor health.
In my opinion,
she came to you
just because he ignored her.
Well...
Actually,
I know nothing about it. I'm just a little girl.
It was just a wild guess.
I said that because I'm jealous.
It's my fault.
I shouldn't have cursed others.
Are...
Are you going to cry?
Jielu,
you...
You know well enough about yourself.
Don't let it happen again.
Now that Ji Heng has me,
she won't have anything
to do with that ice face.
It's okay as long as you're happy.
It's a waste of time
to show mercy to you.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to see my brother.
He's got many things to do recently.
If Meng needs my help, remember to tell me about it.
Why?
We're men.
If he needs help,
it's better for him to talk to me.
You're even not as reliable as Xiaojiu.
I...
Enough.
I'll let you know in case he needs help.
Why is she in a rush?
Ji Heng is waiting for me.
I can't keep her waiting.
It matches perfectly.
Even a fly couldn't come in.
Is it necessary to set up such a ward?
They can't come in
and you can't go out.
I said I'd be your tutor. Do you think I'm kidding?
Are you serious?
Definitely.
What do you want to teach me?
Through closed training of ten days,
from morning to night without rest,
your skills will be taken to a higher level.
I'm happy beyond words
to have you as my tutor.
I've never accepted any apprentice.
Numerous people have dreamed of that.
Then why did you lock me down?
What's the relationship between the two things?
I did it to train you.
Fine.
Now that you said that,
I'm afraid you'll lose face
if I lose in the final.
Do you mean you don't want pimpon fruit?
Yes.
Of course I do.
Then go back and have a good rest.
We'll start from walking on snowy stakes tomorrow morning.
Yes, sir.
His Majesty invested so much
to bask in the sunshine
on the snowfield.
It's nothing.
Today,
you need to practice so that you walk on them
as easily as walking on firm earth.
Try to do it blindfolded tomorrow
and make sure you come and go freely.
On the third day,
you'll practice swordsmanship and master the skills.
Your Majesty,
you've overestimated me.
I've deactivated your magic arts,
but you managed to stand there for a long time.
You're quite competent.
I...
I forgot to tell you.
Without magic arts,
I'm actually afraid of heights.
See?
You asked me to do that on purpose, right?
You wanted to touch me up when I fell down.
Are you talking in your dream?
Or why are you holding me?
Your hand is still around my waist.
It seems you can keep your feet.
You're narrow-minded.
I'm just kidding.
Don't be so mean.
How could I come and go freely
on snowy stakes blindfolded in one day?
You're just making a fool of me.
You wouldn't teach me
your unique skills. You're so mean.
I've heard
you should count yourself lucky
if you have a master who
likes to make fun when you're young.
You'll benefit from it the whole life.
I didn't read much,
but I think it's a strict master.
Really?
I forgot.
Pretty much.
Now that you want pimpon fruit,
then just do as I say.
It's not hard
to let you win out by playing tricks,
but unfortunately,
they invited me to be the judge.
Do you think
I could let people employ trickery?
You must've done lots of such things.
Just pretend that
I've become cautious suddenly.
Thank you for spending time
on training me.
No problem.
It's rare
to meet someone who's as unpromising as you.
I want to challenge myself.
Zhihe was that hopeless,
but you still taught her.
Zhihe?
Many years ago,
I taught her for some reason.
But she gave up.
She got a new master later.
Do you mind
that thing very much?
Nah.
But she didn't learn a lot
from me.
Do you know why?
Because she thought she didn't need to learn anything
since I was there.
If I were Zhihe,
I would also think
I don't need to learn anything.
You?
You're different, Xiaobai.
I've placed
great expectations on you.
We've talked a lot. I'm thirsty.
I'll go brew some tea. You keep practicing.
Would you like a cup?
Come down.
Turn around. Close your eyes.
Did you hear me?
Cheng Yu, you're in a good mood.
It's rare to see you feed fish leisurely.
What's up?
Nothing special.
I just miss Fengjiu.
I wonder how she's doing in Fanyin Valley.
Don't worry.
She was pretty good
last time when Li and I saw her.
If you're really worried about her,
I'll set up a ward
so that you can have a look at her.
They...
Xiaobai.
Shouldn't you at least say something like
"sorry for biting you"?
Sorry.
Are you really sorry?
I have no reason to lie to you.
People lie
just to make themselves happy.
See?
Fengjiu is safe and sound.
She's living in Fanyin Valley joyfully,
with His Majesty staying with her.
They're closely associated.
It's great.
But...
I know what you're worried about.
As for fate,
even Si Ming can do nothing about it,
let alone us.
You're too slow.
Make yourself steady
whenever you step on a snowy stake.
Here. Drink some tea.
You're sweating.
Ji Heng.
Yan.
Yan, get up.
It's late at night. I want to sleep.
Hurry up, Yan.
Stop sleeping.
What are you doing?
Hurry up.
Well. I...
I want to sleep.
I...
Hurry up.
Where are we going?
It's late. Where are you taking me?
Let's go see my brother. He's drunk.
I just went to Jiuge,
but a ward was set up in her yard.
So I have to come to you.
Isn't it common for Meng to be drunk?
Why are you so surprised?
Don't go back.
He's been drinking at Zuilixian Restaurant
for several days and nights.
He wouldn't listen to anyone.
You're the only one I can ask for help.
It's just because of that thing.
In this case, it's a little troublesome.
Keep an eye on Meng.
I'll go there with Xiaojiu.
Okay. Hurry up.
Xiaojiu.
Your Majesty, please don't torture me again.
Let me have some sleep.
You and the ice face
have come so far?
I knew he's not as loyal as I am.
He failed to refuse a beautiful woman like you.
How did you come in?
I have a chance to get close to Ji Heng.
That's great.
What are you talking about?
Is it a dream?
It's not!
I'm here to take you to cheer a friend up.
What's going on?
Something happened to Meng.
Ever-victorious General.
My Ever-victorious General.
Meng,
let the deceased rest in peace
while the living must move on.
We need to bury it as soon as possible.
You're finally here.
Meng,
don't be too sad.
A dead person couldn't come back to life...
He's so heartbroken although it's just a token of affection.
I can't imagine what he'll do when he loses her.
He's crying bitterly because of a cricket's death.
He's affectionate.
Meng.
It's just a cricket.
I'll get you an invincible one
tomorrow.
You know nothing about it.
The cricket must've absorbed aura of nature
after staying in the valley for a long time
and become a pretty woman at midnight,
or Meng couldn't love it so much.
The cricket did absorb some aura of nature,
but that just made it live a longer life.
It couldn't have turned into anything.
But the one who sent it to Meng
is his crush.
He met a girl many years ago.
He got the cricket and the jar from her.
Since then,
he's been fascinated by her and promised to marry her.
So he's still single nowadays.
For Meng,
the cricket means a lot.
The cricket died the other day.
It made him miss that girl even more.
So he drowned his sorrows in drink.
A member of your clan can only
marry a person from the same clan.
That girl must belong to a different clan
now that Meng can't marry her.
If she's alive,
why doesn't he pluck up the courage to chase her?
It's no big deal to violate the clan rules.
Groaning for a cricket
is not what a real man should do.
I guess that girl is far away from him
and meeting her is impossible,
or he couldn't be crying so bitterly.
Who on earth is his crush?
I know.
Really?
On the day when His Majesty came here,
I heard Meng talk with his cousin.
I heard it by accident.
It's the Princess of Qingqiu.
Exactly.
But we're far away from Qingqiu
and she'll be the empress of Qingqiu.
I'm afraid Meng couldn't have a chance.
If it's true,
you'd better ask him to give up.
That princess is married.
Has Princess Fengjiu got married?
Why haven't we heard of such a big event?
Feng...
The person Meng had a crush on
is Fengjiu?
Yeah.
She is the only possible one.
It couldn't be God Bai Qian, right?
Thank you for saving me.
You saved me today.
I'll definitely pay you back in future.
Oh, no! It's broken!
Take mine instead.
Here you are.
Let's discuss it.
That explains why the jar looks familiar.
It's really you.
It happened many years ago.
I can't remember.
Looking at him carefully,
I found he looks like that boy
who blushed when he talked to me.
What to do now?
Shall we tell him the truth?
No. Don't do that.
If you do,
he'll suffer all his life.
Never tell him the truth. Got it?
Let's go.
You said
Princess Fengjiu is married.
It's just hearsay.
That's to say,
she may still be single.
Good. Great.
What do you want to do?
What you said
makes sense.
Do you also think
I should take the risks
to pursue what I love
regardless of the clan rules?
Actually, half a year ago,
I already thought about
surmounting all obstacles
to pursue Princess Fengjiu,
but unexpectedly, you fell down
and made me unconscious
as soon as I got out of town.
I thought
it was the will of heaven
and I was destined never to get close to Princess Fengjiu,
so I gave up.
But what you just said
sounds a little reasonable.
I miss Princess Fengjiu
but she knows nothing about that.
I should tell her
how I feel about her.
Accepting it or not is up to her.
Destiny let you tell me about that.
I've decided to
break the clan rules...
- ...and pursue what I love. - Hold on.
Hold on.
It's not destiny.
It's not what you're destined to do.
Look.
Your colored glaze jar.
It's still here.
So what?
The cricket is dead
but the jar is unbroken.
It means
it's not time for you to break the rules
and give up everything
to look for Fengjiu.
If heaven thought
it's time for you to do that,
the jar must've been destroyed
when the cricket died.
Is that right?
Exactly.
Speaking of breaking the clan rules,
you may look courageous by doing that,
but your clan members will be heartbroken.
So you'd better not do that easily
to avoid having a guilty conscience.
But you just...
Oh.
Meng,
if you need something to express your feelings,
it doesn't have to be the cricket.
You can turn to...
The colored glaze jar also works.
That's right.
It sounds reasonable,
but why do I
feel so dizzy?
Because you've drunk too much.
You're not sober.
You're not clear-minded.
Go back and lie on your bed.
You'll understand everything when you sober up.
Okay.
Servants.
Take me back to my mansion.