Eternal Love of Dream
Episode 23
I know you didn't mean what you said.
It's not easy for you to get it over
within such a short time.
That's not true.
I was just thinking about something,
and I didn't see you come in.
Don't deny it.
You've lost a lot of weight since I saw you a few days ago.
Cheng Yu.
Do you know what Romance-Forgetting Water tastes like?
Come on, Fengjiu.
You can't follow in your aunt's step.
You can't compare us.
Aunt and His Highness Crown Prince...
His Highness has always cared about aunt.
But His Majesty...
He doesn't even know who I am.
Stop talking about him. Let's go.
To where?
Don't stay in the mansion all the time.
I'll show you a good stuff.
What is it?
Something more tasteful than Romance-Forgetting Water.
Good tea.
This is a new tea I brought back from Mount Qinyao.
God Zhe Yan is such a great predictor.
I just got back from Qingqiu today.
And you knew it right away.
I came here to discuss something
with you.
I'm all ears.
I have a good friend
who likes Fengjiu a lot.
He asked me to propose a marriage for him.
I know you treat her well.
I'm wondering...
Your good friend is
Immortal Lord Cang Yi from Mount Zhiyue?
Exactly.
He came across Fengjiu
and fell in love with her at first sight.
So he particularly asked me to be a matchmaker.
I thought he would make a worthy suitor
for Xiaojiu.
So I came here to tell you about it.
But...
I'm not sure if Xiaojiu will like him.
Immortal Lord Cang Yi doesn't come from the gods.
But he manages to keep the mortal realm
thriving with his own power.
Definitely one of the best among junior immortals.
I noticed him earlier.
He and Xiaojiu are well suited.
Li,
what are you doing here?
So the marriage...
I will ask Xiaojiu
about it first.
After all, it depends on her.
Of course.
As the officiator of the marriage,
I even brought the marriage contract.
As long as Fengjiu agrees to it,
we'll get the marriage settled right away.
I know you hate to see her leave.
But she is going to marry someone eventually.
I'm waiting for the wedding feast.
Silly girl,
you still can't get over him.
I can get over him here.
But not here.
I descended to the mortal realm to help him
experience romance misfortune for paying back the favor.
I made him fall in love with me,
and love me deep into his bones.
And then I ignored him
and hurt him deep into his bones,
so he could end the romance misfortune
thoroughly.
Now he's back to the Sky Kingdom,
and everything goes smoothly as he wished
with no obstacles.
You'd think I helped him with
his romance misfortune,
paid the favor
and I've fulfilled my wish.
But no one know that I'd wanted to be nice to him
rather than just pay the favor.
I like him so much.
But I had no choice but to hurt him.
I broke his heart.
But my heart hurt even worse.
Your Majesty, are you feeling okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Flowers bloom and fade all the time.
People meet and get together by fate.
Your Majesty,
Si Ming has finished your book of merits
in mortal realm.
Do you want to take a look at it?
No.
Tell me.
How could I get over His Majesty?
The best way is
to find someone
who loves you and cares for you.
Someone who answers to
whatever you say.
Someone who cares about
all your emotions.
With someone being so good to you,
over time,
you will forget about
His Majesty who didn't treat you well.
Right.
You're right.
Okay.
Drink this
and get over His Majesty for good.
Don't get stuck in this over and over again.
I'm a woman from Qingqiu. I need to be decisive.
You are wearing the bracelet
Ye Qingti gave you every day.
How do you feel about him exactly?
If I hadn't gone down to the mortal realm,
and changed the misfortune,
he wouldn't have died.
I owe him my life.
I will find a way to save his life.
Who's eavesdropping on us?
Don't, don't.
It's me, Lian Song.
It's you.
Cheng Yu,
do what you have to do.
I'm heading back to Qingqiu.
Bye.
Is it a bad time to come?
What are you doing here?
The short knife is finally finished.
I came here to give it to you.
I should have presented it to you earlier.
But you borrowed my design drawing.
So it took some more time.
It's good that you take it out
when no one else is around.
Or
others may get upset.
It's my present for you.
It has nothing to do with others.
I'm not in the mood for jokes today.
You can go find others.
Cheng Yu. You...
Cheng Yu.
What do you mean others?
You are confusing me.
Where do I find others?
You promised to go on a date with me last time.
But you haven't finished it yet.
You ran off in the middle of it.
This time, you have to...
What exactly do you want?
I want you to promise me
to help me with the ceremony.
You...
I've got too much work to deal with.
Just help me check the list of people
attending the Mile-fleurs Ceremony, will you?
Why should I?
You promised to go on a date with me last time.
But you ran off in the middle of it.
If you don't want to help me with the checking,
you can finish the date with me.
I'm an easygoing person. I can...
If I help you this time,
it'll clean the slate, right?
Of course.
Okay, I'll do it now.
I will get this goddamn deal over!
Cheng Yu, no rush.
I'm not used to that. Cheng Yu.
It hurts!
Cheng Yu, you...
Wait for me.
These pictures in my head are so unfamiliar.
Are they what I went through in the mortal realm?
Why do I have memories of them?
Who is the woman
in my dream?
I thought we were going to Yuan Ji Palace.
Why are we here?
Who said the checking has to be done
in the room?
You were confined to the room due to your friend.
Why don't you come out and enjoy the flowers with me,
check the list with me
and get your mind out of things with me?
Get my mind out of things?
Okay.
Let me show you
how I get my mind out of things.
I didn't know you
like the short knife so much.
You can't wait to
try the short knife out,
and see if it's handy.
Rascal!
Your Majesty, pardon me for
disturbing you.
Take it.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
His Majesty has become quite reserved
since he came back from the mortal realm.
Do you think he came across something bad?
You!
He came across something bad?
He's the one who put whoever came across him
through bad things.
He's the last one to come across bad things.
He... he's the worst thing himself.
Get up.
If you are hurt,
I don't need to check the list.
That's not gonna happen.
I've worked so hard to get a yes from you.
Cheng Yu, it's hurting me.
Wait for me.
Sister Fengjiu,
why are you drinking so much liquor?
Don't go in.
Why?
Uncle wants to see you.
My father?
Yes.
And he wants you...
Father.
I miss you so much.
She's very sad.
Look at you.
You are going to be the female monarch of Qingqiu.
Don't act so childish.
Come with me.
Father.
I'm sorry to get you mad again.
Before I went traveling,
I told you that
you are the natural successor of the female monarch of Qingqiu.
You can't do whatever you want like you did before.
Do you remember
how you promised me?
And what have you done during my travel?
You descended to the mortal realm in secret
and even mourned for a mortal.
How absurd!
Raise your head and look me in the eye!
You are the future female monarch of Qingqiu.
You were born to be different than others.
Others can do whatever they want.
But you can't.
After a few more years,
you will take the place as the female monarch of Qingqiu.
If you keep behaving like this,
how are you going to shoulder
the responsibility as the female monarch of Qingqiu?
Father.
I'm sorry that I upset you again.
I was so silly.
I shouldn't have gone to the mortal realm.
I shouldn't have...
I'll let it go this time.
But this is a little lesson for you.
Don't make the same mistake ever again.
Got it.
From tomorrow,
you have to spend more time
on study,
making up for those lessons that you've missed.
Okay, father.
Keep in mind
what I said.
Are you clear?
Yes.
And one more thing.
God Zhe Yan came here today to propose a marriage
for Immortal Lord Cang Yi from Mount Zhiyue.
He even brought the marriage contract.
What's your idea about this marriage?
Tell me.
How could I get over His Majesty?
The best way is
to find someone
who loves you and cares for you.
Someone who answers to
whatever you say.
Someone who cares about
all your emotions.
With someone being so good to you,
over time,
you will forget about
His Majesty who didn't treat you well.
I'll ask you again when you are sober.
I agree.
I will marry him.
You have to think it through.
Marriage is a big thing.
It's no joke.
Immortal Lord Cang Yi.
I don't know him.
Great! Great!
Right in time.
You have to think it through.
It's time for me to find my fate.
To love someone and forget someone else.
I want nothing.
Father,
you can look forward to my wedding now.
Go.
Yes.
Don't keep Lord Cheng Yu waiting.
I am so gracious with my work.
Lord Cheng Yu will definitely be impressed.
Chong Lin.
Third Prince.
His Majesty has come back.
But why are you looking so unhappy?
After His Majesty got back,
he seems worried.
And he wanted to check the book of merits of the mortal realm.
I wonder if there's anything wrong.
He didn't say.
So I dared not to ask.
Okay.
You can go and ask Si Ming to come now.
Yes.
Did you get the tea
from Immortal Lord Xi Hai?
It's said that the tea buds once in 3000 years.
How rare!
You finally got Lord Cheng Yu to
help you with the busy work.
Why do you have time to come here studying tea?
Although Cheng Yu matters to me,
you also
matters to me greatly.
It's not like you
to have such a solemn expression.
If my memory serves me right,
last time I saw this expression is hundreds of years ago
when Lord Cheng Yu left the mortal realm and went up the heaven.
If I didn't know you so well,
I would have thought that you are being jealous.
You put a lot of thought
to trick her into checking the list.
But now you are here at my place.
If I didn't know you so well,
I would have thought that something happens to you.
Your Majesty.
Third Prince.
You can have Chong Lin deliver it to me.
Why bother yourself?
You didn't want to read
the book of merits in mortal realm before.
But you changed your mind all of a sudden.
I'm afraid that there's something wrong.
So I came here myself.
If there's anything that Your Majesty have doubt on,
I can explain to you.
Put it there.
If there's nothing I can help with,
please excuse me,
Your Majesty.
Looks like I'm not overly concerned.
When I first heard that you wanted to know about
your misfortune in mortal realm, I was worried.
Strange as things are,there must be something wrong.
I've got more curious
after seeing it today.
What are you curious about?
The first curiosity is with Si Ming,
who's so careful.
But given his character,
it sort of makes sense.
But the second curiosity.
Only you can tell me about it.
Why would Emperor Dong Hua, who's always been indifferent,
suddenly become interested in
his misfortune in the mortal realm?
If you feel like something isn't right,
you can ask me.
Perhaps I can give some advice.
Anything wrong?
Do you mind
if I take a look at it?
You were the emperor of State of Chengyu in the mortal realm.
A woman named Zhou Mengxi saved you in the war.
You fell in love with Zhou Mengxi.
But she died of illness very soon.
And not long after that, you died of grief.
It turns out that you were such a romantic in the mortal realm.
Anything wrong?
Why is it wrong?
There's nothing wrong.
I just feel like it doesn't match
my memory.
What memory do you have?
The experience in the mortal realm is like a dream.
You are not a man with obsession.
If it's nothing serious,
just let it go.
Don't hold on to it.
Well, then,
your feelings for Cheng Yu. You should let it go, too.
Lovesickness is also a form of happiness.
You don't understand.
Oh, I've got something to deal with.
I have to go now.
You're finally back.
You left all the work to me,
and got away yourself.
I thought you had left.
Am I an irresponsible person?
Of course not.
I'm not like you.
Cheng Yu.
I have something important
that I want you to answer me seriously.
Can you...
The person that you are trying to protect.
Your friend.
I don't want to know how she's involved in
His Majesty's misfortune.
But the safety of His Majesty
matters to the Four Seas and Eight Deserts,
which involves a lot of things.
Things that you even can't imagine.
It's okay that you don't want others to know about it.
But you have to make sure that
what you have done
won't put His Majesty in danger.
We have no intention to hurt
His Majesty at all.
The thing is...
we can't tell anyone about it.
There's a reason for it.
She didn't do it on purpose.
Don't worry.
It won't happen again.
She...
dares not try again.
Cheng Yu.
Does it mean I've done you a favor again?
Do you owe me once again?
How stupid I am to believe
you could talk seriously!
I almost got tricked again.
I'll take that as a yes.
I'll be an idiot if I answer it.
I'd better get the list checking done
and clean the slate
thoroughly.
No.
You have to answer it first. You can't just...
I have nothing to say.
I...
Damn.
I just wanted to make fun and
change the serious atmosphere.
Now I'm screwed.
Do you believe that I didn't mean that at all?
You know the answer already.
Lord.
Let's talk it through.
A gentleman uses his tongue but not his fists.
I'll let my fists talk to you.
Is that okay?
Don't hit me.
Stop there.
Li,
you can't play with your mother's phoenix crown.
Sister Fengjiu, it's yours.
What?
You promised uncle a few days ago
to marry Immortal Lord Cang Yi,
and signed the marriage contract.
So Immortal Lord Cang Yi
had the betrothal gifts delivered the next day.
What?
God Zhe Yan came here today to propose a marriage
for Immortal Lord Cang Yi from Mount Zhiyue.
He even brought the marriage contract.
I agree.
I will marry him.
No.
Sister Fengjiu, where are you going?
I'll go ask about it.
Father.
The marriage that I agreed when I was drunk a few days ago.
Please cancel it for me.
You have made the promise yourself.
As the future female monarch of Qingqiu,
how could you go back on your words?
Father,
I don't want to get married yet.
I want to spend more time with you.
If you don't want to get married,
you shouldn't have fingerprinted that day.
I was drunk and dizzy then.
That doesn't count.
It's too late.
I have replied to God Zhe Yan.
The engagement is settled, and the wedding date will be set.
You can start preparing for it now.
Father,
are you going to risk my happiness?
Xiaojiu.
You've made the choice.
Before doing it,
you should have thought it through,
instead of being impulsive.
Now you've made the decision,
you should not regret it.
You have to be responsible for yourself.
I can't help you
this time.
That's bad.
Sister Fengjiu,
where are you going?
I have to leave here.
Sister Fengjiu, are you going to run away from wedding?
Your mother said it.
Run if you can't beat the enemy.
I have to break off the marriage.
The best way is to flee.
Sister Fengjiu, why don't you ask my mother
to speak for you?
Your mother is getting married soon.
How can I bother her at this time?
Who else can speak for you then?
Since you mention it,
I think of someone.
So
you are planning on escaping?
Yeah.
It's all your fault, uncle.
My fault?
When God Zhe Yan proposed the marriage
for Immortal Lord Cang Yi,
why didn't you stop him?
So you have to be on my side
no matter what happens now.
But it's you who nodded the marriage.
On what ground should I help you?
You know I drank a little then.
But uncle.
You have to persuade my father to cancel the marriage,
so that I don't have to run away.
But it seems like father is determined
to marry me off.
You
are such a pain in the ass.
God,
Immortal Lord Cang Yi from Mount Zhiyue sent a letter.
You can go out now.
Yes.
Brother.
What does the letter say?
Did Immortal Lord Cang Yi change his mind?
The mortal realm is in turmoil.
Immortal Lord Cang Yi has gone down to deal with troubles.
He can't escort the bride on the wedding day.
Brother,
Immortal Lord Cang Yi
can't even escort the bride back on the wedding day.
I'm afraid he doesn't really like Fengjiu.
I think
we should cancel the marriage.
On Qianqian's wedding day,
Prince Ye Hua can't escort her either.
Does it mean their wedding
has to be canceled?
Brother escorting the bride has been a tradition in the gods.
But they don't have such a tradition in Mount Zhiyue.
Besides, Xiaojiu is unwilling to
marry Immortal Lord Cang Yi.
Why do you have to force her into it?
I know.
You've doted on Xiaojiu.
But it is different this time.
Xiaojiu agreed the marriage,
and signed the marriage contract herself.
How can she break off the engagement now?
A dishonest man
can't survive in this world.
How would people in the Eight Deserts and Six Directions
view us?
Brother.
That's enough.
Say no more.
The marriage will not be canceled.
Xiaojiu
should learn to grow up.
Do you know who is Immortal Lord Cang Yi?
He is one of the best among junior immortals
after chaotic era.
And he is the best
of the best.
Such a man sees in Xiaojiu.
And he's not roundabout at all.
Instead he asked God Zhe Yan to be his matchmaker very openly.
The great achievements he's accomplished
in thriving the mortal realm for tens of thousands of years
and his forthrightness toward the marriage
really deserve to be respected.
But as a princess,
Xiaojiu
came back from the mortal realm
and even mourned for a mortal.
She just made a fool of herself.
She acted so recklessly before
and now she wants to break off the marriage.
If I let her do that,
She will definitely cause great troubles in the future.
Since Xiaojiu was appointed
to succeed the monarch of East Desert,
she has never done anything correct.
The most important thing for me now
is to find her an excellent husband
to help her reinforce the throne.
Immortal Lord Cang Yi
will be a perfect choice.
He's such a good person.
We can't afford to insult him.
Don't you speak for Xiaojiu anymore.
If you want to do something for her own good,
you should persuade her into marrying.
Brother.
I know this man has so many merits.
But does it matter more than her happiness?
It's her happiness we're talking about.
Is marrying a suitable man more important
than being happy?
Fourth brother.
You've been an immortal for quite a long time.
Do you actually think everything
will go the way we want as immortals?
We couldn't ask for more
if things don't go the wrong way.
Immortal Lord Cang Yi
will be a saving grace for Xiaojiu
in becoming a qualified Princess of Qingqiu.
She can't go wrong any more.
There's no other way.
Looks like I have no choice but to run.
Sister Fengjiu,
but you can't just hide yourself
until the wedding day.
Maybe we can find another way.
There's no other way out.
Unless Immortal Lord Cang Yi doesn't marry you,
there doesn't seem to be a better way.
Right.
I should have thought of it sooner.
Sister Fengjiu, where are you going?
Li, take it.
You go back
and tell my father that I'll go meet Cang Yi.
I can work it out myself.
Uncle, uncle.
Something's up.
Li.
Slow down.
A real man has to keep
calm in face of changes.
But...
Sit down.
Catch your breath first.
You catch your breath now?
Okay, go ahead.
Sister Fengjiu wanted me to
tell you that she would answer to what she did.
She would take care of the engagement on her own.
And you don't have to worry about it.
It's good that she comes around.
Where is she now?
Sister Fengjiu went to Mount Zhiyue alone
to break if off with Immortal Lord Cang Yi.
What?
She...
Uncle.
A real man has to keep calm in face of changes.
Catch your breath.
Immortal Lord Cang Yi.
I'm Bai Fengjiu from Qingqiu. I came here to see you.
I'm about to go to the mortal realm to deal with troubles.
I didn't expect to see you
before I leave.
We really are destined, aren't we?
Immortal Lord Cang Yi.
There's a misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding?
How come?
I didn't have chance to
show my feelings for you before.
But since I saw you saving a young boy
in the temple fair,
I have fallen in love with you.
I can swear to god that
my feelings for you
have been real.
I want to get married with you
and spend the rest of my life with you.
Immortal Lord Cang Yi,
I don't want to marry you at all.
I'm sorry that I signed the marriage contract
when I was drunk.
We should cancel it.
Why?
I'm aware that
you don't know me yet.
But that's not a problem.
If we are together all the time,
you will fall in love with me.
I heard from God Zhe Yan that
you are still young and fond of play.
So I found some novelties for you
in mountains of Immortals in the mortal realm.
You can take them now if you like them.
I will treat you better in the future.
I know how you feel for me.
I really appreciate it.
But I have promised to mourn for someone.
I can't get married during the period of time.
I've heard about things
between you and the mortal.
A mortal can't dominate
his death.
I don't really care about it.
But I'm indebted to him.
So I've kept my promise to mourn for him.
I'm willing to mourn for him with you
and pay back the favor together with you.
Immortal Lord Cang Yi,
I will ask you one last time.
Are you going to cancel the marriage or not?
No.
Fine.
Then I'll deal with it our way in Qingqiu.
I am the Princess of Qingqiu.
So my husband has to be better than me in every aspect.
Let's have a fight.
If you win,
I will say yes to the marriage.
But if you lose,
the marriage has to be canceled.
You must be joking.
I've always respected female immortals.
I will never fight with a female immortal.
Since you don't want
to fight with me,
I'll take it as your acquiescence
of canceling the marriage.
Thank you so much.
Wait.
My feelings for you are real.
Since you want to test me,
I will accept the challenge.
Be careful.
Are you okay?
There's no clear winner yet.
Let's go on.
Stop.