Eternal Love of Dream
Episode 54
You're finally back.
Have you seen Dong Hua?
I waited for him for so long.
Why didn't he come back?
Why did he lie to me?
I waited for him for so long like a fool.
Which word he said is true?
Fengjiu,
you're pregnant.
Feel relieved.
Your uncle and I will be here for you.
Your Majesty!
I pay respect to Your Majesty!
I still need to cultivate in reclusion
to refine and blend the dark energy inside my body.
Your Majesty, I'm willing
to serve you at the expense of my life.
When I'm not around,
you shall be the one
to lead the demons.
Yes!
This is how it feels to have power.
Gods,
just wait!
Xiaojiu!
Yan,
why are you here?
Aren't the demons...
I've got something urgent to attend to.
Do you know where Xiaojiu is?
Today is their wedding day.
How come they are both missing?
That's why I'm here.
For the demons, the ice face...
Your Highness!
- Chong Lin! - Chong Lin, how come you're...
Something bad has happened in the Fanyin Valley.
His Majesty asked you to meet him
at the entrance right away.
Your Majesty!
Miao Luo has broken out of the Miaoyi Chasm.
Please maintain the ward. I'm going inside.
The valley is filled with dark energy.
How can you go inside?
Protected by the golden blood,
the dark energy can't hurt me,
I'll leave it to you.
Miao Luo is out?
How are the demons now?
What about Xu Yang?
Didn't he stop Miao Luo from stealing the blood tear?
Demon Lord Xu Yang is dead.
Miao Luo!
I'm gonna kill you!
Yan,
His Majesty is the only one
who can handle Miao Luo in the whole word.
If you go inside now, you'll get yourself killed.
So what?
I'll never spare her!
Calm down!
The royal members
of the inseparable king birds are probably dead.
If the Fanyin Valley opens,
all the living creatures
in the Four Seas and Eight Deserts will suffer.
Guarding this place
is the first step to restrain Miao Luo.
All you know is to draw out your sword.
What's the use of that?
As a demon lord,
the last lesson you need to learn is that
putting away your sword is
for drawing out your sword better.
Fengjiu, are you OK?
How are you?
Haven't heard from you in the Sky Kingdom,
I came to visit you in Qingqiu.
His Majesty didn't come.
I've given him time,
but he still stays in the demon clan.
There's no one else here.
If you feel sad deep in your heart,
just have a good cry.
I don't want to cry.
I just can't understand it.
Fengjiu,
feel relieved.
No matter what happens, His Majesty is sure to come back.
By then, we'll definitely ask him
to explain to you until you're satisfied.
Cheng Yu,
His Majesty loved me a lot
in the Dream of Aranya.
If he finds Ji Heng pitiful
and wants to stay by her side,
he just needs to tell me.
I won't force him to marry me.
Even if I'm...
I won't force him to stay.
Fengjiu...
I dare not tell my father, either.
I'm afraid that if he knows, he'll get mad
and go to argue with His Majesty.
After all,
love must be mutual.
Fengjiu, wait for me.
I'll go and find Lian Song.
He surely knows where His Majesty is.
I'll definitely help you.
Having been refined by Miao Luo,
the dark energy in the Miaoyi Chasm
is harder to purify than that of the Ten-evil Lotus Land.
I have to find a way to suppress it.
I should find Miao Luo right away
and destroy her with the dark energy.
Send another one hundred demon soldiers
to the Baishui Mountain.
Yes!
Demon Lord Nie,
we haven't started a war against the gods yet.
Is it too...
You should figure out the current situation.
Who is the leader of the demons?
I'm calling the shots now.
You!
We're both demon lords. How can you...
Just leave.
Yes!
It's been three days.
Here are one fetus protection pill
and one abortion pill.
I'll keep your secret
whatever your decision is.
♪ Whisper love in dreams. ♪
♪ Everything I think about is for my lover. ♪
♪ In one moment, I forget about what confuses me. ♪
♪ Because I'm surrounded by love. ♪
♪ Until I get hurt after giving all I have, ♪
♪ I finally understand how cruel you are. ♪
♪ I'm just afraid the fate might not recognize lovers, ♪
♪ setting hundreds of tests to keep them apart. ♪
=Tai Chen Palace=
♪ It's like falling leaves tapping on the gate. ♪
♪ I used to be a fool who followed you all the time. ♪
♪ The transient affection ♪
♪ only gets deeper for trouble. ♪
♪ If we become strangers only
to recognize each other again, ♪
♪ will you remember our past? ♪
♪ I am willing to die if you trust me. ♪
♪ I don't care to be lonely. ♪
♪ I can't decide whether to leave or to stay. ♪
♪ The vast universe changes nonstop. ♪
♪ Never have you stopped fighting for our love. ♪
♪ Go far away in your shadow. ♪
♪ I'm free but I have nothing. ♪
♪ Let memories gather dust. ♪
♪ I can't see us be together forever. ♪
♪ It's like falling leaves tapping on the gate. ♪
♪ I used to be a fool who followed you all the time. ♪
♪ The transient affection ♪
♪ only gets deeper for hatred. ♪
♪ If we bid farewell only to meet again, ♪
♪ will you give up on us. ♪
His Majesty and I
have really gone a long way.
In the first half of the journey,
I was the one who kept chasing after him.
It was hard,
but luckily, I was blessed by heaven
and I finally caught up with him.
Because I was the one who wanted him from the very start,
however tired I was,
I felt OK.
He does love me,
but he may also have feelings for Ji Heng.
When I fell into the Dream of Aranya
and struggled between life and death,
he chose me.
But now Ji Heng is in danger,
so he chooses Ji Heng.
Having failed
to keep his word,
he's ashamed to meet me in Qingqiu.
This love was hard-earned,
and I've always wanted to treasure it.
But I'm really too tired.
Your Majesty, I've tried.
I've given you enough time.
As long as you can come,
I'll believe anything you say,
but you didn't come.
Now that I'm also pregnant,
♪ Hide the hopeless dream in the bedside sleeve. ♪
I can't stay in Qingqiu anymore.
Your Majesty,
♪ That's my craving for all my life. ♪
from now on,
I'll live my life without you.
♪ ...so torturous. ♪
I can't fully purify the dark energy inside.
On the opening date of the Fanyin Valley,
we won't be able to stop the dark energy
from leaking outside.
What shall we do?
We have to find a magic instrument
to seal the Fanyin Valley,
thus resolving future trouble once and for all.
Why are you all here?
Who's accompanying Xiaobai?
Oh, gosh!
I forgot to visit Xiaojiu on my way.
Your Majesty!
Ice face!
When he wakes up,
please teach him
some cultivation tips.
When he's ready to ascend to heaven,
I'll help him wash away the mortal dust
in the Ninth Heaven Jade Pool,
so that he can become an immortal.
You...
I'm fine.
I've thought through everything these days,
and I'm all set.
When I come back from the mortal realm,
I'll drink with you again.
You're going to the mortal realm?
According to the rituals of Qingqiu,
once I become the monarch,
I have to experience the mortal realm.
I was delayed by many things,
but it's not too late to go now.
Well,
I've got a charm for you. Put it away first.
If I'm still not back
when Qingti is about to ascend to heaven,
use it to inform me,
and then I'll come back to find you.
OK.
I loved to eat sweet food the most,
but now I love to eat salty food.
Gungun, you like salty food, right?
Gungun,
you must be white and chubby.
After you grow up,
I'll take you to Qingqiu to meet our family.
But what I fear the most is that
your grandpa and grandma will force
your father to take his responsibilities.
So I have no choice but to act first and report afterwards.
Sorry to make you go through all this.
What to do now?
No wonder I couldn't find you however hard I tried.
Fengjiu went to experience the mortal realm
without leaving a message.
Who knew they would miss each other like that.
One day in heaven equals one year on earth.
How sad she will be when she stays in the mortal realm.
No!
I'll find Si Ming
and see if he's got some other ways.
Your Highness, please decide as early as possible.
Later,
the Sky Kingdom may not be so stable.
Though His Majesty is busy looking for Her Highness Fengjiu,
he still remembers to find a new place
for us to settle down.
Inseparable king birds are caring and loyal.
Your royal members sacrificed themselves in the valley
for the safety of the Four Seas and Eight Deserts.
His Majesty won't forget the favor.
Leave the tragedy of the Fanyin Valley in the Fanyin Valley.
That's the wish of our royal members.
Immortal Official Chong Lin,
please tell His Majesty.
Since it's a disaster for the Four Seas and Eight Deserts,
the inseparable king birds
certainly have no reason to avoid it.
I'd like to lead the inseparable king birds
to fight alongside the gods.
Your Highness.
All my families are gone.
I'm the only royal member left.
The inseparable king birds
have chosen me to be their monarch.
Your Majesty.
My decision is the common decision of my people.
Miao Luo owes us a huge debt of blood.
We must make her pay.
If she's not killed,
no place is safe for us in the world.
I request His Majesty to keep us
to resist the enemies with gods.
However, Immortal Official Chong Lin,
please take the old, the weak, women,
and children of our clan somewhere safe
for they don't have the power to fight.
Yes.
I'll definitely report your resolution
to His Majesty.
Demon Lord Yan asked His Majesty
to send you a message.
He said that
now the demon clan is not stable.
After Miao Luo is killed,
he'd like to share his land
with the inseparable king birds.
Demon Lord Yan was always a good friend to my elder brother,
but the demon clan is not a good place
for the inseparable king birds.
Immortal official Chong Lin, if there are still
inseparable king birds left after Miao Luo is killed,
please take them to Qingqiu.
My elder brother always
wanted to visit there.
Yes.
Elder brother,
did you have any regret in your heart?
Just let everything miserable come to end
after the tragedy of Aranya and the end of your life.
Though your love was not responded to,
you died for what you believed.
The tragedy of the Fanyin Valley won't repeat itself.
From today on,
I'll become a monarch of indomitable spirit!
Gungun has gone to school.
Life in the mortal realm is really boring.
I might as well find a quiet place
and live in reclusion for a while.
Mother! Mother! I'm back!
Gungun, you're back!
Your hair turns white.
Come on, it needs dyeing.
Sit down.
Mother,
why do other students at school
have black hair,
while my hair is born silver?
Because we're immortals.
The color of our hair is certainly different.
Do other little immortals look like me?
Of course not.
Of course, some of them do look like you.
When you go back
and see Li, you'll see.
Mother, who is Li?
He's also a little immortal.
You should call him "Uncle".
Does he also have silver hair?
No, his hair is black.
We're both little immortals.
How come we have different hair colors?
Actually, as immortals, we don't
care much about our hair colors,
but since we're in the mortal realm,
we have to follow the mortal rules.
Sit still. It's time to dye your hair.
Let's go back to the Sky Kingdom.
Then I don't have to dye my hair.
OK. We'll go back.
But I want to
take you around to see the mortal realm.
OK, as you wish.
Fengjiu is really good at cooking.
There's no dish she can't make in the world,
but there's only one dish that she doesn't make,
and that's the qilin plant.
It's not because
she hates it
due to its taste or property.
It's just that the qilin plant
only grows in the Sukhavati,
and it can't grow anywhere else.
As a child, she loved to eat the qilin plant,
so she wanted to grow one in Qingqiu.
It took her three hundred years.
She missed many classes
and was beaten cruelly by her father several times.
It really took a lot of work.
She felt so tired,
so she gave it up completely.
From then on,
she never ate the qilin plant,
let alone using it to make dishes.
She can be really stubborn
sometimes.
Cold-hearted as Bai Qian is,
she's actually warm-hearted
compared to Fengjiu.
What's more,
Fengjiu is not aware that
she's somewhat heartless.
Instead, she always finds herself sentimental and emotional.
It's just like she has never noticed that
she wouldn't eat the qilin plant any more.
What a great metaphor!
Now His Majesty
is another qilin plant abandoned by her.
As the Emperor of the Three Realms,
His Majesty has his own difficulties.
If the vast universe becomes unstable...
In our family, we don't restrain our children.
She can go anywhere she wants
to experience the world.
We never stop her.
If you ask me,
I really don't know where she has gone.
Actually, if His Majesty really wants to
find her, he should have a way.
However, I'm just worried that
His Majesty has given the last chance
to Her Highness Fengjiu.
Like His Majesty,
Gungun loves to eat the cakes I make.
Mother! Mother!
I'm back.
Look what I've made for you.
The chestnut cake!
Wash your hands before you eat.
Mother,
why do you have four pieces,
while I just have three?
Because I'm an adult,
and you're a little boy.
I can eat one more piece than you.
Mother,
my schoolmates' mothers
never grab their cakes.
But we're immortals.
As to such things, we certainly should
follow the immortal rules.
Is that so?
But you once said
we were in the mortal realm,
so we should follow the mortal rules.
Did I say that?
Under this circumstance,
we still have to follow the immortal rules.
Otherwise, what if we forget about the immortal rules
when we're back to the fairy land?
Fine.
We'll move to another place in a few days.
Mother,
we're fine living in the publishing house.
Why should we move?
If we move,
I won't be able to play with my friends.
Because you're a little immortal.
Your appearance
remains the same
for a very long time.
If we stay here
all the time,
those mortals will get suspicious.
So we have to keep moving.
I see.
Then after we move,
I'll go
wherever you go.
Eat another one!
In the mortal realm,
you saved Her Highness Fengjiu once.
To repay your favor,
Her Highness Fengjiu brought you back to life
with the pimpon fruit
and gave you half of her cultivation.
Time shifts and things change.
I suppose the mortal realm is completely different.
I should've been dead for a long time,
but now I'm an immortal.
Many mortal emperors have failed
to be immortal despite all their efforts.
By then,
according to the rules of Immortal Record Book,
the baptizing ceremony must be performed
by the one who gave you the body.
Her Highness Fengjiu will go to the Ninth Heaven Jade Pool
in person to baptize you
and help you ascend to heaven.
Get prepared.
What was my relationship
with Her Highness Fengjiu back then?
Reborn as an immortal, you forgot about
everything when you woke up.
It's good for you.
Why do you have to remember your dream
and add to your trouble?
Why did I have such a dream?
His Majesty is the Emperor of the Three Realms.
This won't happen to him for sure.
I suppose
he's fishing in Tai Chen Palace now.
What are you playing?
The spinning top. Haven't you played it before?
No.
It's so pretty.
Did you make it yourself?
No, my father made it.
Your father?
Yes, my father is awesome.
He can make not only spinning tops but kites.
If you like it,
you can ask your father to make one for you.
But I only have a mother. I don't have a father.
Why don't you have a father?
Isn't it enough to have a mother only?
But everyone has a mother and a father.
Everyone has a father?
Mother! Mother!
Gungun, what's up?
Do I have a father?
No.
I gave birth to you myself.
But my schoolmates
all have their own father.
But you're a little immortal.
In the immortal realm,
it's possible for someone to have a mother but no father.
Why is the fairy land so different from the mortal realm?
In the mortal realm, adults don't grab kids' cakes.
Adults get up at midnight
to tuck their kids in.
Every kid must have their father.
Mother,
are you using the fairy land as an excuse
because I can't seek confirmation?
Gungun, you must be too stressful due to your schoolwork.
You're not obedient now.
How about this?
Cut class tomorrow.
I'll take you to the mountains
to absorb the essence of the nature.
Mother, don't threaten me with food
every time you're in the wrong.
Ordinary magic instruments won't be able
to suppress the dark energy
of the Miaoyi Chasm, let alone
the entire Fanyin Valley.
Even God Zhe Yan can't...
I found it!
Where?
There's actually a way to seal the dark energy.
Are you OK?
Be careful when you're back.
Remember.
You said each race has closed their gate.
What does that mean?
Well,
Your Highness,
no race can send demons
to feed Her Majesty any more.
Please...
Let's wait and see.
Ye Hua and Bai Qian are out travelling.
I've sent people to look for them.
In a few days,
God Zhe Yan and God Bai Zhen
will also come to the Sky Kingdom
to discuss the important matter.
The Fanyin Valley is about to open.
We can't wait.
The starlight ward is so dangerous.
Plus, Bihai Cangling is closely linked to you.
If anything goes wrong with Bihai Cangling,
will you be in danger?
We'll know by then.
Dong Hua!
I'm all set.
I just...
Just what?
I just want to see her again.
You...
What on earth did His Majesty say?
Go back now and keep looking.
So he still wants to use Bihai Cangling
to seal the Fanyin Valley?
Over tens of thousands of years,
no one has ever opened the starlight ward.
As to the consequences...
Let's go!
It's time to eat.
Stop reading. Let's eat.
= Please come back to the Nether World =
Mother, what's this?
Gungun, it's time for us to go back to the fairy land.
Since you refuse to send any demon,
I may send you instead.
Demon Lord Yan,
why are you here?
Are you kicked out by the gods?
Nie Chuyin,
today will be your day to die.
I'm here to avenge Xu Yang's death.
Today,
I'll bury you with Xu Yang.
Tomorrow, when His Majesty decides the titles and ranks of
the immortals just ascending to heaven,
the Ninth Heaven Jade Pool will be opened for the last time.
In future, the Ninth Heaven Jade Pool
will be sealed forever.
The Sky Kingdom will no longer
list those who become immortals by rare chance
on the Immortal Record Book.
His Majesty wants to see you,
and he's finally thought of a good way
to find you.
If he had wanted to find me,
he would have found me long ago.
Now by doing so,
he's really cold-hearted.
He is...
Gungun is my son. His Majesty is his father.
He's the reason why you don't want to come back?
I'll go to the Sky Kingdom first.
As to him, could you
look after him for a couple of days?
Your Highness Fengjiu, please feel relieved.
Mother, can you take me with you?
I've never parted with you
my whole life.
Gungun, be a good boy.
I've really got something important to deal with.
I can't take you with me.
When it's finished,
I'll come back and pick you up right away.
Then promise me.
Make a promise. Keep it for one hundred years.
Please take care of him.
Thank you.
Yan,
see?
With your current cultivation,
you're no match for me.
Just go to hell!
No way!
I can
still fight!
Yan,
be reasonable.
As demons, we've been suppressed by gods
for tens of thousands of years.
Now,
after Dong Hua and Miao Luo are weakened by each other,
demons can
develop and flourish.
I'm afraid it'll be your golden opportunity
to replace the demon king.
If I can help demons develop and flourish,
why can't I replace her?
Don't chase rainbows!
Yan,
I'll give you one last chance.
Acknowledge allegiance to me,
and I'll guarantee the safety of your race.
Otherwise,
you'll die today.
Why are you laughing?
I'm laughing at you.
You're just a puppet.
You have no future.
Go to hell!
I've told you if you're disloyal,
you will come to no good end.
Your Majesty!
No! No!
No!
Miao Luo, I know Dong Hua's secret.
I'll tell you if you kill him.
Your Majesty, don't trust him.
He was close to Dong Hua in the Fanyin Valley.
They're on the same side.
Now it's your turn.
What's Dong Hua's secret?