Eternal Love of Dream
Episode 27
Where is this place?
I heard that Bai Fengjiu from Qingqiu
offended you in the past days.
Bai Fengjiu is the most beautiful lady
in the Eight Deserts and Six Directions
second only to the God Bai Qian.
She became the female monarch of Qingqiu at such a young age.
It's so lucky of you to have her.
She surely deserves the title as a beauty.
I surely am!
So men do gossip as well?
She is indeed beautiful,
but not so clever.
Why am I not clever?
It was you who teased me again and again!
Now Bai Fengjiu is famous
in the Eight Deserts and Six Directions.
Why?
She rejected to marry to the Immortal Lord Cang Yi,
created a tremendous uproar in the palace on Mount Zhiyue,
and destroyed the statue of Cang Yi,
which greatly humiliated Bai Yi from Qingqiu.
This female monarch is too bold.
Who knows what things she will do
against the rules in future.
Like you said,
Bai Fengjiu is indeed good at
losing the face for the Qingqiu clan.
You dare to speak ill of me now.
If I show my original form as the female monarch of Qingqiu
in front of you,
you'll spread such awkward things
across the Four Seas and Eight Deserts
which will lose all the face of Qingqiu!
My father will never forgive me for that.
Thanks for
letting me win.
It's undetermined yet
who will win.
Enough of this!
I lose to you every time.
This is so boring!
It's so chilly!
Ever since the Haotian Tower was rebuilt,
I've never practiced yet.
Today looks like a good day.
How about...
Let's talk about that tomorrow.
I gotta go now
for something else.
One is willing to fight and the other one is willing to suffer.
They are a good match!
It's so hot!
Why is my life so hard!
Why do I need to suffer from the ice and fire!
What kind of strange smell is it?
Your Majesty,
it's very humid these days.
It happens that there is Hengwu incense on the fairy mountain.
I switched with it.
Are you used to the smell?
Hengwu incense can eliminate the humidity
and help one to tranquilize and fall asleep.
It's a good spice.
I don't like the smell,
but it's good for her.
God! God!
Bad news! Bad news!
God!
God Zhe Yan!
God! God!
Bad news! Bad news!
Go away!
How impolite you are!
I'll tell your mother about that!
God Zhe Yan! God Zhe Yan!
Bad news!
Something very bad happened!
- Come with me! - Enough! Enough!
Don't pull me!
What happened?
Sister Fengjiu turned into a piece of silk handkerchief.
That's not a big deal!
It's nothing but a kid's magic art.
Sister Fengjiu turned into a silk handkerchief
and was taken away by His Majesty!
Please help me get Sister Fengjiu back
from His Majesty!
That's really naughty plot for a story.
Don't laugh at her.
His Majesty doesn't know
Sister Fengjiu is that silk handkerchief.
Stop it!
Stop shaking! I got it now.
I'll get Fengjiu out tomorrow.
Get her out now.
Do you think
His Majesty will give it to us
if we go for a silk handkerchief in the middle of the night?
Besides, after all your crying,
everyone will know the whereabouts
of Sister Fengjiu.
That makes sense!
Then we'll do it tomorrow!
I'm worried that
Sister Fengjiu will suffer with His Majesty!
I'm so hungry!
Where is this place?
What a narrow escape!
I almost lose my life under the chopping knife of His Majesty!
Thanks to my good luck!
Neither threats nor forces can subdue me.
Neither wealth nor honor can corrupt me.
No sweet and sour fish.
Refrain from it!
I cannot take it!
Your Majesty, the Third Prince wants to meet you.
OK. Got it!
Yes!
There you come finally!
We have the deal that you come with me
to practice the manipulation of the Haotian Tower.
I would not come out if I wasn't hungry!
Let me fill my stomach first.
It's been so long.
Why are your cooking skills not improved at all?
I've got a new feature!
This time, I must be able to beat God Zhe Yan's Jiuli Pot!
Keep your eyes open!
Chong... Chong Lin!
Chong Lin!
I've rearranged the mechanisms
at the top of the tower.
Try it again!
Thank Your Majesty for saving me!
What is it that smells so good?
I made sweet and sour fish.
Let's try it together.
You made sweet and sour fish?
I know your cooking very well.
Besides, you are not in the Imperial Kitchen.
I can make her show herself.
It smells so good!
Perfect combination of color, aroma, and taste.
Your cooking skill has improved.
This taste is...
Not bad.
If Lord Cheng Yu has the luck
to have this dish,
she will surely recover soon.
What happened to her?
She is not herself these days.
At first, she just had a minor headache,
but it gets a lot worse these days.
She can barely get out of bed and stand
and usually falls into coma.
I had wanted to invite Fengjiu, the Princess of Qingqiu,
to accompany her,
but I just couldn't find her anywhere.
How come Cheng Yu gets so sick?
It's getting late now.
I've gotta send the medicines for Cheng Yu!
Hope she is fine today.
Bye for now!
Third Prince,
make it clear before you leave.
What happened to Cheng Yu?
Your Majesty, God Zhe Yan wants to meet you.
Let him in!
This way please!
How cozy this is!
This pavilion is elegant and interesting.
This auspicious beast censer is exquisite and extraordinary!
I suppose this is made by...
God Zhe Yan! God Zhe Yan!
Get down to the point!
I don't mean to cheat you,
but I come for a trivial matter.
What is it?
This little naughty boy stole the silk handkerchief
I brought for her mother yesterday afternoon
while I was taking the afternoon nap.
He came back quite pleased with himself
and realized the loss of it
only after he was asked.
It's said
you've taken it!
It doesn't matter if it's a normal handkerchief,
but it's made by his grandma
who is the Fox Queen of Qingqiu.
It means a lot to him.
So I'm here
to retrieve the handkerchief.
Zhe Yan is so good at making up fantastic stories.
What a spicy ginger he is!
Now His Majesty has to release me.
Li  really has great comprehension.
He asked the most powerful
and merciful god to help me.
I underestimated the friendship
between him and me as an elder sister.
This is the handkerchief I took at the Ninety Heaven.
Is this yours?
No, it's not!
Is it not this one?
If not,
you could find it out at Yuan Ji Palace.
Maybe Lian Song took it.
It's just a handkerchief.
I don't think you'd lie to me and keep it.
You won't do something
as disgraceful as that.
This handkerchief is real.
If so,
I'll need to give this handkerchief
to Bai Qian.
Bye for now.
Take care!
Come on! Let's go!
This is not the one!
His Majesty won't lie to us.
Come on! Let's go!
- It's not! - Let's go!
- Bye for now! - This is not the one!
Don't go!
- Not this one! - Alright! Alright!
God Zhe Yan, why do you lose
and fail to get Sister Fengjiu out?
You didn't do your best.
I'm breaking up with you today.
So be it!
It isn't your uncle that he kidnapped.
Why do I need to offend him openly?
Don't worry!
I've deduced Fengjiu's fate last year.
The fate plate shows she'll survive.
Let's wait and see how she goes.
Maybe it will turn out the other way around.
You can deduce fate
just like Si Ming?
Certainly!
But I haven't done it for several thousand years.
It's another thing as to its accuracy.
Deduce my fate.
I'll see if it's accurate or not.
Li!
Are you in the snares of love recently?
What are the snares of love?
It's...
Didn't you break up with me just now?
Time has changed.
Tell me now!
No!
Say it!
Till when do you plan to hide yourself?
So,
turning into a handkerchief is your hobby!
Your Majesty, your deduction is ridiculous!
Fortunately, I'm calm enough
not to be taken in.
Good!
I'm right in need of a handkerchief to clean my sword.
I'll use you for that.
To clean a sword?
To clean the well-known legendary weapon
which ranks among the top 10 of the ancient weapons
and can cut iron like sapropel,
the Legendary Sword Canghe!
What to do now?
I had planned it for the long term.
I thought
as long as I stay patient,
His Majesty will sooner or later set me free
if he gets bored of me one day.
That's the softest and most stable way
which hurts my face least.
Why would he use me to clean the sword?
His Majesty usually does as he says.
Besides,
he accepted the invitation of fight from Demon Lord Yan.
It looks like
he's gonna use Canghe for a good killing.
This is not good!
I have to get out tonight.
What has become of Cheng Yu now with her illness?
I have to get out for Cheng Yu anyway!
How can I stare at him
like this
without getting ashamed?
Luckily, he didn't recognize me.
Damn!
I didn't learn the lethargy formula well
when I attended school.
I've gotta
to cast it for a few more times.
Let me bury you here first.
It won't matter anymore wherever I am
if I stay together with His Majesty!
This is a precious Hanshi grass.
Its root is good for forgetting sorrows.
Its flower is premium seasoning for cold dishes.
Si Ming brought that particularly for me.
What a sad day that was
that I forgot to bring back this babe!
It's so heart-breaking!
It's not too late now
to make up for it.
The garden in the eyes of fox
is indeed different from that
in the eyes of mankind.
And it's different in the past
from it is now.
The unhappy things I had
in the Tai Chen Palace
is more than the happy things.
But all that I have in mind now
are all good things.
In that case,
I don't need to mind that much.
When I can speak,
I'd persuade Dong Hua into coming to Qingqiu.
By then, I'd say to His Majesty that
by when
I'll bring you to Qingqiu to watch the stars.
One! Two! Three!
You're still so ignorant
even though you're entangled by your own magic art.
You're one of a kind under this world.
No wonder God Bai Yi thinks about
finding a really good man for you every day.
Dong Hua,
you tore me and Ji Heng apart
which resulted in her suffering in the mortal realm.
Now she is so sad that
she left me without saying goodbye.
It's all your fault!
I must make you pay for it.
I don't believe you won't come.
Where am I?
Why am I here?
Oh no!
I clearly got out yesterday.
Why am I here again?
Am I caught and taken back again?
But I don't remember that at all.
Did I fall asleep
so what happened thereafter
is just my dream?
I'm even thinking of escaping
in my dream
and I dreamed in such a detailed way.
Let me do it all over again tonight
as it is in my dream.
How good will it be if it's all true!
It will save so much trouble for me.
There you are finally.
You dilly-dallying
ice face!
I've been waiting for you here for so many days!
Show your weapon!
Let's finish the fight as soon as possible!
If I don't beat the crap out of you today
to revenge previous humiliation,
I'll write my name upside down!
This is Yan Chiwu, one of the seven demon lords
with the title as a demon barbarian.
Are all demon barbarians
white-skinned Adonis?
Please!
Damn you!
Enough talking!
Let's fight the crap out!
Check it out!
This is my newly developed Yanmo Formation!
It took 7,000 lives from the mortal realm.
Even though they are all evil lives,
it took me great efforts.
If you dare to hurt them,
it's a cutoff to their six-realm encounters
to return to good.
Gods like you praise yourselves as kind-hearted people.
Show me how
you're going to break my Yanmo Formation.
Done!
My taking of 7,000 lives might be a breach of the sky moral
and deserves to be punished,
but the punishment should be the thunder
from the sky.
Shouldn't the gods like you
do your best to help them through?
If your sword gets stained by their blood,
you'll be convicted with killing.
You killed without any hesitation.
Don't you feel afraid of the sky's punishment
for your charge of killing?
Charge of killing?
I haven't handled any war affairs
in the past several hundred thousand years.
You have forgotten my style
when I was in charge of the life and death
in the six realms.
Damn!
Your Majesty!
Stay in there! Don't come out!
Your back!
Ice face, you despise me, don't you?
Fighting with families aside.
Watch out, Your Majesty!
Xiaobai!
Damn Yan Chiwu!
If it's not because of you fighting with His Majesty,
how could I get blown to this damn place?
In spite that His Majesty teased me so awfully,
he is good too
as he gave me the Tiangang Shield
to protect me.
I'll forget about all the past grudges.
But how does His Majesty know
my personal thoughts?
He called me Xiaobai in a great rush
just a few minutes before.
Why was he nowhere to be found
at the time when I fell off the cliff?
Xiaobai.
His Majesty calls me Xiaobai!
I like that!
Just think from his perspective.
If I were His Majesty,
I protected someone with Tiangang Shield,
but this person does not help in the fight
and she just witnessed me dragged off the cliff
by my enemy hand in hand.
I would not just watch,
but also stab him with another two strokes to vent my anger.
Two strokes to vent my anger.
The ice face really sucks.
Fighting with him will bring nothing good.
We even ran into the opening of the Fanyin Valley
at the top of Mount Fuyu
and fell onto the steep cliff.
Where is the Fanyin Valley?
You're intimate to the ice face.
How can you not know that?
Haven't you heard of the inseparable king birds clan?
Inseparable king birds?
The Fanyin Valley that inseparable king birds inhabit?
That's right!
It opens once in a cycle of sixty years.
And it shows one tiny crack every time
which is called the Fanyin Valley.
What a coincidence it is
that you came in at the time it was opened!
The wind under the feet
right blew us in at this time
as there is nothing left to blow.
And that crack
is right in the size
that allows two of us to come in at a time.
What luck is that?
What did you say?
Do you think I...
That hurts!
Did you
beat me up just now
while I was in coma?
That's impossible!
Qingqiu people are well-behaved.
We will never do something like that.
Yan, you've thought too much!
OK!
If you call me Yan again,
I'll cut off your tongue.
Then how should I address you?
Address me in the way
strong people are addressed
in the mortal realm.
Warrior Yan?
Warrior Yan!
That's more like it!
Warrior Yan,
why do you want to fight with His Majesty again and again?
Why do you dislike His Majesty so much?
As the Green Demon Lord,
of course, I need to protect the woman I love.
It's wide-spread in the Four Seas and Eight Deserts
that Dong Hua is a god without any desires,
but I know
there is someone he truly loves.
Do you want know who it is?
Ji Heng!
How do you know?
It is indeed Ji Heng?
His Majesty doesn't necessarily like Ji Heng!
Ji Heng is as clean as ice and as pure as jade.
She is innocent and elegant.
Her beauty makes the fish sink, wild geese fall and flower blush,
and obscures the moon. It's beyond words of description.
A man
whose heart doesn't throb
for a beauty like Ji Heng
doesn't deserve to be a man.
You think her good
because you like her.
You're intimate to the ice face.
How do you not know who he really likes?
What's your name?
You look kind of familiar.
Are you the immortal from Tai Chen Palace?
I have absolutely nothing to do with Tai Chen Palace.
I'm Bai Fengjiu from Qingqiu!
Bai Fengjiu?
What a poor taste!
Ji Heng is the best in the world!