Eternal Love of Dream
Episode 47
Is it delicious?
The sugar fox that you made tastes the best.
If you like it, I'll cook some more for you.
I also like the purple potato cakes.
No, I won't cook them for you.
Why?
His Excellency and Her Highness
are really deeply attached to each other!
Yeah!
They love each other so much
that we all admire them.
It's really admiring!
Just seeing this, they admire us.
Hanging out during the day
is not as free as that in the evening.
I know somewhere quiet.
I can take you there.
Where?
Just go with me, then you will know.
You know I'm scared of snakes the most.
Why do you still take me here?
With my company,
they can't hurt you!
You are Aranya here.
It was with their care that you grew up!
Since Aranya was born,
she had been staying there.
Maybe they still know you.
Even if they know me, I dare not go inside.
Why do you take me here?
Do you still remember,
in the Fanyin Valley,
it was through this Python Formation that
we entered the Dream of Aranya by accident?
I'm wondering
if there is something secret in the Python Formation.
Really?
Can we get out?
After all, the Python Formation was made artificially,
which is different from the real one.
After you entered the dream,
I heard
the Dream of Aranya
accidentally drifted to
the Python Formation near the Jieyou Spring.
According to my observation,
the Dream of Aranya
is similar to the Ten-evil Lotus Land,
both of which are magic wards.
Since you could easily
break the Ten-evil Lotus Land to get out,
it may not be difficult to get out
of the Dream of Aranya, either.
Right?
As for this...
Unless you are injured.
So
you had been injured before entering the dream.
Your Majesty.
Tell me the truth.
I don't think
here you are as powerful as you are outside.
How did you get injured?
In order to enter the Dream of Aranya with you
without breaking it,
I had to discharge ninety percent of my power
to enter it in the flesh.
Discharge ninety percent of your power?
Then it must be...
Your Majesty,
you risked your life for me.
It's nothing.
I have gone through so many battles related to life and death.
Don't do such silly things any more.
I was not badly injured.
If you really don't want me to do silly things,
the only way is
to prevent yourself from silly behaviors.
How could you turn the topic to me again?
The Dream of Aranya
is different from the Ten-evil Lotus Land.
It's much bigger
and more powerful here.
I'm not sure that I can avoid hurting you
while using magic power to break it.
So
let's try to find out
something strange of the Python Formation.
How is it?
How?
If we want to get out of the Python Formation
and the Dream of Aranya,
we have to take the course of Aranya's life
to continue our way.
We can only do this for the time being.
Let's go.
Moye once told me that
he left the Fanyin Valley
after the event of Quanyin Beast happened.
Shen Ye and Aranya stayed in the mansion.
Although they didn't show their heart to each other,
they were deeply attracted to each other
with a sweet life.
Really?
If I have to
take the life course of Aranya,
then I have to...
Naturally, you can't do that.
Then just do as what we said before.
I can keep a distance with Shen Ye.
Moye also told me that
I didn't need to care much about the details.
When I have to make any choices for the big events,
if I do the same as Aranya did, that's OK.
Did Su Moye tell you
what the next big event was?
His Majesty's demise.
It seems to be a long time before that.
Let's go back now.
Having walked for a whole day, I even have blisters on my feet.
Really?
I will give you a foot massage.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
You can go back first.
What are you going to do?
Don't worry.
I'll be back soon.
Who sent the letter here?
It turned out that you went to take the cotton rose ointment.
Was it necessary for you to behave so secretly?
There isn't cotton rose here.
So I can't make cotton rose ointment.
Then I just took this.
Are you going to
hide everything from me?
Why do you think so?
What about this?
How can you explain it?
It's not worth mentioning.
No need to let it disturb you.
It says in the letter that
this is the fifth letter.
No wonder that
I can always smell the flavor of ink.
You have burnt all the letters, right?
It doesn't matter.
I know what to do.
The magic instrument that you asked him to make
has come to the last stage.
As for such masterly magic instrument,
it is the most dangerous when it comes into being.
If it can't be made successfully,
all the efforts will be in vain.
There may also be backfire.
So you'd better go back quickly.
As for Shen Ye...
I know how to behave properly with Shen Ye.
I'm sure to deal with him well.
But I'll be out for a very long time.
Very long?
How long is it?
Several months?
Several years?
Well...
At least several days.
It's just several days.
You said as if you were away for a long time.
Absence sharpens love.
Isn't it long enough?
How could you say that
you were not good at talking?
Your Highness.
Your Excellency.
What's wrong? Chacha.
Tell me!
Here is message from the palace that
His Majesty and Her Majesty haven't seen you for a long time,
so they asked you to go to the palace
to relieve their lovesickness.
I pay respects to father and mother!
Rise!
Thank you, father.
How are you doing these days?
Father, I'm fine.
I heard that Lord Xi Ze had been living
in your mansion these days.
How do you get on with each other?
We get on peacefully
with each other.
It's good.
Just peacefully?
Rumor has it that
Lord Xi Ze and you are closely attached to each other,
which is very admiring.
Mother,
I did go out with Lord Xi Ze
to the fair,
but we didn't do anything that degraded
the decency of the imperial family.
Never mind.
Xi Ze used to be cold.
Since he is kind to you,
we feel very happy for you.
Thank you for caring about me.
If you don't have anything to say, you can leave now.
OK.
By the way,
Shen Ye is making swords in your mansion, isn't he?
How is it going?
Though I don't know much about making swords,
yet I have never heard
he had any worries
or troubles.
So I think
his work goes smoothly.
You think it's smooth?
Such important weapons are being forged in your mansion.
Shouldn't you go to ask something about them?
You're right, mother.
I'm going back to see how it is going.
Well,
I can go back with her
to see how it is going.
Good.
As mother and daughter, you hardly have chances
to talk with each other.
Go ahead.
Then you can have a talk with your father
and wait for me for a while.
I will.
Mother, you know how to make swords, right?
No.
Could it be that you want to take the chance
to talk something with me personally?
Why did Xi Ze have a fancy for you suddenly?
Mother, you are so strange.
How could you ask me such a question?
Lord Xi Ze has been my husband for a long time.
But I heard that
Lord Xi Ze always lived on the Qi Nan Mountain.
Your marriage just existed in the name only.
Mother,
those are just rumors.
Lord Xi Ze and I are always attracted to each other.
Could it be that
you prefer to believe the slanders of the evil people
rather than believe your daughter?
How dare you talk to me like this?
Please calm your anger, mother.
I was just telling the truth.
I'm wondering why you suddenly mentioned Xi Ze.
Could it be that you are worried
after hearing we love each other?
Relying on Xi Ze's favor,
you dare to talk with me like this.
I dare not.
Aranya's mother
really hates her so much.
Mother.
Let me take you to the sword forging room.
No need. I can go there myself.
It's so strange today.
Your Majesty, it's not a long time after your last visit.
Aren't you afraid of His Majesty's suspicion?
Don't worry.
He allowed me to come here.
I don't need to worry about anything.
I'm not the one who is to rebel.
Anyhow,
I won't get you involved in it.
You are not as calm as before.
Today I come here
to ask you again.
If you'd like to join me,
tell me your opinions.
If not,
just tell me directly.
Even without you,
I will still take actions.
Your Highness.
What's wrong?
The steward said that
Lord Shen Ye invited you to the Mengchun Courtyard.
What?
He invited me to the Mengchun Courtyard?
Yes.
Did he tell you why?
I asked steward and he said he didn't know.
I got it.
I'll be there soon.
Do you know what that is?
It seems to be a magic instrument.
What is it used for?
It is the Glaze Lamp,
which can collect primordial spirit and memories.
Collect primordial spirit?
Inside of it
is Aranya's primordial spirit.
I made this dream
to bring Aranya back to life.
It was you
who made the Dream of Aranya!
Didn't you say that
you felt pity for Aranya?
I don't want to know who you are.
But
I want to tell you
I'm not as ruthless as you said.
My heart is in the dream.
This place
was made to bring Aranya back to life.
I have been using the Glaze Lamp
to collect her primordial spirit,
hoping that
she could come back to me.
So
the demon is not in Aranya's heart
but yours.
Yeah.
Since she died,
I have been in this dream
experiencing her life with her
and collecting her primordial spirit
the moment she died.
Aranya
will know
you have such deep love for her.
After the Earth Immortals die,
can they come back to life again?
With natural death,
the same as ordinary people, the Earth Immortals
can use Spirit-Forming Lantern or other ways
to come back to life again.
Even if the primordial spirit is vanished without trace
and the Spirit-Forming Lantern can do nothing,
as long as this dream is made,
everything can start from the very beginning
and even the dead can come back to life.
Moye and I missed a play.
I am still guilty about it.
Unexpectedly, you were also acting.
Why do you tell me now?
I didn't want to tell you,
but because of your appearance,
you have occupied Aranya's body,
everything has been different!
Xi Ze has changed.
The Stone Formation of Quanyin Beast has gone.
Even Qing Hua came to see me in advance.
Originally, in each life,
I can collect some part of
Aranya's primordial spirit.
Clearly I'm going to make it in this life.
But unexpectedly...
Beyond your expectation, maybe because of me,
all your efforts will be in vain.
I know
there must be someone secretly instructing you
to take Aranya's life course
to go on your performance.
He
is Su Moye, right?
Yeah, it's him.
He also wants to know what happened.
Why does he want to know it?
He is not qualified to know it.
Because of his appearance,
Aranya left me.
But in the last two years of Aranya's life,
he went to the West Sea.
What does he know?
He doesn't know Aranya's last choice.
If you want to get out of here,
you can only listen to me.
Because of you,
everything is changing.
Only by going back to the original course
can I finish collecting her primordial spirit.
You want to bring Aranya back to life.
Is it because you want to make up for your past mistakes?
What I have done wrong can't be changed.
I never wanted to cheat her.
Anyhow,
I must bring her back.
At that time, either she resents me
or regards me as a stranger,
I will tell her face to face that
there were too many misunderstandings between us
and we missed a lot.
I love her.
I don't want to lose her again.
OK.
I can help you.
It's not because of you
but Aranya.
She really had a miserable life.
I want her to come back to life again
and know that
someone is so deeply attached to her.
Who are you?
You wanted to kill me the moment you saw me.
Then don't blame me for breaking your plan.
Stay here.
What's wrong with you?
I've seen everything.
What did you see?
Aranya's memories.
Lingshu Stage.
Letters.
Quanyin Beast.
Both Aranya's primordial spirit and memories
have been in your body.
You're right.
Let me take you back.
Don't you always want to know what happened?
Go to see it yourself!
Most are very trivial things.
Too many things happened.
Just choose a time randomly.
You moved the Solanum pseudocapsicum trees
to the courtyard that day.
They have blossomed and born fruits by now.
There are also Solanum pseudocapsicum trees
in the Python Formation.
I used to eat such fruits when I was young.
It was said that there weren't such trees
in the Python Formation in the past.
But they rooted, sprouted
blossomed and fruited over a night.
Maybe the God also had compassion for me.
You did have true love with Aranya.
Aranya's love for you
was sincere and pure.
But you were
not that sincere to her.
Yeah.
Aranya loved me so deeply,
but I was too coward
and I didn't cherish her.
The period when Aranya stayed with you
was the happiest time in her life.
If everything had stopped at that moment,
it would be good.
It seemed that all the things happened later
made her feel sad.
Actually,
you can choose not to know her.
What did you see?
You and...
You and Aranya were playing chess.
And then?
Chacha came in.
Your Highness.
Your Excellency.
His Majesty...
Why are you in such a hurry?
Take it easy.
Here comes the news from the palace that
His Majesty died of illness.
My father was always in good health.
How could he suddenly...
Wait for a moment.
Wait for me.
Leave the game as it is.
Wait for me to come back.
Go ahead.
I still remember these things.
What happened later?
Then Aranya went to the imperial palace,
seeing his father who was in the bed
without breath.
Although her father never liked Aranya,
she cried with deep sorrow.
I thought
she didn't like her father.
And then?
Aranya wanted to help Xiangli He
to deal with the funeral of her father.
But she was refused by her mother.
So she returned to her mansion alone.
Your Highness.
Where is Shen Ye?
Prince Xiangli He invited him
to return to the Qi Nan Palace moments ago
to host the funeral of His Majesty.
I was about to send someone to inform you of it
when you came back.
The archmage left just minutes ago.
I think he hasn't gone far.
You can leave now.
Yes, Your Highness.
It turns out that,
compared with me,
you care more about yourself.
You sent me this that day
to say goodbye to me.
Unexpectedly, I didn't feel it.
Aranya was eager to see you,
but you just left without a word
and didn't wait to see her for the last time.
Shen Ye.
What did you go for?
How can you be so selfish?
I couldn't control the situation,
which was beyond my expectation.
If it's possible,
could you please tell me
what Aranya was thinking in the end?
For example,
did she resent me?
No.
She didn't resent you.
She just felt a little regretful.
Your farewell to her
was so veiled.
Later she was put into prison, right?
You, go over there.
Yes.
Guards.
Arrest Aranya!
Take her to the palace!
You...
What are you doing?
What did I commit?
Why do you arrest me?
Don't talk nonsense.
Take her away!
Yes.
Hurry up.
Uncle.
Aranya.
Do you confess your sin?
I don't know what I have committed.
Regicide!
How dare you say that you don't know your sin?
He who has a mind to beat his dog
will easily find a stick.
How stubborn you are!
If it goes on like this,
you're sure to be condemned to death.
Guards! Take Aranya away.
Put her into the prison to wait for punishments.
- Yes. - Yes.
Take her away!
This part
is too miserable!
How heartrending it is!
How could a mother
be so cruel to her biological daughter?
I didn't expect that
Qing Hua put Aranya to death behind me.
The biggest mistake I made in my life
was that I misread her.
Aranya did believe Qing Hua's mischief
and intended to die.
With thousands of arrows penetrating her heart,
living is no better than dying,
which is such a feeling!
I have told you that
what I did is to cheat Qing Hua.
No matter what you said is true or false, just put it aside.
Even if it's true,
how could Aranya know it then?
Aren't the incontestable evidence
and words more reliable?
I remember Moye ever told me that
he asked Aranya
if she resented you some day,
what the reason would be.
Do you know her answer?
Aranya said
it must be the reason that she got you
but lost you again.
For example, you fell in love with her
but gave up her later
and loved another person.
I pay my respect to Your Majesty.
Why are you in a panic?
Leave us alone.
Yes.
Sister.
It was reported that
they had made it.
Was it big enough?
I'm wondering if the night owls clan will dispatch troops.
Don't worry, sister.
The place attacked
happened to be under the administration
of the Eldest Prince of the night owls clan,
who has a hot temper
and is a born fighter.
It's unreasonable that he won't be tricked.
Sounds good!
As for me,
I have well-prepared
and am ready to dispatch troops anytime.
It's done!
The magic instrument that you want to forge
turns out to be a mirror.
This is
the Miaohua Mirror.
Miaohua Mirror?
As for the Miaohua Mirror in the Sky Kingdom,
I have heard of it.
The two...
It was modeled on that one.
But I have made some changes.
Although it's small,
as for the dead people's previous life and present life,
we can see all of them through this mirror.
You mean,
through this mirror,
we can see
how Aranya died.
Yeah.
I never knew
there was such a magic instrument in the world,
which can show the previous and present life of an immortal.
It's really fantastic!
I infer that
it was Shen Ye
who made the Dream of Aranya.
Shen Ye?
Then,
what did he want to do?
I don't know.
Well,
let's see what he did
and then find out the relationship
between Xiaobai and Aranya.
Then
let's start from the first time that
Shen Ye met Aranya.
I remember Aranya said
the first time she saw Shen Ye
was when she was young.
It was Shen Ye's birthday.
Are you sick?
There is no medicine in the Fanyin Valley
better than the blood of the archmage.
Let me save you.
It appeared that
the real first meeting
was much earlier than she knew.
Although you live in the snake nest,
you are not a snake.
You are the princess of the inseparable king bird clan.
So you must have a name.
Since your parents don't want to give you a name,
let me give you a name, OK?
Aranya.
This is your name.
If I say this word,
it means I am calling you. Understand?
Aranya.
Are you OK?
It turned out that
Shen Ye ever raised Aranya with his blood
when he was young.
And the words on Aranya's arm
were also carved by Shen Ye.
According to this,
their fate
was much deeper than mine
from the very beginning.
Fate
is always marvelous.
I always thought
it was Aranya herself
who desired for the fate with Shen Ye.
Clearly,
it's not true.
Shen Ye didn't seem to
be sincere to Aranya.
If not, how could he stand by and see her go die?
Could it be that Shen Ye changed his mind
after he grew up?
Do you want to go on watching it?
As for what happened later,
I know it generally.
Your Majesty.
Can we start watching from His Majesty's demise
and the time when Aranya was put into prison?
I want to know
if Shen Ye tried to save her.
OK.