Eternal Love of Dream
Episode 43
It's just a meal.
Why do you have so many dishes prepared?
Your Highness, you have been badly injured
and shed a lot of blood.
I'm so worried about you.
I hope you can get more nutrition.
Your Highness, let me serve you.
Don't bother. It's okay.
I just need more practice.
Your Highness.
Moye.
Why are you in a hurry?
Is there anything urgent?
Lord Xi Ze
asked me to go to Qi Nan Palace at once.
Xi Ze?
What happened?
Here is the thing.
Dong Hua asked me to go there in the early morning,
so I come here
to give this to you.
These are letters I mentioned last time.
Aranya wrote them to Shen Ye.
These days,
I've copied some of them.
What?
You've copied them out?
Here is the thing,
I copied
some letters in Aranya's handwriting.
Others
were just copied out
in my own handwriting.
Now that Dong Hua wanted to see me soon,
I have to leave the rest to you.
Okay.
Moye, you're really my bosom friend.
What I hate most is writing.
Remember.
Every two or three days,
send a letter to the Mengchun Courtyard.
No problem.
Okay.
I have to rush to Qi Nan Palace.
I'll leave it to you.
Your Highness,
be more careful when you read these letters.
What if others find it out?
Right. Thanks for reminding me.
Put them away.
Okay.
Take care. I'm leaving.
I heard you just moved to the Mengchun Courtyard,
so I wrote this letter to greet.
I once stayed in the yard for three years.
I was afraid nobody would go there
so that the beautiful view could be wasted.
Now that you're there,
I feel much relieved.
Luckily, Moye gave these letters to me
in advance.
Since I'm not Aranya,
it would be impossible
for me to write such letters.
I like to enjoy tea and make wine in my spare time.
When I was living there,
I buried some good wine in the yard.
The plum wine under the Mid-Lake Pavilion is the best.
It's a pity I don't have a chance to enjoy it.
I want to send it to you.
You may feel sad when you're alone.
I hope the wine can help you forget bad moments.
Wen Tian.
Wen Tian?
Did Moye get it wrong?
Isn't it a letter
for Shen Ye from Aranya?
Why is it Wen Tian?
Your Highness.
How is it going?
Your Highness,
for the several days since Shen Ye moved in,
he has never stepped out.
He ate little.
It seems he's a little upset.
Did the food not agree with his stomach?
You told us to take care of him,
so I asked people from the Qi Nan Palace about his taste.
All dishes were cooked
according to his flavor.
Got it.
Maybe Shen Ye
hasn't got used to the life here.
How about showing him around?
Don't let him shut himself in the Mengchun Courtyard all day.
Got it.
Oh.
Take this letter to Shen Ye.
Don't say anything
if he asks where it is from.
I see.
Aranya wrote these letters to comfort Shen Ye
when she knew he was in a bad mood.
She must've
been in deep love with him.
Those who fall in love may all do similar things.
Back then, to save His Majesty,
I even gave my fur
to Nie Chuyin.
Your Excellency.
Thank you.
Why does she still write letter to me?
We've been in the dream for a long time.
Xiaobai is finally back.
Your Majesty,
I've got a question for you.
Go ahead.
How did you and Fengjiu
fall into the Dream of Aranya together?
Is Fengjiu your...
I know what you want to ask.
You're right.
I like Xiaobai.
You're so straightforward.
Because I've missed much.
I don't want to miss her anymore.
Xiaobai said
you told her that
she had to experience the whole life of Aranya
to get out of the dream world.
To be honest,
I've never been to the Dream of Aranya.
It's just a guess.
It's also the only way I can figure out.
But I found the dream world is extremely dangerous.
What will happen is unpredictable.
Besides,
Xiaobai got injured for Aranya.
Her unrecovered primordial spirit was seriously damaged again.
Your Majesty,
Fengjiu got badly injured
because of my negligence.
Please punish me.
I couldn't control
what Xiaobai will go through.
So,
I have to make her primordial spirit recover soon
and leave here with her.
You're right.
I asked you to be here
because I need you to help me with something.
I'll do anything as you say.
Okay.
I'm making a magic instrument.
It's delayed since I need to look for some materials.
With the instrument, I can know Aranya's previous life.
We'll know how to get out of here
when we find out how it was created.
I need you to give me a hand.
I'll try my best.
Good.
Your Majesty.
Please tell me
the secret of the Dream of Aranya.
If Emperor Dong Hua can't come out,
Lian Song won't let us go.
And Meng will go into the dream world.
By then it'll be too late.
The Dream of Aranya is a taboo in our clan.
It's about the royal family's reputation.
I'll never tell anyone about it.
Jielu, as a member of the royal family,
you broke the rules on purpose. You're doubly guilty.
Your Majesty, it's not the right time
to consider the reputation.
Nothing is more important than life.
If you want to punish me,
just do it and I won't complain.
Please tell me the secret of the Dream of Aranya.
Just kneel here if you want.
Stay here and think about
what's the most important for the royal family.
All of you can go back now.
You don't need to stay here.
I'm worried about Ji Heng,
so I'm going to the Yulin Courtyard.
I'll be here if I can be of any help.
The imperial palace never needs me.
I'll worry too much if I go back there.
It's better to stay here.
I'll keep a distance from you
if you think I'm bothering you.
Never mind.
Xiaojiu is lucky
to have a good friend like you.
From tomorrow on, you don't need to make this for me.
See?
My hand is getting better.
Your Highness,
Lord Shen Ye has got a better appetite
in the past two days.
He also went to the Mid-Lake Pavilion.
It seems he feels much better.
Your Highness,
Lord Shen Ye asked me
to hand this letter over to Wen Tian of the imperial college.
Wen Tian?
Yes.
Give it to me.
That letter
was written to him
in the name of Wen Tian.
Don't tell him about it.
Don't let him know.
Keep it a secret.
Got it.
Your Highness,
what did Lord Shen Ye write in his letter?
Nothing special.
Just some words to express his gratitude.
Give this letter to Shen Ye.
Your Highness, you're amazing.
You've even prepared a letter in reply.
Just a coincidence.
This morning,
I thought of some good books
in the Mengchun Courtyard,
so I recommended them
to him to kill time.
You care about Lord Shen Ye so much.
I'll do all I can
to take care of him.
You may leave now.
Got it.
Your Highness,
you're so nice to Lord Shen Ye.
He's our guest.
We should be thoughtful.
Don't make that again.
Wen Tian.
Wen Tian really exists.
The handwriting is the same.
And even the content has no difference.
But why?
That day on Lingshu Stage,
you said those words to me
as if you were an onlooker who had known the truth.
Are you Aranya or not?
Aranya even set up a puzzle
for Shen Ye to solve.
She has good taste in art.
I didn't expect she's even expert at playing chess.
I have a headache at the sight of the chessboard.
Your Highness,
this is a letter from Lord Shen Ye.
Chacha.
Shen Ye said
he saw a few interesting travel notes
in the study of the Mengchun Courtyard.
Do you know where they are?
You mean
those travel notes you like very much?
I remember
they're put on the bottom shelf.
Why did he mention the travel notes suddenly?
I didn't mention anything about them
in my previous letters.
Is it possible he happened to find them
when he tried to get something to read
and he thought they were interesting after reading?
Maybe.
Oh.
Give this letter to the steward
and ask him to take it to the Mengchun Courtyard.
Yes, Your Highness.
Judging from the letters,
Shen Ye and Aranya have the same interests.
Oh no.
I've sent almost all the letters copied by Moye.
What should I do next?
I have to learn to imitate her handwriting.
Mr. Su.
Where is Aranya?
She asked me to send a letter.
She's in the yard.
Your Highness.
You scared me.
How is it going?
How many letters have you sent?
I've sent all letters copied by you.
Well.
You've made no progress on your handwriting.
Didn't you
need to practice calligraphy in Qingqiu?
Yes, I did.
It's...
It's because I injured my hand.
Aranya is the one who got injured.
Your hand is in good condition.
Alright.
Why are you back?
Where is His Majesty?
Well.
He's making a magic instrument.
I'm back to get some necessary materials
and look you up.
That'd be great.
Help me with these.
I can't stay for long this time.
I'm afraid there is not enough time.
Well.
You shouldn't be that lazy.
Oh.
How is it going with Shen Ye?
Have you met each other?
Speaking of him,
he's really a weirdo.
Since he moved to Mengchun Courtyard,
he's never stepped out of
that place.
But,
why is it Wen Tian's signature
in Aranya's letters to Shen Ye?
Who is Wen Tian?
She's
a teacher of the imperial college
who once lived in the Mengchun Courtyard.
At that time,
Aranya thought Shen Ye wouldn't read those letters
if he knew she wrote them,
so she wrote the letters in Wen Tian's name.
That explains it.
She had to write letters in another woman's name.
Aranya was really humble in the relationship.
If I were her,
I'd speak everything out.
In that way, there might be a slim chance.
Aranya
was not overcautious,
but she was afraid
Shen Ye would think it was out of sympathy,
so
she maintained
Shen Ye's dignity with great care
like that.
Aranya really had given much thought to it.
Later, I asked her to make a decision
and told him she wrote those letters,
but unexpectedly,
she chose to
let the real Wen Tian meet Shen Ye.
Did Wen Tian show up?
Yeah.
A lot of things happened between them later.
Moye,
I thought
Aranya was stronger than me
and she was more big-hearted.
But I didn't expect she'd been so pitiful.
She was in love with Shen Ye silently,
but he never knew about that.
Yeah.
But trust me.
I'll help her achieve her aim
and take good care of Shen Ye.
Oh.
Shen Ye would send you some wine in a few days.
Don't forget
to find a chance
so that Wen Tian and Shen Ye can meet each other. Got it?
Your Highness.
You may leave now, Chacha.
He solved the puzzle so quickly.
And he gave one back.
Aranya,
you were so careful and humble in the relationship.
And you didn't dare to tell Shen Ye how you felt.
The only thing I can do
is to tell him your true feelings.
Time flies.
This has already been the 18th letter.
It's time to get the wine.
Aranya,
this is the good wine you mentioned in your letter.
Gather frost-dyed berries to brew wine.
Store it underground for three seasons.
Then dry Fujiezi collected in autumn over a fire
before immersing it in the wine for half a month.
In this way, the wine will get the fragrance
of the herbal medicine.
After that, seal the wine again
and put it underground for two years.
Yeah.
It's time for me to send you some wine.
Your Highness, another letter from Lord Shen Ye.
What's that?
This is the wine.
Lord Shen Ye asked me to bring it to Ms. Wen.
Put it on the table.
Lord Shen Ye even knows how to make wine.
Shen Ye began to
write longer and longer letters.
He must be in a better mood.
Your Highness,
Lord Shen Ye looks the same as before,
but I guess he's in a better mood.
He plays chess, makes chess playbooks,
or goes to the Mid-Lake Pavilion.
That's good.
Chacha.
Is there a teacher called Wen Tian in the imperial college?
I remember
she once lived
in the Mengchun Courtyard, right?
Exactly.
Invite her to come here.
Got it.
It's getting
more and more boring.
I wonder how His Majesty is doing.
Oh.
Your Highness, what's up?
Chacha, I need to go out.
Your Highness, where are you going?
Stay out of it.
Invite Wen Tian to my mansion now.
Got it.
So much honey.
I wonder which kind His Majesty likes.
How are you, young lady?
How are you?
Come have a look. Which kind do you like?
The green one.
The yellow one and the red one.
Put the three of them in one jar.
Okay!
And that one.
The yellow one.
Okay.
Thanks.
Chacha, I'm back.
Your Highness, you're back.
Ms. Wen Tian has been waiting for you for so long.
Rise, please.
What's in your hands?
I found this chess playbook in the study
and was going to take it back and study it.
I met Chacha on my way
and she said you wanted to see me.
Did you have dinner?
Not yet.
Take it.
Have dinner with me.
This way.
To be honest,
I invite you here today
because I want to ask you to do me a favor.
Your Highness, just tell me.
Since that thing happened to Junuo,
Shen Ye has been staying
in my mansion.
Entrusted by someone
to take good care of him,
I've been communicating with him
through letters,
in the name of you.
Do you mean
you wrote letters to Lord Shen Ye
and signed yourself "Wen Tian"?
Yes.
You must know that
there has been bad blood between him and me.
I was afraid he'd be more resentful
if he found I wrote the letters,
so I did it in your name.
I see.
I admire you for your kindness.
It's just there have been so many things to deal with recently
that my strength doesn't equal to the will.
And I don't want to let down the one who entrusted me with it,
so I wonder
if you can take it over
and look after Shen Ye for me.
You did me a lot of favors.
Of course, I'll help you in return.
Can you tell me what I should say in the letters?
There is nothing special.
You just need to share with him
some interesting things in daily life.
I wrote these letters
to Shen Ye
in your name.
I've copied them out for you
lest Shen Ye finds anything wrong.
I have to emphasize
one more thing.
Please imitate my handwriting
when you write him letters
to avoid giving the game away.
Please trust me.
It's not hard for me.
I'll count on you.
Your Highness,
why did you suddenly want to make sugar figurines?
I promised Xi Ze
to make him some other day.
I'm free today.
So I have made these sugar foxes.
You're really quick-witted and nimble-fingered.
I didn't know
you can even do that.
These sugar foxes are so cute.
Really?
Do you think he'd like it?
Trust me.
His Excellency likes
everything you make.
Alright.
Then,
I'll give Xi Ze ten.
These are for my master.
I'll give him five.
As for the rest...
Oh.
Shen Ye sent me some wine the other day.
It's impolite not to reciprocate.
I'll give him five.
Your Excellency, you've got a visitor.
Come in.
Your Excellency. Mr. Su.
What's up?
Her Highness Aranya
asked me to take this to you.
Mr. Su,
this is for you.
Why...
Why does he have ten
and I have only five?
Did you eat on the way?
Mr. Su, you got me wrong.
Her Highness told me clearly
His Excellency has ten
Mr. Su has five.
I am going.
Come on, Your Majesty.
Don't be so mean.
It's not as good as God Zhe Yan's wine,
but I've never
drunk such refreshing wine
since I left Qingqiu.
Lord Shen Ye, why are you here?
What wine were you drinking?
I've been unoccupied these days,
so I...
Your Highness.
I think I lost my chess playbook
in your place today.
Wen Tian, it's a good timing.
Let me introduce you to him.
This is Lord Shen Ye.
Lord Shen Ye, this is Wen Tian.
She used to live in the Mengchun Courtyard.
Nice to meet you, Your Excellency.
The wine has strong delayed effect.
I feel dizzy.
I must go. See you.
Your Highness.
Lord Shen Ye and Wen Tian
wrote a few letters to each other.
Ms. Wen sent him two small gifts.
One is a straw white-headed sparrow
and the other is an embroidered pendant with auspicious patterns.
Lord Shen Ye sent her two books in return.
Their relationship is moving so fast.
They even began to send each other tokens of affection.
Where are they?
I think they're playing chess by the river.
Leave them alone.
Got it.
She pushed her beloved away
to another woman like that.
If she were more fearless
and dared to tell him her true feelings,
would they have a chance
to stay together?
I've changed my mind.
When the moon shines brightly in the sky
and the wind blows through the bamboo forest,
let's have a hearty drink
and forget all worries.
After today,
it'll be the time for us to fall out.
Xiangli Aranya.
= Xiangli Aranya =
You're the one who wrote those letters.
You lied to me and made a fool of me.
Do you think it's interesting?
You found it out so soon?
How did you know that?
Oh no. What a fool I am!
I could have denied it.
I wrote back to you
with sincerity.
Does it make you happy
to see me end up like this?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
How about having some tea?
Calm down. Take your time.
Actually, you shouldn't have thought like that.
How could I be happy by lying to you?
Fine.
I won't write letters again.
Okay?
What you said to me
on Lingshu Stage that day
was totally different from before.
Your response today
was also different.
I've never heard Aranya could make sugar figurines.
And I've never received sugar foxes.
What on earth is going on?
In this dream world,
nothing changed,
except you.
You've changed so much.
I didn't expect Shen Ye would be so angry
after finding out the truth.
It seems he's not
inconstant in love.
Something must've gone wrong.
I can't fall asleep anyway.
I'll go see what's happening in Mengchun Courtyard.
Why are birds twittering at night?
Your Majesty.
Xiaobai.