Eternal Love of Dream
Episode 51
So Chenxiang ran away from home
to save San Sheng Mu
who was pinned under the mountain.
Some people run away from home to fulfill filial duty,
while some send no messages back
after running away for more than half a year
which makes their families worry.
Li,
when you grow up,
you should never follow this bad example.
Sister Fengjiu is back after running away from home!
Good boy!
Is your uncle telling you stories?
These are just stories from the script.
I'd like to hear something fresh.
Can you tell me?
I like to hear new stories the most.
Sister Fengjiu,
I didn't tell them that
you fell into the Fanyin Valley...
Li,
just go somewhere to play.
I've got something serious to talk to your elder sister.
I'm really tight-lipped.
Though I learned from Third Grandpa
that Sister Fengjiu and Brother Dong Hua kissed each other,
I didn't tell them.
Uncle,
why are you still here?
Why didn't you go back to Qingqiu?
I'm waiting for you.
Without taking you back, how to handle
the great event in Qingqiu?
No need to wait for me.
After all, I often go out to play.
It's not a big deal in Qingqiu.
If you stay here because of me,
God Zhe Yan will surely be angry at me.
It seems you've forgotten about
an important event concerning you recently.
What is it?
So you've really forgotten about it.
Then let me remind you.
Your Weapon Hiding Ceremony
is right after 15 days.
Right! I've really forgotten about it.
Uncle,
just pretend you haven't seen me today.
I'll be back 15 days later.
Originally, I could transform into you
and fulfill the ceremony on your behalf.
Now that you're back,
you should fulfill your own duty.
I...
There're still 15 days left.
If you sleep four or six hours less every day,
you'll have enough time to prepare for it.
But I only sleep eight hours a day.
Poor girl!
But young as you are,
you'll be fine even
if you only sleep two or four hours a day.
You're not asked to stay all night long.
Just be content with it.
I see.
I'll get ready for it.
Though the formalities of Qingqiu
are not so heavy as those of the Sky Kingdom,
the major formalities shall not be missed.
Fine.
Both of them have returned safely.
You can finally stop pulling a long face.
Thanks to you,
they're back safely this time.
Without me,
Fengjiu can still come back safely.
That was Emperor Dong Hua.
Would he let any harm come to her?
Right.
You just worry too much.
Didn't you also lose much cultivation
guarding for them?
Only when they returned safely
did you feel relieved to come back
to the Sky Kingdom, right?
I'm probably influenced by you.
What?
I feel uncomfortable
with you staring at me like that.
I wonder why you haven't visited Fengjiu yet.
When she was in the Sky Kingdom previously,
you hung out every day.
Now she's got no time to play with me.
Are they so intimate that they don't even
want to part with each other?
Well,
she's bothered about how to persuade
her family into accepting His Majesty.
However, the Weapon Hiding Ceremony is also coming.
Now, she's even more bothered.
The Weapon Hiding Ceremony?
It's a ceremony which must be held
after a new monarch of Qingqiu succeeds to the throne.
The new monarch must forge
a handy weapon in person
and hide it in the Holy Land under his or her rule
in front of immortals from the Eight Deserts
on the very day of the ceremony,
so that the future generations can use it.
I remembered.
I also participated in Bai Qian's
Weapon Hiding Ceremony back then.
In the Four Seas and the Eight Deserts,
it's really a great event.
Is she ready?
She forged the Hexu Sword
long ago,
but as to the sword box...
Unfinished?
She thought
there was still time.
Even if she played for two months
after Bai Qian's wedding banquet,
she still got time to make the box.
However, she fell into the Fanyin Valley
and forgot about the whole thing.
Now,
she is surely sparing no efforts in
choosing the material
and style of the sword box
and dares not get distracted.
She's careless,
just like you.
No wonder you're friends.
But she has Emperor Dong Hua
who excels at making sword boxes.
With the help of Dong Hua,
the sword box can be finished in a day or two for sure.
At such a critical moment,
if Fengjiu doesn't
turn to him for help,
she really wastes a great talent.
Perhaps with a few soft words,
Dong Hua will make the box for her to save her the trouble.
Why should she be bothered?
Such a romantic trick does sound like your style.
No wonder you can't become friends.
Fengjiu said that
surely nothing could go wrong with the help of His Majesty,
but if she relied on him all the time,
she would be too unmotivated.
Moreover,
His Majesty also doesn't want her to be
a loser who can only rely on him.
He will only help her arrange the schedule
of making the sword box.
As to the rest,
he probably won't help.
Let's make a bet.
I'm also curious whether His Majesty
will make the sword box for her or not.
Back then, Bai Qian's Weapon Hiding Ceremony was so grand.
Fengjiu can't lose.
If I win,
you should attend Fengjiu's Weapon Hiding Ceremony
to support her and bring attention to the event.
If you win,
I'll personally fetch some fat fish in the Pundarika Pond
and have Fengjiu cook sweet and sour fish
for you for half a month.
She's really good at cooking.
The wagers are fairly good,
but given Fengjiu's situation,
it's better that I win.
No.
It's not so good if I win.
If I eat the sweet and sour fish cooked by Fengjiu,
jealous as Dong Hua is,
he will definitely make me spit it out.
That's it.
I originally wanted to apologize to aunt,
but I didn't expect that
the Weapon Hiding Ceremony is only 15 days away.
I haven't finished my sword box yet.
= From the 1st day to the 5th day
making a 1.3-m Han Nanmu box =
= From the 5th day to the 10th day making patterns at joints,
at the bottom and on both sides of the box =
= From the 10th day to the 15th day inlaying two pieces
of Yufu-jade-carved Foling flowers at the top =
According to the progress chart,
without accident,
the sword box can be made in 15 days.
Dong Hua, just wait.
I will get back at you.
Your Majesty,
you...
Nie Chuyin,
go and get me some demons to eat.
Demons?
Hurry up!
Yes!
Go.
Yes.
Your Highness!
Bad news!
Why are you in such a hurry?
Bad...
Bad news!
Her Majesty...
Your Majesty!
Your... Your Majesty!
Your Majesty,
by making such a fuss,
how can we hide from others?
They're nothing but a dozen losers.
I need more.
Right.
Your Majesty, you're extremely powerful,
but to help you recover your power,
I'm afraid there won't be many demons left in our clan.
How can we fight the gods then?
Are you questioning me?
I beg your pardon.
I dare not.
Majestic and powerful as Your Majesty is,
you're fearless to heaven and earth.
It's a supreme glory for our clan.
The Miaoyi Chasm keeps being strengthened.
I need to get the blood tear as soon as possible.
From today on,
send one hundred demons for me to eat every day.
Act without fail.
One hundred demons?
Yes!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty,
how about this?
Yes.
Your Majesty,
how about this?
this time...
This place is nice.
Your Majesty, the cool breeze is blowing outside.
Her Highness Fengjiu's desk is not put in the right place
to enjoy the cool breeze.
Let me also move Her Highness's desk.
Good idea.
Yes.
I remember that last year
when I was also playing the game of go
with you in Tai Chen Palace,
I advised you that
if one day,
you come round and want to marry an Empress,
Zhihe might be a good choice.
But now, it seems that
Zhihe is not a match for you.
As to my foster sister,
her heart was pure.
Moreover, I was indebted to her parents,
so I would naturally look after her all the time.
Maybe because I cared for her too much,
she was too spoiled.
So you sent her to the Lord of the West Sea
to discipline her.
Upright and righteous,
the Lord of the West Sea makes an excellent teacher.
If Zhihe can learn a thing or two from him,
she is bound to make some progress.
You do worry a lot about her.
But after years' waiting, you've found Fengjiu.
It's worth it.
Only she
deserves to be your Empress.
Are you drunk today?
I rarely hear you say something nice.
I didn't drink today.
I just heard something from Cheng Yu.
Cheng Yu asked Fengjiu
why not ask you to make the sword box for her.
But she answered that
she wanted to do everything on her own.
And that she didn't want to rely on you all the time
and become a loser in the end.
When I heard it,
I thought she didn't mean it.
Little girls
always want to feel cared and loved.
But you didn't help her,
and she's fine with that.
She did mean
what she said.
Xiaobai is sensible all the time.
Your Majesty!
Your Highness!
What's up?
The inseparable king birds and night owls
have been resettled properly.
I've made inquiries in person today.
Is it too cautious
to make inquiries every day?
However,
there are many people in the Sky Kingdom
and they gossip with one another.
Fairy maids and servants will surely talk about it.
I'm afraid Her Highness Fengjiu
will notice that sooner or later.
Never mind.
Now she's busy preparing for the Weapon Hiding Ceremony
and has no time for distraction.
After the ceremony,
I'll take her to Bihai Cangling
and we won't be back until the wedding.
You're too protective of her.
She's still a little girl.
She deserves to enjoy
the happy hours before the wedding.
Do you want some cakes?
No.
What about the porridge?
Yes. Good.
When will you take me back to Qingqiu to meet your parents?
After I persuade grandma and father.
How come I spoke out my mind?
Will His Majesty get angry?
Are you tired?
Get some sleep if you feel tired.
I'm not tired. Just lean on me.
Please be patient these few days.
After I persuade grandma and father,
I'll take you back to Qingqiu.
Fine.
Your Highness,
for these days,
Her Majesty ate one hundred demons
every day to improve her power.
I'm afraid if it goes on,
demons will be exterminated.
I'm also aware of that,
but if I don't follow
Her Majesty's order,
I'm afraid I'll also be killed.
Your Highness,
forgive me for being outspoken and disrespectful.
I forgive you.
Go ahead.
In my opinion,
Her Majesty is bent on having her own way.
I'm afraid she doesn't take
your wish seriously.
You mean...
If Her Majesty keeps doing so,
the foundation of demons will collapse.
What if gods and demons go to war
or Her Majesty turns mad and bloodthirsty in future?
We might as well trick other clans
into feeding Her Majesty.
In this way, we might be able to protect our clan.
The Weapon Hiding Ceremony is in less than two days.
Finally, it won't be long before the whole thing ends.
I remember you've finished sketching the sword box.
It's so late. What are you drawing?
So you're drawing a house.
Why do you remain silent?
I've finished the sword box.
I couldn't fall asleep for the moment,
so I began to draw the picture.
Actually, I'm not used to living in the fox cave
left by aunt in Qingqiu.
I've long wanted to build a small bamboo house
in the bamboo forest outside.
And I've drawn the house before,
but it didn't have bedrooms for you and fox cubs,
so I want to draw the picture again
and ask Mi Gu to build it for me.
Though in one year, you may only
live in Qingqiu for half of the year,
I still feel...
Is this one for me?
I'm unoccupied actually.
Tai Chen Palace and Qingqiu are no difference to me.
I can live in Qingqiu all the time.
But I think
I should share a room with you.
Why did you get me another room?
I've been thoughtful.
If we quarrel with each other,
where can you sleep?
If you don't have your own room,
should you sleep in the study?
I think
no matter how angry you're at me,
you should not kick me out.
Let's talk about these things later.
These are all minor details.
What's the most important now
is to figure out how many rooms
we shall leave for the fox cubs.
What do you think?
The number of rooms equals the number of fox cubs.
Is that right?
Well,
let's leave one room.
But I want to leave two rooms.
Because with two fox cubs, it can be fun and lively.
But I'm also thinking that
if they're too close to each other,
they may not be close to me.
What if they don't play with me by then?
Then let's have two cubs.
No need to change this picture.
Leave my room to them.
That's a deal.
But...
I haven't finished yet!
If we don't go to bed,
how can we have fox cubs?
But, have you seen my sword box?
Have I done a good job?
I've seen it! It's wonderful!
You have to get some sleep.
You've worked hard for days. Aren't you tired?
But...
I...
Many people have come.
When holding ceremonies,
Qingqiu never sends out invitations.
Immortals from the Eight Deserts having time
and feeling interested
are all our guests if they come.
For those who are not free or interested,
we won't force them to come.
Well said.
This is the Qingqiu's style.
However,
despite that,
we can still estimate
the size of the event,
the occasion of the event,
and the famous immortals from heaven and earth
who would actually come.
Your Majesty!
Have a seat!
God Zhe Yan,
His Majesty seldom attends ceremonies.
Why would he attend Xiaojiu's Weapon Hiding Ceremony today?
Well,
you'll see later.
What's special about the Weapon Hiding Ceremony?
Today,
Her Highness Fengjiu will pass the formation
with the newly forged Hexu Sword.
Only after she passes the formation can she set foot
on the one hundred grass steps
and hide the sword into the Holy Mountain.
If she fails, there will be another divination,
and the Weapon Hiding Ceremony will be held again
one hundred years later.
Who set this formation?
This formation was a magic trick
planted by Emperor Bai Zhi in person
when initiating the Weapon Hiding Ceremony.
When the ceremony platform opens,
the magic trick works automatically
to form unpredictable formations.
Since it's set by Emperor Bai Zhi in person,
it must be hard to pass.
The Ceremony is a grand event
because it's a demanding task for the new monarch.
If she fails,
her efforts in forging the sword
in the previous one hundred years will be wasted completely.
Moreover, she will lose face.
Competitive as Xiaobai is,
no wonder she stayed up all night.
You're lucky to see
Fengjiu's Weapon Hiding Ceremony with your own eyes.
In Qingqiu,
they rarely wear fancy clothes and hold grand ceremonies.
This is the most important ceremony
in her life.
A few days ago,
Ye Hua drank with me.
He found it a pity that
he was unable to see God Bai Qian's
Weapon Hiding Ceremony in person.
He could only imagine what she was like
according to book records.
Well,
what was Xiaobai like when she was born?
Never let Ye Hua hear what you just said.
He may think you're trying to piss him off.
You're both son-in-laws of Qingqiu,
but having tasted love earlier than you,
he's really experienced.
Be careful if he tricks you.
What's in your hand?
You mean this?
These are snacks that Xiaobai made for me.
I'm afraid they might melt in the sun,
so I keep them in a glass box.
She is going to have a grand ceremony
in front of thousands of immortals from the Eight Deserts.
You actually asked her to make snacks for you!
Are you a bit shameless?
Don't do me wrong.
The second time I saw Xiaobai,
she kicked a flowerpot toward my head,
but she calmly made Mi Gu the scapegoat.
It's not a big occasion.
Do you think she'll get nervous easily?
According to rank,
her grandpa also has to sit in your right hand seat.
She actually dares to make you love her.
In such an occasion,
she certainly won't be nervous.
Now that you're ready,
it should be easy for you
to handle several formations of
the Weapon Hiding Ceremony.
How come you're so nervous?
Uncle, I'm not nervous about that.
I...
Is my father here?
Are you kidding?
Your father will host
the Weapon Hiding Ceremony for you today.
Can he miss it?
What about mother?
What about the other uncles?
It's important to you. Of course they've all come.
Those who should come are here,
and the one who shouldn't come
is also here.
The one who shouldn't come?
Who?
Emperor Dong Hua.
Why is he here?
How come I didn't know?
Well, didn't you know he would come?
Uncle,
I've got something to tell you.
What?
After the Weapon Hiding Ceremony,
I'd like to introduce someone to father.
Can you go with me?
Hold it.
Let's talk about it
after the Weapon Hiding Ceremony.
It's time.
Distinguished guests, please enjoy the ceremony.
The Weapon Hiding Ceremony starts now.
If I keep fighting to stall for time,
I won't be able to break out of the formation for sure.
Though the formation
cast by grandpa changes constantly,
the number of immortals forming the formation
remains to be ten all along.
In this case,
the other shadows
can only be illusions.
Good! Good! Good!
Awesome!
Terrific!
Good! Good!
Wonderful!
Exchange love glances
with the one you love in public.
I've never done that actually.
How I failed to live up to my reputation as a playboy!
Finally, I can show off the sword box
I've worked so hard to make these days.
Hide Hexu
in the hall!
Long live the martial virtue!
May Heaven bless the East Desert!
A magic weapon is forged
by our virtuous young monarch!
Hide Hexu
in the hall!
Long live the martial virtue!
May Heaven bless the East Desert!
What a feast shared by the gods!
But to me,
it seems that one step is missing
in Her Highness Fengjiu's Weapon Hiding Ceremony.
Showing up now
and saying those words,
Nie Chuyin obviously wants to cause trouble.
I wonder how Qingqiu will deal with him.
I heard that demons are natural
and unrestrained by rituals.
I didn't expect that Demon Lord Xuan
actually values rituals so much.
Today in Qingqiu, we hold
an ancient ceremony on our own land,
but we still have to trouble you to teach us the procedures.
How embarrassed we are!
God Bai Yi,
I'm wronged.
How dare I teach you?
But luckily, I've seen
two Weapon Hiding Ceremonies in the primitive time,
which I admired a lot.
I remember that
after the sword testing, it was the sword competition.
How come in Her Highness Fengjiu's Weapon Hiding Ceremony,
the sword hiding follows the sword testing directly?
What's going on?
I heard that the Weapon Hiding Ceremony of Qingqiu
does include sword competition.
Immortals of the same generation
can all challenge the new monarch.
It's fine if you lose,
but if you win, the new monarch will give you a promise.
Why have the recent Weapon Hiding Ceremonies
cancelled the sword competition?
I heard that Emperor Bai Zhi
set the sword competition
to motivate the descendants of the Bai's family
to work hard since childhood
so as to stand out among their generations.
But when it came to God Bai Qian,
given that she's a girl,
the Empress pitied her so much
that she cried before Emperor Bai Zhi every day.
Later, Emperor Bai Zhi
also felt sympathetic,
so the sword competition in the Weapon Hiding Ceremony
was cancelled automatically.
It's tacitly assumed that
if Qingqiu has another female monarch in future,
the sword competition will also be cancelled automatically.
If so,
Nie Chuyin has broken the rule
by requiring a sword competition today, right?
Unfortunately,
it's not recorded in the Ritual Book of Qingqiu,
so it doesn't count.
By coming here today,
he can get some benefits.
Anyway, he makes perfect sense.
Since the rules for
the Weapon Hiding Ceremony in Qingqiu remain the same,
there should be a competition.
I've long heard that Her Highness Fengjiu
is extremely good at sword skills.
I'd like to compete with her.
Even if there should be a sword competition,
you and my daughter are not of the same generation.
How can you compete with her?
Please be self-dignified.
God Bai Yi, you wronged me again.
In Qingqiu,
Fengjiu belongs to the third generation.
I'm also a third-generation demon lord.
In this case,
Fengjiu and I are of the same generation.
God Bai Yi,
I'm deeply engrossed in sword skills.
I want to compete with Her Highness Fengjiu sincerely.
I'm a demon,
but I'm not afraid to lose.
Her Highness Fengjiu is a goddess.
Is she afraid to lose?
It's supposed to be a competition within your clan.
After he said that,
it actually becomes a competition
between the descendants of the two clans.
Though gods and demons are on good terms
with each other these years,
there's actually animosity deep down.
Provoked by Demon Lord Nie
and watched by immortals
from the Eight Deserts and Six Directions,
Xiaojiu has no choice but to compete with him.
I just don't get it!
Why doesn't he fulfill his duty as a demon lord
instead of adding trouble to the event
and gaining the reputation of bullying the weak?
Father,
since Demon Lord Nie insists on competing with me
and it's hard to meet such a highly skilled sword master,
I'd like to have a try.
I can learn a lot for sure.
Your Highness, you're straightforward.
Well,
good!