Eternal Love of Dream
Episode 46
Your Highness,
Mr. Su is leaving for the palace.
So soon?
By the way,
I've made a few sugar foxes for the master.
They are in the study.
Fetch them for me.
I noticed a small bag
while I was cleaning up the study last night.
I saw a note on it for Mr. Su.
I came here just to consult Your Highness
if you'd like to hand it over to Mr. Su.
Chacha, you know me best.
Your Highness!
You made one portion for me again?
Yeah!
Even the cleaning attendants
in my place have sugar foxes.
You certainly have a portion as well.
But yours are bigger than theirs.
I sent some to Shen Ye as well.
His taste is very different from yours.
I heard he gave them to the boys there.
They all said they were good.
Try one and see how it tastes.
Your Highness,
did you mention this to anyone else?
No!
Only those who are close to me know it.
That's great!
Remember
not to mention it in the future.
It's good to you.
Why?
Because it's against the rule
for you to make sugar in person
and give it to the subordinates and people like us
considering your identity.
The previous Aranya
wouldn't do such things.
I was too careless and didn't think that much.
That's so considerate of you.
It's fine. Be careful in the future.
By the way,
in three days, Junuo will come out of the capital city.
Aranya did Shen Ye and Junuo
a favor before
by arranging them to meet for the last time.
So this time,
I've bribed the prosecutors
to arrange a parting scene for them
by the side of the river outside the city.
Do I need to do anything?
Aranya didn't follow them there at the time.
So, I can't follow there either.
If you are free,
it's fine to take a look.
Sure!
By the way,
I thought about the story
you told me about Aranya and Shen Ye
last night before going to bed.
Lord Xi Ze never
went out of the Qi Nan Mountain at the time,
so he had nothing to do with the affair
about Aranya and Shen Ye.
But His Majesty
moved into my place
with Xi Ze's identity.
I'm afraid
this is a great change, isn't it?
Yeah!
I'm thinking about it too.
The part about the Quanyin Beast is definitely gone!
So,
we gotta think of other ways
to push Shen Ye to express his affection.
Well,
don't forget this!
Oh yeah,
I almost forgot it!
See you!
It's really another state of mind
to look at Lord Shen Ye
after knowing Aranya's fate.
Archmage,
tomorrow is the day for Junuo to come out of the city.
I've bribed the prosecutors.
Will you go to see her for the last time?
I'm talking to you. Did you hear me?
Yeah, I do!
Where will it be?
By the riverside outside the city.
I'll lead the way by then.
Are you going, too?
Definitely! Anything wrong?
No!
It was arranged by you.
So you can go as you like.
Well said!
I'd go even if you mind it.
You used to be a person who didn't care about people's business.
Says who?
I do care about people's business.
Maybe I don't care much about the others' business.
However,
I'm pretty interested
in your business.
I heard my mother came yesterday.
She came to check out the progress of the sword.
She's too concerned about this sword.
I'm afraid that was not the only words
she said to you explicitly and implicitly, was it?
As I saved Junuo,
she came to say thanks to me.
I also helped to save Junuo
at the Lingshu Stage.
Why didn't she even come to see me?
She has been behaved like that to you
ever since you were born.
You could put up with it in the past.
Why can't you bear it now all of a sudden?
Why should I keep bearing it now
just as I have borne it in the past?
Prosecutor,
come here!
What can I do for you, Your Highness?
You just don't understand it, do you?
If you keep staring at them like that,
how could they talk?
Forgive me for my stupidity.
I'll have to disappoint you
for your affection.
I'm
no match to you now.
I just hope
we can sign a deal for our next life.
If I had the next life,
I would surely not disappoint you.
Do you really think I saved you
because I have feelings for you?
You said that
I was your little sister that grew up together with you,
so you wouldn't leave me alone
even if I made any mistakes.
But you're not a nosy person.
You clearly knew there would be severe consequence
on the day at the execution ground,
but you still took the risk.
Isn't that because you like...
I saved you
just because I wanted to save the only heir of your father.
A man of honor repays his debt.
If you have to thank someone,
thank your father for showing great mercy to me.
Then why are you here today to see me off?
I'm just taking the chance to take a walk outside.
Shen Ye,
you've hated Changdi and Aranya the most ever since we were young.
But you've treated me the best.
Junuo,
your mother's blood is neither pure nor auspicious.
You and Changdi have the same mother.
You are self-abandoned.
There should have been no difference.
I've looked up to you too much in the past.
I'm not pure or auspicious.
How about Aranya?
We have the same mother.
Now she's married
but she still seduces you.
Isn't she more impure and ominous
and self-abandoned?
Yet, you're still willing to be imprisoned by her.
Yes, I am!
So what?
Prosecutor, time is up!
You should send her on the way.
Yes, Your Highness!
Your Highness!
Lord Shen Ye!
You must be thirsty
after so much talking to Junuo?
Would you like a cup of tea?
Alright, as you wish!
Where is the tea?
Here!
I've just made it.
It might be a bit scalding. Blow it on!
This tea is not of high grade.
However,
the water comes from the dew
collected from lotus leaves.
I'm not sure if you can get used to it.
It's wide-spread that you and Lord Xi Ze love each other a lot.
You are a paragon for all the royal families.
How come you have the time to be here?
I come here just for fun
and see your attitude to Junuo.
I found that
you were indeed a person of no tenderness to women.
Your Excellency,
Her Highness Aranya should be right up there.
Hold on a second.
Lord Xi Ze,
are these flowers picked particularly for Her Highness?
Sadly, they're not as good as Yueling flowers.
But I can make do with it.
Shen Ye,
do you have to show the poker face to me?
This is how I am!
You don't have to.
What do you mean?
If we are both so arrogant,
we'll have to miss each other.
Why are you so careless?
It's cold water.
You're taken in.
You!
Shen Ye!
I've always been waiting for you to say it.
Aren't you gonna say it now?
What do you want to hear?
You tell me!
Yes!
You helped me save Junuo
and allowed me to make the sword in your place.
I forgot to thank you for that.
That's not it!
Then what should it be?
Shen Ye,
is it so difficult for you
to say it?
I like you.
What did you say?
I said I liked you.
I've been always liking you very much.
Don't you know it?
Your Highness,
you're joking.
Shen Ye,
there is nobody else around here.
Why would I conceal
my heart-felt words?
I know
we all have had our own marriage contracts.
But...
But I can't lie to my own heart.
Enough! Stop talking!
Shen Ye,
I came today
not to see off Junuo
but to seek for your confession.
As long as you say to me that you don't like me,
I'll leave you alone
from today on.
I won't feel any pain
or have anything to do with you at all.
Aranya,
I love you!
Don't leave!
Don't leave
from now on.
Lord Xi Ze, you are really thoughtful to Her Highness.
Am I?
I've disappointed her so much before.
I just feel sorry for Aranya.
She didn't hear it till the end of her life.
You have known very well that I'm not Aranya,
but Aranya treated you so well.
She loved you so much.
Yet, you never admitted you loved her.
Shen Ye,
you disappointed Aranya so much.
You're not Aranya.
Who on earth are you?
Chacha, why are you here?
Your Highness,
Lord Xi Ze saw it all.
Your Majesty!
Is he really jealous?
How come it's raining now?
Your Majesty!
I just feel sorry for Aranya.
She didn't hear it till the end of her life.
You have known very well that I'm not Aranya.
But Aranya treated you so well.
She loved you so much.
Yet, you have never admitted you love her.
Shen Ye, you disappointed Aranya so much.
How do you think of the flowers?
You sit beside me
to interrupt my reading.
It's too dull to read alone.
I accommodate myself to Your Excellency so much
only because Your Excellency
couldn't live without me for a second.
The stem is too long
and there are a lot of leaves.
Thank you for your appraisal!
All that I can do
is to guess what you want.
If you address me as Your Excellency
and yourself as maid again,
I'd throw you out!
Your Excellency said that many times,
but never did it in reality.
Turn around!
It's just a joke.
Are you really mad
and want to throw me out?
Sometimes, I feel it's not enough.
Sometimes, I feel it's very good.
What is not enough?
Aranya,
you probably meant this
when you said it was not enough.
What are you doing here?
I should be asking you that.
This is my bed.
Your bed is over there.
You actually came back early, didn't you?
No wonder
I couldn't find you anywhere
for the whole afternoon.
Now you almost got on the wrong bed.
Are you dizzy from too much sleep?
I was walking outside
and forgot the time.
Just got back and carelessly laid on the wrong bed.
What happened to your face?
You...
What on earth were you doing?
Have you been in the rain the whole time?
Why didn't you find a shelter
or create a shelter
with your magic power?
I was thinking about something
so I wasn't aware of the rain.
Chacha is really a good fortuneteller.
Xiaobai,
why did you evade me so worriedly?
To avoid arousing suspicion?
I have already been so weak,
what can I do to you?
I won't do anything to you if I could.
I feel dizzy.
Please stay with me for a while.
What suspicion to avoid?
It's hard not to feel dizzy
as you've been in the rain for 10 to 12 hours.
I'll get you some warm water to have a dip.
If you can still move,
take off your clothes and get covered up in the quilt.
If you can't, then stay still.
I can't.
Then take the dip with clothes on.
Now I can.
Alright. Go for the dip.
Your body is so hot. You must be extremely sick.
Come on!
I feel dizzy.
Call me if you need anything.
I'll be right here.
Xiaobai,
I thought of the past while walking.
What did you think of?
I've let you down so deeply in the past.
I'll forgive you
whatever you say or do
as I owe you so much.
So, you just need to speak out
the real thoughts in your mind.
I won't be mad
or blame you.
What are you talking about?
It didn't look like acting as to how you treated Shen Ye today.
Since I have to
live as Aranya,
I must act as vividly as it could be.
You said
Aranya's affection to Shen Ye
deeply touched you.
Yeah,
I did.
So what?
So you're just too devoted
to being Aranya
and starting to like him.
What are you talking about?
You're not acting
as Aranya anymore.
You have fallen in love with Shen Ye.
When did it begin?
Was it the time he saved you in the serpentine cage
while I didn't make it there?
You want someone
who can save you when you're in danger.
You think he is the one, don't you?
Don't think too much! Enjoy the bath!
What nonsense is that?
He won't faint in the water, will he?
Your Majesty!
Why did you hide under the water?
I was thinking.
You're too noisy!
Alright! Go on with it then!
Remember to wear some clothes before coming out.
I'm going to make the bed for you.
Which part of Shen Ye is better than me?
I haven't made such comparison before.
Will Shen Ye say nifty words to entertain you?
He said you were good-looking and nice
with strong capability.
I didn't say such nifty words,
nor could I.
But are you really unable to see
how well I treat you?
You're really jealous.
I didn't know it's this late
or expect you to treat me like this.
So,
you became jealous and ran out there into the rain?
I was thinking about what to do,
but couldn't come up with a way.
Killing Shen Ye
might be a good idea.
However,
perhaps, you'll be sad about that.
Thank god you still cared about my feeling
and didn't kill him.
Though you made me sad,
how can I make you sad in return
as a man!
I can't believe you said you couldn't say nifty words.
Were these nifty words?
There should be a limit for your jealousy.
It's time to bring it under control.
I like you so much.
How could I like someone else?
Have a good rest tonight!
Is the quilt...
Now that you have no feeling to Shen Ye,
why did you say those words to him in the afternoon
and hug him?
Are you still jealous?
Eh...
I'm going to sleep now.
Do you want to know the consequence of pretending to sleep?
What happened between me and Shen Ye
was no more than an acting of play.
I didn't expect you to be so weak to take it.
Will you be jealous if I talk to someone
in the future?
Tolerance is a good code of conduct.
You should learn that!
You're still suspicious of me?
I knew you were jealous,
so I went out searching for you for a long time
and stopped it after that.
I was afraid that getting myself wet
would worry you more.
I knew you were wet from the rain.
So I prepared the coldness-dispel soup for you to take a bath.
But you still don't believe me.
Xiaobai,
it's my fault.
What happened to His Majesty?
Why is he incomparably attentive tonight?
What's wrong?
Don't you feel dizzy since you got wet in the rain?
Forget about that!
Why didn't you sleep?
I... I forgot that
I need to get up early in the morning to make sweet potato cakes.
I'm not hungry.
But...
according to the tradition,
a couple
must take purple sweet potato cakes
on the next morning of the consummation.
So, you want everybody to know
we just consummated yesterday.
No...
I didn't mean that.
I...
Don't stand
on ceremonies.
Sleep with me for a while.
There you go!
Come!
Have a try of the purple sweet potato pancakes I made.
You made them anyway.
Hush!
Chacha and the others haven't known it yet.
I made them in secret.
Soft, sweet and glutinous. It's just to the point!
You can even make such good purple sweet potato cakes.
You should say something else if you intend to praise me.
That's sort of demanding.
I'm not good at saying nifty words.
It's such a surprise that you attach great importance
to these customs and rituals
as you're generally playful and restless.
I wouldn't care if it was an ordinary day.
I just thought
this had to be done today.
I know the reason to some extent.
It's probably because
we're finally together.
Take it. I feel embarrassed.
The magic instrument is about to be finished.
I can't complete a magic instrument
as masterly as this with my power alone.
I beg Your Majesty to do it in person.
There seems to be some ink smell in the room.
Are you writing?
Is there?
It should be the sandalwood.
Come!
Sit here!
What shall we do in the afternoon?
Where do you want to go?
I want to go to the fair.