Eternal Love of Dream
Episode 7
Si Ming, silly you!
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I would rather knock her out to send her down
than leave her here
to be mistreated like this.
It's too late to say that.
Her Highness has decided to leave.
I can't tolerate it even if you can.
After all, he's the Emperor.
So what?
Can the Emperor mistreat anyone?
Now, she...
I've visited Immortal Hanshan.
Immortal Hanshan...
His Book of Fate records the fates of gods.
- Si Ming, you... - They're not meant to be.
However hard you force it,
you can't change Emperor Dong Hua's fate.
In fact, it has nothing to do with Emperor Dong Hua.
So we can only sit back
and watch Fengjiu suffer?
We can still help her on one thing.
That's a deal.
We'll get back at that Demon Lord for Fengjiu.
Lord, mind your words.
The less people know about it, the better.
It concerns Her Highness's reputation.
Your Excellency!
Your Excellency,
you haven't decided which gift
to take to the banquet in Tai Chen Palace tomorrow.
I've chosen one.
Is it OK?
Prepare another one.
Yes.
Your Excellency, whose name should I write?
Qingqiu.
From someone anonymous.
Yes.
Your Excellency, the Third Prince is here.
Tomorrow morning,
send these two celadon-glazed lotus candlesticks
to Tai Chen Palace.
Yes.
Be extra careful!
Watch out!
Si Ming.
No need to be so courteous
to welcome me.
Your Highness!
Your Highness, what brings you here
late at night?
Is Cheng Yu here?
No, she's not.
Really?
Yes.
Dare you swear to
the candlestick?
I swear if I lied,
I'll end up alone with no wife or child.
Fengjiu! Fengjiu!
Silly you!
Fengjiu,
listen to me.
There's no future.
I...
It won't end well.
Gods of the Sky Kingdom
are hypocritical and false-hearted.
No, Lord, that's not true.
Fengjiu, I'll have another drink with you.
Please!
Lord Cheng Yu, I didn't expect you to be so active.
I'm so flattered.
I'm at your disposal.
Let's...
Don't pull my collar!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Your Highness, your wedding dress is here.
Look, it's so beautiful!
Really? Let me have a look.
Your Highness,
I have something important to report.
What's up?
His Majesty has chosen Ji Heng,
the First Princess of the demons,
to be the Queen, and the marriage
will be held on an auspicious day.
What?
Let's go back to the Palace now!
Yes.
♪ Whisper love in dreams. ♪
♪ Everything I think is for my love. ♪
♪ In one moment, I forget about what confuses me. ♪
♪ Because I'm surrounded by love. ♪
♪ Until I get hurt after giving all I have, ♪
♪ I finally understand how cruel you are. ♪
♪ I'm just afraid the fate might not recognize lovers, ♪
♪ Setting hundreds of tests to keep them apart. ♪
♪ It's like falling leaves tapping on the gate. ♪
Even if I have to cut our connections,
I'll always remember
how you cared for me these days.
You saved me before.
I have nothing to pay you back.
These sweet potatoes are roasted by me.
I'll give them to you as your wedding gift.
I don't know
whether you can get them or not.
Will you think of me
when seeing them?
It's fine, anyway.
♪ Go far away in your shadow. ♪
♪ I'm free but I have nothing. ♪
♪ Let memories gather dust. ♪
♪ I can't see us be together forever. ♪
Your Majesty, you've done nothing wrong.
You don't know I'm Bai Fengjiu from Qingqiu.
You don't know I like you.
You don't know how hard
I've tried to win your love.
We're just not meant to be.
Your Majesty,
I failed to win your love,
but I've tried my best.
I won't fight for us anymore.
I give up.
Your Highness,
if anything goes wrong now,
how should Tai Chen Palace explain
to the guests when they come
to congratulate His Majesty tomorrow?
Explain?
You should worry about
how that demon princess should explain to me first.
Rather than watch her
take away my foster brother and humiliate me,
I might as well...
Your Highness.
Your Majesty, please.
As to Princess Ji Heng...
What banquet?
What Tai Chen Palace?
Dong Hua,
you idiot!
How can I take advantage of you?
I'm so pissed by Emperor Dong Hua!
His Majesty and Princess Ji Heng are made for each other.
You don't have to...
Nonsense!
He's just a conscienceless idiot!
His Majesty didn't refuse it himself.
Why should we?
Forget it.
It's useless talking to you.
What happened to you?
You tell me.
Damn it!
I forgot about my task.
Cheng Yu!
Let's go to the banquet together.
I've something to attend to.
Your Emperor is getting married.
You should go and congratulate him yourself.
I've got something more important.
What's more important than His Majesty's marriage?
However precious those furs are,
they're no match for you.
Gorgeous!
Really gorgeous!
You!
You gods are really arrogant.
You show no respect to us demons.
Demon Lord Nie, though you're extremely daring
to look down upon Qingqiu,
you're really a good judge of people.
God Zhe Yan, that doesn't sound like a compliment.
What's the point of humiliating me?
Humiliate?
Well,
do we need a reason
to humiliate a Demon Lord?
Fine.
I dare not provoke you.
Let's go to the Sky Kingdom
and let the Heavenly King rule.
Let the Heavenly King rule?
When tricking Fengjiu,
did you ask the Heavenly King to rule?
You tricked Fengjiu into giving you
the fur with your silver tongue.
We can't blame you for that.
So...
So if we grab the fur
with our own skills,
you can't blame us, either.
Well, cut the crap!
Let's fight!
Fengjiu has been out for so many days
without any message.
As her uncle,
how can you still read travel notes?
Father,
you've become more verbose in recent years.
Compared to what I've done in the early years,
the trouble she's caused now
is really nothing.
You!
When Bai Yi is back,
ask him to discipline his daughter well.
Also, as her uncle,
you should pay attention
to find her a good husband.
Her father is not worried.
As her grandfather, why do you have to worry?
You!
Listen to yourself!
Bai Qian has waited so long to get married.
Should we let Fengjiu make the same mistake?
Father, rest assured.
Well...
Li,
why are you here?
Grandpa, I went to Shili Peach Forest
and grabbed some good peach blossom branches.
Sister Fengjiu told me she had planted
peach trees from Shili Peach Forest in Qingqiu for many times,
but none of them grew.
If I can succeed in growing the peach trees,
Sister Fengjiu is sure to praise me
when she comes back and sees them.
I shouldn't have asked Bai Qian
to guide Fengjiu back then.
Following Bai Qian,
Fengjiu became so mischievous
that she often climbed trees to catch birds
and went into rivers to get fish.
Once, when her uncle was napping,
she actually plucked
all the feathers of Jingwei.
Sister Fengjiu is so awesome!
I made one mistake before.
I won't make it again.
Li,
if you follow those two mischievous troublemakers,
I can't imagine how naughty you'll become.
Where're you going?
The fourth generation of our Bai family
should be well-mannered.
Come with Grandpa!
Grandpa, what does this have to do with me?
I'm wronged! I'm wronged!
Let's go! Who wronged you?
How have I wronged you?
If I see you
do such a vicious thing again,
from heaven to earth,
wherever you go,
I'll make you pay.
I won't calculate the interests
for keeping the fur these days.
But dare you appear in front of Fengjiu again,
I'll destroy your entire clan.
Don't worry.
The fire will go out
when those furs are burnt down.
Hope you'll keep this in mind,
and do good deeds more often.
Si Ming,
today is the big day for Tai Chen Palace.
If they see me, I'm afraid I'll have to
endure many unnecessary and overelaborate formalities.
Can you send Fengjiu back to Peach Forest?
Your Highness, rest assured.
Lord.
I have to send Her Highness back to Qingqiu.
Can you go to Tai Chen Palace first
and receive the guests for me?
Don't worry.
Don't ever mention Emperor Dong Hua in front of her again.
Yes.
Come here.
It's been warm these days with gentle spring breezes,
and the Yi Shi San Heaven is bursting with happiness.
Your Majesty, I congratulate you
for tying the knot with Princess Ji Heng.
Right! Right!
Where is Si Ming?
What have you been up to lately?
Your Majesty, I've long heard that
you've got a spiritual fox by your side.
Rumor has it that it's clever and lovely,
and it can even read people's minds.
Ignorant and ill-informed as I am,
I'd really want to take this chance to see the spiritual fox.
Your Majesty, please grant my wish.
The little fox is mischievous.
It's now in confinement.
I'll show it to you
when it's more obedient.
Lord Cheng Yu,
recently, I've thought several ways
to make food with tea.
A moment, please.
Let's talk in private.
What're you doing? I haven't finished yet.
You're so audacious.
If His Majesty is not in a good mood today,
you're bound to be punished severely.
I just want to destroy his good mood.
Heartless as he is,
I just want to dampen his spirits.
What're you talking about?
In the vast universe,
who doesn't want to offer His Majesty gifts
to add joy to this happy occasion?
But you just...
Well,
I've also prepared your gift.
Remember, don't say it wrong.
Who asked you to do that?
Everyone wants to flatter him.
Not me!
Fine! Fine! Fine! I see.
You remain aloof from the world.
You...
What a meddler!
Lian Song,
when I endured hardships
in the mortal realm to become an immortal,
you really helped me a lot.
But I know,
this is just your way of tricking women.
in the future,
please don't mind my business.
But do you know
why you went to the mortal realm to endure hardships?
Sister Fengjiu!
Sister Fengjiu,
what happened to you?
Her Highness was injured in the Sky Kingdom.
Now she's short of magic power.
You must take good care of her.
I see.
Today, I have a lot of official business to attend to.
I can't stay here for long.
Just take her to God Zhe Yan.
Remember,
don't let elders of Qingqiu know about this.
OK.
Your Highness, you really don't want me
to cure the wounds on your neck first?
No need.
I want them to heal by themselves.
Your Highness, take care.
Sister Fengjiu, what happened?
I embarrassed myself.
I disgraced Qingqiu.
It's no big deal.
You've done plenty of things
to embarrass yourself since childhood.
Get up where you fall.
You were the one who told me that.
Jingwei,
you do keep my words in mind.
Your Highness!
You're back.
I heard someone grabbed your fur.
Who on earth hurt you?
A Demon Lord
or someone from the Yi Shi San Heaven?
It had nothing to do with him.
I was to blame for not being careful.
So you got hurt in the Yi Shi San Heaven.
Well,
I can't beat him,
but I can blow off the roof
of Tai Chen Palace.
Shall I give it a try?
It really had nothing to do with him!
He knew nothing.
He just doesn't like me.
He just treated me
as a disobedient pet
till the end.
Emperor Dong Hua
is not the lucky guy.
Stop crying.
If your uncle sees you like this,
how sad will he be?
If your aunt sees this,
she will tear down Tai Chen Palace
before I do.
Your families are very protective. You know that.
I disgraced Qingqiu.
I'm glad you know it.
You should gain your dignity back bit by bit.
How?
It's quiet easy.
Your Highness!
Leave me alone.
Don't come inside without my order.
Yes.
Finally, someone's here.
Xuan Demon Lord Nie Chuyin pays respects to Your Majesty.
You're the leader of Xuan Demon Clan.
You actually know me.
Your Majesty,
I didn't expect to see you here.
I put a drop of blood tear among demons.
Over tens of thousands of years,
no one actually dared to summon me.
What do you want?
Your Majesty, please tell me how to break the seal.
I want to serve you.
Really?
Yes.
Your Majesty, after you were sealed,
demons declined gradually.
Though I have low cultivation,
I do want to bring back our past glory.
I never believed
such high-sounding reasons.
Just tell me what you want.
Now that Demon Lord Xu Yang
is content with the current situation
and shows no interest in challenging the gods,
I'm afraid the grand cause of reviving our race will be delayed.
I want to...
Take his place.
Your Majesty, to be honest,
though I'm of limited cultivation,
I do want to exhaust my abilities to revive our race.
More importantly,
I want to do my bit
in setting you free.
Aren't you afraid to see the world in utter disorder?
In utter disorder?
That's better than being bullied and oppressed by the gods.
Good!
You're really a descendent of demons.
To help me break the seal,
you should bring me the soul-locking jade first.
The soul-locking jade?
After the War of Mount Fuyu,
it turned into dust
and went with the wind.
Mount Fuyu is located
at the border between the fairy land and the mortal realm.
Even if the dust fell into the mortal realm,
given the chaos and disorder caused by endless war,
it would surely absorb all the hostile energy
and form the soul-locking jade again.
Your Majesty, I'm willing to
risk any danger to serve you.
Come to me after finding the soul-locking jade.
Yes!
What a happy day!
Yes.
Wonderful!
What a happy occasion!
We haven't had such a big gathering for a long time.
Look, how magnificent!
Yes!
It's your big day. Can't you just smile?
How come it's you?!
Zhihe?
Go and invite the Heavenly King over.
Yes.
Yan Chiwu?
Where did you hide Ji Heng?
Foster brother.
Call me "Your Majesty".
Ji Heng...
Ji Heng disappeared last night.
I...
I've made a big mistake because I got confused temporarily.
Your Majesty, please show mercy!
Do you know you've committed the sin of deceiving me?
-Your Majesty! -Your Majesty! -Your Majesty!
What happened?
Ji Heng is missing.
Ji Heng doesn't deserve my foster brother!
Shut up!
Father, I failed to manage the wedding well.
Please punish me.
Zhihe deceived Emperor Dong Hua
and Lian Song failed to fulfill his duty.
The wedding shall be canceled today.
Guards!
Yes!
Put them into prison.
After figuring out the truth,
I'll definitely give Emperor Dong Hua an explanation.
Yes!
Ji Heng!
Princess!
How dare you!
Ji Heng, what are you doing?
Yu Ru!
Guards! Guards...
Yu Ru! Yu Ru!
As the future wife of my foster brother,
how dare you...
So don't tell anyone else.
As the future wife of Emperor Dong Hua,
I made such a big mistake.
How should Tai Chen Palace and the demons...
So, Princess Zhihe,
why not let me leave quietly tomorrow.
Without the bride,
there will be no wedding tomorrow for sure.
in the future, His Majesty will still be that dignified
and aloof Emperor high above.
Is that OK?
Foster brother's wedding ceremony,
can not become a joke.
You don't want the wedding dressing.
I want it.
It must be a conspiracy of the demons.
Now that Ji Heng is missing,
Demon Lord Xu Yang will surely
take the chance to attack us.
In my opinion, we should declare war against the demons first.
-Right! -Declare war! -Declare war!
Declare war against the demons!
We absolutely can't!
If we fight the demons, all the living creatures will suffer.
In my opinion,
we should find Ji Heng first.
After figuring out the truth,
we can still declare war against the demons.
It's a waste of time looking for her.
Right! Right!
You!
Everyone, don't act rashly
to make the world suffer.
Right, we can't act rashly!
The Heavenly King is here.
Your Majesty!
Xu Yang pays respects to Your Majesty.
Xu Yang, you've come at the right time.
I have something to discuss with you.
Me, too.
I need an explanation for the whole thing.
Bring him here.
Yes!
Old Heavenly King,
release me if you dare.
How despicable of you to fight me when I was outnumbered.
Yan Chiwu!
Xu Yang?
Look at me! Why are you still talking to them?
What're you waiting for?
Don't be rude!
Your Majesty,
Ji Heng ran away from the wedding first.
Then Yan Chiwu tried to snatch the bride in public.
As to this marriage,
the demons were so impudent that
they should be punished severely.
Cut the crap!
Give Ji Heng back to us!
Otherwise, I'll beat the crap out of you!
How dare you?!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, it concerns the two races this time.
It's better to decide after figuring out the truth.
Fine.
Ice Face,
don't think I'll thank you...
For releasing me.
Let's go.
Your Majesty,
is it appropriate to do so?
It's a private matter. I'll handle it.
Your Majesty, do not be bothered.
You shouldn't have stopped me.
I haven't finished yet.
Ji Heng must have been hidden by that Ice Face.
Good for him.
He actually blames us instead.
In my opinion, no need to talk with them.
We should've fought them directly.
Look at you!
You're a Demon Lord after all!
Coward!
Shame!
Yan Chiwu,
how dared you snatch the bride?
You almost got us in trouble.
It's a waste of time
talking to a mindless demon as you are.
Trouble! Trouble!
That's all you know.
You even dared not defend your own sister.
Coward!
I don't want to talk to you because I despise you!
Pooh!
Say that again!
Yan Chiwu!
Pooh! Pooh! Pooh!
Your Highness.
What's up?
According to reports from guards,
Min Su is also missing.
This is odd.
Have they planned to escape in advance?
Your Highness, don't worry.
Demon Lord Xuan was afraid that
Min Su might try to ruin Princess's wedding,
so he specially asked me
to put soul-tracking fragrance on Min Su.
He'll expose himself sooner or later.
Send more guards to search for them at once.
Yes.
Chong Lin pays respects to Your Majesty.
What's up?
His Highness Lian Song urged me repeatedly
before being sent to prison
to send you a message with his exact words.
Go ahead.
Dong Hua, thanks to you,
now I have to be in prison.
Actually, it's fine to be in prison.
I can be graceful and charming
even I'm in prison.
It's just that you actually didn't involve me
in the marriage escaping plan.
I've really wasted my trust on you.
That's almost all.
Chong Lin.
Yes, Your Majesty.
It seems that Lian Song is punishing you.
Go and finish your task.
She can only rely on herself in the future.
Yes.
Take care.
Your Highness.
Without the help of His Majesty,
I might not be able to see you again.
This time, the Qiushui Cold Toxin
can be suppressed much longer.
Follow the plan.
Set aside your worries and rest well
after reaching the Fanyin Valley.
Your Majesty,
thank you for suppressing the Qiushui Cold Toxin for me repeatedly
with your cultivation.
I'm deeply grateful.
Your Highness,
I have to tell you something.
No hurry. There's ample time ahead.
It's late. Let's leave now.
Your Majesty, how are you?
After getting injured
in the Ten-evil Lotus Land,
you were not fully recovered.
These days, you've used lots of cultivation
to help Princess Ji Heng
suppress the Qiushui Cold Toxin repeatedly.
Why not leave everything behind for the moment
and take a rest to recuperate?
I'm fine.
But I didn't expect
Zhihe to be
so obsessed.
How's she doing?
Princess Zhihe remained silent after being sent to prison.
She has to undo the knot
on her own.
Your Highness, has His Majesty
found the cure for the Qiushui Cold Toxin?
Not yet.
But this time,
His Majesty used lots of cultivation
to suppress the poison.
And he specially chose
the Fanyin Valley for me.
He said it's clean and pure inside the valley,
which is good for my rest.
His Majesty is really kind and righteous.
Yes.
Indifferent as His Majesty is,
I didn't expect him to value his former subordinate so much.
This time, for a promise to my father,
he did his best to help us escape.
I don't know
when I can
repay his kindness.
However, Your Highness told me
His Majesty is not the one you love.
Otherwise...
Why do you bring it up again?
I'll repay His Majesty's kindness some other day.
Now, the most important thing for us  is
to run away from this place.
It's late. Let's go now!