Eternal Love of Dream
Episode 56
You created the starlight ward
at the risk of losing your own life.
Dong Hua,
don't you have any compassion for me?
My compassion for you was the reason you escaped last time.
This time,
I will show you no mercy.
Today,
I will give you the satisfaction.
Great.
If you seal me in the starlight ward,
none of us is getting out.
You will go to hell with me.
Right.
Ice face can fight.
You took half of your heart out to make this ring for me.
His Majesty can't just die like that.
Chong Lin.
I want to see him.
Look. The stars are falling down.
I'm afraid it's too late.
No, it's not.
We're not destined to be together.
But that doesn't mean
we can't die together.
His Majesty's got to be fighting Miao Luo
somewhere.
Do you know
where they are now?
The stars are falling down to the Fanyin Valley.
So His Majesty's probably there.
You may get to see him alive
if you rush over now.
Your Majesty.
Dong Hua.
Are you really going to die with me here?
I've made myself clear about
why I'm here.
Don't ask me over and over again.
You are indeed fearless.
If my death is a price to pay
for the peace of the Eight Deserts and Six Directions,
it's worth it.
I didn't know you could be so ruthless with yourself.
I'm not ruthless.
It's you who has this overwhelming obsession.
Obsession?
I, the demon king, have no obsession.
Don't forget that
you were the one who made me a demon.
Chong Lin.
Are you alright?
The dark energy is too strong.
Even starlight ward
can't cleanse it.
Looks like His Majesty is determined to
fight Miao Luo on his own.
Lian Song.
Do something about it!
No one can enter the ward,
except His Majesty.
Yan.
Yan Chiwu?
Why are you all wearing a sad expression?
It's true that we can't enter the starlight ward.
But ice face will come out eventually
when he defeats Miao Luo, right?
The stars are falling down already.
Don't you see it?
That means an immortal is dying.
You mean...
Ice face...
He's not getting out?
Your Majesty.
- Your Highness. - Your Highness.
Fengjiu.
What are you doing, Ye Qingti?
I know you want to break in and help His Majesty.
But I can't just watch you die.
Let go of me.
Your Highness.
I'd rather be hated by you
than let you die for nothing.
Qingti.
Only the one who created the ward
is allowed to enter.
Others won't be able to get in.
Let go of me!
I don't know much about things in the immortal realm.
How could I know if you're lying or not?
Qingti.
His Majesty's life is at stake.
I won't do stupid things.
I just want to take a close look at him.
Let me go.
The stars are falling down nonstop.
Is any god dying?
Something's up.
What's going on?
Follow me.
Let me go!
Xiaojiu.
- Fengjiu. - Your Highness.
Fengjiu.
Your Highness.
Xiaojiu.
How did she get into the starlight ward?
It's because of the colored glaze ring.
That's half of His Majesty's heart.
With half of His Majesty's heart,
of course Fengjiu could get in easily.
I don't know if Her Highness is His Majesty's misfortune
or the other way around any more.
Xiaobai.
How could this happen?
Blood from nine-tailed fox's heart can cleanse evil spirit.
Her cultivation has been weakened
after she was stained by my blood.
Dong Hua.
Even now,
you are still protecting the fox.
I want you to lose the love of your life forever
and experience the heartbreaking pain.
Xiaobai.
Stop the bleeding from your wound
and wait for me under the Lingshu Stage.
I will take you home soon.
You are lying again.
Look.
Blood from nine-tailed fox's heart can cleanse evil spirit.
But I couldn't have cleansed Miao Luo's evil spirit
so fast.
If you hadn't fed me with your golden blood
in the Dream of Aranya,
I couldn't have done that.
After you lied to me for so many times
and I got you wrong for so many times,
we are still together now.
Aren't we destined for each other?
Your Majesty.
Don't push me away every time.
You think you can kill me by doing that?
You still don't get it, do you?
You can't kill me by doing that!
What's wrong?
Do they win or lose?
There seems to be nothing going on.
Should we just wait it out?
Xiaojiu, wait for me.
I bet
I will break the ward
and get you out.
No.
The starlight ward is set for
eliminating all evil spirits.
If you break in while evil spirits are not eliminated,
everything in there will be destroyed.
Dark energy is so strong now.
Ice face has to fight against Miao Luo
while injured heavily.
He and Xiaojiu don't seem to have energy
for removing the dark energy.
What's wrong with me?
No.
Dong Hua, don't.
Don't make me disappear.
Dong Hua.
Seal me!
No, Dong Hua!
Dong Hua!
You are all immortals.
Can either one of you do something about it?
There's one way
that may work.
What is it?
When the ward is being broken,
if there's a strong force supporting from the outside,
the people inside may be saved.
You mean
we gather all our powers
to force the ward open
and then we let the ward destroy all dark energy
after we rescue them out?
No one has ever tried
this way before.
I don't know how it will turn out.
The condition is critical now.
As long as we can save ice face and Xiaojiu,
it's worth trying.
Third Prince, what do you think?
We don't seem
to have another choice.
Okay.
Everyone.
We will work together
to open the ward.
When the ward is open slightly,
God Zhe Yan,
you and I,
the longest living immortals here
should get in
and rescue them.
That's for the best.
Others will stay here
to keep the dark energy.
Let's get ready.
It must hurt a lot.
Xiaobai.
No.
I've worked so hard to finally see you.
It doesn't hurt at all.
You shouldn't be here.
You made starlight ward
to smash Miao Luo
and the Miaoyi Chasm, along with yourself.
Although I'm not so smart,
I've loved you for so long.
I know what you're thinking.
Tell me.
How can I get you out?
Why do you want to get me out?
Because I broke your heart?
But you broke my heart, too.
Let's call it even,
okay?
I want to be by your side.
You want me to keep you company, right?
Yeah, you're right.
I did want you to come.
I've always wanted to take you along wherever I go.
Even when I'm going to die,
I don't want to part with you.
But I can't do that, Xiaobai.
You have a long way to go.
You don't want to take me along.
But I'm afraid I'll have to go before you.
Dong Hua.
It hurts.
Say something nice to me.
Cheer me up.
What do you want to hear?
Tell me that you like me.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Promise me that
you will hold my hands
when I'm about to die.
Wherever you go,
I want to be with you.
Dong Hua.
Hold my hands and don't let go.
Okay.
♪ Whisper love in dreams. ♪
♪ Everything I think about is for my lover. ♪
♪ In one moment, I forget about what confuses me. ♪
♪ Because I'm surrounded by love. ♪
♪ Until I get hurt after giving all I have, ♪
♪ I finally understand how cruel you are. ♪
♪ I'm just afraid the fate might not recognize lovers, ♪
♪ Setting hundreds of tests to keep them apart. ♪
♪ It's like falling leaves tapping on the gate. ♪
♪ I used to be a fool who followed you all the time. ♪
♪ The transient affection ♪
♪ only gets deeper for trouble. ♪
♪ If we become strangers
only to recognize each other again, ♪
♪ will you remember our past? ♪
♪ I am willing to die if you trust me. ♪
♪ I don't care to be lonely. ♪
♪ I can't decide whether to leave or to stay. ♪
♪ The vast universe changes nonstop. ♪
♪ Never have you stopped fighting for our love. ♪
♪ Go far away in your shadow. ♪
♪ I'm free but I have nothing. ♪
Dong Hua.
Open your eyes!
Please stay awake.
Open your eyes, Dong Hua.
I will hate you if you close your eyes.
Dong Hua.
♪ It's like falling leaves tapping on the gate. ♪
♪ I used to be a fool  ♪
Dong Hua.
♪ who followed you all the time. ♪
♪ The transient affection ♪
♪ only gets deeper for hatred. ♪
Thank you.
Don't talk.
From now on, you will listen to me, okay?
♪ I'd rather wake up from
my sweetest dream to keep you safe, ♪
Just forget me.
Dong Hua.
♪ I can't decide whether to leave or to stay. ♪
It's in my nature to love you.
How can I forget you?
Dong Hua.
♪ Never have you stopped fighting for our love. ♪
Come on. Open your eyes.
Dong Hua.
Open your eyes.
♪ I can't see us be together forever. ♪
Dong Hua. Dong Hua.
Dong Hua.
♪ Hide the hopeless dream in the bedside sleeve. ♪
♪ That's my craving for all my life. ♪
♪ I said I love you, and I'll honor that promise forever. ♪
Dong Hua.
♪ How could I get close to you
if your mind settles as still water? ♪
Dong Hua.
♪ If I was in your eyes, ♪
♪ remember not to let tears take me away. ♪
♪ It turns out that the love is so torturous. ♪
Qingqiu will let go of hatred
and accept inseparable king birds.
We really appreciate it.
We are following what the gods do.
To move on
and be friends with the demons.
This way.
It's me.
I'm here to bring you home.
Yan.
Don't talk.
I'm afraid if you start talking,
I'll lose the courage to
speak out these words.
I used to think that to love someone
is to give
and to become the person they like.
Even if it means turning myself into someone else,
my love for him is all that matters.
Even if it's like a moth to a flame,
it's the best kind of love.
I didn't realize
until I lost you that
the best kind of love
is that I can remove all my camouflage
and be who I am.
I can be a kid if I want to.
I can cry and laugh in front of him
without pretending.
I can act like a spoiled child if I want to.
I can get into a huff
if I want to.
Whenever I feel upset,
he will stretch out his arms for me
to lean on.
I didn't know that the best kind of love
has always been around me.
I didn't even know.
Yan, I'm sorry.
It took me so long to finally
realize how important you are to me.
The sweetest word in the world
is nothing poetic.
It's that I don't want to part with you
as long as you're by my side.
I want to be with you for the rest of my life, Yan.
Yan.
From now on,
I want to be the one who loves you.
What's wrong?
Why are you not talking?
Don't you like me now?
I...
No, no, no. I...
It's not like that. I...
Ji Heng.
Of course I like you.
Loving you is the most important thing in my life.
I... I...
Jeez, you finally see me.
I'm... I'm more than happy.
I...
I finally did it!
You are finally in love with me!
Ji Heng.
Look at you.
You're not going to regret it, right?
I think... maybe...
maybe...
we should
go to the bedroom now.
Let go of me. Let go of me.
What are you talking about?
I'm not going to the bedroom with you.
I'm kidding, girl.
Ji Heng.
I'm here with you.
From now on,
we will never part with each other.
You're working in Tai Chen Palace.
Have you noticed any beautiful new fairy maids
recently?
Good one.
You're getting to resemble Dong Hua.
Third Prince.
Demon Lord Yan, you're here again.
I'm passing by.
Third Prince, you're losing this one.
I was distracted.
So I made the wrong move.
Come on, Qingti.
Let's play one more round.
I have to go back to the Tai Chen Palace for my duty.
Sorry.
I'll get going.
I'll play it with you.
I thought you hate playing the game of go.
It's true.
But I haven't seen you for a while.
I miss you more than
I hate to play chess.
The starlight ward has already been broken.
And you've been stopping by Bihai Cangling
for the past three months.
You have nothing better to do in the demons, do you?
I lost my way, okay?
God Zhe Yan, you're right.
Fox clan of Qingqiu
is a treasure waiting to be dug up.
No one would have expected it, right?
As blood from nine-tailed fox's heart
and His Majesty's golden blood cleansed the dark energy,
the starlight ward was broken automatically.
With that,
Bihai Cangling was saved.
All have survived safe and sound.
Except Fengjiu.
I'm really worried about her.
She's still in a coma
with her spirit hurt.
Lord,
I'm not a quack.
Even if I was one,
Fengjiu would be blessed enough to be fine.
They all say she and His Majesty are not meant to be.
But what I think is that
Fengjiu and Dong Hua are a destined couple.
They're one in a million.
That's right.
They shouldn't have listened to the Fate Stone.
All they did was in vain.
They're supposed to be together.
The Fate Stone was so absurd.
If it were me,
I would be mad enough
to crack it open.
Third Prince, you've really got some balls.
Well, yeah.
Who was the one being so sacrificial
and dragging God Zhe Yan
into entering the ward
that day?
Fengjiu was obviously more useful.
The one and only nine-tailed red fox in the universe
should be so powerful!
She's indeed my friend.
Idiot.
Hey, mind your tongue.
Who's the kid?
You can tell that.
from his hair color,
He's Dong Hua's child?
What is Dong Hua?
Is it a place?
I'm my mother's son.
Uncle Xie Guchou, where's my mother?
Your mother is hurt.
But she will wake up after a few months of rest.
She used to compliment you a lot.
That you are calm and responsible for your age.
Let me see
if you're really responsible.
Go in there.
The smell of medicine is so strong.
Mother.
Mother. Mother.
Who are you?
I'm Bai Gungun.
Who's
Bai Gungun?
My mother's son.
Is it so surprising
for you?
You even dropped the bowl.
Uncle, you're so good-looking.
Who are you?
Gungun.
I'm your father.
Mother, father, you are kissing again.
I want a kiss, too.
The journey of life is so long.
Fate can't decide my life.
I, Bai Fengjiu, will bring Emperor Dong Hua
into my life no matter what.
Because
I love you the most.
For the three eternities,
you little fox
are bound to be mine.
In every eternity,
Dong Hua belongs to Fengjiu.
Both of you are mine.