Eternal Love of Dream
Episode 50
You're awake?
Who are you?
You don't remember me?
Do you know who you are?
I'm Bai Fengjiu from Qingqiu.
So,
you just forget about me.
Take a good look at me. Who am I?
Are you a little fox from Qingqiu?
Are you my classmate?
Or,
did you have a blind date with me?
It seems that
you've really lost your memories.
What a pity!
For what?
I originally planned to go to Qingqiu
with you to meet your family
and discuss how to hold our delayed wedding banquet
to make you my Empress.
Now that you've lost your memories,
it has to be postponed indefinitely.
What?
Will you marry me?
I didn't expect that
you had forgotten it all.
Wait!
Where are you going?
I'm going to find Lian Song
and ask him to send you back to Qingqiu.
Then, won't you marry me?
Now that you don't remember me,
I have to let it go.
Actually...
Actually, I kind of recall something.
In the Dream of Aranya,
we were a couple, right?
I was Aranya, and you were Xi Ze.
What happened in the Dream of Aranya doesn't count.
Since you can't remember me,
don't force yourself.
I kind of recall it.
What do you recall?
You seem to be Emperor Dong Hua.
Seem?
You are Emperor Dong Hua!
I'm Bai Fengjiu from Qingqiu.
I'm your girl, Xiaobai.
Ouch!
I dare not trick you next time.
Next time?
No. Never.
What you just said,
does it still count?
What did I say?
You said you would marry me.
Take a bath in hot spring first to recover from fatigue.
We're leaving the valley.
I'll have Chong Lin get everything ready.
After we get out,
I'll marry you.
OK.
Aren't you coming?
We haven't got married yet.
I didn't mean that.
The royal family of the inseparable king birds
and the royal family of the night owls
would like to guard the valley.
Your Majesty, please approve.
Do you know
what will happen to you
if the Miaoyi Chasm is broken?
Your Majesty,
having sealed Miao Luo for tens of thousands of years,
the Miaoyi Chasm has been filled with her dark energy.
If Miao Luo breaks out of the seal this time,
the entire Fanyin Valley
will be filled with dark energy.
By then, all the living things
will surely be plunged into an abyss of misery.
Wherever the dark energy reaches,
it will become barren
and lifeless.
Are you all clear?
Your Majesty, please approve.
We're willing to perish with the Fanyin Valley.
Your Majesty,
though we're not so competent as gods from the Sky Kingdom,
we're honored as royals by our clans
and have enjoyed high positions and great wealth.
If we don't stay now, we'll be too ashamed
to see our people in future.
Exactly!
Though the gods from the Sky Kingdom have great magic power,
their magic power will be removed after entering the valley.
Also, the magic tricks they learned
are not as pure as those learned in the valley.
In the Fanyin Valley,
it's nice to have some help.
I've arranged for the clansmen
to evacuate from the valley.
The gods from the Sky Kingdom are also ready for assistance.
We're willing to guard the valley.
Your Majesty, please approve!
Then please join me
in guarding the Miaoyi Chasm.
Thank you, Your Majesty!
This is the Lianxin Mirror
specifically used for purifying the dark energy.
It can help you confine Miao Luo.
Thank you, Your Majesty!
Elder brother!
Jielu,
why are you here?
Why do you all stay
but me?
I also want to stay and guard the valley with you.
I'm also a royal.
You're still a kid!
I go to school with you now.
You can all stay.
Why can't I?
Jielu,
if we all stay here,
who can our people rely on?
For this trip to the Sky Kingdom,
they need someone to make decisions
and lead them.
Do you want our people to seek living
in the Sky Kingdom on their own?
Can you leave instead?
Elder brother,
you're the future king of the inseparable king birds.
You should take our people to the Sky Kingdom,
and I'll stay here instead.
Silly girl,
you're the only daughter of uncle and aunt.
I promised them
to take good care of you
and keep you safe and sound.
Then,
you'll all be back, right?
Well,
we're preparing for the worst.
But with His Majesty on our side,
we won't end up like that.
But I can't!
Elder brother,
I can't do it on my own!
You like Her Highness Fengjiu so much.
Are you willing to never see her again?
I have no one to care about outside the valley.
I grew up here as a child.
Just let me stay.
I...
I do like Her Highness Fengjiu.
I'll miss her in my heart.
But I'm also the prince of the inseparable king birds.
It's my inescapable duty to guard the valley.
I won't leave,
and I can't leave.
Jielu,
we decided together that
you should leave with our people.
Mother,
uncle, aunt,
and me.
Why?
Jielu,
though you've never experienced the outside world,
you've always been our hope.
If one day,
we are really at the critical juncture of life and death,
as long as we know
we've still got you to lead our people,
we can feel relieved
and spare no efforts in dealing with the situation.
Elder brother!
Mother asked me to send you a message.
Let the tragedy of the Fanyin Valley
stay in the Fanyin Valley.
She said you would understand it.
But why do you have to stay?
You haven't fulfilled your wish yet!
Mother is old.
They need me.
Moreover,
Jielu,
do you really have no one to care about?
Who are you thinking of right now?
Elder brother,
you're making fun of me.
I still expect you to grow up and get married.
Don't panic.
It's just a temporary separation.
Then
you must all be safe and sound!
I will guard this place well
and wait for you to return.
Magnificent and unhurried,
yet filled with deep emotions.
Terrific!
I was playing randomly.
Sorry for my poor skills.
You helped Xiaobai and me
out of righteousness this time.
I haven't thanked you yet.
I'm so flattered.
Your Majesty, it's the honor of a lifetime
to be able to serve you.
Also, you know that
I have my selfish motive.
That's hardly a selfish motive.
You just want to know the truth.
Right.
For all these years,
I just couldn't get over Aranya's death.
After entering the dream world this time,
I finally
have taken a load off my mind.
Such a result
may not be the one you wanted.
To me,
I certainly don't want to see that
Aranya was deeply in love with Shen Ye.
Nor do I want to believe that
Shen Ye was also deeply in love with Aranya.
But after brooding it over here for days,
I've gradually realized that
such a result,
the truth,
was actually better than I speculated.
I feel relieved for Aranya.
She didn't love
the wrong guy after all.
It's rare to think like that.
Something strange has happened inside the valley.
His Highness Lian Song didn't tell me the details,
but I can guess a thing or two.
Your Majesty,
anything you ask,
the people of West Sea will surely help you.
It's too early to ask for help.
I know how to deal with it.
Jiuge,
this is a letter from Yan to you.
Yan?
When did he become so genteel?
See you.
Xiaojiu, I'm so glad that you're back!
Can you drink wine or eat meat now?
If you can,
meet us in private in the Zuilixian Restaurant right away.
Meng wants to give you a farewell dinner in private.
Since you fell into the Dream of Aranya,
the inseparable king birds
have known that we lied about who we were.
But due to the ice face and Lian Song,
they dared not inquire about our true identities.
Meng asked me in private several times.
Given that he's a friend,
I told him who I was honestly.
Though I said nothing about your identity,
he mistakenly thought that you were also a demon.
Yan was quite smart this time.
He actually remembered to hide my identity.
Actually,
whom Meng loves is the legendary Fengjiu.
It's not you.
We're friends.
Even if he knows who you are,
he stands no chance against the ice face.
Whether to keep hiding your identity
or to tell him who you are,
it's up to you.
It seems that back with four seasons,
the Fanyin Valley is picturesque.
It's really a reclusive land of peace and happiness.
The Fanyin Valley was originally built outside the mortal realm.
Back then, I chose this place
to suppress the Miaoyi Chasm
and neutralize the dark energy in the world.
It costs more than half of your cultivation
to suppress the Miaoyi Chasm once.
To completely purify it,
I'm afraid you'll have to use all of your cultivation
and end up falling into a deep slumber
for tens of thousands of years.
Moreover, Miao Luo also needs to be handled.
Now we can only stabilize the Miaoyi Chasm
to confine Miao Luo.
After figuring out the way
to get rid of Miao Luo once and for all,
we can make further plans.
Though you're the most powerful
in the Four Seas and Eight Deserts,
there're still several powerful gods
in the Sky Kingdom.
You shouldn't be the only one to carry the burden.
Moreover, now that heaven and earth have settled
and the conflicts within the demons
have been eased due to the whole thing concerning Miao Luo,
you should go back to rest and recuperate in Tai Chen Palace.
A wedding will be held in Tai Chen Palace.
You're going to have an Empress?
I promised to marry her after getting out of the valley.
You're actually the last to taste love,
but you're going to get married before me.
Well,
now that your marriage is settled,
you can set your mind at rest.
Well,
as to the pimpon fruit you gave me,
I've given it to Lord Xie.
Feel relieved.
Yan,
why did you waste magic power
to come to the Fanyin Valley?
I thought you wouldn't come back after leaving in a hurry.
I'm here to pick up Ji Heng.
The musician.
Right,
you've liked her all the time.
His Majesty really loves Xiaojiu?
Dignified and majestic as His Majesty is,
he actually ordered to hide the truth
from her for her sake.
Unbelievable!
He's just too naïve!
You can both be with your lovers.
Lucky you!
I wonder whether I can see Her Highness Fengjiu again
the rest of my life.
Her Highness Fengjiu doesn't even know I like her.
Meng,
in your mind,
what is Fengjiu like?
A first-class noble lady as she is,
she must be pure and kind.
She likes animals
and never touches mundane things such as wine and meat.
Moreover...
Who is he talking about?
So strange!
Another dancing girl?
I think...
He's talking about Her Highness Fengjiu
from Qingqiu in his imagination.
...she likes animals and insects.
She won't even
kill a fly.
Meng,
has it ever occurred to you that
if Fengjiu is not the person you've imagined her to be,
will you still like her?
What do you mean?
If Fengjiu is the same as her,
will you still like her?
How is that possible?
If Her Highness Fengjiu is the same as her,
I might as well knock into a piece of bean curd and kill myself.
I am Bai Fengjiu from Qingqiu.
I gave you the Ever-victorious General as a gift.
I also gave you the colored glaze jar.
When I saved you,
I didn't tell you who I was.
And I've kept it from you for so long.
Meng, I'm really sorry.
You're really Her Highness Fengjiu?
Yes, I am.
Her Highness Fengjiu who doesn't touch wine or meat
and who loves insects and animals?
Meng,
you might have misunderstood me.
Actually,
I...
What did you just drink?
Wine.
What did you eat?
Rabbit meat.
What's nailed on that bamboo chopstick?
A fly.
Meng!
Second Prince!
What's wrong with him?
Well,
the dream he's had for several decades was just shattered.
He passed out because he couldn't bear it.
Second Prince!
Women!
I'll never believe women!
The woman I worship the most turns out to be no difference.
Which woman can I count on around the world?
What happened to him?
Given the way he behaves,
will he do anything silly?
I didn't expect to drive him mad.
Shall I follow him?
What if he takes it too hard?
Just leave him alone.
If you comfort him,
I'm afraid he won't just have a broken heart.
It's good for him to cry.
He might come round after crying.
In my opinion,
you shouldn't follow him.
For his safety,
we'd better go and check him out.
When did they become so close?
Only they think the meat here is delicious.
It's tasteless actually.
I'll cook something delicious for you when we're back.
OK.
Actually, the refreshing soup is my signature dish.
When we're back in Tai Chen Palace,
I'll make it for you to build up your health.
Good.
We're about to leave here.
I actually feel a bit sad.
Before we go,
I'll take you somewhere else.
I didn't expect that you gods
would care about people living under the Sky Kingdom.
Xiangli Meng is affectionate and loyal to friends.
You've tricked him for so long.
He waited outside the Dream of Aranya on his own,
ready to sacrifice his life
to save His Majesty and Fengjiu at any time.
Nor did he blame you for not telling him you're a demon,
and he still remains to be your friend.
Xiaojiu is to blame for breaking his heart.
Meng
is pure and honest.
I'm afraid he may seem fine,
but he would actually hide somewhere to cry secretly.
Meng!
Silly you. Are you too sad?
There's sand
in my eyes.
I fell accidentally.
Are you really sad?
Do you really like Xiaojiu?
She takes you as a sincere friend.
Her friendship for you is real.
But the woman you love
is a completely different person imagined by you
who meets all your requirements,
but that woman is not her.
Exactly.
After all these troublesome matters are handled,
I'll take you outside the valley
to have a good trip around the Four Seas and Eight Deserts
and the mortal realm.
Then you can find a real girl to love.
OK?
Actually, I'm not sad.
I just...
I just feel embarrassed
after calming down.
Embarrassed?
You mean you passed out after she told you the truth?
I was always wondering
if I met Her Highness Fengjiu,
what I should tell her first,
and how I should express my love to her.
I was so embarrassed just now.
A long-time friend suddenly became
the woman I loved for so long.
Also, I told her
I loved her many times shamelessly,
but I couldn't even recognize her.
How embarrassed I was!
I even made you worry.
I'm so sorry.
Then just tell her you love her.
Since you feel regretful in your heart,
you should let her know how much you love her.
Whom she loves is her own business,
but no one in the entire world
can stop you from loving her.
But
she and His Majesty love each other.
Why should I bring contempt upon myself
and add trouble to her.
She and the ice face love each other. That's their own business.
What does it have to do with you?
Cheng Yu calls me shameless all the time.
I should ask her over to see
there's actually someone
more shameless than I am.
Don't interrupt!
Meng,
you're smarter than I am.
You should consider it yourself.
Who sets the rule that in the world,
only mutual love is allowed to exist
while unrequited love is inferior to that?
If you love someone who can't love you back,
isn't it also love?
You love her openly and sincerely.
You never force her to respond to your love.
If you want to let her know you love her, just go and tell her.
If you don't, just keep it in your heart the rest of your life.
Anyway, I'm your friend.
Whatever you want to do,
as long as Xiaojiu won't get hurt,
I will always support you.
Does it make any sense?
I...
I want to express my love to Her Highness Fengjiu.
I haven't told Her Highness Fengjiu
I love her in the right way.
Then just go.
Let her know how much you love her.
I support you.
After you tell her, if you need,
I can drink with you.
Let's get drunk!
I'll go with you.
They're over there.
We can only accompany you here.
The rest is up to you.
Yan! Your Highness!
Thank you!
Every time I look at Meng,
I find myself extremely vicious and wicked.
Indeed you are.
But compared to him, we both are.
Where are you taking me?
Your Highness Fengjiu!
Your Highness!
Your Majesty, I want to
talk with Her Highness Fengjiu in private.
Fine.
Your Highness,
I was so rude just now because I was drunk.
Please forgive me.
Meng,
in my heart, you've always been a good friend.
Though I didn't tell you the truth,
you don't have to be so polite.
So are we still good friends?
Of course!
Jiuge is a good friend to you,
and you're also a good friend to Jiuge.
In future, just treat me
as Jiuge.
Because that's the real me.
Actually, I'm very happy that
I can...
I can
let the woman I love know that
I love her.
Your Highness,
I've got
no regrets.
How come you've got no regrets?
Only when the woman you love loves you back
can you say that you've got no regrets.
In the future, you're bound to meet someone
who truly loves you.
By then, you must spare no efforts.
Just learn from Yan
and make her love you
as deeply as you love her.
Do you understand?
Yes!
Shall we leave and give them some space?
It's an once-in-a-lifetime opportunity for fun.
Someone is actually trying to win over Emperor Dong Hua's woman.
How I wish I could watch closer!
Why should I leave?
I knew it! No one from the Sky Kingdom is good.
You should leave actually.
By watching them,
I can step in if anything unpleasant happens.
Why do you look at me like that?
You just want to watch the drama, right?
You're too straight-forward.
I guessed right, didn't I? Asshole from the Sky Kingdom.
The one you called asshole
actually taught you how to play the game of go
and how to win Princess Ji Heng's heart.
Is this how you treat your master?
What master?
I hate playing the game of go the most.
You're burning the bridge after crossing the river, right?
I...
So fast?
Have you told her?
Yes.
What did Xiaojiu say?
She said we were still good friends,
and she asked me to learn more from you.
Learn from
me?
Learn from your shamelessness for sure!
She also said that
next time I loved someone,
I should make her love me
as deeply as I love her.
Then you should live up to her blessing.
Actually, I knew it from the start.
When I first met Her Highness Fengjiu,
I knew she would never love me.
She was so gorgeous,
special, charming,
and distinguished.
I knew it all.
Even if I were not from the Fanyin Valley,
even if I were from the Four Seas and Eight Deserts,
I would still be the most unimpressive one
among tens of thousands of people
pursuing Her Highness Fengjiu.
You both said that
the woman I loved was an imaginary figure,
not the real Fengjiu,
but Yan,
do you know?
I always wanted to leave the Fanyin Valley
not because I felt lonely in the Fanyin Valley
for it was winter all the year round,
but that
I met Her Highness Fengjiu.
I wanted to see her again.
Even if we couldn't talk,
it's fine.
I started longing for the outside world
after meeting Her Highness Fengjiu.
To get closer to her,
I collected all the information about her,
even the fake one.
As long as the information was about her,
I just couldn't let it go.
I knew the unrequited love wouldn't work,
but I just couldn't give up.
It's not because
I'm silly,
but that
she's Her Highness Fengjiu.
I had never felt the warmth of spring, summer and autumn,
but Her Highness Fengjiu
made me feel warm
and made me realize the way to get warm.
I'm really happy
to know you
and become good friends with you.
I can talk to you freely and frankly,
but when I saw Her Highness Fengjiu,
I was speechless.
I could only wish her the very best.
Don't turn around.
You're sure to meet someone
who matches you
and loves you deeply.
Now she's found her happiness.
Stop looking at her.
Just walk straight ahead.
Right!
Don't turn around.
The road is ahead of you.
Just go your way.
What's this?
I've sealed the primordial spirits of Shen Ye and Aranya
into this tree.
As shadows,
they still have primordial spirits?
Right.
They should have vanished into the universe
after they died,
but if everything in the world is inferred with common sense,
then many feelings will be wasted.
Now that I've sealed them here,
it's up to the will of Heaven
whether their fates can change millions of years later.
Though they're shadows of us,
their feelings for each other are deep and sincere.
Your Majesty, by choosing such a good place
to settle them down,
you've sort of made up for their regrets when they were alive.
We should go back now.
Why are you smiling?
I suddenly remembered that
when I worked as a fairy maid in Tai Chen Palace,
you never paid attention to me.
Now you've actually asked me to go back with you.
It feels like a dream.
I didn't know it was you.
What if you had known?
If I had known,
we wouldn't have wasted so much time.
Ignorant youngsters,
you actually want to confine me?
Lianxin Mirror?
It's actually the Lianxin Mirror
which can purify the dark energy!
Dong Hua,
you really gave me no chance.
You forced me!
Nie Chuyin,
come to me now!
Your Majesty,
Xu Yang has set the ward with his life.
To enter the Forbidden Land
and take out the blood tear now,
Xu Yang must die.
But with my current power,
I can't kill Xu Yang and others all at once.
Try everything.
Kill him!
Yes!
Dong Hua has sealed part of my power.
If I want to break out of the ward,
I have to obtain the last blood tear.
Take it to me
as soon as possible.
Yes!
What're you doing?
Demon Lord Xu Yang,
I just saw you reinforcing the ward.
I was intended to help you.
Is there anything wrong with the ward?
I feel that something is wrong,
but I can't figure out why.
Let me help you reinforce the ward.
I'll help you, too.
Demon Lord Nie,
please tell the other demon lords that
the ward needs to be reinforced.
Make sure that they come with you.
OK.
Xie Guchou,
haven't you made a body for him
with the pimpon fruit,
why isn't he awake?
I just finished the body three days ago.
Moreover, buried under the imperial palace back then,
he had no bones left
but a tiny bit of primordial spirit sealed in the Nether World.
Unfortunately, after sleeping for a hundred years,
his primordial spirit has fallen into quietus.
If we resurrect him hurriedly,
I'm afraid the dark energy
inside his primordial spirit won't be removed.
So what?
Even if he's awake,
he'll be muddleheaded
and intellectually reduced to an infant.
What can we do
to make him stay clear and bright?
I do have a way,
but...
Please tell me.
If an immortal
is willing to give him half of his or her cultivation,
maybe he can remain clear and bright when he's resurrected.
Just take my cultivation.
Don't you want to think it over?
Qingti sacrificed his life to save me.
I just need to give him some cultivation.
No need to think about that.
One more thing.
According to the rules of the Immortal Record Book,
Ye Qingti has become an immortal by a rare chance,
so the person who bestowed him with an immortal body
should go to the Ninth Heaven Jade Pool
to help him wash away his mortal dust
for him to become a real immortal.
OK.
When he wants to start his cultivation,
I'll help him.
Take it easy.
The immortal body was just formed.
Haste does not bring success.
When the immortal body can take it,
I'll inform you for sure.
OK.