Eternal Love of Dream
Episode 36
Aranya,
you've left so long.
I've created this dream world
where every tree and bush,
every person and animal
and all other trivial things
exist for you.
I missed you
and let you be wronged and driven to death.
Someone told me
you could start over
if such a dream world is created.
It can even revive you
by collecting your primordial spirit
like Spirit-Forming Lantern.
Over 200 years have passed.
I'm afraid
I'm the only one who still remembers you.
Do you know?
The two of us in the dream world
have met at this moment.
I'm going to see you,
Aranya.
Can I never
get out of here?
Now that I've lost my memories,
I'd better take my time.
What's destined
cannot be avoided.
If I'm not doomed,
I'll find the truth out sooner or later.
Now that I'm Aranya,
I'll get on with it.
Where is it?
There are snakes everywhere.
It's early in the morning.
Where is everyone?
Chacha.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, you're awake.
Yeah.
Where have you been in the early morning?
Your Highness, did you forget?
You're happiest
on this day of every year.
What's special about today?
Come over.
Put it here.
Open it.
Prince Qing, happy birthday!
Don't come over.
Stay back!
She gives him a kiss and a hug on this day of every year.
Stay back.
What's wrong?
- Hurry. - Wait for me.
Hurry.
Wait for me.
I want to go there too.
Hurry up.
Wait for me.
Where are you going?
Where is Xiaobai's primordial spirit?
It's a dream world,
but it's well built.
It looks quite like the real world,
without any difference.
I'm afraid it'll take some time.
Please enjoy.
I'll never lie.
Do you know?
Princess Junuo
hurt herself the other day.
I think she fell off a horse.
- Did she? - Really?
Absolutely.
My younger sister
is a private servant of Princess Junuo.
She told me about that.
It's said
His Majesty asked Lord Xi Ze
to come and treat Princess Junuo.
I've never heard he has a younger sister.
Me either.
It's really hard to get Lord Xi Ze there.
Really?
Really.
Believe it or not.
Xi Ze?
By practicing Correction Magic,
I can change
the inseparable king birds' memories of Xi Ze
and go to look for Xiaobai like this.
Your Excellency.
What's up?
Their Majesties want to see you.
They said Princess Junuo's condition has worsened.
I see.
Okay.
Your Highness, you didn't call in Prince Qing.
He's so angry as to swallow three oxen.
He must miss you very much,
so I asked them to take him here.
Your Highness,
what's going on?
Did I like him very much?
You and Prince Qing hated to part
with each other.
He left your palace the other day
just because he was sick.
Really?
You must be so excited
as to be terrified, right?
Chacha, come over.
Tell me the story about me and Qing.
Your Highness, is it a test for me?
Yeah.
What's the reward if I win?
I'll tell you after you answer my question.
Prince Qing is a green snake
saved by you when you were young.
You treated him like your younger brother
and named him Qing.
Everyone in the imperial palace,
from senior eunuchs that serve His Majesty
to common servants that do chores,
calls him Prince Qing to show their respect.
It's not easy to pretend to be a princess,
but it's terrible to be one
that likes snakes.
If I overcome my fear of snakes,
I'll be the genuine Princess Aranya
in everyone's mind.
Then I can catch fish and shrimps and do anything as I like.
But if I don't,
they'll find out I'm fake sooner or later,
and then I'll be at their mercy.
No way.
I have to find out a countermeasure.
Your Highness,
shall I have Prince Qing carried here?
No. Don't bother.
Chacha,
I have one more question.
These will be yours
if you answer it correctly.
Okay.
Please go ahead.
Who do I like the most
and who do I hate the most?
Um...
Don't you know that?
Of course I do.
But you're so straightforward
that I'm a little embarrassed.
There is nothing embarrassing.
Answer me.
As for who you like,
you're already engaged to Lord Xi Ze.
Unbelievable. Aranya is even married.
No.
I can try to accept a snake,
but what should I do with a man?
With all due respect,
I think who you hate most
are Princess Junuo and Princess Changdi.
Why do you say that?
Now that you asked me,
I'll answer you honestly.
The two of them are
your sisters,
but they always bully you at ordinary times.
Even I can't bear it.
They always bully me.
Your Highness,
you have a tragic life experience.
It's a different case for them.
They always ride the high horse
because they think they've won Their Majesties' favor.
You're tolerant,
but I feel very uncomfortable.
My parents have several kids.
Some win their favor and some don't.
It doesn't matter.
I'm used to that.
Your Highness,
I don't think it's fair to you.
I understand why Princess Junuo is treated differently,
but Princess Changdi has the same status
as you.
Why is she so arrogant and aggressive?
Why does she dare to bully us?
However,
seeing what happened the other day
when you and Junuo had a horse race,
we've got revenge more or less.
Did anything happen to Princess Junuo?
She fell off her horse.
I've heard her arm is badly injured.
It's a pity you didn't see that because you had left the track.
It was exciting.
Nuo,
are you feeling better?
No.
It's more painful.
Why hasn't Lord Xi Ze arrived?
Her arm is seriously injured.
What should we do
if any sequela happens to her
so that she can't use magic arts anymore?
Stop talking!
If you hadn't instigated Aranya
to have a horse race with her,
she couldn't have been injured.
I didn't expect
Aranya is so good at racing
as to make a spectacle of Nuo.
Enough.
Forget about it, mother.
It's my horse that stumbled.
It's not her fault.
Nuo,
you should know how much expectations
I've placed on you.
Don't let such a thing happen again.
Got it.
Your Excellency, this way please.
Xi Ze, you're here.
Junuo hasn't recovered from an arm injury
despite the imperial doctors' treatment.
I have no other choice
but to ask you to come here.
It's okay. Let me check first.
Where did she hurt?
How did it happen?
She fell off the horse when she had a race with Aranya.
Nuo did it just for fun,
but Aranya rode too fast.
Nuo was anxious and wanted to catch up.
Then she ended up falling off.
She's seriously injured.
What?
She just fell off a horse.
Why is this happening?
It's easy to heal the wounds,
but she was terrified when she fell off
so that her mind and spirit were damaged.
It'll take some time to heal that.
What should we do?
I'll stay in the imperial palace in the coming days
to treat her carefully.
She'll get better
in half a month.
That'd be great!
Servant!
Prepare a nice palace
for Lord Xi Ze.
Make sure it's close to Junuo's palace.
Got it?
Yes.
She's pregnant.
A fetus is the best home to primordial spirit.
To recuperate,
her primordial spirit has to go into the body of someone
with great magic arts.
I'll check
and find the truth out.
Hearing what Chacha said,
I don't think things are going quite smoothly
with Aranya as a princess.
Unfortunately,
I can do nothing about it.
Your Highness, did you want to see me?
I have one more question for you.
Your Highness,
you've asked me lots of questions.
What else do you want to know?
Tell me
which my favorite restaurant is.
The only one you like to go
is called Zuilixian Restaurant.
Zuilixian Restaurant.
That'd be great.
I won't have meals at home tomorrow.
I'll go to Zuilixian Restaurant.
Let me go with you.
Don't bother.
Have a good rest tomorrow.
I'll go there alone.
You can leave.
It seems I have to fight poison with poison.
Your Excellency.
How is Her Highness doing?
She just went to bed.
It's midnight.
I need to transfer energy to treat her.
Don't bother us.
Got it.
Xiaobai.
Are you there?
Junuo is injured.
Consequences may be serious
if I try to contact Xiaobai's primordial spirit.
Xiaobai,
I've got only 10% of my power,
so I can't take you out.
You'd better stay here for a good rest
now that it's a suitable place for you.
Give me some time
and I'll take you out later.
Your Highness,
this is Braised Snake you ordered.
That's all the snake dishes
served here?
Yeah. That's all we have.
Look.
This is Braised Snake Meat.
This is Quick-Fried Snake Meat.
This is Snake Meat with Spicy Salt.
Enough. Stop it.
I see.
You can leave.
Okay.
Your Highness,
you don't eat snake meat at ordinary times.
Why did you order so much today?
Can you eat it up?
I just suddenly want to try it.
You can leave.
Got it.
Please enjoy.
Aranya?
Sorry. I'm in a hurry.
Come on. What a bad luck.
Aranya.
No.
Why am I recognized at this place?
He must be one of Aranya's friends.
Oh no.
I should've come here with a maid.
Such being the case,
I have to try my luck.
Aranya.
Don't you remember me?
Yes, I do.
You're...
I'm Shen Ye.
Right. You're Shen Ye.
Don't you know me?
Um. Yes.
I know you.
I do.
But there is something urgent.
I must go.
What do you think?
Is it warm?
Your Highness,
you scared me today.
You left despite the heavy rain.
Why didn't you wait till it stopped?
You're drenched.
What if you catch a cold?
I met someone today.
It was Shen Ye, the archmage you mentioned yesterday.
Oh.
If Shen Ye asks you
about what I did today,
tell him I'd been busy.
It's weird.
Shen Ye doesn't get along with you.
How could he ask about you?
Is it because...
you made trouble again?
Not get along with me?
But judging from
the way he looked at me,
I don't think it's like that.
Do you mean
your relationship with him in your childhood?
In my childhood?
When you were young,
you went to congratulate him on his birthday
now that he was your cousin,
but he said you were dirty
and threw out all your gifts
after listening to what Princess Junuo and Princess Changdi
had said about you.
Since then you've stopped contacting him.
You're so generous
as to consider you're still friends,
but I don't think
he deserves to be your friend.
Is that all?
It's really weird.
It must be more than that.
Your Highness.
Did Shen Ye come here to ask about me?
He didn't ask me anything.
But I have some news
which will make you happy.
Your master is back.
Mr. Su is back.
He's waiting for you in the antechamber.
Your Highness.
Who came back? My master?
It's Mr. Su Moye.
I know
you'd be surprised.
He said he'd be back in half a year
when he left,
but
just a month has passed and he's back.
Does Aranya also have a master?
Well. Chacha.
His coming back is a great thing,
but I didn't have a good night's sleep yesterday.
And I have a headache because of the morning wind.
I'm afraid it's not the right time to see him.
So...
You should've avoided the rain yesterday.
I'll get a doctor here
to treat you.
Hold on.
Don't bother.
I just need a rest.
Ask my master to go back.
Tell him I'll go to visit him later.
But...
No but. Go ahead.
Mr. Su, please have some tea.
What's up?
Is Aranya still sleeping?
Yeah.
Did everything go on well with her
during the past month?
Nothing was wrong except that
Her Highness fainted after seeing Prince Qing.
What?
She fainted after seeing Prince Qing?
Her Highness has acted weird these days.
Maybe I thought too much.
Mr. Su,
you'd better go back.
Her Highness is feeling under the weather.
She said
she'd visit you and apologize later.
Mr. Su.
Is she feeling under the weather?
I haven't seen you for a month. Are you okay?
As my disciple,
wouldn't you let me sit down?
Master, please take a seat.
Shouldn't a master
be as grey-haired and white-bearded
as the Supreme Venerable Lord in the Sky Kingdom?
I can't believe the young man in white
is Aranya's master.
Hi, master.
Have you grasped
what I taught you?
I have a bad memory recently.
I don't know what exactly you mean.
Before I left, I asked you to learn to
dance with Qing.
Dance with Qing?
Where is he?
He's sleeping.
He's also greedy for sleep.
Does he want me to get him a cup of tea?
I wonder
how Aranya gets along with him.
I should've asked about it.
Master, have some tea please.
It sucks.
Does the tea taste bad?
I'll get it changed.
Chacha.
Don't bother.
Let's drink this today.
Have a taste.
Is it good?
Is it familiar?
Yeah.
It's like I've drunk it before.
That's right.
As expected, it's you.
I hope you're well,
Princess Fengjiu.
What did you call me?
Am I not Aranya?
Of course you're not.
The two of you look alike,
but you're completely different.
Who am I?
Fengjiu.
Bai Fengjiu, Princess of Qingqiu.
Let's go.
I'll take you out for a walk.
Do you mean
here is a ward called Dream of Aranya
and it's made of her dream?
Yes.
It's not the real world.
You fell into this world
from the Python Formation in Fanyin Valley.
You didn't come back after a long time had passed.
You were surrounded by four boa constrictors.
Prince Lian Song thought
Empress of Snakes could drive those boa constrictors away,
so he asked me to save you.
Empress of Snakes?
Right. It's my mother.
Who is Lian Song?
It seems your amnesia is serious.
Second Prince of West Sea, you are here.
Why did you want to see me?
Just now,
Emperor Dong Hua of Tai Chen Palace
and Bai Fengjiu, Princess of Qingqiu,
entered Dream of Aranya in the Python Formation.
They entered Dream of Aranya?
Exactly.
I remember you lived in Fanyin Valley for years.
You must be familiar with the dream world.
And your mother is Empress of Snakes.
I hope you can enter the dream world
and take them out.
Okay.
Now that we're friends,
I'll take Emperor Dong Hua
and Princess Fengjiu back.
Dong Hua will protect Fengjiu,
but unexpected changes may happen anytime
now that they're in Dream of Aranya.
Once you get there,
the first thing is to find them.
Trust me.
I know what to do.
I didn't expect that
you became Aranya
and even can't remember who Lian Song is.
The dream world is dangerous,
but you took risks to come here for me.
Thank you very much.
But
are you really Aranya's master?
You know I'm someone else at the first sight of me
while nobody else did.
It's true that she's my disciple.
When she was 25,
I took her out of a snake pit
and brought her up.
She's not my descendant,
but I treat her like my own flesh and blood.
I had something to deal with in West Sea,
so I left the valley for two years.
When I came back here again,
that lively girl had gone,
only leaving
a tomb covered with grass.
But the inseparable king birds stated categorically
she committed suicide.
Committed suicide?
Is she dead?
Yeah.
But I don't buy their story.
Over the past 200 years,
I've been investigating the cause of her death.
But they hid the truth well.
So when
Lian Song asked me to save you
after you fell into Dream of Aranya,
of course I'd come in and have a look
now that it's about Aranya.
Besides,
I also need your help.
You're the only one here who knows about my true identity.
Just let me know if I can be of any help.
The dream world
is created by someone
based on the world where Aranya lived.
Everyone and everything
that existed in Fanyin Valley at that time
can be found here in the dream world.
Anyone of Fanyin Valley
will take the place of the one created correspondingly
if they fall into Dream of Aranya.
For example. When I came here,
Aranya's master,
that is,
the "me" created correspondingly in the dream world,
disappeared at once.
Do you mean
I came into Aranya's body
because Aranya is me
and I am Aranya?
It's a little weird as for your case.
I guess the creator of the dream world
made some small mistakes
because of lack of skills.
Anyone who falls into Dream of Aranya
can't remember what people in their own world look like.
When I just came in,
I already had a vague impression of your appearance.
I think that's a small accident.
Maybe you becoming Aranya
is another accident.
Actually,
nothing but a tomb has left about Aranya.
For the mortal inseparable king birds,
they don't exist anymore if they die.
Anyone in Dream of Aranya
could be replaced
by the corresponding one from Fanyin Valley,
except Aranya.
I have my head in the clouds.
I didn't quite get it.
Forget about it.
Just tell me
what I can do to help you.
After that,
let's figure out a way to leave here.
At the very beginning, the dream world
might be exactly the same as the Fanyin Valley back then,
but as time goes on,
it has nothing to do with the valley anymore.
I guess someone created it
just to change the tragedy that happened to Aranya
so that her life could have a happy ending.
But Aranya is dead.
A happy ending here won't make a difference.
The creator is just deceiving himself and others.
Well.
Now that you're in the body of Aranya,
I hope that you can follow
the choices and decisions Aranya made
so that everything in those years could reappear
till her death.
Maybe it's the only way you could get out of here
and go back to Qingqiu.
That's also what I need your help with.
I want to know the truth behind Aranya's death.
Isn't there another way to do that?
I'm afraid not.
But I've heard
Aranya was innocent and elegant.
She was otherworldly
and she liked snakes.
How could I be convincing?
These are some letters Aranya wrote to others
when she was alive.
Study them carefully.
As for Prince Qing,
you have to figure out a way yourself.
It's really complicated.
I didn't expect anyone to save me,
but Emperor Dong Hua took risks
to save me.
I have no idea about that either.
All I know about Dong Hua
came from Lian Song.
I don't know what happened between the two of you,
so I can't give you any advice.
It's a little weird.
You two fell into the dream world at the same time.
You should've been at the same place.
Your Excellency.
Take the pills to Princess Junuo
and ask her to have a rest-cure.
Got it.
Xiaobai,
I'll know if you're in Junuo's body
when she's fully recovered.
Quick.
Put it here. Right.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, do you have a headache again?
No.
I feel much better these days.
Your Highness,
please say something to Prince Qing.
You were under the weather the other day.
Without seeing you,
Prince Qing has been dispirited for several days.
Really?
Qing...
Qing, be a good boy.
You didn't see me just for a few days.
You don't need to miss me so much.
Your Highness.
It scared the hell out of me!
I'm scared to death.
Your Highness, you're awake.
The imperial doctor checked
and said it's nothing serious.
You're just frightened.
But Your Highness,
how could you be frightened
by Prince Qing?
You were very close to each other.
How close?
Prince Qing used to
eat and sleep with you.
You've ignored him for several days.
I really don't have the heart to see him suffer.
Qing is troublesome.
I have no other choice
but to get used to him for the time being.
Um.
Chacha, don't think too much.
I'll be nice to Qing.
That'd be great.
Oh.
What? What's up?
This is a list sent by His Majesty.
It's the list of followers
who'll go to Her Majesty's birthday banquet.
Please have a look.
Followers? What are they going to do?
I've heard that a new cruise is made
for Her Majesty
and we'll go to Guan Chen Palace in the south
to view camellias.
Shen Ye. Xi Ze. Junuo.
Changdi. Aranya.
I'm also on the list!
You must be kidding.
As the Second Princess,
of course you're on the list.
That'd be great.
Now that we're going to the south,
Qing couldn't board the ship
now that he's such a large snake.
He couldn't have a chance to bother me then.
Oh. Your Highness,
Lord Xi Ze is also on the list.
The two of you should meet each other.
You're husband and wife, anyway.