Eternal Love of Dream
Episode 26
Si Ming.
These days I heard
the gossip about Lord Cheng Yu and Third Prince Lian Song,
which has been spread all over the Sky Kingdom.
What happened to them on earth?
How could there be so much discussion?
It's not a hot topic any more.
Recently,
there has been another anecdote
spreading in the Sky Kingdom.
I'm not interested in it.
It's just too popular.
Obviously, you're not interested in gossips.
Neither am I.
But
tell me something about it.
Frankly speaking,
neither you nor I like gossiping.
It doesn't matter for us to have a talk about it.
Your Highness, you can never imagine that
His Majesty who we usually think
upright with self-discipline
can't be judged by his looks.
Your fate with him was stopped that year.
In my opinion,
it was to protect you,
which is really worthy.
What's wrong with His Majesty?
I heard that
His Majesty had a stunning fairy
in Tai Chen Palace
who is greatly favored by him.
So it appears that
this is the reason
why he doesn't leave Tai Chen Palace for these years.
Indeed,
with a beauty's company,
even though he doesn't leave the palace,
he won't feel lonely.
Your Highness, don't care about it.
Anyhow, you have nothing to do with him now.
I told you this
not to worry you.
Which fairy does His Majesty have a fancy for?
I'm not interested in it.
I'm just asking casually.
In private, we...
They have different predictions of this fairy.
But it's really a mismatch between His Majesty and love affairs.
Except his foster sister Princess Zhihe,
they don't have other predictions.
But Princess Zhihe
has been serving her punishment in the West Desert.
In my opinion,
it's less likely to be her.
As for the fairy,
actually
there was only one exact thing.
It was said that, six or seven days ago,
Third Prince Lian song saw His Majesty
taking the fairy to bathe in the hot spring in Tai Chen Palace.
Bathe in the hot spring?
You don't believe it, right?
I was also very surprised after hearing it.
Unbelievable!
Well, speaking of this,
there was also another talk the day before yesterday,
which was well organized, analyzed
and a little believable.
Unexpectedly, the figure in the talk
is someone around us.
We have never heard of it.
Who is she?
She is your good friend, Lord Cheng Yu.
It's said that Lord Cheng Yu
is the illegitimate daughter of His Majesty and the fairy.
Your Highness.
You are really clinging when you insist on something
while you feel free when you let it go.
It's an advantage which even God Bai Qian is lack of.
When God Bai Qian meets
something elusive,
she won't give up until she makes it clear.
However, you just deal with everything
according to your capability.
Admirable!
To be honest,
I'm really qualified to bear
this title.
I didn't prepare well then,
so there were some jokes.
But now
I remember one of my mottoes.
You've been living for more than thirty thousand years
with numerous mottoes
collected.
Which one do you mean?
Never fall in love with a man who is involved with another woman.
Incisive!
Lord Cheng Yu.
Lord Cheng Yu is quite beautiful.
If she was really the illegitimate daughter of His Majesty,
the fairy must have been a national beauty.
I'm going to see Lord Cheng Yu,
Find a right chance to ask her something about it.
I have helped you get the schedule of His Majesty.
Cheng Yu.
You really do me a great favor.
All right.
Let's get down to business.
As the respected immortal among the gods,
Emperor Dong Hua has lived in seclusion
in Yi Shi San Heaven partly,
but there are still some responsibilities that
he doesn't discharge to the Heavenly King,
such as taking charge of the name book of the immortals.
Each year on the fifth day of the fifth lunar month,
the immortals who have finished cultivating in the world
need to climb to the 36th Heaven, Daluo Heaven
to pay a visit to His Majesty in Qingyun Hall,
asking him to give them a suitable rank.
However, there are so many immortals.
As for my thing, the fewer people are involved, the better.
There are so many people here.
Just wait me to finish my words.
According to the routine,
after all the immortals leave when the worship is over,
His Majesty will incidentally check Lianxin Mirror
in the Qingyun Hall
and stay there for a while.
Then in this moment,
I can go to get back my bracelet.
It's the fifth day of the fifth lunar month tomorrow.
Well,
I still have something to do in my palace. I'm leaving first.
Cheng Yu.
You really do me a great favor.
The fifth day of the fifth lunar month.
My mother told me that
when asking for payment of debt,
someone must act quickly, accurately and cruelly,
avoiding others' denying of the debt at the very beginning
with enough vigour
and properly affirming the debt
to others.
Only in this way can the person
give you a perfect answer.
Sister, I won't grab it with you.
Eat slowly.
I'm full. Just enjoy your food.
With something else to do, I'm leaving first.
Sister Fengjiu.
Where are you going? I also want to go with you.
With something urgent to do,
I can't take you along with me.
Let me go.
Sister, tell me where you are going.
I'm sure not to cause you any trouble.
Who annoys you?
It's not bad to have more helpers during a fight.
You can't compete against him.
Fengjiu.
No,no, no. It's not what you saw and heard.
You teach your younger brother like this?
No. No.
Li. I will bring you some delicious food.
Study hard!
Sister Fengjiu.
Why is Sister Fengjiu so busy recently?
She always takes me along with her.
Maybe there are something new in the heaven.
She's just joining the fun.
Maybe the worship meeting has been over.
Is His Majesty is inside alone?
Who are you?
Bai Qian from Qingqiu.
Your Highness.
His Majesty is inside.
It's just the right time.
I'm going to discuss something important with His Majesty.
Don't let any other people go inside.
I'm sure to award you later.
It's true that His Majesty is here alone.
Was my tea-crystal bracelet
left here that night?
I am sleepwalking,
going to the wrong place.
It's true that you left your bracelet here.
There was also a hairpin
as well as this
pinning flower you dropped in the hot spring.
Just come for it.
Really I am sleepwalking, going to the wrong place.
And...
I seem to be sober suddenly,
spiritually clear,
maybe thanks to the great miraculous brightness here.
Your Majesty.
Indeed I have something
to take back from you.
I didn't come to the wrong place.
Please keep them for me.
I'll get them back later.
Owing to my obtrusion,
your worship meeting is disturbed.
I'm sincerely sorry for that.
I'm sure to specially hold an assembly
to apologize to you another day.
OK.
You won't take them by yourself
but wait for me to send them to your hand, right?
See? she runs away.
She is shy.
Her Highness Fengjiu.
Really it's her.
I heard that, today in Qingyun Hall,
you played tricks on Fengjiu in front of all the immortals.
The Immortal Official
named Chong Lin who is loyal and upright
is very worried,
hoping to keep your image of
integrity and justice.
He even came to discuss with me.
Have a discussion about integrity and justice with you?
Is he over drunk?
Forget it.
I won't fuss about it with you.
I'm here to tell you something serious.
With your interruption, I nearly forget it.
The demons in the South Desert
have some unusual movements recently.
Xu Yang became depressed
because of his sister Ji Heng.
Nie Chuyin is healing his wounds.
And the man
called...
Called what?
How could I forget his name?
He is Yan Chiwu, one of the seven lords of the demons.
Because of the joint-marriage between you
and First Princess of the demons,
he asked for a fight with you.
Without precaution,
you were locked in Ten-evil Lotus Land
by him with soul-locking jade,
which made you quite embarrassed like a drowned rat.
Do you still remember him?
What's wrong with him?
If it hadn't been the red fox,
half of your cultivation would have been spoiled by
the demons and evils.
You destroyed his deployment.
Yan Chiwu was ashamed of you.
It was said that he was taking action again recently,
getting even with you.
I'm waiting for his battle letter.
I heard that you were cultivating your mind recently.
With decreasing care of fighting, you're not interested in it.
Is it possible that you think it was he
who caught the red fox?
Unexpectedly, there is something you care so much.
Yeah.
Fengjiu from Qingqiu is also a red fox.
Is it likely that you show appreciation for her
because of this?
How imaginative you are!
Why not go to Hebi House to tell stories?
Uncle.
I have just run away from the dating feast.
I don't think it's good for me to go out
to be seen in the public like this.
Yesterday God Zhe Yan went to the heaven,
preparing to tame the Red-fire Beast to be my new mount.
It appears that you want to tame the Red-fire Beast with him.
It doesn't matter if I go out to be seen in public sometimes.
It doesn't matter.
It's beneficial to my body and mind.
That's right.
Go out for a walk often.
Maybe you can meet your Mr. Right.
Then you won't let down your father.
What's your purpose to her?
Do you think she is good?
I think she is interesting.
Interesting?
It's really difficult to get your words from your mouth.
Here comes the Heavenly King.
I will go there first. Hurry up.
This way, please.
Please.
Unexpectedly, a fairy who is under punishment
could be so brilliant.
Since you have been here
serving your punishment for hundreds of years,
you can return to the Sky Kingdom.
What do you think, Your Majesty?
OK.
Thank you, Heavenly King.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
The Heavenly King
is discussing something serious with the officials.
As the Princess of Qingqiu,
you can meet the prestige of heaven
and hear His Majesty's instructions.
Why not listen calmly, attentively and respectfully?
How could there be smiles all over your face?
I dare not.
Something just occurred to me.
In Qingqiu, if an immortal
is guilty of something,
only after he makes a great contribution
can he be listed among the immortals again.
Unexpectedly, as for the gods,
one can be so easily forgiven by having a dance.
At first, I was worried about Princess Zhihe,
so smiled with a relief.
Later, I felt the laws of the gods
are liberal and full of kindness,
so I smiled with appreciation.
However, it suddenly occurred to me that
Princess Zhihe is talented and skilled.
Naturally she will be absolved.
What if an immortal
who is neither talented nor skilled
committed a crime?
So I smiled with doubts.
It's just my superficial opinion.
Please don't laugh at me.
When it comes to harsh words,
she has a glib tongue.
She is no worse than you today.
I speak more briefly than her.
The doubts of the Princess of Qingqiu is really good.
The laws of the Sky Kingdom are always strict and impartial.
If Princess Zhihe wants to return to the Sky Kingdom,
she must make a contribution in the battlefield.
This is also a law in the heaven,
a clear rule.
Since it is so,
as for Princess Zhihe's return to the Sky Kingdom,
let's talk about it later.
I can go to the battlefield instead of her
If she has to make contributions in the battlefield
for the purpose of returning to the Sky Kingdom.
When in Qingqiu,
we heard Princess Zhihe's parents who have passed away
ever fostered Your Majesty.
You really have affection and faith. Your Majesty.
As foster brother and sister, His Majesty and Princess Zhihe
are really kind and respectful to each other.
OK, just let it be.
It's just a casual party.
You can freely walk around to know each other.
No need to crowd here.
There is scenery everywhere in Baoyueguang Garden.
You don't need to stand on ceremony.
Thank you for your kindness, Heavenly King.
So long, Heavenly King.
Having known Your Highness for a long time,
I feel so lucky
to see you by myself today.
I've long been looking forward to meeting you.
You look abnormal. What are you doing?
Stand still. Don't move.
I planned to rehearse for more days to show you,
but
it's good to show you tonight.
As you said, you are repaying my kindness, right?
Enjoying the beauty of flowers with Lord Cheng Yu,
I feel greatly honored.
There is something that I need to explain to you clearly.
If it's something bad,
don't talk about it tonight.
No.
I just appreciate God Zhe Yan
without any other meanings.
I know you have feeling for me.
They are not the same thing.
Don't talk nonsense.
Cheng Yu, we...
Shut up.
Are you OK?
No.
It doesn't count this time.
Turn to me next time you are in trouble.
Cheng Yu, have you ever thought that
maybe this is the will of heaven?
We can never pay off to each other.
It's so strange!
Why does my heart beat so fast?
Am I sick?
It must be.
What are you doing here?
I'm drinking juice.
This is wine.
Are you going to fight with someone?
Can you take me along with you?
I'm so little.
I won't cause you any trouble.
Can you take me?
You're drunk.
Maybe.
I feel dizzy.
Do you still remember the way?
Let me send you back.
You're lying.
You told me that you were going to give
someone a lesson.
Then you asked me to wait you here.
But you didn't come back.
It's I who went to look for you.
When did it happen?
Not long ago.
♪ Falling flowers have a soft voice. ♪
Don't move.
♪ The wind talks to the Bodhi tree. ♪
I don't have the wrong memory.
We fox always have good memory.
♪ When it comes to destiny... ♪
You mistake me for someone else again.
Who am I?
Your Majesty.
But
♪ Acacia sees time flying... ♪
Dong Hua, you're really bad.
Why?
You said I was a pet.
You didn't ask me to stay when I left.
♪ It's melancholy and sorrowful. ♪
I don't remember
I told so.
It turns out to be that this morning in Qingyun Hall,
the fairy that Emperor Dong Hua played tricks on
is the Princess of Qingqiu
who has long enjoyed a good reputation,
Her Highness Fengjiu.
His Majesty protects his foster sister so much.
I'm wondering how Her Highness Fengjiu feels in her heart.
I can see something in essence,
which can be understood in another way.
I am seated far away from the main seat.
I'm not sure if my opinion is right.
Tell me.
In the mortal realm,
actually it's something about
the younger sister striving for her elder brother's favor
with her sister-in-law.
Probably the younger sister
has some attachment to her elder brother.
The sister-in-law also hates to see the younger sister.
Then the dispute came into being.
It's really what you said.
You have strong perception and a clear mind.
I'm wondering who is your commander.
You really have a promising future.
What's this?
It's...
It's His Majesty's clothing.
How could it be here?
What happened?
It's Brother Dong Hua's clothing, right?
When your father was young,
he called Dong Hua uncle.
Should I call him according to Sister Fengjiu's address
or my father's?
What happened on earth?
It's nothing serious.
You were drunk last night.
His Majesty did a good deed, sending you back to Qingyun Hall.
But you were so drunk,
holding the front of his gown tightly without loosing your hand.
Unable to wake you up,
he can do nothing
but take off his gown and leave it here.
Hmm,
maybe he was also on the way.
Anyhow, he did a good deed.
Neither his good name
nor my good name was damaged, which is good.
As you know,
His Majesty can't stay overnight in Qingyun Hall.
With his gown leaving to you,
it's not convenient for him to go out.
Besides, in Qingyun Hall,
there aren't any clothes which are suitable for His Majesty.
So Li went to borrow clothes
from Bai Qian.
However, it was the wedding day of Bai Qian and Ye Hua.
Maybe they had a sound sleep.
So Li yelled loudly in the yard.
I'm afraid all the people in Xiwu Palace could hear it.
What did you say?
Just tell the truth.
Brother Dong Hua took sister Fengjiu back to Qingyun Hall.
Sister Fengjiu prevented him going back,
so Brother Dong Hua accompanied her for a while.
By the way, he also took off his gown.
He has no gown to wear.
So I came to borrow a gown from father.
Mother.
Is my father in your room?
I yelled like this.
I said I would forget you.
Why do you always turn up in front of me?
Sister Fengjiu.
You frighten me.
What's wrong?
My mother asked me to give uncle's letter to you.
= Fengjiu, I miss you so much.
You take Li back now! Father Bai Yi =
What does he say?
He said it was not long before I went back to Qingqiu
and asked me to have a good preparation.
Time passes so quickly.
I don't want you to go back.
These days,
I can have a good time with you.
Later,
when you miss me,
just go to Qingqiu to see me.
Fine. When can we go to play?
After I send these things back,
then we can go.
OK.
Foster brother.
Is there something strange about this gown?
The court banquet has been over.
Choose someday to go to the West Desert.
Foster brother.
Sister Fengjiu. Hurry up.
I'm coming.
Let's go.
Let's enjoy ourselves today.
Sister Fengjiu, shall we still go out?
Of course.
We shouldn't let down the good days.
Let's go.
Princess Zhihe.
You haven't gone to the West Desert yet.
Foster brother has tender affection for me,
asking me to stay for more days.
His Majesty and Princess Zhihe
are really kind and respectful to each other.
Probably you can get along well with His Majesty,
living happily.
Tell me
if it was you
who threw the purple gown to Tai Chen Palace just now.
Don't attempt to bewitch my foster brother.
You'd better give up the idea.
Zhihe.
For one thing, you haven't returned to the West Desert with sin.
For another, you look down upon the laws of heaven, offending me.
With a good mood today,
I won't fuss about it with you.
Am I right?
Who are you?
Bai Fengjiu.
You must have something to do with Xiaojiu.
Don't bully Sister Fengjiu.
Don't attempt to bewitch my foster brother.
Your Highness.
Sister Fengjiu. Look.
It seems that
the birds droppings and you bring out the best of each other.
Let's go.
Bai Fengjiu, just wait.
Her Highness Fengjiu.
Princess Zhihe.
Sister Fengjiu, what are they doing?
I don't know.
As for our identities,
we mustn't eavesdrop anything.
Sister Fengjiu.
I really want to know.
Are you curious about it?
Yes.
So you must be very careful.
Don't expose your identity.
You know?
Yes.
Come here. Li.
Hurry up.
What are they doing?
They are having a bet of long match.
They are betting on Brother Dong Hua.
Uncle.
Grandpa.
They're betting on Grandpa Dong Hua
whether he will marry you
or Princess Zhihe.
You are so little.
Do you know what is a long match?
I don't know,
but I am eager for knowledge.
I asked an onlooker immortal
about it.
He didn't have a clear explanation,
but just told me
there were 25 bets on Princess Zhihe
with only three bets on you,
which are bet wrongly with carelessness.
I still don't understand.
But I don't want you to wait for long,
so I came back secretly.
Just before I left,
I saw him arguing with a brother,
asking if he could transfer his three bets
to Princess Zhihe.
Have 200 bets
on me.
I am so young. How could you teach me to cheat?
That's because,
as for anything related to Qingqiu,
I wouldn't like
to be inferior to others.
Maybe this is the spirit of a monarch.
If you don't believe me, just think about the past.
According to younger uncle,
you never won first in your study.
All your subjects are inferior to others,
some of which even rank the last.
That's because
no one is perfect in everything.
It's not likely that you never rank the last.
Nonsense.
I never won the last.
Take it.
Just bet on me.
Besides,
you have never won the last
because you haven't had a Buddhist theories.
You can't imagine how difficult it is.
Is it so difficult?
I saw Brother Dong Hua...
Grandpa Dong Hua
fishing while reading a Buddhism book
for fun.
He is abnormal.
No.
The fragrance is so heavy.
I can't resist it.
I will wait for you in the forest ahead.
What did you do to her?
She praised you like this.
Praise?
Cheng Yu praised you like this?
No.
Cheng Yu praised me that I was a rascal.
You have bet on me?
Several brothers laughed at me
that I didn't have a good judgement.
But I still firmly
bet on you.
Good.
Although we suffered financial loss today,
yet
we reversed the losing game.
I'm so happy today. I will take you to have a spring field trip.
I heard, several days ago,
you received the battle letter from Yan Chiwu
and would go to Mount Fuyu in two days.
Chong Lin specially took Canghe Sword,
asking me to polish it.
But I don't think it's such a situation.
How could I meet him here?
I...
Hmm...
If he comes here,
just say that you're catching butterflies here by yourself.
What did you think when you made Canghe Sword?
On the area as small as a palm,
you tried hard to chisel
over ten thousand sections with zirconite
and over five thousand holes in different depths.
It really caused me much mental fatigue to repair and clear it.
Is it possible that you hide
some secret mechanisms in it?
No.
I just had too much free time.
Unexpectedly, in the Eight Deserts and Six Directions,
you are always eulogized
peaceful in mind,
integrity and upright.
With nobody to disclose you,
how does Chong Lin make it?
As you said,
What do you think?
I also think it's hard for him to do that.
Glad to see you, Your Majesty.
Glad to see you, Third Grandpa.
Li.
What are you doing here?
Grandpa.
I am catching butterflies here.
Lightly.
You are pulling my ear.
This is...
I lost a handkerchief.
I have looked for it for several days.
Lightly.
Feng...
The handkerchief may feel painful.
It's clear that the handkerchief has the style of women.
How could it be?
I heard that someone said I was abnormal.
An abnormal person uses a handkerchief with the style of women.
Is it strange?
No.
As you said,
it's not strange at all.
It's too late.
Aren't you going to enjoy the lotus by boat?
Yes.
In the afternoon when it's not windy,
there won't be elegant taste.
Let's go now.
Li.
We'll play with you next time.
So long, Your Majesty. Third Grandpa.
Am I hunted by ghosts
to change myself into a handkerchief?
It's better to be a tree.
According to His Majesty's cultivation,
even he can see through my camouflage at one sight,
he can't root me up
and carry me back on his back.
Since it is so,
it's most likely that he has known
who I am.
With such a performance,
he just waits to make a fool of me.
Now that it is so,
I still can't
show myself as the Princess of Qingqiu in front of him
to lose the face of Qingqiu.
Anyway, I won't confess that
I am Bai Fengjiu from Qingqiu.
I just disguise myself as a real handkerchief.
Maybe when he finds me not interesting,
he will throw me away.
As long as I close my four senses,
he can do nothing to me.
Where are they going?
I am so dizzy.