Don't know what I'm talking about
A veteran's soldier
Don't care what the future holds
I'll put you through all Dear
What is love and what is lack
Give that Mrs. You can't let the magic flow
March and I aren't leaning toward the bright future
And I'll follow you
To the place I turn
It was a despair in the throwsai
Though my and love do not have a flower
If you do not want it to last
Episode 17
No.
Hey,
it's you that
Update princess Chongyang's
maid.
You...
Why the hell you don't know how to be vocal?
Embroidery?
What is it?
Tell me.
It smells good, Yang Yang.
Have you made dinner?
What are you doing here?
You think this is your home?
This...
Is not it?
Who allowed you to be here?
Get out of here.
Our home doesn't welcome you.
I don't need your welcome.
As long as Brother Chong Yang welcomes me,
I won't cook for you.
You...
Take these things with you.
Get out of here.
I'm not leaving.
I'll be working hard for the whole morning.
Why do you have to be so loyal to me?
Besides,
we will live in the same house in the future.
We will learn to live together.
Who allowed you to live with us?
This house doesn't have your room.
It's okay.
I don't care.
I can live with Brother Chong Yang.
Enough.
Don't be angry.
Have a taste.
I've been cooking for a whole morning.
Who's sweating?
Who knows
if you'll poison inside.
I've been found out.
If I really poison inside,
will you drink it?
Drink it.
I'm not afraid of poison.
Then drink it.
It's sweet.
What is this?
It's...
Red sugar water.
Red sugar?
No, it's not.
Miss Chu.
Do you want some red sugar water?
Jin Nanxiu.
Recently, my body has become weaker.
It's getting more and more painful for me.
I even lost my strength in the garden.
It seems that I've lost my last breath.
It's getting closer.
You're here to hide here?
I was supposed to cook for you.
Changsheng and Yingying have made you angry again?
It's okay.
In fact, every day
is a good day.
In the past,
I was on a boat alone
to the south of the river.
I've seen a lot of beautiful scenery.
Unfortunately, no one told me.
Now,
you and them are with me.
I don't have to feel lonely anymore.
So...
So I want to stay with you forever.
What forever?
I'll stick to you forever.
I'm afraid
I can't stay with you for the rest of my life.
You're the one who's been with me.
I just want you to be a flower.
You're not
anything to me.
Drink it forever.
It's like a,​
as if
everything we've happened
is nothing to me.
Don't you like me at all?
My memories...
They're always like this.
The more I think about it, the harder it is to get close to it.
The more I feel pain, the more I think about it.
Every snow flower is like you and me.
Let time pass by.
The sky is full of light and fire.
The eternity is there.
The flowers are falling.
All these moments are written.
I thought Xiyin's hometown was the Zouyan Flower of Jinanxing.
Now it seems that Xiyin's hometown is not Zouyan Flower,
but the person of Jinanxing.
Then let's catch Jinanxing now.
Maybe he is the daughter of the family who has been looking for him.
It's not that easy.
He has a relationship with Chongyang.
Chongyang doesn't say it, but he treats Jinanxing differently.
Now that you have caught Jinanxing,
you are not making me go up.
The family is wise.
But since Chongyang is so fond of Jinanxing,
you can use this woman.
Yes. Then I'll go down first.
Jinanxing, are you really a Yan woman?
Only Yan women can be hardworking.
I always thought Yan women is just a legend.
For thousands of years, no one has seen a Yan woman.
Hua Ling, you saved me.
Tomorrow.
Little.
You let me kill you, not just indulge you,
you want to tell me it's not about anything,
now on our lives.
I've been stayed too much love.
I thought I've been through so much with you,
but the iron can good deed.
Attendant Jin.
Go upstairs and have a look.
Stand by the window,
Let me go.
Cheers to Nan,
you have driven me away.
So you move here?
Yes.
Miss Zhu,
You're here to buy flowers?
Jinan Xing,
you're the one who took a boat
and jumped from the sea.
It's really hard.
Why did you care about me today?
I didn't care about you.
I just understand
why you've been talking about Brother Chongyang.
Then tell me, Miss Zhu,
why do I keep on holding him?
How much money
can you sell for your entire life?
You just care about Brother Chongyang's career
and his unreachable wealth, right?
Miss Zhu,
you're so smart.
But no matter how rich Brother Chongyang is,
how much money can he give you?
This money
needs your 100 songs tightly documented.
I'm so sure
of thisHarvest my 100 songs.
Where you're going,
I'm not going to leave Nan'an City
and won't ever near Brother Chongyang again.
I'm not sure.
Ms. Zhu,
I think what you said
makes sense.
But,
my goal
is not to let 100 people know,
but to let 1000 people know.
In the future,
there might be 10,000 people.
You...
Can you give it to her?
Ji Nansheng,
why are you so greedy?
People
are not greedy.
Besides,
if I'm with Chuang,
how many boats do I want?
Do I even care about your money?
You...
You think...
You think Brother Chuang really likes you?
He's playing with you every day.
He'll throw you away.
You can't even get a penny.
Then you'd better pray to him to get rid of him.
Otherwise,
you'd have to be angry for the rest of your life.
Ji Nansheng,
let me ask you one last time.
Are you leaving Nan'an City or not?
I'm not leaving.
Nan'an City is not your home.
Don't say you're rushing me away.
I'm not leaving even if Chongyang is.
I've been waiting for so long.
Wait for me.
What can I do?