YoYo English Channel YouTube
Yingying
Brother Zhuang Yang
Fortunately
I am waiting for you
How did you become like this
Mao Xieci
He turned my face like this
He also lied to me
He took Jin Nanxing away
Where is Nanxing?
I don't know
I will take you to the hospital
Yingying
Sorry
I was too worried
If I could go back to when I was a kid
Yingying
You have become an ordinary person
Chong Yang
What does it feel to see someone you care about leave you
Now you finally understand
You killed Yingying
Yes
Where is Nanxing?
Don't worry
She is alive now
But when she dies
I can't guarantee
Meng Xieci
Why did you do this
I don't know
You are asking me why
Because of Hua Ling
Because I didn't save her three years ago
You blame me
I shouldn't blame you
My Meng family has served you for generations
Even the first one in the ancestral training is that you Chongyang's order is higher than everything
Including the lives of our Meng family
Even the lives of my family
I have done it for generations
I am no exception
But you
I only asked you this time
You saved my wife's life
But you said you couldn't save her
I can't save her
The Yongye clan
Can't awaken people who have lost consciousness
Even if you force her to wake up
She didn't think about her life
Would you like to see Hua Ling like that
So what
She is stronger than a cold corpse
Now
Even the corpse
What did you say
How is Hua Ling
She left
Where is Jin Nanxing
Did you make a mistake on Jin Nanxing
That's right
Yan Yan
The body of a girl is the best container of foreign countries
The missing girl at the top of the mountain
It's all you, right
Correct
I should have been there
When I was looking for that token
I doubted you
Pity
You trust me too much
Xizi
Why do you say
We will become like this
Chongyang
You are too naive
Do you think I will still be like before
To be your brother
I want you to be like me
Lose your lover and suffer for a lifetime
Then I will ask you one last time
Nanxing
You used to have a brother
Zhu Ying Ying
Now why are you the only one left
Like a dog in a dead family
Meng Xi Ci
Where is Jin Nanxing
Chongyang
Do you think I don't know
You are just like me now
Are you an ordinary person
Is it really easy for you to kill me now
You are really not afraid of the sun
As long as you tell me
Where is Jin Nanxing
What do you want me to do
I promise you
it is good
In this case
Then break your wish
I will do it
Chongyang
Chongyang, you go quickly
Don't come
Nanxing
Chongyang
Chongyang, what's wrong with you
You go quickly
It's okay
Meng Xi Ci told me
In your body
Bones have been removed
The insect has gone out of my body
But the flower spirit did not come back
Chongyang, don't stand here
You go quickly
I'm fine
Meng Xi Ci killed Yun Ying
He is crazy
I know
I know everything
Chongyang
What's wrong with you
Don't waste your energy
If it was before
This chain is for you
It's not a threat at all
But now
Don't talk about iron chains
I'm afraid you can't even pull a rope
Meng Xi Ci
What do you know
Chongyang
What does he mean by this
Nanxing
You don't know yet
Chongyang
Is dying
Meng Xi Ci
Don't talk
It seems that the old god
I don't want you to die so easily
Chongyang
What does he mean by this
Aren't you from the Youyue tribe
Won't the Youyue tribe die
Chongyang
You didn't expect it, did you
I actually know
The secret of the stone flower
Just when you were seriously injured
I guessed it when I came to me
Stone flower
What's wrong with the stone flower
Chongyang
You can't bear to tell him even this
OK, let me tell you
Then let me tell you
Don't want to drink
Suddenly
The year is like a person who is lost
Lock the door of memory
Eternal promise
I lost you
How to balance
How to bear to be broken
The more you want to try hard not to get close
The more painful it is
Every snow flower is like you
Let time pass
The fire in the sky
Embrace that moment
Tears fall
This world is all colors
You only belong to me
Even if it's separation
It's a life and death song
So what