[birds chirping]
[Seongmin's mother] Don't worry.
That will only be a few days.
Yeah, I know.
It's all right.
I'll go talk to your brother-in-law.
Seongmin.
Your uncle here, he'll be staying with us
for a little while.
I won't be staying here too long.
I think we'll get along just fine.
Seongmin.
Can you really read that?
Yes.
Can you read Russian and German too?
[Seongmin's uncle]
Have a look at this one.
Anarchism
It's gonna open up a whole new world.
[♪ ominous music playing]
[loud explosion]
[Seongmin's mother] Jinchul!
- Jinchul!
- [Jinchul] It's all right.
- Don't worry about me.
- No, Jinchul! No, wait!
He just reads. He's done nothing wrong!
He's not part of
the independence movement!
He's done nothing wrong!
Stop!
Stop! No! Don't take him!
[panting]
[Seongmin's mother] You reported him,
didn't you?
[Ilsik] Why would you bring
a freedom fighter into our home?
[Seongmin's mother] How dare you?
How could you do such a thing?
He's my little brother!
[Ilsik] That idiot will be
the death of this family!
[Seongmin's mother] He could die in there!
[Seongmin's mother cries]
How could you do such a thing?
How could you?
[Ilsik] You should be thinking
about our family!
[Seongmin's mother]
My baby brother is going to die in there!
He's gonna die!
[overhead creaking]
- [creaking continues]
- [♪ discordant music playing]
Uncle Samsik
[♪ theme music playing]
The Two Truths
Choi Minkyu made
another ridiculous request.
What now?
I really think this is going too far.
All right, come on. Tell me, what is it?
The opposition is too far ahead
in some districts.
Don't tell me… the ballot boxes?
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Why did you come over here
this late anyway?
[Kim San breathes deeply]
Yeojin was arrested by the police.
Can you get her out?
Things will get complicated if I do.
- [Kim San] So you don't want to.
- It's not that I don't want to.
[sighs]
Is she really a concern of yours
right now?
Yes, I'm worried about her.
If we let her out, she'll continue
to hold us back, you know that.
Fine, forget it.
Don't do it if you don't want to.
[Doochill] I'm not saying I don't want to.
I'm just saying it will be a headache,
that's all.
You're going to steal
ballot boxes, really?
I'll get Choo Yeojin released.
Are you satisfied?
[door closes]
[sighs]
[officer] Explain to me.
What kind of orders did Choo Intae
give Yoon Palbong?
What don't you understand?
None of that ever happened.
Choo Intae was the one behind
Choi Hanrim's conspiracy,
isn't that right?
Sir, I don't know who that is.
I don't know Choi.
[indistinct whisper]
- What?
- Yes, sir.
Miss, we're done here. You can leave.
What?
[officer] You're free to go.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[Inwoo] Are you okay?
They just let me go.
Just like that?
Someone must have said something.
Who?
That Sineui Alliance tip…
you don't know who sent it in?
No.
Who would benefit
from the Sineui story getting out?
[Inwoo] I'm not sure.
It's either Kang Seongmin's rival
or someone who wants to be.
Kim San?
Yoon Palbong, Kim Kwangmin, Kim San.
Someone is behind them all.
The person who made my father a monster
is the one who got me
out of there just now.
The same person who got my father killed,
accused him of being a spy,
and now they've begun turning San
into a monster.
You'll help me, right?
[sighs]
It's best we don't tell the boss.
[reporter 1]
The upcoming presidential election
has been set for March 15th,
the campaigns have now entered
their final stretch.
Both parties have addressed crowds in
urban and rural areas across the country.
All voters are listening closely
to the candidate's fiery campaign speeches
and will soon decide which one is worthy
of leading our great nation.
- Vote for change!
- [crowd] Vote for change!
Thank you all!
- [cheers and applause]
- [camera shutters clicking]
[staff] Mr. Kim, over here.
- How have you been?
- Fine, sir.
- And Ms. Minji?
- Oh, we're both working in Statistics.
It's been hell.
[chuckles]
The Reconstruction Bureau,
it's almost finalized.
The discussion shouldn't take much longer.
Not Home Affairs,
the Reconstruction Bureau?
Yes, that's correct.
Please be in touch.
[soft chuckle]
- Take care of yourself.
- You too, sir.
[camera shutter clicks]
Director Jeong is waiting.
I should be getting back
to the office then.
Why is it so hard to get ahold of you?
I've been busy. You're doing well?
You know where General Choi Hanrim is,
don't you?
No, I don't know where he is.
I'll believe you.
Mr. An Kichul wants to see you.
Listen, the ball's in your court.
See you when I see you.
[Professor Hwang] Wow.
Do you really think we can pull this off?
Opposition party observers and reporters,
they'll be everywhere.
Let's get more people.
No, we can only use
people we really trust.
There's an alleyway on this side, here.
- It goes from there to there.
- [Han Soo] Okay.
[Professor Hwang] Let's see.
There's a tunnel right there.
- If someone can stall them in front of it…
- [door opens]
…you could get there in 20,
if you really hurry.
Ah.
A tunnel! What do you know!
So the girl's got a knack
for robbery then.
Can I trust someone like you in here
with the safe?
Can I head home now?
Sure, you've earned your meal. Hmm?
- Go see a movie.
- Uncle Samsik.
[Doochill] Hmm?
When did you get here?
I've been here for a while.
You're stealing the ballot boxes?
No, not at all.
I have something to tell you.
Let's have a smoke.
[Professor Hwang grunts]
[lighter rasping]
We're making preparations just in case.
Don't go through with it.
The old and new factions are discussing
the parliamentary lineup.
It's all empty promises.
I told you not to trust
any of the things that they say.
Do you really think
Sun Wooseok will keep his word?
They'll fight for bigger pieces of the pie
until the party splits. You'll see.
Why do you think I suggested
the parliamentary reform?
It's risk-free and gives us the advantage.
Huh?
Do you think we're doing this
for Kang Seongmin?
[Kim San sighs]
Stealing ballot boxes is dangerous.
- Don't do it.
- [sighs]
It's fine as long as we're discreet.
Listen, you have nothing
to lose here, Minister.
If the Liberals win,
we introduce a parliamentary system.
And if the Democrats win, you get
your National Reconstruction Bureau.
[exhales]
Is that why you came here?
I think General Choi Hanrim
is in contact
with commanders of other units.
And you don't know where he is?
We said no secrets.
I thought we were on the same page.
Hanmin is meeting the other officers
on General Choi's behalf.
[sighs]
- So they're really committed to the coup?
- Rachael came to see me earlier.
She said An Kichul wanted to meet.
Rachael?
What should I do?
Should I take the meeting?
What does she want now,
that little pufferfish?
March 15, 1960
Seoul, South Korea
[reporter 2] March 15th.
Since this morning, there's been a steady
stream of citizens casting their ballots.
In light of the recent espionage
allegations against Mr. Choo Intae,
the election is expected to be
a close call.
Many political commentators are predicting
that this election results will be decided
by the inner city voters
who strongly support the Democratic Party.
Support for the Democratic Party
is particularly high
in the 20 major districts
around the capital.
Even after the allegations
against Choo Intae,
these voters have not wavered
in their support of the candidate.
By many estimates,
the Liberal Party's immediate goal
is to diminish the Democratic Party's
overwhelming lead in major cities.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Mister Kwangmin.
- I wanted to ask--
- I'm sorry, I have nothing to say.
- My father, he--
- I'm very sorry.
I'm really scared right now.
Please stay away.
You better not be caught this time around.
If it seems even a little dangerous,
leave the ballot boxes
and get out of there.
If you're caught this time,
I can't save you.
[sighs]
Okay.
By the way, who's this new guy?
It's his buddy, Jongchul introduced him.
Right. Yes, he's my brother.
- [Han Soo] Right.
- Oh.
You're related?
- Right. He's my older brother.
- Yes, we can trust him.
All right, just be careful. Huh?
Here, pass them out.
[manager] There's a map.
Take a good look at the locations.
Memorize these spots.
Democratic Party
[Sun] Yeah, yeah.
You're getting accurate vote counts
from each district, right?
- [staff] Yes, we are.
- [assemblyman] Yes, sir.
Okay. Feeling good, right?
[chortling]
You've checked all 20 locations,
- haven't you?
- Yes.
You can do this?
Well, damn, I gotta.
[♪ ominous music playing]
Jeong Hanmin met with officers
on General Choi Hanrim's behalf,
didn't he?
He came to see me too.
[sighs]
- [telephone ringing]
- [staff] Chairman, there's a call for you.
Thank you.
This is Committee Chairman, Kim San.
San, are you busy?
I'm supposed to stay until results are in.
Can you come to the Banya Hotel?
Is it urgent?
Banya Hotel
[Hanmin] San.
Did you vote yet?
What's going on?
What is this?
The plans to relocate troops.
We'll take control of Gyeongmudae,
Army HQ, broadcast stations,
and key institutions.
If we block the streets,
it will take half a day.
But we can't afford to have
an indecisive commander
at this critical moment.
Hmm?
When the time comes, I'll decide.
Decide what?
Let's meet with Jang Doosik later.
You tell him
it's on General Choi's orders.
I think that… we can convince Doosik.
Why the hesitation?
It will take half a day.
How will you handle the repercussions?
That's why we need General Choi Hanrim
- to be the face of the operation.
- Hey.
[whispers]
You want the general to take the fall?
We're prepared for this.
You and I
can start a new era.
[♪ tense music playing]
Is that what San told you?
Yes.
Just now.
[Kim San] Well done, Hanmin.
[Hanmin] Well done.
General Choi Hanrim is under our control.
What do you mean?
General Choi isn't making any moves.
The field officers from each unit
are also staying put.
Yeah, so?
We could… do this all on our own.
We could take over South Korea.
God, you're a lunatic. Let's go.
[Hanmin chuckles]
I never said any of those things.
Is any politician
more talented than you are?
And is there a general out there
more competent than me?
Competence alone
doesn't make the world go round.
It's not possible.
It is if we have General Choi on our side.
Yeah, he may be General Choi,
but what can we do with someone
who is currently being investigated?
Well, we have Albright too.
General Choi is also popular
with the Americans.
You're not making any sense.
Cheongwoo wants special laws
regarding industrial complexes.
And you want the Reconstruction Bureau,
don't you?
I'm saying we can get all that at once.
Hanmin.
Let's just stick to Uncle Samsik's plan.
Why is he so special?
Why should we do whatever he says?
[Hyunseok] "Take advantage of General Choi
and stage a coup d'état"?
Yeah.
And you went along with it?
I told him it was a preposterous plan.
You used General Choi's name
to get all the officers together.
Aren't you the one who called me?
[Hanmin] Welcome.
Thank you, sir.
55th Howitzer Regiment, Captain Lee Sooil.
55th Howitzer Regiment, Captain Lee Sooil?
Okay, come in.
That's right.
- That's when we first met.
- [slams on table]
General, please,
I think we should wait a little longer.
You can achieve what you want
without going through with the coup.
If you continue to stall,
you'll lose your chance.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[Hanmin] General.
What's the matter?
Your location's been compromised.
You're in danger here.
I'll escort you to the bunker.
General Choi's at the bunker,
I just took him over there.
Has he made a decision?
Yes.
- Where is General Choi?
- The General's inside. Please follow me.
Victory.
[♪ suspenseful music continues playing]
I did plan the troops' relocation,
but the overall plan
was all Samsik's idea.
The 55th Howitzers, the 3rd Marines,
and 12th Airborne Brigade
will move into the capital region.
The Capital Defense can block roads
around the Han River,
if they do, our mission will be a success.
In 12 hours, it will be done.
By which point, our troops
will have already been deployed.
They should… stand by for now.
Don't you see what happened?
Kim San set everything up
from the very beginning.
Who would think
to exploit General Choi like that?
He's the only one.
Fuck! This is why we need
to turn the world upside down.
Hanmin.
Don't talk about it, make it happen.
[sighs]
Yeah, then what?
Will you join me?
That depends on what you do.
From the beginning, those bastards…
were always planning to betray us.
- From the beginning.
- [sighs]
They'd always planned to use General Choi.
That's quite the story you got.
You should have been a writer, huh?
Jeong Hanmin is a real motivated man,
but I can't see him acting by himself.
Who's the brains behind this?
Kim San was always against the coup.
I believe anybody can change their mind.
[Doosik] Kim San is the one
who planned this coup d'état.
Kim San, his greed got the better of him.
That man is not innocent.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
I'm telling you right now, I can save you.
[Doosik] Samsik…
everything I'm saying is true.
[chuckles]
General Jang Doosik was appointed
Commander of Capital Defense.
[Doosik chuckles]
Lieutenant Colonel Jeong Hanmin,
Capital Defense Unit.
They decided to promote me two ranks,
to Lieutenant Colonel.
- Do your best.
- Commander, thank you.
I was named
Deputy Commander of Capital Defense.
[Doosik]
We've been rewarded for our efforts.
Jeong Hanmin and myself.
Who is the person
who didn't stand to gain anything?
It's Kim San, isn't it?
Who do you think
went to the Albright Foundation
and suggested General Choi?
[♪ suspenseful music continues playing]
Hello, thank you for meeting us.
I'm Rachael Jeong
of the Albright Foundation.
Oh, nice to meet you.
- Is General Choi here?
- Yes, he's waiting for you upstairs.
Shall we?
Whose idea do you think it was
to use Choi Hanrim?
Rachael.
Samsik can't know about you…
about you meeting General Doosik today.
He trusts me, I have to tell him.
It's the only way.
Albright…
Who benefits from having Choi Hanrim
dragged into it?
You can choose me,
and the Albright Foundation is yours.
Welcome, sir. I'm An Kichul.
[Kim San] I've heard a lot about you.
I'm Kim San.
- Nice to finally meet you.
- Yes, nice to meet you.
Please sit.
[door creaks, closes]
Résumé: Choi Hanrim
[exhales deeply]
Is parliamentary reform possible?
Personally, I don't think it is.
I don't care
if it's a parliamentary system
or a presidential one.
All that I really want
is to make South Korea a wealthy nation.
I share your thoughts on the matter.
Then do you think General Choi Hanrim
is a worthwhile investment for us?
Take Cheongwoo's capital,
the Albright Foundation's network,
and add to that
General Choi's leadership and reputation,
why wouldn't he be good for us?
What about Uncle Samsik's plans?
[breathes deeply]
[chuckles]
Who would take a dirt road
when you could just take the freeway?
Sounds good.
Really?
[scoffs]
How interesting.
Who benefits from having Choi Hanrim
dragged into it?
All right,
so An Kichul stole our plans in the end.
And Jang Doosik betrayed us all.
What more is there to say?
Even then…
I never agreed with the coup d'état.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[knocks on door]
Ah, you're here.
Are you startled?
Why…
[clears throat]
What are you doing here, General?
I brought him here.
I asked him to.
[Rachael] Petron Harvest is going to send
a secondary investigation team
to the Philippines.
So we've run out of time.
There's a chance that everything
we've been working toward will disappear.
That's why we've come
to a kind of agreement on this issue.
Lieutenant Colonel Jeong
has already enlisted
the commanders of key units.
55th Howitzer Regiment,
3rd Marine Regiment,
and 12th Airborne Brigade.
55th Howitzer Regiment,
3rd Marine Regiment,
12th Airborne Brigade.
You've been busy going around
abusing General Choi's name.
It was thanks to you
that I heard about the coup.
[Sooil] Thank you.
Jeong Hanmin.
I was against the coup d'état
until the very end.
If the Democratic Party won the election--
[Hyunseok] Would they still win
after Samsik stole the ballots?
The Democratic Party
was set to win the election!
Why would I stage a coup d'état?
- [♪ tense music playing]
- [sighs]
It's time for you and your generation
to lead our country.
And I'm willing to be a stepping stone.
You're someone I can trust.
- Kim San, I really need your help.
- General.
The Democratic Party will win
this election no matter what.
And then you'll be reinstated.
We'll establish the Reconstruction Bureau.
There's no need for us
to stage a coup d'état.
You shouldn't stand by
and let them deceive you.
[♪ tense music continues playing]
Jeong Hanmin told a different story.
General Choi was first…
brought up at the US Army club.
The day the military reform declaration
was issued.
The declaration I wrote.
Yes.
We first discussed him that day.
- [Kwangmin] Hey.
- [Hanmin] Hey, Harrison.
Did you hear?
It's a mess out there.
What's the matter?
Oh, the younger officers
issued a declaration.
[Hanmin] About what?
See for yourself.
[sighs]
"We condemn all factions, corruption,
and political activities
within the military.
We will discipline all military personnel
involved in fraudulent elections.
We will enforce punishments
on generals involved in corruption.
We demand new reform within the military."
[Hanmin] Did you see this?
- No, show me.
- [Hanmin] Here.
[Harrison] Do you know who Choi Hanrim is?
He's the general of the First Infantry.
I hear the military are planning a coup
with him as their leader.
What will you do
if General Choi stages a coup?
What can I do, huh?
What? You wouldn't join him?
- What?
- There's no one like him in South Korea.
Whether he stages a coup or doesn't…
he's going to do what's right.
[♪ tense music playing]
Kim San said that General Choi
was unrivaled in Korea
and that we should join the coup with him
Is that really what Hanmin said?
Yes.
That was just an emotional response.
I've never tried to seize power
or steal anyone else's position.
My only goal was to establish
the National Reconstruction Bureau.
[♪ tense music continues playing]
[Michael]
The military looks set to appoint
a new First Operations Commander.
A new commander?
General Choi Hanrim is highly regarded
within the military.
He's also very close
with the US Army Commander.
- Choi Hanrim?
- First Infantry Commander Choi Hanrim.
I've heard of him too.
[♪ tense music intensifies]
We need to keep an eye on him.
All of us do.
We can bribe the National Assembly…
not the military.
So you think it's difficult,
but not impossible?
[Doochill] That day, An Kichul
was already planning on staging a coup
with Choi Hanrim at the helm.
And we didn't have the slightest inkling.
- [knocks on door]
- [door opens]
He just fell asleep.
[Kichul]
He was in critical condition last night.
[Doochill] I see.
He's going to pull through.
Do you think I'll do well?
Huh?
What… Ah, of course.
To be honest, I'm a little scared.
Scared that I'll ruin everything
my father has achieved.
Well, I'll assist you where I can.
His influence over the Federation
has been too great.
[Doochill] Once we reform the system,
that'll be over.
[inhales deeply]
[exhales sharply]
Is parliamentary reform possible?
Yes.
[Yosub] Don't do…
anything dangerous.
We need… parliamentary reform first.
Start with that.
[Yosub groans]
Father, I don't think
parliamentary reform is possible.
[Yosub] Reform…
parliament…
and get Kang Seongmin…
and Samsik.
Get them…
- [gasping breaths]
- [Kichul] Father.
[Yosub groans]
I'll take care of it.
Don't you try…
to stage…
a coup.
Swear to me.
- Mr. An has… he's passed away.
- [Cheongwoo members sigh]
[Cheongwoo member 1]
I'm sorry, my condolences.
[Kichul] Thank you.
[Cheongwoo member 2]
God, I can't believe it.
This is just…
[lighter rasping]
[sighs]
That kid, An Kichul…
[Doochill] He used Rachael as bait
to seduce our friend, Kim San.
- [Kim San] How are you?
- I'm well. How are you though?
Not bad.
Well, it seems like everywhere we go,
- you seem to be the talk of the town.
- Yes, I know. I feel uneasy.
I'll see you around then.
[Doochill] Luring Kim San to Room 806
at the Banya Hotel
was all part of Kichul's plan.
Actually, Mr. Kim.
Why don't the two of us
have dinner tonight?
[Rachael] Mr. Kim.
You are well acquainted
with General Choi, correct?
[clears throat]
Yes, I am.
General Choi is in Room 806.
- Here?
- [Michael] Right now.
[Doochill]
Kichul used the Albright Foundation
to drag Kim San into the mess.
It's a method I've often used,
so I know it well.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Good evening, sir.
Thank you for being here.
Thank you for having me.
Capital Defense Unit, General Min Soochul.
My name is Kim San.
General Choi Hanrim was my idea.
[Kim San] What?
I'm the one that chose you too.
I think South Korea lacks the capacity
to become a democracy right now.
That's why we need an incredible leader.
That's the dream I've had
since I came to Korea.
To make a great leader for us.
Samsik can't know about you…
about you meeting General Doosik today.
Let me deal with that.
[Doochill] And then,
Kichul tempted Kim San
with that pufferfish of a broad.
- Full of poison…
- Why is it so hard to get ahold of you?
- I've been busy.
- …and swishing her pretty tail.
You know where General Choi Hanrim is,
don't you?
No, I don't know where he is.
I'll believe you.
Rachael came to see me earlier.
She said An Kichul wanted to meet.
Rachael?
What should I do?
Should I take the meeting?
What does she want now,
that little pufferfish?
[Doochill] Kim San told me everything.
Who would An Kichul even know
in the military to plan a coup with?
Just think about it.
The military, politicians, Albright.
They all have one thing in common.
[Doosik] Kim San.
- He's the only one it could be.
- Well done.
South Korea…
isn't capable of becoming a democracy.
You know that.
[Doosik] We didn't know it at the time.
Kim San is sticking right by his side.
Yeah, of course he is.
That's why we're here tonight.
[Doosik] Kim San planned the whole thing.
Don't you get it?
[Kim San] How did it go?
I found a place we can keep
the general safe.
Kim San. What are you doing down here?
I'm here to escort you from here, sir.
Follow me.
Shall we?
- Sure.
- Yes.
Why are you so protective of him?
I think it's time to head back.
[exhales sharply]
Don't you think it was San
who took advantage of Hanmin?
I can tell just by looking at him.
The Minister doesn't use other people.
Not like I do.
Our dear Minister is a pure soul.
His dreams are all he thinks about.
So don't you think
he would go after his dreams
no matter the cost?
[sighs]
Everything went wrong.
Did you meet An Kichul
on February 12, 1960?
Yes, I believe so.
- Who proposed the coup d'état once again?
- [sighs]
That was me, sir.
Who had the initial plan
to manipulate General Choi Hanrim?
That was all my idea.
Exactly!
[slams on table]
Did you remove General Choi
in order to stage a coup?
Yes, because I couldn't stand
seeing him called a spy!
[footsteps]
So you've been here all along?
Minister.
[Doochill] Minister, that's you, isn't it?
[sighs]
I thought I'd never see you again.
I'm being investigated.
My God,
why did you have to be so stubborn?
I told you not to trust
anything Wooseok said.
But you were blinded by your dream
of the Reconstruction Bureau
and you ignored me entirely, didn't you?
- [sharp inhale]
- [Hanmin screaming in the distance]
[Hanmin] No, no, no!
I was right, wasn't I?
Minister?
[Doosik] Let's get this over with.
Go have a drink.
[Doochill] Minister, I was right,
wasn't I?
[Kim San] Yes.
I'm sorry for being so stubborn, Uncle.
It's so great to hear your voice.
[sighs]
[♪ closing theme music playing]