Then should we have some fun?
Behind you!
Everyone, do you want more?
- Do you want more?
- Yes!
Are you ready?
Why... why are you acting like this to me, really?
You called me.
Me? I didn't call you.
You did. From a long time ago.
From a long time ago, I didn't know you.
It's okay. You know me now.
Excuse me. I really don't like cold, rough, or beastly men.
It's okay. I like you.
Why does he keep saying that it's okay? I'm not okay!
Since I already took care of the annoying things, play with me now.
- Why would I do that?
- Because you called me!
I'm telling you I didn't call you! Seriously!
Can you please not come towards me? I'm going to use violence too!
Don't come toward me! I'm telling you don't come toward me! Don't! Wait!
Don't move.
That's right. You're doing well, you're doing well.
Now, turn around slowly.
That's right! Good boy.
Now stay still like that. Just like that. Stay still.
Stay still like that. You are so well-behaved!
Taxi! Taxi!
Taxi!
Ahjussi, can you go with full speed to Kanghan Hospital?
Please...
Someone is chasing us. Does he have a death wish or what?
He is crazy! What to do with him!
Kill Me, Heal Me
Kanghan Hospital
Episode 2
Wait!
Don't move!
I don't want to play pets now. Since I played with you, you have to play with me now.
You're all grown-up now! Why are you asking me to play with you?
What are we going to do? Are we going to play with strings or stones?
We can think about that on our way. I don't have that much time right now.
Am I a person who have time deposited in some bank vault that I can withdraw and use?
I'm a busy person as well. A busy person!
I am different from you. I don't know when I'm going to appear.
No... What is he saying? Is he some Crown Prince that escaped from the palace?
Are you possibly, on parole?
It's a place that is harder to escape from than the palace or jail, and is ten thousand times more cramped. Get on.
Please really stop now. I really have to go to the hospital. Okay?
That's enough, please give me a break! I already told you I don't like rascals like you!
I really don't like hospitals.
Take off your clothes. When I saw you fight before, you bled a lot. I will look at your wounds.
Don't we have to go in?
By judging Doctor Oh's screams, she isn't hating it.
Wear your pants! I didn't tell you to take off everything!
You told me to take off my clothes. Do I have to put them back on?
Can you look down?
Psychology Department
Oh Ri Jin
You are a psychiatrist? That isn't good.
You and I could have a bad fate.
Oh my! Did you just find that out now?
What are you doing right now? Excuse me!
Excuse me. What are you doing right now?
Excuse me.
See, this is my name.
Shin Se Gi
Remember this, until you die.
I'm getting goosebumps.
Excuse me, Shin Se Gi. I told you countless times that you are not my type.
Remember. The person who has my face but has a different name is fake.
There is only one Shin Se Gi, who has this face.
I'm the only one. So you
have to remember my eyes.
I'm done treating you, so you can go now. Bye!
Doctor Park!
Is there anything I can help you with?
Should I stand in on your shift or help you with your dissertation?
Look at how this wretch is rolling her brain.
Hey. Why are you coming now?
This brat, you're just finding a way out when you've lost your patient!
From now on, know that you won't be off for a while.
You must want to die.
Can I take her out for a little while?
Take her out.
What?!
- By all means, take her out.
Doctor Oh, what are you doing, not getting ready to go out?
He's waiting! Quickly.
Put on some makeup prettily and wear pretty clothes. You don't have to come in today.
- Excuse me, Doctor Park-
- Hurry and change into some pretty clothes.
Doctor Park! Doctor Park! It's not like that!
You should have told me earlier.
No, Doctor!
Oh Ri Jin
Secretary Ahn Gook
Yes, Secretary Ahn, what's the matter?
I found Doctor Seok Ho Pil.
Really?
That's great. Which hospital is it?
Kanghan Hospital
I realized it for the first time at that time. That there was a monster inside me.
The punk's name is, Shin Se Gi. He's the same age as me and...
Yes?
...he's very violent and has a savage personality.
Who is this? Cha Do Hyun!
It's been a while, Doctor.
I was waiting for you after getting a call from Secretary Ahn anyway. Wow~ How long has it been?
I'm happy to see you. I'm really happy to see you!
Are you really happy to see me?
Of course, I am. When did you get back?
You tried to kill me through different ways.
Why would I be happy to see you?
Shin Se Gi?
It's taking longer than expected.
Go back first, Secretary Ahn. I'll go home after meeting Doctor Park.
The blade is very sharp.
Isn't it cool? If I give it to Yo Sub as a present, he'll really like it.
You know Yo Sub well, right?
He's the personality of a 17 year old boy who's living in your body, right?
That's right. He's a fellow obsessed with suicide.
I'm going to give this as a present for staying quietly all this time.
Well, I could use this on you before that.
What is it you want to say?
Tell Cha Do Hyun that he should give up on the amalgation treatment completely.
To also not think about getting rid of us,
interfering with us,
and getting in our way.
If Mr. Cha doesn't give up on the treatment, what will you do then?
Then you should make a move.
Put Cha Do Hyun to sleep.
So that he can't wake up... forever.
That's something impossible.
So?
Mr. Cha is your owner.
You are only one of the alternate personalities he created as a defense mechanism.
Shut your trap.
I am me.
Not Cha Do Hyun, but Shin Se Gi.
If you try to get that guy and I fuse into one,
or make this guy remember his lost past,
then... Yo Sub will use my present very properly.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
If we die, Cha Do Hyun will die and disappear with us.
You pathetic...
Guys!
D-doctor. Doctor! Doctor!
What's going on?
Se Gi,
Se Gi came and left.
Are you alright?
Huh? Ah, I'm alright, I'm alright.
My neck is thicker than most people.
My nickname is "Toad", "Thick Necked Toad".
Anyway,
I think Se Gi has gotten stronger.
How should I put it? Although I can't make a judgement right away,
he wants to be the owner of all the personalities, you included.
Are those words saying that he wants to get rid of me?
He asked me to put you to sleep. So that you can't wake up forever.
It's certain that he has an objective.
That objective is making him stronger.
But he said something very notable.
He said he found his first love or something?
It's possible for personalities to love, too?
Of course, it's possible.
However in a case with a violent personality like him,
he can mistake violence and obsession for someone as love.
Also, in the case that he cannot get the other person's heart, that affection, can be changed into violence.
If it comes to that, the other person will be in extreme danger.
He said he found his first love or something?
No way, Chae Yeon?
Yes.
Mom? Yeah, I'm doing well.
Doctor Oh! Aren't you on duty today?
You're so pretty today.
I'm doing well.
Ah, seriously. But why isn't he coming out? I'm going to run into all the hospital employees.
Excuse me...
Excuse me!
Excuse me, I know it's rude, but who are you?
"Although it's rude, who are you?"?
I mean... If you know it's something rude, why would you ask that?
She's a very~ dangerous woman. She's a megalomaniac.
Oh, yes. You came back to the hospital safely.
I see. hat's a relief. That's really a relief.
Uhmmm... Be strong.
But I have to go somewhere urgently. I'm sorry.
Wait a moment!
That's it?
Then what else...?
I really didn't want to say this,
but from the club, you were the one who followed me around like your life depended on it, saying that you like me! It wasn't me!
Wait a moment! Wait a moment.
Get your grip tighter and calm down. Listen to me.
Oh. Yes.
That's why you misunderstood.
Misunderstood?
I'm sorry. To a person who is already hurt, I caused more pain...
Wait. Who are you saying is hurt?
I understand that hospital life must be difficult, but I hope that you overcome it. Be strong.
Be strong. Be strong. But I really have somewhere to go, so I'm really sorry.
I'm very sorry. I'm sorry.
What is this? Was I just rejected?
What kind of pathetic melodrama is this!
- Vice-President!
- Secretary Ahn, how are you here?
What happened?
Se Gi threatened the professor.
- What?
- I will tell you the details later. I need to use your car.
What?
Um...
Remember. The time that I fell for you...
Oh, yes. That's why you misunderstood.
Please, Chae Yeon. Answer your phone! Please answer it!
Hey, Cha Do Hyun, where did you run off to?
Oh, Chae Yeon.
Oh my! Did you get in a fight?
I thought that you were a good student who only used your fist to grab pencils.
You even know how to use it to beat people up?
I have something to say.
Is it important?
I hope that you consider it like that.
Go on.
From now on, if I surprise you with words and actions that aren't like myself, ignore me.
What?
If I treat you badly or visit you late at night,
or call you to come out, or cross the line that I must not cross...
If I do those things, that's not me.
Are you drunk?
If someone who has my face has a different name,
or does things that I don't usually do, that's not me. Run away as far as you can.
If I don't let you run away, just hit me. You can hit me until I lose consciousness.
- Hey, Cha Do Hyun.
- Chae Yeon, which wine do you want me to open?
I was having a glass of wine with Ki Joon Oppa. Do you want to continue inside?
Oh, it's okay. I'm done. I'll leave now.
Chae Yeon.
Last Christmas, thank you for calling me.
Thanks to you, my Christmas was warm.
I was happy.
This woman is so fearless.
After having me in a shower gown over here, how can you call Do Hyun?
Who is the person who just shouted out that you are here?
This is a territorial fight between men. It's a type of howling.
Oh, so I'm your territory?
You're enjoying this.
A man's pure love is women's dreams.
How should I say it? It's fancy and meaningful,
but it's also like a supplement book that fills the 2% missing in the main volume?
Does Do Hyun know that you are a fox?
If he finds out, he will be more interested. It's sexier than the concept of a childhood friend.
I think that Se Gi grew stronger.
He must have gotten an objective.
The objective will make him stronger.
Make Cha Do Hyun fall asleep forever.
So that he can't wake up.
Listen Shin Se Gi. If you touch any of my people, you're dead. Do you understand?
I would rather die to get rid of you. If I'm not alive, you're not either. If you become stronger, I will become stronger!
Are you listening to me, Shin Se Gi? Are you listening to me, you bastard?
Bastard...
From now on, I'm going to start working at ID Entertainment.
Please prepare the financial reports, income statements, and current business condition report of ID Entertainment for the past 3 years,
and the plan for next year. Also the profiles of the employees and the company's artists, without leaving anyone out.
Did you decide to stay?
If he has a goal, even if I go back to America,
he will get on the plane again. Then there is only one solution.
I am not going to run away.
I have to face him directly.
My short term goal is the board meeting in three months.
Until then, nothing can happen to me.
So I need to have the newest technology
that can watch and control him.
Wake up at 6:50 AM
While I'm asleep, I will lock myself in the house using secured lock devices.
January 8th, 2015, woke up at 6:50 AM.
While I am awake, I will make sure that a security camera watches me.
Exercise at 7:00
I need a room to exercise. When I get stressed or feel nervous,
they can attack me.
I need keep my emotions and condition at a normal level all the time.
Lastly, I need a secret physician.
Since Se Gi attacked the professor, it could be dangerous to ask him to treat me.
Look for a secret physician that can replace him.
But he must be a person who can take his secret to his grave.
I will keep your secret until I die, so tell me.
How did you escape?
Ms. Heo Seok Hee! If you don't take your medicine and keep on refusing treatment like this, you're going to be delaying your discharge. Do you want that?
This place and my house are both prison.
There are only doctors in my house and the hospital.
All the doctors in my house are going crazy because they can't make me a doctor,
and the doctors in my hospital are going crazy because they can't make me their patient.
Doctor Oh, did you have experience to study six more years in order to enter medical school?
I don't think that's a thing that people do.
I just want to live while dancing. Is that something that is considered crazy?
So, why don't we just go together one day?
If you take your medicine well and get treatment, I'll go with you.
-Really?
- Really.
-When?
- How about when I am off?
Then we can go today. You are off today!
- Why are you surprised?
- Your eyes!
Yes, people kept telling me that I look like a Siberian Husky, so I changed my eyes.
It's twilight burgundy color. It's popular in the clubs nowadays.
Are you sure?
Of course. It's EXO Baekhyun's makeup during the Seoul Music Awards. Don't you know?
You don't know. So lame. But you have a talent of booking a man.
Booking? Who? Me?
Stop denying it, Doctor Oh Ri Jin. It's already spreading throughout the hospital.
- Hello.
They said that you found a man while looking for a patient, but was rejected after two hours.
Serves you right!
They say that a maggot can roll around.
Not in my wildest dreams would I think that Doctor Oh has a genius talent in finding men.
And she was even rejected after two hours!
Our Doctor Oh has to go all the way till the end. She is very fierce, like a general!
As I see it, she failed in playing hard to get. When that man tried to take off his pants,
she was screaming at him to hurry up and put his clothes on, but she was saying something entirely different on the inside!
Hey, hey! She is pitiful. Treat her nicely. Do you think that she dated before?
Why haven't she? We should take care of her. She might get PTSD (Post-Traumatic Stress Disorder) from this.
She is denying the fact that she got rejected.
Hey, but is there an opened window? Why did it become so cold all of a sudden?
It's not booking!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Doctor Oh, aren't you off today?
He was the one who followed me because he liked me, and he was the one who disappeared because he is busy,
and when he played around, I never went along with him. So it's not booking!
Oh, Doctor Oh! These were the clothes that the man you booked was wearing, right?
The cleaner told me to give it to you.
It's not booking!
Recycle Bin
Salvatore Bocchetti
Made in Italy
Shin Se Gi.
Don't try to speak up just because you were wronged.
If you keep saying that you were wronged, you will just resent that person more.
So the elder said,
"Turn that feeling of being wronged into a door leading to asceticism."
The person you are trying to reach is not answering the phone...
I was rejected. Yes, I was.
Recycling Bin
Yes, this is not lingering feelings or expectation.
I just want to join the 'CSER(Ah Na Ba Da) campaign*'. Why?
(*Conserve, Share, Exchange, Reuse)
Because it's not fake leather but real leather. Why?
Because it's made in Italy!
Oh my!
It's your father!
You're here! What is this?
Is it a gift to me? Let's see!
Ah! This is not yours! It's not yours! Give it back!
Father! I said it's not yours!
Hey, how is it? It suits me, right?
What do you mean, you look good? It looks cheap now that you've worn it.
You seem to be very satisfied.
Yeah! I know, I know... Take it off quickly.
Now that you're here on your day-off and
you even brought a present for your father. You grew a lot.
This is very vintage. I really like it.
And look at this. Doesn't it look like real bloodstain?
They even made these kind of details!
Wow, the leather from Italy is very high quality.
Dad, I will put my life on the line and say this. This is too small for you.
It's not small. It's not.
Honey! Have you chopped all the firewood?
Ri Jin!
Mom!
Omo!
When did you arrive?
I just came! Were you well?
I was well, of course.
I missed you!
Your father caught a wild pig so that he can make a barbecue for you.
Yay!
Honey, have you chopped the firewood yet?
Honey! You're going to chop the firewood, right?
I'll chop them in a moment! You go in first... go in, go in.
Let's go in. Are you hungry?
I'm hungry, I'm hungry!
Honey... This doesn't go up.
It's too small!
Dad is still the same.
Still the same? He is getting better every day.
He still think he's a young master of super rich family who runs a brewery. He squandered away almost all his fortune long time ago.
He just liked people and helped everyone.
He's probably going to be like that, acting like a young child, for the rest of his life until he dies.
Why? That's our father's biggest strength and charm.
If everyone in the world is like Dad, our department won't even exist in the hospital.
Women who take care of people like your father will make sure that the psychological department doesn't end, so don't worry.
But why is Ri On so quiet? Did he go somewhere?
I don't know. He tortured himself writing his novel at daybreak. He's quiet now, so he must be sleeping.
Can you stop your brother from writing mystery novels?
He only talks about people dying.
He writes his own books and cannot sleep at night because he gets nightmares.
Really?
Is he stupid?
Lonely man...
My heart almost dropped!
Are you an item thief?
Who sent you? Is it the next publisher? Is it Eiru Media?
Could it be, Jerry Bruckheimer, that punk?
Your mother sent me so that you can eat.
Oh Ri On came down.
I came.
Look at your dark circles. You are a panda, not a human!
How many people did you kill yesterday?
I killed about two people.
I have two children, and they all do things that just hurts the parents.
I'm scared that one will get hurt by her patients,
and I'm scared that his mind will get ruined by doing that.
Ri Jin, since you are off, give your brother consultation.
Our family is already excellent. What do you need a physician for?
The beginning and end to the health of the mind is the happiness of the family.
Wow, wow. Are we going to do a public service advertisement now?
Come outside and help me with the fire.
I finished with the firewood. It's too cold.
But where did you get the jacket? It's totally awesome!
Here.
Ah.
This. Put it here.
Wow.
Here are the beers!
Yeah! It's the beer made by Dad!
- Wow!
- Beer, beer!
- Me too! Me too!
- Here's one for you, Mom!
Oh, it's cold!
Shall we toast?
Should we? Toasting is nice. Here, cheers!
- Cheers!
- For everyone's health!
For health!
Coffee Gallery
The stars are nice.
If you finished eating, you should go in and sleep. Why are you drinking coffee so late at night? You should be resting.
Are you going to work all night again?
Yeah. I have to sleep after killing at least two more people.
I heard that you are not able to sleep because you get nightmares.
Aren't you getting too into it?
Did the consultation begin?
I don't know how this will sound to a writer,
but you have to differentiate between reality and the imaginary world.
If you get too into it, in the world that you created,
you can get hurt.
Aigoo, aigoo, aigoo... Don't worry, this Oppa knows to properly do that.
Why do you think that I decided to become a mystery writer with the pen name Omega?
By the way I see it, it's unnecessary.
Listen well, Doctor.
As Omega, I am a writer with a mystic identity who writes mystery novels
and lives a homme fatale lifestyle.
But as Oh Ri On...
Right there...like that burning star over there,
I'm a freed soul.
And my life as Oh Hwi-
When did you become three? Who is Hwi?
I sometimes use it to seduce women.
Oh Ri On is sounds like a name of a chocolate cookie, (There's an Orion ChocoChip cookies)
so those women call me Oh Hwi.
Oh...
End of counseling.
You have split personality.
I'm saying that I can live a safe, comfortable and pleasant life
by defining myself into different people.
Just like...
Jekyll and Hyde.
There is only one Shin Se Gi with this face.
What?
I'm the only one.
W-wait a minute.
-What is it? What is this tension? What is this?
- What?
What are you doing?
Ah...
It's nothing.
But...
if you live while separating yourself into different people,
is it fun?
Rather than saying that it's fun, it's a way to protect yourself
from this cruel world. It could be the heart's strategy.
It is something like that.
What?
- What?
What? what? what?
What? What? What?
There is only one Shin Se Gi with this face.
I'm the only one.
So, you...
don't forget about my eyes.
Be strong.
Be strong. But I really have to go somewhere. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
He is different. The eyes...
You came?
You came earlier than expected.
Yeah.
Did anything happen overnight?
Fortunately, it's been quiet for the past few days.
According to my record, I never lost consciousness or time.
Although what's important is what's going to happen from now on.
Then can we proceed with the board meeting as planned?
Aigoo, Chairwoman.
Hello, Uncle.
I should have visited you to give my greetings, but I meet you like this.
No. That greeting isn't that urgent.
To a child who must not have been even adjust to the time difference yet
after quickly wrapping up his life in the States, having the board meeting on his first day,
would be too harsh, don't you think, Chairwoman?
For the company and for himself,
it's a sound judgement to start working as fast as possible.
You worry too much.
Even though ID Entertainment is just a new venture for Seung Jin Group,
isn't the Vice-President title too burdensome for a child who's just starting?
Because President Cha Ki Joon has already laid out the foundation for him well,
he will learn from you.
Since he was burdened with an important position, he
will become more responsible.
You can go up first. We will use a different elevator.
Then do so.
The door is closing.
Don't fall for his smile.
A good-natured persona, a considerate persona, and a benevolent persona,
they are all his disguises. That is his strategy.
The more a person has dark ambitions, he hides his true self.
Oh, nice shot!
I'm always touched by your skill. What is your strategy?
It's not enough to always just hit the ball perfectly.
Sometimes, the ball sets it up itself.
Anyway, the start isn't so bad today.
Yes, that's right. It's there. Seung Jin Group!
No, he's not the President yet.
The Vice-President of ID Entertainment.
Ay... why don't you get me?
ID Entertainment. ID Entertainment!
Let's go first.
Honey! Even if my son is the only future successor of Seung Jin Group,
how can he swallow it all in one shot? There are also some intended for others.
I told him to earn his position, starting slowly from the bottom.
Aigoo, fine. I will buy you not only one meal, but two,
so just find the date.
Hey, Dong Seo! (wife of her husband's brother)
I'll talk to you later.
Sister-in-law, sister-in-law! It's me!
Aigoo, seriously.
What is this embarrassment, after coming for a round of golf?
Because of that vulgar and impudent thing who doesn't know embarrassment...
That vulgar and impudent thing seems to be me.
Sister-in-law, am I right?
I will talk to you later.
Sit down. Let's talk, Sister-in-law.
Please-
Can you not call me Sister-in-law?
I call my sister-in-law Dong-seo. Do I call you North-South then? (Dong-seo can also be East-west)
Why am I your sister-in-law?
Is your name in my family (Seung Jin) registry?
It's just a piece of paper.
Just because there isn't a paper, is there anyone that doesn't know that I am Cha Joon Pyo's wife?
Stop dreaming. Nobody in Seung Jin thinks of you as family.
You, really! Hey! Why do I have to stop dreaming?
My husband is still alive, and my son Cha Do Hyun
- is the only successor of Seung Jin. Why would I?
- Talk with me after you let this go.
- Let go.
- Talk after I let go? You rude wretch!
Do you want to be embarrassed by me! How dare you?
Vice President Cha Do Hyun
Do you like the office?
You came, President?
What is this? You are already creating distance between us after calling war?
What do you mean, a declaration of war?
Stop acting all innocent.
The battle between the successors of Seung Jin Group started.
People who are watching us from outside are very interested.
Aren't you overdoing it, when we just do entertainment management business?
Let's go easy. Easy, okay?
It's been 500 years since the King was chosen through descent, but that was the Joseon dynasty.
I haven't even properly introduced myself to the Board.
Why are you already talking about a bloodbath?
I'll see you at the board meeting later.
That day, I saw you leave the club.
You transformed into a completely different person.
Oh, that day?
My friends who studied with me abroad
suddenly contacted me.
You must have partied a lot in America.
Did you do drugs?
What?
Be careful. This is Korea. Many people are watching.
I'm leaving.
What do you mean I'm having a hard time?
Your daughter is very strong.
You don't have to act tough.
Just pick someone decent from the hospital and marry him. Just stay at home after.
But you have to pick one from the doctors, not the patients.
Mom, I have to park now. I'm hanging up.
Daughter, thanks for the present.
It's a little small, but I'll wear it well!
Oh Ri Jin.
Oh Ri Jin
Hello?
Is it Shin Se Gi?
Who are you?
Me? I was a person who was embarrassed by you in Paradise Club.
Where is my jacket?
Where is my jacket right now?!
Jacket? If you can tell me in detail what jacket you are talking about--
-You bastard!
- Don't touch a single thing in my leather jacket that you ran off with,
and just bring it to me as how it is.
If you don't, your woman is going to die in my hands.
- My woman?
- You coward! You're going to pretend not to know anything, huh?
Don't you know the owner of this phone?
Oh Ri Jin from Kanghan Hospital.
Listen carefully.
Bring the jacket to Taesan Textile Distribution Factory by 1 o'clock on the dot.
The woman will die if you don't have the jacket,
and if you are late, then she'll die.
If you report to the police and bring someone with you, she will die.
Hello?
Where are you going?
I'll be right back.
Vice President!
Vice-President, you can't be doing this right now.
The board meeting is starting soon!
I have to find it.
Vice President!
For now, go back to the company.
You have to attend the meeting, no matter what.
I will take care of this after reporting to the police.
Unless I go, a woman's life will be in danger.
It's something that Se Gi did!
Even if you, who doesn't know anything, go, you can't solve this!
It's something that has to do with someone's life. I have to at least go, even with empty hands...
Secretary Ahn, please hit me.
What? What are you talking about?
I have to call out Shin Se Gi.
- Vice President!
- The only person that knows what happened that night and where the jacket is located is him.
The only person who can solve this is Se Gi.
But even if I do that, it isn't guaranteed that he will come out.
He reacts keenly the most when I get angry or hurt.
This is the only way. So hit me.
I can't do that!
It's a command as your superior.
I will endure and take responsibility for everything that will happen after this.
So help me, Secretary Ahn.
Hurry! There isn't enough time!
Okay.
Hit me.
Hit me!
I'm sorry.
It's too light. Hit me harder.
It's not enough.
Hit me harder! Please hit me harder!
Alright.
I got it. Then I'll do it in one shot.
Yes!
Vice President!
Are you okay?
Shin Se Gi?
Geez~ Did you just hit me?
You rude rascal.
Did you just hit me? Huh?
Perry... Park?
That's right. I'm Perry Park.
Look at how he packed this firmly!
You rude rascal!
Call (Deal)!
Good choice.
What did you just say?